Hello everyone and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever, et cetera, et cetera. We got Gibbontake over there.
Hey guys, go to Gibbontake.site to read the Lord of Ghosts comic. It's good and you should
like it and you should read it. Yeah, it's good. It is good. I'm all proud of it.
I am its biggest fan. I am the most known best ghost of the Lord of Ghosts comic. That's
its defining characteristic. We've also got a creator of new video game, Tom.
Yo, go to tomolver.itch.io slash ninja suffering to play ninja suffering.
Indeed. But can someone acquiring all those big juicy boigas really be said to be suffering?
These are the questions of our time. I don't know. You eventually die, so.
I guess that's true. Just like real life. Indeed.
Speaking of dying, Endless Jess, good to see you buddy.
Hey guys, I'm here this week, so that means we get to talk about the Final Fantasy 7.
All right. All right. I'm opening up another tab. I'm going to start up an audiobook or
something. It's it's funny. You guys say that somebody messaged me on Discord yesterday and was
like, you know, I just want to tell you the last like four episodes of PCP have sucked.
I hate to talk about Final Fantasy 7. Funny. I feel the exact same way.
If we can certainly talk about that. I'm bored. I never want to talk about it again.
What do you know? Talk about Ninja Suffering, the better video game.
Sure. Sure. Hey, here's the thing, Tom.
And me and me, Ben Saint, patreon.com slash Ben Saint. I'm the last one.
Okay. Right. Yeah. I won't even like watch videos about it anymore. Like I see
like guys who like normal under normal circumstances. I'd be like, hey, that guy did a review,
but now it's like, no, no more. I'm done. Everyone's talked about it. No, I've talked about it.
No more. No more truly exhausted by the discussion. However, unfortunately for me,
I am in the middle of my own labor by Sisyphean task to articulate my full thoughts. Right.
It is a struggle of the critics. I have been thinking very strongly about undertaking
a similar labor. However, because I have other things on my plate at the moment,
sure. I've put it to the side and also I'm thinking maybe that's better because then
if and when I ever actually do it enough time will have passed that the market will not be
as flooded. Yeah, that's true. That's that would be a good thing. I think people are waiting a
little bit for like, I don't know, whenever like a new video game comes out and I find it interesting
and people talk about it, there at some point there comes a time when the definitive video has
been published by someone like a, I don't know, like a Matthew Matosis review of Dark Souls 2.
That's also my fear is that the longer I wait, the more chance there's going to be for like a
nine hour Matthew Matosis come out and fucking I give up forever.
Matthew Matosis would stoop so low as to play Final Fantasy 7.
I certainly hope not. He's smarter than that. Hey, you know, I did beat the true Super Boss the
other day. And so I finally, I did that thing. It was kind of fun. Kind of fun. Okay. Well,
that's interesting. Right. Well, wait, wait, I've got a breaking breaking news. I have just a piece
of breaking news. We don't have to discuss long, but it's that so right as I was doing the voicemails
before we started this very episode of the PCP, it appears there was a shooting in front of the
apartment building next to my house. I heard a loud rat, tat, tat, tat. And as I do, I'm just like,
Oh, I assume that's just bangs and pops as I hear in my neighborhood. I always think it sounds like
a gunshot, but I never really know. I thought I thought shootings didn't happen anymore. It's
It's only coronavirus news now.
Maybe they shot coronavirus bots.
That's what the news is telling me.
All the things that we thought were problems
are no longer problems.
This is the real problem, guys.
We're serious this time.
This is clearly a case of cabin fever.
They're going haywire.
I have no idea what happened.
I did run over to the building after a while.
There were a bunch of cop cars.
There's like 10 cops, I don't know,
like six, seven cops swirling around.
I have no idea what's going on.
I looked for people who are dead.
I did not see anything.
I didn't see any ambulances or anything.
But that did happen.
And good ol' Sensi.
I love living in the ghetto.
It's great.
That's all.
Okay, well, moving on from video game talk
to real video game talk.
Real video game talk.
Tom, Izumi the burger eater.
I played it a bunch of times,
but sometimes burgers don't appear
and I run out of stamina and that feels unfair.
How does the burger algorithm work?
How do you decide when and where they appear?
That's probably the biggest problem with the game right now
is just that they spawn every five to eight seconds
at a random Y location.
So the platforms and the burgers use two separate,
I guess, equations, but they're like baby equations.
I don't know how to do math.
And they just spawn in different locations.
And so the way the game works right now
is that it's just the same three platforms
over and over again.
Just when they get to the other side of the screen,
they just instantly teleport back to the other side
at a random Y value.
So it kind of gives the illusion that you're moving somewhere,
but you're actually just staying still
and things are scrolling.
So then there's a separate piece of code
that controls the burger spawns.
I was considering for a while to possibly make it more
like Dark Souls and have burgers be something
that you start with three of them
and you can just use them whenever, kind of like S this.
But I wanted to very much have it be a one button game
that you could play on anything.
And I couldn't think of a good way
of integrating something like that
without having to put another button or something.
So I kind of just said, I guess we'll leave the thing as is.
And if anybody like Gib asks me why the burger spawns,
so shit, I'd be like,
well the game's called Ninja's Soffering,
it's all about the inevitability
of like life first purpose proposal.
Yeah, but it's like, I play the game and I'm like,
I hear Jack's blade has like a billion points
and I'm like, okay, let's see if I can get a billion points.
And it just seems like luck.
It seems like luck if you get the right burger spawns.
There is some R and G.
Well, sorry, my high score was like 500, 600.
So I'm feeling pretty good about that.
Is your complaint Gib that the burgers just spawn
in almost impossible to reach spots
or that they simply don't appear at all?
No, not necessarily impossible to reach,
although that sometimes is a problem.
It just sort of feels like I can go for too long
without seeing a burger and like I'm playing perfectly well.
I'm like jumping, not losing that much stamina,
but I just don't get a burger in time before I die.
And I'm like, yeah.
But you said Tom, they appear every what,
five to eight seconds?
Is that still true?
Or is it just like you're getting a lot of eight second ones
and it's just fucking over?
Yeah, maybe, maybe I'm getting a lot of eight seconds.
I think the thing is, from what I understand,
like the reason it feels like it takes so much longer
is that every 100 points, the game speeds up.
So once you get to like five or 600 points,
you're doing way more jumps
because the game's moving faster
in those five to eight seconds.
So the longer you go, the less, the same amount of time,
like physical time is passing,
but you're doing a lot more platforming
because everything's moving at a higher speed.
That makes sense.
Yeah, it's more of the story is get good.
It is like Dark Souls.
No.
No RNG in it.
It's all about your own reaction time.
Like it, it's, there's no like, oh.
Oh, there's some RNG.
Will that guy's weapon clip through the wall
that yours bounces off of
when you're trying to dodge out of a room?
It's up to chance.
You just have to know which enemies have Vorpal weapons,
which is all of them.
Yeah.
You don't ever.
Yeah, I love them.
Remember Vorpal weapons guys?
I do.
Fucking sick.
What did they do?
It's like sometimes you press the S.
They instantly cut off your head if you crit.
They were the best.
Wait, in Dark Souls?
No, Dungeons and Dragons.
Dungeons and Dragons.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Right.
Vorpal weapons are stupid, by the way.
I fucking hate them.
Dungeons and Bunions.
I just started playing D&D again.
Oh, hell yeah.
I got roped into it.
I am a frog.
Dope.
That's it?
Like, like.
Dude, it's sick.
I'm a little dark frog, man.
Dude, frog heck of standing habitant?
Fuck yeah.
Dude, that's what I'm talking about.
He's a brewer.
He was like a folk hero.
He was like a folk hero from his hometown of the pond, right?
Like, it's all about the pond,
but he's like the town hero
because he led a water strike, right?
He led basically a hunger strike, but for water,
he led a hunger strike, a water strike to protest imperialism,
but from the dry folk.
And now he's their fucking champion
of their shitty little pond with like a hundred people in it.
But he's the coolest one of those like
shitty little hundred people.
And now he's finds himself whisked away
to this fucking magic cave that he can't get out of
and it's a struggle because he needs water.
And if he doesn't bathe in water for one hour a day
for six days, he'll die.
So the first game, which is all about like finding a wizard
and being like, how much will can I pay you
to please just make me a tub of water?
Please conjure a tub of water for me so I can live.
And it worked.
Worked like a charm.
If he was stuck in a desert, would he, A,
and he had to acquire water and there wasn't any around,
would he either try to find an enemy
and bleed them and use their blood
or would he try to hurt their feelings
and collect their tears
as that is a superior water source?
Probably blood, but the thing is he can't,
he doesn't, just drinking, it's not enough.
He has to bathe in it.
Okay, so we need to kill a lot of people.
He needs to really get ambitious.
No, he needs to manipulate, like upset a lot of people.
He needs to troll a lot of people, make them cry.
A true Pakistani note.
He's like frog Jesus, basically.
He is a God among frogs.
Someone was asking him about,
tell us about the history of your world
and the DM was like, just improv it.
And I was like, well, everyone knows
that the world started 60 years ago with the great flood
that created the entire pond.
What else was there before the pond?
Doesn't matter, it's not important.
I was thinking today,
I've had sort of weird annoying mind fog.
I was just like pacing around my room just thinking,
but like nothing was, like neurons were like trying to fire,
but there was no, nothing in the chamber.
I was trying to think of world building and characters,
but I was only just thinking of those words.
I wasn't actually doing anything creative.
World building and characters.
I was imagining, like thinking of stock footage
of people writing on laptops
and like people sitting down at desks to write.
And I'm like, that's me right now, but I'm not doing it.
And I don't know what's going wrong with my brain.
I think I might have dementia.
I think I might be going to die soon.
I just wanted to think of something creative.
It was really annoying.
I couldn't think of anything.
You just have to think creatively.
Oh, sorry.
I also experienced constant brain fog.
I have a D&D story to go with Ben's.
Yeah. Oh, fuck.
It's like this one time, a couple of years ago,
I started playing D&D with like a group of people that I know.
Because I had never done it before.
And I was like, this will be cool.
So I meet this D&D group and like only one of them
I actually know and the rest are like her friends.
So we're playing D&D.
It's me and my old secretary, if you remember her.
Oh, of course.
So we were playing D&D and so I was making my guy
and I made a guy called Bartholomundus
who is like a dragonborn monk.
But I, so he's like a lizard man.
And I just played him as Donatello.
And I would do the voice for like the whole session.
And it was awesome because like I would take
completely insane risks
and do the most retarded shit imaginable
that was like bound to get the whole party killed.
And it was like really frustrating everyone.
And like one guy in particular was like really mad.
And he was even more mad because like everything I did,
even though it was like the stupidest possible decision,
I would like roll a 20 every time.
And like it would work out great.
And this guy, he like thought he was like
the king shit of the D&D group.
He was, and he was like, I'm a bard
cause I'm a ladies man.
And I seduce all the women cause I'm a real charming.
And you could tell this man was not a ladies man in real life.
Of course.
He was like the stereotypical D&D player.
Like all the things that could be wrong with a human male.
At once.
But he, for...
Such as being a woman, for instance.
But for the purposes of the game, he wanted to be a bard.
And he was like really like,
he was really like playing it up.
Like he had a voice too.
And he was like in character the whole time.
And he was like trying to like swagger and be confident.
And all right.
So he's the bard.
And he's like trying to seduce all the characters.
Was Donatello doing the rapey stuff?
Alongside that?
No, I wasn't doing rapey stuff.
Donatello was a rapist.
Bartholomundus is not.
That is the one key difference between these two characters.
I see.
Yeah.
He was just like,
he was so like,
this is like I'm gonna be the coolest guy in the D&D party.
But like I became like really popular in this group.
Like by the end of the first night,
everyone loved me because I was fucking funny
and I was doing stupid Donatello shit.
And like all my dumb plans were working out successfully.
And he was over here like trying to be a bard
and seduce people.
And like all of his like cool ideas just didn't matter
compared to my complete retardation.
And he was getting more and more frustrated.
And that's the story.
It just, I ruined his entire D&D experience,
but I had a great experience.
The struggle between like the D&D veteran
who's really interested in like playing their character
seriously and immersing in the lore versus just,
I guess it would be the Chad doesn't give a fuck
about the setting or characters or anything.
Like I would be,
I feel bad except that I don't
cause he was a fucking jerk.
And he was like really smug and elitist about everything.
And I enjoyed ruining his time with my antics.
I understand that.
It's just that I've been that guy too many times
and it feels bad to reflect on how everyone hates you.
Okay, actually it was only one time
when I D&D'd in college.
I know I've talked about this like years ago,
but I made my one campaign and I planned like,
you know as I do,
I planned like every detail of the entire setting
and it was about like two brothers or something,
one of which like was involved
in like a demon summoning plant
or demon summoning fucking ritual or whatever
to like gain power over his brother
who he was like rivals with or whatever.
Like I don't know,
fucking Saban and Edgar from Final Fantasy VI,
but I don't know evil and dark or whatever.
And so I like sprinkled clues throughout,
like, whoa, there's like a corpse of a demon here.
That shouldn't be here.
Like some Dark Souls world building in my head.
And I mean, I don't know,
it went along fine until at the very end I had laid,
ooh, in my master plan,
I had laid all these hints that like,
while of course you could go for the bad ending
and kill the demonic brother,
I in my infinite wisdom as DM had sprinkled
tons of details throughout that he was actually savable.
If only you would try to negotiate with him.
He would renege on his good ways
and you could get the true good ending.
But then my fat friend Mike was just like,
fuck that shit dude.
And he fucking snapped his neck
and the worst part was that I got visibly mad.
And I said, well, you killed the Lord,
you get nothing, you get no rewards,
you leave the castle, you leave the kingdom,
you get nothing for this.
You ruined the good time,
you ruined my master fleet constructed core.
Yeah, that was odd.
Why would you do that, Mike?
This guy was so mad that he couldn't have his little
like alpha male fantasy of like being the Bard character
because I was too busy making the game fun.
And like, he was the only one who was mad.
Like he was just sitting there like stewing over it,
like for like four nights in a row,
he would stew it every time I did anything.
And everyone else was like laughing and having a good time.
And like, it's not like I was being like
deliberately disrespectful to the lore
or the story or the game or whatever.
I was just like, well,
and like, it wasn't even my fault that the character
ended up like a weird Donatello type
because I just, I'm like, okay, I'll make a lizard man
because lizard men are cool.
And this is his name.
And like, as I started playing like,
I just like, it's just my sense of humor
and I was just making people laugh.
And like, it started out,
he was just getting mad at me just for being funny.
And so the more mad at me he got,
the more funny I got.
And so he kind of created his own monster
because the more funny I got, the more powerful I got,
and the more stupid my character became
in response to his visible frustration.
And so he did it to himself.
And eventually it just, I don't know,
I thought it turned out great.
Like I had a great time.
I had a great first D&D experience.
The point of D&D is to have fun at the end of the day.
I made friends who I never spoke to
or cared about seeing again, but friends nonetheless.
Indeed.
Which are the best kind of friends you can have.
So there you go.
The moral of the story, kids is just be cool.
Which you can do by going to teespring.com
slash whatever it is by the just being cool T-shirt.
I rolled my character's name randomly.
And by that I mean, I literally rolled like,
I had a consonant dice and a vowel dice
and I just rolled that shit
and just went with whatever it was.
And the name that it came up with
was Higgs Ozoks.
And I thought that was pretty fucking based.
Higgs Ozoks the Dry.
Who ironically you said is a brewer?
He is a, yes.
And I was gonna have him be a woodcarver
because I sort of wanted him to be frog Jesus.
But I was like, it would be ironic if he's,
if he had, because when you're a folk hero,
you gotta have some like humble profession
that you come from.
And one of the options was brewer.
And I was like, that would be pretty funny
if he was the dry, but he made booze.
Okay.
That's one of the intellectuals in the crowd.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you really think about it,
you might ascertain some significance,
some juxtaposition of concepts there.
But I doubt it.
Have you ever played D&D?
I know Tom has, I think we played together once.
Oh no, we just did more games.
I never did a D&D that had stats.
I did that one campaign with Munchy
and a bunch of other people
that didn't really go very far,
where I was playing,
we were playing in like a Scandinavian like fantasy land.
And I was playing like a crippled boy
who had found like a Boston Dynamics robot.
Like ancient technology, Boston Dynamics.
And he had tried, like his quest was to try
and like save it from like shutting down
because it needed batteries.
And they don't know what the fuck batteries are.
And so he, like he has no legs.
And the Boston Dynamic robot is like his legs.
And that was a pretty cool character.
I really liked that.
But they never really went anywhere.
That we didn't really get to a point
where we were having adventures.
It was just sort of like starting up.
We didn't have stats or anything.
Yeah, the campaigns die in their infancy.
No stats, damn.
What is it without stats?
Nothing.
I mean, like when you and I did another one.
You just jerk each other off.
It was a Homestuck one.
What was that Homestuck one we did called,
or was it Luke?
Oh, Sperb, Sperb.
Sperb, the Homestuck RP.
Have I talked, I'm sure I've talked about that.
Yeah, you talked about it.
That was like no stats.
It was better.
Did a lot of it through texting.
The thing with the DMing,
like you were saying, Nate,
like you had you perfectly crafted a story.
It seems like a fool's errand to try and do that.
Cause basically what you're doing.
See, what I was doing was video game design
when I should have been doing like talking
with friends design.
Like you're writing like a story,
but like you're writing a story like in a public place
and people can just come up to your laptop
and type something in and you have to keep it in.
So you're like, oh God, fine.
Like you're trying to write a novel,
like fucking Game of Thrones man.
Type in his thing and then some jackoff says,
huh, and then they take a shit.
And he's like, that's stupid.
No, that's not correct.
Your character isn't that doing that now.
Yeah.
It was a, you know, I mean, it was my first time DMing.
I way over prepared kind of, and I learned it,
but it also kind of soured me.
And I'm like, well, fuck this shit man.
It seems like so much work.
You need to be a real like lover
of seeing people interact in that sort of setting
to get into DMing.
Being a DM is like, it's like a,
it's your new hobby if you do it.
You can't, you can't just like,
I mean, I guess if you want it,
maybe you could just like show up and just improv it.
Or like, I guess you could buy a pre-prepared campaign,
to the time that wouldn't work out so well.
The pre-prepared campaigns are stupid though.
You gotta, you do have to do a lot of improving,
no matter what.
Even if you're good, and even if you prepare shit,
you do have to be able to like adjust your plans
on the fly.
I think we, like we as the PCP could do
like an improv D&D thing.
Somebody just makes shit up.
Yeah, we were supposed to,
we were supposed to frickin' do it.
We were gonna do that one by Don Jolly, right?
Yeah, we were gonna.
He said that Don Jolly made a game,
and we were gonna, it was like,
it's called the Gorefest, I think.
Gorefest, yeah.
Yeah, we were gonna play it at Radcon,
and we never got around to it.
That's true, that's true.
We could still do it.
We could still do it any time.
We could just do it in a Skype call,
or a Skype call, wall, discord.
Yeah, imagine.
The fuck is a Skype?
I don't know.
Never think about Skype.
Try not to.
I've gotta use Zoom,
that all the kids are talking about these days,
for a Mother's Day.
I think, Mother's Day Zoom call.
The change from Skype to Discord
is the point where reality shifted
into a parallel, worse dimension,
and the point where Discord is now shifting into Zoom
is gonna be an even worse dimension than that.
We have to stop changing these things.
We have to stop bringing new timelines.
We all need to go back to AOL Instant Messenger.
Yes, that was, because that was when
life was last good.
Oh, good new bed, after all.
I don't know, right?
My biggest memories of AOL Instant Messenger
are being a kid with crushes in high school
and middle school, acting on none of them,
and feeling bad a lot about my inability
to talk to women.
I didn't have that in AOL.
I had that in MSN.
Yeah.
Was that one removed?
That was around the same time.
Yeah, similar kind of things.
I had the email address of a girl I liked,
but she wrote it, and I typed it in wrong.
No, I think she wrote it, and I couldn't read
one of the dashes or an underscore,
and I got it wrong.
And so I emailed her, but I didn't realize
that it was the wrong one.
Did you just assume she hated you or something?
Huh?
Did you assume she was just blowing you off and stuff?
I can certainly see that happening.
I can't remember what happened.
It wasn't that big of a deal, but it was just very,
oh no, she doesn't give a shit.
I wish you never noticed.
I wish those things never existed,
and that we lived in the Stone Ages or whatever,
because then I never would have had
those late night, extremely embarrassing
like hours and hours long conversations with girls.
I just wanted to say, I am sexually attracted to you.
Please understand that fact.
Ignore all the stupid shit I'm saying.
That is the point of this conversation.
Instead of, you know, just going on and on
about whatever the fuck happened at school that day.
Oh, it's, I did that.
Truly a waste of time.
I mean, I skipped the small talk
and I made an embarrassing comment
that was too sexually charged,
and I think-
What's wrong with that?
You know what, it's not embarrassing.
It's better to err on the side of that than-
I agree, I agree.
You don't want to err on the side of that.
You waste less time that way for sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I feel like I became not like a big rumor,
but like a little bit like a guy.
He cares about sex.
What a degenerate, no one does that.
My biggest fear was that anyone would find out
that I was sexually attracted to anyone.
That was my nightmare scenario.
No one can, to this day, I don't want anyone to know
that I feel those things.
It would be career ending to say that-
It is, it is, yeah.
That was pretty shitty.
Yeah, indeed.
Good times, good times.
Yeah, pretty good.
No one should have that power over you ever.
That's what it truly means to be a man.
That's true.
That's why Migtau is the greatest man on the planet,
and I aspire to be just like them.
I really was not a fully developed human being
until I went to Japan and became the samurai warrior,
and it felt real good.
Yeah, you became a real man in Japan,
but as soon as you came back,
you reverted- I lost it all, yeah.
You've never been a saint since.
Yeah, that's true, unfortunately.
That's where my heart, what is it, my heart?
What's that fucking line from it in that poem
that the fat kid wrote to the hot girl?
Oh, yeah, mine burns there, too.
My heart burns there, too, or whatever the fuck it is.
Yes, that's me for the land of Nippon,
my Japanese brethren.
You know, me and Michelle have talked about
winding up a trip one of these years,
maybe next year, I don't know, maybe the year afterward,
specifically to go see the Sakura Blooms.
Oh, and Victor was telling us about his trip
and giving us some tips about where to go
for reasonably cheap flights,
and it's not even, I don't know,
if you have $3,000 that you're willing
to invest in that kind of a trip,
which you could save up, not too hard for,
yeah, you could make that shit happen.
It doesn't have to be just a dream, ladies and gentlemen.
One of these days, go see the Sakura Blooms.
I have a dream of walking the earth
and being around no one and disappearing,
and the dream kinda, it's hard to rationalize that
with also having someone who wants to go places with you
because it's like, oh man, someday I'm gonna go over here
and to this country, and I'm gonna go over there
and I'm gonna travel the world and go to all these places,
and then you meet someone and they're like,
oh yeah, we can do all that together,
and it's like, no, you don't understand.
The whole point of me traveling is to have no one
be around me ever again.
Me traveling is not a fun thing to do
with somebody who I love.
It's a break glass in case of emergency.
All the other options have been used up.
It's time for this now.
I getcha, I getcha.
I guess with me, I mean, my real everyday drive,
all I wanna do is play the video games
I wanna play sometimes and work.
These are like my, and I gotta know, exercise sometimes
and eat the food I like.
It's like, yeah, cause like if I have someone
I like hanging out with here,
what the hell's the point of going anywhere else?
Yeah, I mean, I physically feel a desire to travel.
Also, god damn it, I just wish I lived near the ocean,
which I will before too long, I think.
That would make my life just feel better.
You know what, you're right.
I think this might be one of those fake opinions
that I sometimes have about them,
and I realize it was all, it's not even true.
It's a nice idea, just the idea of being like
an explorer, but like, you know, like a rugged,
like I don't give a fuck.
I'm just gonna walk around the world.
I saw a video once of like a guy who took a picture
every day while he was traveling the world
and his beard grew to like two meters long or whatever.
And I was like, that's a cool thing,
but then I realized how annoying it would be
and how expensive and time intensive
and like planning would, you know,
you can't just do that without dying instantly.
There's gotta be cheaper ways.
Like if you're, obviously if you're traveling the world,
I assume you're not, well, I mean,
you're not gonna fucking like, I don't know,
drive through like all of Europe and all of Asia.
No, this particular guy like walked across
like the entire, like from, I don't know, China
to fucking Italy or whatever.
Britain or something?
Yeah, yeah, okay, okay.
I think there's like, I think there's like a clear line
between like couples traveling
and like finding yourself traveling.
Like when it comes to like couples traveling,
I have like, I have like these little dreams,
but they're not like goals.
They're more like images where I see myself like,
hey, it'd be cool to take that special woman
and just be like on the street in Paris,
just like sitting while that Paris music plays
like in that episode of X-Men
where Wolverine finds God and Rogan Gambit are like sitting.
Yeah.
Like I always picture myself as Gambit in that exact scenario
and like, yeah, that'd be fucking cool.
You know, lecturing my woman about atheism, like,
I say it's all random, Cher.
Live hand you a full house or a busted flush.
That'd be fucking cool.
But then when I picture like solo traveling,
I picture like, like everyone thinking,
like faking my death and living in a temple
and like fucking Thailand or something for a year,
like up in the mountains.
Like doing chores, like carrying like the stick
with the two buckets of water on it, up the steps,
you know, learning to like find some kind of spiritual remedy
for this affliction that tears us all apart daily
in this cruel world that we live in, this cruel society.
You know, I had a buddy, I had a buddy in,
I don't know, high school growing up
who went after I left high school and stuff
and joined a monk, I don't know, what do you call it?
Like he gave us all his possessions
and did that shit.
Buddhist monk thing?
No, it was like a Jesuit monk, like that kind of thing.
It was like Christian oriented, I think.
He just did that for a while.
And the funny thing was, like afterward,
you know, I can't speak to what's going on in the guy's head.
I don't really know him particularly well,
but afterward, after like years of doing that,
he just kind of seemed like the same guy.
I was just kind of like, what was gained?
What was gained by all that?
Maybe he just enjoyed it.
It was enlightening in some way.
I'm not privy to.
Frankly, we've never really talked about it that much.
Well, that's the cruel irony about personal growth.
It's not like on TV where the character arc happens
and everyone can see it and appreciate it.
You know, in real life, you learn and you grow as a person,
but like it's still like in your head
and everyone still treats you like the same old asshole.
If he hasn't changed his hairstyle visibly,
it doesn't count as character development.
Like in time-skaps and anime.
If you don't make a fucking YouTube vlog series
that people can watch as a TV show, then you haven't changed.
If you're not constantly narcissistically talking
about yourself in public for all to see and comment on,
then nothing you do counts and no change has actually occurred.
What you can actually do is like take your life experience,
put it into a character and write a story
and then people like the character and then they like you.
Yeah, then you go surprise motherfuckers.
It was me that you liked all along.
Did you guys ever read Siddhartha by Herman Hess?
I think I read that.
I don't know what a book is.
Our dad told me that that book was about Buddha.
It's not.
It's not literally Buddha, no.
But he doesn't mean Buddha in there.
So Buddha is a character briefly, I think,
if I remember correctly.
He's mentioned, I guess so.
Maybe I should get in the back of the doubt.
It's just about a guy finding enlightenment basically,
which ultimately ends with him like he's just like a man
who like works a river crossing,
but he goes through like all this, I don't know,
like he follows a path of spiritual enlightenment
much like the Buddha did.
He goes gay.
That's how he finds enlightenment.
He gets his river crossing boyfriend.
No, Ben, no, that's not the canon.
That's your fanfic, Ben.
They're just best buddies.
They're definitely gay.
Okay, they may be gay,
but the thing they're gayest for
is crossing that fucking river and they love that shit.
Sure.
They do that shit over on the same page there.
And I don't know, that book was pretty cool.
I think that was one of the books famously I did
before growing a brain,
but even then I think I still got the gist.
There's probably a lot of like fucking farmers out there
who just like are, I think enlightenment just means-
Who also just whisper ohm into their gay lover's ear.
Right, right.
And fucking giggle about him.
As they peg him from behind.
God.
It makes me wonder, the way that like he ends up
after reading that book, it made me feel like,
are there just like people out there
who just don't spend every waking moment
like concerned with like their destiny and like the future
and are just like enjoying being alive
that like technically count as enlightened.
I think, cause that's kind of what it is, right?
That's what that's what Buddha's about.
It depends on your perspective on what enlightened is,
I suppose, I think for a lot of people
that would be like enlightenment,
understanding that the impermanence of life
and how all you're striving for
doesn't really matter at the end of the day.
I finally beat my high score in Ninja Suffering.
Holy fuck.
Congratulations, Tom.
Well, that's what you're high score.
Wait, wait, wait, go back, go back to the thing
about how everything's meaningless work.
That's what I wanna talk about.
It's like, hey guys, when we die, we'll forget everything.
Well, that's kind of a hideously depressing irony
where like the person actively seeking enlightenment
by seeking it is less enlightened
than the stupid dumb shit who just doesn't care
and is fucking sitting around all happy and shit
like a fucking bastard.
As the timeless phrase goes, ignorance is bliss.
Okay, but surely like, I mean, in Siddhartha,
the guy like goes on a quest and then he like,
you couldn't call that guy ignorant or whatever
because he's seen it all.
But maybe it's fair to say that like,
because he's like deactivated the nodes of his brain,
that's like, well, what was the point of worrying
about all that?
I will just help people cross this river
and that'll be my life
and I'll enjoy the simple pleasures inherent in it.
Is that like, you know, willful ignorance perhaps?
Or is that just a realization that through all my struggles
of trying to understand what's going on in the world,
I find that like the answers were all, you know,
just to be present and enjoy life
and there is no greater truth I could discover,
I don't know, like that I have the tools to find.
We don't have Star Trek tri-quarters,
so I can't figure out more than, I don't know,
even that, that's all like physical stuff.
I mean, tri-quarters?
That's what they call their little scan things.
They used to deduce everything in Star Trek.
I don't know what it means.
It means something, but I don't fucking know.
Gabe, what were you saying something?
Well, I was saying like personally,
the idea of there being like a, you know,
an enlightened state where you understand the universe.
Like I hear about these things,
people talking, waxing philosophical
about having, you know, understood things finally.
And I'm like sitting here and I'm like,
you know, I don't know whether I have or haven't.
I don't think I'll ever understand the moment,
when or whether or if I ever like understand anything.
Like how best to enjoy life,
whether I'm wasting my time,
not striving for something where I could be,
or whether it's not like important to do that.
A lot of the time I just think,
oh, if I don't fucking care, I'll just jack off
and it'll be fine.
We all agree that like, okay,
we don't know about any afterlife or any of that bullshit.
Maybe it exists, I don't know, probably not.
No reason to think so.
So like all we've got is like the time that we're here alive
and like what quantifies as a good usage of that time?
Is it like-
Jacking off.
I don't know.
You're right.
It's the only thing that qualifies.
I'm curious, what's more enlightened theoretically
about like being a river crossing guy
who helps people cross versus like literally
just the extreme example of being hooked up matrix style
to like a pleasure machine and just, you know,
getting that fed to your brain at all times
to keep you like perfectly satisfied.
What is more enlightened about that
rather than just recognizing, you know?
I've thought about this because there was, you know,
it's a common like idea.
I've seen it before.
The idea of a machine that just gives you pleasure
is disgusting to me as a person who knows
that I'm not currently in one and I could go into one.
If I was born in that and I had no other knowledge,
then obviously I'd enjoy it.
Because there's like a very, like there's a fakeness to it
that I can perceive as a person
who is not currently hooked up to a machine,
although I might be, you know, in some like real matrix,
like, oh, there's a fucking another level to it.
But like, if there was a choice, you know,
do you want to get hooked up to a pleasure machine
or do you want to suffer in the life
that you currently live in and sometimes feel good?
I'll be like, nah, I'm good.
I'll just, you know, poke at rocks on the ground.
I mean, that's pretty fun.
I don't need pleasure all the time.
I would just leave me alone.
I mean, okay.
I mean, I don't know, like, is it all just hedonism?
Like, because we know that like a perfect pleasure machine
certainly isn't a realistic thing.
It's like, oh, don't be tempted by, you know,
like drugs or stuff like that
because it probably won't work out very well.
Like, what's the metric?
Is it specifically like happiness in life?
Is it?
There is no metric.
I mean, it depends on the individual.
Oh, this fucking sucks.
This is a stupid question.
If there's a hypothetical, like, it's just good
and there's no bad quote, this just is pleasurable.
I would still be a bit like iffy
because I know that it's a machine
and I feel like real things are real.
Even if once I'm hooked up, I would be perfectly happy
hypothetically, then I just still would be like,
nah, nah, you have fun, kids.
I'm just gonna die.
I'd rather die.
I've been living my whole life with the idea
that eventually I'm gonna pass away
and that this is what life is.
I don't wanna fucking, I just don't wanna think about it.
Just leave me alone.
I hope I don't die.
But that's what the machine is for.
The machine will make you not think about it.
Nah, nah, these people come into me with clipboards
and goggles and they say,
wait, this is the new fucking science thing.
And I'm like, shut up, I'm jacking off here.
I mean, I think the mechanism, fair.
I feel the mechanism we have in our brain
that makes us feel like, oh, that's like fake and gross
is a thing that's been built into us
that's like a human skepticism of things
that are too good to be true, must be,
and truly it'll actually be bad for me in the long run.
But I mean, what if they work out the bugs?
I like being a stupid monkey,
scrabbling around on the ground with rocks
and not knowing how to do things.
It's funny, it's just funny.
I like being that.
It's funny.
I kinda feel the opposite.
I'm always hoping to find that new plateau of wisdom
and like better myself as a person.
Nate, I think you agree with that.
The rest of you too,
I don't know why I singled out Nate.
Only Nate, only Nate.
You know, and I feel like, yes, every year,
I do feel like infinitely smarter and wiser
and like I've grown as a person
and I'm better than I was in the previous year.
But I have yet to cross the threshold
where all of that increased exponential wisdom
yields happiness or any kind of contentment or...
I'm concerned.
It seems to just make me more miserable every year.
The more better a person I feel.
I'm concerned that now,
now that I'm deeply depressed all the time,
I have crossed that threshold
and now I do have the clearest idea that I've ever had
and it's just that the truth is bad.
Oh God, listen, I would have been better off not knowing.
Oh, don't talk about how the truth is bad.
I don't wanna think about it.
My perspective is that pleasure is bullshit and wrong
and it should be a spice in life and not your end goal.
People should be searching for purpose, not pleasure.
Those are different things.
Purpose is doing something that is long-term,
continues to be something that you build towards
and you understand that purpose means
you are going to have bad times.
Things are going to be hard and it's going to suck.
I think I did hear once from somewhere,
I read it somewhere, somehow it got in my brain
that the idea of happiness as a state of being
as opposed to just a fleeting emotion
is a relatively new concept in human history
that was invented in the last 100 years or so
and that invention of this idea of just being happy
has irreparably destroyed humanity.
Yeah, I don't think it's good.
I think it's damaging.
It's like a state that cannot naturally be achieved.
It's only been in the last 100 years
that that was even something that could be conceptualized.
Back in the day, you were a surf, work in the fields
and it's just like, what do you mean happy all the time?
I'm happy when I don't have the plague.
Right, it's like life was kind of like miserable.
Happiness is just the absence of all the bad things
you're usually thinking about
for like five fucking minutes or something.
Yeah, definitely true for me.
I don't even live in the present.
I'm mostly like 90% of my time,
I'm either like dwelling on horrible things
that have happened in the past or things I regret or rue
or I'm imagining a wonderful future
where I've achieved enough or accomplished enough
that I feel good enough to no longer
have to constantly dwell on the horrible past
and I'm always kind of like back and forth between those two
and like the only time I'm ever in the present
is when I'm jacked off.
That's the only time I wanna be in the present.
I don't know, I think it's a fairly agreed upon fact
that I seem like a fairly upbeat person overall,
perhaps of the more upbeat among this group
and it makes me think that like I think the reason for that
and maybe it's literally that I'm,
I guess the uncharitable it would be stupid
that I just don't spend a lot of time
concerned about the bad things
and I'm just focused on the stuff I'm trying to do to,
like right now my focus in life in general
is to make enough money so I'm not losing money every month
and we'll be able to grow and then buy the things I want
which I know are like the things
that lead generally to happiness.
I don't know, owning a house would be nice.
Like having enough money to have property,
having money, you know.
I definitely feel infinitely better in general
when I am engaging with a plan of action
or actively doing something or working
or accomplishing something,
which is why I was really happy
for a few brief months there
when I started going to the gym
before the US government decided
that I should be fat again
and close down all the gyms everywhere forever.
For a year.
And I'll have an excuse
because my gym is in my basement.
I could be working out this whole time, but I'm not.
Oh boy.
Jesse, it could be worse.
You could have a spine injury
that prevents you from doing any exercise whatsoever anymore.
They're still on about that, Tom.
Let's get over it.
Oh, listen to this, we've heard about that.
I'll get over it, pussy, wonk it off.
I wish, man, I tried using the Bowflex
in the house yesterday and it fucked me up pretty bad
and I was like, well, I guess I'm not doing that
at any time soon.
I cannot exercise outside of a gym.
My brain cannot do it.
It's exponentially worse not exercising at a gym.
Plus I hate body weight exercises.
They're fucking pussy shit.
I want to do fucking bench.
I don't like going to the gym.
I like my basement.
But that's the whole point.
The other thing is-
I don't like going to the gym
so I want to get in and get out as quickly as possible.
That's not about motivation.
When I'm at my house, I still don't like working out
but my computer's right there.
Well, the main thing is I've never been able
to really live alone for any extended period of time.
I'm always have other people in the house with me.
Like I'm quarantined with other people in the house.
I don't want people in the house hearing me
or seeing me work out.
It's fucking embarrassing.
It's not embarrassing at the gym
because everyone's doing it.
But the idea that someone else around me
knows that I am actively concerned about my health
fills me with humiliation and rage.
Are you simping for your own body?
That's fucking gross, dude.
What is this shit?
It's imagined up.
It's almost like a tesset admission that I'm fat.
Yeah.
Like, no, I'm not.
I just wanna be a little bit healthy.
I will not admit to being fat outside the gym.
Even worse, it's that you care that you're fat.
Just being fat can be cool.
But if you care, ooh, cringe, big cringe.
Since the gym closed, I have become a fucking planet.
I am so grotesque.
I look at myself and I feel like I lay in bed
and I sit in a chair and I feel my fucking fat folds
flopping over the edges of it.
And I'm just filled with so much hate for all things.
Hate for the government who created this conspiracy.
You know, everyone has their own ideas
and conspiracy theories about the coronavirus.
You know, there's no truth anymore.
No one really knows what's going on.
My chosen personal conspiracy theory
is that this whole thing was manufactured
to get me fat again because they knew that me being
in shape and me being happy with myself
would be too powerful and I'd overthrow
this whole stinking corrupt system.
So they had to do something to close down the gym
and keep me from it and this is what they thought of.
This is their excuse and it's working so far
and I just, I'm so sad.
I'm so angry, I was so committed.
Like when I finally started doing it, you know,
it took me, it took me my whole life.
When I finally started doing it, I'm like, oh my God,
Islam is the way in the light.
I finally see, I am enlightened.
I will never stop coming here.
I will come here every single day
and fucking clang and bang and kick ass and I did.
And I did great and I lost like 30 pounds or something.
Like I was 240 when I started.
And by the end of it, I was 210 in a span of like,
I think three or four months and I'm like, oh my God,
I look great, I feel great.
This is so cool, I'll never stop doing this ever.
And then like 2020 started and for the first few months
of 2020, I was staying with family like in another state
and I couldn't get into planet fitness
because they're like, oh, you need your driver's license
to get in here and I'm like, I don't have it.
I took a train here so I couldn't get in the gym there.
And so then after that, I went to Virginia with you guys
and then we fucking binge ate and fucking drank
and that was even worse.
And so then as soon as I got back from that,
it was like, oh, now everyone's quarantined.
You can't even go outside.
You're not even allowed to move.
You're legally required to stay in bed
and be a sack of shit.
And so I'm already like, I went from 240 to 210
and now I'm back at 233.
And like, even though I'm not as fat as when I started,
like it feels more fat because I now have been
to the mountain top and now to even be back down here,
feels even more grotesque than it used to.
And I'm going fucking stir crazy with it.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna snap people.
The worst thing about the quarantine,
just for me personally, how my life has been affected
is that I can, that's like the main way
that my actual day-to-day life has been affected
that I cannot go to the gym when I want to,
which, I mean, yeah, I've got my fucking pull-up bar.
I'll do push-ups.
I fucking hate it.
Pull-ups, I guess, are okay.
But I fucking hate all this body weight exercise is stupid.
I don't even believe in that body weight.
I think they literally are fake.
It's just, yeah.
Just like, like standing on a treadmill
and being able to like run in place
or like walk up an incline in place
and like listen to music while you're doing it
or just like finding like sitting at the weight machines
and doing the, you know, the rote activities
that are like, you know, that are illustrated on the side
that you can't possibly mess up.
You know, just like turning your brain off
and doing those things.
That is the only correct way to work out.
Any of these fucking like,
any of these like workout without weight machines,
fucking shit that people did in the caveman days,
it's fucking barbaric and I refuse to do it.
Oh, oh, do burpees.
I don't want to do a burpee.
No, I don't ever want to fucking touch it.
I don't, a burpee is like what you do to a fucking baby.
It doesn't sound like something that a grown man,
a civilized person would ever do
and I refuse to take part in it.
I hate the word burpee.
I just find it very, I mean, I don't want to do it.
It is when you do like a squat jumping jack thing.
It's like you, it's like you late, you get in a pushup
and then you stand up and then you jump
and then you get back in the pushup.
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
It's dishonorable and it's shameful.
You'll never catch me doing one.
Why on earth is it called a burpee?
I thought it was like a baby thing.
I don't know.
I don't know where it came from.
Everything that's been named in the last 10 years
has been terrible.
For some reason we lost the ability
to name things in a cool way.
The name is the barrier for entry.
I can't do anything called a burpee.
I won't, ever.
And you know, on the other point.
What about a slurpee?
A slurpee I will do.
I prefer a slurpee.
And that's part of the problem.
I'd fucking, I like going to the gym
because I like just having the ambiance.
Nobody ever, I've never made contact
with a single fucking person in the gym ever
under any circumstances, no matter what basically.
But I like having them there
for the tacit, ominous feeling of oppression
that if I do something embarrassing,
if I even just sit there and don't do anything there,
if from the side of their eye,
from the corner of their perception,
it will be noticed that I'm being that guy at the gym.
And that little bit of motivation.
Not to mention just the fact that I have to get my gear
and go to the gym.
It commits you to getting a workout done and getting done.
Whereas I spent two hours working the other day
because I was just watching some fucking
Star Trek Voyager while I was exercising.
Don't do, because it's in my fucking work room.
It's in my room with my computer.
What am I gonna not watch TV while I exercise?
Well, that would be retarded.
Of course I'm going to.
And the workout took twice as long
and I wasted tons of fucking time.
It's a nightmare.
It's horrible.
I don't like it.
Gyms are bad.
I'm happy to pay money.
I want the financial burden on my back
forcing me to go workout more.
And you're right about that.
The constant looming threat of doing something wrong
at the gym is what gets your ass and gear the most.
Absolutely.
I have the fucking, okay.
I don't know if I've told this story before.
This was like the dumbest thing that I ever did at the gym.
And it's still, I still think about it.
And I feel horrified at the thing that I did.
I was like, so I was at the gym
and I was on like one of the machines
just like lifting the weights and fucking doing the thing.
And you know, when you're done with it,
you get up and you go and you get your little paper towel
and you get your little spray
and you just come back and spray it down.
So I finish and I get up
and I go to get the paper towel and the spray
and I come back to wipe down my seat
and there's this like guy standing there by the machine.
And he's like a disability, like deformed guy,
maybe like retarded or something, you know?
He's he had, you know, yeah, retarded people with this.
You can go to the gym, you can workout too.
That's not, I'm not judging you, man.
Even though you're creepy, even though you're shaped wrong
and a person should not look like you.
God did not grant you his favor, but that's all right.
Yeah, and he's like this weird like,
like he's like five foot tall
and he's got like this huge, like misshapen,
like bulbous head and like a sloped forehead
and like this weird dummy look.
And he's just oddly shaped in every way.
And he's just kind of staring blankly,
like in the way that a bad person does.
Okay, yeah, right.
So like I come back with my spray
and my paper towel to wipe down my seat
and he's just standing by the machine, staring at me,
like staring into my soul, like right into my eyes
and not saying anything.
And I'm just like trying to ignore it.
And I'm like awkwardly like just like silently like
patting down my seat.
Let's get this over with so I can get away from this guy.
And he, and he's just standing there.
And he's like really close to me now.
And he's like looking right in my eyes and I'm like, hi.
Like I just said like hi to like,
to give him, to satisfy him somehow,
give him the human acknowledgement
that he clearly craved.
And I'm like, hello.
And he's like, hello, hello.
And I'm like, oh my God, what does he want?
What does he want?
And I walk away and so I'm like, I'm walking.
I'm like, oh my God, I can't believe that.
What a weird guy.
What a fucking, and I'm like,
I thought for about like five to 10 minutes
I was thinking that's stupid son of a bitch.
That's fucking retard.
Fucking standing there staring at me.
Piece of shit.
What an asshole, fucking cocksucking bastard, motherfucker.
I hope he fucking dies.
And I'm like, I'm thinking like that
for like a good solid five to 10 minutes.
And after a while, all at once it hits me, wait.
I went and got the paper towel in the water
and I went to a different wait machine.
Oh!
And I was wiping down his seat.
That's why he was staring at me.
I was the retard in the story.
Wow.
And I still think about that late at night
when I can't sleep and I will for the rest of my life.
Like in that guy's world, he has a story about a retard
he met in the gym who just came up
and wiped his seat for no reason.
And the retard was me.
And he'll be telling that story
to all of his retard friends for the rest of time.
He's like that guy from Midsommar,
like the inbred guy who actually has the true wisdom
who can like touch God and convey God's message.
In this case, it's that,
bro, you're on my fucking machine, bro.
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
I'm just thinking like how I would react,
like how furious I would be
if a stranger came up to my seat
and started wiping it, you know?
I mean, it would be a nightmare.
But that reminds me of the no man's land,
the nightmare scenario of there's two things.
One, where you like step away from your fucking machine
to go get a drink of water.
But the worst one of all is when you're mid-set
and you realize you have to poop.
And you're like, oh God,
this means I'm gonna be away from a machine
for like five to 10 minutes.
So you arrange like a full like barrier
of like your water bottle, your backpack.
I don't know, your fucking, your wrist wraps,
your weight belt, if you got it,
in like a semicircle around.
So everyone knows this is your machine.
And when you still walk, and still, despite that fact,
there's a percentage of the time when you'll come back
and there will be a guy who's like kicked it all aside
and is on the machine
and is now currently doing the exercise
and you have to have the talk.
Bunch of savages.
Bro, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, I was away.
You're the one apologizing,
even though clearly he is in the wrong.
There's a conflict of morals here.
Yes, it is wrong to occupy a machine for too long,
but what's a man to do when you realize,
you can't work out when you have to poop or even pee.
It can't be done.
You have to step away.
It's one of the nightmares of the gym.
And then you have to have contact
with another person at the gym,
which is the ultimate worst situation possible.
The ultimate sin.
It can never be allowed.
And it's a nightmare, it's a nightmare.
I mean, when I was going to the gym,
I would go and look up the Planet Fitness
on the Google app and see the times it was least busy
and try and make sure I could fit that time into my schedule,
just optimize not having to see anybody.
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
Just didn't want to interact with people.
That's very wise.
Is Planet Fitness a 24 hour?
Yes.
Yeah.
Because I usually go like two in the morning.
Dude, my gym has 24 hour posts on it.
Do you know what that means?
Do you know what they mean by 24 hour?
They meant, in real fine print,
on weekdays, starting at 5 a.m. on Monday.
There have been, I think more times than not,
I have gone to the gym and it has been like Sunday night
at like 6 p.m. and the doors are fucking shuttered.
Cause oh, it's only 24 hours on the weekdays,
on Saturday and Sunday nights, we close early.
And I think Friday too.
These people, I'm gonna burn it down.
Next time this motherfucker happens,
I'm going to pour the bacon grease
from the Arby's next door all along the lines
and burn this motherfucker down,
create an explosion with all the fucking,
what is that stuff, the chalk,
the weight chalk for the barbells or whatever,
which obviously they don't have
cause it's a pussy gym, but whatever.
Fuck them, it's horrible.
You know, all this talk about Planet Fitness,
I'm realizing that I haven't been to the gym
in like almost like a year and a half.
My membership is still active
and I bet that even though they're all closed,
they're probably still charging me monthly,
even though none of them are open right now.
I got an email from Planet Fitness saying,
don't worry, we're not charging your cards during this time.
Okay, that's good.
I should check if mine is doing the same.
Thank God for that.
You better go to the gym soon Tom,
cause I've been waiting for the next Q and A.
I know dude, it's a nightmare, it's a nightmare,
but there's extraneous circumstances now.
Cause there's a gym that's actually right near me
because I used to live here years ago
and then I left and then I moved back.
But the gym right down the street is called Workout World
and back in the day, I had it like a subscription
or whatever, I was a member at Workout World
and then I moved away and I couldn't cancel my subscription
but I was like, hmm, I know
and I canceled my debit card
and I got a new one, so they stopped charging me.
So like four years ago, I owe like a hundred dollars
to Workout World and I never paid it back
and like it's still there on my credit report
but it did like nothing.
So I just, I got away with it.
I fucking got away with it, boy.
Well, you know, it's just that those practices,
okay, they've got their rules or whatever.
The fucking gym rules about like when you are
and are not allowed to cancel are so fucking draconian.
You have to like pay for like an extra month
before they'll let you leave or some shit.
Why can it not just be?
Hey, I'd like to cancel.
At the end of this month, please take me off.
Like every fucking time they make you pay
for at least one extra month.
Well, okay.
And there's a cancellation fee sometimes.
They locked me into a year contract.
Like they wouldn't let me sign, I don't know.
I guess I did sign up for a year contract
but like whatever, I used every tool at my disposal.
A gym's entire business model is subsidized
by fat people who sign up in January
and then never go again.
Yeah, I mean, you're right.
But they're not willing to cancel the subscription
because that's giving up.
That would feel bad.
Yeah, right, right.
No, it's true, it's true.
I don't blame the gyms.
That's a real thing.
That's a...
Sure.
It's happening.
But yeah, no, I don't want to be one of those guys.
Of course not.
So I won't work out.
I'll just cancel my subscription.
Just cancel my fucking debit card.
Better money, better idea.
Man, no, I keep thinking, I keep thinking
I should probably start lifting again.
It'll be depressing because I'll have to do it by myself.
But I'll probably feel better.
You will 100% feel better.
Everyone always feels better after the exercise.
It's true.
Yeah, yeah.
I gotta get the demons out somehow.
Exactly right.
I guess so.
I'm gonna do it, ladies and gentlemen.
Yeah, I'm gonna work out today.
I'm gonna get that.
It's gonna happen.
You're welcome.
Feel free to hold me to it.
You gotta call our mom today.
Oh, true.
But I've got, when was that, six we said?
Okay, I've made about six, yeah.
I think I'll have time beforehand.
An hour and 44 minutes from right now.
Tick, tick, tick.
In case you're wondering.
The doomsday clock marches ever onward.
Has anyone used Zoom?
Do I need to be scared or intimidated about setting up Zoom?
I don't think so.
I've never used it.
I haven't used it.
Both my parents are, and they're idiots.
I'm at the age now.
I'm not learning any new apps or social media things.
I don't care.
Discord would do this job.
I wish they just had Discord, but I don't know.
Whatever comes out past this point, I'm not interested.
I'm not gonna be a part of it.
This is what it means to truly become an adult,
to give up on trying to follow trends.
Say, this is it, I'm planting my flag, not moving.
There's like two levels of getting old.
There's one where you hear about the new thing
and you reject it.
And then it's when you get to a point where you're so old
that you don't even know anything.
And you say, yeah, sure, why not?
And that's why all the really old,
my parents are on Zoom doing talks with their friends.
You know, up to the point.
I've resented, yeah.
What am I supposed to be excited about with Zoom?
Like, we already got nothing.
You can do video conferencing in Discord.
You can do it through Google Hangouts.
There's already things that do the same thing.
I think it has some new features of,
you can have tons of screens on screen at once
or something that's different.
Zoom didn't require login at the beginning.
So if you didn't have an account,
you can just still use it.
You can still go join other sessions and stuff.
So that's why it kind of rose above.
But this is just lower barrier of entry.
Yeah, that's nice.
It's free.
You don't have to sign up.
Well, low barrier, you know what?
I guess low barrier of entry really is a feature.
It is.
Like, I guess that's why.
It's arguably the most important one for mass appeal.
Yep, yep.
Hey, on the getting old thing,
up to this, I'll plant my flag.
Up to this point, I have famously resisted the idea
of a Gurren login sequel.
But now, I suddenly realized that Gurren login
only covered two of the important stages
of development of a man.
One is when you go from childhood to adulthood
and you improve yourself and learn how you can affect
the world and make positive change.
Part two is when you, as an adult,
have to recognize that the world is an imperfect place
that your power will not be enough
to just change the entire world all the time.
You have to play within the system to a degree.
But I need a sequel.
Mate, that sounds like the worst fucking sequel
to Gurren login.
That's not the exact opposite of what it should be.
Well, first of all, that's already the show bed.
That's already the show.
Yeah, that's part two.
Yeah, like, Spiral Power itself is not enough.
It would destroy the world.
It would destroy the universe.
But we need a true sequel.
When is, in fact, when Cevote is an old man
and you begin to resent those
who are now trying to change the world
and you hate that they're exerting any influence
and it makes you mad.
And does he become, what's his name?
What's the fucking old guy's name?
Sigmund Freud, a grandpa from the Simpsons.
The guy who ends up as a head in a jar.
Oh, Lord Genome, Lord Genome.
Does he become the new Lord Genome?
Well-bent, famously, I busted this wide open
that really Lord Genome is just like Rossiu,
that he's not like anti-change.
He's just protectionist and he views his rigid control
of the world simply as a means of protection.
But now it's not about protection.
It's about hating people who are just making things new
and complicated and that makes you mad.
And that's what I want.
I can't wait for Nate to last Jedi Gurren Lagan
and take a beloved protagonist
and turn his ideals on its head.
That's again, that's what I want.
On her agenda, sounds great.
That's great, that's called maturity.
Look it up sometime.
UrbanDictionary.com defines maturity
as whatever Nate just said and it feels good.
Okay, sick.
Actually, I'm curious.
Maturity is defined as what Urban Dictionary doesn't have.
It's nice, cool.
That's a great, that's really funny Urban Dictionary.
That's a real dad joke in our show.
Hey, you know what I did today?
What's that?
I bought 500,000 bells worth of turnips.
Okay.
My entire attic is filled with turnips.
And God, please don't make me lose my investment.
Somebody last week commented,
Animal Crossing is the new politics of this show.
Hey, that's an improvement.
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with that.
Market spike.
I have yet to purchase my first turnip,
but this Sunday, I'm gonna keep my eyes peeled.
I've got like 200K in the bank.
I'm a risk at all.
Today is, Nate, today is Sunday.
Oh my God.
Oh, she's already gone, isn't she?
She already left, God damn it.
You fucking idiot.
Shit.
She left at noon.
Next Sunday then.
Hey, speaking of it being Sunday
and having something in the bank,
guess what tonight is?
It's money in the bank.
It's a wrestling topic.
Oh yeah.
Is this the one with the suitcase talking about?
It's the annual WWE Money in the Bank pay-per-view.
And it's cool.
I love wrestling and fucking wrestling
because of the coronavirus and the quarantine
is going insane, like all of it, everywhere.
Yeah, it's just empty rooms, right?
Yeah, it's mostly empty arenas.
The other day, they did like a,
Matt Hardy made his debut for AEW
and he ended up running over Sammy Guevara in a golf cart.
Look at this fucking sick picture I'm uploading here
in a minute.
Yeah, right.
And you fucking suck it now.
Come on, piece of shit.
First of all, I've gotta react to this.
Sephiroth, Happy Mother's Day.
Out of my way, I'm gonna post that to my mom
and hope she gets it.
I see this image still loading.
What a piece of shit.
It doesn't sound like, I can't see the large image,
but I see a boy as a young lad
being running away from crazy Matt Hardy
in a golf cart.
Yes, that's what I'm trying to post.
Who else is there in the cart?
Okay, so that's Kenny Omega riding shotgun,
hanging out the cart, saying to Sammy Guevara
who's running away in a straight line
like in that movie that everyone hates, Prometheus.
Prometheus, whatever, yeah.
He could just run to the left or the right
to get away from the golf cart.
Kenny is hanging out shotgun, pointing at him,
saying, we're gonna fucking kill you.
Matt Hardy, of course, is laughing like a maniac as he does.
Like, right before he did it,
Matt Hardy got in the golf cart
and he looked to the cameras
because this was all happening live.
It wasn't like a pre-taped thing, like usual.
So there was no way to fake this.
Like, he really got hit with this golf cart
and it looked fucking brutal.
Yeah, that's a serious blow.
So when Matt Hardy was getting in the golf cart,
he looked at the camera and he said,
I need you to document these events.
And the commentators were like,
we are Matt, it's on TV, this is live TV.
We are documenting it.
So that's fucking great.
You've got people on that show
running each other over with golf carts
and the money in the bank pay-per-view, that's tonight.
So normally what the money in the bank pay-per-view is,
is that there's, it's a ladder match
with like six to eight guys, you know,
however many they can cram in there.
And they're all scrambling to get up the ladder
and grab the briefcase,
because the briefcase has a contract for a title match.
So that's what they do every year at around this time.
But this year, because everyone is losing
their fucking minds with cabin fever
and we have to keep coming up with waste to entertain ourselves
or else we'll all commit fucking suicide.
Instead of doing just a ladder match for an empty arena,
which would be like totally pointless and stupid,
they're doing the money in the bank entire pay-per-view
from the WWE corporate offices in Stamford, Connecticut,
which is just like a big corporate office building.
And they're starting at the first floor of the building
and they're gonna fight their way to the roof.
And I guess the briefcase will be on the roof.
And I am like, I'm 99% certain somebody's going off
of the fucking roof and somebody's going to die.
Did you say how many floors it was?
It's a tower, it's like a skyscraper.
It's a tower, okay, okay.
Yeah.
Oh my God, the image finally load.
Matt Hardy's manic fucking grin on his face is,
that's good shit, that's good shit.
Who's this boy running from him again?
That's Sammy Guevara, the Spanish God.
Oh, does he have a gun?
No, it's just hand pointing.
I thought it was a gun too.
Okay, I was just looking at a gun.
Well look, just shoot him.
He does point like a gun, like that is his thing, so.
Okay, it looks like he's holding a gun.
So in Canon, it's a gun, yeah, sure.
It's like an invisible fucking gun that he has.
Oh, okay.
Points at people before he runs them over.
Yeah.
Fantastic.
Wrestling's cool.
Well, keep me posted.
I wanna know what the fuck happens in that.
Does someone go over the roof?
I'm 90% certain someone will go over
and I'm 99% certain that if someone does,
it'll be AJ Styles.
Because he was the one who got buried by the undertaker
at Wrestlemania, he got buried alive.
And then he just recently showed up again,
not mentioning it.
So like totally like, yeah, whatever, I'm still here.
I got buried alive and murdered, but I'm still fine.
And also the other two guys in the match,
Gals and Anderson, who the undertaker also murdered
in that match, they were shortly after they were let go
of the company because of like Corona layoffs.
So they were fired, so they didn't show up again.
So in Canon, they are just dead.
Like they were never seen again.
Undertaker murdered them.
So AJ Styles was buried alive and killed
and both of his best friends are killed
and he just shows up and he's like, yeah, I'm better now.
And now we're gonna climb to the tower
and he's probably gonna fall off again.
And like I'm hoping that AJ Styles' new gimmick
is just that he's like immortal now
and he falls off towers and yeah,
it's gonna be fucking dope.
Wrestling's fucking rad.
Hey, by the way, I was just gonna say
about the Animal Crossing thing before.
Ben, Munchie, I and Kazzy,
we all visited each other's islands the other day
in Animal Crossing and it was a great time.
And it was fucking sick as hell and I loved doing it.
And we all hung out on various places
and we all went to each other's islands.
We went to each other's islands.
We traded fruit. We exchanged fruit.
I now have all the fruits, it feels great.
Here's me, Munchie and Ben all gathered in front of my island
or my flag on the island of Prophesia.
I kept trying to give you pears
but eating them by accident.
Oh yeah, he kept eating the, he had three pears.
He put one down on the ground and said,
okay, Kazzy, he was giving me the Kazzy.
I'm gonna now give you one.
Proceeds to eat the fucking bear.
Okay, I will now do it again.
Eats the other one.
Well.
I found some extras though.
I now have them all planted.
I cannot wait for them to bloom.
I'm gonna make orchards.
It's gonna be sick.
It's gonna be great.
Don't you have to like pay for online?
Yeah, I do.
You did it.
I fucking did it.
I paid Nintendo 20 of my American dollars for one year.
Ben is simping hard for Nintendo right now.
I went for the full year.
I forget who it is.
It's like $9 for a month
or you can just do like 20 bucks for the whole year.
That's not bad.
It's pretty fun.
It's fun.
Like years ago or like a year ago.
I spent like, I spent $300 on the,
like contributing to the RFCK Kickstarter.
So like whatever, doesn't matter.
I mean, I just got a deal.
I forget when.
We were talking about Switch stuff years ago
and I think someone in the PCP comments just said,
like, hey Nate, I'm on a family plan.
I have an extra slot.
I can just add you for free and you get Nintendo online.
I was like, okay, let's do it.
Let's do it.
So I just have, comment on this video.
I forget who it is, who is doing it, but you are.
Yeah, someone did that for me as well, which is pretty based.
It is thoroughly based.
No doubt about it.
So thank you.
Thank you.
It's helping me hang out with my boys on the internet
and it feels good.
But has no one got a comment on my flag?
My flag that I'm so proud of for proficient?
Oh, I already did.
I still have this amazing wrestling image full screen.
So I didn't even see the next one.
Scroll down and look at my flag.
Haha, it says gay epic.
The R street is stunning.
Thank you.
That's all I wanted.
That's all I, just an acknowledgement.
Thank you, thank you.
And I don't know why the image is sideways.
I will fix that for the leg of the show notes.
All right, well, that's all I had to say
about Animal Crossing.
It's a great time and I can't wait to develop my land more.
Oh, I've got chrysanthemums.
I'm gonna breed more chrysanthemums.
Hazy and Munchies land is like a barren wasteland.
It's like an undeveloped third world country.
It is embarrassing.
It's a disaster zone.
Didn't they just start playing?
Yeah, I know.
No excuses, no excuse.
But it's funny to say it.
Here's the punchline to my wrestling anecdote.
Someone already made a meme of the image
of Sammy running from the golf cart.
There it is, there it is, everybody.
This is just such a boomer meme.
But what can you say?
What more could you expect from R slash memes
by you slash glorious Gilmore?
Thank you, sir.
For your contribution.
William Gilmore, he's a critical role fan.
God damn it.
The fact that the meme maker's name is on it
makes it better and I hope no one would cut that off.
I think he's so proud of this meme.
I hope he forever gets credit for it.
Wait, did you think he manually added that
or is that just like something
that's automatically generated via R memes?
I hope he manually added it.
That would, I mean, he really should have watermarked this.
He doesn't.
No, that's gotta be an auto gen thing.
Well, for sure.
They're doing God's work either way.
Meme attribution is just cringe in general.
Just like memes are meant to be,
memes are in the public domain by default.
Memes are the new currency though, Tom.
They're the new social credit score.
This is what we'll be using when the lockdown ends.
We're transitioned to a new government style
where it's based on your gamer score, basically.
And that's what I want.
You're telling me that we're,
out of all the possible systems we could implement,
we found the one thing that was worse
than capitalism and went with it?
I sure hope so.
It sounds great to me. God damn it.
You know what?
Sometimes there's threads on V on 4chan
about like how many platinum trophies you've gotten
speaking of gamer scores.
It dawns on me.
I don't think I've ever gotten a platinum trophy
on any of like my PS4 games and, you know, it should-
Because you do things with your life, Nate.
It bothers me a little bit
that I've never gotten a platinum trophy.
Just a, not even one.
I know I shouldn't care, but I kind of do-
Time for the new saga of Nate
trying to get one platinum trophy.
Okay, I've committed-
I mean, you'd platinum Kingdom Hearts too, of course.
That would be the game to platinum for you.
There are games that I have definitely done everything in.
The first one I ever did was Super Mario Bros.
2 Advance for GBA.
I did literally everything in that game
and I got all the check marks on the thing.
God, that felt good.
You know, I feel so like ripped off by the world.
Like, I used to 100% games all the time.
Back in the day, before there were no trophies,
before there was proof that you could fucking show people.
Now all these kids, you know,
they get these fucking participation trophies
that they get for everything
and they just go, oh, look what I got.
I got a nice little thing on Icon on my PS4
for doing a thing in a game
that any fucking baby shit could do.
You know, you get a damn trophy nowadays
when you're just watching a cutscene.
Back in my days, I fucking 100%
a goddamn Donkey Kong 54 and I didn't get shit for it.
Oh, and that's a grind to fucking 100% that shit.
Jesus Christ.
I believe I, no, I didn't 100% it,
but I was replaying Banjo.
I didn't even beat Banjo 2e
because I got a little bit bored, like halfway through.
Banjo Kazooie, I loved
and was happy to like basically 100% that.
I got the fucking ice key, man.
I got the fucking eggs and shit,
as many as you can get by entering those fucking passwords
in the horrible ass fucking password
entry thing in the sandcastle.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
That's a fucking Vietnam flashback.
Just take the 10 minutes to enter those.
Yeah, that sucked.
But I did it, man.
I needed to complete it.
So yeah, I guess that's 100% completion.
They should like, if you get like a platinum trophy,
they should send you a physical trophy.
It should be like getting a plaque on YouTube.
You should get some certificate of achievement.
Maybe they could print out or something.
No, because that could be faked.
That shit can be faked.
You need an actual signed,
but like the Dean of Video Games at Video Game College
should give you an award.
Yeah, I agree.
So that when I apply.
Melt down the disc and turn it into a trophy.
There's no reason to play anymore.
Yeah, it makes sense.
When you 100% the game, you have no need for it anymore.
The PS4 just starts spinning really fast
and it just melts your disc into a trophy
and spits it back out.
I mean, we talked about enlightenment.
The video game exists, right?
To just feed you visual and auditory and input,
tactile feedback.
Once you've absorbed all that information,
you're just that step closer to enlightenment.
And yeah, there is no need for it to exist anymore.
You could just give it away or whatever.
But I was thinking about this because
I was looking at the trophy selection for the FF7 remake
since I beat like the super boss.
And I feel in myself, I have done the biggest
and most important things in the game,
but then they're like,
well, why don't you play every chapter on hard mode?
I'm like, hard mode isn't even hard in this game.
It's just annoying with the like MP conservation thing.
And I already found a way to exploit the system,
which is just when you find one of those boxes
that you break to get MP back,
you just break it, get the MP, save and reload the game.
And the box just reappears.
So you can just do that as much as you want.
Cause it's terrible game design in my opinion.
It's not challenging.
It's just annoying.
So I don't know, I don't feel bad about it at all.
Point is, point is,
there's a bunch of these fucking challenges
that aren't even fun.
Like when I first did the like the Don Corneo raid,
yeah, I got everyone's worst dress.
I got Tifa's worst dress and heiresses and clouds.
But then I did it again and I got their best dresses.
And now the game wants me to go through it again
and get the middle dresses.
No, no, I don't have time for that.
That's fucking annoying.
I had to go back stupid.
And do like, because I missed one of the Colosseum battles
in Corneo, like the, one of the extra heiress battles.
So I had to like, I had to, first I went back
to like the chapter before you saw him the tower,
thinking like, okay, I'll go back here
and I'll do all the Colosseum battles.
Well, you can't select heiress
cause she's not in your party at that chapter.
So I had to go back to the chapter
where you're in wall market with her.
So I go back to that chapter thinking,
okay, I gotta do her two stupid battles in this thing.
Well, it starts you out at the beginning of the chapter.
The Colosseum battle is at the end of the fucking chapter.
I had to do the whole stupid shit all over again,
going around talking to people and putting on dresses.
Not good, make me mad, make me mad, make me sad.
One of these things doesn't make the,
like this doesn't make the game like awful,
but because the game is structured this way in chapters,
that's been the story of my fucking life.
Like replaying sections of the chapter
in order to get to the place where I can now do things.
We used to just call this end game content
and you could just do it all at the end.
But because we got chapters here,
that's just like a unique annoyance
of this particular style of game.
I mean, it's not the end of the world,
but it was fucking annoying.
And now that I beat the secret boss,
I think I clocked in 75 hours to beat all this shit,
to finish like everything of note in the game
as far as I'm concerned.
And I don't know, Superboss was pretty fun.
I enjoyed it, but that chapter shit
was full of the fucking birds.
I don't even want to complain anymore.
It's just gonna give me more shitty comments
I have to fucking respond to.
Yeah.
See, I don't know, all things like that,
I mean, when I make my video, I'm gonna mention that,
but none of that is like a big deal.
Like any fucking game has imperfections, you know?
Like you ever like, you see a comment of someone
who's like so wrong and like so aggressively hostile
with their wrongness, like you have to respond to it.
So like, you do that thing where you're so fucking mad
that you take each fucking line
and you respond to every line with a fucking paragraph
explaining exactly why the person's fucking wrong.
And then I got it and I got this like massive retort
and I'm looking at it, it's like after,
like by the time I'm finished writing it,
I don't even want to post it anymore.
And it just sits there and I'm like,
well, what the fuck do I do with this now?
I don't know, save it for a fucking script later, I guess.
So like, it's like, I don't want to click post
because like there's no point
because then he'll just respond to it
and I'll be caught in the loop forever.
So like I tab over and then I'd like go about my day,
I don't have the spirit to,
I don't have the strength of will
to just close that tab and just forget about it.
So the comment stays up, unposted in that tab.
And then it happens again later in the week
with a different comment.
And then I just got multiple tabs up of like comment wars
that only I know about that even the other person
in the comment thread doesn't know is happening
that only I have to bear the weight of and live with.
I have done that.
This is why every site has to adopt
the way Newgrounds does comments.
It's perfect.
Which is what?
Because on Newgrounds, someone leaves a comment
and then the artist, only the artist,
the person uploading the content can respond once.
Oh my God, you're describing a perfect world time.
You're describing everything I've ever wanted yet.
It exists on Newgrounds.com.
I would sell my fucking soul to have that on YouTube.
You know, the only thing is I,
when I see a comment like that, there are some comments
that they say a certain thing.
And I know for them to have reached this conclusion,
there has to be so many things,
like I can see their whole history arcing backward
to know like all the things that have happened in their life
that have led them to this point.
And all the like skewed perspectives
they have to have brought to the table
to have interpreted what I was saying
in this particular way.
And luckily I'm able most of the time
to quickly do the calculus in my head of,
okay, I know in order to express my point
and correct this person,
it would take me way too much time.
Because like you can't even just tell them
the thing they got wrong and expect them to understand it.
That's not enough.
You have to like do the detective work
of like telling them what happened in their life
and why their entire perspective on the world
has been wrong from day one in excruciating detail.
I feel that a lot, I feel that a lot.
Well, hey, we've been talking for a while.
If you want, we got voicemails.
We can go to them unless anybody else wants to, you know.
Let's fucking do it, dawg.
Yeah, let's make it happen.
Okay, just a moment, I'll bring them up.
Speak pipe, link, ladies and gentlemen,
down in the description.
Let me just mention about the RFC kick starter.
We won, we won the game.
We did it.
Day one, you guys made like 7,000, 5,000, right?
7, 20, 7, 250?
Right.
It's like 7,000 change.
I donated a bunch at the end to meet that last goal.
And we're gonna make like a million fucking,
I'm going to, have I talked about talking
to the fucking Chinese people on alibaba.com?
Not here, so yeah, clarify.
I have like talking to a bunch of people
and like I have to haggle with them.
I have to like, I've been talking to one,
been like, shipping is like that much?
Like, ah, you could get me a better shipping rate, right?
And she's like, oh, it's kind of high right now
because of COVID, but like maybe if we like
order in like a month, then maybe it'll be lower.
Like, okay, just give me the sample.
And talk to this other guy who's like, okay,
we can make you these, but they'll be cheaper,
but they'll be iron, but that's okay.
But because they're iron, we can only cut certain shapes.
Like, we can't cut all these shapes.
You can only cut like most of these shapes.
It's like, ah, okay.
So it's like, okay, maybe we'll go with those
for like some of them.
And these, this other guy for some others.
I don't know.
It's very complicated.
I've been like going back and forth
with a whole bunch of fucking people.
The struggle is real.
This will be a sad one.
The struggle is real, but we're gonna make like,
when I've make the order, and like a couple of weeks
or a month from now, I'm going to be receiving like,
like dozens of pounds of like huge bags of like
thousands of items, and I'm going to hold them
and dive into them like Scrooge McDuck.
I personally put down $60 for like seven pins or something.
He jumped into a bunch of pins.
So they're gonna have like the things.
No, I'm gonna take those off.
I'm gonna take those off first.
You want the real shit, the raw experience.
And that's what I'm gonna do with my seven pins
added to my pin pile.
I'm definitely getting the slime corp pin,
which is the only canonical pin that already exists
in Canon.
So that's the good one, obviously.
I guess so, yeah.
And I gotta get the big coin.
I want a big old fucking slime.
You get the big coin.
Is the final vote up?
Is it counted?
I wanna know if that gun girl pin is actually gonna be
made or not.
Okay.
Well, this might be the final vote.
And let me, let me, let me, let me, let me,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
The final,
I mean, if you have to look things up.
No, I don't have to, I'll just need to look at the fricking,
just look at the vote and see what's going on there.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
The voting booth.
Okay, I said in the chat that it was like the vote for four.
I think it's actually gonna be at least,
if there's no new designs,
then I think it'll be for at least seven,
possibly more.
So like, it looks like probably gun girl will get made.
She has 15 votes.
And there are a bunch with more than that right now,
it looks like.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Like seven more pins will get added.
I think we funded, we needed to vote for four
when the poll went up,
but then we hit three more during the stream,
I think, unless I have that wrong.
So yeah, I think seven.
So what is this?
It looks like the top votes now are four.
Gun girl is number four.
Number 10 is the top one, I think.
The slime heart, the levy, jevy, stay dead.
The mega slime.
The mega slime, gun girl, and then.
Six, which means.
Investor.
Right, right.
Kola already picked can man.
I think Kola already picked can man as her choice,
so I'm gonna skip that one.
And then, wait, E is mega slime.
Looks like you're in the clear with gun girl though.
It looks, yeah, probably.
More or less.
By the way, can I, is there a number of times
I'm allowed to vote?
Cause there's a couple I just wanna throw a vote on,
just for fun.
No, you freaking ding dong.
You vote for any, vote for as many as you want.
Okay, just check.
Like the point is that if everyone just votes yes
on the ones that they would want.
They all evens out anyway, right?
Yeah.
Then the ones that will get made will be the ones
that the most people want.
Right, I thought so.
Okay, okay, cool.
So yeah, vote for as many as you want.
Sick.
Well, there you go.
I mean, so if you pledged, did you,
I assume you pledged, Gib.
How much did you, how many pins did you spring for?
Gib pledged, Gib was like the first one to pledge.
Yeah.
I was excited.
Cause I knew, cause it's like, they're cool.
How many pins did you get though?
I have a place for pins.
I think I'm getting 13,
but like two of those count for the challenge coin.
Oh yeah, right, right.
Yeah.
Sick.
So yeah, a bunch.
Nice.
Well, congratulations on a successful Kickstarter, Ben.
Yay.
It is very nice.
I just had to update you.
Another one I've supported.
By the way, I just want to say,
I really think that this like Kickstarter
for specific projects thing is a smart way to go business-wise.
That's what Kickstarter is for.
I mean, no, you're right,
but I plan on doing like more small Kickstarter.
I just think it makes sense.
And like as long as you deliver successfully,
cause like it, cause the reason it is good
is because you basically can get the,
you basically get paid for it.
Instead of like investing the money to spend,
it might theoretically be cheaper to do it yourself
because you don't have to like pay any Kickstarter fees.
But, you know, aside from that,
it's safer because if you run the Kickstarter,
then people pay for it ahead of time
and you don't assume the risk of like investing in product
that you then must hope will sell.
Right, right.
That's very true.
You know if there's market interest.
Yeah.
Exactly right.
And I don't know, like Mia,
I mean, yeah, that is a big one right there.
And then you have the additional benefit of like,
as opposed to, I mean, I don't know,
I plan on personally like having a Patreon model
going forward for a long time.
And then also when there are specific projects
trying to get people to fund those, you know, in addition,
like me and Digi will eventually do our thing probably
and do like a Kickstarter for like, I don't know,
like some amount of money for some product
on the other side or whatever.
I don't know, just an idea,
but I don't just seems like a good idea.
All right, anyway, that's all done.
So if you didn't get any pins too fucking bad,
you missed your window.
You'll have to wait for,
I think we might do these once in a while,
like maybe six months from now or a year from now,
maybe we'll do this again and we will,
and again, you will be able to,
people will can submit their own vote and like,
but like all the ones that got made this time
will be available to be made next time too,
because the manufacturers will keep the molds.
So we won't have to pay for them to like, yeah.
So we'll be able to order like another hundred
of like an old design at like, you know,
just for the manufacturer costs, which is pretty low.
Yeah, that's sick.
That's sick.
So I think that's the plan.
I think that's, yeah, they're not gonna be available
just to buy any time you want,
but they will be available through like,
future events like this.
Cool.
Well, voice mail time, ladies and gentlemen,
leave, click the link down below
if you wanna leave voice mails at the speak pipe link
and with their good, we'll plan.
So let's get to them.
Oh, this is a public service announcement from beloved,
so this is like of the pre voice mail one.
It's Marinpan, one of our admins
from the PCB Minecraft server.
It's something he wants everybody to know.
Let's hear he has to say, go.
Hey, remember that Pokemon MMORPG game freak
is never gonna make because of their bad idea only policy.
Well, it's been under your nose this whole time.
Pixelmon is a sexy little mod that turns Minecraft
into a fully functional Pokemon game
with mechanics up to date with ultra sun and moon.
And this May 20th, you, that's right you.
Look at me when I'm fucking talking to you.
You have the chance to become the coolest guy.
Come join the procrastinators, Minecraft servers,
first Pokemon championship tournament for your chance
at the highest title in the land,
in video games and in IRL.
For the next few days until the tournament
we'll be disabling the wireless, so you can come in,
build a team and show the world you know about Pokemons
live on Shekels for Hekels.
Stay tuned for monthly free days,
be there or be square.
There you go.
Okay.
I could tell he was trying to think of something else
to say.
So when this episode goes up, it'll be Friday the 15th
and the tournament is on the 20th.
That's right, that's right.
So definitely as of today.
So you will have five days to get into Pixelmon,
the PCB Minecraft server and get a team together.
We will presumably there will be future tournaments
in case five days to do that is kind of a compressed frame.
Well, you know, I talked to MarinPan about that specifically.
So it turns out there is,
I mean, the people who are already in there
have been planning for this for a while.
Yes, that's right.
So just to be clear, on the 20th, on this channel,
the P ProCrastinators podcast,
we are streaming on the Shekels for Hekels,
a Pokemon tournament in the Pokemon,
the PCB Minecraft server.
It's gonna be great.
And yes, the MarinPan, the guys are organizing it.
There will be prizes and all that good stuff.
If you just want to be in the tournament
and just get humiliated,
they just go in there, catch a bunch of shitmonds,
enter the tournament, lose in the first round,
but we will have to acknowledge that.
That's fine.
But even beyond that, there's another thing going on,
which I mean, Ben was getting at,
which is that we are opening up the PCP Minecraft server
for everyone for several days until the tournament.
So we wanna see people just hanging out in the server,
watching the tournament with us.
It's an event we're doing just to get people to come hang out
for a couple of days and shit.
I get it.
Yeah, yeah.
Now I fucking get it.
It's all the pieces are coming together.
So we'll have in the description.
I don't know exactly how it'll work,
but we will have a write-up,
I think MarinPan was putting together one,
of links to everything you need to join the server.
And again, it's gonna be open to everybody
for a span of five or six days or whatever,
so you can come in, you can just spend a few minutes
and look around the world if you want.
You can join the PCP Minecraft server
for free, temporarily.
That's right, for about a week or so.
And after that.
Until the tournament.
And we're thinking of doing future events like this.
How cool would it be?
How cool would it be to have the stands packed?
It would be odd.
With little Minecraft CDs.
Your little Minecraft boy will be visible
on this channel during the stream
as we are watching the tournament live.
You could be in the stadium.
That sounds really fun.
That sounds really cool.
It's a fucking great idea
that MarinPan and Lumia came up with.
I had talked about competing in the tournament,
but even back then I was like,
boy, I feel like I'm so far behind on catching mods,
and now I must be so far behind.
Well, let me tell you,
because I was curious about this too.
So by far the hardest part is catching the Pokemon.
And by the way, there is a write-up,
I'm sure it'll be in the show notes,
about the specific rules for the tournament.
Catching the Pokemon is the hard part,
but leveling them up and EV training them
is actually super easy,
and it takes a little bit of time,
but the old, the horseshoe crew house
that exists in the spawn point,
like Mage set that up when she was admin,
to just make it really easy to grind all your Pokemon
to like level 100 in like a few minutes
against these like level 100 Blizzies.
With the Blizzies, right?
That's right, and EV train them too.
So it's the other stuff that's harder to do,
but actually getting level 100 Pokemon pretty damn easy,
and the boys on the server will tell you all about it
if you want to stop by.
I don't know how to EV train,
but I do, I got all my guys to level 100 with the Blizzies,
but it takes like 10 minutes of Pokemon if it's bad.
So I don't even fucking know how EVs work, frankly.
I don't know how to reset them.
I don't know anything, but I've been told
that it's easy to do.
Oh, if you give them a Thunderstone,
it turns into a Jolteon.
Yes, shit then.
Besinga, indeed my good man.
So there you go.
So I mean, even if you don't want to participate
in the tournament, it would just be really fun
to just be on the stream with us.
On the 20th, which is by the way,
at 3 p.m. Eastern Standard Time, is when we're starting.
Just come hang out and spawn.
Let's have a big fucking party on the server.
You don't have to pay anything to stop by
for the couple of days.
So fuck it, man.
Do what you want.
It's gonna be a good time.
That is pretty hype, I gotta say.
It's gonna be sick, it's gonna be sick.
And our boys, our admins,
have more plans coming in the future.
So hey, do you like Minecraft?
We're, you know, we've been hearing these thoughts
of like, oh, you know, I like Minecraft,
like PCP, blah, blah, blah,
but not to Pixelmon.
We are working on some ideas
to address those concerns as well
in ways that give everybody what they want.
But we'll get back to you on that.
We got, we're cooking up some ideas.
Anyway.
Maybe I'll hop back in the server
so that this week in a fuck around with my team
a little bit.
That's a good idea, that's a good idea.
Everyone's welcome.
We can have, I don't know,
a big old fucking tournament as long as we want.
Okay, onto the next one.
So, okay, here's our first big boy one.
How many more, how many more?
I think we have a total of nine.
Oh, God.
Okay, we'll go through that.
We'll strap in for another hour.
Holy shit.
It will go through him fast.
I promise, guys.
All right, this is a good one.
Here is a Discord at everyone rant.
Go.
Why does everyone get so fucking angry
when you add everyone on Discord?
Like, what the fuck?
It's just a notification.
Why are you so pissed?
I didn't like kill your dog or anything.
Jesus Christ.
Everyone.
I have like never seen anyone where I add everyone.
And then it's like, they're fine with it.
Everyone is fucking mad for some stupid reason.
It's retarded.
It's a notification.
If you don't want it so much, turn it the fuck off.
There you go.
Thoughts, agreement, disagreement, valid.
But also it's valid that everyone's mad.
They're both right.
Yeah, yeah.
I feel like, you say turn it off,
but I don't know why that it always,
like at everyone's always give me notifications anyway.
Even if I mute and like suppress them,
it just doesn't work.
I feel like it just doesn't work too.
Maybe I'm doing something wrong, but I don't know.
Like I mute the entire server.
I mute the chat.
I mute every chat just because I don't like notifications
and I check them periodically.
But at everyone's and at here's,
they still, they just seep through.
I don't know how it works.
I feel like I'm missing something.
But hey, I did want to say on a larger point here.
So recently I realized what I should have been doing
all along was I think I saw you doing this Gib.
When I've been streaming, I'm like, oh, you know,
I should just like let people know I'm doing this
in more places than Twitter.
So I've just like added people on like my patron server.
And then also, I think in the PCP one.
And I've got a couple of people being like,
oh, I got two notifications.
I'm seething with rage about that.
And they're not wrong.
I get it.
But I'm wondering how much I should care
that one or two people are mildly annoyed
by an at like that, you know, at that time.
Doesn't matter.
Like the worst that could happen
is that they leave your Discord.
That's true.
Reverse Spectrum, fuck you.
I think it was Reverse Spectrum.
Keep seething, bro.
But like, you know, I posted my Discord at everyone
whenever I have like a...
I mean, I add everyone into the Discord.
I add everyone into the ones that I run.
Yeah, I mean, the PCP one, I was thinking like,
I mean, you know, I know it's not my Discord,
but I figure there's probably people here
who might be interested in seeing it.
So is it, is it a, you know.
It's not a problem when we do it.
It's if you're in someone else's server
and you add everyone, that's when people like do like stop.
Yeah.
Like that's what people get mad about.
That's the run of the mill annoying shit.
I mean, what you should do is you should just go
into your server settings and disable
at everyone function for anyone but you.
Before the Iowa caucuses and before Super Tuesday,
I went into like a bunch of different servers
and I didn't care.
I just added everyone.
I was like, remember to vote.
Remember to vote for Bernie Sanders.
Right, of course.
I knew I would get banned.
I didn't care.
Did you get banned?
I only got banned from one server.
And I don't even think I got banned.
I just got kicked.
Was it the Ted Cruz fan server?
It was in a server that I absolutely did not care
about being in at all.
It was from the Amy T Falcone fan server.
Do you know who that is?
No, I'm gonna Google it though.
She was one of the contestants on strip search
and she is a Penny Arcade.
She's a Penny Arcade orbiter now
and now she's on the Acquisitions Incorporated C team.
Well, that's cool.
Oh yeah, I remember.
It was fine.
But yeah, that was the only server I got banned from
for relentlessly adding everyone
telling them to vote for Bernie Sanders.
Ben, please have mercy on them.
They can only handle so much.
Well, they fucking, they executed me.
Well, fair enough, fair enough.
It's out of my hands now.
Amy Falcone fan server, just where I would wanna be.
All right, well, all right, there it is.
There's your info on that.
All right, next one.
This is a voicemail god, PCPPSA.
Okay, I forget what this was.
Let's find out.
Yeah, I play Final Fantasy VII.
I like using, you know, the spells,
such as fire one, fire two, and fire three.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Okay, I'll play this game.
What the fuck is this spells?
What?
They spelled fire wrong.
Kingdom Hearts is a bad video game.
That's it.
Go watch my live streams and watch the VODs.
I have, all right.
You still haven't beat Clary yet?
I'm right there.
I'm just training for her right now.
We're making a plan.
I have never watched a BGE Nuzlocke
and I feel like it's mostly because
of a large time investment.
Like how many episodes is that?
How many hours of my time is that?
You should watch, it's called Value for Money.
That's totally understandable.
I don't blame anybody who doesn't like,
who isn't like doing a task.
Zero money and how many countless hours of content.
How many people have watched like my eight,
my six hour Ratchet and Clank two stream?
It's a lot of value for no money.
And it was fun, but like,
I don't expect any of you to watch that.
Well, sure, sure.
How many people have watched the legend
the entirety of the Rowdyfuckers cop killers,
Pokemon, XD, Gale of Darkness things?
I think not all of those.
It's billions, not all of those.
Billions.
With a B.
It's just a matter of like putting in the tedious work
of like cutting it down to highlights.
True, true.
But what you know, for my first Nuzlocke,
no Needra did that, I believe.
I think he's the one who made a full,
like the entire Nuzlocke for Diamond up to,
like he made it like in a couple days before the Elite Four.
And he really killed it with that.
It was fucking sick.
Yeah, I think I may have looked at that.
I don't know, what was it?
Like, how long was that?
It was probably still like 20 minute video highlights.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, a lot of fun stuff does happen.
So I think that was a pretty great video personally.
I mean, it like condenses like the,
I had to grind friendship.
So there were like several episodes
of me just walking back and forth
while we just talked about whatever on the stream.
See, that's kind of more of what I would like
is like the stories you can tell,
like D&D-esque stories of you doing strange,
funny things on your Nuzlocke,
rather than watching like a really long video highlighting it.
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
Like a lecture.
Someone do a lecture on the fucking Nuzlocke.
Like the grinding story I've heard you tell before.
And I was like, yeah, like I can appreciate the,
I can get the gist of why that's cool
without having to experience all of it.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my God, I was playing Pokemon Flip,
or sorry, the Voltorb Flip in the gold,
what is it like, the Goldenrod Casino yesterday.
And when I realized that like, when you went around,
I had to get 14,000 like Pokcoins or whatever it is in there
in order to buy the TMs I needed of Swords Dance
for Heracross and Thunderbolt for my based electrode,
Lubshorne.
And so I could one-shot that fucking Gyarados piece of shit
with the electrode.
After using a light screen turn one, baby.
Fuckin', I, when I was realizing
how ineffectual and pathetic I was at that game
and how if you make a mistake,
you can be kicked down from like the higher level
of fighting tiers all the way back down to level one.
It was then my third eye open, I realized,
wait, I'll just use save states and cheat.
It's the greatest idea I've ever had.
And then I did it and it was great
because you can't even lose money.
You can only lose time in that game
because there's no monetary investment.
The house literally cannot win.
You can only lose.
So I allowed myself to do it.
That's a funny story in context,
but it's not that funny to watch for like three hours
of me grinding it to have that realization later.
I mean, I don't know, me and the people,
we talk about fun stuff while we're doing it or whatever,
gushing about rage and seething about the remade,
et cetera, et cetera.
Every now and, you know, that's,
it's been like a highlight reel,
like the YouTube nuzzle locks,
like my nuzzle locks are basically,
they're basically a highlight reel.
But like, there was no original or there was.
I only talk during certain parts.
But I still get comments.
Every now and then, a little YouTube notification
with someone that's like, dude, I watched this again.
Like I watched this back in the day,
please do another one.
And I'm like, I want another Ben nuzzle lock too.
I mean.
I know.
Have I already said what I'm thinking?
Yeah, you said of a, not Yo-Kai watch,
but the other one, the Temtem.
I was considering, and I don't know if it's a good idea yet.
I have to look into it,
but I was considering that maybe
when I get back to streaming, whenever that is,
whenever I'm ready to do that,
I will start a new nuzzle lock
and it would be a Temtem nuzzle lock.
And then I would probably cut it down
and make like a highlight YouTube show.
I think probably.
As the number one fan of your nuzzle locks,
I want that to exist.
The only, I don't know how nuzzle lockable Temtem is.
Like it seems like it is, but it seems like it's,
I don't know.
You might need to really say how it looks.
I was making Temtem.
I would absolutely make sure it's compliant with nuzzle locks.
I think there is like a nuzzle lock mode.
Oh, well that'd be sick.
Or maybe it's like,
oh, well that'd be sick.
Or maybe there might actually just be a nuzzle lock mode.
That would sure take the fucking pain out of me.
But you know, Pokemon Uranium had a nuzzle lock mode
and it made me really mad because there was a, okay.
It seems one of the rules that it imposed on you
was that it would not let you catch duplicates, right?
But it did not count different Pokemon
from the same evolutionary line as duplicates.
So if you had a tentacruel,
if you had a tentacool and you found a wild tentacool
and you didn't catch it, right?
It would consider that to be the one you're allowed to catch.
And it would be like, no, you can't catch anymore.
Like that was your chance.
Even though obviously, obviously the spirit
of the dupes clause is that, no, that would be a dupe.
Like that's effectively a duplicate.
Fuck you, okay?
Yeah, that sucks.
That the Uranium nuzzle lock mode
had that one glaring flaw that made me so mad.
And that might be why I didn't end up playing that game.
Lamar.
Fair enough, fair enough.
But, you know, maybe I could go back and do that.
Maybe we could go back and do that for like RFCK
because it's like toxic waste mutation.
Yeah, that sounds awesome.
Ooh, my brain.
I mean, that would be a long-term commitment
doing a full nuzzle lock one of those.
But I mean, I would love it.
Oh dude, it'll be just like Pokemon XT Gale of Darkness.
It'll be the greatest time ever.
No, it's such a great game.
No, no, no.
It won't be miserable at all.
It won't be the worst thing you ever,
just for like a year of your entire fucking life.
Do it.
I love nuzzle locks.
I would watch that.
I want to see that.
Oh, oh my God.
That's a great idea.
Briefly on the subject of highlights,
I really feel like I might at one time
want to go back to my given gaming streams
and like sift through them to find like the good moments
because there are a lot of like really, really funny
like Game Grumps-esque like laughing moments.
But they're so buried.
Like nobody knows about it.
You need like an editor, man.
Like me and three other people.
Someone who catalogs this shit to do that kind of stuff.
The day is getting closer all the time.
It is approaching.
When I can, when I have,
when I will have enough like saved up inventory
of Let's Plays and highlights to relaunch,
it's a blue glow channel.
And that day will be glorious.
There will be some, just a never ending stream.
It'll be like you've entered the land of milk and honey.
You found the promised land of funny Let's Plays
where Mako energy flows from the ground.
It's just gonna be, I think about all the time.
I fantasize about this far off day in the future
and it gets closer every day.
Cause every day I accumulate more footage
and I sit here and I tediously make my little highlight reels
and I make the thumbnails.
The other day I sat here for fucking three hours
making thumbnails for all these like backed up clips
of footage and I'm just, I'm like a mad man.
I'm just sitting here plotting the day
when I can be like, Hey, everybody, guess what?
There's a schedule now.
There's gonna be a funny Let's Play
every day for the rest of your fucking lives.
And they'll be like, Oh my God, we love this guy.
And I'll be like, yes, money, all the beautiful money
for all the entertainment for you
and all the money for me.
I want that man.
I'm waiting for it.
Hey, Jesse, where is, where is the like the,
the Dark Souls thing that I was,
Oh, Poise Boys.
Like you were playing a Poise Boy
and then S.H.I.E.L.D. O'Neill, my character.
Me and Gibbon did like a multiplayer Dark Souls run together
where the, where the conceit was we would try to,
we would both make characters specifically maxed out
in Poise just to kind of explore this forgotten stat
in the series and it was called Poise Boys.
And my character was called Tank McSpank
and his character was called S.H.I.E.L.D. O'Neill
and it was awesome and I have all the footage
and I was looking for it the other day
and I couldn't find it.
And like I had this moment of like, oh my God,
did I delete the Poise Boys footage at some point
to like save on space?
Oh no, I can't find it anywhere.
I must have deleted it.
What a fool.
I could have, I could have finally used it.
What a foolish, foolish man I am.
But then miraculously I was going through
like the, my little dashboard page on YouTube for the channel
and like turns out I did delete them for space.
But first I made sure to upload the raw footage
as private videos so I still have it.
I still have the Poise Boys footage.
Thank God.
It will be seen someday come hell or high water.
Hmm, hmm.
Excellent.
Hell yeah.
All right, let's move on to our next voicemail.
We got plenty more to get through.
All right, so this one is Shaggy
gives us the good news by Jelly Beaner.
All right, take it away.
Little brothers and sisters today.
You'll be listening to a PCP passage
from the patron saint of wrestling, Jesse.
Please turn to chapter 69, page 420 man
in your PCP branded Bibles.
Let's hear the wise words of Jesse.
Fucking Jews, mutilating our babies
and selling their balls in a cold bag
next to the ice cream.
I hate Jews.
Here, Jesse is clearly telling us
exclamation point dab on the Jews.
Now, where are those who pose the dabbing of Jews?
They're like Jews in sheep's clothing, man.
To them, I say exclamation point dab.
Will the congregation please stand
in all dabbing unison on the Jews?
I'm up, I'm up.
Everyone stand up.
I'm standing. Absolutely.
That is so fucking weird.
That clip is- What's that from?
I can't remember.
Why did it end?
That's it, that's the end of the sermon.
I know, it's sad, I know, I know.
Dab, isn't that from like fuck cars or something?
It's from fuck pizza.
And like- You're right.
It's like someone just asked me about it the other day.
Someone like messaged me like, where's fuck pizza?
What did you delete fuck pizza?
Like I didn't delete fuck pizza.
It got fucking taken down for hate speech
because of that Jew joke.
Right, right.
And it's like, you know, and like obviously,
I don't remember the context, but the video's about pizza.
I was fucking, you know.
I think I remember, like you said something like
how we cost at some point.
That's right, that's right.
Yeah, the punchline was how we cost.
Cause that's why I was talking about,
I was talking about how oven pizza is not real pizza.
And it's not, it doesn't taste good.
DeGiorno sucks, the commercials are lies.
The oven sucks and from the oven became, you know,
and became like a Jew joke.
And because the Jew joke then went into the punchline,
which was the fucking how we cost as in hungry howies.
It was not, it was a fucking pizza joke.
And they took down the video for hate speech.
I mean, you know, obviously retarded,
but I don't know, yeah, what can you do?
That's YouTube for you.
That's YouTube.
Michelle got her Twitter taken down for,
it was like a black guy pointing a gun at the screen
and it was something about like a begun thought
is was like her text and like that was considered
like a violent threat or something,
which I mean, it was a man with a gun.
Okay, sure.
But you know, it was a joke.
You just can't, you know, when you're in charge,
you just can't-
No, it was big, it was big champ.
It was big champ.
Oh, that's right, yeah.
A silent thing.
Big champ is onto Michelle trying to, you know,
subvert their-
They wanted her oil.
God.
She was getting the word.
I'm mad thinking about it.
I'm mad all over again.
How he cost is like the best joke I've ever fucking written.
They took it from me.
What can you do, man?
Hey, let's move on to, what do we got here?
Blasphemous Nats, Gold Dig Grotto.
Jesse saves the PCP?
Okay, apparently I think that's the full title.
All right, let's take it away, go.
Hey boy, what you doing down by the river?
I'm searching for gold, mister.
We ain't gonna find none.
Ain't much of nothing around here no more.
Why is that, mister?
Well, once in the topics done dried up,
well, saying the horse cock nostalgia
is the only glue keeping them together
is it's putting it nicely.
Chatsky's gone and unshatsky.
If the brothers make one more
unfact check political statement,
the dam's gonna burst.
Mages dead, digital brother up
and went on some kind of grid-based system of rule.
All of ours are furry
and hippos selling nudie mags of his juice starter.
Say, ain't you seen the wanted posters?
No, mister.
Well, then PCB boys trying to skip town
with that their OVA money.
Sheriff, big news on the front.
We found the boys camped out near the kick starters.
Shit, let's go.
All right, PCB boys, here's the fact.
We enjoy careers now
while you still got a little something left in ya.
Hey, hey, god!
Sir, I don't think they'll listen to no reason.
Damn it, we're going in.
Ah!
They got me good.
Oh, no, mister.
Boy, look at me real.
Get the fuck out of here.
Them PCB boys might be high and dry,
but like the whiskey from my pappy stash,
they'll still give you that good kick when you meet me.
Don't let them hook ya.
Bad Con 5 isn't real, it's not coming.
She sure fits the ass one.
He's back!
That's it.
That's the end.
I feel so comfortable with the whistle.
How did Jesse save us?
I don't understand.
That was fucking amazing.
I mean, that was nuts.
I mean, the density of memory going on.
Voice grail.
Voice grail, I think Blasphemous Nat.
Well, just put, yeah, I mean, I'm at, yeah, fuck it.
Oh, that was Nat Blasphemous?
Blasphemous Nat, Nat Blasphemous.
I'll put Nat Blasphemous in there.
Well, I mean, I'm going to nominate it for Voice Grail
to basically, like, as like a smoke screen
against what it's saying is absolutely true,
we are running away with the Ovi money.
Radcon 5 is all a smoke screen.
We are moving to South America.
There is no more content coming.
This is the end.
We will one day up and disappear into the wild west
and right into the sunset.
Oh, God, I just had a great idea.
That whistle.
That whistle was nuts.
The little bit was the bomb.
This is actually maybe too good an idea,
and I shouldn't say it here because we might use it.
Sensor this, Eleazar, please.
But what if we...
Yeah, never mind.
Okay, good idea.
Okay, on to the next one.
That reminds me, go to onlyfans.com slash pump911.
Oh, Christ.
There's a whole new image on there.
I'm going to take that voice.
Every time I talk about it, I get a new person.
It's free money.
Yeah, I'm saying that voicemail is in Voice Grail now.
I'm going to canonize it in order to disguise its message,
in order to recuperate its messaging,
in the same way that Labor Day is about
socialist protesters getting murdered by the cops,
but it's okay.
We made Labor Day a national holiday,
so now it's actually about working hard.
The government condones this, right?
We've recuperated the messaging.
That's what we're doing.
Don't worry about the man behind the curtain.
I'm also putting it in here so that he'll...
Was that really the end of the story?
I didn't quite understand.
Did Jesse save the PCP?
Did he?
Is he the one who chased off the...
I think he was coming back to finish the job.
Oh, okay.
I was dreading that it would just be another out-of-context Jew joke.
We would then be inundated by dozens of the same fucking...
Like some mad man out there is just flooding our inbox
with us saying bad things about people by accident.
I love a good out-of-context clip.
It's my favorite.
All right, next voicemail is...
Don't do that.
Let me see.
Ranting Raoul, perpetually blue-balled.
Okay, thanks, Raoul.
Go.
What are you guys' thoughts on Patreon and Sentence
stuck in with the development cycle of video games?
Like, I'm tired of seeing these shitty porn games
perpetually stuck in early alpha
because every fucker feels the need to cram their niche fetish into the game.
To me, it just comes off as people giving up
the integrity of the art just for a quick butt.
Maybe it's a cynical take on games development,
but god damn it, I just want a good set.
Well, I see.
He's getting blue-balled by these porn games not releasing
because they're in development hell.
I mean, games being in development hell in general is cringe.
And stupid.
And a big problem with the crowdfunding model, for sure.
These porn games have no incentive to be finished.
The longer the development takes, the more money they make.
I can't blame, you know, somebody wants to do it, whatever.
I get it.
But like, a better model, I think, for a game,
I mean, it depends on the size and scale of the project, obviously.
But it seems to me that Kickstarter is a way, like,
more manageable thing for, like, for the investor, for, like, the...
Well, I mean, the danger of that is that
you might get the funding you asked for,
and then you might discover that you didn't ask for enough
and you can't finish the project and you can't deliver on it.
Like what happened with Charles Barkley, too.
That's true.
I mean, I'd like to think that they could,
if in a situation like that, maybe,
I mean, maybe it's overly optimistic,
but you could just be honest with your audience and say,
like, guys, we realized that this was beyond what we thought,
so we're going to, like, open a second round of funding to do this,
and maybe we'll offer some additional benefits.
Yeah, I mean, that is the danger, too, I guess.
Neither is perfect.
But I mean, I would never fucking...
I would never fucking a Patreon, a porn game, dev, so...
Yeah, I would never pay for porn, but, you know,
I could theoretically see myself supporting,
probably via Kickstarter, a game that I thought was amazing,
even, you know, I like porn games, so maybe that would happen.
But a Patreon model, I...
There's so many bad incentives with the Patreon model.
You know, look at your boy, Yandere Dev, it's, you know...
Yeah.
There's some issues with that timeline.
You know...
Never pay for anything.
If something was, like, very much in my wheelhouse,
and I was like, this is exactly what I want.
I might buy it, like, I might buy it,
but I don't think I would...
I can't see myself crowdfunding, like, a porn,
like a porn game or something, because, yeah,
because this is what happens, they end up in...
I don't...
The only time you should spend money on porn
is a commission of, like, you getting...
A very specific thing.
Like, a very specific new, like, you know,
the exact character you want in the exact way
that they can do it, that otherwise would not exist.
Yeah.
If you really care about that sort of thing,
I've always thought that, like, I mean,
once you get that post-nut clarity, I mean,
I often find, like, I've never spent money on porn,
but I regret the time that I invested.
I'm like, why was I concerned?
I should have just rushed to the nut,
and then I'd be free to go about my day doing other things.
So I've always thought that it's not a particularly valuable
commodity when...
I don't know.
I mean, I've never done it,
but, like, I guess I get the idea.
Like, if it's fine, I don't think it's down or anything.
Yeah, whatever.
If you want to do it, that's fine.
But, yeah, I mean, I would always...
The only times I've backed a campaign,
I've literally backed two.
Yours, Ben, for Vapors 2 or whatever,
and this new one for the RFCK pins,
because they're the only way I can get those things that I want.
Those?
Those are very small.
Those are small, like, achievable projects.
They are to be done within a specific, you know, frame,
speaking of which, still waiting on the last four,
but they keep telling me they're almost done.
My guest artists...
We thought dates are gonna open.
Jade and Nexus have both told me,
reassured me, again, of late,
that their guest vaperettes are nearing completion.
Okay.
I'm sure.
I believe that Munchie and Kazi will not be far behind with theirs.
I have faith.
Shane, maybe spend a little less time
on the Animal Crossing Munchie and Kazi
and a little bit more on finishing the vaperettes.
Yeah, maybe get off of Snack Time Island,
you fucking degenerates.
Log back into reality once in a while,
why don't ya, and wake up to your responsibility.
Maybe if you looked up from your fucking smartphones.
From your damn Pokemon Go machine.
I fucking finished mine in 2019.
Yeah, I've had yours and Cheesy Manfredo's
for a fucking eternity.
I'm sure they'll be worth the wait.
Well, it'll be pretty good, and I'm pretty sure,
I'm pretty sure that at this point,
probably there are people who have pledged to it
and have just forgotten about it,
and those people have already given up
and probably have no expectations
and will probably be floored and stunned
and their jaw will be...
Those socks will be rocked
when they receive a package in the mail from yours truly.
Ben, we call that the Ghost in the Shell Best Anime Ever Model.
That's the way to go.
Yeah.
Keep them waiting so long it feels like a gift.
It feels like there was never any hope or expectation.
All right, next voicemail.
How many more?
Please end it.
There's a total of four, and we can go quick.
Christ.
Zach C.G., I believe is the name.
Okay, Zach, go.
Did you, bro?
Where is rode the rack on four?
Chapter five.
You said that we'd get a fifth.
Chapter, you know I'm not satisfied.
Did you, bro?
Where is rode the rack on four?
Chapter five.
You said that we'd get a fifth.
Chapter, you know I'm not satisfied.
Oh!
Did you, bro?
Give me that!
Ride the rack on four!
Chapter five, motherfucker!
Chapter five.
Yeah, you're right.
Well, look, clearly nobody has time to be both an author and a psychologist, so he had to pick a lane.
God, no, we need that constant.
I don't know if I could say he chose wisely, but he chose.
We need that content so that we can get, so we can have, I think it ties into the,
the, the, the, not the OVA.
All the Brad stuff, the lecture.
No, no, no, this is the other fucking stretch goal we did.
Music.
The dojin, the dojin.
Oh, yeah, the dojin.
I, I think it might tie into the dojin.
Maybe?
That's maybe, I mean, it certainly could.
Maybe.
Okay, whatever.
Whatever, I don't know.
Still all very ambiguous.
We must have the dramatic conclusion.
Yep, yep, we need to know.
Did they get to radcon four?
Did radcon four happen?
We'll just never know.
I don't even know.
I don't know.
Feels like it never happened.
All right.
You've been shamed, Iggy.
Next one is, oh, okay.
This is Final Fantasy VII Spells Such As.
All right, sounds good.
Let's go.
This is a PCP PSA.
I have an announcement for you all.
I think, in my opinion, now is the time to get into BGE's Nuzla.
Hmm, yes.
He is hitting a point now where he is going to be grinding for a while
for the final gym in HeartGold.
I recommend catching up on all the episodes
uploaded to his livestream channel and trust me, his rival,
that they are all very action-packed.
VMG, sign it out.
You know, I forgot about this, but it's true.
Final Fantasy VII originally just called him like Fire 1, 2, and 3.
I could really forgot.
Really?
And this reminded me.
Yeah, yeah.
Wasn't it like a Fire Raga and Fire Rurara?
Wasn't that already in other Final Fantasy games?
Well, it was in.
I know it was in eight onward.
I thought it was in seven.
You know, going back, in Final Fantasy, the only Final Fantasy games that came to the west
were Final Fantasy I, I, IV, and VI, and I'm pretty, you know what?
I really don't know historically if when Final Fantasy VII came out,
they had adopted the like, like for the Fire, it's Fire, Fira, and Fire Raga are like the
three main ones.
I don't believe this.
I think this is false.
Dude, I checked it.
I checked it out.
FF7 had the one.
I did not remember that it was the numbers, but yeah, they do it.
No.
I'm about to replay it.
You're lying to me.
I shall confirm.
Oh, I'm going to play the PC one.
I wonder if it maintains.
Well, geez, I fucking googled Final Fantasy VII Materia, and why don't I have the answer yet?
Because of the remake, Ben, that's why.
Because the remake's clouding our cultural consciousness with this deluded,
next voicemail, next voicemail.
All right.
Okay.
Fair point.
Oh, okay.
We've got 15-year-old Sam and any, any success there, Ben?
Here, I'll look at.
No, I found, I found something that said Fire, Fira, Fira Raga, but no, but no,
it's about the remake.
It's about the fucking remake.
I don't want to know about the remake.
Die.
I'll find it.
All right, Sam, take it away.
Go.
Hey, PCP, long-time listener, first-time caller.
I'm an A-head.
That's besides the point.
So now it's May 9th, and I started the One Punch Man Regiment May 1st.
But by this time, I've doubled what I've usually been doing.
And so what I want to say is progress is the best feeling a human can feel.
It's not the results.
It's the knowing that you are getting better.
Thoughts and opinions?
Wait, what?
He just said that progress is the best feeling.
It's about the journey, not the destination.
That's the meme.
What's about the journey?
Is this about just life advice?
He was doing the One Punch Man Fitness routine for the last week or two,
and we were saying it feels great.
Yeah, if you imagine yourself as you are now, like, yeah, I feel all right.
But imagine if you were way worse off, you know?
Then it would be like, gosh, getting closer to this would be like,
like, you don't feel constant elation that you are currently the way you are.
It is always the feeling of getting better that gets you going.
Right.
It's about achieving that purpose.
It's why purpose is better than happiness.
Well, I mean, I certainly agree.
But I think that happiness is a state of mind that is achieved sporadically
through having lots of positive things in your life,
one of them being purpose, and another one being, I don't know,
whatever, health and things like that.
I don't know.
By the way, Ben, I did pull up.
I just went to the wiki real quick.
I found it on Cades of Gnarsh.
Yeah, OK.
So you see.
I found it on Cades of Gnarsh.
Yeah, it's true.
They are numbered.
They are like Cure 1, Cure 2, Cure 3, Ice 2, Ice 3.
There is, on the heel materia, there are spells which are called Poisona and Isuna,
but those are like Poisona.
That's like a specific cure version.
That's the spell to cure poison.
So it's not, yeah, no.
Right.
Weird.
Well, there it is, ladies and gentlemen.
Anyway, by the way, let's not forget, this guy was 15-year-old Sam.
Ooh, Sam, starting working out at 15 prime, primo time to start lifting.
You're about to, I mean, you're about to fucking have a growth spurt if you haven't already.
It's the best time.
It's perfect.
Right at the beginning of high school or whatever.
You're going to be swole as hell.
And by the way, it is a real thing, noob gains.
Right when you start working out, the going from no exercise to some exercise is by far
the biggest single jump in your fitness growth or whatever.
So he just said he doubled his push-ups.
What's the 80-20 rule?
You get 80% of the results out of 20% of the effort.
We absolutely applies to fitness, no doubt about it.
So yeah, and then make it a habit, keep doing it, dog.
All right, we've got one final voicemail in a similar vein.
This one is, my fitness pal is the most flaccid app on the earth.
All right, go.
Nate, you bitch, mother, cock, suck, fucker, poof.
Listen, you go around recommending my shitness pal.
Listen up, bitch.
Does my fitness pal track micronutrients?
Oh, it tracks vitamin A.
It tracks iron.
Are you going to get your potassium requirements for the day from it?
Like, listen, listen, listen, listen.
When you use chronometer or whatever else app you want to use to track your vitamins,
you actually start to min-max your diet.
You actually start to eat healthy.
You actually start to eat spinach.
Rather than it being like, spinach is this sort of gross food
and I don't really know how much of it to eat, but it's healthy.
So I feel like I should eat one.
You're like, no bitch, I need exactly 25 grams of spinach.
So I can fulfill my vitamin A and vitamin K for the day.
And you can go fuck off and die.
And you don't even need to use these apps very much.
It just gives you an understanding of like, oh my god, broccoli is so high in folate.
This will help me min-max my stats and become a god so easily.
Like, you don't even need to use it for long to get an intuitive understanding
of which vegetables are useful and why you should eat them.
Stop using my fitness pal and go fuck yourself.
Also, love the show.
All right, so that was pretty good.
Sounds like good advice.
What do you say, chronometer?
I think that's what he said, yeah.
I think my roommate uses chronometer.
You know, I hadn't heard of it until I heard that.
He showed it to me and I was like, it looks like that looks complicated.
All you need to know is my fucking macronutrients.
The protein, fiber, carbs, the...
All you need to know is the more green stuff you eat, the bigger you become.
Okay, well first of all, first of all, my fitness battle does track your nutrient.
It does track your micronutrients, not just your macronutrients.
I don't know, maybe not a ton of them.
But I mean, potassium, one of the things he raised, it is tracked.
It is in there.
You just have to go to your nutrition tab in your calorie counting thing.
So it is there and I have used it in the past before, but it is true.
I definitely am an if-it-fits-your-macro shitter and I always was.
But for the record, I was that at like my fitness peak.
So I'll just, I think that Ben's 80-20 thing is true.
Maybe chronometer is just better and I should switch to it.
Maybe this one's a baby version.
That's fair.
But you can obtain incredible results by just counting your macronutrients and not
worrying too much about your micronutrients.
Because if you get your macros right, you will be eating good amounts of vegetable and,
I don't know, stuff.
I mean, sure, it's possible that you won't, but you should.
And that should be part of what you do.
It's kind of inevitable.
So my thinking is that if you're getting your macronutrients right,
that already commits you to a pretty significant commitment to just getting
shit right overall in your diet.
You probably will be getting your micronutrients pretty good as well.
So you don't have to really worry about it that much.
But his point is also valid.
So I don't know.
Try chronometer.
See what works better for you.
Just as long as you're putting some energy into it,
you're probably getting a ton of benefit.
As we said, newbie gains are the biggest single jump.
So just be doing it at all and you're in pretty good shape.
Next one.
That's it.
We're done.
That was our last voicemail for all time.
Now that they're over, I miss them.
I feel the same way.
Thank you, everybody, for leaving them.
You can leave more at the speak pipe link in the description.
Keep coming.
It was good batch.
Good batch this month.
Oh, you know what?
We actually had one from Psy, where the gist was that the voicemails are bad
and he hates them because they don't have continuity.
And I didn't want to play little things.
It was a bit long.
Psy of YouTube or Psy of Relief.
Oh, Psy of YouTube.
Yeah, that guy.
Really?
The water park enthusiast.
Yeah, he left a voicemail.
And we didn't play it?
It was kind of long.
And it was just was.
And I mean, he was saying that the voicemails are bad because the dick show does voicemails
and there's a topic of discussion and there's continuity.
Whereas with us, it's all random.
So there's nothing for them to specifically talk about.
And while I agree that could make it better and it might be good to be here.
That's stupid.
That sucks.
That's just not the standard we're looking for.
This show had topics for years and everyone did nothing but fucking complain about it.
Well, to be fair, we never, I mean, we never like would tell people next week is a voicemail
calling with like a relevant voicemail or whatever.
Maybe that, I don't know, maybe that.
Did voicemail and topics even overlap?
Okay, guys.
What's next week episode going to be about?
Hey, that actually reminds me.
We don't know what it's going to be about, but you know who will be there?
FitMC is going to be here next time.
And he's going to, yeah.
Why?
FitMC, we just talked to him and, I mean, me and Gabe were talking.
We were like, we should get a guest.
And then we said, let's get Fit.
So he's going to stop by.
Okay.
I guess so.
Yeah, why not?
He's a good man.
We've been saying we should have more guests.
We say all the time.
If you got a voicemail for FitMC, you should send that in.
We should have FitMC.
The same thing you want him to respond to.
That's, you see, I'm glad we brought this up.
That's a good idea.
We should have FitMC on the Minecraft thing when we do the fucking battle.
Yeah.
Oh, is he going to be there?
He should.
He should be a guest commentator.
Yeah.
I don't know if he cares about Pokemon at all.
Probably not.
But it'd be funny just having that regardless.
I'll ask him if he wants to.
I mean, he, you know, it is, it is sweet.
He was like, dude, I'm like, he was like stoked.
Like now that he's had like a million subs,
there's that thing that happens where he'd be like,
Oh, do I want to like waste his time?
But like, we have such like a little baby thing here.
Do I want to bore him with an offer?
But that probably, you know,
they probably still like to get invited to things.
What about, you know, who is that fucking guy?
You're going to know him.
The guy who on Twitter said that he would be on any podcast
that has over like 5,000 viewers.
Oh, McAfee, McAfee.
McAfee.
We should get fucking McAfee the week after that.
We probably should.
I mean, literally why not?
He'll do it.
You know, you say that and I understand the impulse,
but like why?
What are we going to talk to fucking McAfee about?
Probably should spend a little time thinking.
Like, okay, we could reach out to him.
What will we discuss?
Did you make the subject matter?
The thing.
The virus?
Computer?
Thing.
Thank you for protecting my computer.
Hey, thanks for fucking up my computer.
Your software fucking sucks, asshole.
I have a virus.
Why did you do that?
Why did you do that, mister?
Did you really kill that guy in that woods or whatever,
in Bangladesh or Bolivia or whatever it was?
So I guess what I'm saying is I don't care about talking to McAfee,
but if anyone else does, whatever.
It sounds fun, but like we should think of what we would discuss with him.
At least a little bit, I think, probably.
I feel like did you?
No, I think it'd be funny if it was like terrible and cringe.
Yeah, we get him on and we're like, okay,
so thanks for agreeing to be on the podcast.
Who are you again?
Oh, that's, see, you know, so like with Fit.
That would be way funnier.
I like, I haven't really been following every detail,
like what Fit's been up to recently,
but I know he's been doing like a bunch of,
like these more like big community Minecraft things.
I don't want to just say,
hey, I haven't looked into this at all.
I don't know what you're up to.
Like, can you just like say it, please?
Can you just like explain to me?
Tell us what is, why you're here and who you are.
We could start it with the classic justify your existence
and just let them take it from there.
Yeah, okay, so call in for Fit.
Hey, Nate, we gotta fucking get out of here,
so we can call our freaking mom on Mother's Day.
That's a half an hour, you're absolutely right,
you're absolutely right.
I just got a call from them on my phone and I didn't answer it.
Bro, epic, suck a fuck, mom and dad.
Yeah, all right, well, let's go do that.
I gotta go fucking install Zoom and shit.
Luckily, we're at the end of the episode anyway,
so support us and show us your love at patreon.com
slash the procrastinators.
There are 27 bonus episodes that you can get access to
for a measly $5 reduce, so go do that
and have fun listening to them and support the show.
And if you only want to do $1, hey, Patreon Discord,
there's that, or give us more, always an option.
Happy to take that money and put it to good use.
You can, of course, play Minecraft with us.
As we said before, it'll be free for like five or six days
when you listen to this.
I'm sure in the show notes we'll have links
to appropriate guides on how to play
because you have to put some fucking files
in the right place, another right version, blah, blah, blah.
We'll help you out with that.
And the tournament will be on the 20th,
which is five days from now, or six days,
or four days, whatever it is.
So won't that be fun?
Come join us in the Minecraft server
and hang out with us while the tournament's going on.
And it'll also be streamed here.
And your friends can look on the screen and say,
whoa, it's your fucking avatar.
That's so cool that he's in Minecraft on YouTube.
And you'll feel very special about that.
And what else we got?
That's it.
Speakpipe, more voicemails, et cetera, et cetera.
Twitter, at TPCrastinators.
We'll be doing more announcements and all kind of stuff there.
More rad content is being worked on.
Take a while.
We're kind of with some junctures,
so we got to work on it for a while,
but you'll see it before too long.
So just hang in there, lads.
And that's it.
So thanks for being here this week, everybody.
We'll be back next week with another one of these
fit emcee hanging out with us.
And maybe more guests to come in the future.
We'll see you.
See you.
Past.
Bye.
Fuck.
Sayonara.