Well boys, you're rich, you love, you're in love. Top it off, you got your own monkey.
Work of two guys from Jersey, possibly one. Well to have these fucks stop talking shit
about us on the internet for starters. What have I been telling you? There's not much
you can do to stop that. Well short of showing up at all their houses beating the shit out
of them I guess. You know with all the money we're making man we could buy a lot of plane
tickets.
Commenters please kill yourselves and free me from this living hell. If your comment is
mean and snythen you can just fuck off and die. Why do you feel entitled to spewing your
bullshit attitude? You're rude and crude and I hate you so kill yourselves please and
be cool. I pronounce the word wrong I don't care. I didn't represent you, yeah no shit
I am myself motherfucker. Think I got a bad attitude while you ain't seen shit. A shadow
band you're ass to deal with it. Hello everybody and welcome to yet another episode of the Pro
Crastinators podcast. I'm hosting today, I'm Digi Bro and we're doing a little sequel
to a topic we've done before. We did reviewer rules, now we're doing commenter rules and
I'm joined by my panel of co-hosts, starting left to right. We got Jesse Wood. Happy Easter
I'm gonna shit on everyone. Endless, endless Jess, not as Jesse Wood. Oh I'm gonna get
into that. Yeah that's gonna be important. Best guy ever? Hey sexy lady. The DeVoo?
www.hi.com. Hippocrit. Yep. And Tommy Oliver. I'm mad at comments. Yes, yeah. The recent
example of a toxic comment section. Toxic. This is a very appropriate time for us to
do this podcast. This is something that has been brewing within me for a long time. Let
me tell you guys, I've been like a caged animal waiting for this topic to come up. I have
so much to fucking say. The people have asked for it too. The commenters want to know how
to conduct themselves. They're just ignorant and they need education. If only it was that
cut and dry. Yeah when we did reviewer rules we sort of hinted at doing commenter rules
and I've had this video idea planned for a long time. I was gonna do like a top 10 video,
top 10 things to make me hate you in my comment section. I've been planning that forever. I
feel like you should still do that. Definitely. Yeah but I have multiple comment videos written
that I'm just sitting on waiting to unleash upon the world. I mean if you put the money
just gonna get the comments. Hopefully this opens the fucking. This just goes to show how
passionate we are about this topic. It had to be done on this podcast for a few reasons.
One cause Jesse always has problems with this commenters. He's been on like a fucking
crusade. I've developed a system. It's a three step system where if you even fucking piss
me off one time. Like I've been doing this for like six years. I've fucking had it.
So from now on, if you even slightly piss me off, the first thing I do is right away
you're banned. You can never fucking comment again. I don't give a shit what your excuse is. If you
say you were ignorant of the rules or if you didn't mean to offend me, fuck you, you're gone. And the
best part is it's a shadow ban. So you don't even fucking know your ban. You're just writing your
comments out and they go into a void. It's a Chinese ban. Yeah so step one is your ban. Step
two, I screencap your comment and I ridicule you publicly on Twitter so that everyone knows what a
piece of shit you are for all time. And the third step. It helps filter out more comments because
a lot of Twitter people will then be like, I think that guy has a decent point so that you can
ban him. Exactly. That's my plan. It'll help foster a better comment section in the future.
It's very clear right now. People who are going to say that you're violating your freedom of
speech, I have it right here. The first amendment. This is what it says. The first amendment is
don't piss me off. I'll fucking kill you. Don't say anything on my fucking shit. Don't say anything
on the internet. You wouldn't say it on my face. Jesse, what's step three? What's step three?
Is that since I have a screencap of your comment, it goes, it gets filed away in a
manila folder for future use in a fucking video where I will even more publicly fucking shame you
and make you, hopefully you'll be watching and make you kill yourself. That's my ultimate goal,
is to make my commenters. It kills themselves in shame. It's funny because we're kind of
slipped down the middle on our handling of comments. I don't respect their right to live as a human
being on this world. They are holding all of humanity back with their bullshit insipid comments
and their refusal to understand anything. They're getting ahead of ourselves. It's funny. I want to
murder them with a shotgun. I have murderous fantasies. I want to find them. I want to get on
a plane and go to all. It fucking bothers me. It keeps me up at night. It makes my skin crawl to
think that I can't fight my commenters. I want to get on a plane like Jay and Son of Bob strike back
and fly all over America and find them and one by one kick the crap out of their pubis fucking heads.
That should be the intro to this video. Actually, yeah, it should be because that scene is amazing.
It really is. I think that's probably the most, I think for an internet content creator, if you
haven't seen this, you can just watch Jesse did a video where he set that scene to the Kill La Kill
song. You can just go watch that. It's one of the most satisfying things I've ever seen. It is one
of my favorite scenes in any movie. It's literally Jay and Silent Bob get rich and with all the money
they have, they realize that they can fly around the U.S. and beat the shit out of people who leave
negative comments on their online content. I've gone through a period where I've had a big video
that gets lots of bad comments. What I was just thinking of is I can just mail them all a ticket
to this exotic trip on a bus and then drive the bus into a careen and kill all of them in one fell
swoop. That seems a lot easier to get away with because they'll just be seen as a coincidence.
The only problem is they're not all going to fit on one bus. There's just too many.
You know what? Maybe we're right to intro this way just so people can understand the level
of passion. Because we all have different ways of dealing with comments, but our hatred for bad
comments is universal and seething. That's true. I think we'll all agree on this one. I hate this.
I know that at least Digi agrees. I hate this stigma of against turning off the comment section.
The only reason I don't turn mine off is because there's a stigma against it.
I don't believe that comments should even be allowed anywhere at all. They shouldn't exist.
Well, Jesse, you keep getting ahead of me here, man. We're already six minutes in
and I haven't even properly introduced this topic. I told you when we were starting this
that I have a lot to say about this topic. I know we're going to get to that. We're going to get
to it. Just let me properly lead us in first. Okay, go for it. Because the part of the reason
for this is not just that Jesse has this ongoing crusade. It just so happens that
me and Tom have both recently have really bad comment sections. I made this video about a race
that got over 3,000 comments in 24 hours, which is way disproportional to the number of views
it has. It's like everyone who watched it fucking commented. I've had to ban more people based on
this video than I have based on any other video for the insipidness of the comments.
Even more than the sort of online? Well, with that one, I just turned off the whole comment
section. And I didn't really ban people back then as much as I do now. And then Tommy Oliver here
recently put out this pony video, which is funny because it was in response to comments he'd gotten
in the past. Tom, you want to explain this? What exactly this is? Yeah, I mean, for the past three
years, I made horse videos years ago. I don't even really do it anymore. To this day, I still get
comments like shitting on this one stupid idea that I had. And so they finally, after years of
persecution, the show basically up and says I was right. So I make this most like tongue in cheek
disgusting meme trash video just gloating because like I'm right and it felt great. So I put like
70 comments in the video that I'll just like try to shit on me over the course of like three years
and then just like blew it the fuck up. I've never so thoroughly seen one group of commenters get
absolutely ass blasted the fuck out like it was on that video. It was amazing. It was great. I
want you to go watch it. It was years in the making. But of course it just inspired like it's
because we took all this time. Me and Nate went back for them. We got to make sure this is airtight
and bulletproof and it doesn't matter. You know, stupidity knows no bounds. You can't expect them
to learn like people. They're not people. They're monkeys. They're animals. I mean, if you look,
if you have a conclusion and you're searching for evidence to find it like, okay, my point is
Tom's wrong. Got to find evidence. You'll always be able to find confirmation. Little minutia, huge
problem voted up. That's exactly what it is. Yeah. So, yeah, Jesse, to get back to it,
the point you were bringing up and I have like a 30 minute video about this on my Digibro After Dark
channel called On Closing Comments. We won't get into as much depth about it because you can just
go watch that video. But like, yeah, there is a huge weird stigma against closing comments that
makes no fucking sense. And the simplest way to explain why it doesn't make sense is that
no other art form has this. Yeah. When I go and see a movie in the theater,
they don't give you a pamphlet with a bunch of rotten tomatoes reviews inside of it when you go
see a movie. No. There's no, there's no other art form that has the comments, except for like,
like with a book, they will actually take good comments people have made about it and put it
in the book to hype up the book. That's the closest thing I could think of to this. But like,
people think that they're entitled to, like, and it's always censorship and freedom of speech is
what they always say. They always say, oh, it's censorship to delete comments. And it's like,
no, it's not because I am giving you this platform. I don't have to. There is no, like,
when people say it's censorship, it's like censorship would be if I told you that,
like, if I shut down your blog that was talking about my video. What is it? I'm kind of on the
other side of this argument because I see a comment section as a place where there is an
opportunity for discussion. And yes, some comment sections are completely cancer.
Yeah, but you, you allow that. Because that's right. I do.
YouTube has a button that you can press that says allow comments on this video or don't allow
comments on this video. If I want discussion on my video, I leave the, like 100% of the reason
there's comments on my videos is that I like reading comments because I have fostered a
comment section that actually has good discussions. Sometimes, sometimes it's shit, which is why,
like, the other day I made a video about positive videos I had done. It was like,
videos about anime I actually like. And the whole video is just me listing all the positive videos
I've done. And at the start of it, I made the horrible mistake of saying comments about my beard
will be deleted. Because every time I show my face on camera, I get a thousand comments about my
beard. And it's super annoying because there's nothing to do with the video. And I don't want
to hear about my fucking beard. So I said that and of course I got like an insane number of
comments about the beard and I was deleting them all. And then I realized that the other
comments weren't interesting because there was nothing to discuss in this video. It was just
a list of other videos. So I just disabled comments on the whole video and that made perfect sense
because there's no room for discussion. There's nothing to talk about on it. So like,
the comments section to me is really just your way of saying, hey, I want you guys to talk about
my video and I want to read it. In a perfect world, it would be a place for discussion,
but that's just not the reality of how it is because people are violent mutants and it's just
sewage. It's graffiti is what it is. It's not graffiti because in no way does it actually
impact the material itself. Because if somebody leaves a comment that completely misunderstands
my intent and they leave that fucking comment on there, other people see it and it affects how
people view my art. Okay, let's make a distinction between closing comments and deleting bad comments
that are purely tacky. It's just a fucking blight on my work, on my blood sweat and tear. I honestly
thank you guys for a little bit too sensitive about the criticisms you get. This is not just
about criticisms. How many times have you seen a comment that spoiled what was going to happen
in the video, that repeated the jokes from the video and therefore if you read, because a lot
of people, because of the fact that the comments are right there, a lot of people do end up scrolling
down and looking at the first few comments while they're watching the video and those first few
comments will almost always be some kind of spoiler, some kind of repeat of the joke that was in the
video. Are spoilers, are those really relevant though? Do those really cost you anything in the
video? I don't know if they do. How many videos are like ruined by spoilers on YouTube? There
could be a lot because if you ruin the punchline of a joke video, then the punchline is the same.
You don't know the meaning of the punchline, so there's nothing to spoil until you already get
to that point. You would be shocked by how often there are spoilers in the comments of YouTube
videos. The comments down there are part of the viewing experience. I could be watching someone's
video and like it, then I read a comment, it puts me in a bad mood, and so the commenters just spoiled
the good mood that the video put me in. Those dang commenters. Friends, then don't read the comments.
That's on YouTube. Just don't read the comments. It's very hard to not read comments there right
there. If the comments aren't supposed to be read, they should be elsewhere. This podcast is not
titled Let's Remove All Comments. It's called Comment to Rules because we want comments to be
good because that won't happen. And a part of that is the creator's ability to remove comments or
allow them. Given you were saying something, what are you saying? I was going to say I think a lot
of the people who comment like just incipid uninteresting stuff is because they use the
comment section like they would a Skype chat. Like they don't have anyone to talk to the video
about, so they feel like it's a community down there. That's true. They can look at it. I think
that's a valuable thing when I wouldn't really want to take it away from people. Well, Nate,
that's a thing though. It can be valuable and it can also be hurtful. It can actually make,
like okay, for something like- It could be. My Digi Bros show, right? My Digi Bros show,
the comment section is really good because it does feel like a community because it's a small
group of people watching it. It's the same people watching every video. So there's sort of a communication
between them and us. We read the comments and there's an ongoing conversation. And I like that
because it's an ongoing series of videos, because it's something that has a narrative to it and
that the commenters understand that narrative, and there really is nowhere else to talk about it,
nowhere else that makes sense to talk about it. But if you had, let's say PewDiePie, right?
There's a reason that he doesn't have comments enabled on his videos, partly because he gets
constant spam in there, but also because to foster that kind of community, he has his own
forum. There's a whole PewDiePie forum where people can actually discuss his videos who
all sort of know the context, who know all the things he's talking about, and aren't just random
people running in and yelling memes and being... Look, that's true. There's no place I've seen
that was more gross than the PewDiePie comment section, especially with spam. But I just wonder
if there's really any harm being done by filling the comment section with those when you just have
the ability to not look at it. You can just not scroll down because you're on a PewDiePie video
and you know that it's going to be... It's pretty good analogy for comment sections that I just thought
It's kind of like the YouTube video is like a party that's being thrown by the YouTuber
and all the people who come in like it's a free party and there's free food and stuff and they
come and they experience it and anything they say out loud within a shot of like the guy who's
hosting it is a comment and anything they say to their friends after they leave or anything is
like something they say amongst themselves or in their own Skype chats or somewhere else
where it doesn't hurt it's not annoying but if you if somebody just comes in and they you know
they try the punch and they don't like it and they say this party sucks really loud and there's
leave like that's a bad comment I hate that guy because you just first of all I don't feel like
it's a party I feel like like my videos are are are for me and my friends and to a much
lesser extent but still they're you know my patrons and that's it everyone else is an
uninvited guest in my house so you better fucking behave yourselves and if you don't
you're dead I will stick my dogs on you I don't begrudge anyone for closing their comments if they
want to you absolutely have the right to do that I'm just simply stating why I'm not interested
in doing that personally or I mean maybe I'll get a video uh that has a completely toxic comment
section you already have one what about your Final Fantasy 7 video those but that's the thing
that is that is definitely a toxic place where people don't fucking understand anything I mean
the half the people who watch it voted down they don't understand my points and it's it's simply
them you know being ignorant of the facts but even then even then I like to think that it is
it's something that could be witnessed by people who do get it they could be like wow
there's something to be learned from this kind of comment section you know right so first of all
everyone listening I'm not bad at interrupting I just rolled a bunch of bad
rolls a bunch of times in a row that's why I was so bad interrupting for seven minutes there
I'm a good interrupter second of all all right uh commenter rule number one wait let me interrupt
you real quick DeVoo uh I've got to say that I'm probably the best interrupter wait actually
did you just both of you did you just compare interrupting to like rolling a dnd type because
that's funny I like that that's a really good analogy I actually I don't know how I have to cut
off I have to cut off everybody because DeVoo I don't want you to say what your number one rule is
it could be rule number two because I already had planned what rule number one was yeah let's
get into the specific things so rule number two make friends on Skype and bitch about YouTube videos
there because we do that constantly we constantly make comments because we make videos and we know
how annoying they can be to read so we say a lot of shit in prayer even if you're just a big fan of
videos then you probably have a whole lot of bitchy thoughts you want to think about and something
makes you mad that's perfectly understandable so just hunt down people who watch the same kind of
videos complain with them and then everything is going good that's the natural order of things
let me tell you about a feature that I didn't appreciate back when I had it but now I really
miss it which is there used to be this thing called a google reader and it was an rss feed reader
where you'd have like you know all the basically any blog you follow you would plug its feed into
your google reader it's kind of like subscribing to something on youtube it would be a list of all
the blogs that you're following right and you could share like you could take something from that feed
and share it with your friends on google and then you could have your own comment section for that
post so let's say I posted something on my blog and then my blog has its own comment section where
people are responding to me but then if someone shared the thing on google reader then they could
just talk about it with their friends and it would give us the opportunity to speak more critically
about the post without having to say stuff right to the guy's face that maybe would be annoying or
you know or or beat defeat the point or derail the conversation so I think that that is definitely
something that should be done I think there's too many people who respond to your video with
comments that aren't helpful for you or for other viewers of the video they're just the guy I don't
know I think this whole I think this whole wall of separation you want to put up between the
person who made it and the people who are commenting on it I'm not sure that's a good thing that's not
that is not what I'm describing okay I'm describing having two places to discuss the video all right
one that you could like could you imagine if all of us took the shit that we say about like the
average like brony reviewer and we said all that in their comments it would be a nightmare it would
fucking ruin their life you know they would hate it they would fucking delete their channel and kill
themselves if they had us doing that because we have this chat we can openly criticize and discuss
people ah so you're saying there's a time and a place for certain comments and yeah I'm saying
that those comments would not be appropriate on the right I think the point is that being on the
internet and having a comment section isn't an excuse to ignore human decency yes like you should
as a proud fortune or I disagree for the same reasons that you wouldn't like like okay you know
I have all my friends right my my offline friends because we all talk together all the time I don't
think any of us really just like splits off into one-on-one groups and talks shit about each other
at least I don't as far as you know as far as you know but uh but like you know in real life I
talk to myself about how much I hate you all yeah you've got all your friends and you you split off
with one of them and you might talk shit about all the other friends yeah but it's not it's not
because you don't like them you just want to vent your feelings about them right and if you brought
those things up to that person they might be hurt or offended and it might you know put a damper on
your relationship in a way that you didn't intend to because you're just venting feelings that that
inside you can deal with because you want to be friends with that guy but you know maybe you
got to complain about that friendship and human decency is based on it's having respect for someone
to shit on them privately and you know the reason why that's part of human decency the YouTube sphere
is a place where you put ideas and then people shit on them because that's just the way they feel
like doing it but that's the thing I don't think it I don't think it makes sense to be that way
like like I said like I said there's no there's never a time like if we all watched Batman v
Superman yeah and we all thought it was a huge piece of shit no one walks up to Zach Snyder on
the street and goes your movie's a fucking piece of shit I might make internet videos we posted we
posted on our blogs for our audiences for us to discuss with our friends we don't go up to the
fucking guy and tell him he's a piece of shit but I mean isn't that possibly worse that you're
like creating you're you're sharing this opinion with all these people I mean they they probably
haven't formed an opinion yet I mean if you're doing that aren't you convincing these people to
maybe be that guy and to you know engage in that I'm convincing them to feel the way I feel but
not to confront Zach Snyder himself obviously yeah not to go up to the guy and tell him he's a bad
person because he made a movie I kind of I don't know like doesn't he need to hear that like dude
your movie fucking sucked do a better job not necessarily because he's just doing what he I
don't know how we don't know movies do we have to get before they hear some real criticism about
how fucked up I mean sure if I mean from the perspective of like business yeah like if if
the people who are paying him are listening to the commenters because they care about making good
movies then it's up to them to tell him hey we don't like what you're doing and we we're not
going to let you have this budget but Zach Snyder himself we don't know what his intentions are
maybe he doesn't give a fuck about making good movies he's just doing what he feels like doing
and that's completely fine that's not fine that's not fine that we have to be subjected to shit
art and then he's not no one's allowed to criticize under his face I mean it's not really his like
okay who's giving him the power to make Batman v Superman look we have to blame someone for the
result of a bad okay well also who are we to say that it's shit art in the first place it's true
I thought that I thought that Batman v Superman was laughably hilariously a fucking train wreck
like on the level of the room and I thought for sure that this would be the unanimous opinion
that everyone would agree with me that it was a fucking train wreck of a movie and then I talked
to a fucking gargag on Facebook and and he's like that was the best movie ever anyone who complains
about it is a nitpicking faggot so then I have to step back and go oh well maybe I am a nitpicking
faggot I don't fucking know shit okay we can't get into a whole discussion about the subjectivity
of art because that's a whole different thing once you come to a conclusion about something
well I'm back in the digits point like I wouldn't go up to Zach Snyder and say fuck you your movie
sucks right I had I had a comment on on my reddit the other day because I have my own reddit board
and people will often post my videos on there and like you know have more private discussions about
them like with me because I'm more likely to read and respond to longer comments on there and one
guy left a long comment about my erased video basically saying that it wasn't that helpful for
for like essentially he was saying that it didn't represent a broad opinion or it didn't represent
like you know his like how most people felt about the show and stuff like that why does that
simply already worth this point it needs to yeah exactly right but that's that's that's kind of what
I what I said in response is I was like I mean I get I completely understood his complaints and I was
just like this video is really for me though it's not really about like it's not like this was not
supposed to be helpful for everybody it was supposed to help for a very certain as I'm listening to
this conversation I'm trying to imagine what a commenter person listening to this podcast is
thinking and I'm thinking that they're thinking yo I wasn't trying to be insulting I didn't call
them a faggot I didn't call them any names all I did was point out some mistakes that they made
in their video and then they flipped on me because they were wrong overreacting so here's here's my
parameters right here are my three conditions for I I think you guys would agree but here are my
conditions for like a criticism in any capacity that I would respect or like versus ones I don't
first parameter is do you know what you're talking about do you really put in the thinking did you
put in the thought did you did you apply critical thinking right to okay are you are you do you have
tacked are you acting like a normal person are you not being an asshole parameter number three
is your criticism effort did was there much effort into it was it a piece of art was your
criticism a work of its own or was it just two sentences of a complaint because that's kind of
annoying I don't think there's anything wrong with a simple complaint that gets to the point okay you
don't need to have all three conditions right but okay because I think people are gonna say that
we're being hypocritical because of the fact let me try to boil that down a little bit because I
think what you're getting to the heart of here is people who say that uh that you can't take criticism
right right I gotta say it's the longer I hold on to my thoughts the more nervous I get for some
reason if I take too long to say my things I freak out and I expect did anybody miss me fuck down
hey give yeah you know like a comment like that video sucks I think a lot of people are gonna say
you're guys being hypocritical because you guys make criticisms like I don't think right here's
here's my here's my response to that all right because people say people say like you know you
can't take criticism when you when you delete their critical comments and I have to get to
the heart of what I think right that's an over simplification and what I think we are doing
because like like me and Jesse said we don't post these to the guys who make the stuff we're talking
about yeah we just post these opinions online which is our reactions to the things that we see
that are entirely about us like there's a reason my channel is called otaku gonzo journalism because
it's about me it's about my perspective I don't send my sao videos to reki kawahara and tell
him he's doing a bad job and the reason that I don't is because to me constructive criticism
has to be from the perspective of understanding what the artist was trying to do because it's not
constructive if you don't know what I was going for like that erased guy who was saying that his
problem with the video was that I didn't you know appeal to a broader audience and he was saying this
is a problem with your video and I'm like but that wasn't my goal with the video my goal was to appeal
to this specific type of person and to myself the fact that everybody got to see the video is just
because that's the platform by which it will reach the people it has to reach I don't know I can't
like go out and find each individual who felt a certain way about a race and just but that's just
something that you accept by using this medium of YouTube you know it's but the fact that that guy's
comment isn't his it's not a point he's making somewhere else he's making it directly to me
and just to tell me hey you did it wrong now hang on I think it's like well I didn't I didn't intend
to do what you think I intended I think he's making it that comment to the other viewers of the video
you know because he posted it on my reddit oh okay so it's like straight like I'm the only one who I
think you know I I realized that I feel this way wrong criticism is worse to me than just insulting
me for no reason because when you fucking lobby some criticism at my art that is fundamentally
based on a misinterpretation or a misunderstanding of my intent and you throw that criticism out
there as though it's valid other people are going to see it and think that it's valid and they're
going to view my shit through that lens but but sometimes sometimes and it's gonna sound crazy
but sometimes they're right no they're fucking not no I know that because if it wasn't perfect I
wouldn't have fucking uploaded it I know what I'm fucking created and I know what my intent is and
they don't I'm endless Jess and you're not all of you are not all of you listening to this
fucking podcast please fucking kill yourselves I agree but I don't think that the creator should
be the end all be all sayer of what is correct what is wrong about the video I absolutely want people
to be able to judge that themselves well here's what if you have people misunderstanding your videos
is that a failing on the audience is that a failing on you people misunderstanding my video
fine but you know what pisses me off me calmly explaining what they misunderstood and ignoring
nice wording and then I either get no reply or they continue to double down on you know what I
would like I would like an oh okay I would like people to exercise just a little bit of humility
you know yeah well I would turn that right back maybe you're wrong about your point you know the
lack of humility when people are not just like wrong or like not just misinterpreting the video
or misinterpreting something you did but like stubbornly wrong like you respond to them they'll
say well this this is this video sucks and you suck because this reason this reason and then and
then you go well actually it yeah actually what I was trying to do was this and then they still stick
to it like no no no no no you're right because yeah because of what I guess and it's like I just told
you that wasn't my intent you little fucking slimy protozoa you don't deserve dude all right all right
I hear what you're saying let me read you something because okay I've got a there here's an example
of something right my on my on my first current login video I'm gonna contain this rain it has to
be let out I have to let it out on my first current login video right there's been this thread
going on for like since it came out which is like a fucking year now almost it's been like a year
and this one argument has been going on for like fucking the entire time brilliant just just the
other day I finally commented on it myself and was like guys this argument has been going back
and forth about how shit current login is or how not shit it is for like a fucking year it's time
to end it no one is budging let us end the conflict now and you know what happened they were both the
two people who were arguing were like you know what dude you're right let's just move on and I mean
now some other fucking idiots are commenting on or like they're like reviving the argument and these
guys are actually you couldn't just ban them both the first time it happened a year ago and you
wouldn't be dealing with it ever again but I'm see but these people grew you know these people
were able to learn that that's another that's another bannable offense actually now that you
bring it up people talking amongst themselves on my video that is very annoying when they do that
no you know I don't wanna get shit my video is about a place to fucking whiter outside and talk to
your buddies otherwise cancerous threats something finally good came of it these two people came to
understanding about each other and I think that's valuable you know you annoyed me for a while but
something I guess I mean to me I just think it's they realize they're sinking too much time into it
and they didn't learn anything they're gonna go right back to arguing with other people but see
they did it until I stepped in and told him what's up you know I think that was that kind of moment
that's something that I'm probably the only one has ever happened well then I'm a fucking grunt
that shows the value of comments I fucking broke new ground there you go 97 percent of the time
I don't want to guys shut up let's I'm over with my car god damn me too just we're gonna get so
many fucking comments about how we all talked over each other it's gonna be a oh that's another
way I'm glad you brought up that one because all you fucking maggots out there who listen to
podcasts and complain about people talking over each other have you ever fucking been in a situation
or spoken to other human beings have you ever been in a social fucking interaction situation
do you not understand of course you haven't because you're all fucking autists you don't
understand how friends fucking communicate with each other this is a podcast we're gonna
fucking talk over each other because we're friends having a conversation have you never
fucking had a Thanksgiving dinner with your family you stupid fucking swine also this is over
Skype and there's a delay so the talking over is significantly worse than it would be if you
all went there talking over each other I can't understand what's happening because you're
talking over each other why can't everyone just ring a little bell and wait their turns to say
what they might have said why can't everything be orderly what would you say I would kind of like
a little bell well tell him were you saying some more I mean I have a couple points I want to make
but I'll say one for when they're more appropriate the one that I want to kind of jump off of from
what you were talking about with your comment section is something that really kind of pisses me off
and yeah again I agree with everything's digi saying like I think everything he says is valid
like I think there's definitely like an etiquette you should probably be following but I also agree
with you because I've never banned any one of my comments I very rarely delete comments because
I just think like it's an open platform whatever like I can think you're wrong but I'm not going
to stop you but what I was going to say something that really pisses me off in my comment section
and just comment sections in general is when people use the YouTube comment section as their
YouTube channel like if you're going to make a huge long-winded big fucking counterargument
like that's the reason video responses exist you know every time like I thought those disappeared
well I mean oh you mean just make a video yeah which is real it still pisses me off that they
got rid of those me too but like how many times have you seen other other people like put the
script of a video in the comments yeah and it's just like yeah you're just trying to hijack this
like yeah I really wish they could make another video that's much easier to ignore make your own
channel and do it it's funny you should say that because I did I dumped basically an entire script
about one of uh Jeff's NHK videos and it was probably like one of the longest things I've
you're the problem just don't clearly I guess yeah and I I I brought this up in my video on
closing comments and and Nate I think that's excusable because you and Jeff are friends so
like right right so you can like it it's always different we've been having this argument for
like a week anyway so right and there's there's differences when you have context for it like
Jeff also left a huge comment on my erased video but I completely saw that coming because me and
Jeff have been debating erased for a long time right and it was relevant that poor misguided
our audiences that they've listened to us argue about erased so him leaving a comment on the
video is kind of continuing the narrative in a way that I actually appreciate but like I think that
with with what Tom was saying um like I raised this point in my closing comments video that
you all have platforms I have a youtube channel you can make a youtube channel I have a blog
you can make which is why the whole free speech argument is completely invalid and does not
exactly and and that's and people will say because I've had this argument before where
someone was like well are you saying that like because you're already a big youtuber so if you
say something then everybody's gonna hear it but if I want to respond to it then that means I have
to go make a whole youtube channel and I'm like yeah exactly the reason I get the reason I get to
have this platform is because I write in a way that other people understand and appreciate I have
opinions that people relate to these farmers who just go out one day and harvest like a million
acres of food what like did they earn that shit they didn't do shit they just woke up one day and
they did that it's not like they spent a fucking six months right that field sewing the field growing
the you know like here's the kind of bad here's the comments can be really bitchy comments and
criticize me I see their fucking putrid comments and it's just it's like I'm looking into a sea of
people and they've all got their fucking jaws hanging open because they want to dig in their
mouths here's really the thing that always gets to me is the fact that these comments don't have a
whole lot of effort they didn't put on put in a whole lot of critical thought because you know
comments are literature they're a very low form of literature but that's what they are literature
is art they're shit I expect you to put in I I expect you to put in some effort some creative
effort I'm glad you like that and here's the thing no matter how no matter how bitchy a comment is
or how uh how much it criticizes me how much I disagree with it how much you could even personally
insult me personal attacks are far less insulting to me than people trying to postulate that my video
is something different than this comment can be anything but if I think it's funny and cleverly
worded I'll let it pass and maybe even thumb it up yeah I will earn my respect oh no I don't have
to be off more than commenters thinking they're funny the vast majority of them sometimes they are
funny oh you shouldn't do this oh you shouldn't do that and they're just not clever it's just it's
just a big waste of my time and that's the thing that you know I want to leave it there's
there's one important point that I want to bring up in regards to that and it's just that I've made
I've made pretty much I've been defending the the usefulness of comments but there is a reality on
the other side of that argument that is there may in fact come a time uh uh uh solid a snake from
Metal Gear Solid 2 he knew what was up one day it is possible that the like any intelligent argument
will be just completely drowned out by the walls of idiocy and just piled on everyone is wrong
about everything and they drown out any kind of responsibility to ban people who say stupid
shit I think that may in fact come a time when that's that's the case and already it's not worth the
time probably like practically I have videos that have gotten like twice the number of comments
that your uh your girl like on no no your final fantasy video has and it's like you know it was
at that level at that point where it just gets too much for me and you know by the way the reason
why I'm so ethically okay with banning is because it saves them time too they're not banned from other
videos well I don't know that's not true because it doesn't save them time they're suffering and I'm
not that's what I like about it I don't think you need to just say this now you could ban every
single person who comments at all if you wanted that'd be totally I have no problem with that because
it's my dream my dream is to wake up one morning and look into my empty comment section and
see that I've banned everyone yeah one day you'll get that I consider it important because and I've
been writing about this for for years even before I was nearly as big as I am yeah that the the way
to get a good comment section is by curating it because people will put more effort into your
comments if a they know you read them yeah you sometimes respond to them and see they see that
the other comments are good I'm just I'm just a lez a fair idealist I guess I just think that if I
don't do anything and hope maybe maybe there's a chance more good things will come as a result
it's just you know it's just my philosophy I mean like if you look at PBS idea channels comments
like I don't I don't know if they delete or do anything like that but because everyone knows
that they have a whole comment response thing that they've always done people leave by far the
best comments on YouTube on PBS idea channel every comment will be some long like thought out
really intricate response to the video because everyone wants to get read on the next episode
comments thing it's a cool strategy you know even I've written some like some really detailed
comments on there and I've been read in a video and yeah you were just mentioned on a video of
theirs well that was for yeah for something else but yeah I you know I have tried to foster that
in my comment section the whole time it's been around I respond to like the most interesting
or intelligent comments or anything I have something to say in in response to I actually like
seeing conversations on my videos when they aren't arguments when people get into long
arguments that's when it's like all right just shut down the whole fucking thread but like
when people just discuss things that that can be really cool because it means that like
I've I've created you know dialogue between people and I like that that's why that's why I
don't just close comments on all my videos because again I like the comments but to me if I want to
keep my comments being good then I have to ban the people who are just spamming bullshit I have to
delete the comments that are that are just fucking stupid because if people scroll down to your
comment section and all they see is a bunch of dumb bullshit then you get stuff like with my
erased video where every fifth comment is someone talking about how shitty the comments are it's
like I can't believe how butthurt everyone is over erased oh half the people are saying it's
shit and the other half are defending it like it's amazing blah blah and like all these comments
about the comments and I'm like did you did you said you said pen ultimate when you actually meant
ultimate uh let me just leave a quick comment about that we haven't even we're 40 minutes into
this and we haven't even actually started laying down any specific things that we don't like we
should just spend venom well I'm going to go ahead I'm going to go ahead and say what my first rule
is because I wanted I wanted to say this at the very beginning of the podcast because people will
have already broken it yeah the first rule of good comments this is absolute never break this
do not publish a comment before you finish the fucking video that's a good one that's a good one
YouTube should make that feature a button you can press that'd be yeah that'd be good actually
here's here's how you do it guys if you have something to say about something that was said
at the very beginning of a video type it out and then don't hit publish yeah wait until the video's
over because there's a good chance that it's going to be addressed like for instance on my uh on
my video about anime getting lazy with its meta there was a lot of people who would comment things
like did you mix up Ava and Gundam on purpose and then they would come back like they would leave a
second comment like oh now I get it because the whole video was full I like what you're doing
is you're not only laying out a rule you're expressing how to do it correctly you're applying
that see pcb is teaching you people all you have to do is type and I do this all the time I'll watch
it like uh like on I think that was one of DeVu's videos where like I had responses to like six
different points did this happen DeVu did I have a video where I had like six different little
micro paragraphs because what I'll do is I'll respond to like I'll type out whatever my thought
is on what's actually no better example the tbap q&a oh yeah yeah I did this on the tbap q&a
they would answer a question I would type out like something if I had to say it in response and then I
just uh go down to the next line in the comment and I'd wait and then once the video was over I had
like six different points and I published it and they were all there nothing is worse than the guys
who who actually leave a comment after every single thing they have to respond to yeah I get some of
those on digi bros where there's this one kid who will like respond to like like eight times to
phrases that we said throughout the video and I'm like dude just type it all out in one comment
you can even edit you can edit comments yeah but like for fuck's sake wait till the video's over
we we might have addressed what your complaint was and if we haven't then you can fucking
leave a comment which can I can I move on to realize is that every time they every single time they
leave a pointless comment I get a notification for it and I have to go through that emotional
rollercoaster of saying maybe it'll be a decent comment maybe and I have to click on it and then
it comes up and it's like my fucking dog died all over again every single time that I say nothing
my advice is to turn off your notifications device yeah I've had the notifications disabled for like
but then how will I know who to ban because I go I read all my comments through the comments page in
my creator studio because that way I can read the whole comment I'm not interested in solutions I'm
interested in my commenters killing themselves and dying you know uh related to that uh do speaking
of of accountability uh another rule I don't know we're on two two or three or whatever here's an
important rule three always every commenter number three every commenter must enable replies this is
non-negotiable you must allow this issue lately have you guys even been seeing this I have I have
actually I haven't seen this in a while there's nothing more disgustingly cowardly than putting
well here's the thing Nate I don't think any of them know they're doing that yeah this is some stupid
google thing the problem is that with with the with the responses thing it's that if you have
something like you can mark in your youtube options like uh I can only be responded to if I'm in your
contacts and people will have that checked without realizing that it means no one can respond to their
comments I kind of disagree with that one because really I I really hate people responding to my
comments I hate getting replies to my comments and I've often considered turning off replies
on my comments I think what the real issue is and a little bitch and a little bitch I'm more like
a fucking hero Nate I'm a fucking hero in a badass because I don't have time to put up with it you
know what I don't want to hear their stupid bullshit because they're fucking wrong my problem is dumb
and gay and dumb and gay and dumb you can't handle the heat get out of the kitchen there in my
fucking kitchen when they're shitting all over men replying to my shit I'll fucking take a fucking
spatula I'll shove it up their nose I'll go up their nose with a rubber hose and I'll spray their
fucking oh so you might hate them replying you mean like you can reply to them but they can't
reply to you but this is like replies in your comment section well I'm saying I'm saying I think
people the problem is not just only not having replies enabled the problem is particularly
when they ask you a question and then don't have yes okay that's what I was trying to do
it's when they when they ask the problem is that they don't seem to realize that they have
got that's a valuable offense right there I don't want that shit my shit with this I almost feel
I sometimes feel sorry for them because I can tell they don't know right and I have no way to
tell them because I can't respond like there's this dude if you listen to this dude I'll bring
this up on digi bros sometimes once I actually remember there's this dude named reddler red who
responds to a lot of digi bros episodes with like fairly well thought out comments
but he has replies disabled and he'll like ask questions or how long he's been doing this
for months guys and he thinks you don't love him digi he's gonna he's gonna actually commit
suicide he's never like asked about it he's never like responded like hey how come you
don't reply to my comments or something but it's like there's no way and I get a lot of those people
who like ask like questions sometimes questions that I really want to answer but I can't do anything
about it it's just like you're fucked I can't do anything you don't have replies enabled I have no
way to contact you to inform you of this information you know so like yeah please enable your fucking
responses if you didn't know that was a thing now you know make sure you have it enabled if no one's
ever responded to your comments and you're not sure why this is probably why um but yeah wouldn't
that be funny that there's like some really unlikable person who's like oh that must be why
they go when they see it's not true and that's the moment where they break and actually kill
themselves holy shit that's great I really hope we can see that in the news oh god there'll be a
picture of all of us this yeah you know and they thought they just had disabled their comments
but really nobody likes them oh no all right let's move on I got one I got I got a problem
okay here it unsolicited advice and this this this is a big one it happened on my
fuck updates video which the worst thing ever happened it went viral which means I got a
bunch of fucking normies commenting on it with their that's worse than that and it also happened
on a recent video that I made called just rambling we're like also this this is this goes hand in
hand with watching the whole video before you comment because a lot of my videos they tend to
not be what they appear to be and you don't see that until later so I got a lot of people commenting
without finishing it and giving me unsolicited advice because the first half of the video
is that I'm going on this really retarded rambly like wrong like I'm I'm totally wrong in a lot
of places in the rant I say stupid shit I'm like empirically wrong I get facts wrong I completely
missed the obvious solutions right in front of me and I admit that but that's the point I wouldn't
upload it if I wasn't aware of it so like the whole point of the that first part where I'm going
on this long-winded retarded rant is because it leads into the bigger point when I start walking
around outside my house and go on a little adventure and people don't get that they just
assume that I'm some run-of-the-mill douchebag swivel chair reviewer you know sending out a video
to my audience please help me with this problem I need your genius advice and they don't check to
see if anyone else has left the other the same comments they're leaving that's another thing
you should oh that's a big one so it's millions they're all the same fucking comment well if you
can't find it you should try this website you should download this media player and it's like
motherfucker if you are watching the video it's safe to say I've solved the fucking problem already
or else you wouldn't be watching the fucking video because it wouldn't exist you idiots this is what
youtube needs have you ever gone to like a help desk or a forum before and you start typing in a
question and all the related things come up it's like is this what you want is this the question
you're looking for youtube needs that my audience they can't seem to just accept that I am smarter
than you okay if you think that you have some advice or some solution I guarantee you that I've
already thought of it and already done it or addressed it in the very video that you're
watching if you will fucking finish the video before you comment okay you don't need to give me
advice I don't want your advice I'm not asking for your advice I'm asking for you to sit down
shut your fucking mouth and let me do my thing like the genius that I am you fucking peons you
just leave comments open because you want the praise because it's everything you're saying so far
just sounds like you know fuck all comments yes I okay I would love to live in a world we're good
comments that are thoughtful and like you know they have that are relevant and and like well
written and spelled correctly and articulate I would love for that you know what I call those
commenters who leave good comments I call them angels because they don't fucking exist I would
love to remember that time shortly after horseshoe finale came out when all those great comments
were appearing all those crazy theories about the video yes that was awesome that was the best
thing ever and but but but it's just it's drowned out it's totally like it's a drop in the pond
compared to all this should have blown it all up because that information got drowned out he was
right he was right he needs to kill right and solidus is always right he was the hero the patriots
are evil those fucking you know the the the once in a in a great fucking eon when someone writes a
comment that that means something like you inspired me or something or like or like actually picked
something up in the video that actually was my intention and actually theorizes and gets it
right for a change those guys are fucking they're you're all heroes to me if you've ever left a
good comment you deserve a badge of honor you deserve to be you there should be a statue built
for good commenters there should be a hall of fame and but but there's so few in fact actually
but those are the people who keep me coming back those are the reason I don't right that I don't
turn off my entire comment section and I wish to comment or hall of fame I've thought about doing
something like that because uh my my friend ghost lightning he used to have this blog called
ghosts of discussions where like it was just straight up a blog where he would take the best
comments from his posts and he would post them on this other blog and like uh it was really
interesting just because it's like he can save and he he was the one who taught me how to like
make a discussion go well because he would respond to every comment he got like no matter how vapid
he would respond to it and therefore he would get these like long intense discussions in his uh
in his um blog posts and so I've always thought about every time I read a comment that's actually
like so good that I want it to be around forever I'm like I really should just open up like a
some kind of site the only problem is it would take effort and I have to go through all my videos
and find all those good comments but like yeah man a good comment like a really good comment
if I've ever hit like on your comment it means you're doing god's work you should just start
doing that now going forward and make a video saying you're doing it and then instantly everyone
will like start shaping up because they want to get on that not a bad idea you know what are the
really good comments they're really good comments that really mean something is patrons and fan art
you know those are the only those are the best comments absolutely yeah uh divus rule number
four I was gonna bring up myself read the other comments especially if what you have is a correction
if you look if you're just having like a raw emotional reaction to the video it's understandable
that other people might feel the same way right like maybe your thoughts are well I agree with you
on this point and I think it's but I feel this way about this thing maybe someone else has already
said that but you you also feel that way that can be valid but if if it's like uh you said uh
I did this to did you just the other day you said 2005 but it was actually 2004 and then like you
don't like you should assume that someone made that comment immediately because when I put out a video
I get about and by the way going back to the fucking finish the video before you comment
I know if you haven't finished the video if you comment before it's been long enough yeah
for you to finish the video I get I'll post a video that's 20 minutes long and it'll have
fucking 20 comments on it by the time 20 minutes have passed and I'm like I should just every time
I think about deleting them all I always consider like I know you haven't finished it so I should
just delete all of these well they skip to the ending you know they skip to the important part
you know that's all the matter you should just disable comments on every video for the length
of the runtime and then open them up hey you know not a bad idea yeah this has been a problem on
YouTube ever since Steve Wozniak first invented YouTube in 2009 back when he was only available
on the linux os Steve Wozniak sounds like the name of a man who gargles balls from it that's
exactly what that's my comment Tom uh the only problem with that is that you'd have to reload
the page to know that comments were enabled afterwards and I don't think a lot of people
would assume that but uh yeah I think I think uh what was I saying right within like minutes
of my video going up everything I've gotten wrong will usually be corrected yeah like if I pronounced
something wrong I'm gonna hear about it immediately and here's the thing I don't care that I pronounce
something wrong it does not matter yeah you have to understand you have to understand reading a
script is hard you'll notice that all those accurate youtubers who pronounce everything right
talk like this hey everyone because you guys are completely wrong on this one
pronouncing things wrong is the greatest sin that any human being can commit
listen if you have ever left a comment criticizing someone's pronunciation
fucking kill yourself kill yourself Jesse kill yourself you deserve to die
hey all right Jesse hang on if I make a mistake editing and I know I made a mistake oh
shit I made a mistake but I uploaded it anyway am I immune from criticism no I'm I fucked up
well I don't I don't want your fucking criticism I don't care
world where you're going around making mistakes all the time like some rank amateur maybe you can
get corrected but I don't make mistakes I actually pronounce amateur the fuck up I pronounce everything
correctly all the time and no one can ever correct me because I'm the correct guy get out of here
I mean yeah Jesse if you correct my pronunciation please kill yourself yeah I do not I don't
care I don't fucking care there's nothing I care about less if you under listen if you correct my
pronunciation that means you understood the word well enough that you knew what the correct word
was therefore I've communicated my fucking point you fucked it up it's a mistake it's not a fuck
if you understand what the word is annoying when I when I'm the only purpose of words is to
communicate ideas if you understand the ideas and the word has been communicated there is no
necessity to pronounce it a certain way it is fucking irrelevant I want to hear more about the
communication to deliberately throw some shit out there like cacophony and it just throws the flow
of the whole video off that's right Jesse's right right out of it it picks me up look it breaks
we argued about this the other day I agree that if he's the way he said cacophony if it's
distracting and it makes the video worse for you that's a valid feeling but to say you pronounced
it wrong is completely irrelevant you should pronounce your pronunciation has made this video
worse for me that's why your video your visual audio medium they're not judging it on based on I
don't want them to judge it I don't care about their judgments it's a piece of pro i don't want
to listen to their complaints about my art youtube is the only place that you can release the kind
of art that we're making and we have to make the platform better that's the point of this whole
podcast if you're saying somebody's name in a video you should have the respect for them to
pronounce it correctly the way god and nature intended and if you're saying the name of like
like like like a word from a foreign language like a japanese word you better fucking pull your
eyes slanted and fucking say it like they do and fucking show a bunch of stupid I don't want to hear
this from the guy who makes entire videos about pronouncing everything japanese wrong and that's
the joke of the video everything correctly when I say that fucking sega genesis attack on Gundam
is my favorite anime of all time where's the respect there you fucking piece of shit
even though it was just said I wasn't even I didn't even hear what you just said
I said attack on Gundam is my favorite anime where's the respect there what are you talking about
animal is hilarious yeah it's yeah that doesn't mean it's respectable you're wrong on purpose
because it's funny that's a whole lot different than being totally serious and accidentally being
an idiot with the way I grasping it straws digi jesse I think this is as you have it there is never
a time when correcting pronunciation in the comments makes you not a piece of shit
I will fucking die on this hill there is no there is no context in which correcting my pronunciation
will make me feel like you haven't become a worse person in my eyes there is no context you're too
sensitive man you gotta you gotta accept that you just make what is sensitive about that mistakes
and you need to be corrected I know I made mistakes I don't care I don't care you are shit
for complaining about it babe your video is objectively worse because you made a mistake
now correct me there's no such thing as objectivity that's not a thing now listen I don't
what you guys don't realize is at least in earlier digi videos a lot of his mispronunciations were
not like things that he was unaware of it's because I have a similar problem right I'm not as I'm not
as vocally talented as jesse is who can just amazingly put out amazing vocal performances
it's really hard how dare you leave a comment on my vocal performances how dare you say anything
about anything I've done ever I'll kill you listen I spent I just came out with a video
that would have come out two days earlier if not for the fact that I have to get up behind the microphone
I can get out maybe five minutes of a good performance then I gotta go eat work out go to
the bathroom it takes me hours to psych myself up and oh my god we've got a badass over here
because I'm talking a bit too fast or a bit too slow maybe you know my tongue will slip
or it's just so hard to focus that's the job that's the job if you can't do it go be a writer
that's not the fucking job that's that's fucking retarded my job is not to pronounce shit right
listen agonize over making sure that every single people aren't the same guy
I know you're correct I spend my hours on this day
I don't believe for I don't believe that there's any difference between saying
you pronounce that word wrong and saying you wrote your review wrong there's no difference
you don't know what my intent was look my intention was not necessarily to pronounce everything right
because I don't give a fuck about pronouncing everything right that doesn't make my video
those are those having a wrong script is one error pronouncing a word wrong in the script is
another error it's not it's not a fucking error because I am not necessarily trying to write
something that's going to pull people out of the list you think I want my videos to be in English
what makes you think that the goal of my videos is to even be in English you don't know that
it might sound a lot my video might sound a lot like English but that doesn't mean that that's what
my goal is did you hear you're lost you're in the woods now I can't listen to me let me break this
down let me break this down for you all right I like the way the word niche sounds I don't like
the way the word I don't like the way the word niche sounds I like the way the word niche sounds
so when I read my script your opinion on what is correct is not relevant right yes it is Nate
because I get to decide what I think is better aesthetically in my video you do not get to
if you think that niche sounds better all right you can go fucking die because that's not the point
of my video it's not to appease what you want me to sound like you say it's not the point but the
point of every video you make is to communicate ideas like your bill I did communicate the idea
you knew what I meant retard who the heck did decide the way you pronounce things Nate it's in the
god damn you can look it up online how to pronounce these words it's not exactly 10 different
results god damn it shut up if you look at pronunciation online every single pronunciation
is different it's a god damn language we have ways of pronouncing things that's a load of shit
everyone knows the first rule of language is that it's flexible if you talk to anyone who studies
language they'll talk about how the second language the word change is fucking stupid
and weird then you say it a better way listen I want if if my goal is for everyone in the
world to start saying niche that I'm gonna keep saying niche so that I can eventually turn everyone
into saying words the way I want them to be said I am a pundit for my ideas pinch shunt because I
think pinch shunt sounds way it sounds cooler nobody gives a shit how do you think it sounds cooler
it's not about what sounds cooler can I just say the the whole the whole crux of this argument is
you're making an error who cares though I don't think does that make your point less
I don't I care that I agree I agree with you that a who does who cares but I also don't think
it's something really weird but I still understand that I'm not gonna say well I don't really like
them or that video there's a very simple point there's a very simple point you made about this
and it's the fact that every single one of us who watched that bunny hop video when he said
cacophony we were like what what the fuck was that cacophony we all did it take when he said
cacophony it actively made the video that's pretty cool that's right it was a distraction
and that was exactly counter to what I didn't mind to make well I mean I minded it in the sense
that you mind it because you're insane the only thing I remember from the video that's right
exactly exactly that's the problem I remember everything from the video and it didn't bother
me slightly because I'm not a piece of shit I don't remember anything I don't I don't give a fuck
about cacophony I don't like it you're all shit I don't agree you are the worst commenters I hope
you die no fuck you and fuck anyone who pronounces words grievously wrong okay you know what there
are some words there are some words that I'll go either way on okay I don't have an opinion on
niche or niche it can it sounds it sounds fine either way but there are some fucking words
that just sound retarded when people say them wrong like cacophony I'm gonna have to agree with
that listen Jesse I agree that cacophony sounds stupid and cacophony sounds better and cacophony
is one of my favorite words I'd love it if more people said it and said it correctly but leaving
a comment on bunny hops video is the same as leaving any other shitty comment if you want to
talk about why everyone's why he's wrong make your own video about how to pronounce cacophony
if your problem with how he says cacophony is that you think it should be pronounced different
that's not his problem it's your problem it's the standard of the language the standard of the
language is always being changed they update the dictionary they update pronunciations you know
I had a I made a video Nate I made a video once the first video I ever got really shat on for
pronunciation was when I said feminity instead of femininity that was too much all right I'm not
with you look you say that but feminity used to be a fucking word that used to be how it was said
I looked it up I did the research feminity was originally the word femininity became the word
because people liked the way it sounded more which means the language it means nothing but
bullshitting what they like feminity sounds retarded whether it's whether it's technically
correct or technically not correct it sounds dumb so we changed it my point is that there is no
objective idea of what it means because it changes based on people's tastes meaning that when you
leave a comment that someone's pronouncing something wrong that's just your taste that's just your
opinion it's not objective there is no objective failure because objectivity isn't real right there
because the way the objectivity is is incorrect because what is objective is that we do have
a standard in the language that we have most of us it's it's a democratic process and we have decided
that we are going to pronounce as an english language cacophony not cacophony my videos
are not a democratic process my videos are things that i post to share my at this point at this point
i'd like to reiterate that this is not an argument about whether it's an objective fact that when
people pronounce things differently than how everyone else pronounces it it sounds weird
and it throws people off that's an it does sound weird i'd just i'd like to say that you just don't
have a big enough of a viewer base nor do i for there to be a large contingent of people it would
never happen to me because i pronounce everything correctly all of them just think that until until
you get enough people with different opinions no see that's just that's just that's just the wrong
way of looking at it jesse that's just hiding when you say that you say that you know you said it
sounds weird and wrong and that's kind of like when people go to your videos and they say the way
that you present your ideas is weird and wrong to me it's it's no that's totally different there is
no standard for how jesse should make his videos there should be no standard for language just like
there should be no standard for art did you i have a really important question where did you write that
shut up did you shut up shut up shut up no he said there should be no standard and that's
let the man speak i just want to say that i don't mind the whole mispronouncing things
as much as nate seems to because honestly i don't even hate it that much i don't even care what you
seem to i don't really give a shit okay i'm sorry go on go on i just the reason i don't mind it so
much is because i grew up in a place where loads of people had loads of different accents and i'm
just like if i hear cacophony or cacophony or whatever i'm just like oh and then i just
nobody knows what we're talking about by the way nobody has seen the super funny
what i was trying to say is that we gotta link it in the description yeah did you i want to ask you
the whole this discussion is pointless because all we're talking about is how much nate and or you
know how much any any of us cares about mispronunciations it's got nothing to do with comments let's
drop this whole subject who's super willing to accept people pronouncing words any way they want
the reason it bothers me so much is that i listen to the all kinds of reason that you're so
sensitive because you pronounce shit wrong all the time you know that's i listen to all kinds of
videos with people with weird accents who pronounce everything differently from how i'm used to and
i just assume well he comes from a different culture he has a different accent than me he
pronounces things differently where is george weedman that's how that's how i feel and people
because of the fact that most of the words i say sound like standard american english they
assume i don't have an accent but i have an accent it's just that only certain elements of the things
i say sound different it's only when i start saying shit like y'all which i say all the time
that people start realizing oh he's from the south and he says things in a different way and there's
words that i've learned in a way that's different from how other people have learned them and when
i use those words people complain at me because they don't think of it as he has an accent they
think of it as he's just saying words wrong i know the context just like all the other problems
did you have a question no no you're oversimplifying and that's wrong comments did these pronunciation
comments bother you this much when they first started happening here and there because i feel like
always bothered me there you go your point is invalid i have always been bothered by pronunciation
comments because of the fact simply as i said earlier with accent though you don't have a southern
accent it's not your act if someone is speaking in an accent and they're pronouncing words differently
i can interpret that in my brain and i don't get because you only think but that only doesn't
weird you out because it sounds so much like a clear accent what i'm saying is that i have an
accent it just sounds a lot like normal english but that doesn't mean it's not an accent there's
certain words that just i just say differently i don't hear that do you hear that hippo normal
english look is there a difference is there a difference between an accent and saying something
wrong definitely is there even a difference i would say yes i think i would say yes i think that
there are times when you when like there are some words there's a spectrum though there are some
words that i have said wrong because i've never heard them spoken before and i've only i've only
read them online and i've never heard them spoken so i say it and i pronounce it wrong and sometimes
someone corrects me on it and i i look it up and i go okay that makes sense i'll pronounce it that
way from now i pronounce the word bosom for like 10 years so there's a lot of words that are like
that there is other words that i that i pronounce wrong because i've said it for so long that that's
just how i say it like for instance i cannot pronounce bakemonogatari i cannot do it that sounds
fine no it's not like it should be well i actually did get closer to how i usually um closer than i
usually do but it should be bakemonogatari right dude you're not japanese it's forgiven but i you
have an american accent i always say bakemonogatari that's literally perfect that's literally perfect
what's wrong no it's not there's an e instead of an a at the end i've gotten complaints about it all
the time that i say bakemonogatari wrong because i say that e at the end instead of an a and it's
because i cannot in the in the context of reading a script i cannot say it the other way because
i've been saying it for like eight years okay well bakemonogatari because it sounds natural
literally a problem with you i can't when i try to read a script and i try to say niche it sounds
so fucking weird because i have to stop everything and over pronounce that word i did it in a video
recently where i was like it's feeling a certain niche you have to have some video some audio fidelity
you have to fucking accept that that it sounds wrong if you say it that way though did you just
motors through his scripts and doesn't pay any heed to them i think they sound better that way
i think when you over pronounce words and you talk slow you sound like a fucking nerd and i don't
want to listen to you i want to listen to people who sound natural who sound like using the voice
that they use in their everyday life criticizing the things that you've admitted are objectively
wrong just aren't allowed to say anything i'm saying that they that i'm saying that they're
missing the point of the video they're missing that the reason i talked the way i feel is because
i want the scripts to sound fast and if you had your way george bush would still be in office
and we'd all be pronouncing strategy as strategic that's the world if i had my way did you if i had
my way then then miss miss underestimating would definitely be a word all right i detected the
problem i've detected that's that's the george bush word and it is that you think that these
comments are somehow taking away from the other conversation of the video i don't see why that
has to be the case i don't think that they do i think they do look and here's the other problem
is that they can they can also be the death of of jokes and inside jokes i for instance i could
never get away with saying simultaneously in my videos because people would go what the fuck
are you talking about but to all of us that's hilarious because the time cube guy says simultaneously
so like i would love to write that into a script but what am i going to get a hundred million
comments going do you pronounce it wrong like and like maybe maybe cacophony was intended to sound
weird in that video we don't know that we do really don't we don't know you can infer based on tone
you can infer you can infer but that doesn't mean you know how many times have you been
farcical on purpose and people don't get it yeah but you don't look it's not his job to make something
that you will completely appreciate and understand it's his job to make his art if you leave a comment
saying that you weren't understandable that's no different from that comment that guy left on my
erased video saying this wasn't helpful to everybody my goal wasn't to be helpful to everybody
now if if i said if i came out and i said hey guys where are the mistakes in this video that
made it harder to understand then you commented that that would be great if i if i actually came
out and said hey where did i pronounce things wrong tell me i want to know i want to correct
myself and make my videos more understandable to more people then yes please you are constantly
asking that question by releasing a video that contains your speech i do not think so i think
that's bullshit i think it's pretty funny that uh that a podcast about like shitty comments has
essentially turned into a toxic comment section with all of us yelling this is the most intense
debate we've had yet on pcp i feel i just like to say that all of you since you're american are
always sounding wrong to me because i am english right yeah so he just said always no one ever
complains that he says always instead of always yeah and that seems it seems natural to you because
all the words he says sound are we even disagreeing anymore i think we pretty much i hope not all
right can we just move on what's the next thing that you shouldn't do in your comments we can
take away from that because i don't don't complain about pronunciation no complain all you want
back no the rule is don't work and if you do complain about pronunciation control f the
fucking thread so i don't have to read okay literally 700 we can all agree we can all agree
one is enough when it comes to that we can all agree on oh and and here's another thing about
the pronunciation thing it's one thing to correct the pronunciation but when i get comments like
the way he says kilua makes me want to fucking stab my ears out well get over yourself you fucking
piece of shit like like like me pronouncing a word wrong has like somehow given you cancer
that's the exact comment that i left on super bunny ops video i said the way you're pronounced
to cough and he gave me an aneurysm i mean that's just a that's a comedic thing it's just like
like the way you said it is kind of funny there are people who have left comments like they were
legitimately offended by the way that i pronounced kilua in my video dude i don't i clearly we're
coming to this from different angles because because i have committed federal crimes yeah
once you're all once you all get the level of comments i fucking get i want you to come back
and have this conversation all right when you've got a video with 700 comments insulting your
pronunciation and come back and tell me i'm just saying i'm defending ideas here i don't even think
the way i mean how lucky are you that you said it's gurren laggin time and no one said anything
about it lag on i said gurren no you said you say at the beginning of the video you say
it's gurren laggin time i did not say it i did not say it's gurren lagoon i totally remember it
being wrong i remember you should have called it gurren lagoon it would have been way funnier
do the whole video over i want to go live in gurren lagoon that's gonna be my japanese anime
all right let's move on let's move on what's the next rule it should be gurren lagoon
why'd you edit that down what who's got a rule let me compose myself Jesus Christ yeah i had to
take a second that was an epic debate hippo hippo say something while i try to think about my next
okay okay i got one okay oh i've got a good one though my blood is like no give it has rule
give it has rule i got a rule i got a rule okay don't ever don't ever post a comment for the
express purpose of getting plus ones because it's just completely pointless and it's so obvious i have
the strength to comment on this video anyway i think i think i mean stuff like i think hippo
means stuff like uh am i the only one who thinks this show is good yeah here's a rule here's a rule
never ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever
start a comment with am i the only one who don't do it i'll fucking murder your whole family that's
a bannable offense that's the worst possible comment you could ever make no you're not the only one
everyone is fucking thinking the same thing you're not special you don't matter you're gonna die one
day and i hope it's today fuck you you know i think that's all that needs to be said about that
plundering
given you should be leading this debate short sweet until the given gets it right there i can't
wait to see the commenters on this video like tripping over themselves to do it right ironically
say that oh yeah that's another one that's another bannable offense when i'm when i say in a video
don't make this particular comment and then they make that exact comment to be cute you're not being
cute you're not being funny you're not clever oh my god aids and cancer at the same time that's a
once again cuteness doesn't solve any problem it cuteness does not excuse anything it never
solved anything the way never when i said don't i when i said comments about the beard will be
deleted i really regret that i didn't say they that you will be banned yeah these people would
have there still would have been the only reason i didn't do that is because i actually was a little
afraid that i'd have to ban all my commenters like i was seriously like if i say that they're not
like they're not gonna believe like they're not gonna understand that i really mean that
and i will ban them all i've just realized we have completely opened ourselves up to a wall of
ironic comments it's gonna be yeah and we can ban them all yeah because they're all and all
and then people who commented before they got to this point that's you're gonna probably
you shouldn't listen to rule number one you gotta watch the whole video you're gonna get
definitely serious and you will always be banned from this there will be dozens and dozens maybe
hundreds of future pcp episodes and you will be egging to say stuff and you won't get to say any
of it and you will be crying on that day and will bury you you had to bury you in a termite
mountain termites will bite your dick until you're dead i'll put a baseball mitt full of ants on your
balls and they'll bite you on the balls i love how they bite your balls devoo always
frames every time someone offends someone in this group he always frames it as once we are really
famous you're gonna be so mad that's always i like that optimize when i'm king i will remember
everyone who slighted me and i will send assassins out across the far corners of the world to slay
to slay all the commenters date to put this simply yeah you can if you've already thought of the
phrase you can say it with me ironic shitposting is still shitposting yes that's the one that's the
one so how about we get to the the one that is my least my most hated one okay the arrogant smug
tone which people don't realize is a big problem they don't wait a minute devoo don't start tone
policing because that's a bannable offense for me i can't stand that shit okay for the content
all right listen when people say that the internet is a huge hive of scum and villainy the internet
is a full of a bunch of terrible people they are not talking about fourchan they're not talking about
people who say you're a fag with in all lower case i mean those guys are a big problem right
but the problem the problem with the internet is people who are like my friend you have really
disappointed me this is not good at all this is nothing i just got one of those right before
we started this fucking day sir the phrase my friend should be like autoband they always end
it with good day the one the ones i've seen the worst were on tom's video recently because
everyone's like dude what happened to love and tolerate brother i'll really let us down the
worst is when they combine that with hypocrisy when they're pissed like they're bitching at you for
being smug in a smug tone yeah don't ever don't ever dare to talk to me like some disappointed
parental figure or some friend you're not my friend the only one if you want to be my friend
become a patron at patreon.com slash ben saint mother fucker because look guys look guys being a troll
being an asshole being a flamer does not i mean okay look capitalization spelling that's a small
variable but that is not precluded there's so many people who will make something that's obviously
obviously meant to piss you off it's obviously trolling it's obviously baiting but they have
a decent vocabulary and they capitalize their their words and sentences and stuff and they think
that because they spelled everything right and didn't have too many exclamation marks it's all
about the exclamation marks right or words that are in all caps they think that's the definition
of trolling no it's not the definition of trolling is whether or not it pisses someone off and it
was intended to be so and so many people will come out with passive-aggressive smarmy terrible
comments and it will think that they're being they're they're fair criticism that's the fair
criticism nothing it says nothing works it's the song you guys have to understand there are so many
times and i think all of you guys would agree with this there are many times where i will add a bunch
exclamation marks or capitalize words to make me sound stupid to lower myself that's being humble
in my book and i can't do that anymore i used to do that more often where i'd be balanced where i
wanted to be like fun and and just like a normal person i'd be like you suck good you know like
even in this very chat like i'll say like these people these wine these scum will utilize they
will they will not let you get away with that they when someone gets into a flame war with you right
they are on turbo alert mode looking for anything you say that has two exclamation marks or more
so that they can then posit you as this you as this troll angry guy right they're looking for
anything they can use to discredit you you know and nothing bothers me more than hold it in their
heart and use it for for everything it's worth they will milk anything they can find to make it seem
like oh you're just being a big violent jerkface don't you realize and this is another fallacy
or as did you would say a fallacy that you can see around all of discussion is um i call it the uh
the first amendment kicks in when i get uncomfortable fallacy right which is i make a video
that's my free speech you make a comment that's your speech too i make a reply that's my speech
you make a reply that's your speech but then i make a reply that's really logical and trumps
trumps all of your ideas and now all of a sudden i'm trampling on i'm trampling on your ideas all
of a sudden the for all of a sudden the oppression begins when you run out of arguments right this
is the problem i've seen ever since the internet was invented in 1975 this this is the most substantive
complaint yet to do and i i very much agree i very much agree you know the saddest part about that
fallacy thing is that uh my best rap i ever wrote for the jephard jesson's father's following of
and i i can't like once i found out that that was the wrong pronunciation i thought oh gary no one
probably can take this seriously and i can't change it because the entire rhyme screen scheme is based
on it being pronounced i pronounce it fagotry that's a good way to pronounce it uh yeah no
smarm drives me crazy because it's this this whole attitude of if you don't have something nice to
say don't say anything at all but then you say that in in a bitchy way and it's like the what we need
to be doing as a society is getting to the point not being nice not not arguing in a way that fits
your parameters of how an argument should be it's getting to the point that world of only saying
nice things is is the medley or solitude nightmare you know that in one of my videos in one of my
videos i say faggot at one point which is very weird because my videos have very few squaring but
there's one time where i decide to use faggot right and i got some comments complaining about it
whatever and there was one that was like i can't believe you do that and i was like you know man
you know whatever yada yada and it shut up you faggot that would have been my response i have a
beautiful example for this one you're done by the way so okay because then you said just you know
shut up about it saying faggot is really annoying and i was like uh you know i i actually upvoted
that comment because he's just saying he just he stopped being all smarmy i want to elaborate on
that don't say that i was going to bring this up uh you people on the internet you commenters
you have ruined the word faggot for me forever like what is what a shame what a shame faggot
louis ck saved it and then it got ruined faggot yeah louis ck made people realize that they could
say it and then they went way too far with it like yeah faggot is like one of my favorite words
ever in the world it it's a beautiful word and it describes a person so nebulous that they can only
be described with that word which is why i am very careful with how i use the word faggot i only say
when there's an impact to it when it really matters and means what i'm trying to say it takes faggot
compilation you'll see exactly artistry at work every every time i've ever said faggot has been
totally 100 the best possible word i could have used at that given time but people throw faggot
around so much nowadays that it just robs the word of any agency and any impact and any meaning
and it drives me insane uh i you know i kind of disagree i i think the fact that it's so meaningless
is what i like it's not meaningless it describes a specific person that you can't describe with any
other word that's why it's so important to keep it put it perfectly when he said yeah you know the
he pulls the dick out of his mouth and says people from phoenix or phoenicia yeah shut up faggot
shut up and suck that dick yeah like that made perfect sense and unfortunately yeah i think it
has i agree with jesse that it's been ruined for me by other people and like i've tried to sort of
replace it with fuckboy because it means yeah that was great it describes the same kind of person
but it doesn't have it's too fun like faggot still sounds like an insult rest fuckboy is a little bit
too much you know how faggot should be used faggot should be like the nuclear option the kill code
like yeah like it should like randy orton's head punt he never he never uses it except sometimes
that when he uses it the guy is like injured for eight months it should be like when you're like
running down some guy with a huge string of insults you're stupid and you're dumb and you're gay and
you're a homo and you're ugly and you're fat and you're dumb and you're dumb and you're dumb and
you're a fucking faggot and then they're dead they are that's the way to do it by the way can
can we hear tom's example yeah i was gonna say the same thing well i mean we've we've kind of gone
off the rails went a different direction i was going to say how i just i don't like it when people
will will when you use like words like that when you use like risqu language or whatever and they
just fucking are on your dick on it instantly and like they take that holier than that thing like
when i said rape corporate raping of your childhood in the power puff girls video and then i just got
this guide like in before i'd even made it public i don't know how we found it i think i put in a
playlist or something and just fucking like when i'll preachy on me about how i'm not allowed to
use that word you need to stop normalizing rape with that kind of language brother that is not
accepted exactly what he said okay so i think you guys might want some guidelines but hang on
before before we get into that debut let me point out right now on dictionary dot com the third
definition of rape is an act of plunder violence seizure that's exactly what i said i responded
with that or violation it is the exact correct word to use for that yeah so people need to
fuck off that's what i said and then some of the respondents me saying that it's like citing the
dictionary is offensive what we know the dictionary isn't isn't what describes words people
decide what words mean and well i will say that sometimes people will be like oh you're not using
this word the exact way i would which they're using it wrong and like go look up the definition one
one time one guy said go look up the definition of the world should he misbed he misspelled word
would and i got on his ass for that all right listen you guys want some i just want to say real
quick tom i don't think i've ever wanted to kill a man more than i have based on what you just
described to me but okay debu let's actually i before debu continues actually sorry i keep cutting
you off but mate i have to know yeah with your final fantasy seven video okay where you like
literally depicted a rape of yep oh yeah how did that go over you know amazingly i only got one
comment that said like ooh was a little uncomfortable with that last scene but overall great video
amazing i was like oh my god when you put that in i know i was debating whether or not i should
just remove it entirely but people actually were okay with it except for one guy who was only a
little uncomfortable but and and that video got like 25 000 views and only one comment really
was amazing okay so i got one winner i like to think that it was due to my jovial tone
overall people were accepting anybody let's go on so you guys want some advice on how to not be
smarmy right so first point don't have short sentences short sentences with very few words
and lots of periods and redundant terminology using the same words over and over again the same
words all the time people do that deliberately to piss you off it makes them sound like they're so
i don't know why it is nothing is more passive it's very nothing is more passive aggressive than
no you don't because yeah yeah this is how it you know i've got exactly what the dude said
oh really okay okay you know i don't like it's true long comments are bad uh short comments are
maybe a little bit better but you know you should just take it the one step further and just not
comment which is really the ultimate uh conclusion i'd like to get to here just don't comment that's
the biggest rule just don't you know go away if you've ever seen the welcome to youtube video
yeah where he said uh hit now for how to comment don't yeah it stands for this don't it stands for
don't i think this is the number one point i can make about how to not be a big smug prick
uh just represent yourself instead of saying this video uh offended this group minority that
i don't represent instead of saying this video has broken this law of conduct and this video has
done this wrong this video has violated this this memo no you have to you have to defend your idea
yeah just say this just stick with this this video pissed me off you know what right that
kind of comment wouldn't really bother me you see it's it's not the fact that people just look
people just liking a video of mine you know that's kind of disappointing right but what
offends me is when people try to represent something beyond themselves all you gotta do is
there's nothing that's more annoying that people getting offended on other people's behalf that's a
big problem that's a universal thing you can see in in comments they're big smug people is that they
always they don't seem to think that they themselves are a valuable resource like go out to their
garage and sit on a squat over the car and just poop on it i want to poop on your car as a human being
i have enough respect for you that if you say something such and such bothers me i can respect
that i can respect that that's how you feel about something but it's that they didn't try to make
it that i make it out like a sort of imaginary rule book for videos that i'm violating which isn't
true that's like i don't know what the definition we gotta stop devu i know you're trying to like
just continue your point even though jesse is mumbling i want to go into your house with a
tooth drive and i want to say i want to poop in the hard to find places so you don't know where
the smell is coming from and you have to live with it forever you just want to do what you poop i want
to poop poop on you want to poop poop on commenters you go do that commenters are pooping i poop on
them okay look commenters are pooping i poop on them comment there the chest pooping is yeah
like uh because like that uh that one right at moderator from a couple episodes ago whatever you
one thing i told him was don't try to represent some sort of objective standard all you got to do
to get our attention to get my attention to make a comment that will leave an impact on me is just
say such and such bothers me and then i can decide whether or not to take that seriously like yeah
everything that pisses me off almost all the piss i've ever had towards comments is that
pretense that you represent something that you don't that's all i want that and i think you're
totally right the only problem is that is that people who are all into collectivism and shit
and feeling offended for other things they take personal offense from being other people being
offended so they are well my god there's just no winning there's no way to win that fight i think
well i mean when it comes to words and stuff yeah but that doesn't apply to like oh you didn't
structure your review correctly you know they're inventing something imaginary like who are you
who are these fucking people saying you didn't structure have you ever made a fucking video
do you know what it's like to be on youtube god these these fucking backseat youtubers
there's nothing worse than them those people need to fucking burn i like that term no like
if someone says this video is offensive then the only response you need to make is maybe for you
but it's not offensive and my god like it's not offensive for the people who liked it who and
that's who i made it for i didn't make it for you offending someone like a bannable offense like
this is the real world we're living in if an idea offends you you can say that that's fine right
that doesn't make it objectively wrong some things are offensive it all comes back once again into
and right offense is always it all comes back again into what do what not knowing what we want out
of our videos right again if you're leaving a comment saying you did this wrong you really
don't know what we were intending to do maybe i wanted to offend you maybe i just didn't think
it was offensive maybe in my culture being offended by that thing i said is offensive to me
like sometimes sometimes the things that offend other people i am offended that it offends them
that is a thing i have experienced right so like yeah circular triggering is a real thing folks
right and once again you don't need to leave your offended comment on my video it's not my job to
give you that platform you have everywhere on the internet too now i understand that because my
comments are open you probably will leave the comment on my video but guess what i'm going to
delete it because i have the power to do that don't want your comment deleted leave it somewhere else
go on twitter and talk about that makes comments suck is i think you know they get frustrated
because they know something pissed them off and i think it comes from the futility that they feel
that this guy's not going to read my comment i'm wasting my time this guy's just gonna say what he
says in his own bubble and he's never gonna even hear me out and that frustration makes their comment
more bitchy right so here's another rule assume that they're going to read the comments because
unless they get hundreds of thousands of views on every video yeah they probably actually at least
skim all the comments you don't people don't underestimate how much youtubers read their
comments most of the time and the real the thing is that that because they get pissed off they don't
want to put in the effort to read the other comments to see if that correction's already been made
they they go into base things like using short sentences they go into all the other problems
that we just talked about because of that frustration that feeling that it's going to be
thrown in the garbage anyway well you know what that's the wrong way of looking at it look at it
like it will get thrown in the garbage unless you calm down and try to say something insightful
because our whole careers here on youtube is about saying things that are insightful
even if it is very critical and that's what i'll say this like i you know i've made it sound like
i delete fucking comments all the time and i do but most of the comments i delete are the ones that
that have no recourse where it's just like fuck you you're a piece of shit and i just delete that
guy and ban that guy you know and also meaningful statement i also will say that like a lot of my
bands are based on if a lot of my bands aren't because of criticism per se they're because
someone either admitted that they downvoted the video or admitted that they unsubscribe oh yeah
that's another thing don't pretend to have some sort of some sort of affection for me when they're
like i unsubscribe really i've never seen any of your comments on any of my other videos oh right
you unsubscribe on my roller coaster three video a video i posted almost a year ago what kind of
subscriber are you taking so long to watch my damn videos i don't believe you for one second
continuing what i was saying that i he's i don't what i don't usually ban is people who who are just
like you know making an argument and i'll usually respond to them yeah and if they're being a dick
this has happened countless times where someone will say something they'll leave a comment in a way
that's kind of like an asshole and then i'll respond and then they will apologize
because where are these people coming from i never get anyone apologizing i get it i never get
apologies all the time i get it all the time no you know because i hate these posts well the
view the difference is that you often respond to people being an asshole by being an asshole
no no no no no no no i do it in ways that that can diffuse the situation what's going on with jesse
over there listen i was slapping the microphone with my wiener context
no that's constructive commentary the vast majority of the comments i got on my big videos
have been like ways to diffuse it but it doesn't work so i'm not gonna i'm not i've
haven't been an asshole in return although i will i am open to the idea that maybe there's
a diffusal technique that i need to learn do you know what i mean whenever someone apologizes please
link me that comment so i can learn how you do it i will i will next time it happens but i get a
lot of those were just someone responds in a way where they're like they disagree with the video but
they phrase it in a really douchey way and i'll usually respond like well my intention was this
and this is what i was trying to communicate yeah i've done that and i and most of the time they
just don't reply i never get i never have gotten a single call the worst the worst the worst fucking
response is when someone will be a complete dick and just try and like shut you down and then you
respond and like just annihilate their argument like calm down bro it's just kidding
if you say anything to someone with even a little bit of edge or if you use it like
a swear word suddenly you're automatically in the wrong because you got angry well mother fucker
if you're saying stupid bullshit on my video yes i am angry i have a right to be where the
comment and i'm just getting where the fuck they want yeah just remember that guy on you um
you're the content creator you're supposed to be the bigger person and i know tom that's
infuriating it's fucking bullshit this guy started i'm not going to read the whole comment
but he's like i tend to agree with your point yada yada i think you missed his opportunity yada yada
and so then you respond um going you just respond like i went off on that motherfucker
i fucking burned him at the stake you at the end and so his reply is wow period okay period oh god
no never say yeah wow yeah and he even goes he even goes i'm even at the end he goes i'm a fan
and i'm not unsubscribing because i like your content but when a fan when a fan he says they
like your stuff and then tells you who who are you think you have a fucking opinion that's worth
anything you're nothing you're worthless i here's oh no you're gonna unsubscribe guess what five
fucking people just replace you subscribe he's saying guys i could unsubscribe but i've decided
have mercy on you i'm gonna be very generous and not unsubscribe oh well he's not merciful what a
good i went off on that motherfucker and i hope he has cancer you know what you know what that is
when someone went when he said like wow period okay period you know what that is it's the internet
equivalent of when somebody starts a fight gets their ass kicked and then stands up and goes come
on pussy come on i'm still going i still want to fight i'm telling you i'm telling you if anyone
ever fucking does that to me you are never getting invited back to gurren lagoon you're never
never guys i gotta i gotta make this i want to make this comparison all right because the thing
about the internet and the reason that people feel so entitled to say this shit is that it's so
abstracted right right exactly we're all we're all far apart from each other we're all on our own
screens you don't visualize it as people being there but the thing is that when i post a video
and 2000 views get onto it in 30 minutes that means that basically everyone's in the same place
we're all doing the same thing we're all at our computer we're all watching the same video we're
all there and i'm standing there like when i post a video imagine this is the exact scenario that i
think it's comparable to you know when there's those movie screenings where the director is there
where the director like like will will be will will they'll show the movie the director's there at
the end he might do like a q&a or something right and that's typically like how these these work
i post a video and i'm sitting there on youtube after i like it's not like i post a video and
then i disappear you know i don't fucking i don't post my video and then immediately go on a globetrotting
adventure or something like that's not what happens i post it and then i sit there for two hours
and read and respond to comments as they come and imagine when i when i when i post up a video
and then i see comments coming onto the video before the runtime of the video is over that's what
all starts to go downhill imagine yourself in a theater that that theater situation where the
director is there and people are standing up and shouting first while watching the movie you would
so deeply offend that direct they would kick you out of the theater first of all you would immediately
be removed from the video because the venue itself has rules about this right the no one would comment
before the movie was over once the director came out nobody would say you fucking suck you'd get
kicked out you would get banned you would get blocked if the director comes out people stand up
they give a round of applause even if you didn't like the movie stay sitting down don't say anything
don't fucking you know or leave get up and leave because you the movie obviously didn't
resonate with you you it wasn't for you it was for those people who were standing up clapping
that's the like bar when the movie ends and everybody stands up and claps that's the like bar
on the video yeah this the dislike bar is shouldn't even exist really because it i mean i i like the
dislike bar only for when it's showing a mass dissatisfaction with something yeah i think it
can be yeah yeah i'm with you on this point i i do agree that there's there's something definitely
to be said about uh the environment you're in and the types of comments that are made but i guess
it's just i i this is a totally separate point now but i really think it's important to have a place
where you can just fucking vent and that's why i love 4chan so much but that yeah that's why 4chan's
there though you could go on 4chan and do that i would love it if every time someone got mad about
my video they went and complained about it on 4chan yeah not in my fucking comments because
again to bring it back to that movie scenario if the director is standing there on the front of the
stage and someone has it like let's say there was a rape scene in the movie yeah and someone gets up
and they say like like this would be an appropriate response you'd expect at a theater uh that rape
scene made me a little bit uncomfortable so i'm curious as to why you put it in there what was
your intentions with showcasing that were you trying to offend or did you have like what was
your intent what was the message you were trying to communicate and then once the director tells you
what message he was trying to communicate you can decide in your head well i don't agree with the way
he presented it you don't have to you don't even have to say anything you can just know that in your
mind right if you got up in that theater and you said how dare you depict rape the way you did
then the director is gonna say fuck off i get out of my theater you know this is what i'm saying
like people because of the abstraction of the internet they don't think of it this way but this
is exactly what it is i am there i am the director of the video i am listening to your comments and
when you come out screaming that is no socially different from standing up in the theater and
yelling at the i think it's a little different but i hear what you're saying okay here's here's
something kind of semi-related based on that is something that really drives me crazy is when
because like we're talking about how people will comment and like you're sitting there especially
in the beginning like reading the comments because like yeah you want to see what the reaction is to
your work it drives me fucking crazy especially because i'm not a big channel when people will
talk about me like i'm not there i prefer to be like in like a third person or just like
talk amongst themselves does this yeah and it's just like i'm right here of this video
that is yeah that brings me to another rule okay do not
shit talk the video makers friends you idiots yeah this happens to all of us especially
like there have been because and this happened to me and tom i think more than anybody else right
where me and tom were both big in the pony community at a time and we would both cover
every new episode of a show and me and tom were good friends and if you watched our content you
would know that because we collaborated all the time we hung out we had all these interactions
with each other and there would be people who would like comment on one of our videos about
how shit the other guys was and like oh they would comment on tom's videos like tom i'm so glad
that you're acting like this because digi lately it's just been a like a piece of shit like loser
and i'm like i read tom's comments you're you're talking to me in front of my face this is happening
to me so much digi on your top 10 youtuber youtube videos video yeah because you put me in both
number two spots and so all these normies from your channel who didn't know about me you didn't
like understand my content immediately had to spout off some opinion about it so you get all
these people like this this one guy was like just use okay sometimes but i don't like he he seems
like a bad but like totally misunderstanding my intent like the most obvious the most obviously
stupid one is when digi bro's channel was down briefly and then uh on the gibbentake channel
hippo oh yeah and people like oh fuck digi and fuck digi and it's like how could anyone who follows
the gibbentake channel possibly like know about digi but also not realize that they're friends
well like i remember that time i think digi could possibly be we're saying like really dismissive
things like right yeah this guy looks dumb you know like even though digi just got done
explaining to you why i like succeeded in like breaking the boundaries or like transcending
whatever the fuck i was doing and like he says like it's not forever but he tells you why the video
was good and why you should give it a chance and they're still being dismissive about it and then
like i gotta do like a whole big thing with these two dipshit commenters on digi's videos
and this one guy he kept like he kept saying the word brony at me as though it were an insult
like uh you used to brony go back and review my the pony videos and it's like do you know
who you're fucking subscribed to oh god that's the kind of calling me as though it's an insult
digi bro is the reason there is a brony fandom you dumb fuck well i guess no brony
some people i would say that digi is 25 percent at least of why there is a persistent
my little pony fandom something like that something like that i think yeah like did you
made all these thirsty ass guys be like oh my god i can make money talking about fucking ponies on
youtube i'm in which is exactly why i got into it too so and this is also like this is part of why
i grew to eventually like really resent a lot of the other my little pony reviewers right right
they never stuck up for it like like with me and tom when people would insult one of us
we would stick up for each other we'd be like hey you know digi watches my videos or hey you know
tom is my friend right you know like get the fuck out of here with that shit there's a lot of like
all these pony youtubers who were all like directly inspired by me yeah they would get all these
comments about how oh you're so much better than digi bro he's such a shit and they would never
say anything about it they would never like uh they would never attack those people they'd never
be like oh no they're thrown they want that thrown to empty it because they don't want to stick up for
anyone least of all right friends or themselves and i'm like i'm like if i inspired you you should
like okay imagine like like i've talked about a lot about ghost lightning right and how he inspired
me to get into blogging if someone came into my video and was like man that ghost lightning guy
his blog went so downhill i'm so glad that you you were such a good dude i'd be like get the fuck
out of here because that guy is that guy is the entire reason i even do this because he inspired
me and there's people who directly have like told me that i was the reason that they started doing
youtube yeah and then they get comments that are like fuck digi bro and they don't say anything and
i know why it's because it makes them feel good they feel good that they are getting praised over a
famous guy over a guy who has more attention than they do so they're like oh you know even though i
don't agree with this at least uh oh yeah i get to fuck you all right if you don't defend the fact that
i inspired you to make your videos you exist because of me you fucking pieces of shit do not pull
and i'm not saying this just to be arrogant for myself i feel this way about everyone who inspired
me if someone throw them stone if someone fucking came to my video and was talking shit about any of
the video make even uh you guys have seen how defensive i get of even ego raptor and i don't
even think he's making good videos anymore but every time someone talks shit about ego raptor i'm
like well i wouldn't be here if not for you always dependent when i talk about game grunts you're
always there digi haters when you guys channeled lead it i was on that equestria daily thread
responding to all my god i i got banned from equestria daily banned from equestria daily uh
oh what a for love for for like being too correct i wasn't even being angry at them now you know i
think that's another theory i have as to why people put up with that kind of hatred it's because a
lot of people don't mind all of the hateful comments as much in general this brings me to the most
offensive but most like possibly the most impactful point i'm gonna make is i think a lot of people
listening to this who maybe even have a little bit of content themselves and they they're listening
to our complaints and they're like yeah you know you guys make a bunch of good points but negative
comments still don't bother me that much and i don't really relate to your guys's opinions well i have
your own throat motherfucker because i'm more important than you and they bother me
well you know that's kind of what i'm about to say you see he's gonna say it's an issue of scale
right well no no it's because it used to be because i've been on the internet forever right
ever since it was invented in 1937 and yeah uh and i would make stuff i would throw stuff out there
and i didn't really have a whole lot of passion i i i wanted to do something but i didn't have a
clear goal a clear motivation then there wasn't anything that i ever like really poured my soul
into and if someone criticized it i was like you know i don't really care it was only when i started
really caring about the stuff that i was making uh that you know it started to really get under my
skin more you know people misinterpreting your intentions is more offensive when you have more
intentions so i just want people to reflect on themselves about that that if you don't think
that offensive comments are that offensive maybe it's because you're not very creative or very
driven rather you know i know that's a really harsh point to make but i think it's probably very
fucking true because like i'm i'm working on like i still do reviews on on on my first channel
but i mean i don't really care too much anymore it's just i'm doing it because like there are
occasionally topics that i like talking about and that's how i make money and so like when people
like blew up on the video i made yesterday like i knew it was gonna incite shit i didn't care it was
just like a dumb thing i wanted to do and like whatever but you know when when there's projects
that i like i legitimately care about i'm way more defensive about it i mean that's why i'm like
stalling trying to make this motion comment because like my like soul is in this project
and like i'm going to be using it to like examine a bunch of like my own commenters can't relate to
that because they don't have souls right it's they're not real human beings they're not really
like that's when when they say shit like that it's way worse because like i remember i started doing
some writing stuff like a couple years ago and like i was like really like putting my own stat
and someone's like oh can i can i look at your work i want to i want to you know like i write
stuff too i want to help you i'm like okay like yeah and like i've been i wrote like one thing
like a week ago it's the first thing i ever wrote he just came back like this shit this is all
shit is fucking awful like why are you even trying and like that's stung like shit because like he
came in like trying to be helpful and then just like shit on it with like reckless abandon and yeah
that's actually really clever and sinister like yeah if i really hated someone if somebody like
left a shit comment and they had videos on their channel i would go to their channel and i'd be like
hey can i do you mind if i watch some videos i think you have a lot of potential maybe i could
watch your videos and i would wait for like a week and i'd come back and i'd fucking destroy
every single fucking thing about their lives and they would die the worst thing that ever happened
to me with with something like that is like there was this guy who was my biggest patron for a year
and a half he would give me a hundred dollars of video wow and and and he did that for like a year
and a half and it took me a year and a half to realize he actually hated me and was trying to
like make me depressed and he gave me like a thousand dollars yeah like and we it eventually
boiled down to this huge fucking argument whoa um when okay that guy is actually psychotic
wow he is dude that's insane he got you tom he he gave you a thousand dollars he sure he sure got
you man hey hey what do you say in this final confrontation go to patreon.com by all means if
you think i'm the worst guy ever please patreon.com slash did you direct all hate comments to the
patreon exclusive section you will ruin my life all right what did he say what was his argument at
the end of that there was this posse of kids who like hung around me and like laughed at every stupid
joke i made and other kids were like dude they're just mocking you who cares there's this group of
people around here who pretend to love me it's great i don't feel offended at all that's like
the internet equivalent of wimp low like they trained him wrong as a joke yeah yeah money is gonna
destroy you yeah by the way if you want a little money no problems right make make comments like i
love you your videos are amazing those are always good yeah right those comments are always nice i
like well sometimes just just like uh yeah um oh shit i forgot what i was gonna say could you
say your thing yeah tom what what happened at the end of that i mean it was it was like what happened
is he gave me a bunch of money for a while then stopped and then we were friends did we just continue
like at that point it like sharply declined in terms of like being friendly but at that point i
assumed he was my friend because it's been like almost a year and it just like constant prodding
because like he knew that i'd like you know like i'm i'm i'd have like intermittent depression
and stuff and he would play off of that and like just like say a bunch of shit and like do a bunch
of things what is this guy a pickup artist trying to get in your pants is he negging you hey there's
nothing wrong with being a sociopath pickup artist it's the right way to live let's not let's not
throw stones at that you know it's it's funny what davu was saying and i guess his ultimate point
was like if you're passionate then it matters more and i guess i've always been passionate but like
i back in the day got even more mad at like negative comments than i do now like i've never
never been able to take criticism i've always been passionate i've not always been confident
there wasn't always individual pieces of art that i put a lot of work into and thought were good
i don't i don't have the ability to delusionally think my content is better than it is you know
it's it's almost funny because before i started on youtube i didn't really have a response to
everything anyone would say at me i do now people can say anything they want about me and i'll
have i don't know like a bunch of shit i can regurgitate that of and it's always correct you
know it's funny how it's always correct i don't even plan that it just happens that way anyway this
is going on really long does anybody have any we should we should list any more points we have
i still have a few i still have a few that okay let's let's get to those let's get to that well
people who think that they're being cute or endearing by insulting me you're not you don't
know me like that you're not my fucking friend you don't get to insult me um let's see uh comments
about my appearance uh uh okay always irrelevant always a little bit hurtful and you would never
fucking say it to my face or you i would strangle you and kill you so don't fucking say it on the
internet because you wouldn't say it i gotta jump in on that too man because again obviously i get
it all the fucking time with the beard and like here's the like okay sometimes people joke about
the beard and sometimes it can be funny and i don't i don't mind being like kind of a meme
you know like on some level like kind of like anthony fantano he's bald and people call him a
melon and it's funny and he's in on the joke and he clearly appreciates that joke because it came
from a funny place where it was like someone some artist he reviewed like negatively like legitimately
called him a melon as it like like i'm all angry at him yeah and so people picked up on that and
started calling him that and it's funny and he likes it and there's certain memes and stuff
that are that can be fun obviously i look like a fucking weirdo i appreciate that and himself
aware of it and like and it can be funny to talk about but like if all you have to say is like uh
shave your face it's like dude i don't belong to you i am not i'm not here to look how you want
me to look if i was i wouldn't look like i i don't understand how people seem to think that
youtubers are so unself aware like we talk this this kind of goes back to the authorial intent
thing where i was saying that like people watch your videos and they somehow think that you don't
know what's in them you know like i'm a guy who writes intensely deeply analytical content
about shows i break down like visual aesthetics on a regular basis i know how i look you know
well yeah i'm a writer uh like how do you not how do you not get what that i like i have to edit
these videos i have to see myself on camera i know what my beard looks like i know what i look like
and the reason that i haven't changed it is either obviously a i don't care or b i like the way i
look and there's people who say things like one recently that just pissed me off so much i couldn't
stop thinking about it this this happens to be a lot so some people know how to phrase a comment
in just such a way that i that i just like i can't believe that they said it yeah and like and it
just burrows into my brain all day and based on the phrasing like if it gets to a nine out of ten
on the smug scale i ban it's like i'm gonna go i said on my on my on my final fantasy seven video
from like a year ago now or something yeah like i got so many like oh this guy he's just he's got
this big beard and he's got a hawaiian shirt i don't accidentally have a big beard in a hawaiian
shirt in that video i grew it because i wanted it and i put the shirt on because it looks cool
fuck you the comment that got to me so much though that was recent was like someone saying
i don't understand how he thinks that beard looks good he he should like beards are meant to be
taken care of they're not meant to just be grown have had god you're violating beard was all i could
think was why does he think that i grew this to look good why would like is that what we assume
everyone everyone's completely obsessed with their appearance and all they care about is looking
perfect at all times let me jump in real quick right there because i have a 10 out of 10 perfect
specimen of a man and the only comments i get on my appearance are to say how beautiful i am so you
made a video yeah where you deliberately looked shitty that's true for the message of the video
and i remember when i clicked on it when i clicked on growing the gun part one you said to me
name why you look like such a fucking scrub in this video right the very first thing i thought
was like what the fuck why is he look because i i remember i know what you look like i'd met you
and i was like did he like completely go downhill in the time since i last saw him and then the video
turns out is about you transforming and and i didn't leave that comment because i finished the video
and then i told you that i had thought that at first and then i and then later in the video it
was proven see yours he's applying several of the rules that we've educated you on in this thing
and i completely didn't see it coming yeah it was just like i saw you as like a nerd and then you
you evolved and i was like oh that's fucking genius because i was thinking about how shitty you
looked and now you look amazing and it's awesome like that's sometimes the point like i like that
i am this character who is this like weird crazy hobo who lives in a dungeon of anime posters
it's hilarious to me and if you watch my after dark channel that that comes through more because
i wear the sunglasses and do weird shit you know like like it's it's obvious but like that's why
i said comments about the beard will be deleted because like i i know i know everything you can
say about it i know what it looks like the reason the beard looks so shitty on camera by the way
is usually because if you actually saw it it yeah it's usually because of the lighting because
in order to make your face appear on camera when you're filming in the middle of the night
you have to light yourself really well and when all that light goes through all the the scraggly
part of my beard it looks really bad if you saw me in person it never looks like that it looks way
more full it looks completely together because i don't have a fucking halogen light blasting on me
when i'm when i'm doing it you know and people like people don't get that that you can film from
different angles and different lightings and everything makes it look different everything
will everything you do will make you look completely different and there's some videos that i've posted
where people will be like oh man you look like you lost weight and you look like uh like you
like you cleaned yourself up and literally all i did was wear a tighter shirt and film from a
downward angle with better lighting like right sometimes i don't have time to set all that up
you know and it's like i i wish people understood why i look the way i do but like all i can assure
you is that i know i know exactly what i look like in the video i edited it half of my career
is analyzing aesthetics it's interesting digi i'm learning something about the differences between
you and i because i'm the kind of guy who takes six months to make a video that will in no way
be worth the effort that's expanded on it to make sure i get all those little details perfect
whereas you take the obviously superior approach of being like well i'm not going to fucking put
the time in to get this done that's retarded no one in the world to do that there's no way i can
it's completely impractical videos that i do because like i i i have ideas for videos constantly
you know and sometimes there's like with that whole the video that was uh that was positive
reviews like here's positive reviews i've done the the only incentive for that video was not to
make a good video it was to make one at that moment right because i was about to make two very negative
reviews about very popular shows right after people have been saying that i've been getting
really negative with my videos and my most recent popular ones were negative videos so i thought
let's counterbalance this and draw attention to positive videos i've made it wouldn't have worked
if i posted it two weeks later it would have no point because i would already be done with the
negative videos and moving on so like the only incentive was how can i get a video out tonight
that proves that i've that i've made positive videos i don't have victor available to light me
well or shoot me with a nice camera because he's been working for all fucking week i don't have
i don't want to show off too much of my room because i'm planning to use parts of my room
for a different video and i don't want it to be shown before then i can't necessarily set up
everything to look good so let's just fucking turn on the camera and ramble and if i'm if i'm lucky
if if my fans are are fucking decent enough people then when i nicely ask them not to
fucking talk about my beard maybe they won't do it how wrong ever was i maybe all right jesse we're
let's let's move on to some of these other points okay i've been wanting to say this this whole
damn podcast oh hey you know i can be able to spend a little bit more i have a really minor
point that'll take one minute you shut your fucking face god damn it you people you can go after me
you people out there do not ever ever
use my full name or my real name ever don't do it you're not my friends you're not a person in
my life you don't know me like that my name is endless jess that's the name of my channel you
can call me that or one of my other 10 000 monikers you can call me drowning in footwear you
can call me the fucking horseshoe boy you can call me whatever the hell you want but jesse wood is for
my fucking friends jesse is for my friends and i can't even describe why exactly it makes my skin
crawl so much it feels like a violation it feels like rape like somebody is in my kitchen touching
my shit or messing around with my stuff it feels dirty don't do it do not call me by my real name
don't ever ever fucking do it jesse ever i i agree with you and i think that i think that it's
with in your case it's a little bit your fault and a lot our fault yeah yeah we're definitely
culpable because we always because we all called you jessie wood no one name to right seriously
have the entire umbrella even if it's a positive comment or a nice comment if you use my real name
i feel i feel raped and i don't respect you as a person and i don't like for the record jess
you have you like well i don't know if you did it in any of the videos that are still available
well yeah because when i started out i stupidly didn't know what i wanted to call myself yet yeah
a man makes mistakes you know in the in the uh the manly lessons to manhood video you're like
i'm jesse wood which is part of why that video doesn't exist anymore right but like yeah i but i
completely get where you're coming from because like well your username is i think the reason
that it happens with you is that a your old usernames were all difficult to use as names and
your you new username is so close to your real name that people just assume that that's just
what to use and sometimes we mean we want to describe like you as a person as distinct from all
the different subsets of you that exist it's like it's hard to describe but i i think endless jess
i think endless jessum rellis them all pretty well yeah which is why i've started calling you
i'm like a hannard people from mass effect okay i got my face name and that's republic
and i got my soul name and that's for my peeps and you ain't my reason i agree with you though
is that i get this sometimes where there's certain people who call me i don't even fucking call
you conrad i can't do it right it was weird no dude it's super weird to me because never
have i put out there that it was that i am conrad it's my you guys are my closest friends online
you all call me digi everyone online calls me digi my name is always digi bro it always is
there's never not the case when people but here's the thing here's why it bothers me because when
people call me conrad especially like with jessie i get that maybe they don't understand that you
don't like to be called that but with conrad 100 of the time it feels like they're trying to be sneaky
it feels like they're trying to say i know more about you and i'm like oh i i'm closer to the
truth creepy sentiment that i've looked into you yeah right because like you only would know that
if you were watching like either watching like interviews or something or you saw me in like a
google hangout because my real name is on my google plus account so like you saw me in a google
hangout and you saw that it was conrad or you saw my facebook or something you saw or you listen to
this podcast well yeah or yeah this particular podcast is only or and i i'm a little bit more
forgiving when it's on digi bros because of the fact that you called your name there yeah right
like me and victor will be on there and victor will call me conrad that's like i think context
it was ego raptor then it became erin because everyone right like everyone calls him erin now
because it it became normal and like i'm more okay with people calling me conrad in the comments
of digi bros because i'm like yeah okay i get called conrad here all the time and like and it
doesn't feel sneaky it's never felt like they're trying to say it's sneaky because like that's
like one of the things that that guy was talking about earlier did because at one point when we
were still like he's still being chummy he bought something off of me so i sent it to him and then
he would start calling me by my real name in all of my comments and then he would mention my hometown
all the time where i live oh hey it's on balan of michigan whatever there is an issue of context
to it i guess because yeah on digi bros your conrad because it's you and your brother and i get why
they'd call you that or like for me like if i went and did like stand up or i released a stand-up cd
i don't know if i'd call myself endless jess on stage i might or i might just let them call me
jessie would if in that case maybe but when i'm on my fucking youtube channel it's like my wrestler
name okay you don't walk up to see him punk and say hey phil you just don't do it he'll punch you
he'll beat you up and i'll beat you up i'll beat up everyone again yeah and and with someone like
cn punk that would absolutely be trying to be sneaky you're trying to be cheeky you're trying to say
i know more about you you know what other people i got i'm an insider i've got a funny thing here
it's just um i i my name nat is out there a little bit some people have called me that sometimes uh
they're calling me guy these days which is fine but when people bring up the name keg standard
it's like bro you need to knock that shit off we've all moved on from those days let's just
let's just move it along you can only have it you can only call him mate if you spell it n eight
that's right and you know i a keg standard isn't even me you know that's not me that was true that
that is this pony man my best friend no guys that yes his own that story when you call me conrad
it doesn't like what you're trying to say is i know more about you than other people but what
in like and i'm going to rape you is implied but yeah what it comes off to me is like creepy
and weird because you know that my other friends online call me digi and they're i like i like it
when i can tell why people know me by what they call me we're like in in my house everyone calls
me conrad but when i hear people call me digi it lets me know oh you know me from youtube you know
me from my life you know if my friend fucking trevor comments on my videos and says conrad you
piece of shit then that's okay because it's trevor and he he's uh you know like someone who knows me
as conrad but like when i go to conventions and someone walks up to me and goes hey digi i can
go okay this guy watches my channel that's why he knows who i am you know and that makes it a lot
easier for me to like contextualize how people know me if you walked up to me at a convention and
i didn't know who you were and you said hey conrad i'm gonna assume that we went to high school
together or something like i'm gonna be trying to figure out why do i know you don't do that shit
folks it's a matter of respect that's what it is jesse you got another i think that was actually one
time that somebody called me by my real yeah online sometime there's only one maybe they were just
talking about that one luxury brand louis of dawn yes which is gives real name all right jesse
next one well davoo had one oh he did yeah okay blame yourself if they get mad don't think don't
psychoanalyze them to think that the youtuber is having a psychoanalysis yeah yeah i got that
string of emails for like a week from that guy who's trying to psychoanalyze me in my inbox oh yeah
yeah oh yeah i remember that that was amazing right because i remember that guy didn't he have a
really fandom as i recall yeah didn't he have a really edgy uh profile yeah he did he did it was
awesome that guy was just like it was like these long unbroken paragraphs that guy was a walking
fedora me breaks that were just that were just him going like tom the way you've left the fandom
proves that you you're just uh you've you've grown more distant and sensitive as a person
oh man that was amazing like even professional ecologists you can fire them and not let them
constantly right well what's your escape from these people there is nothing so so that commenter guy
who i was reading from before who was commenting on jesse he made another one he said your words
sound like those of a hurt person oh yeah i remember that one and i don't think my and get this oh
and i don't this is like the most egregious of this particular thing ever yeah and i don't think
i don't think my words are the thing that hurt you oh god shut up i think i think i think you're
responding to something or someone else with your bitter words i'm sorry jess and i wish you the best
and you know and you know after i dane after i dane to lower myself and do him the favor of
explaining to him in seven paragraphs why he's a fucking piece of shit he still has the nerve to
not even take any of it in and just reject all of it with some bullshit psycho analysis to try to
cop out of it and back out with his tail tucked between his legs he's a coward they're all fucking
cowards who don't want to accept what that is when they've made a mistake that's intellectual
cowardice he's looking for any excuse to not accept the argument so that's that's what that is
whether he can't or he just won't that's what it is and i'll okay jesse beat him up next one um
okay i uh i don't have any much more rules written down but i want to talk about one
commenter specifically from a recent episode of this podcast and i'm not gonna i'm not gonna go
off on them but i'm gonna illustrate a couple of things we talked about so it was during the
dark souls race and i was making my anita sulkeesian jokes my legendary hilarious anita sulkeesian
jokes right the the most important character jesse's ever created yeah and and some guy was like
uh those jokes ruin the whole thing anita sulkeesian is not funny now i have two complaints with that
sentiment the first complaint is first of all motherfucker i am the expert on funny i know it's
funny and you don't and you can't say that something is not funny when everyone else in the call
on the podcast was laughing uproariously at it the whole that's right that's pretty much defeats it
right there but the but the second issue that i have with it is that it speaks to what we talked
about early earlier with misunderstanding my intent this guy thought that anita sulkeesian
was not funny because he was viewing the joke through the lens of well this guy's making fun of
anita sarkeesian and he's making fun of social justice and that's been done to death and its
old hat and i totally get that but it's a misunderstanding of my intent and my intent
is what makes the joke funny because i'm not doing it to shit on social justice warriors
i'm doing it because i have a fondness for anita sarkeesian i think she's hilarious it's true
and and and my character anita sulkeesian first of all anita sulkeesian has been my dark souls
character since 2011 she's been with me on these journeys the whole time i have more of an attachment
to her than any other character i could have possibly made so it's not just me making fun of
social justice warriors it's funny because she's my girl and she's just she exists in dark souls
she hates men she is immune to poison and is fucking funny yeah i mean that the it's got nothing
it's got nothing to do with me pushing any kind of agenda it's just a funny thing that i made like
five years ago and i stuck with it because i like her anita sulkeesian video from the blue glow
like if you haven't seen it it's amazing because i mean even if it was just a joke on social justice
warriors what is the joke the joke is that she is immune to toxic which means that you actually
made a character and put all of the stats into immunity so that you could run around a toxic
environment and it wouldn't affect you and you have gone out of your way to make this makes the
game harder killing all of the male in a race no less that's hilarious yeah in the middle of a race
he went out of his way and still beat my time by the way by a landslide yeah he he still rang
two bells before i rang one while taking time out of his day to murder all of the male npcs
and then pose proudly after doing it that shit was hilarious the fact that it's anita sulkeesian
is a very clever pun but the fact that it's a joke on her is not why it's funny it's a
fucking well-delivered joke you did it perfectly and not appreciating that just because you're
like you know but it's i'm sick of anita's yeah whatever dude it's funny that's why we laughed
at it and the guy clearly didn't think about why it was like nobody he clearly just thought it was
uh it's an anita nobody is more sick look at the crap nobody is more sick of that joke than me
but the fact that i'm so sick of it makes it even funnier to me when i do it right yeah because
yeah all right well well are we done have you wrapped it up i guess we've wrapped it up i could
go all day on this topic we could go all day but people i've got an undertale video to finish
it's coming what are these days i just want to say i'm just gonna end why i leave comment why
i like comments because i don't even get this mysterious elusive discussion that digi always
talks about i don't think anyone can really contribute much since i'm the one who put days
into thinking about it you know um i don't almost never do i watch an analysis and have
much else to add on to it myself i leave comments up because it helps me gauge the reaction of a
video i want to know not only how many people decided to watch it but how many people had a
some sort of verbal reaction to it right that's what i like and i just think that
a comment that doesn't amuse me isn't very useful if it doesn't seem like it's going to
amuse anyone else it does it's not worth existing you know and i'm making the world a better place
by deleting it yeah i'm with you there i don't i don't only leave comments open just for like good
discussion i like to me it it signifies that people are engaging with the content because like
if all i had was views and all i had was likes i don't know what kind of views those are if a
video gets a hundred thousand views and no comments then it's like did people even really care or
engage with the content or people just like what were they thinking when they watched it so like
the comments allow me to know that like yeah people are people give some level of a shit about what
i just made you know and uh and so yeah no matter what the comments are it's nice when i get a lot
of them and that's always a good like okay this is something that people really cared about or it
resonated with them you know even with something like the erased video if i didn't have so many
dumb comments having a bunch of negative ones at least tells me that the video was something that
inspired people to feel away you know like it gave them feelings whether they were positive or negative
but when yeah those kind of comments let you know you know what people are wanting which you could
throw that away if you want but at least it's information yeah it's the dirty side of it all
your all your bitching does have an influence on us whether we do specifically what you said or
not we never do specifically what you said but we at least with me i do it's a tangible detail right
it is it is like i'm i've been making like people don't understand specifically around what people
are going to misunderstand yeah a lot of people don't like they'll they'll say that they didn't
like the video and then they'll try to explain why and it's probably like often it's not really that
like they don't completely get what even like it's it's kind of like when the the film crit
hold tangible details thing where he talked about how people will blame the hair color of the actor
for the fact that the the performance wasn't good when if it's a good movie and they do a good
performance then you'll accept a character even if they don't look like how you thought they were
supposed to right like with with my videos sometimes like with the erased one i've gotten a
lot of complaints that just kind of missed the point of what i was trying to do and like
so they're not helpful they're not helpful that they're negative but constructive criticism is
really rare remember that right but like you know there are times where i i will just look at the
fact that no one got it and that can inform me now with that particular video i knew people
weren't going to get it and i didn't care like i wanted that video to be what it was and i knew
it would have a negative reaction but there have been times in the past like with my zanko no terror
video which is kind of similar to that one where there was a lot of negative reaction to it that
i didn't expect and it made me realize that i had written the video wrong not for the reasons
necessarily that people responded to like people would say this and that and get mad at me but what
i realized when i assessed like okay this video is making a lot of people mad why and then i realized
why and i didn't do that anymore that's why you should talk only about your own opinions don't
try to represent a fictional rule book because that will help us learn from your opinions
faster that's a very good point okay let's wrap it up but before we go i oh given you want to say
something yeah i was just gonna say um that uh my uh comments are uh the best by the way does
leave the objectively best comments of anybody as you can see on his twitter if you follow not
the comments that i leave i mean that's that's true but also the comments on my videos oh i see
because i i am the most likable guy that's true and i make the most likable videos over at
youtube.com slash patreon.com slash ben saint yeah your comments are like just confused most of the
time it seems like they're just like it's not his hypocrite i'm giving take share hypocrite
it doesn't offend people so long as you don't run a kickstarter you'll never get a contingent of
haters that's that's true okay now before we go i have one announcement i want to make which is just
i am officially i'm putting out a bounty on the pcp mascot because i don't know who the fuck that is
and it's been bothering the fuck out of me i think it might be Saito from bakuman i don't know but i'm
telling you if anybody can find that out leave a comment whoever is the earliest comment you know
well we will give you some sort of reward you know don't comment it's Saito from bakuman give us
proof yeah there needs to be like a contest who can leave the best least horrible comment the
the comment that is good yeah we've good we'll we'll reference it in the next thing the best
comment on the video that too and now find me that page people and you'll get some sort of reward
we'll figure it out so go ahead and do that that will be the best comment it will be the best
automatic that's a meaningful comment remember everyone the true point of all this is just you
should suck my dick and if you don't want to not be on the moon good a good comment and
geon gurren lagoon
i let everybody say goodbye
yeah yeah yeah uh
my dick i'm
i don't want to do it
oh
what the hell is wrong with me i'm supposed to be making money i'm supposed to be creating
funny think that the people gladly will pay for artistic genius that's what they
came for instead i'm tweeting hashtag repeating that's why there's no
weed and holes in the ceiling yeah it's quite the burden it's a hard knock life being a genius