Hello, everybody, and welcome to another clusterfuck of an episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am your host today, Tom Oliver, and we got a host of degenerates with us to talk about whatever the fuck comes up from our brain matters.
We got Digibro.
I'm alive for you. I'm awake because of you.
I'm flattered. We got Mage.
Pizza Hut, Pizza Hut, Kentucky Pie Chicken, Pizza Hut, Pizza Hut, Pizza Hut, Kentucky Pie Chicken, Pizza Hut McDonald's, McDonald's, Big Donald's, Big McDonald's, Pizza Hut McDonald's.
We're on endless war for the bit there, and then a deviated drastically.
I just always.
To get us back on track, we have Munchy with tiny hats.
Whoa, heaven let your light shine down.
We have Nate.
I'm at the Pizza Hut. I'm at the Taco Bell. I'm at the combination Pizza Hut and Taco Bell. That's me.
My favorite.
And of course, the one, the only, the yang-gang himself, Ben Zayn.
We've got the American Jesus. See him on the interstate.
We've got the American Jesus. He'll ever whelming millions every day. You guys like bad religion?
Ben, Ben, how's it feel to be on the cutting edge of political thought, Ben? How's it feel to be on the fucking, on the forefront?
It's exhilarating, Munchie. Exhilarating.
Titillating. Listen, you just, you just, you know, you know, blind yourself for the aesthetic, you know,
if the Mac parallels, walk up to a nearby cliff edge and just spout your fucking drivel for all the
pros to waddle up in here every single day. And soon enough, you're gonna be more powerful than the president.
Here's the thing. Thing about bad religion, I realize, is it's basically Linkin Park in the sense that it is like purely,
it is pure, it trades on pure emotionality over any like, like real, only, only the villain,
only the villain that is being railed against is just like, you know, society, bad politicians, you know,
evil, general evils of society, capitalism and all that, you know, rich people, instead of with Linkin Park, it's just teen angst,
just general angst. So once you hit your 20s, you just switch over? I like that better. Ben, you're so fucking killer, poor dude.
You just love being a teen. You love hating your parents. You love rebelling against the system. You're the most like killer core
person on earth. Why would I, why would you ever stop? Why would you ever want to grow out of it? Every, every single, like,
you know what, every single thought you have, I think that's an interesting thought. Then I, then I weave it back into the
overall Benson narrative. And I think, oh, this is actually like, you know, extremely in character. There's no
deviation. It sounds like every step that Ben takes is another mistake to you.
Ben, when we were young, we listened to Bad Religion, Alien, Ant Farm, obviously you led because you were the older
one. My friend, you remember my friend, Stefan. There are people who listen to Alien, Ant Farm. Absolutely. Well, let me
tell you about it. Pretty much just that one single. Any, are you okay? Right? Yeah, you're okay. You're okay. Now,
Ben, do you remember?
Well, whatever. It's good. It's a good cover. I think they're both good in different ways. But Ben, remember when we were
young? My friend, Stefan, made me, he burned me a CD of a bunch of Bad Religion music and like a couple other
things, including that Alien, Ant Farm cover. Yep. Just to introduce me to his favorite band and I listened to it over
and over and over again. Ben, I remember there was a time, I briefly, that played on the air and I remember you
said, uh, that's my favorite band. That's my favorite band right there. What, Alien, Ant Farm? Yeah. Yeah, that was a brief
period. Yeah, dude, absolutely. Alien, Ant Farm was never my favorite band. And I remember, okay, this is why I
think that, because I remember a brief episode where I said, hey, Ben, I've got, I've got a surprise for you. I've got a
secret to tell you, Ben. No, no. And it's that, guess what my favorite band also is? Your unrelated reasons. It's Alien, Ant
Farm, dude. And the rage, Ben, the rage at the fact that I would dare insist that your favorite band was also my
favorite band, you know, was enough to shatter galaxies. It exploded. I, I don't, the blows rained down on me from
all. I believe both of you. I believe that that wasn't Ben's favorite band and that he was that mad anyway.
I think it should be that mad at anyone whose favorite band is Alien, Ant Farm.
Yeah. All right, that's fair. Okay. All right. Yeah, good times. But then I grew up in and the cure became my favorite
band. Yeah. Okay. Really? Yeah. What an amazing musical history you guys have. Mine was disturbed for a very long
while. Oh, that's really, that makes a total sense to me weirdly. Just like, because all their songs are, they have the
same kind of underlying aesthetic as the kind of stuff you like that like, I'm going to explode and murder everyone around
me. No, no, mommy, don't do it again. Don't do it again. I'll be a good boy. I'll be a good boy. You know, early musical
taste is very incredible. So I mean, it seems totally natural that just when you're young, whatever music is around
will like the first shit you hear will just be your favorite. I remember the first time I realized music was
good was listening to the cure on someone CD at Boy Scout Camp. And I was like, entranced. I was like, whoa, is that music? I don't
fucking get it. But now I do get it. This is like good.
The reason why is because this was before Lime Wire, like back when you first got it. So you weren't spoiled for choice yet.
You couldn't just go on Lime Wire and find 10 billion songs. Like the world is at my fingertips. I mean, even today,
whatever the kid, like the first song he listens to and likes, he'll be like, well, that's my favorite song. Therefore, whatever's
popular will just be somebody's favorite.
I just remembered I think the reason why the reason why Stefan burned me that CD was because I brought it up to him because I
had heard some bad religion. So there was like one bad religion song on the soundtrack to Tony Hawk's Pro Skater
2. And I was like, I like that song. And I talked to him and he's like, oh, yeah, I know that band. I'll burn you some, some, some
tunes from that's nice. And I was like, cool. What a champ. Yeah, friends are cool. Shout out to Stefan. What a good guy. Shout out to
Stefan.
So is Stefan Molyneux?
Rest in peace.
Every day, I'm robbed of having this fucking teen musical experience, because I'm convinced that like, if you're above
30, you don't know what like headphones are. Because every single day, I have the same ritual. I go downstairs. I'm trying
to mind my own business. I'm just trying to get in and out of the kitchen as fast as possible before the mobs start
to spawn. But you know, it's like when you run into like a mob of spawning, you just try and raid the chest for all the
cookies and all the watermelon seeds. And then of course, the skeleton start to spawn in rows of three. I try and do that
but with scrambled eggs instead of cookies. So I sprint downstairs, usually trying to do this. Like I debate doing the
Super Mario 64 and long jump down the stairs and break all my bones. Every single day I get closer and closer to doing it.
And I'm going to die that way, I guarantee you. Anyway, I'm downstairs. And then I have my headphones in, you know, listening to
music, you know, thrashing about a little bit. And then every single day, every single moment when I have my headphones
in, people just try and talk to me. And it's like, guys, listen, I understand. I understand I'm your son, you want to speak
to me. Say to me, hey, let's speak now. And then I'll take off my headphones. Just stop. I'm always like this. Learn
my routine, learn how I am. Please, I beg you, I just want to be undisturbed. And then when I take them off, I'm not even
spoken to. Mom, I hate, I hate my parents. I'm gonna fucking, I'm gonna listen to bad romance to load up that CD
bin.
Would you like to see how it feels, mommy? Here it comes.
Have you guys heard of the band tattoo? TATU?
TATU.
My sister loved that band.
Two girls and two sisters?
I don't remember there.
No, it's too hot Russians who make out and shit.
Maybe they're also sisters.
That was the whole point was that they make out.
Yeah, I think I'm confusing them with another like sister duo.
I don't think they were sisters. But yeah, they had the whole lesbian thing on. Like, I really liked their music before they
started singing in English. And there was this one song I don't even remember what it was called. But I like my sister had
a CD and I just played like the first song on loop for hours. And then I remember her coming into my room all
angry. It's like, can't you stop listening to that same song? It's depressing as shit. And me, me not understanding Russian
was like, oh, okay.
Me, an intellectual.
Another band.
Me, an intellectual committing suicide.
Another band that really shaped my life. Like, I have only been to one concert. It was of this band, the band Lordy actually
listened to their songs yesterday and it was like, oh, the good old times. And I had a Lord Lordy. Yeah, I'm sending in the chat.
The image of Lordy is, are you familiar with guar?
They're, yeah, they're the ones that wear like the rubber.
I had the biggest question the lead singer.
Guar is the ones that wear like the rubber like monster costumes.
Yes. Yeah, Lordy also does that, except that they're the like the the Christian version.
That sounds incredibly killer.
Look at the second chat, the gross disgusting chat.
This is crazy.
That I had, I had a huge crush now.
Whoa, this is the sickest shit.
Dude, this is just steam steam powered giraffe.
Wait, wait, wait. Yeah, kind of.
By the way, which one did you like?
Which one did you like?
The lead singer.
The one in the middle.
Okay, like in the makeup around me.
And I don't know how he looks out of the makeup.
Yeah, yeah, oh my God, the face of the knee.
Oh my God, the severed face on his kneecap.
That's fucking sick.
Look at his belt buckle.
It's another face with a bit with a severed face.
You know, mage makes a lot more sense now.
I'm not going to lie.
Like this explains a lot.
Oh, look at the artistry on that, though.
You know, this is super sick.
It was a super sick.
It's pretty sick.
I'm all about it.
You know, this guy should be in Halloween too, mage.
Don't forget to include him.
I'm still waiting for it to come out.
The first the first bands that I got into,
my friend was burning me CDs with like
Demo Borgia and Children of Bodom and Shakespeare.
He was super into metal.
And that's how I got into it.
I was I was I was part of the goth click in my high school.
But I was like, I was just kind of a hanger on like I had,
you know, had like one pair of fucking hot topic trap pants.
You know, I had some I had black t-shirts.
I had long hair pants, Ben.
Trip pants, not TRIPP trip.
OK, yeah, trip, you know, yeah, with like the bondage rings
and all the zippers and shit.
I had one pair of of acid blue trip.
What? Oh, you got to go classic black.
No, man, I had the blue and black checkered pattern, you know,
and like they that's not what was great about them was that.
Well, no, they were more like punk, like a neo goth or something.
Whatever, they came from hot topic.
Who gives a shit? Right.
What was great about them is I wore them to every convention
because they had just these fucking insanely massive pockets.
And it was like having two mobile purses on your.
You could steal everything.
No one would know.
Yeah, well, like one time was my friend, Josh, used to wear
trip exclusively wore a pair of black trip pants.
And we went to see a movie one time and he had put like a whole
two liter of Mountain Dew in like a whole box of KFC in one pocket.
Dude, imagine like imagine the marshal potential there.
But you do like a spinning roundhouse kick and explode an entire
Mountain Dew container on someone's fucking face.
It was for acid damage.
You always have to carry all this bullshit, like all the extra schedules
and maps and shit. And so I would just have.
Yeah, I just I just I just want to paint a picture of my click.
So I was in this goth click, but I was more of a hanger on.
I didn't go to like concerts or anything there.
There were like two there were like two guys who were sort of the de facto
like top dogs and everyone else.
And like those guys like found bands.
Those guys went to concerts.
Those guys were hard.
They had like a ton of fucking like that.
I'm impressed that your fucking goth click actually like did things
because at my school, the goth click was just a bunch of stoners who did nothing.
Not all of them, but a few of them did.
And so their music, their musical tastes kind of trickled down.
Right. And Steph.
Stefan was in it, too.
My other friend who and he he had the pants.
He didn't go to like concerts, but he was he would he found me anyway.
They're their musical their musical discovery is all trickled down.
And so I was I was given like, yeah, children of Bodum and Cradle of Filth and stuff.
And I was like, yeah, well, I guess this is what I like now.
Dark time for music.
That was yeah.
Yeah, I think it was the worst show ever.
My they are the worst band ever.
One time my friends were over in my basement playing Dungeons and Dragons
or procrastinating and not playing Dungeons and Dragons just fucking around
shame instead of playing and someone put on a Cradle of Filth album
and our dad came down and I with with disdain in his voice.
He asked it was really funny.
He asked, like, oh, how did he say it?
It was like, hmm, so what are you listening to?
Songs about devil worship?
And I was like, yeah, I like sputtered with rage.
Don't fucking.
What? No.
Satan's misunderstood, dad.
You will never get it.
Basically. And he never and he never did.
Does have some songs about devil worship.
They absolutely do.
At one hundred percent.
It was wrong.
But he was uncool about it.
It's really funny because at that point in history,
my mom was way into black metal, specifically because it's about devil worship.
Our dad likes smooth jazz.
James Taylor, James.
Yeah, James Taylor, who I have.
I have come to appreciate some of the stuff that our dad liked.
Carolina on my mind.
Absolute banger.
Absolute banger of a song.
I've come I've come to love James Taylor.
I've come to love Genesis.
Yeah. And so that was all good.
However, he did have a habit of putting on like very, very dull,
like, on basically unlistnable, like smooth jazz, like medleys.
Well, that was just the anime study music of his generation.
He said it pretty much.
Chill beats to study too. Yeah.
It's true.
But I don't like it.
Me neither.
Hey, by the way, speaking of bad shows, I know this is a bit.
I think this is a bit of a cliche, but it's just that my buddy, John,
once went to a a Dragon Force concert and said it was like the dullest
piece of shit show I had ever been to.
I know exactly.
No, they're not slow, not because I've seen them twice.
And the first time it was early in the day because they were like the first
band at Oz Fest, and it was actually great.
They played all their songs accurately.
They had a couple of trampolines they're bouncing off of and shit.
It was cool as fuck.
So then they headlined a show and me and my brother Victor, because Victor is
a biggest fucking Dragon Force fan in the world at the time.
It was his favorite band is all he listened to.
We saw them live and they were all clearly fucked up.
Like, OK, OK, in different ways.
Like the singer was drunk.
The guitarist was on was seemed to be on Coke or something.
And then like one guy is like on speed.
Like they're all on different drugs.
And they sound like they're all on different drugs.
Like everybody's playing their parts wrong.
And so they sounded like shit to the fucking.
OK, the drummer just seemed like he was playing a blast beat nonstop
with no thought like he was just like, oh, this is what the drums are.
The guitarists were like playing the wrong parts at time.
And I swear to God, there was one part where one of the guitarists, Sam
Topman, was like playing the wrong solo.
And I think somebody was like trying to tell him.
And I saw him mouth to the guy.
They all sound the same.
In many ways, the guitarists said that.
Yes. And like the singer kept like throwing water onto the crowd and shit.
And he just seemed like pissed off for some reason.
Dude, they're getting too hot, getting fizzled.
Dude, it was a miserable show.
I literally deleted all their music off my computer after that show.
I was like, how old were you, how old were you like 18?
Yeah, OK, OK.
The illusion was shattered.
That's rough. I mean, I guess I guess touring will take a toll on you after a while.
I well, I've heard a lot of stories about the fact that they suck live.
And I think it's just because they do a lot of drugs.
Like definitely possible, because they like when when I saw them earlier
in the day, they were fine, because they hadn't started drinking yet.
And like at that that Ozfest, I met the two guitarists, because they were
just kind of wandering around, talking to random people.
And they were both of them are completely incomprehensible,
because I don't know if you know, but Dragon Force is a super group
and they're all from different countries and they all have no fucking idea.
All right. So they come over.
Is that Chinese guy who like actually Chinese?
Or is he? Yeah, he's actually Chinese and sick.
And the other guitarist is like just British and they're but they were both
sloshed because like we saw them somewhat after their show
and they were coming up to us, telling us how there is two Catholic girls
who they were trying to fuck because they were really hot.
But they're like they're both neither of them.
I think they're both virgins and they were like trying to pitch to us
this dilemma of like, should we fuck the hot girls we already have?
Who might not put out or should we go hunting for new hot girls?
But this came out like, yeah, well, we got this whole fucking bitches.
Like they're totally sloshed, incomprehensible.
Wait, wait, OK.
So he was describing to this to you a random fan asking for your advice
on which hot girls people it was me and Victor and my cousin, Boyd.
And like they had come to us after talking to another group of random people.
Like they were making fun of this.
Consensus, they were like an opinion.
They were yelling this out on stage or they were.
No, they're just walking around and this is like a huge festival as a Ozfest show.
So like there's, you know, food stalls and shit.
And they're just like walking around the stall area talking to random people.
And like there we came up to them because we had seen them talking
to these other two guys and they were making fun of this dude
because he was wearing this shirt for like a Christian hardcore band
that was at the show and POD.
No, POD is not a hardcore band.
God damn it.
Anyway, they were making fun of it because it had like a dinosaur on it.
And they were like, doesn't isn't dinosaurs evolution?
I can't have that on a Christian band.
And like, OK, it was funny.
Then and then after the last show, because the headliner I think was Slipknot,
after that show, we're leaving the pit and the two guys are just like kind of
standing at the entrance of the pit, like high-fiving people as they walk out.
And they said to us, we fucked those two girls.
They were awful. Yeah, all right.
OK, makes sense. Makes sense.
Virgins. It's terrible. No, that's great.
So, yeah, after that show, I was like, I wonder how the girls felt about it.
And we never we never got to hear their side.
I'm sure they were fucking terrible, too.
They're both shitfaced.
Like they probably whiskey dick out the fucking ass.
But yeah, it was like after that show, I was like, oh, Dragon Force
are so cool, we got to meet them and stuff.
That is the second time never listening to this band again.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. All right.
Well, that's a fascinating story.
Yeah, I can't believe that they were so forthcoming with with asking
just random people up.
But it's so cool that they were that they were just walking around
seemingly aimlessly begging for advice.
Who's going to criticize them?
Who's going to be like, too much information, Mr.
Dragon Force, man?
I mean, it was such a.
I wish he was fucking me instead.
It was legendary in particular
because it was the two guitarists who like, you know, they like stand back
to back and play guitars on stage and shit.
You just have the sense that like they've just become this power duo
who doesn't just hangs out and tries to fuck girls together.
I imagine they did it in front of each other, like going by the way
the story is playing out.
It had to be all in the same place.
Thank goodness.
I mean, or that reminds me of the time that I met X celebrity
at a grocery store in Los Angeles.
Tom Cruise, I told him how cool it was to meet him in person.
But I didn't want to be a douche
and bother him and ask for photos for anything.
He said, oh, like you're doing now.
I was taken aback.
And all I could say was, huh?
And he kept cutting me off, going, huh, huh, huh?
And closing his hands in front of my face.
I walked away and continued with my shopping and heard him chuckle as I walked off.
When I came to pay for my stuff up front,
I saw him try to walk out of the doors with like 15 milky ways in his ass.
Has anyone put a stop to this?
The girl at the counter was very nice about it and professional.
And she was like, sir, we need to pay for those first.
But first he kept pretending to be tired and not hear her,
but eventually turned back around and brought them to the counter.
When she took one of the bars and started scanning it multiple times,
he stopped her and told her to scan individually to prevent electrical interference.
He said and turned around and winked at me.
I didn't even think that's a word.
After he scanned each bar and put them in a bag and started to say the price,
he kept interrupting her.
He's laughing.
He's just laughing.
At a copy pasta.
I'm sure he's read a hundred times.
Oh, it's one of the best.
It's one of the best.
All right, that's it.
I'm done.
That's a great story, though.
Tom Cruise, sorry, we had a bad first meeting.
Was it Tom Cruise?
I thought it was.
Apparently, the origin is Flying Lotus, whoever that is.
I don't know who that is.
I've heard it with music, man, I think.
No, electronic musician, Flying Lotus.
He's a he just did a music video that was made by Shinichiro Watanabe.
Oh, sick.
Yeah.
And he's the guy who who I wrapped over in my Shintaro Kago video.
That was a flying lotus song because he had a cover.
Meeting celebs at fucking in a.k.a.
real celebs or fake celebs, E celebs is always a magical experience.
It's always the highlight of cons.
We see them, you know, outside of the smoke and mirrors game
at the console playing, just walking around, maybe being a hot dog
or a pretzel with cheese sauce, just walking around and you know
that you can engage them at any time.
Are you among them, doctor?
Well, who literally feel that way about you.
That's true.
So then I would initially imagine actually and expo, not the legendary
expo, but last an expo was particularly weird because I was like stopped
more like vastly more so than one would think.
Like very often, like very often, like I think like seven times a day.
That's a lot.
I know for fucking little old me.
So it was extremely weird.
It was extremely weird to be in that scenario because from my perspective,
it's not as though like I'm I have like a panel or like, you know,
I'm an anime guru or man.
Your face isn't even online that much comparatively speaking.
Yeah, that's also another thing to think about that a lot of times people.
I don't know what people like imagine me as.
Maybe they imagine me as my curvy avatar or something like that.
I guess your image is pretty powerful, though.
Like people are aware of what you look like.
Yeah, what were you wearing?
Were you in like a pizza jumpsuit?
Because I was definitely I was I was in the pizza jumpsuit.
One of the days I was I was in the curvy shirt.
I was in my iconic wear.
So that's OK. Good.
I'm so happy people don't know how I look like.
Yeah, that's a plus.
I'm terrified of people stopping me in the middle of a street being high mage.
And I I I'm spooked.
Well, you got to try it.
Well, it's awesome with that.
No, I'm scared.
I got scared.
Well, how are they going to they're going to praise you?
Are you like, oh, I mean, the thing about it is
once you're in that position, you cannot go back.
So like, you know, I get being cautious about it.
And frankly, I mean, I don't know, I've been listening a little bit to like
with this like James Charles shit going on or whatever.
I don't know, just for whatever reason,
I've been looking back at like a couple of like fucking like PewDiePie.
Like what is it?
The controversy memes.
And there was one about, I don't know, like foosie tube or something.
Whatever point was like PewDiePie was just saying like, yeah,
I fucking hate being in public.
It's the worst.
And I'm like, make make sense.
Probably gets harassed like a lot every time he's in public.
So you would be getting stopped everywhere, I would imagine.
And I know he's like, obviously the far reach,
like the most convenient stuff.
I enjoy it at a convention because you're going there.
You're kind of there for that, yeah.
And like if it happens randomly every once in a while,
like at my level of fame, it's exciting because it's like, wow,
people in the place I live know who I am.
That's cool.
And it's only happened like three times.
Well, maybe like five times.
Like, but yeah, it's it's I've been most of it was in Rochester.
Weirdly, like I would get one guy recognized.
We had a grocery store at a theme park and at the mall.
Like I think those are the convention there, right?
Did they have an anime convention?
Yeah, and I did the convention.
And, you know, obviously people knew who I was at the con.
But like I had never been stopped anywhere in Virginia Beach before.
But in Rochester, it was like a few times.
And like it's always like, wow, I feel like a walking legend, you know,
but like, yeah, yeah, it would very easily cross a threshold.
If it was happening even once a week, I would get right.
Right.
So with PewDiePie, it's got to be daily.
And none of us have really gotten to that point or even close.
So I mean, yeah, and like when you like the things like I'm two of my own
own or anything, it wasn't a convention, which vastly increases the odds.
But even sure, of course, still though.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, I should like VidCon where people are straight up in danger
because crowds are swarming to such ridiculous degrees.
Videos of VidCon are fucking crazy, dude.
They're like literal like swarms of dude.
OK, because it's it's totally dystopian.
It's it's fucking crazy seeing like a crowd of people all with their phones out,
circled or like surrounding Casey Neistat, all like with video cameras
about their head to vlog seeing Casey Neistat in the exact same experience
that all of these other like hundreds of people are doing.
So this person's vlog, if you're vlogging that moment, you're just like a fucking
like a complete sheep.
You have no agency whatsoever.
Just it is fascinating exact same fucking thing.
Things like that, things like that really seem to me to like make me believe
not only that like human beings are complete like sheep, but it's specifically
that like, oh my God, like my fellow human beings would absolutely like
trample me and tear me apart for the sake of like some small gain of their own.
I mean, not to that degree, but I was just thinking about this like yesterday
and I want to talk about it, that yeah, it fascinates me.
The level people will go to to just like touch fame,
even though it's not hard to get and it's like more work.
It's really well, it's really interesting to me like how people think of it
because I've seen plenty of people in online circles who just kind of become
friends with a lot of famous people by just messaging them and like literally
mean literally like, yeah, like there's there's lots of people just because
they work at that person and they think, oh, that seems like a cool guy who I
bet I could have a fun conversation with.
And so they just approach you and, you know, do so well.
And then like your friends and then there's other people who like view you.
If you even have like, say, 10,000 subscribers on YouTube, they think you're
like untouchable, like I can't believe you would have time to risk.
Like I still today have times where I respond to somebody's comment on YouTube
and they might be like, oh my God, I can't believe Digi Bro responded to me.
And I'm like, dude, I hang out in like a discord server of people.
Like I'm fucking easy to reach like message me.
I just don't know.
It's I just don't know.
And it's really funny because like my mom is very much a fame chaser of this sort.
And like she loves going to concerts and she always tries to meet the band.
Like she has, she's a huge fan of the band System of a Down and she like has, you
know, pictures she's taken with the band members that she like treasures.
Like they are, you know, the most important things she has is like these
pictures are like momentary interactions that she'll remember forever.
And like I, I, I guess I understand that.
But for me, I've gotten into a position where like the people who I look up to
or admire, I can just hang out with because I'm famous.
Like I got to go to Dick Masterson's house because he's never even seen
any of my content.
I don't think like I just am somebody who happens to be your lecture moderate.
Oh, except for the lecture.
Yeah.
But like he had had me on his show even before then just because he knew that
I was a guy who had a lot of followers who happened to be at his live show.
So he brought me on the show to talk about it.
And it's like, that is the basis of our relationship is I'm a guy who has
followers who is a fan of his, you know, and it's just funny for me to think that
like there are people who call into that show who are like, oh man, I would,
I would do anything to be able to get a spot on the Dick show.
And it's like, I just kind of got it just because I am somewhat famous.
And like, I think anybody, I don't feel like it's hard to do.
I feel like it's pretty easy to just, you know, if you even open your mouth on the
internet about anything of interest and like 10 people follow you, you're already on the path.
Like you just got to keep doing that and you will get bigger.
We've certainly lowered the bar for entry massively.
Speaking of like, well, when you said about when you left a reply on a YouTube comment
and someone was like, oh, should did you bro replied?
They reminded me of like, one time I commented on some random video and someone was like,
oh, you're you, you're Lathalora major.
Wow. Fancy meeting you here.
And I'm like, yeah, I enjoy media online as well.
Fancy that.
But that also like gives me like a scary thought.
It was like, when you're famous, it's kind of hard to just leave random comments on videos
because people will just like take it as like some sort of mega statement that like you posted.
You're like, oh, hey, I like your music.
And suddenly a news article, did you bro, I liked this music.
He supports the artist.
We see people, yeah, make articles about that kind of shit with really high profile people.
So yeah.
I have been from the very beginning very careful about that.
Like I won't comment or like something unless unless I do completely stand by it because I expect that.
Yeah, you're forced to make those kind of at least weigh that as part of your decision.
And it sucks.
I mean, it's kind of life.
You say it sucks.
But all you have to do is make it all to count.
You know, like just, I mean, true, make a sock puppet that you can use to comment.
Tons of people do it.
It's interesting when you go to, if you go to a lot of like famous YouTube channels and stuff,
they often don't use that as their main one because like you'll go to say ego raptor and like
he has no subscriptions.
And it's like, well, you obviously subscribe to people on YouTube.
You must have another account, you know, I think that's pretty common.
True.
In fact, I've kind of been meaning to do that just for the sake of convenience.
So I just don't have to think about this so I can just be like, yeah,
whatever this is my fucking, in fact, I have several accounts that I use for like uploading,
like test uploads and shit like that.
I want to make one just for shitposting because I get, there's times where I watch videos and
I have something really mean to say and I'm like, if I say this as myself, people are going to be
like, what the fuck?
So I need to make a just shitposting account.
I guess I, I don't know, not to make it too serious or anything, but like I think about like,
if that's like kind of fucked up to like hide who I really am when I make a certain comment,
like the same exact thought crosses my mind all the time.
The thing is who you really are, like, I mean, as a content creator, you are,
you're only showing a little bit of yourself anyway, like who you really are is always veiled.
If anybody had a direct read into any of our minds, they would hear all kinds of, I mean,
I don't think there's anybody whose mind is sanitary who can like not think anything fucked
up or bad at all.
So like, you know, ultimately it's just about like, which thoughts do you decide to represent
as part of your character?
I think it's totally fair to represent other thoughts as part of a different character.
I got you.
And isn't that a fascinating thing?
I kind of feel like a lot of what the modern world is going to is the sort of the expectation
that everybody is clean all the time.
And I mean, it just goes in line with this like old post that we've made before posts mattered
and you could shit talking, nobody cared.
But now that's being, it's being recontextualized and changed.
And I mean, I get it.
I get it.
It's just, I think as we get more and more into each other's heads,
we're going to see more and more shit we don't like seeing.
And we need, I think the best thing we need is some sort of exhaust valve to be like,
okay, you know what?
I shouldn't care that this person said this fucked up thing at this time.
I should not care that much because we all say fucked up things and think to ourselves,
fucked up shit as long as it's not hurting anybody directly.
The sort of combining of two things where on one hand,
all of your interactions you have are like encased into marble and you cannot scrub them
clean no matter what you do.
You can delete a post.
It doesn't mean it's not going to be on the way back machine if it was a really
controversial post or anything like that.
So really, there's not anything you can do.
But also because of that, yeah, now people are really scared of posting things that
may be considered controversial or bad.
So then it can breed a situation where there's no bad posts on a particular profile because
they've made it to be that way intentionally.
So then it can have an air of perfection or pristineness that is not natural.
What the cultural shift I want to see the most is to not be so hard up on trying to not be wrong.
Like it feels like it's if you say something wrong these days,
people will jump down your throat about it.
And like, I don't think that being correct all the time is that interesting or necessary or like,
you know, makes you a better person because everything you say isn't wrong.
In a way, I think it's less about you being wrong and more people just wanting the gotcha
moment being correct on the internet, getting their limelight.
Yeah, very much so.
And it's kind of sad.
They want to be able to feel like they have something over you, which it's understandable
because it's it's sort of like justified bullying in a way.
It's like, yeah, the reason people bully is always that, you know, they someone has power
over them, they want to have power over someone else.
And like in a culture where we understand that bullying is wrong,
it's like, how can I bully you but be correct in doing so be justified.
And it's like, oh, you said something wrong.
I'm going to harangue you about it.
And it's like, yeah, but who gives a shit?
And the mental, the mental gymnastics some people go through just to twist your words
into being wrong so they can be right is scary.
This may be a provocative example, but like the whole projared thing going on recently,
I'm very much reminded of.
And at first, I mean, obviously a lot going on there.
But like the first thing that we all hear much going on there.
To the OK, the only thing I want to get into is specifically that like, OK,
at the point that we're at now.
So like, obviously, Jared was involved with some degree to other women.
I don't know what the timeline is.
But like the timeline is actually kind of important because it sounds like they were
going through like a period of breaking up since like February.
So like, I don't know exactly when these the whole underage thing again, like maybe.
OK, here's my point.
I'm going to bad things were said about Jared.
And I'm sure some of them are true.
But we really don't know exactly what is true and what he knew when.
And like if he did bad things exactly at this specific time and on the whole charge
of like cheating on his wife, all I'm saying is she says that he cheated.
His response is we actually had a more complicated open relationships,
which it seems to a degree is true.
So my only thing is, well, shit, this is complicated.
I don't know what to say.
Yeah, yeah, he did in his most recent.
The wife confirmed it as well.
She said eventually.
But that's the thing.
And it's just like it's such a clusterfuck.
And what?
The last update was he put out a message that said like and she responded to it.
But he said like, yeah, we like we had an open relationship and blah, blah, blah.
Things get out of hand.
Things went bad.
So what did so what did she what did she say to that?
Basically, she said like that's I think she agreed that it was somewhat true.
But like the thing with Heidi, for example, like went way beyond what they had agreed to.
Right. Yeah, that's what I meant.
Like that went like she specifically said, like, don't do this.
Okay. So like now in order for us to make a determination who's bad and who's good,
I need to know the timeline, the motivation of characters involved.
Like exactly.
And so my point is I cannot sort this out.
I can't do it.
No.
Nor should you have to for any reason at all.
Yeah.
Right.
That's what I'm getting to.
I absolutely hate things like this.
Because on the one hand, like for some some weird part of my brain is fascinated by
internet celebrity drama.
But at the same time, I'll be checking out of the grocery store and I'll see People Magazine
and I'll like puke in my mouth.
And this is the exact same thing.
It's just people magazine for E celebs on Twitter.
Yeah.
So I was I was deeply ashamed of myself for finding myself like totally like engaged in this.
And like, I'm a totally hypocrite.
Me too.
Discuss myself.
I'm so happy to announce that I have I have no idea what you're talking about.
And there's I'd like to make a public statement.
I have no idea what any of you are talking about.
You're a champion among us.
To me, there's like there's there's it's like with something like the pro-jaret situation.
It's so it's so like again, like you said, unclear and also it's just something that
like if I was a fan, this doesn't affect his content in any way.
Like if he actually did like have sex with an underage girl or like send
dick pics to underage girls, then that's it's that's bad.
I'm okay.
You know, the authorities might want to get involved with that.
You know, like whatever.
I mean, it's the stuff the stuff about the stuff about cheating on his wife.
That's, you know, maybe bad.
But I don't give a fuck if somebody cheats on their wife.
Like it's no one else's business at all.
The stuff.
Okay.
The stuff about the underage girl, I find the timing of when all that happened to be very
suspicious.
Like, isn't it strange that his wife outs him as a cheater?
Public opinion suddenly turns against him.
And then only at that moment, a handful of people come out and say,
oh yeah, he did all these other bad stuff too.
And he's fired for it.
We were investigating this whole time, but only now are we going to say anything about it.
Everybody acts like the people who come out and confess are such heroes.
But it's like if you've known for years and you haven't said anything, only now when it's
publicly safe to come out and like dog pile, like you're just as much of an asshole.
Like I have no respect for you.
Well, I mean, again, like maybe these people are true heroes who felt super scared by the
powerful pro-Jarrod.
And only now, I'm just saying, maybe that's true.
I don't fucking know.
I smell a little whiff of bullshit on that whole thing.
But at the end of the day, at the end of the day, like these allegations are criminal and
therefore should be decided in a court of law and not in the court of public.
Well, you know what people say.
I think it's weird for an like granted.
I don't think anybody gave a fuck about pro-Jarrod at the time this happened.
I think him bleeding all those subscribers was more like people having an excuse to
Like he hadn't uploaded a video in like four months, right?
And he hasn't been relevant in years.
His videos have very low view counts even among the ones that was due to like personal issues.
But I mean, that is true.
Whatever the case may be, people, I don't think like people act like
I'm so offended he cheated on his wife.
If he was making great content, people wouldn't care.
Like John Tron, when he got into his whole racist thing,
he had a huge backlash.
His whole subreddit turned against him.
He lost a bunch of subs, put out more videos that people liked and it completely blew over.
I mean, people will get over this because honestly, because this this issue,
like what's the substance?
I mean, I'll tell you what it is.
It's a whole lot of virtue signaling.
It sure is, buddy.
I don't like that Projara did this thing.
So I'm unsubscribing.
And I'm just like, what even is the virtue of this for a guy cheating on his wife?
I don't like cheating.
I would not do it, but I don't understand the moral.
It's like, it's just some social contract you have with the government.
Like it's not, you know, why are we judging somebody on the basis of like what their sex life is like?
I just don't get that.
I mean, yeah, people, people don't think about this,
but let's just paint the theoretical scenario about a man who's in a somewhat open marriage
with a wife who let's just say for the sake of possible example is horrible to him.
I'm not saying she was, but like, okay, maybe it would make sense why they drift apart.
And he is like with other women and as we've established some degree of open marriage.
Now that's just a hypothetical.
I have no idea how good or bad this man was.
But like, because that's possible, I just think that it makes sense to just like hold off and
let people with knowledge sort it out.
I have an interesting, I have a different perspective that I gained this past week because
I was saying this before the show started.
So I've been listening.
I have been while I've been working and doing other stuff.
I've been binge watching a ton of like the Penny Arcade D&D games,
specifically the C team with Amy Falcone and Chris Straub and some other guys.
But they did a crossover event with another group called Dice Camera Action,
I think, or AKA Waffles Incorporated.
And the thing that's relevant there is that two of the players in that game,
a long running game, are Pro Jared and Holly Conrad, which is very interesting.
That game is mostly played over Skype calls, over video chat,
but for this special crossover event, they all came and they sat in the room.
So this is what happened.
Is that what you're trying to say?
Maybe.
Oh, definitely.
I'm pretty sure that this is during when they were cheating,
or they were fucking each other at this time that this event was recorded.
And I don't know, it was just really weird with this new context.
I was watching them and the two of them are like,
they will make goofy faces at each other and they look at each other a bunch.
And funny enough, their whole character arc is like,
they're like star-crossed lovers that can't be together.
Yeah, straight up.
One of them is from a family that has packed with demons,
and the other is from one that have packed with angels.
And it's like, if they get together, the multiverse is destroyed.
So they make a deal with Asmodeus to change their fucking family.
And I'm like, oh my god, I can't fucking believe this.
Isn't it crazy?
That is fascinating.
It's fucking crazy.
I would like, I want there to be a psychological study
on how often do people's D&D campaigns just reflect their inner,
like what they want to be happening in real life, or how they see themselves.
I am 100, okay, I've been watching the C-Team.
I am 100% convinced that everyone's character is just what they want to be.
Yeah, fascinating.
I mean, mine was when I was playing Niga Rafiki and I had 500 bottles,
5,000 bottles of ale, and that was all I had.
Word.
Like, I don't know, Chris Straw plays this drow who is a complete introvert,
who doesn't understand social interaction and hates his physical body,
and is disgusted by his physical existence
and only wants to consider high-minded divinity and stuff.
And the dragonborn Donar Blitzen, he's this fucking high-falutin,
fucking narcissist Chad guy who's played by this shlubby guy who loves sports and wrestling.
The list goes on.
I'm convinced.
I'm absolutely convinced that everyone's D&D character is just what their inner self looks like.
That is fascinating perspective.
Whether they intend it or not.
By the way, on this issue, I just want to be super clear.
I hate cheaters, and more than anything, I hate liars.
People who lie regularly are absolutely scum to me.
But the issue is, yeah, exactly, I despise lying at every capacity.
It's just that I don't actually know what accusations are true or false,
so I can't identify who's the bad guy yet.
But when we do, look, we'll probably never know for sure by my standard.
Here's the thing.
So in addition to all that, I've been listening to some Slavoj iek.
And in particular, this started with the Jordan Peterson debate.
And he raised an example in that that I want to dig into more about where it came from
and who said it originally, because I think he was quoting.
But he said something about, imagine a husband who is jealous of his wife.
He's convinced that his wife is cheating on him, and he's upset by it.
And he said that even if it's all true, the husband's jealousy is still pathological.
Because it's too late, it's already the ship sailed, and she's gone.
You know, I don't really know the explanation, but I think it's like,
well, you can't control what she's doing.
Like, if you are obsessing over this, and this is causing you great grief,
and you continue, you've got to do something.
Yeah, break it up, or do something about it.
Don't just be a fucking jealous, cucked husband who's upset about it.
Like, do something.
And I don't know.
I kind of feel like maybe that applies to his wife.
I don't know.
The point is, I don't feel bad for his wife.
I think his wife probably is.
Probably.
You know, this doesn't give me any...
I don't know, man.
And judging by the way she's acted on Twitter, I don't think you should feel sorry for her.
But...
She's what on Twitter?
Just the way she acted.
Just by the way she's acted.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't feel any sympathy for her.
I don't...
I'm not...
Even if Jared did her wrong, that doesn't make me think she's good, you know?
Nate, I'm curious, like, I know you say you hate cheaters,
but would you ever like...
Like, if you found out that...
What's her name?
The girl, Sapa Kanakin.
What am I thinking of?
Oh, Joanna Newsome.
If it turned out Joanna Newsome was cheating on a fucking...
What's this fuck?
Chewboy.
Andy, Andy...
If Andy...
Cuck...
Why can't I Cuck?
God damn it.
Samberg, Andy Samberg.
Say Andy's thing.
If you found out she was cheating on Andy Samberg,
would this affect your listening to her music at all?
Okay, you know, so unfortunately, I think that it probably would.
I don't think...
I think that it's...
That's amazing to me.
Like, I don't...
I don't want it to.
I just think that I'd be like, man, this sucks.
The thing is that like most...
I think, first of all, most creatives are damaged individuals,
and second of all, most people are doing something fucking.
I mean, I agree.
I just don't want to know about it.
I mean, it's just like I kind of assume that like there's always
going to be something about everybody that if I knew it,
I mean, even just...
Like there's lots of music I listen to from people who I think
are like politically fucking retarded or something.
And like, I know that.
And maybe it enters my mind every once in a while,
but like if the music is good, the music is good.
And like, I just kind of have to assume that if I knew everything
about everyone I listened to, I would not be able to listen to anything.
I mean, I think if I knew everything about any individual,
I would find them contemptible and disgusting,
because I'm sure people would feel the same way about me
if they knew like my innermost thoughts all the time.
So I agree.
But like, I just think this is why I don't want...
I don't want to know.
I don't want to know what's going on in people's heads.
It's really fascinating to me, though,
the like what gets into people's crop,
because it's like there are a lot of rappers, for instance,
who have literally murdered people,
and like nobody holds that against their music.
And then you've got like...
Like Pro Jarrod's a way worse person for cheating on his wife,
you know, potentially, as opposed to murderers.
Or like Kanye West, who like Kanye gets like totally assblasted
by like the whole black community for like wearing a Trump hat.
And it's like some...
You guys are listening to people who kill people.
And like people are like, oh, I don't listen to Kanye
because he has political opinions.
He has a hat.
I don't like.
It's a funny thing, dude.
It's a funny thing.
Someone on Twitter, I saw this was on the day
that the Pro Jarrod story broke.
Someone was like peanut butter, like normal boots,
when John Tron says his racist shit, like,
oh, fuck you, we don't want to be associated with you.
Pro Jarrod, when he treats on his wife,
oh, you know, we're sorry, man, you know,
hope things get better for you.
And I read this and I'm like, yeah, those aren't even similar.
Why would you, like, why is it hypocritical
to react differently to those two things?
It's like, oh, these two people
both did something that I disagree with.
Why is there not an equal outcry for both things?
Well, you know, I suppose they could be making the point
that like, you know, like cheating on one's wife
is more, you know.
I think being racist is worse than cheating on your wife.
Well, okay, I mean, we'd have to get into the discussion
of like, was it in fact racist?
You can make a case.
Okay, well, I'm just accepting this guy's premise.
Okay, if you accept the premise, then I'm with you.
John Tron said horrible.
I actually don't know what John Tron said
that was this event.
I'm unclear exactly.
Is that what he quoted in statistics?
It was willing to meet this guy on his own terms.
Okay, sure.
And I still hate it.
The John Tron thing was just that he made the awful mistake
of debating with Destiny.
And...
Well, yeah, fair enough.
And that was basically it.
It was just him and Destiny had a debate
about the fact that he was like into Sargon and shit
and like was kind of...
Now, there's a fucking thing
Oh, boy.
I have not had any more fun than making...
Like Sargon's current downfall
is the funniest thing in the fucking world.
I don't...
Okay, I've heard the thing...
I've heard the thing about joking about raping MPs.
I don't know what he actually said.
I don't know what an MP is.
Well, did he know where these two worlds...
Two worlds are colliding right now
because I'm over here just following Brexit news
as like hardcore and as intensely as possible.
Every day I wake up and I read the BBC.
And then like from like off screen,
like there's a glimmer of light in the distance.
I squint my eyes.
And then in three frames max,
there's a punch from who other than Sargon of Akkad
entering the political sphere out of fucking nowhere.
When?
I thought I left you behind.
How did you get here?
Ben, are you aware that Sargon is running for office in...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I did.
I did.
Yeah, a position in the EU.
Dude, it is the funniest.
Fucking thing in the world.
I've seen clips of him just being like really belligerent
like in public, like at his public appearance.
Sargon of Akkad is a fucking moron.
He's an absolute moron.
He absolutely is a fucking moron.
And he is running for office that he...
Because the party that got him
is basically a totally irrelevant party
that is just clinging to him
because he is more relevant than they are.
So like they see him as like,
oh, famous YouTube guy.
This is our ticket.
This is our ticket too.
But the fact of the matter is that while Sargon is,
you know, somewhat internet famous,
he's not necessarily taken seriously
and less and less so
as he continues to make a fucking fool of himself.
And there's this great...
I highly recommend this particularly to Nate.
There's this YouTuber called Porcelain,
spelled P-O-R-S-A-L-I-N,
who does these like hour and a half long documentaries
about people that are extremely well made.
And he...
That sounds nifty.
He's definitely...
He himself is a like far right poll meme lord.
But the people who he rags on
are other like right wing people
who have just fucked up so badly
that they are now laughing socks
within their own community.
And so he has one about Sargon
that's like an hour 45 minutes,
fucking hilarious.
Just it goes to his entire history
and every dipshit move he's made.
But like the most recent one...
That almost feels scary in a way.
That almost feels like going back
to what we were talking about earlier
where it's like okay,
well, he's made mistakes,
but he's just made one too many
that broke the candles back
and now he has like a hit piece video about him.
That's the thing.
The thing about it though is that,
and this is why I'm bringing it up
because with Pro Jarrod,
I'm like guy cheats on his wife.
That's unfortunate.
It's bedroom politics.
I have nothing to do with it.
You guys sort that out.
With Sargon, he's running for office.
So what he does, does matter.
What he says, what his like positions are
when he's saying it in interviews.
It's like the entertainment value
in watching this man dig his own grave
is in that he is so self-important
that he believes that he's doing something good.
Like it's one thing if like say,
if something I did,
like let's say I did some heinous act
and it came to light,
my best course of action would be to apologize, right?
It would be like, hey man,
I'm sorry about what happened.
This was something that happened in my day-to-day life.
Maybe there's more context or something.
I don't know.
Like this is a fictional scenario.
But with Sargon,
this is his public statements
as a man running for office.
Like as a public figure,
he is saying and doing things
that are so hilariously retarded
that you have to make fun of him
so that people understand
that if you're going to run for office,
you can't do these things.
What's he saying?
The most recent one and funniest is
he was defending Amos Yee.
You guys remember that guy, right?
I do.
Amos Yee, yeah.
Yeah, he's a pro pedophile guy.
He patroned me and Jesse for a little while.
He was a pedophile who is like,
he's like the world's-
I don't think he is specifically a pedophile.
No, he is.
He's been to jail several times for pedophilia.
Okay, if you say so.
He is a many times incriminated pedophile
who is also like a public defender of pedophilia.
And basically his platform is
that because there have been cases
wherein the child was not harmed
or wherein the child enjoyed the relationship,
it therefore is not always not okay.
Did this guy have you-
Want you to read a thing on how they marketed?
Yes, I did a bit on him and how they marketed
because he wanted me to market his video
defending pedophilia.
And I just made a clip talking about it
and explaining why I thought it was wrongheaded.
Because the bottom line is
there's no way to measure the psychological damage
done to somebody.
It's like you can't say,
oh, the kid enjoyed it and therefore it's okay.
It's like you don't know what the long-term effect
of that could be.
There's so many questions to be asked
and it's like in this sphere,
there's always going to be an arbitrary line.
You know, what we decide is the age
is always going to be arbitrary,
but we have to have something
just so that we as a society can say,
all right, here's a hard and fast rule,
just follow this rule.
The bottom line is-
And to be fair, to be fair to his point,
we are technically repressing some freedoms,
but it's for protection.
We repress freedoms all the time.
The whole basis of society is repressive.
You don't have the freedom to murder people
because we repress that.
It's like, dude, the bottom line is
you don't have to fuck kids.
You can just wait till they grow up.
How hard is that?
Oh yeah, but let's get back to the Sargon issue.
So Sargon had apparently defended Amos Ye at some point,
so this gets brought up in an interview
for a political interview.
It is important how he defended him
because there's a lot of different ways to defend him.
Well, he basically restated his argument.
He literally said, like,
well, you can't say it's always bad
if sometimes it goes okay,
and everyone was just like, all right, Sargon.
But I mean, that's true.
All right, go ahead and say it.
Yeah, all right, all right.
It was just, yeah.
The fascinating thing about all this
is I'm actually a big Sargon fan.
A big Sargon fan.
Are you really?
And I really am.
I unironically am.
How?
That guy's so retarded.
He's a complete stooge.
Look, I'll tell you how.
It's because where you guys are asserting
that he's, you know, like a grandstander
and, you know, I don't know,
doing it maybe for attention or something.
I mean, I've been convinced, maybe I'm crazy,
I've been convinced he's doing it for principles
that he believes.
Oh, no, I totally think he's doing it for principles.
What are you talking about?
I never said he was a grandstander.
He's just retarded.
Yeah, okay, for no.
Oh, I mean, you can make a case for that, sure.
I used to sort of like his content
and then I stopped caring.
He is like, he is just a complete, like, alt-right stooge.
He doesn't even know what he's doing.
Ben, he's not even on the alt-right.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Listen, listen, listen.
He doesn't even get it.
He doesn't even know that he's doing it half the time.
But he just...
Why do you think he's no better than the guy?
He's just thoughtless in the things that he repeats.
I agree with what you're saying, Ben,
that he is thoughtless.
I don't think that that,
I don't think he has led himself to the conclusions
that alt-right people have.
No, that's not what I'm saying.
I mean, he argues all day against identitarianism.
He does function as an unwitting mouthpiece
for like conservative fucking, I don't know.
I mean, I've seen some Sargon stuff.
I've never seen him be a mouthpiece for conservative...
Ben, what's the position that he is a mouthpiece on
that he's unaware of, if you can think of something?
I mean, isn't he kind of in bed with like, metaphorically,
not in like a pro-Jarrod kind of way, you know what I'm saying?
There he goes.
But he's kind of in bed with like, Lauren Southern
and that fucking guy who sells the brain pills and...
Alex Jones, you mean?
The brain pills?
No, not Alex Jones, well, maybe him, but the guy who just...
No, the fucking...
Paul Joseph Watson?
Ben, I mean, okay.
Yeah, well, Watson, Watson.
I'm not, this isn't, I'm not trying to catch or anything,
but like, I asked you for like a position
and you're saying he's associated with these people, therefore.
And that doesn't seem like it.
Well, isn't he?
Okay, isn't, okay, I'll give a position.
It's, he kind of seems like he's one of these,
like, Islamophobic, like, you know, no, no refugees ever,
kind of.
I mean, he definitely believes strongly in border control,
but I just think there's a principled argument to make for it,
for, I mean, in his case, the sake of the British populace
and protecting their lower classes from immigration,
which pushes down wages, which is bad for their people.
And I mean, you can argue that,
you can say that he has malicious intent or something,
but I mean, I think his case is reasonable.
You're misreading me.
I'm not saying that he has malicious intent.
I'm sure he does believe the things he says
and generally thinks that he is saying the right things
for the right reasons with good intentions.
I just think he is a stooge, no fucking clue.
Just the only question of this is,
so do you, do you think it's fair to say that like,
like you said, if he's reaching the same conclusion
as alt-right people, let's say, of, you know,
close the borders, something like that, then reaching that
for any reason is like playing into the hands,
even when you have like a decent argument for it?
Because I mean, what can you do?
What can you do if you really believe it?
You could get smart for one thing.
Well, here, okay, here's what I'm saying.
I mean, I've seen like, okay, in particular,
I've seen videos from Sean, the YouTuber Sean,
where he deconstructs Sargon's points and stuff
and arguments that Sargon has made
and shows that like the things he is quoting are wrong.
That he is like knowingly or not,
he is quoting like, you know, Nazi sympathizers and stuff.
He is repeating facts that are demonstrably false.
Things like that, okay.
You gotta remember, you know,
Hitler was right about some things, you know, like,
everybody's right about some things.
Even a broken clock gets right to two times a day, as they say.
Right.
Is that true?
Is that, have we tested that?
I just think it's unfair to say that just because
an alt-right person also said the thing that, like,
to me, alt-right is a totalizing position.
It's like, if you don't believe literally all of the things,
then you're not that.
Alt-right breathes air.
I, that's true.
Do you condemn the breathing of air, I guess?
That's solid, solid.
Two things.
Number one, I just want to comment on this MOC guy.
He looks like, like, if you put, like, the dryer on high,
you three Econin, like, left them there for like six hours
and he tumbled out and, like, was completely broken.
Like, his hair is just constantly unkempt and just, like,
it just obliterated his, like, more, like, like, like,
like, if Econ's atoms were just, like, splattered,
maybe, like, like a millimeter or something,
but now he's just constantly, like, a being of chaos.
Also, number two, I wanted to comment on Sargon of Cod,
not in a political sense, but more like a political analysis sense
about what, giving a little more context about him running.
So he has joined the UK Independence Party,
which was the original party behind Brexit,
well, not behind, you know, a major proponent and whatnot.
And what's funny about UKIP is they are in a fucking tailspin right now,
and they and the leading party of the conservatives
are just fucking dean obliterated
when you hear conservatives don't think
conservative America is different.
Right, right.
But so UKIP was the Nigel Farage party,
but now Nigel Farage left,
and so now they've just been in that for that and numerous other reasons.
They've just been crashing and burning.
And so I like the aesthetic, the image, the painting
that is being depicted in real life of UKIP,
soaring high, getting, you know, Brexit, the vote,
and they've just been a victorious moment,
and then just through the constant struggle of Brexit,
Nigel Farage leaving due to controversy within the group,
and now they're just, like, in, like, a burning sinking ship.
They're like, oh, god, who's our poster child?
Who's our poster child?
We need a new fucking guy!
Sargon of Akkad, that works!
That's fine!
Anyone, anyone!
It's the two-headed dragon of Sargon of Akkad and, um, Count Dankula.
Count Dankula, which Count Dankula seems like he's in it for the meme.
Like, he, he's always just looks like a smiley fucking guy.
He's just like, yeah, like, I don't know if any of this is working or doing anything,
but I'm here, because this is, this is clearly hilarious.
Sargon, meanwhile, is taking it completely seriously,
and everyone's just laughing at him.
Well, here's one of the reasons why I like the guy.
I mean, sure, okay, but he just got his entire channel demonetized,
and what is his response?
I'm gonna keep going.
I mean, is this the mark of, like, a bad person or someone who's, you know...
Nate, fucking, do you realize how much fucking...
That restarted his career.
Like, this dude was not really relevant,
and then suddenly everybody's talking about him again, because...
I mean, how is 800,000 subs irrelevant?
I mean, he's making a fine living doing his shit.
Okay, having subscribers has nothing to do with relevance.
What is his fucking view count?
Well, you just made it about relevance.
No, I'm saying that view, I'm saying subscriber count does not imply relevance.
You can have dead subs forever.
Okay, sure, that's, that's fair.
His videos get decent view counts, don't they?
I don't think like there's...
It's not that I'm saying he's not, like, at...
Like, I'm not saying he's not at all relevant.
Like, he literally is nobody now.
I'm saying that, like, at the height of Gamergate, he was the guy.
Like, he was the guy who made that movement as big as it is.
And now...
Those are the days.
Now, you know, and he's been trying to somehow get back to that.
I don't know if you saw the whole...
I mean...
Oh, you just gotta watch the fucking documentary, god damn it.
What better argument is there against Sargon of Akkad
that he was a Gamergate guy?
He was the Gamergate guy.
I mean, again, we would just reach totally different conclusions on that
than we have as we have in the pack.
I guess so.
Here's an example.
This comes from Sean on his Curious Cat.
Example of Sargon being a stooge.
He repeats the fascist lie that Heather Hayer died of a heart attack
because she was unfit rather than being hit by a car
driven by James Fields at Charlottesville.
This was someone was hit by a car at a protest or something.
And the right falsely spread the rumor
that she actually died of a heart attack.
Ha ha ha, isn't that funny?
No, she was just murdered because someone ran her over...
Okay, sure.
...because a fucking right-winger ran her over with a car.
Okay, great.
We've heard his side.
Now we need to dive into exactly what situation he said that in.
I mean, maybe our boy Sean is literally lying
and it was like a joke, he said.
I don't know.
I need to find out.
I'm totally willing to believe that Sargon just heard that
and thought it was true.
Yes, and that's what I think he does.
Right.
Well, that's why I think he's a moron,
because it has nothing to do with his political opinions.
I don't give a shit.
It's just the way he presents himself in talks
that like, I get the sense that this dude
like just kind of, you know,
listens to the talking points of other people,
collects the ones that sound good and parrots them,
and then has no...
The ones that support his,
the ones that support his sort of general...
Right, and he has no idea how to really defend those things in argument.
Because like, when Sargon makes scripted content,
he's just like, you know, making a formulated point
on the basis of whatever data he has.
And that can come out fine a lot more easily.
If you listen to the man debate anyone,
he clowns himself into oblivion.
He is so bad at debating.
He just kind of talks over people and shuts them down
and continually insists that they're not really listening to him or that...
Or like, he just...
It's really embarrassing.
Actually, I watched recently a video of him talking to an interviewer
and she completely didn't listen to him at all.
And like, no matter what he said,
she just kept pressing her own words and questions.
And it's just...
Anytime you talk to the mainstream media,
you're fucked because they don't give a shit.
Yeah, it was just so aggravating.
I stopped watching.
It was me and Byter, we were watching together
and I was like, Byter, stop.
No, I don't want to watch anymore.
Was that the Sky News clip?
There was a whole clip I was seeing about Sky News
put out this video where they heavily doctored it,
but he secretly recorded the whole thing
and the context was totally different there.
I just know he was talking to a female interviewer
and she was...
That's a totally different context
because the mainstream media will fuck you
no matter who you are to further their own agenda.
But Sargon, when he debates people on the internet,
like internet, blood sports, whatever the fuck you want to call it,
he's not a good debater.
He says a lot of stupid things and that's gotten him in trouble.
He always tries to do this thing where he...
He always tries to be clever.
Like, he's always trying to throw what you say back at you
or try to find a way to make it into a funny joke
and he's really bad at it.
Again, I would recommend the Porcelain documentary on him.
It's basically a chronicle of his whole career,
I mean, everything he's ever done
and why exactly his own team is turning against him now.
It's pretty funny.
What do you mean by his own team?
Is that like UKIP or his employees?
No, all the other right-wing YouTube crew.
Everybody in the skeptic community...
Who's the right-wing YouTube crew?
Just everybody.
Well, the main guy who's sort of...
The main reason, I think,
that he's gotten into heat with his community
is because he's beefing with Mr. Medeker
and looking like the asshole in that beef.
And so because people...
And also the Ralph Rettort.
So like, because Medeker and Ralph
are sort of the more relevant voices now
and are memeing on him so fucking hard,
it's turning a lot of people against him.
It doesn't surprise me at all that Medeker is memeing on him.
Medeker takes the piss out of everybody
when they treat anything with any sort of seriousness.
Medeker seems to be there to just laugh at them.
So if he starts running for office,
of course Mr. Medeker is going to shit on him.
That just seems like his wheelhouse.
It's more intimate than that.
It's more than just guys making videos about each other.
It's like there's a legit beef.
Just I don't want to go into all this
because I had to watch an hour and 45 minutes
of all this being explained to me.
We are being People Magazine right now for isolates.
I'm seeing Ethan Ralph tweeting about the breaking news of Sargon
and it is UKIP's Carl Benjamin hit by milkshake in Salisbury
in fourth attack this week.
Damn.
Now see, that's not okay.
Don't fucking throw milkshakes at a guy just because we're talking.
I mean, no, it's kind of funny, but it's no.
I don't think it's...
I can accept that.
You're just making his case stronger by doing that.
Yeah.
I'm just over here leaning back in my chair
just with the rag-to-wee theme playing in my head
with my glass of fine wine.
The glass of fine red wine.
It wasn't even just wine.
It was the fourth milkshake.
Yeah, the fourth milkshake.
And reminiscing about how in the Skype calls,
I would be talking to Gigi's ex-girlfriend Cookie Cutter
about Gamergate and talking...
And I was linking to her talking about the state of video games at the time.
He hit Cookie Cutter on the show.
Yeah, great idea.
And I thought about each hand.
It was just a glorious time.
You see, guys, I understand.
I'm sure Sargon's done many stupid things.
I've heard many of them myself.
And that's...
And perhaps I'm the naive one.
Perhaps I'm the fool who's just hearing the things I want to hear
and discarding all things that are relevant.
Totally possible.
It's just that when I hear things like him getting shut down monetarily
and getting milkshakes thrown at him,
and I see his videos and he's like,
not going to stop me.
I'm like, that seems like an honorable person.
I mean, that's okay.
Because...
But I'm not going to stop him from doing what.
Nate, if you understand...
I don't know, trying to lead UK to the independence that he thinks it needs.
And I'm like, I don't know, UK.
Sure, go for it.
Look, it's so fucking easy to spin that shit.
Not just...
Okay, people are doing that to him and that sucks.
It sucks that people are doing that.
But to act like him soldiering on through that is such a bold move.
It's like all those things will empower him.
They make his position stronger.
But I already agree with his position.
So I mean, it's working out pretty well.
It's like he gets to play the victim now.
And don't give me any of this fucking shit, people.
I don't agree with every position he has, Jesus Christ.
Well, it's not like he arranged this to like,
oh, now I'm going to make sure people hate me
so I can play the victim in their court.
I don't even think...
What?
I don't even think that.
I just think that if people act...
Well, here's my advice to people who don't like Sargon.
Don't throw a fucking milkshake at him
because you're going to empower the position.
Like, you are doing the opposite of him.
And victimhood is not proof that your argument is correct.
I totally accept that.
What specifically do you agree with him about?
I mean, how about the fact that the UK should have the right
to determine whether or not it wants to open its borders to immigrants.
Therefore, it should leave the EU so it can control that.
Seems reasonable to me.
Sure.
I mean, yeah.
That seems to be like the major issue.
I can see the logic.
I mean, that seems to be his entire platform right now, right?
Because like, Brexit's been dragged out for what?
Like, three years now and people won't have another vote or some shit?
It was supposed to happen in March.
Dude, it was supposed to happen several times over by now.
I mean, the official, like, actual big dick date was, yeah, in March.
Now it's in...
I believe they pushed it back to November,
but that's a definitely 100% no fucking way happening.
I see it in 2020.
If then, dude.
I see it if then.
I think the goal right now seems to be just wear the people out
so the UK stays in the EU.
Yeah.
I mean, that could possibly be the goal for some people.
Dude, you hear people making the case for it every damn day.
By the MPs.
There was some fucking lady debating on...
I mean, I'm sure this argument is thrown around all the time.
That's like, okay, like, I get the idea that like, no, no, no.
The people were gaslighted and misinformed,
and therefore the first vote, like, it does not accurately reflect
what the British people would have thought.
Therefore, we need to either cancel it or try again or something.
But see, now we're getting into like the nitpick stuff of like little...
Of course, we have to cancel it and restart it after like three years
of our own gaslighting and fear mongering from mainstream media.
I like how literally every election has already functioned that way,
but because some people don't like the results of this one, it's suddenly...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's literally how the whole world is run.
All an election is, is a battle of propaganda.
At that time and place.
Well, Brexit has been just been a constant bag and forth between people
who really want Brexit and people who really don't,
and then just people trying to compromise,
but no one can come up with a proper compromise.
I mean, there is no compromise.
Either you leave the EU or you don't.
And I mean, you had a referendum and leave one.
And if you do like a pussyfoot, you know, like misstep,
and instead of going like hard Brexit, you know,
World Trade Organization rules.
If you just go somewhere in the middle and you know,
oh, this isn't what a lot of people want because it's not hard enough.
It's like too soft.
But like if you go for like a Norway style and like just give up your seat in the EU parliament,
just for no reason, just for like, you know, cause...
Yeah, it's just insane.
That's just not going to appease anyone.
That's just going to make everyone mad.
So it just seems like there's going to be no compromise.
And so now everyone's getting upset at everyone in power from every angle,
like even people who want it or mad people who want it,
even people who don't want it or mad people who don't want it,
because they don't want it, you know, hard enough.
Has everybody seen the CGP gray video about how there's literally no way
to give every people what they want because of the Ireland divide?
And how Ireland will...
I mean, it depends on who you're asking.
I mean, if you ask someone, if you ask like a conservative from...
You know, our conception of conservative from like the north of England.
The Tories.
Yeah, if you ask a hard line Brexiteer, it's the proper term, I should use that,
who's like not in Northern Ireland, they'll say,
yeah, just fucking World Trade Organization rules, we're out of that with any other country.
If you ask someone in Northern Ireland that obviously have a different opinion,
you know, no one can agree.
No one can agree.
I foresee great troubles.
I mean, if we're not, if you can't define already, this is a great troubles.
And I do mean troubles with the capital T there, astute listeners.
Indeed, indeed.
Well, fuck, I mean, I don't know.
So what have we learned?
I think that we've learned that when any two parties look at a particular object,
they most see the characteristics of that object that for whatever reason,
appeal the most to them, positively or negatively.
And I think Sargon is certainly one, we all are.
I want to say in closing, just to be clear, that like,
I'm not even going to say whether I agree or disagree with Sargon's politics.
It's more like I don't care and barely even know.
All I see is a man who makes a meme out of himself all the time unintentionally.
And the face of the man is the dopiest, most vacant, most self-important fucking face.
Mostly it's his face.
That's most of what I have a problem with, that he just looks like such a
fucking dipshit.
He just looks like he thinks that he's the smartest guy in the room,
everywhere he goes, but also has no idea what's happening.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I mean, I would disagree with my conclusions, but I understand how you arrive there.
Yeah, fair enough.
So I've been playing some tabletop games lately.
Yeah?
You know who does that? Sargon of a cod.
Let's all go subscribe.
That's not true.
Is that true?
Yeah, no, he has a D&D thing he does like weekly.
Really?
How could he not do tabletop games?
The man's a fucking turbo nerd.
You know, maybe I underestimated this guy.
Yeah, going back to D&D.
Could he be the genius that we've waited for?
Well, I shouldn't say that I've started, but I'm participating in my first D&D campaign.
Your first ever, really?
Yeah, first ever.
Tell us about that.
Like I said, I've been watching the CT, I've been watching the Penny Arcade D&D stuff,
and I've been like, oh, it's fun.
I like it.
Despite our vast immeasurable differences, Ben, we're not so different, you and I.
You were just like me trying to make destiny.
Yes, question mark, question mark, question mark.
Anyway, I wish Hippo was here because he's in the D&D campaign.
Wait, wait, who's playing?
So it's me, Hippo, and a few other people from our friend circle outside the PCP,
and we're all hanging out.
I feel more specific, it is nameable.
Hang on, hang on one second.
I'm checking my notes.
I didn't authorize any friendships outside the PCP with you,
so we're going to need to cut that off.
You know, it's been a long time coming, you know, frankly.
Okay, you know, sure.
No, we got to get them on the payroll.
Oh, that's fair, as in paying us, as in paying us for the right to...
They're renting Munchie out as friend.
That is an exclusive PCP right, so they need to check with us.
The bin, you will know the DM, because it's 610,
the Hippo Pageant Model of Health and Treatment Services.
Yes, I've seen him on Twitter lately posting stuff about learning Japanese.
Yes, yes, yes.
So anyway, we're only a few sessions in.
Ganbarimashou.
It's very hard to do it.
What are you playing?
What's your character?
Uh, I am playing...
My character is a Prussian who wants to unify all ethnic Germans under one flag,
and not in a racist way, just in a cool way.
That's my boy.
What fucking game are you playing?
Not in a Hitler way, but in a Bismarck way.
Of course.
What game are you playing exactly?
Well, we're playing...
We're not playing D&D, we're playing a...
A...
Oh god, I don't know what it's fucking called.
Fate, I think?
Okay, I heard it.
I think it's called Fate.
Oh, I think I heard it.
It's very loose on rules.
Yeah.
Wait, is that the one?
It should be.
What's that?
There's some game...
I'm not sure if it's Fate, but there's one where you have to define everything about your character,
including the circumference of their anus.
Wow.
Oh no.
That sounds like Munchie's kind of thing.
Hold on, hold on.
Anal?
I'm circling.
Anal circumference.
Well, good luck on R&B.
I didn't have to define that.
Okay, no, no, no.
That one's called Fatal.
Okay, real quick.
Obviously, the center of your anus is always going to be a zero circumference.
Is this like the brown hole around it?
Well, I don't know about that.
It's how far it can stretch.
Oh, okay.
Okay, okay.
That makes sense.
Yeah, we're talking about maximum circumference.
Right, of course.
Before you...
God, why did we waste all the time on Sargon when we could have talked about this the whole time?
I know.
What were we doing?
Talk about assholes.
I think the topics are one and the same.
Quote from Darren McLennan.
So basically, Fatal is the date rape RPG.
Sign me up.
But that's not what we're talking about.
Well, I mean, I wish it was.
You know what?
Oh, guys, PCPDD campaign by D&D.
I mean, a Fatal campaign.
I think that's a...
Sounds like a plan to do.
Yeah, I think it's in the near future.
I guess I'm in.
What's Hippo playing?
Hippo is playing a crippled boy, a crippled lad, who is on top of an aged Boston dynamic
robot, and the Boston dynamic robot carries him on.
Awesome.
That's cool.
I like it.
Awesome.
Well, tell them it.
Tell us about it.
I don't know if you want me to get into the raw fucking details or anything.
Yeah, a little bit.
Maybe an overview.
Yeah, whatever.
Okay.
Well, Sixen's whipped up this, again, not a very serious endeavor,
because I don't think anyone wants to do that, especially me.
I can't imagine a worse fate than tuning in for two hours to fucking hardcore roleplay
for realsies.
Honestly, that was my opinion before.
I'm starting to get a little bit more into it now that I have a firmer understanding of how
things work.
But nevertheless, Sixen is obviously a Swedish boy who's whipped up a Scandinavian escapade.
There isn't really a clear plot right now, but we're just hanging out and trying to get our
bearing straight and our sea legs.
Because, again, I've never done this before.
I think that no one else has done it before either besides Sixen who was DM'd before.
It's fun.
I want to play.
Is it fantasy?
Like, is there magic?
Are there monsters?
Yes.
I describe it as like, imagine, it takes place in one of those post-apocalypse,
which just means that people have reverted back to medieval times,
but there's an excuse to have technology in it.
That's the way to do it, yeah.
So we're in sort of a middle ages runic setting, like Scandinavia.
Sounds pretty sick.
There's bards, there's magic, but there's also obviously Boston Dynamics robots,
and I have a pick a lot because, of course, I do.
Indeed, of course.
Why else would you play oppression for any reason?
Yeah, literally, unironically.
So, yeah.
So what's interesting about it to me is that it's sort of very weird experience,
because I am very, like, sort of weirdly far removed from roleplaying.
Obviously, legendarily, mythically, my old Pokemon roleplays are known throughout the land,
and I used to roleplay very heavily in the Pokemon Mystery Dungeon
fandom, but that was many years ago, and very different than a live-action Dean.
I'm just going to say D&D when I say what I mean.
That's fine, yeah.
I'll wheel you.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
I've never done a D&D thing like that.
And it's weird that all my conventions or ideas of how to create a good story
sort of don't apply, and when I try and do them, they're working against what it's meant to be.
And that's just like...
What do you mean?
What I mean by that is that, like, when you are presented with a scenario by the DM,
and you have to work through a problem, be it through diplomacy or with force,
it's not really...
It's instead of saying to yourself as a writer,
time to write an interesting exchange between two people, between two characters,
which I am crafting with my own hand, and I'm the deciding factor, it is I have to pretend
to be someone else and work for my own advantage, or the character's advantage, rather.
So instead of...
I mean, obviously, it's not like they are completely separate things, but instead of,
you know, writing arcs that I can very clearly define because I am in control of the scenario,
I am at the whim of the DM, and I am at the whim of wanting the best for myself.
So, obviously, while characters may want the best for themselves in fictional scenarios,
it's not so clear as in I have to make the decision, which will further my own goals,
and I have almost paradoxally, because I have more agency, I have less,
because I can't affect the game world, I can only affect my actions within it,
so I'm always going to be looking for positive scenarios for my characters,
which is not actually maybe the most interesting things that could happen.
Like, I'm never going to put myself in bad scenarios, or there is not a
eyebrow game player enough to do that yet.
If it's what your character would do...
Well, sure, but if it's not what the character would do, then I wouldn't do it.
But, I mean, the most interesting scenarios are when there's conflict.
That's true, yeah.
So, obviously, I'm not a... these are sort of like first impressions.
I don't know if what I said have made any sense,
since I'm still trying to work out the terminology in my mind.
I mean, I mean, I... to me, it's like, okay, you got your character,
you got his motivations, you got your stats, you got your dice,
you walk yourself into a conflict, and then it's like, you decide,
like, what would my character do if there's a conflict there?
You know, you roll the dice, you pick what stat you're using,
you pick what equipment you're using, and like, here's how I'm handling this.
And like, one thing about the C team that I've been watching is Tycho,
the DM, is always... he's always asking... it never ends with a,
this is what my character does, my character uses this spell,
my character, you know, uses this skill.
He always asks, like, okay, tell me what that looks like.
It's like, okay, I'm using Intimidate.
Rosie tries to intimidate someone, and he's like, okay,
but what does that look like?
And she's like, um, well, you know, I think Rosie would attune herself
to the plane of shadows, and she would like, I don't know,
maybe she would make like an extra plane of shadow,
like a loom up behind her to make herself look bigger or something,
and like, I don't know.
Like, there's like specific, like what... you know,
it's like the dice and stuff are sort of like a prompt,
they're sort of like a storytelling prompt.
And you can decide what things look like
and decide how things progress, but like within this boundary.
It sounds like a really good way of DMing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like, like, for example, like,
when he, like, when the warlock, when Cathriss summons a demon,
it's not just, oh, okay, I pick this demon,
and like, you know, I make this circle,
and the demon shows up, and I roll to command it, and stuff.
That's just the beginning,
because like, the demon will show up, and then he'll like,
they'll, they'll role play like a conversation with the demon,
where like, the demon will introduce himself,
and like, you'll find, he'll tell you his, his name and stuff,
and then they'll be like, they'll like discuss,
like, what am I here on this plane to achieve,
and like, why should, like, what will you pay me,
like, what will you give me in exchange for my services,
and stuff like that.
It is, it's a very, he digs in, he really digs into it.
Well, it sounds like a lot of fucking work to me, frankly.
Well, it's fucking, it's storytelling.
Yeah, I think that
D&D just falls into the same, I don't want to say problems,
because that implies negatives,
but just like hurdles that normal things don't,
because it's a game, you know, is a role playing game,
in which, you know, it's almost inherently about empowerment
to make it feel satisfying to you, the player,
who is engaged with it as a player.
So it's almost inherently supposed to be, again,
I keep coming back to this idea that
it's supposed to be positive for you,
where a lot of my most, the most interesting stories to me
are things in which characters fail,
or do they not accomplish their tasks,
or they are flawed in some way,
which I guess could apply to the D&D characters.
And obviously, it's, again, I don't want to seem,
imply that they are so radically different,
right in a good character, or being a good player,
but it's just a difference in perspective
that makes it suddenly different
in ways that I do think have somewhat massive implications,
when, again, you are not in control of the scenario,
and you just have to be empowered to make decisions
in which may not be the most interesting narratively,
but just make the most sense for the game at that present.
It sounds to me like you are grappling with the age,
the age-old conflict of role playing versus role playing
R-O-L-E versus R-O-L-L.
Is that, do I have the right of it?
I don't explain further.
Like, you know, there's the aspect of the game
that is about storytelling and playing a character,
and then there's the aspect that is about seeing numbers go up.
Right.
Well, yeah.
The most difficult thing about playing D&D
is when you have a group that's just interested
in rolling dice and swinging swords,
because that's, you can just go play a video game
if you want to just do combat and stuff.
That's how I see it.
That's me, my dudes.
When I play D&D, I'm like, I barely even look at my numbers
or my ability.
I'm not even interested.
The greatest...
That part is just sort of incident.
D&D's greatest strength is that you can do anything.
You know, the DM allows,
because you can say you want to do whatever you want,
as long as the DM allow you to make a check for it,
you're not bound by a preset amount of mechanics,
like a video game or something.
Anything you can think of, you can do,
and that's what really makes it interesting.
A lot of the times I've played with people are just like,
I'm just going to roll my dice and swing my sword.
I'm a fighter.
I'm just like, this is a slog.
You've got to play with it.
Like the best group I ever played with was early last year,
it was me and a couple buddies,
and we were all just really having fun with it,
and the DM was another of my friends.
He's really lax about things,
just to have everything be fun.
My character is like a half orc, way the drunken fist guy,
so I would have to drink whenever I would need to use drinking stuff.
So I'd be drunk halfway through the campaign.
Then my friend was a bard, and he brought his guitar,
and he'd just sing all the time,
just make up stupid songs the whole time we were playing,
and it was the best time ever.
That's right.
You also have to have a good DM for those sort of things,
because if the DM himself or herself,
they're interested in just rolling dice and swinging swords,
then you can't really have fun in that sort of way.
If you're interested in rolling dice and swinging swords,
you probably shouldn't be DMing,
because you have to add all the flavor
that binds everything together.
Did I tell you guys about...
It is extremely like numbers light.
There are very few instances where like our stats matter.
Well, I like that.
That's how they're like kind of game.
It's not as though you don't roll dice or anything like that,
and I will say my least favorite part of this experience so far
is rolling the dice,
because it just feels like it's random self-control
in a situation where it's like,
I know to not use like my finishing move or something
that effect in opportune moments,
so it wouldn't be narratively satisfying.
By the way, my finishing move is I can split things in half,
and only in half, 50%.
And I can do this two things, like all things.
So I can split like people in half,
but I can also split like atoms in half.
And cause a nuclear explosion.
Oh my God.
But anyway, I know to not use that all the time,
or else it would just be boring,
but rolls are just like when I want to do something,
that seems like it shouldn't really be an issue,
like just attacking someone.
You know, now it's just like,
oh, I have a chance to not do it,
and I just don't do it for some reason.
And now the DM has to come up with like a weird reason
why I just now suddenly don't for some reason.
It's your, well, it's your skill at attacking
versus their skill at avoiding your blow.
That's, you know, there's a conflict there.
There's two individuals each trying to achieve something
different.
It's not skill-based.
It's chance-based is what is the problem.
I mean, it always really comes down to that in the-
It is chance-based, yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, that's always been my biggest issue with D&D,
is that like there's so many times
where you can just get terrible RNG.
Like that was like the biggest problem
with that character I was talking about.
Thrax, the half orc drunk man, he would just constantly miss
even though his punches could like destroy anything.
And like the gimmick was just like,
he's so drunk, he can't hit anything, I guess,
because like my dice rolls always suck.
Dude, I've sounded somewhat negative here,
and I don't mean to be.
Hold on, I want to say that reminds me of in Morrowind,
in Elder Scrolls Morrowind,
you, it does a random number generator every time you attack.
So you can literally see your spear go into an enemy
and see the word miss pop up above their head.
D&D is a little better at that.
The first, when I tried to play that game,
all I did was like, I was in the starting village,
I just like walked out of it, tried to attack a monster,
missed like 12 times in a row,
and stopped playing the game forever.
That's understandable.
That's RPGs.
Yeah.
Well, I-
Well, it shouldn't be, I mean, like in an action RPG,
I feel like the whole point is that that abstraction isn't there.
That's true, I agree.
I think it makes sense.
I get it.
And in D&D, it's not that way,
because like really, you don't see what's happening,
what's happening if you're fighting like an armored guy
and you fail to overcome his, what's the AC stand for?
What's the-
Armor class.
Armor class, right.
Like you just chink, you're off his armor,
which makes sense.
He's got fucking armor on, your sword bounces off it,
or he's a speedy fuck.
Or he's a dodger, he's dodged your flow,
or there's a magical repulsion or something, you know?
So it feels unsatisfying,
but really it actually is perfectly reasonable.
It makes sense within the logic of the world,
but the problem is that the dice tend to rob you from agency
in a game that's biggest strength is that you can do whatever you want.
Yeah, I agree, Tom.
That's a good way to put it.
Well, I mean, I think the idea is that like,
you know, as your character advances and your numbers do go up,
you become more empowered to like make the things
that you want to see happen happen.
Well, of course, of course.
As you gain more spells,
and as you get better at doing things in general.
I know, I guess it's a whole, like it wouldn't be meaningful
that you can overcome a foe if you didn't have to work up to it,
if like in a previous version of yourself
would have failed at accomplishing this.
I think the only, I mean, I totally get it,
and I still love D&D on the whole.
That's why I made a whole video about how it's the greatest thing.
But the only issue is like, if you were playing a video game,
like if you were playing Final Fantasy VII
and like at level 1 through 10,
you have like a 50% miss rate, like you'd want to kill yourself.
And like D&D tends to have like a 30 to 50% miss rate,
especially at low levels.
That's true.
Because you're, you know,
you got to hit like 15 or something,
and if you're only getting like a plus four bonus at starting out,
like that leaves a lot of space for you to just fuck up.
This is unrelated to my experience,
because there are no levels,
and I don't know how that works in normal D&D.
But I probably come across as like negative
or like a non-enjoying experience,
but all contrary, my friend, I'm quite enjoying it.
It's just, it gets my brain percolating,
because it's again something that I have not experienced
in really a long time.
This idea of having to like work with other people
to achieve an error,
because obviously I have given my character faults,
and I've given my care,
I have a general idea of how I would like an arc to go
for said character.
But now I have to work that into what,
what Sixen wants is DM,
and what the other players do in the game,
and what situations we find ourselves in.
And I feel, again, it's a weird paradox
where I have agency in the sense
that I am controlling something,
but I have such a limited agency
in that I am at the whim of the DM and the other players
in a lot of circumstances.
And the dice, where I would want to maybe finish off
a character or a fight in some way,
which would be relevant to my character's arc,
but I simply cannot, because I can't get a good role.
And then I remember the first altercation where,
I mean, you know, this isn't a problem or anything,
but just this, this game, this is a good
sense I have for how the game will go,
where it's like I had a specific way
in which I wanted to finish off the first boss
that we encountered that would be relevant
to the character's arc.
But obviously, everyone else does two,
because everyone else is their own character,
and everyone else wants this to be relevant to their,
because they are the protagonists, they are the player.
So when the turns went, and I was,
like the person right before me got the kill,
and you know, in a particularly glorious way,
it was like, ah, shit, I have to be like better.
And by better, I mean luckier, I guess.
It's an interesting scenario.
I'm enjoying it, I wish Hippo was here,
you know, he is a part of it after all.
I want to, maybe next week we can hear his thoughts.
Sure.
You guys can fucking hash it out.
Yeah.
My, again, my thoughts may seem negative,
but they're merely contemplative,
they're merely contemplative on the philosophical quandaries
they have, well, plain D&D.
Contemplative, that word should be pronounced.
If you're interested, there's obviously way more details
that I'm sparing the audience for,
because I'm sure it'll be really boring,
but if you're interested, we can really wrap it up.
Yeah, sure.
I don't want to say I've been playing a game,
I've been playing a game with some friends
being DM'd by a friend of mine.
It's called Dogs in the Vineyard, and you play,
and yeah, and you play as a dog, a dog of the faith,
and the faith is a, you are basically a combination,
I said this before, I'm sorry if I'm repeating myself,
but the audience didn't hear it yet.
You are a combination mailman slash missionary
slash detective slash lethal enforcer
slash pizza hut slash Taco Bell.
For the, for a fictional version
in like a fictionalized United States
of like the Mormon Church.
Okay, okay.
Oh, and in Deseret?
I, what?
A Deseret is the proposed Mormon super state,
if you don't know what it is,
obviously it does not take place there.
I haven't heard that term so no,
but this is like an alternate,
there's a couple of things that are different,
that went different, like the history of China,
there was some kind of like holy rebellion
in China that succeeded in this world
that didn't in the real world.
Okay.
Yeah, there's more to it.
There's still time, China, get to it.
But yeah, and you have a big coat,
you have like a custom coat,
because this is like a part of your mark of office,
like the people in your community.
So you're not a literal dog, are you?
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay, okay.
Dog is your type.
Gotcha, gotcha.
And you are this, you are a guy,
you are a fucking going around,
you're like a holy warrior for Mormonism.
And...
Sick.
My character is Charlie Yang.
That's Chinese.
He is Chinese, he is the son of immigrant railroad workers,
but he is deeply resentful of his,
he just wants to assimilate,
he just wants to fit in,
he resents his parents for being workers,
he resents them for being Chinese,
he resents white people for not,
for seeing him as different.
He's a very resentful, conflicted guy,
but he has a cool coat with a dragon on it.
Well, fantastic.
Is this like a battle series?
Well, there is fight,
like we came to this town for,
the DM sent us to this town for,
they were tithing too much,
and we suspected that something was wrong there.
And it turns out that, yeah, they were,
they were overworking their,
like there's strict strictures in the book of Enoch,
laying out like how,
basically they're laying out like workers need,
you know, they shouldn't work too many hours in a week,
they need at least one day off a week.
Sure.
And they were not observing,
they were not observing these things.
Those bastards.
Turned out,
turned out there was a cult going on,
and there was like some demonic possessions,
we had to baptize a baby that had a demon in it,
we had to name the baby,
we had to fucking,
we had to, we had to fucking kill a few guys,
they were doing some demon shit,
and that wasn't cool.
Yeah.
I try, I try so hard,
I am like, I'm playing my guy as like a complete conciliator
who's tries to avoid conflict at all times,
who just wants to,
he just wants to save souls,
he doesn't pull his gun out unless,
things aren't really bad,
there was a shootout,
people were shooting at us from the windows,
I had to lasso a guy out a window,
you know, it was,
it was pretty all right.
There were hatchets were thrown,
hatchets were embedded in skulls,
but you know what,
it's all for the king of life,
you know, praise him.
Is that the Mormon God or whatever?
Yes, in this world,
he's called the king of life.
Okay, sick, sick.
I have,
there's every one,
at one time I was like,
I think I had to,
I think I was trying to like,
exercise a house or something,
and I had to improv,
I had to improv like a,
like a passage from the,
from like the holy book or something,
I just came up with something on this,
but that's the kind of stuff I like.
Yeah, that's cool.
Like what would you,
what would you say?
Like what's a,
what's a thing?
What would you,
what's,
what kind of thing would happen in this scenario?
Blessed be the man who layeth his wife
upon a green grass,
only twice in the full moon,
and not three times,
for that would be too much for her,
you know,
womb.
Right.
Something,
yeah.
Something like this.
I made,
I made up a little parable about like a,
like a,
someone,
some,
a holy man coming on like a rich community,
with like the,
they like,
they favored like the,
the local authorities,
they favored like earthly authority over,
over the king of life.
Oh no, no, no, no.
And they were,
yeah,
and they got rich off of that,
but God smote them
because they had their fucking priorities
all mixed up.
Yeah.
Okay.
He's,
oh yeah,
he's smote him.
Oh,
he's smote him all right.
Demons are real,
so I guess God is definitely real.
Oh,
I should think so.
Mm hmm.
I,
I wouldn't even question it.
Sounds fair to me.
It's a really,
it's a really weird system.
Like there's not like attack and defense.
You basically just take turns
doing shit.
And like your,
and like attack and defense are all like
rolled into one thing,
and there's just like huge dice pools,
and like every turn it's like,
you're bringing in,
you're bringing,
you choose,
you roll your initial dice,
and then the next turn it's like,
well,
oh,
I have a trait
where it's like,
you know,
I'm,
I went to school,
my character has a trait that's like,
I went to engineering school
so I could run railroads
instead of build them like my parents did.
So like,
if there's like an engineering scenario,
I'll be like,
oh yeah,
I'll bring that trait in,
add some more dice.
Next turn,
someone shoots at me,
oh,
I pull my gun out
and shoot back at him.
Now I bring my guns dice into it, you know.
I'm just imagining
as the dice pool grows,
like you get to like a giant,
like there's a dark soul style giant lever,
you need to full,
a full body like pull,
which opens the door,
it's like a gigantic vat full of dice
that all begin rolling,
all at once.
That's,
that's the,
that's the dream.
That,
that is the dream.
So many weapons.
You gotta unlock,
you gotta turn the key.
Oh shit.
That's what it was like
when they dropped the bomb on Hiroshima
for every individual person,
they had to take individual damage,
you know,
you know how it was,
or Dresden,
whatever,
it's all good.
When the bomb starts dropping,
and like the emperor,
and the dice start rolling.
It's like everyone roll initiative.
Shit.
Rat,
Ratcon for D&D campaign, dude.
Maybe.
Hey.
RFCK D&D campaign, dude.
Munchy.
Remember,
remember mice,
the convention?
Of course, of course.
Remember what you were thinking about?
Okay.
Well,
it's been less than a month
since the like table applications are open,
and they're already closed.
Oh, well.
What?
I checked it a little while.
Yeah, like I didn't,
I didn't think they'd be gone instantly.
They opened up in April,
and now it's May,
and yeah,
according to the website,
they're no longer taking applications,
so I'm very disappointed.
I mean, what were you waiting for?
Did you want to be in?
Yeah.
Me and,
me and Kazzy talked about it,
talked about getting the table together,
and I haven't talked to her about it,
but I kind of thought you were maybe
going to join in on this,
since you're like moving here.
No.
Well, I mean,
to get a table there?
I mean, I'm a comics artist,
so why would I?
No.
Oh, okay.
Well, I guess I should tell her.
Rest in peace, investigator.
We fucked up,
and that's all fucked now.
And I feel terrible about it.
It is life,
and it's all my fault.
You'll just know for next year, I guess.
I don't know if you want to.
There's more conventions.
I guess this one's really good,
and Casey Green was there,
and Abby Howard was there,
and I wanted to be on the other side.
I didn't want to go there
as a fucking consumer,
as a fucking sheep there
to spend money on this crap.
Should I get over it complex, dude?
I didn't.
It's terrible.
I don't blame him.
I feel the same way.
I, too, am a man filled with pride
that is unwarranted, but, you know.
I'm literally not even going.
Like, I'm not even going.
Oh, man.
You just don't fucking see that way.
It was awful.
It was awful going there
as a fire expert.
No, you just got to take after Munch.
You got to go up to Casey Green
and ask him about the Smurfs 2 movie.
That's how you get it.
He'll let you on his podcast eventually.
Send him some pickup lines on his Tumblr
for, like, three months before the convention.
It's not impossible.
You're just talking about how
fucking celebrities aren't as mysterious
as they may seem.
Just fucking talk to him.
Just think at the end of the day,
he's just like Sargon of a Cod,
just a regular person.
Okay, here's what you do.
You go to conventions,
and you see about how no one pays attention to you.
And then you go to fucking whatever,
the round table, and you're like,
oh, I just won't tell anyone that I'm a comics artist.
I just won't let them know
about my many, many feats.
It should be implied by my very presence.
Yeah.
You got to be more...
Oh, I'll eat too much credit.
You can't be so fucking sad
that you aren't telling anyone
about how great you are.
Just let them know.
Well, if you had a bad time...
I'm not sad.
I'm just...
Also, I won't be going to that for a while
because I broke my toe yesterday.
Oh, no.
How'd you do that?
Again?
This is a partnership.
Yeah, with same toe.
Oh, no.
I just...
With same toe?
Yeah, I just stubbed it really hard into a door
as I was walking through,
and I instantly was like,
that's definitely...
Mistake after mistake.
Ben, I would highly recommend just
tilting your field of view
like five degrees lower at all times.
Do you wear slippers?
Look lower.
No, I don't wear slippers.
I think you should.
It's too hot.
It's too hot to wear slippers.
It is getting warm out.
Okay.
I cannot resonate with what just
has happened at all.
So you were walking so fucking hard
into your door that you stubbed it?
I was just walking at a norm.
I went to my door.
I opened the door.
I kind of simultaneously was opening the door
as I was taking a step with my foot
like to walk through it,
and the foot and the door just collided
in the cross section with enough force.
But it broke your toe?
You going to the doctor or anything?
Did you already go?
I'm in bunchy.
Remember last time he broke it just by like
walking into a room and he was running at the time.
I don't remember last time
because I wasn't there in that house.
I'm feeling discomfort.
I was moving at a slightly faster than walk.
I'm no, I'm not going to the doctor
because every time I've broken my toe,
I've just gone to the doctor.
They've just been like, well, you can tape it.
Yeah. Okay. Fair enough. Fair enough.
And I'm just like, I mean, I can still walk.
Yeah.
I mean, it hurts a little bit
and I'm trying not to walk too much.
But like, you know, I can still walk.
I'm not like crippled.
I just, I don't know.
It probably in like a week or two,
I won't even feel it anymore.
And it'll be like, it didn't even happen.
Well, all right.
Well, I'm glad that the one PCB member
that has an issue related to their feet and legs
is going to be, you know, healed up real soon.
Good job, Ben. You know, good job.
Yep. Don't worry, everyone. I'm fine.
You know what? Everything's great.
Guys, can we all just give it a round of applause
for this, for our state of physical health?
I feel good. I'm brave. It's true.
Hey, I'm a brave boy.
We were talking before.
I have one thing I wanted to bring up.
We spoke briefly about access journalism,
kind of, not really.
I don't know what, I've never,
I've never heard that phrase before.
Well, okay. That is a phrase.
I'm joking.
What are we talking about?
I just woke up.
Like talking to celebrities or whatever.
Okay. Well, here's my point.
Here's my point.
So I just hit 100,000 subs and that's cool.
Congratulations.
Now that I did that.
Oh, yes. Thank you. Thank you.
Now it's time to have a pro Jared style fallout.
Oh my God.
Cheat on the PCP with the pizza party podcast.
I've been here since 100,000 subs.
Can't wait for 90,000.
Can't wait for 80,000.
Looking forward to it.
I'm, I'm, what was I fucking saying?
Oh, right. Okay.
So, so I was talking to the gaming Brit the other day,
just passing.
And I was like, yeah.
He was like, hey, congrats.
He's like, you getting your silver play button?
I was like, you know, I, I don't know.
I've been waiting for like,
there's supposed to be like a prompt for that or something
and like the thing I don't know what to do.
He's like, why don't you just message like support?
I was like, wait, you can do that?
He was like, yeah, just like Google, you know,
fucking support.
And this is what he had to do to get his or something.
And they'll hook you up.
And so I was like, oh, okay.
Now apparently, this is a support.
Let me know if this works because if it does,
I have, it's been fucking four years
and that prompt never came.
Did you, okay.
Did you, did you ever?
Cause I have done this now.
So first of all, I am now verified on Twitter.
Cause I, sorry, not Twitter on, on YouTube.
Cause I reached out to the people on this help thing.
And there was a lady.
I think this is only available once you have a hundred
thousand subs.
I think is literally the cutoff point.
But once you have it, I just reached out
and I just sent him messages like,
Hey, I'm the, you know, best care for this is my channel.
Like I've got two issues.
One, I was hoping I could get verified.
Let me know what I have to do for that.
And two, dude, you got that, you got that check mark.
I look right now in the fucking thing.
It's a great check mark.
I know it's not blue on YouTube.
Look in the gross discussing audio links.
There it is.
There's my check mark.
So I, so I like, that doesn't mean anything
other than that.
I'm like the real me, I guess.
Like Sargon says all the time, you're now a shill
and I can't trust you.
Well that, that's on Twitter.
It's very different on Twitter versus YouTube.
It's a very different situation.
Yeah.
What I, I've actually tried to get verified on Twitter
and I just found out they are not accepting
applications for Twitter verification.
So I don't think there is even a path anymore
to Twitter verification of any kind.
God, what's young Venus going to do?
I know, I know, he never did it.
Oh God, our dream has been shattered.
Oh, no one tell him.
I think what you need to tell him.
No one tell him.
He still hasn't verified Satan and I.
There's still a path.
You just become a journalist for some like
big old world publication is what you do.
And I think you will get verified.
I just don't think there's like a process
for the average person to get there anyway.
Okay, but, but on the subject of the silver play button,
so did you tell me if you've ever gotten this?
Cause like she said, like I was talking to this lady
and I'm like, hey, help me, you know,
verify and then silver play button.
She's like, oh yeah, no problem.
Like I'll send you an email in a little bit.
What she sent me is an email with a voucher code
and a link to like go here, put in this voucher code.
It prompts a window.
It says like type of your name or it said best guy,
but you can change it.
I just left it best guy ever.
And boom, hit okay.
We're now currently processing
your silver play button order.
It will be there in like, you know,
a couple of weeks or whatever.
So I think it's done.
It's on its way.
I think I need to go.
Amazing.
Gower, cause the email that I will help you do
is the same way Brent helped me.
I've only checked it like twice ever,
which is when my channel got taken down
to figure out why and what to do about it.
So it could possibly be buried in my email somewhere
ages ago.
I'll show you exactly what was sent to me.
But even beyond that,
I will give you exactly what fucking notification thing
I found and I just messaged her and said,
Hey, I want a thing.
They're like, no problem.
We'll do immediately.
Nope.
Done, done.
Yeah.
And it takes a long time for it to actually process as well.
Well, that very well may be the case,
but like it is underway now.
It wasn't before and now it is.
So I'm, I'm feeling pretty, pretty chuffed about that.
So yeah.
Oh, and the point I wanted to make about that was like,
okay, that's all well and good.
But like, you know, like a months ago,
my boy, a lobster boy,
Tyrar A. Dewey, ASMR guy, he, um, no.
It's just that he reached 100,000 subs like a while ago.
He's like 125,000 or whatever.
And like he made a video or whatever
and just said that like once he hit 100,000,
life was just so much better.
Like they were so nice and they were so helpful
in like the chat thing.
And this is the thing is I never even once attempted
to reach out to YouTube before I hit 100,000 subs.
So I have no basis for comparison,
but based on my experience now,
it's basically been great.
It's been super great.
It's an, it's like an unwritten thing,
but I think everybody understands that when you hit 100K,
you are just treated in some way differently by the system.
And like generally when people hit 100K,
the next couple 10,000 subs come way easier.
Yeah.
Yeah, that does, it always seems to happen.
And that's certainly my plan.
I mean there's like tiers of YouTube, obviously.
100K is one, when you hit a million,
you go like super fucking pro and then like you're a god.
Is that just, is that just from people that see that number?
No, I think it changed the way that the system treats you entirely.
Because it's where they take you seriously
as a YouTuber basically.
I had to fucking-
Because you're actually making them decent money now.
I am busting for a shit.
So nobody addressed me for the next few minutes.
Okay, you got it, dog.
And the only other thing about that is,
I think, did you said it's like implicit?
It's like not specified?
I think it is in fact 100% articulated,
at least parts of it, that you just,
at the very least you just don't have access
to the support staff until you hit 100,000 subs.
And once you do, then you do.
Then they will talk to you.
I want, I am games to hit 100,000,
so I can just like talk to somebody in real life
and just shit on them.
Be like, I fucking hate your company so much.
The only problem is-
It's great that I can finally talk to someone about it.
The only problem is,
you're just dealing with outsourced IT people who,
you know, they're not making any decisions at all.
It's the closest thing I'm ever gonna get
to Wajiski yourself,
so I'll take what I can get at that point.
I guess, but you know, honestly,
I was in a Digi's podcast,
the Whirling Dervish podcast the other day.
And I was just thinking,
I still resonate with his attitude
to why he's not here to hear this praise,
but it was just like people who have issues with YouTube,
it's just like, I mean, adapt and overcome.
I mean, you know, every job has issues.
The particular ones on YouTube are-
Of course you have to adapt or overcome.
That doesn't mean you have to be happy about it.
Oh, that's fair.
That's fair, I suppose.
I am sure this was discussed in the last episode,
since it's obviously the talk of the town,
at least in my closed off cave-like home,
and never leaving the town.
I assume that is the talk of the town.
I mean, after the two, still ongoing,
you were working on it just before the show, in fact.
Oh, that's true.
I had just finished filming,
and we'll finish after one.
You've only got like 10 more, 11 more videos to go.
Yeah, pretty much.
Pretty much.
At the time of recording.
The worst of it is over now, at least I assume so.
It's downhill for sure.
So now, looking back, I'm on your channel right now,
and the most viewed, which I don't know
if that's the measure of success here,
but if it is, then the best video is
Weaponized Thickness, Anatomy of a Meme.
That is number one.
It's true.
Close behind, well, not close behind it,
but just relatively big videos are, you know,
the Final Fantasy VII video, the hockey rant,
and the fairy tale is still dead video.
Now, that fairy tale one's only been out for three days,
but I think that will be cemented as either number one in time
or number two beyond the Weaponized Thickness one,
which, by the way, that Weaponized Thickness,
I think it only stands on the fact that once again,
I just put Galco in the thumbnail.
I'm pretty sure that's like 99% of why anyone cares,
and I guess the meme is known to some people,
so I suppose, but.
Now, obviously, you would know better than anyone.
I want to know currently how this Meme math
of a specifically success-wise compares to the first one.
I have no reference point for these numbers here.
I have no reference for if 10K being the standard
or like, you know, the high to low teens
being the standard of view rate.
Is that normal?
Is that good?
Is that fine?
Is that great or is that bad?
Compared to my, like, the generally released videos I do,
like, 10K for a video is quite low,
but the thing is, like, these are made very fast,
and 10K in one day to then produce the next day,
a 10K video and so on is, I mean, it's for my channel
and for my, you know, track record is great.
It's, I mean, this will absolutely be like a huge spike
in both viewership and, you know, AdSense earnings and stuff,
just for all the actual views that I'm accumulating,
just from all the fucking videos.
The cost I'm paying, however, is almost,
not to mention many videos, like the Thibidus,
some are like 20K, 30K, et cetera,
but the cost I am paying is absolutely.
I am losing subs.
I am 100% losing subs as a result of this,
but, however, the funny thing is,
now we'll get to comparing it to the original Miamafa,
is just that, like, I think that,
so right before this started, on day zero when I announced,
I'm gonna be doing YouTube full time, Miamafa 2, go.
I got, like, a thousand and a half subs or something,
and so a lot of those was because
Monkey shouted me out on Twitter,
and a couple other people, too.
I can't remember, everybody.
And that gave me a huge spike in subs for that day,
but then I've definitely been losing some,
and it's hard to know if it's those people
who were just only there, you know,
because they were told to be,
which frankly I don't even want.
I don't even, I'm happy to have people's,
you know, pity subs or whatever,
but ultimately it's basically worthless currency
in my humble opinion.
So I want much more organic accrual of views or whatever.
But anyway, point being that it's hard to tell
if this loss is just those exact same people
being like, eh, whatever,
or if it's legitimately followers
who've been accrued over time who are saying to themselves,
yeah, I've seen enough here.
He's really spamming me.
I'll come back after Miamafa.
Now in either case, I am not at all upset about,
I'm losing, like, maybe like 30 to 40 subs a day,
maybe 50 sometimes,
and I don't even think that if that rate continues,
I'll be below 100,000 by the end of Miamafa.
I think I'll be a-okay.
But I mean, in the question of is it worth it?
I mean, 100%.
Subs only exist to facilitate viewership anyway.
So frankly, the only thing I'm feeling
is I feel a bit of an ego attachment
to being over 100,000 and dipping back below
would be a somewhat of a blow to my ego.
But then, I mean, you know,
you obviously can't operate with that.
It's your primary motivation.
So, you know, fuck it, I've already committed.
I mean, if you're losing 30 a day,
you would have to go, that would be 20 more days.
Maybe more like 50 to be a little harsher.
I could dip back under at the end.
It's possible.
Yeah, yeah.
So, you know, but that doesn't really matter.
The net gain far, far outstrips the net loss.
And again, this is only going on for like 12 more days,
and then it's over.
So, you know, whatever, man.
Have, is this behalf of a easier or harder than the last one?
Well, it is harder in some ways and easier in others.
So, I'm working only, I'm working more than half time,
but like, I don't know,
I'm working a little bit less at my day job.
But the thing is, I now have a dog and a girlfriend
who both live with me.
And that, just that, that reality of driving her to work
and doing a bunch of other stuff
does take up some amount of time.
So, well, I gotta like walk him every once in a while and shit,
you know, so, like, to be distracted,
the other Miamafa was like a pure, just me,
do shit, no distractions, nothing else matters.
But I'm not in that exact same position now.
So, I've got no choice,
but to kind of do things every once in a while.
Now, it's fine, it's not a big deal.
I've got a little extra time.
Just slid out a darker, browner version of the exact Popeyes
four piece I ate yesterday.
Fascinating.
It's much, much spicier on the other end
than it was going into the mouth.
Tell me I'm not.
Great.
You are a criminal.
How interesting.
Okay, finish at my point,
because I've been talking about this too long.
Popeyes also sucks, by the way.
They're not great.
I went to Red Lobster, no, not really.
Yeah, I went to Red Lobster the other day.
I was looking for an inky mageage.
She wasn't there, but it was great.
It was delicious.
Love is lobster sucks.
It wants you to think that it's not.
Cheddar biscuits, Munchie.
Cheddar biscuits.
Man, fucking get that shit in a fucking box of bombs.
If you go into a restaurant for cheddar biscuits,
it's not a good restaurant.
Well, people go to Olive Garden for the breadsticks.
Exactly, case and fucking point.
Yeah.
All right, fair enough.
I'm not a high-brow man.
Me and my friend Lorenz.
Me and my friend Lorenz,
the guy who is running the dogs-
Oh, wait, fuck you, Munchie.
I took my parents out when they visited
to the nicest restaurant in Cincinnati
when they were here.
So you don't know, you've never even seen.
I want my fucking good boy boys with a weird monster.
You have never seen the kind of quality.
Oh, I want a great chocolate cheese
and get the fucking gummies for 3,000 points away.
I'm not a high-brow.
Munchie, at this fucking restaurant,
you order your entree, entree two and entree three
and dessert and salad at the beginning of the thing.
It's a whole- Lorenz, you better-
Your pea brain cannot imagine the level of cuisine
I have obtained in my life now.
But what about the service?
I can imagine.
Fantastic.
Incredible, man.
Also, to agree to that restaurant
because he was trying to court me, I think.
Oh, actually, Digi.
Actually, the precinct is one of the top restaurants
in the city.
That is not the top restaurant
where I took my family later.
That was my first thought.
But we went one step above to this place called...
Fuck, what's it called?
It's like the Lotus.
I can't even imagine the hotel.
Because that was the nicest restaurant I've ever eaten at.
I know, but I've found a way to go even further
beyond Super Saiyan 3 style.
And it's incredible.
The food looks like an entree over $100
for just like the one item.
This... the meal was many hundreds of dollars
for four of us.
Damn.
It was...
Yeah.
Not last New Year's, but the years before that,
I went out to a fancy steakhouse with the Kazi.
And I was... I basically just was like,
what, unprepared for like what fancy restaurants
actually entailed?
Yeah, it was crazy.
Because obviously I looked at the menu
and I saw the price and I thought,
OK, this will be a lot of money,
but that's OK.
Because, you know, it's a special occasion.
And so we go out, but I don't realize
that like you are like forced to buy like an entree
and then another entree and then an appetizer.
And like you are forced to buy all this other stuff.
Kind of.
Because the seats are so expensive
that they are losing money if you don't buy all of them.
So it was a...
True, true.
Like literally, I'm not saying that like you were forced to like,
you know, it was incentivized to.
I mean, like literally they said,
unless you buy all these things, you can't sit here.
That's crazy.
Because it's New Year's.
That's not how the 1B and 8B went to work.
No, they're a little more cashed that place, the precinct.
Well, well, anyway, in any case, that's how it was there.
So we finagle the situation where we would sit at the bar
and just pretend that we're 21 and then get an entree there
and only the entree.
So the entree was expensive, but you know, it was worth it.
But if we had been normal,
then it would have been like cut ruple as much
to get all the extra bullshit.
So fair enough.
It's a scary life.
It's a scary life out there dining.
All right.
This is all heresy.
Me and Lorenz, as I was starting to say before,
we have pooled our expertise.
And we are making, we are starting a keto cooking collaboration.
Our next project.
Oh, sorry, Ben.
I just want to say the restaurant, Orchids at Palm Court Reservations.
Orchids at Palm Court.
OK, sorry.
Sorry.
It's the best place.
Look it up.
Keto donuts.
All different flavors.
We're going to make them fruit flavor.
We're going to make cinnamon.
We're going to make them vanilla.
We're going to make them chocolate.
We're going to go fucking nuts.
We're going to fry them.
It's going to be, it's a miracle.
We're collecting all our ingredients.
Good.
You're collecting all the necessary objects required for this endeavor.
And I am so excited.
Again, Ben, different philosophy at the beginning
and different execution, but the end results of both of our lives
are also delicious meals currently.
And I'm very enamored with what you're doing currently.
And I would love you to say, Ben,
is much excruciating detail about these donuts as you could possibly.
What are the ingredients for a keto donut?
Okay. Well, there's a big, there's a big ideological divide.
Lorenz is convinced that we need to go the almond flour route.
And I believe that coconut flour is the way to go.
So we're going to, we're going to experiment with each.
We're going to maybe do a half and half version.
I've ordered xanthan gum to add to the, xanthan gum to hopefully give it
like a more like sticky, like actual doughy consistency.
So they'll hold their ring shape when they're dropped in the oil.
There's also an ideological divide between baking and frying.
I think that if it's not fried, a donut is not a donut.
It's just a, it's just a circular cake.
There is, there is the possibility,
there is the possibility of a, of a sugar-free jelly filling
that might be, that might be stripping towards at some point.
Mine, mine too, mine too.
There's a possibility of making a, of making a sugar-free
version variant of the Boston cream, of the Boston cream.
I'm very interested in this Ben, because I'm back on keto,
started two days ago, and I'm, I'm invested in the narrative now.
Watch out, Tom, because there's a lot of keto-delito going on these days.
I know, I know, I know.
I gotta, I'm staying on my toes.
There's a lot of kidney stones.
We're, we're a person, we're a persecuted people.
I'm like kidding.
I'm staying on my key toes as it is.
Oh, there you go.
Make sure I don't get deleted.
Oh, too bad I can't, because I fucking broke one.
That's the first part of the deletion, dude.
You gotta be careful.
I flipped fucking out yesterday.
I was listening to a podcast, and someone completely unrelated to our,
to like anything diet related, mentioned being in ketosis.
And I just like, I was in the kitchen, I just flailed uncontrollably,
and like dropped all everything that I was working on,
and just had like a fucking seizure,
and ride on the floor for like an hour afterward.
So it reminded me of Ben saying-
You know, that sounds, that sounds, that sounds like a problem.
You know what I think would give you probably increased mental clarity and focus,
so that that kind of thing wouldn't happen?
Please, tell me more.
It's ketones, Munchie.
It's always ketones.
Tom, you should come, you should come over.
You should come, you should get in here and make keto donuts with Ben.
Yeah, it sounds actually fucking cool.
You know what I'm gonna do for you?
I'm gonna be in Boston.
Get over here to Monkey House.
I'm gonna be in Boston real soon.
I'm gonna try and find a keto recipe.
I want to exchange recipes, Ben.
I want to exchange recipes and dishes.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna figure out how to make a keto thing.
I've been making, I've been making keto cakes.
I'm gonna make keto cupcakes.
I've made keto, I've been making keto pizzas.
That's my new thing.
It is, it is a whole world.
It's a whole world of weird experimentation that I am just,
I was just going nuts with.
Think we should move two points now.
It's really fun.
Yeah, I guess we're at that time.
Okay, but before we do, I want to say I got something arrived in mail today.
I ordered like this little blanket to put over my shoulders
because my shoulders always get cold.
It can be like in the heat of the summer,
but if I don't have something on my shoulders,
I just feel uncomfortable.
And it's like the cutest, softest thing.
And I'm just so happy.
And I'm just like, I just, I shove my face in it
because it's just so soft.
How nice.
And I-
Mages, sounds like you need a cake.
It's from age.
New cake.
You need to put on a fucking shirt question mark.
No, why are you wearing a shirt?
I think you need, you need big world of Warcraft shoulder pads.
That's the answer.
Good idea.
For sure.
It's just, it just makes me so happy.
And I love it so much.
And I've been wearing it throughout the whole podcast.
And I just, I just, it's, I, I've been petting it
because it's just so soft.
It's so soft.
We got to put that in the shirt.
I, uh, I initially-
Mages, line us.
I initially heard I bought a little blind kid
to put on my-
Ha ha ha ha ha.
No, no, did you know?
Yeah, even, even, even Mages servant
can't see what she looks like.
Had to be a blind kid.
No.
But can he see why kids love the taste
of cinnamon toast crunch?
No, she can.
He's blind.
No.
I'm sorry.
He can see it with his mind's eye.
Well, hey, team, it feels like a good place
to transition to voicemails,
if I could say so myself.
Yeah, you can do it.
Munchy, do you have those prepared?
Indeed it does.
Of course I do.
I, speaking of cooking,
there is a productive teen
that would like to have a word with us
on that issue.
Just, you know.
Teenagers.
To, to, to continue it.
Let me go over to Techno.
Here we go.
I'm looking at the charts for anal circumference by the way.
Hey, what's up, PCP?
I am the productive teen, 17,
and I hear to tell you that I like
that you talk about food sometimes.
Yeah.
I'm a culinary student,
so that's pretty self-explanatory.
Keep up, keep talking about food.
Well, lucky you.
Well, just, done and done, done and done.
I just, I want to say someone in the comments
last episode said something about the teen CP,
but they didn't spell it T-E-E-N-C-P.
They spelled it teen-C-P.
What?
As in like teen-C-tiny.
The teen CP?
Yeah, the teen CP.
Well, teen CP is the son of Zoomer Joe,
as we all know.
As we all know.
Shout out to that guy.
I'm going to finally pull the trigger,
just because of that voicemail on a vlog
I've been meaning to do for a while called
How to Food,
an instructional guide to millennials on how to food.
I don't think that's interesting.
What's the general thesis here?
It sounds scary.
Just basically, if you want to eat food,
here's how you should do it.
You open your mouth, you put the food in.
Do you follow this advice or is this aspirational?
Yes.
No, it's advice I follow.
Okay, okay, cool, cool.
Well, give us the deeds, dude.
Don't fuck with me.
I'm going to make a video about Jesus.
He's going to make a vlog about it, god damn it.
No spoilers.
Oh, god.
Maybe, I hope, my hope is that I vehemently disagree
and I can make a response video,
calling you.
Oh, good idea.
No, man, you'll love it,
because I'm going to start off by ranting.
Like, I'm just going to, for no particular reason.
By entering ketosis live on camera.
For no reason other than to make it more clickbaity,
I will start off by just shitting on HelloFresh.
Hey, fair enough.
Yeah.
All right, well, that's exciting.
Nightmare.
Capitalist nightmare.
God, I still like get like seething mad,
like opening my fridge, like thinking about food,
just thinking like, how is he so fucking stupid?
How does he not see?
How does he not understand?
And as stated last time we had this debate,
I don't even like HelloFresh.
I don't even like it.
You're supposed to be so mad that you don't like it vehemently.
Wait, speaking of food delivery services,
someone on Twitter added me in response to a picture
of Asterios Cocanos with Nathan fucking What's His Name
from Garfield Eats.
What?
Apparently Asterios brought up Garfield Eats on a podcast as well,
and he fucking met Nathan something.
I don't remember his last name,
but the guy with the tiny edited mouth.
God, our clout is pathetic.
We really need to get it up there.
We got to get the Garfield Eats guy on a PZP.
Imagine.
Whoa.
All right, all right.
Guys, well, Nate, I'm sorry, Ben, I just want to say
that you're a nightmare, and I hate you,
and I think that this person living under your brutal political regime
will agree with me.
This is Kill Ben.
Pain, misery, and more pain.
It's the year 2021 in the Ben St. Imperial Calendar,
month three, day 13.
After his kidney stone yielded many clones,
they proceeded to rape and pillage our lands.
Governments fell apart.
The world collapsed.
World order is in chaos.
We all live in shacks.
Me, my neighbors, everyone lives in shacks.
He sends his clones out twice a week to piss test everyone.
If you find someone not on keto, he takes a finger,
but he's really into the inter-agagement life.
So he tells you a knock, knock joke while he's taking your fingers.
Oh, but it's the same fucking knock, knock joke every single time.
He doesn't get any new material.
I was out looking for food scrounging the lands yesterday.
I came across a water fountain.
I think to myself, you know, water's keto friendly.
I get some fresh what?
No, no, more monster zero, more fucking monster zero.
He's always drinking bang energy.
We just get monster zero.
Nate, you should be the most worried.
After everything collapses, he takes your enterprises,
becomes best guy ever, locks you in a cell,
and you only get carbs.
And he laughs every time.
He loves it.
No, in my protein.
Destroy his kidney stones.
Kill Ben St.
Save the future.
Will do.
And with that, I would like you to direct you
to the link in the description to a free text.
You can play entirely with your superpower
and enlist fucking Rowdy.
Kill that piece of shit.
Ben St. in real life.
I am ordered a direct attack.
Ratties, no more video games.
Get a real gun in real life and shoot him in Boston, Massachusetts.
I beg you, please don't let this happen to you.
Do not let him take over the world.
Get fucking Rowdy.
Hey, Munchy.
So I'm not sure.
I could save this for RFCK on Wednesday.
If you can, you definitely should.
Okay, well...
You can give me a teaser, but don't spoil it or anything.
I sampled some new energy drink flavors.
Ooh, oh yeah, that's RFCK.
Okay, yeah.
All right, no more, no more, no more.
Hey, specifically...
Okay, I have a bunch to...
I have much to...
Before we start the next...
I do too, actually.
I do too.
Oh my god.
I'm just thinking about how there's those people
who are like the psychotic fans who think that
that they're being sent messages to kill the president in media.
And if Munchy had one of those fans,
it would not be secret messages.
They would just be like, oh, kill Ben St.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Exactly.
Guys, Munchy, before you go on,
I've got a fascinating thing that just happened to me.
And it's just that on Twitter,
someone sent me a message of the kind that I've long dreaded
and I finally just got one.
This is a message from someone who's essentially saying
that they are disappointed with my newest video
about the One Piece manga, in effect.
It's about manga, but I talk about One Piece, of course.
He's disappointed because I'm so adamant
about reading manga solely through scan relations.
And if I really loved manga as much as I say I do,
I should support the industry
and should give this media their two dollars
to read it monthly or whatever.
One Piece is like a super mega corporation.
It's like it doesn't need any more money.
I mean, Oda is fresh beyond his fucking wildest imagination
and he's the only person in the machine of One Piece
who you should give any fuck about.
So at this point, it's like Oda's spoken for.
Anything else you're spending on it
is just going into the machine.
I mean, there's something to be said for...
I support the peons who help bring the manga to me weekly
in the magazines and whatnot.
I suppose.
But like, so that's all cool.
And I support the industry, I don't know,
like obviously I'm in favorite existing.
But like, I don't think this man's understanding
the context of me having read this series.
When I first started reading One Piece,
what was I supposed to read?
The non-existent English releases?
And now look, okay, maybe I'm behind the fucking times
and I should catch my moral compass up to the real world.
But I've made basically my entire One Piece career
has been in scan relations.
I'm ass deep in the scanlation world.
And I'll just say, I frankly just don't care that much.
I mean, that's totally true.
If I can save a buck by doing something for free,
I will absolutely do it.
I don't even fault you, dude.
I think your position is totally fine.
It's just that I just don't care.
That's my position.
All right, I mean, that's it.
I just thought that was interesting.
I've been expecting something like that for a long time,
or perhaps my rampant video game piracy,
or I don't know,
I stole Sony Vegas to make videos with all these things.
What, Nate, I understand that you're witnessing.
Boy, isn't it nice that content on the internet
is freely distributed
and not bound up in the hands of big corporations
and the people that have all the money?
Like, isn't it nice that these things
are just available to the public to be used freely
for the betterment of time?
I recognize, I am doing something wrong.
I simply accept my immorality.
That's how I feel about it.
I don't think it's necessarily wrong.
Nate, I understand that you enjoyed the first episode
of my Whirling Dervish podcast.
I did.
I was talking about it before.
I very much enjoyed, especially,
my favorite part was your,
just talking about how people who do YouTube
and then are overly critical of it
as if they have no control over being involved with it.
I was just kind of agreeing with that.
You'll enjoy the second episode
because I go on a long tirade about how physical media needs to die
and how supporting,
like, I don't want to support an industry
that gives me anything less than the best possible experience
because it's like,
I'm always going to choose the best experience.
If downloading Torrance is the best experience,
why would I pay for something worse
when they have the option to offer me something better?
Which is what, you know,
it's the classic game, Newell Piracy is a,
what was the service problem?
Service problem, yeah.
And, you know, to that point on this
Viz Media thing or, you know,
by paying for One Piece or whatever,
when it is literally infinitely easier
for me to just Google Read One Piece Online,
bam, there's MangaReader.
Like, I don't, oh, great.
I don't have to like sign in or give money to someone.
I would, yeah, I'd argue, again,
this is a service problem.
I know Gabe's kind of shifted on that
over the years, I guess, but.
Imagine if you typed into Google Read One Piece Online,
the first result was Viz.
You clicked on it and you read it right there
and at the bottom of the page,
there was just a fucking tip jar
and it's like, it just says, like,
click this button if you loved this chapter
to donate a dollar to, you know, to it.
And then you just, like, people would just do it
because they're like, oh, this chapter was great, click,
you know?
Now, considering my own, would I ever, ever click that?
The answer is no, I will never click that button
to give money I don't have to, but other people will,
but other people will.
I would be surprised if you never had a moment
where you read a chapter and you were just so excited
and the button was right fucking there
I mean, maybe, if I knew it was like going to Oda
or like the editor, whoever,
the people actually making the product.
You guys are witnessing the fall of Titans right now.
Ben St. obliterated, literally killed, hopefully.
Yeah.
Nate, his moral compass shattered.
Shattered, yeah.
He obliterated.
And now the third in this building trilogy,
Tommy Oliver.
This next tape has only one track.
I'm gonna write it all the way to the Poly Station.
Oh, it's been too long, hasn't it, Tom?
Percy?
Yes?
Have you seen Thomas?
He's late with his shipment.
Oh, oh, no, your grace.
In fact, I heard he drove off a cliff.
Suicide, eh?
The butt controller scratched his toby belly.
I suppose it was only a matter of time.
You'll have to work double shift to make up for his absence.
Well, uh, you see about that, sir, I...
What is it, Percy?
What's the matter?
The fat controller leaned in and Percy whispered.
Well, I, uh, I suppose I'm a conch.
The station's empty.
I thought you would be here, Tom.
I long for the touch of your feminine fingernails on my back.
I guess there is no manicure for depression.
Wow.
Okay.
That was a journey.
Holy shit.
Oh, the fuck was that?
I just went on a journey.
It's, it's, it's a fourth loss tape.
This is the fourth loss tape.
Incredible.
Center around Tom, obviously.
Would you like to explain what has happened here, Tom?
Because obviously you would know better than anyone.
Um, I, I...
Would he?
I don't even know.
I just, I just went on a journey there.
Uh, I guess...
I mean, I mean, we're hearing these voices,
voices from your past, I assume,
or were you a train conductor of some sort?
Did you have an associate with a blue in some way?
I mean, back, back in, back in the day, I...
I think he was a train.
Back in the day.
I was all about that shining time station.
Maybe I'm just an actual projection
of Thomas the Tank Engine all this time.
Yeah, probably.
Probably.
I legitimately couldn't tell if that was a clip
from an old show at first.
I mean, parts of it were...
So well produced and acted.
No, I don't think it was, dude.
I think it was all good.
No, I think that was just...
The acting on Percy's accent.
And I mean, the fat controller.
Incredible.
No.
Uh, I, uh, there's a new storyteller video
after this episode goes up.
It's just a face reveal.
It's Tom this entire time.
Oh, are you saying that that was supposed to be a video
by the new storyteller?
Is that what was going on there?
Well, no, that was a hidden...
Well, I mean, for, for all intents and purposes,
it could be.
Okay.
We don't know.
I mean, it's a lost tape.
The Lost Tape Archive, he finds ancient secret tapes
recorded by us exposing our histories.
Okay.
And in this one, in this ancient tomb.
So, I mean, if Tom is indeed the new storyteller,
it will reveal.
I'll stick it to the video.
Was this because we did the whole Thomas the Tank Engine
joke last week?
I don't fucking know, dude.
Maybe.
I don't even remember what I had for breakfast this morning.
Oh, wait.
Yes, I do.
It was nothing.
Well, there's one thing we've learned.
It's that Percy is a cunt.
And, uh...
Alright, so what else, Tom?
Even back when I was like five, I knew that.
Oh, by the way, I just want to say, Lost Archives,
this and all the other ones have been absolutely fucking primal.
I think we have a contender for the voicemail grail.
Oh, yeah, I think we've got to add it.
Yeah, I think we've got to add it, yes.
Now, you know, I forgot to add someone last week, I think.
People in the comments were making suggestions
about who should be on the Hall of Fame,
and I agreed with every single one.
Oh, yeah, okay.
I think we shouldn't get too much in the business
of retroactive ones, but maybe the next two.
Well, let's see if we have something.
Let's see if we have any more contenders, shall we?
Yeah.
Oh, yes, I agree.
And I think we might, right here,
with a humble lad by the name of John.
Let's see what John has to say, or rather, sing.
One, two, this one's a question for the whole damn PCP.
That is, I want to know your favorite song.
But that's too easy, so we'll turn it up a notch.
Find the truth of the good and something wrong.
Sometimes great music can exist.
In media, you'd otherwise resist.
Where have you seen put to waste?
Good music that's locked in a cage.
The source, of course, it blinds you with rage.
I've heard this before.
This is Adrenaline by Tricell.
It's a kick-ass song.
It ends the arrow among a sense and an amaze.
That's, that's the one.
Subjectively I say this show is not okay.
But the song is so good, it takes the pain away.
The washer spins, you hear the bass, a giddy does her dance.
Her brother doesn't get to wash her underpants.
It puts me in a trance.
The brainwashing sits in, I drink my gin.
New episodes begin.
So what's your favorite song you know?
That comes from a bad movie, Game or Show.
John, that was great.
Oh, that's amazing.
That was better.
What was that even better than?
I want that set to the actual E.D.
So I could watch the Geary Dancer sexy little
lolly ass to that song.
What, what was the, I don't know.
Before we even get to the question,
before we get to the question, I just want to say
the dichotomy, because I picked out the show notes
because Nate was doing the math of the things.
And I did the voicemails for this.
And the dichotomy, there was an entry to the voicemails
of a dude saying, if anyone else other than Nate
picks the voicemails this episode, this won't get in.
But smoke weed, dude.
And that literally would have gotten in.
It would have gotten in.
Dude, it would have gotten in.
You say blame Munchie that you weren't.
Yeah, so your spotlight.
Fuck you, you're, I'm not even going to name you.
So die, just fucking die.
So there's just FYI.
John, John in parentheses, Ori Emo,
and I guess I'll put Aromanga, already got in
last episode into the PCP Grail.
But so, so he's a legend.
He's a legend.
What is the name of the Hall of Fame?
We call the voicemail Grail, as we're calling it.
It's just the Grail slash jail.
And you're in jail.
It's the voicemail versus the voice jail.
The only man in jail right now is the Japanese man, Yuta.
And he'll never get out.
I'm, I'm trying to, I'm going back.
I'm trying to find where people made recommendations.
So are we going to answer that guy's question?
Yeah, yeah.
Of course.
I mean, if we're sticking with like anime EDs,
if that's something that could count,
the OP to the show, Denpa Onato Seishun Otoko,
or electric, wait, I don't even remember
what the fuck that translates to.
Denpa means train, I think?
I don't know.
It's, no, Denpa.
Denpa Onato Seishun Otoko.
It's, it's the opening theme is by a band
called Shinsei Komate-chan.
It introduced them to me and they became my favorite band.
I dropped the show after the first episode,
but I've come back to that OP countless times.
That's cool.
There's a difference between a song from media
that you hate or media that you haven't seen.
And while there, I can't really think of any songs of,
for media that I hate.
I can definitely think of songs that I love
from things I'd never played,
which I think is arguably way more embarrassing
where you start humming a song and then someone's like,
uh, you know, oh, you like a cave story.
I'm like, uh, no, I just got recommended the theme song.
Egg passage.
And I really like it.
That's like it in my head.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
So fucking good.
So there's a lot of instances where I, uh,
shamefully listen to music, uh, of things I've never seen.
Like again, cave story.
I listen to the Cowboy Bebop soundtrack a lot.
Well, that's just based.
I know it's all, it's all good.
I mean, the Cowboy Bebop soundtrack shows up on like,
recommended lists of just good jazz albums.
Like, I don't think there's any shame in listening to that.
Even though fucking Kano learned how to make jazz
for that album.
Incredible.
But, but I literally don't even know what Cowboy Bebop does,
or if it's like a Doctor Who scenario.
Who is this man?
There is no Cowboy Bebop.
What are his credentials?
Where is he?
Get him out of here.
Does he even bebop?
All right.
I don't know.
I mean, here's just an easy example.
I mean, I love a lot of the music in MLP,
but I also love MLP.
So, I mean, it's not embarrassing at all,
but a lot of people might think it is.
So there you go.
There's my answer.
That's a flaccid shit.
I really have to wreck my brain to find a show I dislike,
but I also like the music of.
So, I can't really answer it completely,
but one song that comes to my head is of a show I haven't watched,
but I didn't hear good things about it.
But I kind of like the opening,
but I think I like the opening music in addition to the visuals.
So, if I haven't seen the visuals,
I probably wouldn't like the song as much,
but I still like the song.
Sure, sure.
Is of Maria Holik?
I think that's.
Yeah, Maria Holik OP.
That would be my number.
Same studio as Denpo.
Oh, another one I brought up.
And yeah, I mean, all their OPs are fucking amazing.
Every Shaft OP is.
Shaft kills it, though.
So, whether the show itself is good.
Oh, you know, I could say.
I also dropped that one.
On the Shaft subject.
Yeah, like, did you say, like, all their openings are great.
Everything for, god damn it, Zetsubo Sensei.
Oh.
Like, I've only finished.
I've only finished season one and, like,
maybe a little bit of season two,
but I've listened to every OP and they're all incredible.
I love Zetsubo Sensei.
Have you listened to the Otsuki Kenji and Zetsubo Shojo Tachi album?
No, I definitely have not.
So, the guy who sings in all the OPs is a guy named Otsuki Kenji.
He's a frontman of a band called Kiniku Shojo Tai,
or the, like, bodybuilding women's club or something like that.
And they did a whole album of songs in the style of the OPs.
It has the OPs on there and then, like,
just a bunch of other tracks of him and all the girls singing,
and it's a good time.
It sounds incredible.
I mean, the best thing about it for me is that it's,
you watch the show, you get used to the voice actors and whatnot,
who are, you know, they're in the fucking show,
all the girls and the main guy and whatnot,
and they just sing in the fucking opening and ending,
and it's, like, the best thing ever.
It's so fucking sick.
And then you go listen to the full songs,
it's, like, even better.
They're so good.
But, yeah, I mean, I should definitely check that out.
Tom, Benny Boy.
Yep.
Any answer?
Any, any?
Um, I guess...
Oh, no.
I can't think of anything.
I'm sorry, Normie.
The only thing I can think of right now is...
Tisk, tisk, tisk, tisk.
The only thing I can really think of is,
I wasn't a huge fan of the game, Crypt of the Necrodancer.
I couldn't get into the game,
but the soundtrack is fucking sick.
Oh, that's a good video game!
Okay, well, I'll agree with that, except that's a great game.
I'm, I just...
Yeah, punk.
It's funny you say that, Tom, because...
I haven't played a lot of it.
My buddy, we did co-op, and I couldn't really get into it.
I hate these SJW games with female protagonists.
Like, what the fuck, guys?
Just shut it down now!
Who are you, Sargon of a God?
It's really funny that you, that you,
that, like, the music is what stuck out to you,
because to me, the appeal of that game was that I could
dance to my own music.
You know, that's cool, but I've tried it, and it, it, it, it...
You have to find the right song.
Like, sometimes, like, it...
Yeah, yeah.
You need to find the right song.
But, that game has such a good soundtrack on its own
that I have, like, no real desire to replace the music.
It's not really my genre, I guess.
I, I was, I just, I put in music by the band Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas,
which is, like, like, heavy metal dance music, basically,
and, um, that made it, like, it was just so funny
to play along to that I made it worth it.
Oh, I, on a, on a stream, twitch, twitch.tv slash stank comics,
I put in, I put in some Hilary Duff Nightcore as a...
Excellent.
As the, uh, as the sound backing sound.
It didn't work very well at all.
Actually, no, the thing is, it was just so fast.
Yeah.
It was, like, this insanely fast beat.
Yeah, you really gotta know the beat.
You know what would probably help a lot is, uh, there's a website called...
There's a website called Songkick that tells you the BPM of any song.
Oh, good, yeah, yeah.
That's what you need.
Yeah.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
We have fun here at the PCP.
But you know what else is fun?
Having sex with animals.
Well, there may be some animals you aren't really sure about how to have sex with.
Well, luckily, we have an ice member teaching us how to have sex with hyenas.
So about hyenas.
Hyenas are my jam.
So I know a lot about the hyena penis situation.
Very cool.
So yeah, it's called the pseudo penis despite actually being a slitheress.
But you'd be surprised to know that it functions more like a penis than like a clitoris.
I am surprised.
Hyena is actually...
I'm a rouse.
Their sex is like docking.
Like the male has a penis inside the female pseudo penis, which has a canal.
What the fuck?
What?
For this sort of like the vagina like is in the clitoris.
It's very strange.
OK, sure.
What the fuck?
When people say, oh, it's a pseudo penis, but it's actually a clit.
It's like it's really just a dick.
Like, I don't know what else to tell you.
But like, which is why hyena society is so female dominated.
It's because the males can't assert their dominance on the females via sex.
Like, if the females aren't into it, like the males aren't going to snake their dick
into the lady's dick.
It's just not going to happen.
But yeah, actually, they also give birth out of their pseudo penis.
And that's just a glory mess.
So you can make up videos if you want.
I guess that would be the yikes.
That's what I have to say.
Hyenas are pretty neat.
Just don't touch their penises.
OK, bye.
Boy, we really fucked up when we opened this rabbit hole.
I'm the one who opened up this mystery box.
I'm about to do it.
Sorry, I was just clapping really fast.
In triumph.
In sheer triumph.
Also, I came on really bad.
Well, hyenas are sick.
I feel bad.
I guess I feel bad for the women.
Hyenas are sick.
I feel bad for the men and the women.
Like, the men are, you know, whatever.
They can't get their shit going because they're smaller and they got small dick.
They got to insert in female dick.
And women, like, have to birth out of their fucking female dick.
That sounds horrible.
Birth out of their dick, dude.
It's made for it.
Holy shit.
I guess.
They love it.
Guys, I love it.
Nature's M-Preg.
Radcon 4.
First stretch goal, docking.
Second stretch goal, live birth.
Stretch goal 5.
M-Preg.
Et cetera, et cetera.
By the way, guys.
We can combine all these.
Are you right?
Thank you, Yeen girl.
There's synergy here.
And speaking of, speaking of Yeen girl, I just want to say you've heard of Yeen.
You've heard of SNEP.
Get ready for the third furry term in this trilogy.
And this is an open letter to every furry.
What is Yeen?
I don't know what I didn't know.
SNEP is Snow Leopard.
Oh, OK.
It's really funny because that girl's voice sounded like Kaze.
And it made me assume.
I thought it might have been her.
Did it?
Did it really?
I, yeah.
Yeah, a little bit.
I think it might just be that furry.
Like, is furry kind of like being gay?
They're cut from the same claw.
Like a voice.
You know what I mean?
I've got big furry voice.
Kind of like tranny voice, you know?
Furry voice.
Muffled by fur.
We will let the audience decide in the comments.
You know, comment is furry a choice like being gay.
Yeah, OK.
But also in that.
Say a choice.
I said a voice.
Is it a choice like being black?
Both are open.
OK.
So post in comments.
Any more of these abbreviation for animals like SNEP or Yeen.
And we have, yote.
For coyotes, yote.
Yote.
Use this sentence.
Want to fuck that yote real bad.
Maybe I'll put some yeens later and maybe a SNEP.
But first, I want to deal with this yote.
Wow.
That's all I wanted to say.
That's good.
I love these terms so much.
Please, I fucking beg you.
I'm sure there's a gold mine of them that I, we aren't.
You know, OK.
You know how when you're speed running Pokemon red or blue,
you choose like one character?
Because the sheer number of times that your character's
like name is said in text box.
Imagine the sheer number of frames you're saving
by only referring because we know how many times per day
you're going to talk about a coyote and how much you want to fuck it.
You're saving so many frames by a briefing that you're saving.
Two syllables.
So many.
Every single time.
That's right.
Hey, if you're, if you're, if you're a coyote, if you're a coyote furry
and you're like a bear, right?
But like not like a bear bear, like a muslin.
You're like getting, you're getting fucking jacked.
You're fucking getting, are you a yoke to yoke?
A yoke to yoke for show.
A yoke to yoke.
Oh, my new Twitter handle.
Well, move on.
Let's go.
Guys, this, I'm, there's going to be hours.
I know, I need a fucking, I need a fucking cold shower after this.
Hours of content coming from this.
OK, all right.
Now, speaking of D&D, we were talking about earlier,
there's someone who would like to play a game with us as well,
but not a role playing game, rather a board game.
This is the game board, Gaylord.
Game board, Gaylord.
Attention, PCB.
This is the game board, Gaylord speaking.
Wow.
I challenge you to beat me in a board game.
Let's play battleship on a five by five grid.
We will be using one, four-tall ship, one, three-tall ship, and two, two-tall ships.
Please place your ships now, and I'll begin my turn.
A four.
You suck my battleship.
Will you hit me?
Who knows?
This has been the game board, Gaylord.
Good luck.
And remember, I won't fucking cheat.
I swear, please trust me for the love of God and everything, holy.
Well, OK, so we are in a dice scenario right now.
We are on a five by five grid right now.
He's attacked A, what was it?
A-F.
A four, I think.
A four.
A four, A four.
All right, A-F.
And he is, let's see, guys, did he sink our battleship?
Let's see.
Look, the game board, Gaylord, is a fool because he told us where he's going to attack before
we even had time to place our ships.
Now I can dodge it perfectly.
OK, OK, so how much?
OK, we have a three-tile ship, a four-tile ship, and a two-tile ship.
Two two-tiles, I think.
Pretty sure.
We are attacking C-six.
There you go.
Damn.
Wait, no, it's a five by five.
Six is off the grid, god damn it.
Yeah, yeah.
C-five, C-five.
Wait, how can you fit that many fucking boats on a five by five grid?
I think you can.
You can.
The biggest one's four, so it doesn't have to be a hit.
Well, we're just hitting constantly, and it's just a race to see if you can sink.
Like, who makes the mistake of missing once and therefore losing?
I mean, that's battleship for you, I guess.
That's a great game.
Well, good luck with that.
Hell yeah.
I've never played battleship before, but let us just show that we will kill you and all of your boats.
You don't need to play the game.
Just watch the movie.
Yeah, that is right.
Is there a movie for battleship?
There is a battleship movie.
Rihanna, I think.
Fuck.
Rihanna starts at the battleship.
Right?
It was like a Michael Bay style movie.
Yeah, it was a Michael Bay style theatrical release starring Rihanna.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, as the titular battleship.
That's crazy.
Well, guys, we seem to have reached it in here.
Wait.
Could there be?
I think there's someone.
I think there's something that needs
to be concluded in arc that needs to be satisfied.
What could it be?
Someone's been building up for months at this point for weeks.
And that's the end of the riddle my ass Batman arc.
Oh no.
There are three voicemails.
I've not listened to any of them.
So we're going to experience them together.
Okay.
Here we go, boys.
Well, you all have been waiting for it.
If you want to dumb, I've got what you need,
because the next voicemail is from a riddle my ass, Batman.
Batman who vapes Ben Saints.
Yeah.
We're not doing well.
Why does it sound like he recorded this?
Yeah.
Do not speak.
I'm sure he did.
I'm going to have a man more.
VG also stands for best guy.
Woo.
Yay.
Why are we getting a recap episode?
You got to have the clip episode before the finale.
Joe, I've never heard about this.
You know, he really should have worked on his recording.
God, they stuck.
They really stuck.
You just skipped the head.
No, no, no, no.
No, I like this.
You got to have Bill that.
He's a man of all names.
First member riddle my ass, Batman.
Yeah.
Welcome to the stand.
Woo.
Oh, Batman.
He's a sheep.
He's Batman.
I said sheep.
Oh, I remember when he saved me.
Oh, that was good.
I can't even tell what the fuck he said.
So God, this is shitty recording.
Oh, I got room to cook.
Oh, yeah.
I just want you to know that when a day in sim comes out,
I'm using you as my lover.
It don't work.
Yay.
I remember that.
He's never fucking had.
I think so.
It's a sign of inclusion of real my ass, Batman.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, yeah.
There it is.
Okay.
All right.
Well, that was the entirety of.
Okay.
Here we are.
The end of an era.
The final battle.
Are you guys ready?
Because, frankly, I'm not.
I feel like I'm underprepared.
I'm not going to battle.
Only Digi remains to be saved, I think.
Well, let's see if he will be.
Batman left.
So members of PCP, are you ready for a final riddle?
Question first.
Yes.
Since there's only one member left,
can we just say it's Digi and go away pretty easily?
Wait, guys, don't do that.
Huh?
Hear me out.
You guys know my lifelong dream has become a loli.
Well, this is my chance.
My ass is so fast that I already have tits.
And I got to do this and get rid of my digging balls now.
This is a perfect opportunity.
Please, help me be a loli.
Are you sure, Digi?
I guess if you eat the balls.
Yes.
Wow.
Okay, Digi.
Riddler, our answer is the riddle you have not yet answered.
Question is...
Jeff.
Wrong.
Yeah.
Oh.
Put him in the testicular tenderizing tuna now.
Thank you, guys, so much.
And this is...
Oh, my God, the pain.
The pain is so unbearable.
Oh, no.
Not the pain.
Oh, my God, the pain.
This is a mistake.
Not the pain.
Oh, my God, the pain.
The pain is unbearable.
Oh, my God.
No.
I'm sensing some pain here.
Balls and dick?
Help, help, help.
Help, please.
This is indulgent.
Let me do this.
Guys, help.
Help, help, help.
Anyone else?
Oh, my God, the balls and dick.
Oh, shit.
Gratuitous.
Damn.
Okay.
What is that?
That was...
Next one.
All right, all right, all right.
Well, I got...
I hate to say it, Digi, but I guess you don't got a dick anymore.
Was that me?
Balls.
Yeah, that's you.
That's you.
That was you.
I feel like I just listened to someone's manic episode.
I have no fucking idea what's going on.
No, Digi doesn't even know what's happening.
Okay, you were over a pit of dick eating piranhas,
dick and ball eating piranhas,
and you told Batman to not save you
by solving all the Ask Batman riddles.
No, no, Batman left.
It's just the PCPs.
Batman and peace.
And therefore, you were dropped into the pit.
It burns.
Right, right.
To become a loli.
Yeah, duh.
Okay, so here we go.
So is there one more?
There's one final thing, right?
Yeah, there's one more.
I just want to say this is real my Ask Batman.
Thank you, PCP, for playing my shitty show
every week, week after week.
You and the audience at home seem to have
really loved this show,
and I appreciate your support.
You did.
A quick apology to Mage and Digi
for dropping you in the dick eating worms.
I had to switch it up every once in a while,
you know, even we had some.
I keep them on their toes.
Yeah, absolutely.
Don't worry.
Riddle my Ask Batman isn't canceled yet.
I am just getting started.
Look forward to new content,
such as silly songs with Batman.
Who wants to be a PCP millionaire?
And reading from Riddle My Ask Batman's fan fiction.
Look forward to all these next time on the PCP.
Same PCP time, same PCP channel.
Yay!
Oh my god!
The legend.
When are we going to get a...
The legend walks off into the sun.
When do we get family feud in Batman's ass?
Oh, silly life.
In Batman's ass, hell yeah.
So I want to remind everyone
that Riddle My Ask Batman has a work of fiction
on Wattpad called PCP, The Ultamite Fanfic.
The Quest for Cold Corona
by Riddle My Ask Batman.
I'm going to read
a passage from the first chapter called
a Passage from the first chapter called
PCP Guy Origins.
1.1111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111111
I hear you scream in your most annoying of high-pitched, glass-shattering, screechy ones.
Fear not, for there were just enough freaks and weirdos to make all the anime and comics,
you know, actual cool stuff that your heart could ever desire.
On this planet there lived in an old, run-down apartment,
one man who swore he would not subcome to the life of a normie
and sought to make his living as an artist.
He had tried many disciplines drawing comics, playing music, mostly raps,
and even writing his world's equivalent of My Little Pony fan fiction.
Always putting his OC in the middle of a love triangle
of whatever characters he happened to be feeling a fancy for the week.
However, his favorite thing to do was to make analytical YouTube videos about his favorite anime.
Well, it is actually rendered to a looser tube on this planet.
Two as a... okay.
They were a bit more self-aware.
Our beloved original handboy, PCPGuy, also known by the name Crass,
short for pro-crass to his internet friends.
He had no real life to speak of.
So that's your tool.
I want to know.
Link in the description.
The stage has been set.
I hope that that's just enough to whet your whistle.
I'm intrigued.
I want to know more about this cast of characters.
Well, there's only one, but you know.
I have a question.
Is there, like, somewhere where you would listen to, like,
a real me as Batman's all of the story,
like in a chronological order?
I mean, they're all on episodes?
Or, I mean, they're in the South Club?
Though, things are getting deleted from the SoundCloud,
so, you know, they're little by little.
But they're all in the episodes.
Archive, people, it's up to you.
It's up to you to save FlashPlayer.
Maybe...
Wait, I mean, are they all still in the speak pipe?
I suppose that's true.
I haven't deleted any from speak pipe.
Maybe I'll just go in and make a compilation.
You know, I've been working on that editor,
that editor show case.
Right, how's that going?
It wouldn't be the same to just listen to the...
Like, surely if you wanted a compilation,
you would want to clip it from the episodes
so that you get the reaction as well.
That's probably true, honestly.
Probably be better that way, significantly so.
Yeah.
I think so.
I think it adds something.
Well, commenters, let us know in the comments
if you want that.
Or just do it for us.
Yeah, that's true.
Or yeah, yeah, that's true.
We've come to the end of Real Me As Batman,
and we've come to the end of this week's PCP.
How do we all feel?
How do we all feel about how we did it this week?
Hungry.
It was long.
Review, review.
They're always this long now, Nate.
This is just how they are.
That's true.
You're not wrong.
They've gotten longer.
Almost three hours.
I'm also hungry.
I'm hungry.
Maybe I can go...
Maybe before my stream at twitch.tv slash stcomics,
I can go and maybe I can...
There's probably not enough time to view keto donuts.
Perhaps not.
My...
Damn.
Next time you hear from me, boys,
you'll see in Boston, Massachusetts,
possibly have met with Ben.
Oh, okay.
And Tom, if he's...
How's his journey?
Yeah, we'll have to hang out again.
Yes.
Yeah, last time was a bust.
Now there will be a bust out of a nut.
You know what I'm trying to say?
Yeah.
Are you saying, Mitch?
Don't set any toes on your way there.
Don't worry.
I don't walk extremely angrily and also am stupid.
His legs flailing wildly in all directions as he walks.
Like kicking the air each time he lifts his legs.
Like as hard as you can.
Like he's going to punt like a football.
Just begging for it.
Get the...
Get the fucking...
Get on our Patreon.
Bonus episodes.
Yeah.
Peace at patreon.com slash the procrastinators people.
$5 for 25 full bonus episodes.
And another one coming before too long.
So keep your eyes fucking healed.
Also, the last one...
I'm really happy with the last one.
I thought it was really, really funny and good.
And we learned a lot of the dark truths about it.
We did.
I realized that I just initiated the close out of this podcast.
But I have to also ask, did anybody on this podcast ever address that I did in fact find
and talk about the pizza party podcast?
I'm sorry.
What?
Was this addressed on a PC?
Question mark?
I don't...
No.
That can't be true.
I went on Who Are These Podcasts and did a whole podcast about the pizza party podcast.
What the fuck?
Well, frankly, I think you're talking out of your ass.
How did you find out about that?
It was not easy.
I had to go into the heart of Tibet.
I found them.
I had to climb a mountain.
I had to find Shambhala.
I had to play Uncharted 2.
This has opened up a whole new avenue.
A whole new avenue of X and Y.
We have to drive in this.
I feel like the mystery has only deepened.
We were so concerned.
We were so concerned if we could find the podcast.
We didn't find out if we should or not.
The answer is we definitely shouldn't have.
It was a huge mistake.
We should keep going.
Yes, someone was concerned if the pizza party podcast got the food.
That's why he's not here.
Oh my God.
Oh, God.
No.
We can't let this happen.
Another lost soul.
All right.
Well, I guess that's it.
I don't know.
Shirts or something.
I don't even know what we do.
There's a Patreon.
I know that exists.
Patreon.com.
The Procrastinators people.
We love the money.
Please give us.
And bonus episodes.
Those are the main drive.
25 fucking episodes.
That's so many.
Jesus Christ.
All right.
We're at TPCrastinators on Twitter.
Updates, releases, et cetera, et cetera.
General upkeep.
There you go.
Hey, you know what?
Okay.
New plug thing for me specifically.
All right.
I like like comments.
Not as in I want you to comment for like the algorithm.
I don't even know if that works.
I don't know if that's the thing.
Probably is.
It's better for you.
I just like reading them.
So no, just make your comments not shit and also do more of them because I like to hear
from you.
Like, I think the only, it's a weird feedback loop where I think that the PCP comments are
terrible because they think we don't read them.
The reason we don't read them is because they're terrible.
So just assume we're reading them and make them better and then I think they've gotten
better.
I haven't looked in a little while.
So for me, I never really read the PCP comments too much, but it's just that for now, like
I consider my job, my job is done once I've released the episode for the month or like
it's scheduled ahead of time or whatever.
I mean, I care about what people think and I want to, you know, whatever, fix things
if they're bad.
Make no mistake.
This isn't for intergagement.
It just makes me feel good that I have made an impact, good, positive or negative.
I don't even know if the comments are good or bad, so I'm neutral, but I guess be good
if you want.
Typically, anything I release, I check comments for at least a day afterwards and the PCP,
it feels like comments from people who are assuming that no one's reading them.
Okay.
Well, be advised people.
We've been saying, I do read the comments most weeks.
I do as well.
Yeah.
Well, there you go.
There you go.
Be good, ladies and gentlemen.
I don't think they're that bad, honestly.
I think they've improved a lot.
There's probably a couple of people out there listening who think, I always comment nice.
Okay.
Yeah, but it's not everybody.
Have a good night.
Bye.
We'll see you next week.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.