I'm gonna bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
That son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Bitch, bitch, bitch.
All right, then, welcome to a canceled episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
It is January 9th, 2022.
It's the new second episode of the new year.
Who do we have?
Cybershell is here.
I'm back for my mandated yearly appearance.
I'm only here because I know there's at least one guy in the PCV audience who probably
like fucking hates me and he's like, oh god, can't believe he's back, he's on another episode
to ruin it.
Yeah, I'm here just to ruin that one guy's day.
I want that guy to leave a comment and explain why.
I want him curious.
Yeah, I want to see the yes-cybershell-no-watch guy.
Oblivion follows here.
Hi, I've ruined everything.
Yeah.
CeCe is here.
The Tails Gets Trolls manager, tape and primer, and me, Ben St, and Gibb and take.
Did you forget Simsie?
Oh, I did forget Simsie, sorry.
I'm the background presence.
I'm only here because we thought Gibb wasn't going to be here and we needed a British person
to direct all those two.
There's two people here that I wasn't expecting to be here, so there's too many, but that's
okay.
We're bringing back the old episodes where people just talk over each other all the time
and yell.
Everybody likes them.
Everybody liked the one with Tisnaker because it was just a lot of yelling, a lot of talking
over each other, and it was good.
That's what people liked it.
Well, that's good to know.
So, Gibb, do you want to explain why are you here?
You weren't supposed to be here.
I wasn't supposed to be here.
I was supposed to be in the air or at the airport because I was going to fly out to
Boston to see Munchie and Ben and everyone, and it's going to be a fun time, but it was
going to be a fun time.
But there's a COVID problem, and it came up at the exact last possible moment it could
have come up this morning, the day I was supposed to be gone by now, but my dad tested positive,
and because we can't be sure that I don't have it already, because it's likely that
if he was infectious earlier and not symptomatic, then everyone in the house is infected, and
I wouldn't have time to figure it out.
So I'm probably going to get COVID in a couple of days, and I can't go and see my friends,
but it sucks.
That's all.
It just really sucks.
Yeah, I also got COVID from my dad.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
He probably got it from work, and yeah, everyone's getting it, but I'm better now, mostly.
Who's had COVID?
Simsie, you have not had COVID.
Cybershell, have you had COVID yet?
I've not had COVID, apart from getting the shot and feeling shitty.
That sort of counts, but no, I haven't actually got it, because I've just been inside all
the time, and I refuse to be social with anyone, ever.
I literally never leave the house except for groceries, but I've still managed to get it
twice.
Amazing.
I'm still recovering from it.
This is the penalty for having things like friends and family.
How dare you?
I lived in a tiny university house with fucking four people, and one bathroom, and my friend
she got it, and somehow none of the rest of us caught it, and in the full two weeks that
she was positive.
Impressive.
I don't understand how that happened.
What was she, pacing in the garden or something?
I don't understand.
Women aren't even real, that's why.
True.
Women aren't as extremely, not extremely, but higher, like transmission easier.
Easy transmission.
It's like twice as easy or something.
You just need to breathe near someone, or not even cough.
Less lethal.
That's a good right, question mark.
I don't really know enough about this shit to be like making definitive statements.
They say that, but then I've seen other experts be like, no, probably not.
It's probably just that people have more immunity now due to vaccinations and antibodies due
to previous infections.
That's probably the reason for the reduced hospitalizations and deaths.
Speaking of reduced.
I've seen conflicting opinions.
I wanted to leave a comment on, I can't remember if it was the last episode, and you're like,
is Ben okay?
His brain sounds a little shrunken lately.
I don't know what that's about.
It is, but not necessarily due to COVID, but maybe due to COVID.
That might just be a natural thing happening to everybody.
I mean, that's a good point because I've been vaccinated twice.
I got the booster and everything too, and I still got it, but the symptoms weren't
bad.
I heard it here first, folks.
Vaccines don't work.
Don't get them.
They don't.
They're an anti-vax podcast now.
You're better off without them, actually.
Okay.
YouTube, please don't pretend I didn't say that, YouTube.
Kill Ben.
The algorithm doesn't like it.
The management at Sims 4 does not support this message.
If COVID does shrink your brain, if everyone gets COVID, it evens out because then everyone
will be stupider.
No, think about it like this.
On balance.
Think about it like this.
If it's smaller, the neurons will have less to travel to be fired from the distance would
be smaller.
You'd actually think even quicker.
You think your brain is going to be ... It actually just makes it more efficient, makes
it more aerodynamic, actually.
The shrinking is superior.
You can have enhanced reflexes like Spiderman.
Maybe it's the racist part of your brain that gets shrunk, and this is a good thing
for society.
Well, I mean Daredevil is blind, but because of that, he has super hearing and proprioception.
Because of that, his brain shrunk.
Ben, Daredevil is not real.
You get COVID, I don't care.
You get COVID, you lose your sense of smell and taste, so probably your other senses get
more powerful to compensate.
You're going to be COVID Daredevil.
It's logical.
You're going to be out there fighting crime with your bandana over your nose.
COVID Daredevil, he lost his sense of smell and taste, but now his sense of ... I don't
know, his sense of balance is really good.
Cum production has increased.
He's also blind, not because of COVID.
He just happened to be blind anyway, so that one didn't get improved.
He's blind because he's a fan of Netflix's Daredevil, so he just wants to go the full
nine yards and cosplay.
That's why he's blind, just because he likes Daredevil.
So anyway, I finally got a test.
I used my last test on New Year's because I thought I would be negative and I would
be able to party on New Year's, but alas, I was still positive.
So I was like, fuck.
So New Year's is ruined.
But then I could not find any more tests, so even though I'm almost certainly was negative
shortly after that, I was not able to confirm it.
So it took me like a week until my friend Dwoob brought me over a test, because he found
one in a pharmacy.
So now I am officially negative, finally.
So that's good news, I guess.
Took a while.
Yeah.
What a hassle.
What a drag.
Yeah, this disease thing ain't so good.
Get rid of it.
In my opinion, the coronavirus is bad.
Excuse me.
I was informed COVID would be over by now.
I'm done with this COVID shit.
I'm done pretending that I'm going to care about it.
I'm just going to pretend like it doesn't exist and go about my daily life and infect
everyone.
At least you're honest.
I think that's the way to do it.
Also the economy.
It's going to last for a couple more years.
Is good.
Coronavirus bad.
The economy, good.
No masks, no doctors, baby 2022.
Are you running for president?
Yeah.
Well, I will be old enough by the next election cycle, so there we go.
Oh, scary Ben, dying of old age.
I shouldn't say that.
I shouldn't say that out loud.
Ben's going to be 78.
I'm as old as Jesus was when he was crucified.
Think about that.
And you've done as much, if not more, with your life.
And I'm going to be crucified.
Jesus didn't even have a podcast.
He had a bunch of followers, sure, but they didn't buy a shirt, so they didn't do anything.
I mean, Jesus was like the first podcast.
The Sermon on the Mount was a legendary podcast.
I feel like I've made that exact joke before.
I say it and I'm like, sounds familiar.
It was a good episode.
It was a good episode, but it goes down with a bit more editing.
I should have gone living full to soul, that one out.
Oh yeah, I'm the only one who can edit good, clearly.
I know that there's PCP mega fans out there that are going to like, anytime you reuse
a joke, they're going to have a comment like, didn't you actually use this joke back in
episode 141?
It's like, okay, thank you so much.
I don't, frankly, frankly, I don't think so.
I don't think PCP viewers are that astute.
I don't think they have what it takes to call me out on something like that.
I think they're a bunch of dummies.
I think they're a bunch of roots.
Therefore, it's okay to just reuse jokes and content from years past.
Dude, I used so many jokes in Cluster Punk Kitchen and no one noticed.
I had to be self-aware about it and still no one could even remember what the joke
that was reused was.
I mean, you use them a certain amount of times and it becomes, and it's endearing.
There's a sweet spot for reuse.
Like, Cluster Punk Kitchen was you as well.
Yeah, it was all revealed yesterday.
Oh, that's right, Gibby.
Gibby, you weren't on the last episode.
We delved into all of the...
I saw the thing and it was like, everything revealed, but I forgot about Cluster Punk
Kitchen.
I remember there was...
Oh, wait, let me ask you.
There was some confusion because there was some guy who would call in to say like, racist
shit and he had a deep voice and I occasionally confused him with Cluster Punk Kitchen.
Did you ever get frustrated?
They'd like, no, that's not, that wasn't me.
I actually don't remember.
I've ever called in and said anything racist, I don't think.
There was a guy who I thought was the Cluster Punk Kitchen guy because he just happened to
have a deep voice, but no, it was just a coincidence.
I don't think that would have been me.
I don't think I've ever...
No, I know it wasn't you.
I'm saying I thought it was you and I said it...
Yeah, I know, I know.
I'm just like, huh, I don't know.
I don't actually remember.
There's so many of them.
I remember the guy as well.
We haven't shown a few of his voicemails on the show because they were just like...
After a while, we eventually just started to be like, stop.
Anti-black lives, sort of like, okay, this guy's fucked.
He's like this very racist shit.
It wasn't even funny.
It wasn't funny.
Well, that's the main thing.
I mean, if you're going to be racist, at least be funny about it.
I mean, kind of.
Yeah.
It's strange to me.
There's like a deranged, like racist person, but who's also still a PCP fan for some reason.
It's like, I better submit my voicemails just so they know it's up.
Well, haven't heard from him in a while, so he may have finally been weeded out of the
pack.
Wow.
Turns out, Ben, figure out, you just have to stop playing the bad voicemails if you don't
want to get the bad voicemails.
Yeah.
If I were to say something racist, it'd be like, oh, black people have small toes and
I don't like it.
It'd be like something stupid like that.
Oh, clip that.
Clip that one.
No reason to live.
Canceled.
Yeah, I voicemail anarchy, basically.
There was like very rare, very rare exceptions for like, and it was only people who made
like repeated attempts to make like deliberately shitty voicemails.
Everyone gets one shitty voicemail.
Yeah.
Yeah, kind of.
It was the only time I would be like, Eleazar, just edit this out and pretend we didn't do
it because it's not even funny.
It's not engaging.
It sucks.
Yeah.
Like occasionally we do have like somebody who has like a weirdo opinion about something
that we address and then it's not so bad.
There's a discussion there.
Otherwise it could be funny.
It's only been like two or three times that someone's just been so like gross, not even
like in a gross like poo poo way because those ones annoyingly get played on the show and
I don't like it when somebody takes a shit and records it.
But like.
Oh yeah.
Oh, that stays in.
That's all content.
But like gross topic wise and opinion wise, it's only happened like three or four times.
I don't like bad people.
Anyone else with me?
You guys don't even understand.
Coming out with all the like the best tips right now, Simsie.
Wow.
No, Simsie, you can't say that.
We have so many bad people in our audience.
You can't say that.
You'll offend them.
Fuck you.
There's so many people that suck that listen to the PCP.
It's our main demographic.
I hope you guys are ready for next week's voice mails.
Uh oh.
I think every week for now they're going to be like 15 minutes long because you're not
going to have all the good ones.
It's just going to be the shitty low effort ones.
No.
No way.
If you're if you're longer than two minutes, you get auto deleted.
I don't care.
Actually, I think the time limit is 130.
So I don't think they evenly.
Oh, on the topic of bad people, I guess I can bring up the I guess I can bring up the
weird shit that happened on Furious Cat for me.
I tweeted about it yesterday.
I saw yeah, I saw you getting or tweeted something about it.
Sure.
Yeah.
I've drawn like a few more like dogs.
By the way, everyone follows Simsie.
Everyone follows Simsie.
Is it at Simsie fart?
Yeah.
Simsie fart because art was taken and boy was taken so I thought whatever and Simsie
was taken.
But I have a Curious Cat page that like Simsie for big, big booby, big booby mommy milkers.
Hell yeah.
There's that website Curious Cat, which is just basically a Q&A website where people
can submit questions anonymously.
And somebody noticed that I'd been drawing slightly more dark skinned girls than usual
recently.
Which is not like intentional or anything.
How dare I exactly.
Uh oh.
We got we got a problem here.
Yeah.
And they and they sent me a bunch of fucking questions that weren't even questions.
They were just saying like, damn, that's just horrible racist chair and it's like fuck
off.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
I don't understand why some of you so motivated just from seeing a drawing to do that.
That's mindbrained.
No, I also, I also don't understand.
People bad.
Uh, uh, if you don't cyber cyber shell, you, you, you must, you understand your, your,
your, your kind of that like that.
Why don't you explain why people do that?
Uh, what do you mean?
Why I'm kind of like that.
I feel bad.
I was making a joke, but now I feel bad.
I was just going to say, this is, um, first of all, you're right.
There, there, there's a bunch of deranged lunatics out there.
I'm not saying it's your fault, but like, this is why I don't even have a curious cat.
I don't want people to be able to anonymously ask me things.
Fuck you.
If you want to ask me something, show me your identity piece of shit.
Yeah.
That's true.
I am.
I just have a curious cat.
I, I support, I support the alternative service, Brony Curious is much better.
Like the people sent cyber shell weird enough shit on Twitter.
Like there was this guy who kept asking or he kept replying to every post that cyber
shell made asking about like if Sonic is pregnant or something.
That guy, at least, you know, those were annoying, but like that guy thought he was being funny.
At least that guy thought he was being funny.
Like, you know, there's a difference between those guys and people who will just go out
of their way to send like deranged racist shit.
The attempt, the attempt, oh yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
You know, I remember, I think, I remember Formspring, that was kind of like Curious Cat, right?
Just a website where you could ask someone questions.
Yeah.
Right.
It's like an ask FM kind of type deal.
I mean, I understand the appeal of those sites.
I wasn't completely shitting on them.
I just personally am like, fuck you, I'm not, I'm not answering any questions, fuck you.
I remember Andrew Hussie had a lot of really good, a lot of people asked him like Homestuck
Lore questions and a lot of info, a lot of great insight was gleaned from his Formspring
answers about stuff back in the day, which was cool.
I like those.
I think Formspring is like dead now, or, wasn't there some shit where Curious Cat was dead
a few like a week ago and everyone's like, oh, yeah, it just came back.
I don't know.
Yeah, I was going to mention that.
And then there was like a bunch of people saying, oh, don't use it.
It's like compromised.
And there was like a day later, people came on like, it's not really compromised.
I don't know why everyone was saying that, but that's why I checked it is because it
came out.
I hadn't looked at it for like months and I checked it and it was just all this fucking
horrible shit over months that someone had sent me.
I think it was about like 10 messages and it's like, what the fuck, why?
People are mental, man.
Yeah, mental.
Do you do you get a lot of questions on and I would no trust me?
Oh, no, absolutely not.
No, really, like that was like 90 percent of the stuff that had been sent to me over the
last few months because I haven't barely used it.
I just checked it because I heard Curious Cat was back and I was like, OK, wait, it was
gone. What? And then I looked and I was like, oh, well, I'm looking at it right now and
it says it's under maintenance.
I don't never mind.
I don't know. Speaking of stuff that I've been seeing recently, have you guys been
playing Wordle?
Have you guys been wordling?
Oh, yeah, I have seen that on my timeline.
I don't even know.
Is that is that a Pokemon?
It does sound like a Pokemon.
Wordle, Wordle rules.
I've played three now and I'm three for three here.
I'll post the.
Yeah, it's it's the if you've been seeing these little graphics, these little emoji
graphics that people have been it shows it shows like your score.
Let me find one.
I did I did one earlier today.
I'll show my score from Wordle 204.
Where is it?
Here we go.
Oh, yeah.
Copy and paste in that.
That looks good.
That looks real good.
There we go.
Read them and we.
OK, I've seen those.
Yeah.
I have no idea what it is.
So it's.
How does this work?
I'm on the page.
It's it.
But yeah, well, you word guessing you make sense.
Yeah, you have to get it sort of like mastermind, but with a word.
You ever play Mastermind?
I know the TV show Mastermind.
It's simple.
It'll just tell you if you get the letter in the right place, it'll be green.
And if you get the letter in the correct letter, but in the wrong place,
it'll be yellow. It's pretty much that simple.
So I got a blank thing and I press A and it's wrong.
So what do I do?
Matt, Mastermind is a game where like your opponent chooses a sequence
of four colors and you basically have to like make a series of guesses
about of like colors, a series of colors, and he has to tell you like, OK,
you you got one color right, but it was in the wrong place or you got one
color right and it was in the right place and stuff like that.
So word is like that.
You guess a fight.
You have to guess a five letter word and you have like five or six guesses.
So you have to put it.
You have to type in a five letter word and then it will tell you
which of your letters in your word were correct, but in the wrong place
or correct in the right place.
And because you have a series of guesses,
it gives you this cute little this cute little emoji code.
You know, your your series of guesses forms a little little pattern
that makes for a nice little postable post here.
Because look how great it is.
Because the question is the same for everyone every each day, isn't it?
So like, yes, why they do it as emojis as opposed to people just screenshotting
the results because we just spoil it for everybody.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. So.
Yeah, don't no, no, no, no, it's not the same.
Same. Everyone everyone gets one word a day
and it's the same word for everybody.
They do it in different languages, too, which is kind of cool.
If you speak multiple languages, you can play multiple games.
So wait, wait, wait, wait.
What is the strategy?
You just guess a random five letter word and then from there
you have some information with which to make more guesses that are more correct.
Yeah, like, see, my first guess, you know,
it gave me that one yellow square.
So I knew that that letter was in the final word,
but it's not in the right place.
I got two greens on my first try.
So that's pretty lucky.
That's super are all the letters, five words.
Or all what all the five letters.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
OK, if you guys enjoy wordal viewers right now,
I'm not trying to hear it a shit on you or whatever,
but I instantly lost interest in this game once I realized
you can just game the system by if you just search the words O read,
hints, clump and gawky.
That's like 20 letters.
You will guarantee to be able to figure out the word, basically,
from just having inputted all those letters.
You know what I mean?
Like there's systems you can do to basically guarantee
that you're going to be able to figure it out.
Oh, I mean, I mean, necessarily if you're just trying to figure it out,
I guess if you're trying to like get the best score.
This is one of those games you have to use the honor system, right?
Because I mean, obviously, like, yeah, you can just.
Yeah, it's about how you really cared that much, I guess, about score.
It's about how few it's about how few guesses can you get it in.
And then you brag and you post your results
and you make you hope that everyone else looks.
Hey, everyone, I'm really good at this guessing game over here.
So I just want to brag about that.
I'm really good at tic-tac-toe.
I win it almost every time against.
I'm really good at hangman.
I'm trying so hard to think of a of a word that ends in this letter,
but I don't.
How do I?
It's impossible.
This one, this one confused me.
This one was a little bit tricky.
This is the third of the last three that I played.
This was the trickiest.
Today was going to be the first one I played,
but I looked at someone's screenshot beforehand and I realized, oh, shit.
That was today's one.
Get fucked, loser.
Can you play a game?
Yeah, true.
I have to wait all the way until tomorrow.
Can you do pass?
I guess there would be no reason to do pass ones
if you can just look up the answers.
I tried to look up if you could like choose a different puzzle,
but it looks like it's just the one for the day.
I don't know.
I didn't look at it too long.
It's weird. Why wouldn't they let you do old ones?
Because it's a big community Web 3.0 metaverse thing, Ben.
That doesn't explain anything.
Web 3.0, I'm just going to keep saying that until you accept it and move on.
Well, oh, fuck.
It's like, oh, yeah, this is all like we're all actually secretly
like solving the human genome with all this like computing power
that we're putting in.
If this was like truly Web 3.0, I'd expect it to be like every time
you finish a wordle, it's like you completed a wordle.
Would you like to purchase your wordle as an NFT?
I would.
Dublock chain.
Would you like some of Dublock chain?
What did I want?
Chain, more like.
What blockchain?
What blockchain shit did I see this week that sucked?
Oh, Bitcoin is crashing a bit right now.
It's it's not doing super great.
What's the point of crypto?
Crypto just crashes every time the stock market crashes.
It doesn't it doesn't free you from anything.
It's completely tied to the bullshit via currency that everyone's like,
oh, it's so it frees us from this.
No, it doesn't.
Did the stock market also crash?
I didn't even know about it.
I haven't I don't pay attention to money.
I refuse to learn about any financial knowledge.
I choose to live in ignorance and be stupid about my cyber show.
I love your bank account.
I love money.
I love money so much.
Yes, you can.
That's how stupid I am about money.
I just give out my bank account details to anyone who will ask publicly
on a password and credit card info and just send me your credit card in the mail.
I'm going to read three credit card number is three.
Oh my god, I just got really overwhelming urge to.
I so the card I'm currently churning is my American Express business cash blue.
And I just got the overwhelming urge to read out the funny little numbers on it.
Obviously, I must every time you talk about hard churning,
I imagine you like dressed up like an Amish person churning butter,
but like sitting there over it's your little car.
It's like that.
It's exactly like that.
You know, I think I imagine making butter like one of those those.
Oh, oh, no, I got covid one of those.
Oh, God, it might be.
There's a fucking satisfying to look at like metal crushing machines
with two like cylinders that grab something and crush it.
I guess that's what I imagine when you card churn.
Is that you're throwing cards into metal roller, a flat roller, crushing machine.
It's a crushing machine.
There's like with like interlocking teeth, two cylinders going inwards to it.
And you people just throw a conveyor belt and like a tub is like a funnel.
And then there's things like oh, but the rollers have like ridges on them.
And the ridges like interlock with each other, right?
Grab things and you can throw like animal carcasses into the animals.
You can throw like steel beams.
You can throw anything.
Well, you can throw the robot dog from Walton Gromit Clochette.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right.
That's right.
I had a little toy.
He was scared.
Oh, yeah, pressed in the pressed in the cyberdog.
What a legend.
I watched all of those with my dad on Christmas.
That was great.
Last Christmas, I gave my dad watched Flushed.
We watched Flushed Away.
We talked about my dad's a big Aardman fan.
We watched Flushed Away and I loved I loved it.
Flushed Away is cool.
It's pretty weird.
It was really good.
I think I talked about it last year, but I thought was like, wow.
I was like, what a what a what a great little what a great little flick.
What a great little like, you know, clean and satisfying
little three act heroes journey that was.
I was very compelled by it.
It was I loved it.
I've never seen it, but didn't they like
like imitate the stop motion with like animation?
They just did it.
The animation.
It was animated by Dreamworks, but in the style of Aardman,
like in the character design style and like with the limited frame rate stuff
on the faces, I think the bodies were completely smooth.
But yeah, it's cool.
Yes, it was a pretty good.
I think that's interesting.
You got Hugh Grant and as the guy, right, as the main man.
Yeah, that sounds that sounds right.
Yeah, that sounds right.
And you got Ian McKellen as the funny frog.
And he goes, I'm a man of quality.
Right. Good movie.
This is a good movie.
This year, I didn't get to watch anything with my family for Christmas
because I was quarantined with coronavirus.
I still fucking pissed off about it.
I'm fucking mad.
I fucking in terms of festivities for new years.
I went around a friend's house and I got very, very drunk.
I was the only person who drank more than one beer.
That's what I wanted to do, but I was still positive.
My dad drove me home and I was almost sick on the way home.
So I had to step out and I just took a piss behind a bus stop.
And I was like, I'm still doing this.
I'm twenty two and I'm still doing this.
And then wait till you're thirty three and still doing it.
Yeah, I got home.
I've omitted like six times and put on trailer park boys on my phone.
And then I then then I suddenly was conscious again.
And it had been two hours and I can tell because six episodes had gone by.
And I was like, damn, I have passed out on the toilet for two hours.
Great. Sounds very uncomfortable.
Oh, I was fine.
I'm a grown boy. I can still do it.
We only twenty two, you're just a baby.
I know.
I feel old because my back always hurts from work, which is great
because I have to haul potatoes all night because I have a night job at the supermarket.
Maybe you should put the potatoes down.
No, but you've got to put them on the shelf, give.
Did you know that?
Did you know that you've got to put potatoes on the shelf in the store?
No, interesting.
Tatoes are interesting shelves.
Interesting grocery store fact.
You know, the shit you're supposed to keep cold
during the night when you're doing delivery.
It just sits in the middle of the aisle for hours, not in the fridge
because it takes so long to like put it on the shelf.
So all that chicken you're eating has just been sat there for at least four
hours every night, not refrigerated, which I mean, delicious.
That's I would do that in my own home.
So what a recommendation is that you need to chuck anything
that's been out for like two hours, though.
Well, what makes you think I would follow a health recommendation?
Well, guess what?
Every single piece of fucking poultry in the shop that I work at
has been left out for at least four hours.
So that's cool.
I hope I don't shop there.
That opens my eyes a little bit.
It's more efficient that way.
I'm not going to say the name.
It's called chicken churning.
Exactly.
Oh, about wordle, when you put a letter and it's gray,
that means it's not anywhere in the world, right?
Correct. That's right.
That's right. Wow.
So it's eliminated.
It snowed here the other day.
It actually just like two days ago, it snowed like a lot.
There's like a foot and a half of snow on the ground
or might be starting to melt finally.
First first serious snow of the winter.
Every time there's snow, I'm just so happy because it looks so pretty.
But then I have to remember, I'm not a kid.
I don't get school like days of school off because of snow.
It just makes my life worse and harder.
Yeah. Fortunately, I'm blessed to be a renter.
You know, I'm blessed not to own property.
So I'm not responsible for shoveling anything.
You know, that's that's that's interesting because when I was a kid,
I was like, oh, I wish I lived somewhere where there was snow
so I could have school off.
But now that I'm old, I'm like, oh, I'm glad I don't fucking have to deal with that shit.
Dude, I did.
Well, if you live in like Virginia or something,
if you even get like a quarter of an inch of snow,
like everything shuts, you don't have to shovel it.
But everything just shuts down instantly
because the infrastructure is simply not prepared.
I got it in four. I got it in four.
That happens once every like five.
Oh, very good.
Now you're addicted.
Now you know the addicting rush of figuring out a word.
Yeah, you know, wordle seems like a thing.
Seems like a kind of give core.
It definitely did.
Game. I love it.
I like it. I like.
I've played it three days straight now
and we'll see how long I keep my streak up.
I was enticed.
I was enticed by the little emoji cubes.
I was just like, who made this?
How are they making money off of this?
I need to know.
I'm not comfortable using this until I know how the it's monetized.
It's not about the money.
It's about sending a fun word puzzle to a fun round.
It's about the mitts.
Game, how did you how did you get it like that?
How did you get no yellows?
I thought of, well, I got lucky on the first one
and then I got lucky on the second one.
And then I got lucky on the fourth one.
Well, there was only like, you know what the word is, right?
I'll tell you how she got it, Ben.
She thought, unlike you, your brain is twisted.
I got the second letter on the first try
and then nothing for the entire thing,
except for the last one where he accidentally got the last letter.
So I got fucked.
I realize I got it first try.
You can nobody nobody plays it on hard mode,
but there is a hard mode.
And what hard mode does is it means that you can't.
When once you guess a letter, you can't like change the letter
like that letter is locked in.
And I was like, huh?
And then I realized, oh, well, that's because
if you didn't have them locked in, you could just, you know,
yeah, guess an entire little system.
I had to work on hard mode.
I just found out about that.
Yeah, my full system.
No, I have to actually think about the stupid word.
I tend to basically play as though I'm on hard mode.
Wait, what?
What's the I put the word in right?
And I pressed enter and then the second one I put a word in
and then I like I could go back.
I could delete letters and no, no, no, no, I mean, again, you could.
Well, OK, you entered a word that had the green letters
in the right place. On hard mode, you have to do that.
Like, yellow doesn't count? What do you mean?
Yeah, well, on regular mode, you know, if you don't, you could have put
Once you've correctly guessed the letter, you can't not guess the letter.
You can't, like, guess something else that you know is going to cover a lot of bases, you know what I mean?
Like, you have to, like, make honest attempts is sort of how it works.
Oh, you mean, like, on the second one...
You can't, like, farm. You can't, like, put a bunch of random...
You can't put a bunch of vowels on your second attempt if you go to green one on your first.
Like, like...
Yeah, you have to use that green letter again.
To, like, see how many yellows you could have.
And be like, okay, these ones are in, and these ones are...
Right.
We have to type a real word. You can't just type random letters.
It should have just been hard mode by default. They should have just done that.
I might start playing on hard mode, actually.
Because, like, I always do it anyway.
So, like, fuck it.
I might as well get cred.
I might as well earn my props.
There better be a special thing on the tweet that you tweet out that's like,
by the way, this was on hard mode, so it's more important than all you other idiots.
It should have a little, like, star.
A little, like, shining star emoji.
Or instead of making it green, they could make it red.
But maybe people would get confused and think it was wrong.
I'm just going to start posting three, or excuse me,
posting five green boxes in a row and saying I got on the first try.
Like, every single day.
Make it purple.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Every day. Every day.
Just, like, Wordle 204, one out of six.
Wordle 204, one out of four.
But I'm just going to acknowledge that I'm cheating.
I'm just going to be like, wow, hashtag blessed. I'm so lucky.
Yeah, don't... Everyone's asking, like, how'd you do this
and just refuse to elaborate.
It's like, I don't know.
I'm the world champion, bitch. I'm the best at Wordle in the world.
If you were as smart as me, you would also get it in one every time,
but you're not, so fuck off.
This sounds like another video game, like, clout swindle
that will somebody make a YouTube video about.
Yeah, this is the new, like, dream-cheating situation
that's going to blow up.
There's a guy who's, like, cheating at Wordle.
It's funny, too, because it's, like, the easiest thing
you could possibly cheat at. It's, like, you know...
Just Google the answers.
You just have to not do that if you care.
Is that Planet of the Apes?
No, it's not.
It's like humans, man. It's not an ape.
Oh.
There's, in the sequels to the original Planet of the Apes,
there's, like, a cult of humans underground
that worship an atom bomb.
Oh, yeah, I remember that.
Yeah, and they stole that for Fallout 3.
That's the anti-Hideo Kojima.
Ugh.
Okay, okay. Star Trek, of course. Disgusting.
Sorry, sorry.
I always like to try to ban.
I'm not allowed to talk about it on PCP.
Can we get Ben off of this podcast and get Nate back on
so we can talk about Star Trek?
No.
Anything but that.
Finally.
Finally, somebody had to say it.
Oh, why didn't Picard care about the Curlin' Nesco
when it was destroyed? I don't understand.
What the fuck? The pothole?
I'm not, I'm not a big, I'm not a big Trek guy.
I've seen some Trek. I guess it's alright.
I'm not a big Trek guy.
That's my opinion.
But, like, TNG's good. DS9's good.
TNG is the only one I've really watched, like,
even a significant amount.
It's the only one that interests me.
I'm a fake fan.
I would occasionally catch a DS9 or Voyager,
like, on TV when I was a kid.
But TNG was the one that I mostly...
I've probably seen, like, a dozen or so.
TNG's very serialized. You can just catch random ones
and enjoy it.
Or excuse me, TNG's very much just, like, you know,
random, you know, they're isolated episodes.
They stand on their own.
Whereas DS9 was more, like,
whoa, it's like a continuing serialized story
that, like, you know, there's, like, season-long arc.
Believe it or not, there was a time in TV history
when, like, the idea of a season-long arc was, like,
whoa, it was really interesting and exciting.
Like, wow, there's continuity.
Okay, when I was a kid,
and I caught an episode of the fucking X-Men cartoon,
and I realized, like, oh, this is, like, a whole, like, arc.
This is, like, a season-long arc.
It's not just, like, an episode.
Like, I have to watch the whole thing to understand what's going on.
I was, like, blown away.
I was, like, whoa, that's so cool.
And then I saw, like, the first three episodes,
and then I missed the fourth one, and then, like, I never caught up.
That's just how TV used to be.
Yeah, you'd have to catch it every week,
and you miss one, then you're just left out of the conversation.
Can you imagine that shit?
Yeah, I do.
Imagine, like, Game of Thrones, but in, like, the 90s.
Like, everyone's constantly talking about that stupid fucking show,
but if you missed an episode, you're just fucked.
If, okay, okay, okay, if Game of Thrones had come out, like,
like, back then, everybody would have had to watch it.
Like, they would have made so much money on ad revenue,
because everybody would have had to tune in to the network at the time.
Yeah, there is something really weird about that.
Like, TV used to be, like, a real, like, yeah.
Like, you knew you were watching it at the same time
as, like, all these other people, whereas now it's just, like,
oh, we release on Netflix, everyone go binge it at your own leisure,
which I'm not even, I'm not even saying that's a bad thing.
I'm just saying it's different.
Man, you guys...
I am.
Yeah.
I don't like that.
Binging is a thing you can do afterwards.
After...
It's a fun way to watch something.
Honestly, I miss the JoJo Fridays, like, how to say, I miss it.
It kind of allows too much to be missed.
It was just a whole thing.
Yeah.
If you do it for the first time.
Yeah, I used to do JoJo Fridays.
I used to do that.
But the, but I mean, you know, streaming exists.
There's no reason Netflix couldn't have released JoJo Part 6, like,
I don't know, they just don't like doing it weekly.
I guess I'm grateful they're doing batches of episodes rather than
just releasing the entire thing at once, but still kind of weird.
I think, I think I have, I have lost a lot of interest
in, like, media in general.
There's, like, very, very few, like, shows or games or anything that I'm like,
yeah, I really want to check that out.
I think one of the few things that could get me
to want to watch the show would be the feeling of, like,
everybody else is watching it.
My friends are watching it.
I want to be a part of the thing.
Yeah.
So that, that, like, community, like, like everybody's watching it at the same
night on the week, right?
We're all going to talk about it the next day.
That, I think that would be a big pull for me.
I think that would be one of the biggest pulls that they could,
they could use to exert their power over me to get me to watch their
stupid fucking show.
And they, and they've given it up.
They've given it up because, like, there's so many shows,
and they're all on streaming, and I could watch them any time I want,
but, like, ah, fuck it.
Hey, bells.
You know?
Why?
Yeah.
Well, it wasn't, it wasn't a weird game like that.
Have you heard of a serialized manga called One Piece that you could catch up
with and talk to people about?
I could, I could.
You could even go in the conversation of Talking Pirates on twitch.tv.
Damn.
Two years ago at Radcon 4, I almost caught up on One Piece.
And you're still writing off the coattails of almost catching up
one time two years ago.
And that, and that was then, yeah, and that was then,
and now I'm like, well, shit, I was almost,
I've been almost caught up for two years.
I guess I'm not anymore.
My friend is watching it.
He's not reading it.
He's watching the whole thing, and he's, I'm like,
Well, that's pain.
You're a psychopath, dude.
Yeah.
That's like, that would take so long to do.
I mean, how did this happen?
I watched the whole thing.
Jeez.
I watched like the first like, the first one.
Just the One Piece anime have filler in my heart.
I think I remember when it was.
I can't remember when it was.
It just has bad pacing.
It was up to like the other chapters.
Okay, okay, it does have, it does,
it does have some filler,
but some of the filler is actually really good.
Right.
Like there's that one arc, like when they come down from,
uh, fuck, what's from Skypea,
they land in that like, in that like prison island
and that's a whole filler arc in the anime.
Yeah.
That's really good.
That's a great.
Yeah.
Mostly the episodes are just really badly paced
and like slow.
It's because after the time skip,
they go to one chapter per episode,
which is terrible.
They're badly paced.
They should just make the episodes half as long.
They try.
15 minute episodes.
They try it.
They go fucking long.
The intros and outros.
And the recap.
It's crazy how long we can get on some shows.
It's insane.
15 minutes of new animation on a show
because most of it's recap and intros.
Crazy.
The intro is like a full three minutes long.
Then you have two minutes of fucking recap
and then like the outro is a full like four minutes
or something like that.
It's crazy.
They're saving as much time as possible.
So one piece is a weekly strip.
Is it still going weekly?
Is that just, it's a weekly strip?
They have an outro.
That's just crazy to me.
He takes breaks every time.
That's so much.
Oda is a little less consistent than he used to be,
but it's mostly every week.
He's got some good, what do you call it?
Some manga I think is good to read like weekly.
Some of it like trying to read as it comes out is torturous.
I really like Kaiji,
but I just have to like deliberately forget about it for a year
and then like catch up on it.
You know what I mean?
Hold on.
You mean ultimate survivor Kaiji?
Yeah.
Kaiji is still going.
Is that still going?
It's still going.
Are you joking?
No, no, no.
He's on this crazy arc right now.
It's like you don't even understand.
How long has it been going for?
Since the 90s.
The thing is, it's not like every week or anything.
That's why I was like,
one piece every week because like that's crazy to me
that you can be that consistent.
Kaiji is not every week.
I think it's either monthly now or actually I have no idea
what the schedule is.
I'm only catching like the English pages as their chapters
as they're translated.
So I don't really know the actual release date,
but yeah, it's still going.
It's literally still going.
Kaiji still having his little fun adventures.
I used to not even read the manga,
but just like knowing that.
Yeah.
His fun adventures.
The lighthearted, the lighthearted realm.
Getting his like ear cut on.
That is a Kaiji ultimate survivor.
Going in like slave jail underground.
See, it's so good though.
It's so good.
Do they, do they keep making the anime or do they?
No, the anime is stuck on,
we're never going to get a season three unfortunately.
I mean, at least that's my guess,
which is yeah, it is unfortunate because I really like,
but you know, it's one of those things for years,
I was like, when are we going to get season three?
When are we going to get season three?
Oh, I'll just follow the give up.
And then eventually I'll just read the fucking manga.
Fuck it, I'll read the manga.
Yeah, yeah.
Feel me.
It's like the attack on Titan effect.
It's like, well, it's gotta fucking read the manga, I guess.
It's extra hard when you know it's just like,
it's just there, it's waiting for you.
Like spoilers are like,
you could go spoil the whole show for yourself if you want it.
I could spoil the show by just, by reading it,
by going and reading it as intended.
Yeah.
And it's original format.
Exactly.
The ultimate spoiler.
I'm so excited for the next season of attack on Titan
to see all the discourse around that.
It's going to be very fun to re-experience it after the manga.
I'm going to be honest,
I watched the first season of attack on Titan
and I was like, oh, this is pretty interesting.
Oh, maybe I'll actually watch like the second season too,
but whatever.
The point is I dropped it and then I was like,
I didn't even hate it,
but I just sort of was like, whatever, I dropped it.
And now the only thing I hear about people is like bitching
about how horrible the ending was.
And now I'm like more curious.
So I think I might get back into it
just to hear people bitch about the ending.
I watched the first season and I liked it.
I thought it was cool.
But then, you know, there was a long wait,
I think for season two.
Yes, that too.
And then I was like, okay.
And people were like, oh, you can just read the manga.
And then I heard some of the stuff
that is later in the manga and I was like,
that sounds dumb.
I don't know.
I dropped it.
So I dropped the show and again, I didn't hate it,
but I was like, this kind of feels like The Walking Dead,
but like for weebs,
because main characters are constantly introduced
just to get killed off in a shocking way.
It's a little cringe.
So yeah, I sort of fell off.
But then I heard, it gets incredibly weird
and political later,
which is why everyone hates it.
The problems I had with it are not problems
that people bring up when they're like,
this is why it's a bad show.
You know what I mean?
So I'm curious as to how it got bad.
I read the whole manga.
Is that what people think the problem is?
Is that it went smart?
And it wasn't just people being like smart.
No, just heard a bunch of weird complaining
about the political aspects of it
and something about characters,
like Aaron's character got assassinated or something.
The main politics is genocide, bad.
And if people are complaining about that,
that's a red flag, in my opinion.
Yeah.
I've read the manga.
I've seen the whole show so far.
It's one of the few things I have actually caught up on.
I don't know.
If you've only seen the first season,
there's at least two more seasons of good animation,
but the good animators are no longer working on it
after they switched studios, which is a shame.
It's so fucking annoying, dude,
when it's like you watch a show, like one punch man,
you're like, like, shit, this is great animation,
and then the next to the next season.
Well, here's the thing, one punch man also had
the best scenes in one punch man season one
were done by the same animator who did all the best scenes
in Attack on Titan.
His name's Howie Fooly.
There was great animation, I remember.
Action, animation, God, he's a crazy man.
Attack on Titan's over, right?
Like the manga ended a while back,
but they just haven't been in a show.
The show is one more season coming in the manga.
Technically, it's part two of season four, I think.
They're cooling it?
I don't know why they do that.
You got to break the last season into two parts.
That's just like a time-owner tradition of milking.
They did that with season three, too.
There was season three part one, and then season three part two.
Oh, yeah.
That's dumb, just call it next season.
It should be actually season four,
and then season four should be called season five,
and then season four part two should be called season six.
That would make more sense to me.
They should go away with calling things season six.
Part six.
I don't see it being set in autumn
or winter or summer.
It just doesn't make any sense.
It is weird. Season is a weird term,
and they don't even use it in England, right?
Numbers.
They call it a series.
We had a series of a show or something.
Yeah, that's so confusing.
It's inconsistent. It's weird.
It's like shit that's made in England.
They say series,
and then everything is important.
It is inconsistent.
Well, yeah, most of the time,
but then other times it's like
they'll adopt the word season
for
a show made in Britain,
and other times they'll use series for a show
imported from other countries.
It just doesn't, it sucks.
Why does it have to be so confusing?
Just call it the show.
You're absolutely right. The season in Moniker makes
even less sense now that everything gets dumped in one day.
It's not even like it airs across the season anymore.
All the episodes are dumped in one day on Netflix.
Oh, that's why they were called season?
Yeah.
That's funny.
Seasonal anime or whatever comes out
during a season,
and it's like, oh, it's the winter set of shows.
It's the this or that.
I get it, but it really just doesn't
reflect reality at all
when you use season for everything,
regardless of when it comes out.
And I don't really have a problem with it.
The fact we use season to refer to a series of episodes
made in a time frame.
English, come on.
They used to have like,
there was a series
which means like
one after the other of like episodes
that could be watched in any order.
And then there's a serial
which is used to refer
to a show that has a narrative
that goes from one episode to the other.
You need to watch all of them, I think.
Either that, it's like one way or the other.
Like a series
show
is like, I don't know,
like a
Doug, and then a serial would be
Game of Thrones.
We call everything season.
I'm okay with season because it makes discussion easier
when you're like saying,
remember in season blood when this happened.
I'm just so used to it, I'll never not call things season.
Yeah.
It's one of those like
languages change and season now just means
that when it refers to a television show
or whatever.
But I don't care about Attack on Titan.
I just wanted to speak about something.
I just wanted to be pedantic.
Neva Diwali now though.
I'm the opposite.
I care a lot about Attack on Titan, but I didn't talk about it.
Hey, what about
this series?
Huh?
What do we think?
What do we think? It's a math joke.
That's like, googly eyes.
With an E and an A and an I
and a dash and an I and a dash and a one.
That's exactly it.
That's exactly what it is. Yes.
I'm glad you understood.
What does that mean, Mr. Say?
That's the summation.
That's the summation sign.
It's when you do a series
that you add up, that means
A starts with the I
and then it's the sum and it goes minus one.
Wow. Everybody laughs at this fucking nerd
for trying to tell us about math.
That's boring.
Remember when the female Titan screamed
and all the Titans ran up and started fighting?
That was cool.
Yeah, I dropped out of school
so I don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
Ben got a degree in physics
or some worthless nonsense
that's not even real.
No, it wasn't worthless
because now when I
have Game Maker open
I can tell my little guy
to jump in an arc and I go,
okay, oh, square
and I'll make a fade out
and I make a fade out and I'll use a little
square root and I'll just say, okay, yeah,
that's a nice little gentle curve.
A nice little gentle curve for my little
video game character, man.
You should track down and email
some more professors.
And be like, this is what I did with my degree.
Look at the pony game I made.
No, I don't want to tell James
a joke about that.
He'd be ashamed.
But it is a cool skill
to be math knowledgeable
that you can put a formula into a thing
to make a pretty thing happen.
It actually is.
I wouldn't know the first thing about
making a cool arc. I would just need to look up
what to do.
The math that I learned was way more advanced.
The stuff that I use is like fucking
freshman year bullshit.
But for what it is,
it is useful to know about
the equations
for a parabolic arc
or whatever.
It's good and shit.
It's helpful.
If I'm ever in a situation
where I need to know the radius or the tangent,
I'd rather die.
I'd rather just be dead.
Sign! Cosine! Tangent!
You ever play
The World Ends With You?
No.
It's like The World Ends With Cosine.
It's that one guy that goes
Sign! Cosine! Tangent!
I was good at playing the new one.
He's the best guy.
Oh right, there's a new one.
The older one was awesome. The older one ruled.
I don't know. I haven't seen the new one.
I heard the switch port of the old one was really bad.
So I wasn't going to buy that. I was just going to buy the new one.
Why was it bad?
It's like a full 3D remake
and it just ruined the combat.
The combat doesn't work without the DS system
kind of thing.
I was skeptical about that.
I don't know.
I mean, the original one was made
the original one
was very specifically designed
for the DS.
So, you know,
I can understand how it's just totally fucked
if you try to play it on anything else.
It should have done a Wii U port
when they had the chance.
Genuine? Yeah.
Wii U was the perfect fucking console
for a World of Few sequel.
OK, the big DS.
Yeah, it was actually the perfect console
for like a lot of
types of games, but like
it died so,
and they didn't really use the touch screen.
World of Few is actually one of the coolest games
I've ever played.
It's actually like, it might be like
top 10 games that I remember
like the most fondly.
I love it.
That means a lot coming from noted media
in Saint.
I used to like things.
There was a time
when I liked video games
and at that time
World of Few was pretty up there.
I was like, yeah, pretty cool.
I've been on my list for a while,
but I have a friend who's like obsessed with Twi,
so I'm like, I gotta play it.
I'm gonna play it at some point. You know, it's got
what, the number of character designs?
How can you resist?
Yeah.
I thought
Twi was like an anime movie.
They made an anime of it recently.
Oh, is there an anime of it? I wouldn't know.
Yeah, I was gonna ask about that.
You might think it's like a visual novel
if you saw like screen shots of it,
but no, it has combat.
It has...
No, I thought this was like
a combination of like Jet Set Radio
and King of Hearts.
Aesthetically, that's not even, you know, that far off
of a descriptor, honestly.
Hearts just do show up in King of Hearts.
Right.
It looks weird as like a cartoon.
Yeah.
That guy is,
he's not pulling,
he's not putting that cup to his lips,
he's putting it to his nose,
and he's sniffing it very hard.
He doesn't have lips.
Yeah, he'd have to like pull his
thing down.
I had no idea that he pours directly into the scarf
and he's just like slurping it up and he's like dribbling
Yeah.
It looks a little stupid
in motion.
In the game, in like the limited
assets of the dialogue
of the game
and the characters moving around on the battlefield.
It looks great. It's beautiful.
It's a masterpiece.
Yeah, it seems like a really stylish game.
I believe you.
Speaking of stylish masterpieces,
I would use for it.
I got into Beth May Cry recently
who's just fucking awesome.
Everybody on Earth should play it.
I put those off for so long,
but I kept hearing Matthew Matosis
suck that series' dick and all these other people
that I respect.
In my mind, I like character action games.
That makes sense. That seems like a really cool genre.
Whenever I play them, I'm like,
I'm not instantly good at the game.
I suck and I'm like, this is bullshit.
But if you really...
I'm actually not a DMC expert.
I haven't even played five yet, which is very shameful.
And then I got through four as well at some point.
And yeah, they're really good series.
I mean, apart from two, obviously, but one in three
are great games and four was also fun.
Yeah, much like with Digimon,
much like with Digimon, I bounced off of
DMC part two.
My friend in high school was like the biggest DMC fan
and I was like, okay, okay, cool.
And then I decided to get two.
So unfortunate.
And I was like, well, this isn't very fun.
It's legitimately bad during my time with this game.
It sucks.
It's horrible.
There aren't even DMC fans that defend it.
There's not even a contingent like, oh, it's actually pretty good.
Everyone just, oh yeah, it sucks.
We all know it sucks. It's a piece of shit.
How weird that they could just do that?
They could just fuck one up real bad.
And it's just bad.
The fact that they were able to make another one at three
and then that one was actually amazing.
That was a big surprise.
Three was the best one.
Making a video game is hard.
They're like, all right, we've made one.
Let's make another one.
But let's do it a little differently.
It was the Dark Souls 2 thing with it.
And then they just made all of the wrong choices.
It was the Dark Souls 2 problem
of having a different team.
And then the guy who directed three
came in at the very end of development and tried to save it.
Where it's like, oh shit, you guys...
He came in all last day.
So how was that game you're doing?
There was a famous infamous story
where it was like the only thing they had done
was the Stinger attack.
That was the only useful thing they had done
at that point in development.
He had to start from scratch when he came in at the project.
Jesus.
My God.
Game development is hard though.
Why did they make it shitty?
Why did they choose to make it shitty?
It's complicated. It's hard.
Speak for yourself.
I have been cranking up.
This week I have upgraded.
I have basically finished making Phantom's Revenge
beta version 3.
I have successfully added
weapon marriage and stock trading
to the game.
Better out of fishing game now.
I think it's all this bullshit.
That's...
Seatall last episode asked if you could fish
and if there was fishing and farming
and I was like, oh, maybe.
No, no, I have to stop.
I have to stop.
Save that.
I think stock trading
is the perfect edition
and that's where I'm like, okay,
game's perfect now. Game's perfect.
Better out of star rank system
like Devil May Cry.
You know, I might
because the game does
sort of like judge you
at the end. The game gives you results
and you can sort of interpret them
in like a how did you do.
Have a bit crushed voice go cool,
huh?
Awesome.
I mean,
Phantom at will.
Not great.
There are circumstances
which will make Phantom
look different at the end.
You can make him cry. You can make Phantom cry
at the end if you are a bad person.
I always wish that if I took like 50 hours
to beat Metroid, that Samus
would like cry at the end and be like, how could you?
I was so bored running
backwards and forwards
between two places that I knew what to do
but someone was controlling me
making me do stupid shit.
This was the big
edition of version two. I'm not going to say
what it was but I added something
that would let you beat...
If you're bad at the game, it would let you beat it anyway
but if you beat it that way,
Phantom cries at the end
and you feel like a fucking monster
and you better go back and do it right
and do it right, you idiot.
I'm going to speedrun for that ending.
If it's faster, that's the only route people are going to speedrun, sorry.
That's true.
That's true. Kill the animals.
Well, you know.
Alright. It's actually not faster.
It's actually not faster. It's just easier.
Okay, that's fair.
I think it would actually be...
Interesting point.
I'm thinking about it. Yeah, I think it would actually be
faster to play it well
and not do that.
Well, you know, I thought of everything.
Don't worry.
Game's a masterpiece.
Yeah.
And those jump arcs.
Who, boy?
Parabolic AF.
I can't wait to see Jeff Keely on stage
next year at the Game Awards and he goes,
the best indie game goes to
Phantom's Revenge.
It is the best indie game.
He sounds like that.
He was just like that.
He's the guy who hosted the Game Awards.
He was the Dorito Pope.
Okay, but there's got to be something
else to him than that, right?
Yeah, he was a...
He was a... Fuck, I forgot
what he did before. He was like a journalist.
He worked for
Game Trailer.
I don't think so.
He works for something. So one of those
Gamescom, Games Far,
Gamesweep, I don't know.
Alright, okay.
He's okay.
I don't hate him as much as I thought I should hate him.
He made Angry Joe look
like an idiot once
and that was pretty funny. So
Jeff Keely gets the zero approval.
That fucking face.
Oh, I was right.
There's this infamous interview with Angry Joe.
He fucking blew Angry Joe the fuck
out. He fucking...
Oh, yeah.
I think, wait.
Was that entirely
broadcast by Angry Joe to say
Jeff Keely fucking sucks.
Yeah, it was.
And then he just shows them talking
and Angry Joe was just being
a complete spaz.
I feel like I know what you're talking about,
but can you fill me in on
what that was?
It was an interview that Angry Joe recorded
with Jeff Keely at the Game Awards and he was
complaining about Jeff's
picks for each category and stuff.
And he was saying like, oh, you haven't even nominated
any MMOs for the RPG thing.
And he was like, Jeff Keely just shuts him down at every
single point and proves him wrong in every single one.
And because it's a video made by
Angry Joe, he like
pauses the video and then he comes on screen green screen
and he goes, see, he's fucking with me, even though
Jeff Keely's just completely proved him wrong.
It's one of the most hilarious videos.
Angry Joe's just screaming like
an idiot and he's completely wrong about
everything.
I mean, it sounds like
Angry Joe owned himself.
It was a legendary
cellphone on his part.
I just realized that
cellphone actually sounds exactly the same
as cellphone when you say it really fast.
Cellphone. Wow.
Men posting their L's.
That's why we just say phone makes you think.
We had to drop the cell.
It says a lot.
It says a lot about society. Perfect cellphone.
You know, I want to go back to
how
David Lynch called them
telephones, even though they were cellphones.
They're still telephones.
They are telephones.
Yeah, we should just go back to calling them that.
They're cello telephones.
You know,
as I was adding stock trading,
I was a bit sad because
I was adding stock trading and I was like,
okay, you're going to do stock trading
through your cell phone, right? Because that's how you do it
in Endless War.
You have a cell phone and you can do,
you can call it the remote stock exchange.
You call it your slime broker and you trade
stocks on the slime stock exchange.
So I wanted to make
the like command subcategory
exclamation point cell phone,
but it was just a little bit too long
and it was like, it like
stuck out a little bit further than like the menu
and I was like, if I change the menu,
I would have to like change every other
menu option. I would have to like,
I would have to move everything,
every subcategory option individually.
I have to move them. I was like, no,
no, it's boring.
That's dumb. I'm just going to shorten it to phone.
But I was like, but phone is lame.
It's not just a phone. It's a gel phone.
This is a piece of lore.
I made an artistic compromise
and I will never forgive myself.
Can you just do like gel-ph?
It's a cell phone.
Or JJ phone.
No, that's
those ideas suck.
This is why you guys are not
game guys.
Well, actually, actually you could
you could have made the font smaller.
Shut the fuck up.
You don't understand.
You don't understand anything.
Just change the text.
That would be a nightmare.
Imagine
imagine if one text option
is just a smaller font than all the other ones.
You would be just close your eyes.
Then I guarantee
close your eyes
does it almost
feel like nothing
changed at all.
You got to change the text.
Let me just say personally
I'm looking forward to this game
and almost as much as looking forward to just playing the game.
I'm looking forward to watching Ben
try to like have to
explain this game to people who don't know anything about it
and try to pitch them to play it when they're going to be
beyond confused.
There's a pony comic you got to read first
and it's related to Sonichu
but it's also like this and it's like that.
My plan
My plan is to
make the game funny
and approachable and cool so that people
will play it on their own and I won't have to explain it
and if they want to
they can follow up and be like
what's the comic this is linked to? Let me go check that out.
The whole thing was just a trick
to get people to read your old
pony comic.
I mean, sure.
Why not?
The whole thing was just a
trick to get more views on T-Bap.
T-Bap was struggling for years now
it wasn't getting views so we had to
put the word out there.
The thing I'm excited to see is Ben's discord trying to convince him
that the game is done while he's trying to add more shit.
I can't wait for that.
You were saying something last week about how
you've basically done the main game and you're just adding
this type of bullshit on top but I just want to go on
the record and say that's the most important shit is
the extraneous bullshit because
that's what really gives the game a soul.
You know what I mean?
Genuinely, genuinely, version 1
beta version 1 sucked
I realized I thought it was good
I thought it was great it was done
but then I was like okay
version 2 there's something I want to add
I added it and now I realize version 1
was garbage. Version 2 was the actual
complete version of the game. The game was not
complete.
Version 3
it didn't need weapon marriage
it didn't need stock trading
but I do think it is better for having them
and I think version 3 is
version 2 was essentially done.
Version 3 is just an improvement but now I'm like
okay it doesn't
it would not be that much improved but anymore
so I think I'm actually calling it
I'm actually calling it.
This is no more major addition
You can only add shit after it comes out
I really want to
I have
maybe you've heard me mention that maybe
in the future it would be funny to go back
and add in keg mode
that would be very silly
it would be funny
it would be a lot of work and probably
not worth it actually
I said it would be easy but it wouldn't be bad
you could make a bunch of sprites or shit
I know you could make it model them
or modify existing ones
but it would still be a lot of work
yeah, yeah
honestly I was thinking
I would want it to play differently
because keg would have to function
mechanically differently from phantom
because phantom
because phantom is a slime pony
and is immune to the electric attacks
of soniches
and it can only be defeated through the use of
bicarbonate soda water
keg would be
he would have no reaction
he would have no response at all to
water but he would be
easily defeated by sonichu
using some sort of move
for example thunderbolt or thunder
or voltackle or etc
etc
there would have to be something
and I thought it would be really funny if
what if keg has a gun
he's just like hey good thing I found this gun
outside and it goes in and
I don't know maybe it's like a speed
it's like
here it is, keg mode is this
instead of a
turn based rpg
with phantom
keg mode is typing of the dead
where he just gets to a new room
and he just has to type a word fast enough
so that he just shoots every sonichu
before they can shoot him and he's like
well okay next room
I love it but I'm biased
I love typing in the dead so I think that's hilarious
so that would just be
an entirely new game basically
just make a new game on top of your old game
just spend every year making a game
that's what a sequel is basically
that's what the virtual dlc is
and all the dev micro games
you'd be surprised how much a different playable character
can have to a game
I'm trying to think
I feel like
oh zero, zero for megaman x
when you could summon zero
in like megaman x3
I think
and you get a sword
oh
zero didn't even have a sword
in the original megaman x
like at no point in megaman x
did zero have a sword
but then like in every other game
yeah all he does is he
megafan I like the series but
I wouldn't have been able to tell you that
I'm a megafan
I forgot when
he got the sword was it in 2
I think it's in
in number 2
or like
I don't think you can play as him in 2
but you can play as him in 3
and he definitely has the sword in 3
I don't know if he has the sword in 2
but he definitely does not in 1
but it's funny because
him being the sword guy is sort of like
kind of his whole thing
that's the one thing people know about him
that's how I know him
he's a little cool he's a laser sword
it's cool
we'll talk about that later because it was cool
they were like well there's a cool guy
so we should give him something cool like a sword
from what I remember
the sword wasn't his main weapon until 4
in 3 he could still use the arm cannon
from what I remember
but then in 4 he
yeah
yeah you're right
in 3 he could charge
he still uses the buster
but like one of his charged moves
is like a sword slash
before he just stopped using the buster
that was after the
yeah
after the graphics change
yeah it went from
yeah it went from SNES to PS1
I hate the way that it looks
I hate the way that
those games look after the graphical
change after x3
I just think it's so much worse
why?
it's like 2
rights are like too
big
well they're not bigger but like
they're more detailed and like
I don't know they're too detailed
I hate it
I really really hate
the way that x4 and on look
I think that the game looks perfect in the x style
and it
it was made worse
by being made better
by the enhanced fidelity
this is another one of those pokemon moving situations
you don't really articulate what you don't like about it
kinda
kinda only mega man was great
when it made it look 3d
because everybody likes mega man legends
like I just said I'm not a huge mega man
lore expert but I sort of know what you mean
I actually have not played
that much legends
but it looks awesome
everybody likes how it looks including me
I love low poly 3d mega man
yeah those games look dope as fuck
what about the 3dx games
it's aced really well
there's one of the x games
I think it's like x6 or 7
you actually have like playable 3d sections
it's like a hallway
it's really bad
I don't know I never played it
I remember hearing people bitch about like x6
those games apparently get kinda bad
but again I'm not speaking from first hand experience
just from watching youtube videos essays about
this is why mega man games get bad at the end
I mean in the mega man
in the mega man zero games
I guess he's still
I mean his sword is his most
iconic weapon but it's not
he is equally able
I mean he has all kinds of
he has a whole arsenal he has a gun
he has a sword he has this boomerang shield
he's got the like arm jabby things
he's got the like extendos spear
I fucking
zero
mega man zero
okay he's got all
kind of like the whole oh man and then
I think it's is it in Z4
is it in 04 that he has the glove
that he can like rip
like weapons out of other enemies
hands and like use them
we're fucking amazing
genius the greatest game ever made
yeah but he doesn't have
a stock market simulation so I mean
how good is it really
no he can't trade stocks on his gel phone
sure he's got all these weapons
he can't marry a single one of them
so what's even the point
I just want to give a shout out to Cruelty Squad
for being another game with an in-game stock
market where you can just like buy stocks
in the middle of a mission
but you know you really need to add to your game
to make it stand head and shoulders above
you need to add like a credit card churning system
you know
you already gamified it
you know how it's fun you know how to do it
I have not
I have not gotten around to playing Cruelty Squad
a lot of people have mentioned like
Cruelty Squad is very endless war
and it's it is in so many levels because
like one it's got like it's like slime aesthetic
and two it's like all about
like a hyper capitalist like corporate
nightmare world which is thematically
like so endless war is also
it's just like it's a little
it's a little less in your face about it
and it's like it really
it really is I could see people
I could see someone maybe they find
they stumble upon Phantom's revenge they play it
they realize like there's stocks in it and like they think like
is this like
is this like a Cruelty Squad spinoff
it's talking about slime and you can trade stocks
don't worry I could genuinely see someone
there's no ponies in Cruelty Squad
people won't get confused
guess what
I just found out Attack on Titan season 4
part 2 is airing today
the first episode
timing though
if only this went up today so the people
if you're listening to this now you missed it
if you didn't watch it I mean go watch the first episode
it's too late
you can't watch it live you can't watch it the day it came out
unless you already did
go watch episode 2 in a few days
yeah exactly
Simsie's lying to me
set yourself up for disappointment anyway moving on
it's fine there's
wait I'm gonna grab a drink
I'm gonna grab a sparkling water I'll be back in one
second
finally now we can talk shit about Ben all we want
and he will never know
we can listen to the episode back and be like
better listen to that part I wasn't there for
you think he's gonna do that 0% chance
I mean we can talk shit about Ben to his face
yeah but
actually right it is funnier to do it that way
let's just okay everyone hold your Ben shit on
until he gets back
I know it's hard to resist
he's really smelly he's just generally quite a smelly
person don't like him
you never sniffed him
that's what you think
you gotta have receipts if you want to destroy Ben's
I can tell he's smelly because I opened up my package
of the vapour
it just reeks
there's vapour in there
it's a bunch of vapour I open the box it's like a big cloud
comes out
a big vape cloud
and it says ha ha fuck you
and it dissipates
my copy of fucking
Road to Radcon
fucking reek I know he pissed on it
I know he did I know he doesn't like me I know he pissed on
my copy of Road to Radcon just to piss me off
he would never piss you off
let it dry out
it's all yellow
oh yeah I was gonna ask him about the
cleave and the weeb stuff
but I guess I will when he gets back
overall
I gotta say I'm glad I never bothered
being like Ben
you gotta chill out with your like tricksy hate
because it led us here it led us to this moment
it all worked out in the end
all the people are like trying to get him to calm down
calm down
you were anti-progress
you were gonna stand in the way of this
it's like an objective fact
that his hatred of tricksy has caused more
good in the world than bad
it is like some weird Dark Souls thing
where it's like fueling him
to keep going even though he's definitely
hollow at this point
I'm gonna buy a cleave and the weeb blu-ray
and I'm gonna
pledge an equal amount to Jesse's
Patreon that month
but not to tricksy
tricksy gets nothing
who's gonna be the first viewer
to buy the cleave and the weeb and then like
take it to a live yig show
and get it signed
oh god
he's gonna be the first viewer to
sign the
back of the box
it's a fat shit on tricksy
on the back of the box
there are live yig shows
I don't even think that's a thing anymore
it wasn't like it was a thing
there were
there was a techie
there was like one or two
one that was run by Wiley
one that they just like came into
at the end and then like another one
that's exactly what I was thinking
Riley Coyote
I can just imagine those
going like a
low taxes party
at his office
where only one person showed up and he was on the couch
passed out
oh yeah I should probably
I was gonna at some point take a moment to shill
my new video that I did
with my pal Bedhead Bernie
yeah I wanted to talk about that too
that was my favorite part
it's a funny moment
I knew a lot about
the history of SA
but that was one thing I didn't know about
it's real
internet boomer hours over here
trying to educate people about internet history
which is one of those things where it's like intellectually
like is internet history like important
no not really
but like at the same time
like I kind of think it is I don't really know how to explain it
and like it's
and it's
it's um
it's nice
I wouldn't say it's important but like so much of what we enjoy
it's easy for that stuff to get lost at time
you know like a lot of contemporary
like tweets just tweets just like things
like news articles with sight from around
you know
low taxes death and stuff like
those tweets are just deleted and like those news articles have like broken links
like internet history is just very
easy people just assume someone else
to like document it and archive it but
you know it doesn't really happen
are we talking about um
the Bernie vids low tax
I mentioned I was shilling my
low tax video that I had
worked on with my pal Bernie
yeah I saw that
I started I saw Bernie
tweet it and I started it and then I was like
oh hey it's cyber shell is in this
neat indeed indeed
um yeah we wrote it and researched
it together but uh he did
oh did you yeah yeah we basically made it
together but he edited and
voiced it because he just better edit
anything and I also didn't want to do it
it's amazing but uh yeah we basically
made it together there is a lot of people like
if you let's you watch to the end and also don't
or read the description then you probably
like a lot of people like oh I'm glad he got cyber shell for
a voice cameo and I'm like I do I did a lot
more than a voice cameo it's okay
that's what I thought yeah I thought you were just
a voice cameo no there's a lot of there are a lot of just
voice cameos so it's a little like I get why
people are like that like I really don't care
it's just one of those situations where I just wanted to make a good video
I didn't like I didn't care so much about
I hope it gets x amount of like views like I
want people to see it but like it's just like
I'm just happy that it's done
the video for us do people
even read the video descriptions anymore
because it didn't say that like you wrote it
nobody nobody read the video description
no answer no nobody
read the video of course not damn
I guess I'm the only one you're right
you're the last remaining video description
reader out there
yeah you're right
I'm the last person who exists to read some
about like internet
archiving where you were
saying somebody
asked in a voicemail like I think
a week or two ago
about
the digi clips
the digi clip stuff it was
the archives are just gone
like those forums have been deleted
and like all the fallout
of the whole something awful raid
on the real digimon believers forums
a lot of it just doesn't exist anymore
and it's sad because
a lot of funny a lot of funny shit went down there
and yeah a lot of
it is just gone
there's a lot of funny shit from like 2015
that's like gone forever let alone
trying to do research on like websites
from like 2003 thank god
for like archive.org and the way back machine
you can't even imagine how barren
and empty the internet would seem if just like it was
constantly like all these major sites
just gone forever you know what I mean
I mean I like lost media as much as the next guy
because I just like think it's interesting
like a million people could have seen this
but like zero remaining copies exist
you know what I mean it's just something weird about that
right but if it's truly
lost like gone forever then there's
nothing interesting about that because
like well what do we there's nothing
even frustrating
yeah I was
going to say if I could go back in time
I would have invested like millions of more
dollars in the internet archive because
like they were really ahead of their time that
shit started like in the late 90s like
he like knew how
important the internet was going to be become
the guy who started it
just like Hideo Kojima
that's what Metal Gear Solid 2 is
I love the part of Metal Gear Solid 2
where Raiden turns the camera and he goes
please just archive the things on the internet
and don't believe everything you read
I need my reuploads
of Digi Bros videos
don't delete your save files
I like the part where Raiden is like
chief
I need
I need a download and chief
is like no you can't have it
because I've put it on the blockchain
and it's the web 3.0
is the future
this internet shit these memes of today
are stupid
bitcoin
Raiden you didn't invest in bitcoin
I can't verify your hash I'm going to have to sell
your NFT
your NFTs end here Colonel
what's really interesting is that Metal Gear
was like one of the first places to use
the actual definition of the word meme
I am aware
before memes actually became
it is funny that meme
is just like a Richard
first of all it's weird that Richard Dawkins
of all people is the guy that
I think he coined it and it's just a gene
but with information
it's just a medic transfer of information
that's all it means
he invented the word
just like Shakespeare he just made up a word
and everyone was like okay
it's like I don't know
I understand English is an evolving language
and people make up words all the time
but in more of a slang way
and that sort of just becomes normalized
where it feels weird to be like this is going to be a real word I'm making right now
and it's going to go in dictionaries and stuff
I don't think he realized people were going to use it
I just quiz it
that way
yeah he probably didn't
he probably didn't expect it
to enter the lexicon
right
how could he have
he was describing what I'm sure he considered
a very hyper
a very specific type of information transfer
whereas the average person you say meme
and they're like oh you mean an image macro
it's like yeah that's what I meant
do you mean a trick tool
come to mean something else
you know I don't know
if any of you other guys were on my team
but they used to call them fads on there
yes I remember before a meme was widespread
people calling internet memes fads
that's a factoid
I don't even remember that
I remember that from Game Facts
more than YTMND
yeah
hmm
I knew what the word fad meant
but I never heard anyone use it
about like a specific image
or a phrase or anything
hmm maybe
I mean
I wasn't on YTMND
and I wasn't even really on Game Facts that much
I was on 4chan
I wasn't really on 4chan
really on 4chan until college
I was on Game Facts but I got
banned based
did I tell it
have I mentioned that a lot of my old roommates
that I was living with until recently
were people from a
forum called
oh fuck it was called
the TLDR
the forum was called the TLDR and it was where
people that were banned from the world of warcraft
the forum
would congregate
and they had lore
they had lore like Gabe Newell
posted one time on their forum
one time and that was like a big
and then one of the mods banned him
was Gabe Newell banned from World of Warcraft
no
I don't think so
but he was banned from the TLDR
which was
that was like a cataclysmic event
I think in their history
does it still exist
is what you mean like they're still
actively posting on there
I believe the forum does
still exist but I think it has mostly
become like a discord
I was gonna say almost every fucking forum
has just gotten evaporated
into discords and stuff
and social media in general
when I went back to look at
the Gaming Steve forums
I think I mentioned this a few months ago
I just went back to look at Gaming Steve
because I used to go there
when I was waiting for Will Wright's spore to come out
I would go there to check up on the latest
spore, yeah, to check up on the latest spore news
I remember the spore hype
dudes
that was like your first
your first youtube videos that are still up
yeah I have some spore creature creator videos
I remember the creature creator came out
and everyone was like oh this is so pog
the game's gonna be even better
I talked about that shit for years
I annoyed my girlfriend
in college by talking too much
about it
and then it came out
and uh
oops
but um
I went back to check those forums
and there was like one guy
there was like one guy
still posting threads
like fairly often
just being like hey guys I played this new game
I thought it was pretty good
this part annoyed me
which is can't let it go
he can't move on to the afterlife
yeah and he
he would just make some threads
every now and then and then like
I was just looking at all these threads he was making
and one guy was like hey man
we're all on discord now
you should join the discord and he's like
no fucking discord
discord's for groomers
fuck that shit
based one forum poster guy
he's literally like the guys in World War 2
who didn't realize the war was over and kept fighting
for like years after
the guy's trying to populate forums
still after the war has been lost
to discord
what video did I see about that one
about that one guy
that one like Vietnam
they think Japanese guy was like living on like
a jungle or something and
that's such a weird story but like yeah it's crazy
weren't there like multiple guys
surprised that there were at least a couple
I saw a video about one specific guy
it might have been an atrocity guy
video or uh
I don't remember what channel it was on
I don't know but yeah there's at least one
sounds like the kind of thing they'd cover on that channel
yeah
it sucks you should be able to have a question
and you could google it
but now it's like oh you want to know the answer to the
subscure game thing you have to join our discord
yeah exactly
oh
it's you got to join our discord
it's just it's just the
the
large discords feel like
you're walking around in a city
and everybody's walking past you
and it's like impossible to start a conversation
and it just doesn't
yeah it's too
it's also like really
it's really inconvenient to find information
how I feel about like a twitch chat once it gets too big
it's just it's it's unusable
I
like
like the the thread thing
is like a conversation about a specific
theory
you click on the topic you click on the thread and you read about
but like in a discord
chat
nobody is like
there's there's a lot less
um I guess strict
rules implored
in in in discords to keep things
on topic
but it just
I don't know it's just a completely
different feeling and it's sort of
to if it gets
to a certain size that discord is completely
unusable for me I have to just
mute it completely
I like lots of individual threads lots of
smaller conversations you can just go pick
and choose and participate in versus one like
giant uninterrupted
stream like I don't know it's it's you
got to find a discord like that's the right size
but then it's like yeah it's like some goldilocks
share it's either way too big way too fast
or you join discord and it's like
three messages a day type situation
I like I like discord
but yeah I do I do think it is a bit
sad that yeah it has
largely displaced forums
I did used to like
forums sometimes
and my experience
most of the forums I was on were kind of like
dead for like a couple years
and then discord sort of revived the community
that was more the experience I had
I don't want to be fully anti discord
I'm sure it has plenty of good things like just
intellectually like they do have a chat program
like there's nothing wrong with that you know
but I don't know
the pivot animation community was pretty
dead before discord revived it
it's it's just it's just
on on many that's actually
a good point there's probably a lot of communities that
can't maybe we're blaming
the wrong maybe we're blaming the wrong thing
maybe it's not yeah this discord
the move to discord might be like a symptom
more than like a you know
a root cause it is um
it is
it's not that I care about
forums more it's just that discord
sucks and I don't like it
it doesn't it doesn't like
it's just unwieldy I can't
get into anything
I can't make new friends on discord so it just
doesn't feel like I can't make new friends period but uh
that's
that's um another another topic
uh
I didn't care that much about forums either but the
the
problem is that everything online is like owned by
the same three corporations
yeah that's kind of what I was about
to say it sort of feels like another
step god
I mean I I guess we're I guess we're going
to the web 3.0 now which is even worse
somehow it works the web 2.0
well yeah it feels like another step
in the web 2.0
of like no no one
no like individual websites like
every what everything is on like a few big
platforms everything is on youtube or on
facebook or on discord or
yeah everything is agglomerated right
one yeah that's exactly
it's not that I specifically miss forums
and like if we all just went back to forums
the internet would be fixed it's just like
forums are emblematic of the old internet
which I miss as a whole
a lot more than I miss specifically for forums
in general we're just a den of like
the leadest pricks and you know a bunch of assholes
circle jerking over power
I mean I guess there's plenty of that on discord too
but it's not the forums for this
holy magical place trust me
yeah yeah
a lot of discords
I feel
totally invisible and a
giant discord but on a forum
I feel like you can start something
and then somebody can call you an idiot
a lot of discords are dominated by regulars
trying to break into a new group of people
like as a new member is very
hard because it's just the two
same group of people talking to each other
and just ignoring all the new people that join
which is a big issue I think
that's just a trend that I've noticed that is strange
yeah
I mean forums are like that too though
you would have your big posters
there were some
yeah for sure that could have been hard to like
you know
dude post count clout was like a big thing
I think
that was just as much of a problem
on forums
if you're a newbie
nobody wants to talk to you
and the threads are
dominated by the
people with lots of posts
on something awful in particular
there was a very big emphasis on forum etiquette
and lurking before posting
if you pay $10 for an account
and you make some posts
it's a lower case and you use
you instead of typing out the full word you
instantly you band off the forum
jeez
see I'm genuinely too young
and too normy to have ever used forums
in like any extent the only times I've looked
at forums is just like looking up
how to fix my computer and stuff and seeing posts from like
well before discord existed
that's where everyone was hanging out
I was on the dark team
in forums for a pivot animation
like all the fucking time
in like 2009 to 2011
that community was pretty great
it was all for animators
and if you were a good animator
like you would get noticed like instantly
and you'd get your
animations posted into like the high quality
sections of the website
which was pretty cool
they had a ranking system
there's beginners, intermediates, veterans
and elites and I moved all the way up
to like the 10 people
who are in the elite zone
doing that shit
the ranking system
was very
controversial later on
because how dare you
rank people's artistic ability
or something
I hope you put that on your resume
I was elite on this forum
on the dark demon forum
on the fucking dark demon
there was one guy
who had like 30,000 posts
his name was Skype and I don't know how the fuck
he managed that
that was a post count of everyone else
some people were just forums
they just spend all their time on forums
and I feel like those people in particular
had a hard transition to discourse
well I mean
how many fucking tweets have I made
since starting my account
too many
is there a counter?
there used to be
I don't think it's public anymore
but there's probably still a way to check
it might be
you've made 17.3k tweets
Ben
I have?
wow, every single one a gem
worth the
17k
wow
I mean my account is pretty old
my account is like 7 or 8 or 9 years old
oh yeah
I'm liking that pinned tweet
while you were in the bathroom we had a brief discussion
about the plebe and the weeb
I'm sad I missed the announcement
it was very funny
all the people
trying to talk you down
you got to stop being so deranged
with your Trixie hate
it all led to this, it was all worth it
yeah
I kind of thought
this is building
it's going to be hard to top this
just going back to shitting on Trixie
in a few snipes tweets
I'm not saying you're not allowed to do it
it's going to be hard to top this
I've been
I've been gloating a little bit
I've been trying to gloat a little bit on Twitter
and they just are
the cowards are simply pretending
they don't notice
they pretend they do not see
I know that they know
I know they're seeing the ads
you made a tweet to this effect
you got Trixie in a bind
she just can't acknowledge it
there's no win scenario for her
she looks so bad
she looks so stupid
there's nothing she can say
to be like
Ben's bullying me about this
there's no angle
that she can take
I'm sure she's told Riley
Riley don't answer
just ignore it
don't acknowledge it
they at least want the complimentary free one
they want
I'm trying to extend the olive branch
I'll give Riley one too
he can have one
I'll give one for Bird
not only is the Radcon
for Kickstarter finally almost
having all his shit fulfilled
but even Kickstarter you weren't personally a part of
you're fulfilling now
Radcon
it's actually
I didn't really mention it
but Radcon 2
the documentary is in there
it's one of the bonus features
people might actually
the watch alongs
are not quality content
they're long
some of them might be funny
but they're pretty low quality
it's content that exists
they might as well go on there
yeah
it was bonus content for backers
so I put it on the disc
but the Radcon 2
that was never uploaded anywhere
and it's edited
it's got interviews
in it and stuff
Victor filmed a bunch of us behind the scenes
at Radcon 2
that's a good little piece
I think it's like 40 minutes
it's an actual little documentary
of what we were all doing behind the scenes at Radcon 2
and I think it's the only place you can see it
that's a quality little bit
of exclusive content
that I think is pretty neat
a tectonic improv provided me
with the links to that
wait
what's up
wait how did tectonic improv
because he was a backer
yeah it was like
backers got a link to like a
what do you call it
a
google drive
that had bonus content in it
including all the watch alongs and stuff
and then of course there's the exclusive
message from Ben Sain
as the first bonus feature
in which I give my thoughts on the situation
it's got to see the message from Ben Sain
that's like
if you haven't heard the message
from Ben Sain
what are you even doing
you're not a real plebe in the weeb head
that's the final piece of plebe in the weeb related content
that will ever be produced
I think so
I think you should be called
dweebs
I think the generic term should be dweebs
I was thinking
I'm gonna make an NFT series
based on like those character designs
they should be called
dweebs
just take that design and run it to like a million
different variations
I can see that
yes just iterate it
do like a stone toss style thing of like
okay I just have a bunch of different eyes
a bunch of different mouths, a bunch of different whatever
and randomize
here they are
dweebs is the name
yeah let's see
do I have anything else to say about that
Trixie is
too cowardly
to acknowledge it
it's probably
this is probably my last hurrah
like yeah I can't
it would be hard to top
what else is there to do
you have to really start from square one
what else is there to say
just solid own
full album
I hope you will buy them
I think I have sold exactly
50 of them
that's pretty good honestly dude
a few
I don't know
I guess I'm not that surprised that there's like a market for it
but like it's just
I wouldn't have also been that surprised if a lot of people are just like
I don't want to buy a blu-ray for this shit
I can just go watch it on YouTube if I care
they don't get the exclusive content though
okay
I'll break it down
buying are like actually people who
you know pledge to the kickstarter
and actually want their thing versus how many people are just like
oh that looks funny I'll pay for it
very few only
that's what I was curious about
interesting
okay
only nine people are like yeah I pledge to the
kickstarter
thanks for making it
can I have my copy
the majority are just like
yeah I want one I guess
I
I spent about
okay
I'll break it down a little bit
I paid slow but on like
$150 to make the files
the
50 DVDs
cost me like $100
or blu-rays cost me blank ones cost me
$100
the cases cost me like 20 for
50 and then printing the labels cost
me like $40
and then
so Ctole got me a blu-ray
burner
but the one he got me broke
so I had to get another one
and I also needed a printer
to print on the
disc which is a little bit
hard to find like I tried to get a printing
company to do it and no one would do it
so I had to
get a printer capable of doing it
fortunately it wasn't that expensive that printer
ended up costing $200
and the blu-ray burner cost
a little less than $100 or about
$100 so all in all
I probably spent maybe like
I don't know
it was maybe like $300
on materials and then
the burner and the
printer were another $300 but like
I keep those so
I don't know if that really counts as an expense
because like now I have a new printer and that's pretty cool
so selling the 50
copies has made it has paid for
all the materials it has paid
the cost of the printer
and the burner and I have made
like a few hundred dollars in addition to that
on top of that. Damn I can't wait to get Phantoms Revenge
on printed onto a blu-ray
Yeah you gotta make a PS4 version
so that you can put it on a blu-ray and send it
I bought another batch
of 50 DVDs
and cases and labels I'm hoping
to sell most of them. I'm definitely gonna buy one
If I don't sell
Thank you. I hope everybody will buy one.
I honestly
I think you mentioned this Samoy. I am impressed
that you went to the effort of making it
like a real DVD instead of just
throwing the files on a thing and like the
autoplay when you throw them on a DVD player
like it has a freaking menu guys.
That's what Trixie was gonna do.
At that point it's like
why even bother having it on a blu-ray because
if you're just gonna have the files basically
just go watch it. You know what I mean?
Yeah.
I was like no. I'm gonna make it like
I'm gonna make this like a nice little
collectible item. A nice little thing to put
on your shelf.
This is gonna be on someone's shelf out there
and someone will be like what the fuck is this
and someone will be like oh boy okay how do I even explain this
okay so there was a Kickstarter and there's this guy
Ben St. and he was really mad about
a lot of things
That's the
I made the back of the label
you know I wrote the whole like
the back of the label is not about what plebe
and the weeb is. The back of the label is about
Ben St. and why Ben hates Trixie.
I saw some people upset about that
in Jesse's server
they just wanted the label to just be about
Wait what? Say what?
I saw some people were upset about that being
the back of the case. They just wanted it to
just be about plebe and the weeb
which I completely wouldn't exist
without Ben St's
furious anger so like you know
like you know I think he earned the right
to put it on the back. Like it's not like he
went into every episode and like
digitally inserted himself going
by the way this is why these guys are dumb
you know what I mean?
Was a relevant blurb
part of the stretch goals?
Ben St. appears on screen, green screen
points that these guys are fucking with me
A relevant blurb wasn't
part of the stretch goals so
the blue rays exist as promised
so that's all that matters
Neither was the coveted
exclusive message from Ben St
Wait how much
How much of the kickstart
of money did Jesse receive?
Do you think?
That I don't know
I heard people saying that Trixie received like 7k
but I don't know if that's accurate
The whole
the whole campaign raised
7k
Is that true?
I said it's not like all of that one
Oh yeah
She said she paid Jesse
something and I don't know
how much it was so I really don't know how it breaks down
Some money
because Jesse had the whole like his
house flooded or whatever
I vaguely recall
like
the money was for editing all of the
episodes
and being in them I guess
but I don't know what the number was
This one
Yeah I shouldn't give a
But the kickstarter for Radcon 2
or the kickstarter for plebe and the weave
included like getting flights
for people for Radcon 2 as well
The stretch goals were
basically plane tickets to fly us out there
to be on plebe and the weave episodes
and I think one of the stretch goals was
like when we get everyone
out there we'll have Radcon 2
I think
it was mentioned somewhere
Right
Let's see
I feel like there was
maybe one other thing I wanted to mention
about it
I don't know
It's just
Money
Give me money please
Give me money
If I have some
I'll probably have a few left over
But that's okay whatever
Maybe like I'll just have
20 or 30 copies left over
It's fine whatever
It turned a profit it's okay
Give away to your patrons
with the left over ones
I've always been interested
in like home media releases
for like internet shows
I have like the first quote unquote season of angry video game nerd
on dvd and I have much other stupid shit
like red vs blue
and mega 64 dvds
I've always been fascinated
by this
I've been fascinated by that kind of stuff
and this is
not only is this that
this is like a physical release of internet thing
but like it's way weirder than that
because of all the shit that's gone down since then
I
I love thinking about someone
it was the same with road to radcon
like on the back of road to radcon
I had the little blurb explaining what it was
I can't imagine reading that
with no knowledge of the PCP
That would be so confusing
It's like someone finding it
and being like what is this book
and then the back of display it's like
okay so there was a thing called radcon
from like a podcast called the procrastinators
and they wrote a book
but then like one of them quit
and then the other one like printed it
and like okay I guess
it's great
comedy gold
mate I'm hoping
it's like
what's the word for like
environmental storytelling
but in real life
it's just sort of it's like a weird artifact
that would puzzle someone
it's not just like oh it's a figure from
an anime it's a book
about
some people on a podcast
it's so exciting right I love that
who are these it's a lesser known
podcast as well it's not like a big thing
no no this isn't like
this isn't like you didn't find
you know the fucking
like D&D
comics from the
my brother my brother and me
thing
that's dumb everybody knows that
you should have like some weird shit
that's some weirdos printed out a few extra
road to radcon and just like leave them like
good wills and just like random places
like so someone at some point will find it and just be like
what the fuck is this
I have like
45 copies just sitting in a box
and I could spare a few
why not
I just imagine someone in 100 years being like
what the fuck was going on in the past
in the past
imagine you're like
you're like
you're like man I'm curious
like what were things like in the
past and then you're like hmm and you're like
just going through random and you pick up
road to radcon you read the back of
like radcon
like did you bro like what the fuck
man the past was fucking
just imagine someone picturing radcon
like 100 people like they just
think it's like a convention you know like they don't understand
in 50
years from now someone will find it and be like
huh what the fuck was going on in the past
like this would have been an NFT today
this would be on the blockchain like
I haven't seen a physical book in years
they find a book like what is this some kind of
physical pdf
NFT I don't understand
wait it's
they pick it up and they're like
wait I can't
funge it it's not fungible but it's not
on the blockchain it's in
physical space it's in my hands
how am I supposed to read this
book if it hasn't been verified on the blockchain
by that point we'll be
at web 4.0 and I can't even imagine
how horrible that'll be
I wish web 4.0
I wish they would just stop counting
I wish they would just stop
incrementing the number so
and then it would all be okay
once we get to web 8.0
then the spiders will take over the earth
and
they'll have a real world wide web
which is all in it
cute
it's finking too far ahead
that was pretty good
I want
everyone to buy
if we ever get that damn
dojin, if we ever get that damn
radcon dojin done
so much merch so much
so much weird radcon
PC shit to purchase
you'll get road to radcon
in your own home for your shelf
you've got the road to radcon
you've got the plebe in the weave
and you've also got phantom's revenge
you're working on which again as I already explained
in the nicest possible way
it's the weirdest, most hard to understand
do you ever plan on making something
that normal human beings can comprehend
and understand without a million years
of internet lore behind them
that's something good about the paper
which is you can just pick it up
and read it
what's the point
if there's not
if you just understand it
I'm with you man, I like the weird internet shit
so don't take it as like
I don't know
yeah, I'll make normal shit at some point
you know, I ain't gonna finish
my fucking Winnie the Pooh
my Winnie the Pooh retrospective
dude, Winnie the Pooh just became public domain
yeah, it's perfect time for that, you gotta do it
but only the shirtless con
if he's wearing a red shirt
you will get sued
have you seen the Ned Flanders meme
if he's
if he's red and yellow
that's Mickey's fellow
if he's shirtless and brown, you're in fair use town
I love it, it's a good bit
yeah, it is
excited though, excited
man, imagine what the
with the twitter artist community
can do now that
Winnie the Pooh is fair use
the possibilities are endless
so if you gave him like
a blue shirt
I guess
there's like little things
like I think Tigger is a Disney character
like you can't just use everything
but I think the rest of the cast should be okay
just don't use
wait, are they guess the original stories might be
fair use now huh
orange
they must be
anything that's Disney original
and also like the specific
like Disney character designs
are not fair use
but
I don't know
so just draw badly and give him a blue shirt
and you can just do the entire film
so like gopher
right, gopher is a Disney original
he was not in the original books I don't think
so tragically
artists, I'm sorry
you can't use gopher, I know you were all like
clamoring for
the gopher fandom is like
heartbroken
the gopher verse
it kind of
it kind of reminds me of how
the wizard of Oz is public domain
but not the red slippers because I was
invented for the movie
wait
you mean
what are you talking about
the wizard of Oz is public domain
but not the red slippers because I was
invented for the movie
oh
right, they were like silver shoes
yeah, they were the 7 dragons balls
there's
a million fucking Oz books
there's a lot of weird shit in that whole
I guess I didn't realize it was public domain
right
there's the wizard of Oz, the warlock of Oz
the mage of Oz
the fighter of Oz, the thief of Oz
the paladin of Oz
the cleric of Oz
the goblin of Oz
a whole RPG
party's worth
of Oz books, I guess
yeah, I've heard
about those, I've never
I mean, I've never read
any of you have read the Oz books
I haven't, I haven't read it
they actually did make a JRPG about the wizard of Oz
for the DS
yeah
yeah, I believe that
I believe that completely
that seems like the kind of thing that would be
right for like a Tim
that would be right for like
a Tim Burton
like Grimdark reimagining
I thought you were going to say
they must have done those
I thought you were going to say a Tim Rogers video essay
about the
wizard of Oz
JRPG
yeah
um
fucking
I don't know, no, did they make
Oz video games? Yeah, they probably did
yeah, it seems like
someone would make um
RPG maker like survival
yeah
indie RPG maker top down
yeah, ones like that
I could see it in my mind
you make the scarecrow scary
yeah
duh
stupid
what are you fucking stupid bro
wait a minute
wait a minute, we can't have dark
themes
in children's media
what was I making fun of
there was some like
some post was going around that was like
oh it was Animorphs
oh
I saw someone posting like
bro, like I just read this Animorphs
book and it's about like child soldiers
and like there's war
it's about how war is bad and like people die
and they get killed and I was like oh my god
this is so
fucked up
they get that one past the censors
I can't believe they made kids
read these in school
they forced them to do it
anything that's like
darker than Barney the dinosaur is
really amazing that kids could actually
watch that
like I know, in the
Animorphs lecture we did
we were a bit guilty of it as well
we also like clapped and cheered and were like
whoa and it was like
all child soldiers genocide
war crimes
there was some war crimes
particularly weird shit in Animorphs
beyond just like you know
child soldiers
body horror stuff that one in particular
I'll say is a little weird but other than that
I don't have anything against dark themes
yeah
body horror
you know what else that annoyed me on twitter
you know what else annoyed me on twitter
this week
a lot of things annoyed me on twitter
I'm gonna throw one of our
former guests under the bus
and say it was very irritated by
Mallory Eudicious's
posts recently
you know her, she's the
the new guy
girl
they've been
they've been posting on their main account about
like I've decided twitter is bad
and I'm quitting
I just kept posting about like
I'm quitting twitter now
oh I can't believe more people are following
oh people are patroning me
quitting twitter is based but like
actually doing it is based
not making a big deal of it
she may
actually do it at some point
but it's annoying to be like
I'm totally leaving twitter guys
I'm really doing it
you saw Lindsay Ellis
she's like done with being a public internet person
and then like as soon as she announced
she's like this patreon
will no longer be putting out things
and it got like 3000 new members
yes
it did
it went from like 8000 to like 12000
that must have been intentional
because she put her goodbye message behind a paywall
okay people got mad at me
because I said she paywalled the message
and people were like no she didn't
but like she definitely did
she definitely did
like the first few hours ago
it wasn't paywalled and then she made it paywalled
oh it's interesting because I was going to say
I think I remember seeing it and it wasn't paywalled
and then that's weird that she would do it in that order
because like you know once it's been out there
it's been you need to text you
just copy paste it it's not even like hard to
replicate
so yeah I did not actually
read the post
so I can't comment on what she
actually said in it
so is that I heard
is that I heard she's quitting
being a youtuber or an internet person
and
it was an interesting
I'm not here to shit on her or anything
I don't want to start drama not that I mean
not that we're even on the same level but like
it was a very melodramatic post and it was a little cringe
and it was she's mad
she still buttered that she got cancelled over like some
dumb twitter take about
freaking like avatar the last airbender
like nobody fucking cares
yeah that whole thing
it was people getting mad at her
for like not like the take itself
like people calling her racist
and stuff like I'm sure when you're a creator
of that size you just have to deal with a lot of
bullshit so like I get it it's not like
how dare she be fed up with twitter
of course she of course she have haters
I didn't think her post was too melodramatic
no she can totally leave if she wants
what is very reasonable is just like
being an internet creator has like
a lot of stresses that I'm just not prepared
for and it's not for me
which I think is fair
that's okay
that's okay you don't
tell me you aren't cut out for being an internet person
you can leave if you want
you don't have to make youtube videos
if you don't want to make them
it's okay
oh yeah that was basically it
well she's like she's like writes books
and stuff too and she's like I don't even know if I want
to write books with my name because my name
is like you know tainted or whatever
it's been tarnished by people
by viewers calling me racist online
jkls
haha
you know
I'm just like
I guess I feel
you know I feel a bit the same way
they're not on the same level but I feel a bit the same
about like you know
Lindsay Ellis yeah some people hate on Lindsay Ellis
some people like call her racist for like
a stupid tweet she made
you know people hate on her like that
and you're like you know Mallory
a lot of people hate her and be like oh she's
a shoplift supporter like she's
a criminal yeah that whole controversy
was incredibly stupid
okay that
it still happens
there's people still make threads
about like Mallory is bad because
shoplifting and like I can't believe
she would support like every time
I lose my fucking
mind every time like there's literally nothing
in the world that makes me matter then people making a
thread about how like Mallory is bad
because she made a comic where someone shop
insanely done and that's like terrible at this point
like for God's sake it's insane
I saw a thread about that
like last week and someone and someone was like
the thread was like guys
what's worst the worst thing about
this the worst thing about this comic
about shoplifting is that she shop lifted
from BIC
or from Blick which is family owned
it's a family
owned company that she was stealing from
and someone responded
in all seriousness
like I can't like that's disgusting
like I can't believe
from a family owned company
and I'm like
she had some article right
she put an article out about like this whole
her dealing with the online harassment and she was like
she was like she was like I wasn't making
this comic to be like it was a bio
I was just like
I wasn't making the comic to be like this is you should
steal stealing is based even though it is a little base she wasn't
she was really just like I wanted just to like make
a comic about a character who like
has like you know just like
yeah like people people thought
yeah people people thought it was
a self insert right yes
it was not meant to be that's what she said when she was on
we had her as a
we had her as a guest and that's what she said she's like
it's literally just a
you know it's it's a fiction it's a comic
about a care I mean she did say in a tweet
that like yeah she used to shop lift
art supplies when she was like a teenager
you know the fucking
uh the woe woe
betide should to get mad about on twitter
okay people getting mad about that it's just like
I can't even write my head around it like what the
fuck is it it makes me so mad
what's what's what's even stupid
oh sorry
well but that okay that's not the
point the point is right yes
obviously that all makes me mad
like never nevertheless
nevertheless like I
definitely don't feel bad for
her because like ultimately
the controversy has gotten her a lot of exposure
and made her a lot more successful I know
that that is the case
and I feel the exact same way about
and I feel the same way
and I feel the same way about Lindsay like
like I'm sorry like I'm sorry
you're upset that like
many people on the internet
don't like you they make
they make they maybe they harass you
in various ways on like social media
or whatever uh they
mean things about you and you get hate
on the internet like I'm very sorry about
that but like fuck's sake
I will I could never I could never
in a million years feel bad for
Lindsay Ellis it's uh yeah
so fucking successful it is a little like
she's got like like sure like
these bad things might happen to you but like
you've obviously gotten so much
out of your internet celebrity
and your position like it's obviously
been a massive net good for you like
I can't possibly be expected
to feel sorry I'm empathetic in the
sense that it must suck having a million
people post dumb shit at you
and say you're racist on Twitter when you're not
like that really probably does suck a lot
and like might take shit out of your mental health
absolutely and you don't have to be on Twitter
if you don't want to or anything like that
but yeah I absolutely agree which is like
I think here's I'm not like one of these like
guys who gives a fucking like
cancel culture but I think
the like sort of accepted theory
on why she's so buttered about it is like
she was very instrumental
and like this whole like
Twitter you know going after
someone when they have like the wrong take
and like really going hard at them and
she just wasn't like mentally prepared for that
to happen to her you know what I mean
wait wait wait
you cut out you cut out she was
she was involved in what now
people in general like
are saying that she was involved with like
going around like you know cancelling people for having
being racist on Twitter like that's the kind
of things that she would do is like start
like these mobs like everyone we need to dog-pile
this person for having a bad take so she just
couldn't believe that it
happened to her like I like like I thought
everyone knew I was on the right side of history
and like I would never be racist so like all the people
like all the people jump down my throat all the people
betray me like you know it must suck
to have your friends like not stand up for you when you
make a take that's not even racist at all and people
like all it's racist and you know people just want to distance
myself from that and not get involved you know what I mean
so I do have empathy
what I'm just saying like the only thing I
want to say is that like I mean yeah if
I were in her position I feel like I'd
handle it better and I'd be able to like
be like well the success is worth it but
everyone's brains work differently and
some people just can't handle that and
there's nothing to be held against from
for it so I
I don't hold I don't hold it again
I don't hold it against okay fair
but I also
don't feel any pity
for her and I never would
I think it's a pretty fair take
like you know when you're making six figures
a year making like media analysis
and then you know
the worst thing that happens to you is people are mean to you online
and it's and it's and it's just
and it's just a little annoying and it's not
even I can't even hold this against her right it's
not that I'm like she did something
bad like with her announcement
and then she got a bunch of support and
and it's just annoying to see her be
like I quit and the response and to have
like an overwhelming like
let's give her some more money
like it's like why
it's like there were just really weird things
in her post like like oh I employ a bunch
of people and like you know like I'm responsible
for paying their salary and I haven't even told them that I'm
quitting making content they're gonna find out when they read
this post I was just like what the fuck is this
shit
yeah that is yeah that is also a point
to it's a bit on having
as much money as you might assume because she
is paying so many people
that's true she has employees
um
I don't know it
it feels a bit like a sort of like
this is
an unfair comparison but you know
that that one
Dar man video god
he's like
where that one Dar man video where it's about
it's about like
it's about
the kid who works as a Dar man
actor getting bullied by people
who say he's in cringy videos
and the basically the plot of the video is like
you know you
you can hate me you can hate me
I Dar man can take it but when you
say mean things about my videos
you're actually hurting
this adorable child star actor
this this young boy who's just trying to get
his career off the ground like this guy
this kid who works for me like I can take it but this kid
you're really hurting this kid
I don't know this seems a little
bit like you know like I like
I Lindsay
well I like I'm responsible for paying
a bunch of people's salaries so
you know I got I got to keep the patreon going
because otherwise how would I continue
to pay all these other people
that I got to pay their
salaries for and like
kind of I mean it's
true well sure
but is that a reason to
but is that a reason
for people to just like pour money
into a you can't
that is now
that is that is now funding
nothing you can't get mad
about people wasting their money and shit
people have bleeding hearts
yeah people I guess
people fucking spend money
stupidly all the time
I mean debatably
stupidly if they enjoy the feeling
of supporting someone then whatever
it's not really
of my business where people do their money
I can understand
that like Lindsay Ellis
leaves
and then people show a lot
of support and it irks
you because where's my
support god damn it I'm still here
okay well there's a little
little more nuance than that
well there's dirt there's a lot
sure sure I just I just feel like
that the whole thing with with Lindsay is
and and Mallory and stuff
like this is that people
either are
super supportive
with their money or they're like
saying things like oh no all
and then there's the
the counteraction to the
like the the reaction
to that is to like say
no don't be nice to them don't be
why are you being so supportive
um fuck
them they're rich and they have
they're rich and they're quitting
they're rich and they're quitting and everyone's like
oh I love it I love it though
well if I was rich
I wouldn't work either
and there's those two sides
of those two takes and I just
feel so exhausted
hearing about either one of them
it's just you know
it doesn't matter other people
it doesn't matter that you're annoyed by people
other people are supporting someone
well you know nothing matters in the end
we're all gonna die I guess
I guess it's just I guess I'm
annoyed by the discourse about it
it really shouldn't
other people quit posting
on the internet all the time
and uh what happens
with them nothing nobody knows
they just leave
they just they just leave and they get
a regular job
I'm not even saying this against Lindsay Ellis
I just mean in general I always sort of have an issue
when people like if you just want to leave the internet whatever
that's fine or I saw this more on forums
two people like I'm they would make a big deal
like I'm leaving the forums they make a big thread
like I'm leaving the forums and this is why
and then like a week later they're still fucking there
you know what I mean like it's a classic
classic that like uh on
on forums that me and my friends owned
we made a rule that if you make a big post saying
you're leaving you get banned that's fair
because people would
people would make those posts and then come back
like a week later you would literally mean
when I was a teenager
you just want people to take you seriously
I understand that stuff is annoying
I just feel like it's
like is there
nothing interesting to talk about these days
that this is such a big thing
I don't you fucking cares
people have been wasting money
on stupid things
you can't be getting mad at other people's patreons
you just don't just don't think about it
you can't be you just can't be
get upset when bad people make money
you want to know how much money Stone Toss made
on his fucking schmorky parody NFTs
oh my god
uh
yeah I saw someone
posting I saw someone
someone
posted about like
oh Stone Toss made NFTs
and like the point was to be like
cringe right yeah but all you're doing is
amplifying him and like spreading that to more people
and like
okay I just
want to say really quick Stone Toss's detractors are like
like
90% of the reason why he's famous
people like oh we're gonna own him
by spreading the amugus meme and all that did
was increase his notoriety and reach
and probably gave him much of children aren't it
like fans
people do the amugus meme for that reason
yeah he just leaned into it
but it's I don't know someone was like
and I responded to that
being like like what's the point
and someone said like it's cringe it's cringe that he makes
NFTs and I was like well
sure I think so
but I know that he made a ton of money off of it
so like he got exactly what he wanted
and someone tried to
tell me like no he's probably just lying
he's probably lying about how much money he made
the one thing about NFTs
and my 3.0 bullshit is like okay first off
you can fake sales I'll give you that like it's not like
without their own possibility but for the most part
this shit is out in the open like we know how much money he's making
yeah it's
quite a lot
that's what
that's what NFTs are for
they're for bilking money out of suckers and like
I'm sure that that's exactly what they did
like there's no reason to think
that this is like a fraud like no
yeah I'm officially at the point
it's so hard to resist making fun of NFTs
we just we just have to live with it
but they get more powerful every time
you pay attention to them like the monsters
and that one episode of The Simpsons
you know the thing that's really annoying
is like people making like intentionally
like oh god
thinking NFTs on purpose to piss people off
and people just take the bait
I was like how could you get mad at this
that one I could tell
that one was so transparently
they couldn't even get mad because it was so
pathetically like scummy
it was like they want me to get mad at this
like that would be winning for them
yeah but people keep
posting about it anyway like they don't
it's the same thing with the George Floyd one too
right right
at least all the video game ones are failing
like the Ubisoft
all these big companies just try to jump in
they're so stupid
but like they don't know how to do it
they're stupid
you mean like
like in-game NFT transactions
Ubisoft did something with Rainbow Six
where they put NFTs in it and they sold like
absolutely terribly and like
people worked out and the minting cost was like
800 times what they made
they just don't
they just don't add anything
and there's the game
stalker and they were going to use NFTs
to help fund the rest of the development
they had to walk that back
yeah everyone screamed at them and they
walked it back and it was like yeah good
it turned out screaming at corporations works
the guy who played Al
Borland in Home Improvement
he was going to do like audio
NFTs
and then everyone screamed at him and he was like
hey sorry
I guess I won't I didn't mean anything
by it and it was great
I do feel a little bad for some of these boomers
and people who just don't they just don't understand
the internet let alone NFTs
and someone's just like hey we can make a lot of money with this thing
you know
he obviously didn't know
like what people were mad at him for
right
someone just came to him
and said like hey what if you
did some voice recordings and we'll
do it on this thing called the blockchain and you'll
get paid and he was like
sure
some people like meet Canyon
did NFTs and sold them and made money
but like when they were like brand new
like that was like a meat like as soon as I learned about NFTs
I saw those and like now they're on record being like
uh yeah we kind of we're not going to do that again
and stuff
yeah psychic pebbles did that
and the other guy that's working on a tv show
right oh god smiling friends that's like
today too isn't it
is that today I think so I think it's today
if it's not today it's like this week
this regard attack on Titan smiling friends
exactly
is that like is that like airing like
for the first time like today yeah
the first like actual episode not pilot
oh right yeah I was gonna say I don't know
oh
yeah I've seen um I've seen
it like gifts of it around
I like the pilot I thought it was pretty good
and I was like I already I had already coped with
the fact that we wasn't gonna get picked up because it was like a year after
the pilot before they announced it was picked up
I had a feeling it was gonna get picked up the whole time
it should
like it didn't make sense for them not to because it was so popular online
and it was really good but you know you never
know what these fucking companies will do
I don't really know what I think about psychic pebbles
I think I've seen like hellbenders
and that was like
alright I'm gonna be honest
did he do with the hellbenders
I didn't think anything he ever made was fun
I never I don't know anything about the leech pilot
only plays or psychic pebbles I've never seen
any of that shit smiling pet smiling friends was my first
like introduction I was like hey it's pretty good
yeah
that was the only thing they
that was the only thing they made
that I enjoyed
he's a
newgrounds animator boy
and he's got a very distinctive voice
and he's very funny
I like his Trump impression
I recommend one of
one of these guys I forgot where
I recommend like only plays compilations of just psychic
pebbles saying funny shit
because it is very funny
I don't even know about these guys at all
because I don't like watch any only play stuff
but I always like like you know only plays
animated like you know I love to see little animated
clips of things so I've seen like exposure from that
and you know
I don't even know why or how
let's place are still a thing but I guess
there's a few people carrying on the torch
because I mean Game Grumps is technically still going
but I don't know how many people are watching that
Game Grumps is ten years old
did you know that Jesus Christ
it's so funny to me how like John was on
one year but like
that cast such a big shadow over the rest of the show
like you know it's been like
Aaron and Danny for nine years now
but people are still like oh I remember
fucking the original series of the original
episodes of Game Grumps
yeah that's the only time I ever
watched it so obviously that sticks
out the most
yeah I mean I didn't obviously I didn't
stick with watching it but like when I did watch
it it was like you know
yeah it was about like one year and one year
so it feels in my
memory like it was like half John
and half Danny
not even close
anymore
now there are people who are born
who can vote feel old yet
I thought you were like saying that like you know people say that as like a joke
but like that could literally be true which is
fucked up
probably not that many
in your old post John
but there's probably at least some
you'd be surprised
at least a few
I think we mentioned this before
or something but
peep kids these days say oh I want to be a YouTuber when I grow up
that's so fucked up
now kids are going to be saying I want to be an NFT
when I grow up
they have higher aspirations
I want to sell my NFTs on tiktok when I grow up
what the fuck is a YouTube
go outside play with sticks and stones
and break your bones
please
no choice but to be on the web
3.0
we got to upload our consciousness to the
blockchain
what would it have been like if
COVID happened when we were kids
that's weird to think about
I don't want to talk to you
I don't want to have done so much reading
they're so literate right now
I don't even want to think
about it
probably nothing would have
changed for me
except I would have gotten COVID
several times and my brain would have been shrunken
I am very excited for being
an old man and saying I lived through the pandemic
no that's depressing
I hate that
I don't want fucking
what?
explain what life was like
to my grandchildren
we didn't go outside
and then they'll be like
we know
the pandemic is still happening
I don't want
to think about it
I died during the pandemic
this is what it looks like when you're dead
in the future
when I'm old
and kids ask me
what was it like
in 2015
I'll be like
whatever it sucked
who cares
let's just
put on our VR headsets
and play some NFT games
whatever we're doing
who cares about the past
what's going to happen
as soon as it's already happened
daddy
grandpa
what's this book
your face goes red
bitch Trixie
I'm gonna fucking tell you about this
a single tear
of rage
fist clenched
my robot fist clenched
because I got
you do the dangles when you clench your fist so hard
that your hand starts bleeding
and you're so fucking angry
that'll be
that'll be like two years from now
I'll be like
I'll snap my walking stick
I'll throw my crutches
out the window
my walker
the fucking image of clenching your fist so hard
that they both completely explode
that's a great visual gag
that's what Trunks does
fingers go through your palms
and out the back
blood everywhere
delightful
I guess
did we talk about
the new episode of the
Tails gets trolled audio
yeah I was gonna say
after I mentioned my low tax video
I was like shilling successfully
completed but I was like
we should also talk about Tails gets trolled briefly
cuz yeah we were both in that
weren't we Ben
yeah I did not know you were in that
why do you think I put
the voice of Tom from Tom and Jerry
in my Twitter profile
wait is it?
he was in the last episode too
which came out last year
they make one episode a year
yeah it's a little slow
but uh
puke does a great job
or um
whatever
I guess I could call him puke when I'm relating
to the TGT stuff because he still credits himself
is that in the credits
it was well edited and it had some nice little
nice little voice like effects
on there like my voice had
a cool like reverb on it
it was like that sounds great
when he told me you were gonna be
a voice in it I thought you were just gonna use
your normal voice
no well I mean
you'd say hello my children
I am Ben St
and I will give you satanic powers
well he um
yeah it's really funny
I mean Cybershell
you just talked normal
but like your voice
but like you're voicing Tom so like
why wouldn't you just talk like a normal guy
like Tom
well sort of the joke is that Tom doesn't like
he doesn't have a voice unless you count that
you know the god awful movie or whatever
but does anyone really want me to like do an impression of Tom from the movie
well actually
actually puke uh showed me
the normal voice actor tried voicing
Tom at first and it actually sounded like Cybershell's voice
that's just
I'm sorry I mean I know there's actually some people
in the comments are like
it took me out of it just hearing Cybershell
because it's just like his voice
you know what I mean and it's sort of a
easy to recognize voice but I'm like
I'm sorry that's just what Tom sounds like
that's just what he canonically sounds like
in every canon
yeah I mean that's what the voice actor
made him sound like so
I was thinking you should take it up with him
I was thinking like um
I was thinking like Darn
I wish I had more lines
and then I saw
right because I was the voice of Satan
who only appears
basically in that one scene
when they drink the blood
in the ritual in the church
wow
but then
I saw the new page
and the new page features
Satan's back
Satan comes back for a big fucking
awesome
scene which rules
yeah I feel bad I forgot
the artist name but that latest page is
fucking awesome
the artist is Rokinot
that one's so good
so I can't wait to like 10 years
from now voice that
dialogue that would be very
I was looking at some
Tom lines from like chapter like
14 or 16 I can't remember
and being like damn someday
I'll get to voice these I can't wait
yeah that would be good shit
oh the porn the porn argue
yeah there's some funny lines
like Tom only is relevant for the next
like 3 or 4 chapters
and then I don't know if he says
anything after that
I'm not since I'm the tgt
expert I'll tell you he appears
until chapter 16
and then stops appearing until
like chapter 23
I just don't even know if he said anything
since Sylvester has died spoiler alert
you know should read tales gets trolled
yeah
we're doing we're doing really well with releasing
the new page yeah you're actually on like a
pretty consistent schedule which is just like
crazy for tales gets trolled you know what I mean
hmm yeah
aside from
the one year when laser bot was
making a new page every day
I asked him I asked the guy
if he would have if he like
had any more
like voices he needed I told I would totally voice
another one it would be funny if he
just gave me like a more like normal character
that I could just talk in my normal
voice
I'm sure I mean I'm sure there's got to be
I'm sure more characters pop up later
I don't know there's plenty if you just
want a small character they could just give you like a troll
just some random troll who shows up
but I'm sure there's also that would be funny
yeah I think I think the next
chapter is when knuckles
goes to the troll camp and smokes weed
with the random trolls
there might be some good
good voices in there
very funny
it's great
yeah
my plan was to get high and I did
and I voiced
yeah I was Satan but I was also one of the cultists
who has like two lines
and I just did like a stupid
that scene is so funny to me the way like
laser bot like he names every character
but then they all just immediately
there was no point in giving them names
I think the one I did
was Bob
he's just
there to deliver like
one line about the church
oh wait no that's Kevin
there's one of them who says what the gently caresses
with that
because that's something awful
but he doesn't say
I don't know if laser bot was making
a something awful reference
like he thought this will be cute because
that's where they found the comic or he
he might have actually just thought
that's something people say
that was a word filter
if you don't have a something awful account
and you see someone say fuck in a post
it auto word filters to gently caress
for non account holders
he might have just thought people talked like that
he might have
but he didn't say gently caress
he said gently cares right
he said gently cares
I don't think he knows what caress meant
I love all the little typos
and little things like that
it adds so much flavor and texture to the comic
yeah it bothers me
because the song
which is probably my favorite song
the one that J Flay made
for that chapter
he pronounces it as gently caress
when it's gently cares
he didn't know the correct word
I was disappointed to see that he
correctly pronounced the word
that was spelled differently
I was
what's the line
he usually does pronounce them
incorrectly
as they're written
sometimes I feel like you have to find a balance
and sometimes you do have to read out the funny
typo
sometimes I will like
if it's like confusing or something
I'll try and just make it understandable at least
well laser bot himself
pronounced because
when they read his comic
and put it in apostrophe and isle
they pronounce it as ill
but laser bot voiced his own comic
one of the comics
or one of the pages was like an animation
that he did
and he pronounced like everything correctly
so
yeah it's an artistic debate to be had for sure
the last line
Satan says is
I will give you one day
to require these requirements
that's so fucking funny
oh god
that was also like the first instance
of laser bot ever using capital letters
in the comic
that's funny
yeah well historic
I don't know why they just use that
for that one line
Satan's the only one
so that was
the entire chapter 16
it was a highlight of my week
what's everyone been up to
I've been drunk this whole time
I've been rewatching game of thrones
oh wow
game of thrones
how far are you into game of thrones
I've watched it all before
but I'm rewatching the first
I just finished the third season
and
those first four seasons are great
they really are great tv
because they still have the books to work off
oh there's so many good little things in there
real shame but it ended
there's so much good stuff in those first four seasons
I never saw the end
I fell off watching it at like
you got lucky
game of thrones is just
like an anime because they had to make up
retarded filler
straight up a full metal alchemist scenario
where they just had to come up with their own shit
except unlike that
George R. R. Martin will never finish the books
yeah
unlike that the filler they came up with
for full metal alchemist is just better
than the actual source material
sorry not sorry
some people do think that
my partner probably agrees with you
that actually happens
because I was looking at
I was looking at a few clips on youtube
before I decided to start rewatching the show
and there was that one
where Charles dance
Tywin Lannister
is gutting the
the stag on the table and he's telling
Jamie you're a fucking idiot for killing Ned Stark
isn't that his first scene
that's the first scene with Tywin Lannister
he was such a good character dude
Tywin
apparently that scene
was written by
D&D
for the show it wasn't in the books
there is actually
some good filler in the first four seasons
that they made up
and it makes the
the ending of the show
a little more strange
I'm kind of curious to see how
cause like
so early on in like
the march south to King's Landing
who if you know
Bruce Bolton
like what happens
with him and his busted son
it's like
I know he's a villain
but he seems like just a regular
who cares kind of guy in the background
and so rewatching it is like
oh they're actually
doing things they're actually like making little hints
here and there
it's great there's so much packed into
even just the first episode
it's great for
for world building it's great for character development
I think there's like a line in the first episode
where it's like they throw
he's just like oh yeah you
what's your name barriced on Darien you go do this
and he's like okay and then like yeah that like
comes up like two three seasons later you actually
meet that guy and he's like a kind of important character
and it's just like there's a lot of little things that
yeah the first time watching it
not only did I watch Game of Thrones you know like
you know not binge watch it I watch it
like basically as it came out year by year
so that's like a different way to experience a show
versus like actually just going through it again
because you can really notice all like the plot
threads that they like lay down
and you can like notice the ones that like
that doesn't go anywhere they never brought that back up again
you know what I mean
man uh
Cracking Tilly Game of Thrones
the show there's just not enough
heraldry there's not enough like
the books like laying on really thick
like all of these like different houses
and stuff have like these very
specific like color schemes
and like animal motifs
and all of the characters are described in ways
that like evoke the animals
that like their houses are based on
and in the show it just
that just can't you just can't do a thing
like that in the show
so they just kind of don't
I feel like it does
like the toys have like the
the armor that looks like fish scales
yeah a little bit
and the Lannisters have their lion
like stuff and
Ben would you prefer if there was always
would you prefer if there was always a guy
stood in the background holding their flag
like whenever a family was holding another family
that would be awesome
up 100% of course
why would you even ask me that
Ben's saying himself
okay they have flags though
it's just the fucking okay some of the shit
that like some of the shit the heraldry
and the armor that they wear in the books
sounds like like fucking Mecca
like they I think
Tywin Lannister has like one where he's like
has like a full suit of armor where like he just has
like his head is just
it's just like an entire like lion
he's like he's like a fully
like suited like golden man with like a full
like lion head and stuff
Ben is correct there is some cooler
shit that they just had to scale down for the show
like even the iron throne is supposed to be like this
massive giant thing
it's just like a prequel show
it's just a fucking chair
they're making like a prequel show
where they're gonna do the throne justice
it looks like but I don't know if it's gonna be good
I don't know who's gonna like
watch the prequel shows
I feel like every all the normies I know
like have completely like
I haven't heard anyone mention Game of Thrones
in the fucking dog's age
seems like people who read the books would mostly be interested
but it depends on if they got
like actually good people to direct it
if it's a good show then you're right it'll be fine
we'll see
I guess I shouldn't prejudge it
they should do like a
they should do like a young Sheldon and make like one about
like Ned's start growing up
with like old Nan
no no it's like hundreds of years in the past
like
oh then it's not even cool
it's not even cool
is it gonna be like pre Targaryen
rule of Westeros
I think it's dealing with the Targaryen stuff
with all the dragons and shit
seems like it could be cool
see it's funny like
in the show I haven't read the books
but like the Targaryens is really
just Daenerys
and her story is interesting in its
way but I really really
liked all of like
the stupid
house bullshit and bickering
in King's Landing
and the North and all of the houses
and like marrying people off to certain
people to get like land and stuff
that's the interesting stuff
a slice of life anime for Game of Thrones
there's
so much more
I still watch that YouTube channel
that Preston Jacobs guy
I haven't even read like half the books
I've only read like three of them
but I still watch that guy's channel and all
he's like he does
he sort of branched out into other stuff that I'm not as interested in
but his like
I mean you can't blame him for branching out
but I agree with you though
I like the book analysis stuff even as a non-book reader
there's some really interesting stuff
there's so much like shit
there's so much shit
in the books that are like
all these like minor characters
have such like specific like heraldry
associated with them and Preston can take that
and be like oh okay
so we can actually like this guy if you think about it
you can actually be like oh
we can like kind of figure out this guy's entire
like parentage and like the whole
like bloodline that he's from
and like therefore like how does he
how does he probably feel
about like
maesters and dragons and
you know like which side would he
probably prefer in this
you know is he a religious
is he from a religious family
does he support like the iron
woods or the other guys
from Dorn
you know like they've all got
all these associations with them
and it's there's just a lot
there's a lot of that stuff
and I feel stupid even
saying it like and it doesn't they had
cut it all from the show like like of course it doesn't
all make it into the show because the books are
like seven of them and they're each like
thousands of pages long
so like yeah the books are so dense
there's so much going on every page
genuinely so many words
there's so many wordles
it's like a fucking that that reminds
me they're making a fucking wheel of
time show
of those books
wheel of time
I remember that
I used to read those books when I was in
like sixth grade
I was I love that shit
I read a couple of them
and I just got too dense
the show looks kind of goofy
it looks kind of goofy kind of
a lot of CGI magic
sparkly stuff and I'm like
huh there's not the vibe I remember from the books
the books
I'm a little curious
wheel of time show
let me just find some screenshots here to
people in the woods
looks medieval
guys in white robes
I'm getting like nothing
I'm getting like no impression
of anything in these pictures
I feel nothing
okay never mind I've lost interest
exactly
the only adaptation of wheel of time
that is worth anything is the song
by blind guardian that song slaps
is it about
the books
yeah it's a song
blind guardian are like this like
symphonic like metal
I've heard blind guardian before
they made a song about wheel of time
and it's probably their best song
and one of the best
metal songs I've heard ever
it's really good
really good shit
I used to get so excited about
TV adaptations of like
things I had read and like oh dude
I can't wait there's gonna be the TV show
it's gonna be so epic now I'm like
I don't care or I actively dislike it
like recently why the last man is a comic
series I haven't read in a long time
I remember really enjoying it back in the day
oh for years I remember
oh I wish they'd make a show on this
oh I'd be so cool oh I wish they'd make a show on this
and like last year they made a show and I was like
whatever I didn't even watch it
they got cancelled after one season
I was hype as a child
when I heard they were making
an Animorphs TV series
and I don't know if you've ever seen the Animorphs TV series
it's like
legendarily shit
I can only imagine
it would be so hard to make a good animated
it would be so hard to make a good Animorphs show
I feel like
it didn't even look good as a kid
I can't I don't even want to see it as
an adult I'm like afraid of what it would
look like to my adult eyes
because I was in like third grade
for that shit
when was the first time you realized
as a kid that movies can be bad
I remember probably when I was like
three years old
it was the first time I watched the nostalgia cringe
yeah I liked everything I ever saw
until I had him explain to me
why it was bad
my bad credit card
oh god
I saw like Harry Potter
and Disney films and I was about it
I wouldn't really listen to movies
so I hadn't even been explaining
how terrible
have you guys seen kick assia
that's a great movie
that's legitimately
one of the worst movies I've ever seen
how many movies have you made
that's what I thought
the other ones are worse
kick assia is the best one he made
it's the first one right
because they get progressive
the second one was
suburban knights
that's one of the bullshot
that's one we can see is big fat bulls
oh kick assia I was thinking of kick ass
like the
luchin door superhero kid
oh yeah the real life superhero
this is the real shit
way better than that
the thing that sucks
about it is not even bad
in a funny way it's just bad
no it's legitimately good
I watch it every day
it's great insight
watch it like a documentary
you're actually seeing all these internet creators
they actually were like
they did this they were forced to do this
by Doug
they were forced to do this
a compelling cultural
artifact
a sort of proto
road to rad con
a sort of proto plebe in the wee blu-ray
is a movie like kick ass
now there's a pretty meme exquisite
hell yeah
something you look at and you're like
why
did anyone make this
what's the story and you look at it and you're like
I don't know just thinking about
you watch something like kick assia
which I haven't seen of course
but I can imagine
and you're not thinking about the story of the movie
you're thinking about like
oh there's that guy I know
him from the youtube
what is he feeling as he's being directed
by Doug Walker to do this fucking stupid shit
right now
that's what you're supposed to think
you can't get immersed in the world of the movie
it's impossible
it doesn't make any sense
and even a hack like Doug
probably didn't think anyone was gonna be
immersed in the story
he must have known
this is a stupid... I don't know about that one
I think he might have really thought he was making
a great movie
I feel like he knew
he was making a funny comedy
a funny comedy that's
somewhat
somewhat self aware about
its status as a sort of
weird artifact that exists to
bring all these internet content creators
together into a single
film
it's a hype moment
a legitimate hype moment for everyone who's fans of
all these people to see a crossover
it's a comedy movie and it's not taking itself too seriously
that's the first one
to boldly flee the last one
is way
more like sincere
it's a lore movie and Doug really thinks
this will be a great
magnuopus for his
nostalgia critic character and it's so
painful
that is absolutely right there's way more of
understanding that
kickass is a silly low budget
it's just like we're all on screen at the same time
isn't that funny
but by the third time they were doing it he was like
this is epic
you know what? fuck you
that's what phantom's revenge is
it's the ultimate send off
to a classic character
and fuck you if you don't think that's cool
is the game gonna suck?
there's no more voicemails
or else Lin's nostalgia critic
would have had to bring even more voicemail characters together
and take it too seriously
Ben saying that phantom home is the
to boldly flee no phantom home's revenge
is the to boldly flee of the slimy
punishment universe is not a good thing
it's a bold statement
I would absolutely describe it
as the to boldly flee
I hope the
final boss is the plot
you know what I mean
uh
the fucking first
movie I ever saw that I was like
oh what the fuck
bad movies exist
I don't actually remember how old I was
when it came out it was spy kids freedy
I saw it in theaters
and I'm like this is a movie made for me
how can you not like spy kids freedy? it has the guy in it
the guy
I didn't know who Frodo was
at the time
fair enough
I mean even aside from that
it was a funny scene
I just remember
here's my memory
I walk into the movie theater
I sit down
the fat kid breaks his piggy bank
on the floor
and then there's flashing lights and there's like a boxing glove that flies
out of the screen into my face
and then I walk out of the movie and I'm just completely
underwhelmed like
I didn't have fun
I feel like I had no fun at all
I think that happened
I feel like I was supposed to enjoy that
I think that happened with me with the second
Narnia movie I think it was
we went to cinema and saw that and I was like
oh this is uh
wait things can be bad
the first Narnia movie sucked
how old were you when Narnia?
I don't think I had even seen the first one
I had like yeah those fucking
old Narnia movies exist I remember
seeing one of my friends
the TV special
it was a TV special
the one from the 80s
I'm talking about the 2008 one
I know that's what you're talking about
that's why I said that one sucks
because the other one is
it has more hard but it's like the special effects
are awful and terrible
you've awakened the fucking memory in me
do you remember the beaver that looks
like a cylindrical
turd
I only saw one of them
it was I think it was based on the 7th book
or the one where if I go underground
or something there's like a character who like turns into a giant snake
and like it just fades
and there's like this fucking weird like
styrofoam like rubber cylinder
that's like supposed to be like
some monster and it just like flops on the floor
and I just remember laughing
so hard I was at a friend's house
I need to look up that clip holy fuck
I completely forgot about it
they never even made voyage of the Don
Treader the fucking cowards
they did
remember this one
that's the one I remember
they didn't make a movie out of it and I didn't watch it
well they didn't do it
with the old
with the old TV specials and that's how I wanted to see it
old TV specials
no look at her
they did it with a crappy nooster
I swear to god my parents
read me the Narnia books
when I was like a wee lad
I retained almost
zero knowledge of them
let me tell you the one
literally the one plot detail I remember
from all those books is there's a part
where like this little rat guy
gets on a boat
and then he like sails off to the edge of the world
and that's all I remember
voyage of the Don Treader
that's the only thing I remember from the entire series
no was he like a dwarf
wasn't there a
no there was a dwarf
yeah
he gets in a little
bucket or something
the ship can't go any further because
either going to the edge of the world
the sea becomes too shallow
and they're like we can't go any further
and the mouse is like I don't care
I'm gonna see the edge of the world or I'm gonna die trying
I'm gonna get in my little bucket and I'm just gonna keep going
see ya
I vaguely remember that
getting that part and I'm just like what the fuck
this is crazy
voyage of the Don Treader
fucking rules
my mom read me
specifically
the one about the line that was in the wardrobe
that was the only one we have
I do vaguely remember some from that one
that one's an iconic classic book
and then I got to school
and then we had a school library and I was like
wait there's more Narnia books
and I read them all
and they were great
some of them were better than others
voyage of the Don Treader is the best one
and yeah
Christian
that's why they call me Ben Saint
now it fucked me up forever
voyage of the Don Treader
I really really loved
I've read it like probably seven times
I've read all the books like at least five times
magicians nephew
I really like magicians nephew fucks
I love the fucking dying world with like the old
red giant son and shit
I like don't remember that one very well
I remember that one as being kind of the
boringest one
it was because I was too intellectual
for your young brain
I mean it probably was
I was probably like nine
so sure
why not
I just remember them going to this world that's like completely fucked up
and everything's dead and like the sun is about to explode
and there's just this fucking
there's this fucking bitch there who's just evil
and like trying to fuck everyone up
and it's great
there's a green ring
and a yellow ring
and they can go to a magical forest
with puddles in it
and that's one ring to rule the world
nooo
no no no
puddles
forest with puddles it's like a dimension
of portals
or something it's like
the puddle dimension that sounds like something from
fucking unicorn jelly
yeah it's like
the subtle knife
it's like the amber spyglass when they cut holes
in the dimension
oh yeah I remember those books
those were cool books
it kind of went off the rails as it went on
I like the second book the most
and then it just kind of got weird
the first one is all about
this one
this
the first one is like it like ends
with the revelation that like oh
actually like
this actually takes place in like a whole fucking
multiverse and like everything you have
sort of experience up until now
is kind of just like some bullshit that doesn't matter
and like
it's just one world among many and like fuck it
the real adventure starts now
and then the second book a bunch of crazy shit
happens and then the third one
is like we must kill
god and
you know
yeah it's just kind of strange from there
the weird the weird church shit
in the third book is like
stupid
it's like dumb I don't know
and then they have to
they kill god
they kill god and they destroy hell
and they kill the big angel
guy who's really bad
no they don't kill god
god's already dead
and he's worthless
and there's a but the angel
who is
basically god we kill him though
because he sucks
and the church is bad and we kill them too
and everyone dies
and they send him to hell but then we're like
fuck hell and then we kill the hell
wasn't he like a Christian though
so why would he say
no this isn't C.S. Lewis these books were written
by someone who's like I'm gonna be the
anti C.S. Lewis
I'm gonna like
do Narnia but I'm gonna make sin
is good and fuck god
can I actually do that because it sounds like
he might specifically have set out to do
exactly that
that book was called Shin Megami Tensei
my parents bought the books for me
my parents are Christians and
they knew that this was what the books were about
but they still bought them for me and said hey
just be aware this is what the offer is like
but apparently the books are good anyways so read them and I did
that's pretty damn nice
pretty chill parenting
considering most people in America are like
Harry Potter is the devil it'll make you Satan
my parents were like fat like when I was really
little and then they got over it
cause they went to university and like studied
religion and were like oh yeah never mind
there's literally no reason to be against
that shit
genuinely the
his dark materials is just like a very
his dark materials
is that what I said?
yeah yes that's correct you just I'm just like saying it
cause you awakened memory
yeah I was trying to remember it's like wait
Amber spyglass, subtle knife
uh
no first one is golden compass
golden compass, subtle knife, amber spyglass
and the whole set is called his dark materials
the el-theometer
yes yes the el-ethiometer
they dumbed it down on the title
I think the first book in English
is just called the northern lights
yeah it is it is called the northern lights
well that sucked I remember reading
yeah that sucked
that sucked shit
that fucking sucked ass and was terrible
okay well in America
in America they called the book
in America they called the book the golden compass
uh
America always gets the dumb titles
no northern lights fucking sucks
the sorcerers don't
children can't know what a
philosopher is
okay yeah
that sucks obviously sorcerers
don't sucks
but uh the
northern lights doesn't even sound
like it's about like a journey to the fucking arctic circle
it does not sound like
it's about
yeah voraborealis
or in this kind of book
she she walked into the northern lights
and was transported to another dimension
delightfully devilish
the author of the author was like
he sat down and he's like
fuck C.S. Lewis I'm gonna get a little
delightfully devilish with my
with my work of secular humanism
but what if
I were to take Narnia and reverse the thematic
that would be
you remind me of a funny
story from my childhood now regarding
steamed hams and literature
those two things overlapped in my childhood
what if I made God an old bitch
and disguised it as a work of
something else
delightfully devilish
I have to tell this story it's funny
when I was um
I was probably like 10 I was probably 10 or 11
I saw that episode of the Simpsons and I love steamed hams
me and my sister were like quoting at each other
all the time we thought it was so fucking funny
we thought it was the funniest fucking thing
we even taped the episode on VHS
with a blank videotape and rewatched it a bunch of times
and then
and then I had a creative writing assignment at school
I was at a tiny school there were literally
four students after me and my sister
joined and then later there were like seven students
it was the tiniest fucking school you've ever seen
and for my creative writing assignment
I just transcribed steamed hams
from memory and I failed
you should have
for plagiarism
did your teacher know what it was
I don't even know if I did
I don't think they did
her name was Mrs. King
she was like the oldest
fuddy deadiest woman you could ever imagine
she fought everything
was a swear word
like ass
some people like you don't like the word ass
well she didn't like the word butt
and she didn't even like the word bum
that was considered a swear word
I know what you mean there's these old people who can't handle
they can't even handle the soft swear words
they can't even handle the soft swear word bum
you have to say bottom
and that's the only acceptable word as one example
what exactly
was the assignment that you were like I know
I'll just transcribe steamed hams
from memory and that will be
that will satisfy my instructor
it was just like write a short story
that was all it was
alright Mrs. King I have my
short story here it's called
who's on first
I'm trying to imagine
yeah exactly I'm trying to imagine
if I was like a first grade teacher
or whatever and like
I assigned my kids that
and one of them hands it back and they've just
they've written steamed hams
I knew you transcribed it
it was like principal Seymour
Skinner who says this like
character names and everything
I basically just like
when me and my sister would just quote it at each other
it was just that
so it was like nonsensical it wasn't like written
so it wasn't like
it was just like the sentences they say to each other
written in a sequence
and like maybe a description here of air
but mostly just for sentences yeah
just the dialogue
I'm trying to decide
that like she must she just genuinely thought it was bad
or did you just
like do a bad job transcribing
I definitely did a fucking bad job
I did not know how to spell a roar
so it's not that like
so it's not that she was like
so it can't be that she was like a first
grader didn't write this this is a work of comedic genius
this is like that this is
this is this is this is national
yeah it's like
it mentioned your to your child's
hands in like a professional like
mean writer level comedy scene
yeah it's just
it's just a steam of
consciousness if you will
nonsense you know I just
want to go on record the people sometimes will groan
when you make an aurora borealis reference now because
that scene was memed like to high heaven
and back but just for the record
that scene is still incredibly funny
I was so glad when it became a meme
it was already in my life
it was not one of the simpson scenes
that I like quoted all the time
as a kid I mean it was it was
a funny scene that I was great
but it wasn't it wasn't like that whole episode
the whole like all the short stories and stuff like
28 short films about springfield yeah
yeah it's a classic
I only saw that one like
once as a kid I didn't
it wasn't one that I like remembered that
well I thought I remember
thinking that it was weird oh you know
I mean I hadn't seen
what do you call it pulp fiction and like
half of that episode is like a pulp fiction reference
and I didn't get it because there's some very
explicit references to pulp fiction
I heard of pulp fiction because
my dad said it was a bad movie
and the director was just
trying to be too cool by doing things out of order
stop trying to be cool you're not cool
that's why
I love that reaction some people go like
they get offended when you try and like do things
in like you know non chronological order
they're like just fucking put it in chronological order
stop trying to be fucking smart
my dad's favorite movie is braveheart
and character has like a moral
like takes a moral stand
or something or makes a sacrifice or whatever the fuck
I mean alright
sure I don't know
he's just a guy that likes a good default movie
I can't blame him my dad's favorite movie
is planes trains and all the wheels because he likes funny things
I have never seen
I have never seen that it's a good movie
my name's fun mum has
I think I've seen that never watched a movie more
than once except for the matrix
she's like never watched a movie
it's like me
it's probably not that uncommon
but it feels weird to me
I like never rewatch movies like I never re-read books
I just didn't do it
I'm a re-watcher I'll re-watch things
I've seen office space literally like
a hundred times
I think the thing that I have probably re-watched the most
times in my life is Fooley Cooley
and I've probably seen it maybe like six times
only six times
that's good that one's nice and short too
Fooley Cooley is basically a movie
not even as a kid when you only had like
ten movies on VHS
and that's all you had and you just watched them all the time
okay
I re-watched stuff a lot less
than I used to
when I was younger
I mean I'm trying to think
if there was stuff that I watched
or replayed games or whatever
I didn't really have anything that I would
re-watch all the time
as a kid
how much treasure planet films suddenly as a kid
and that is a cool movie
I just kind of watched every movie that we had
re-watch a bunch because we didn't have a lot
and we didn't have good television
it's just weird that like kids today
never have to re-watch anything if they don't want to
they'll just go on their little phone or tablet
and you know you can see an infinite supply of
new content but easily
I re-watch YouTube videos at the time too though
yeah me too there's plenty of YouTube videos I go back to
I could not tell you how many times
I've seen
Rolling Rocks with A-Press
you know what I mean?
I've seen that like three times
you know what actually yeah
you didn't know about Darth Vader's suit
oh my god dude Simzi Simzi that video is
fucking amazing
there are a bunch of
I've listened to like
I've listened to all of Jenny Nicholson's
videos multiple times
just for instance
she has some really good ones
she has really good ones
when I was editing the PCP
last week I was grabbing clips from
Journey of the Spark right for that segment
where I talked about it
in the
one of the credit sequences Jenny Nicholson was voicing
Rainbow Dash
in Journey of the Spark I forgot about that
really? yeah it's funny that she was
so in the Brony like her Brony
community like dissection video
was really interesting
I worked with Jenny Nicholson on a few projects
I worked on Friendship as Witchcraft
that was one of the few videos from her I watched
she was
she was the voice
of Kagan Phantom's mom
in Phantom Reviews
Hearth's Warming Eve
she did a voice
she has one line
at the very beginning of that video
LeMau
oh and then she did
because we put Kimmy Sparkle
in one of the
the
music the song video
the cutie mark for Fuffle videos
and she voiced
two lines from Kimmy Sparkle
I did an animation of Kimmy Sparkle
like bursting into flames
and dying horrifically
it was going to be in that
I live Compossible a lot animation about John Delancey
because I was on that project as well
why wasn't it?
they cut it out
why?
fuck off
we sent it to Jenny
and she loved it
and when I met her at Fiesta Choir 2014
she was like oh my god you animated that thing
and was like super
like happy about it
which was cool
when I met Jenny
at the last Bronycon
we were walking
because there were like two buildings
and we were going to a room in the secondary
building
so we had to pass through a sky bridge
and I was walking towards the sky bridge
and I was just unsure where to go
and I had just made up my mind
I'm going to ask the next person I see
like is this the way to the building
and it just so happened that the person that walked out
of the sky bridge was Jenny Nicholson
with like two other people
and I was like oh okay
so I asked her like hey
is this the way to the building
and she was like yep it's right through there
and I was like okay cool
and then I kept walking
and then Nicholson's met Ben St
yeah right
you jealous of her
yeah
you should hear her tell that story
when she's like can you believe the time Ben St walked up to me
and asked me where the sky bridge was
I was like holy shit
so I was just going to keep going
but then like the part
because I was like at the front of the pack
like other people were behind me
Nate was back there and Michelle
and I think a bunch of the other people we were
to be like oh hey I'm
you know I
we're these people we talked to you this one time
and like he had a whole
I'm keg!
I didn't hear what he said because I was a bit too far away
but I turned around and I was kind of like
I saw him like schmoozing and I was like
yeah alright
like I get it but also like
we were in a hurry like we're going somewhere
we're going to a panel
but I didn't interrupt
he bit you went I made the weapon
you always thickness me remember
but I didn't interrupt because I was like
yeah yeah alright it's Jenny Nicholson
you got to talk to Jenny Nicholson I get it
uh
but then uh yeah so
that's the story of how I met Jenny Nicholson
in BronyCon LeMau
I remember that
I think I was next to Nate
I barely have seen her videos
but I knew her from being
Kimmy Sparkle
and from Friendship is Witchcraft
I never watched that
really are you
I always meant to
but because I never
ever ever
look or watch or read or play anything that I say
I'm going to get around to that
I never did
you didn't have
you didn't have context for Pinky's Brew
nope
I mean I know that it's a song where she's
like a gypsy making a potion
Pinky's Brew and what's the other one
what's the other one about
the other Pinky song
Gypsy Bard
Gypsy Bard and Pinky's Brew
yeah
which I guess you're not supposed to say those words anymore
I fucking
what's the appropriate word for that
I don't know I think you're just not supposed
you're never
you just don't talk about them ever
she said
in her video that like
you know it's a slur
and it's like okay but like
it's the name of the song and like
kids on tiktok sing it and they sing the words
and it's like okay
well
cats out of the bag and there's no
there's no getting off of this train
we're on
there's a whole song about Twilight wanting the fucker
brother and I animated part of it
it was great
that was the section I did
you you animated that
part of it
yes I did
I did not know that
yeah I've been around
I had no
okay I've
wow I like I had the feeling like I've always
known that like some guest
artists like someone like made that section
and that was you it was you
this whole time the song
I animated it in like exposed
two days or something
it'll be okay
wow all right every time oblivion
full speaks he reveals a new
great secret link
to some other thing
always some kind of plot twist
that's uh that's just so fucked
up man that's just so
twisted it is so fucked up
it's twisted
it turns out
it was just oblivion full
yeah I think
so I think so yeah
true sad but true
you make all those puppets
you're puppeteering everyone
dude I get messages all the time I never have to
advertise my commissions
like ever like I get like a few messages
a week and now from people being like
hey do you still do those vectors and if I
want if I feel like it if they have a really
easy design I'll just be like sure
and then I get like a hundred bucks and then I knock it out
in a few hours
there's still demand for pony vectors huh
yeah there are
I get people I thought all
any and all pony fandom would
be stomped out forcefully
to make way for the new brony fandom
for the new generation of the show
no they'll never die
does anyone even care about the new generation
did it start I can't remember
yeah the new the new generation
okay but the new generation like
kind of acknowledges the old generation
and it like doesn't really invalidate it
so like you can bronies the next
generation there's there's no conflict
in being like a g a g
a g4 brony
and like being into
the new the new
one like you can a smooth
smooth transition of power
there's no problem with being a g4
brony but if you're one of those fucking g1
grandmas we're gonna fucking kill you
wow
yeah that's my sister dude my
grandma literally
she's dead now but I growing up
I knew her as one of the biggest
my little pony collectors in the united states
like I would go in her basement there was
like a wall of these fucking ponies
so I was always just
so to you my little pony with grandma
the ponies were fine
I'm a little curious did she have anything
to say about the brony phenomenon
I'm a little brony curious
I asked her about the
brony thing she died in like 2015
or something so she wasn't like she
didn't fully she didn't get to fully experience it which is
can you think of a greater casual life and being a
little pony fan and not getting to experience
friendship is magic
wait friendship is magic came out
in like 2010 though that
surely was a lot of time
yeah sorry I
she was contemporaneously surviving with it
I just never asked her about it I don't think she was ever
like she never talked about the new show or anything
she was a big fan but she was a big closeted
brony like she didn't tell you about it
she never
she never lived to see twilight
grow into a long legged giant
horse freak princess creature
she didn't get to finish it is what I was saying
she lived just long enough to see horseshoe finale
on her death
that's what she could check out
I don't know anything about what you're talking about
does she grow into a long
freaky monster
do you know princess celestia
no
okay well she's got a long neck
the princess
princess celestia is the ruler
of the horses but she's like a big
horse like she's just bigger and longer
than all the other horses and at the end
of the series twilight sparkle
fucking pokemon evolves
and grows up into a long
freak like celestia
only big boys
can be in charge of society
that's the message it's literally it's the
it's the almighty tallest from invader
zim that's the rule
it literally is
that's funny is it like in dark souls
how the more powerful you are the bigger you are
yes yes
yes it is
precisely like that
almost all of my
pony knowledge besides from like
watching a jenny tekelson video on that brony
thing comes from just like memes
and animation memes I've seen from like two
snacks you know the cool animation guy
there's some pretty
high quality animation
stuff out there for brony's
okay two snacks is probably most known
for his vtuber stuff now like the eco vocal
thing it's that guy
animations that were popular
in the early brony fandom
my brony knowledge comes from
asking ben and gibb things when I talk to them
oh god
as soon as he said the eco vocal thing I knew
that's not actually from the show but it's
approximately what she looks like
that's freaky
yeah she went through the fucking
junji ito cave hole
I want to see her kill someone with that horn
I think I've seen taller ponies
before but I just assumed that they were
adults and everyone else was kids
no the god queen
of ponies is long and everyone
else is a little
is a little marshmallow
and squeaky and small
and a twilight sparkle grows up to become
queen of the ponies and the
old queen I guess dies
or like retires to some
she retires to a beach
do they not show her getting small
does she get small once she leaves the power
no I don't think we ever see
what becomes of princess celestia
she presumably just goes away from her
you think small luna
could they coronate every
could they coronate every member of the
community and make them all tall and then
everybody gets to be tall probably not
because twilight was able to become
this creature through a
fucking like
magical confluence
of like mystical
knowledge and it's probably
like a once in a lifetime miraculous
event that will never be
sorry main character is only
so she's the chosen one
a little bit
is she the reincarnation of
the son of the sage of
six paths
that's a narrator
that's right
applejack gif
his awakening memory is holy fuck I remember
it
remember when Naruto made a big frog
appear okay okay
that was great
that was great that was a
pretty cool
cyber shell did you ever see one called
um oh god what was
was it um
the one the one where celestia
is like you're a bitch who likes bananas
you know that one
oh my god
triggering some neurons in my brain
I don't remember what it was called
you're a bitch who likes
bananas you're a bitch who likes
bananas
I got a fucking
t-shirt from my sister that
had a meme referencing that on it
that specific video
that was the shit now that
was the shit back in the day
whoa that frog is so huge
what the fuck it's a really big frog
I saw a thread
I saw a thread on twitter
I found the video
oh yeah friendship is magic bitch there it is
there it is I mean it's a great video
it's really funny
I saw a thread
it is
I saw a thread on twitter about a guy
who found a green
tree frog in his romaine
lettuce from whole foods
and it just lived
like he just
he bought romaine lettuce from whole foods
and he
just it was in his fridge for like days
and he pulled it out
and he pulled out some romaine lettuce
and there was just a green tree frog
living in his refrigerator
the whole time
and he's just one of those fridge
frogs you know
he made it his pet
it briefly escaped but he found it
he found it crawling around his door frame
so you know
he got it an actual like terrarium
and he named it toby
and uh
that's the story now he's his pet frog
that's a good
free frog
did he say to the frog you seem chill
you seem chill you could stay bro
I get it
I don't
I guess because he was in the fridge
wouldn't he die in the fridge
because he's cold-blooded
like don't frogs don't cold-blooded creatures
need to not be in the cold
or they die?
I thought it would just slow down his metabolism
and like help him survive honestly
but maybe
he wraps up in a little lettuce blanket
I mean being cold-blooded means they can be cold-blooded
it means they want their blood to be warmed
by like the sun and stuff but like
it would be worse if he was warm-blooded
and then he locked him in the fridge because then he would definitely die
I thought when you're cold-blooded
you need heat
or you die whereas like if you're warm-blooded
you can generate your own heat
I thought it was like that
am I crazy?
I don't think reptiles are real
I think it was just a conspiracy
I mean yeah the reptiles are the government
really
those are the real reptiles
what Simsie what is this?
you seem chill
it's just an image I really like
I love the
yeah the HD trailer and just the horrible
JPEG artifacts
they're so funny but they are sometimes
dude I'm manually painting JPEG artifacts
cause it looks like you got it from your grandma's facebook
yeah
do you actually have live info?
I did
I did a fake
a fake picture
of me like
what do you call that pose
like that meditation pose where your legs are crossed
and you're like
doing a thing
I don't know
my legs crossed and I was like floating off the floor
and I was supporting myself
with just my two pointer fingers
and the image was fake I was actually sitting
on a
like a box like a fire proof box
or something
and I photoshopped it out by
instead of taking a picture I actually ran a video
where I sat in that position
on the box with my fingers on the floor
and then I stood up and walked away
and removed the box so that there's like
an empty background
different frames of the video
I gotcha
it helps to do that on the video
I was doing a whole Captain Disillusion thing
I was just gonna say
I looked too clean
so I got a green and blue brush
and just painted in little like squary little things
around it to make it look more JPEG-y
and that made it more convincing
yes absolutely crushing your
like removing quality somehow
like makes things more believable sometimes
which is weird to think about but yeah
I was just watching some Captain D
the other day I watched
the one about playing in traffic
he's a great
Tuber for sure and he's one of those guys
that's been doing it for like 10 years
and like go back and watch his early videos
or yeah this is one longer than 10
it's been longer than 10
it hurts my brain to think that there are
YouTube videos that have been up for like 15 years
but you're absolutely right the point I was just trying to say is that
go back and watch his earliest stuff and it's not like
shitty it's still good stuff it's still good
it's like exactly the same
the highest quality that YouTube could support
at the time which is like 240p
well the interesting thing about those old videos
is that if you watch from now they're actually
16x9
which is interesting
because most videos from back then people would add
the black bars at the bottom and then
when we got widescreen there'd be extra
black bars so there's just black bars
on all sides he avoided that
he did like some weird
like codec
he injected some code into the upload
that made it so that it was
properly 16x9 and when YouTube
upgraded the video got formatted correctly
and he's the only fucking person
who did that that I'm aware of
that's insane
that is pretty cool
I don't even know how he fucking did that but he had the foresight to do that somehow
what the fuck
I know YouTube allows different video resolutions
I know I've seen some shitposts that are just
very very very wide
but doing that shit back in the day was very impressive
yeah back then no you had to
it was just like fucking
quote unquote standard resolution right
god damn that's
I sometimes wonder if he ever regrets doing the
face paint thing because it's very cool
branding and it's recognizable and
it's probably just a huge pain in the ass
cause he can't stop doing it now
I'm sure he's had moments like that
but his face though
it's so distinct like you gotta have a visual
brand like nah
no I like it I'm not at all
I'm sure he like
you know it's like this is a pretty good
you know it's a brand
it's iconic I can't like stop it
but like
I feel like he has mentioned that it's like
it's very tedious and it doesn't help
when he's trying to like be punctual
with like a fad
and try to make a video about it
when he's gonna do all of this work and editing
and like 3D work on it
that too god yeah
you can't just do a retake because you'd have to like
you can't do a retake but like you know he has to do the
make up every time he wants to do it
how long do you think it would take him to get his make up done
like he can't be that bad
he's probably pretty good at it now
he's gonna go down to like 40 minutes or something
that's still a long fucking time at least for me
40 minutes
that's just me going off memory
you can't just slap that shit on your face
especially like the black part like you know
he does a good job
apparently like he's gone faster at it
I mean 40 minutes ish is what I remember
hearing but I could be wrong
I mean looking at that even if he was twice as fast
even if he only took him 20 minutes that's still 20 minutes
that'd be such a pain in the ass dude
I'm just lazy as fuck because I thought of doing that
is so like horrifying to me
I had seen I had seen
Captain D's face
like I've been seeing his face for a long time
and only like this year did I like
find out like what he does
and like what his videos are about
yeah I only got into him
it was a couple years ago for me
but like yeah I somehow managed to like
you know there's a million people on YouTube
he can't really be in touch with every popular creator on YouTube
but like he's really he's very popular
and like he makes good videos
I would recommend him to like pretty much anyone
so like I'm just surprised I agree like how did I not find him earlier
and I still found out about him a couple years ago
so I was just like damn I felt the same way
I watched the one about laminar flow
and I was like damn why didn't anybody tell me to watch this before
this is great
yeah like I've never even heard of him
until just now so
check out his channel there's some good stuff on there
yeah I'm looking at it it didn't start getting well known
until like 2015
the first one I saw was the portal
to like Sedona or whatever that weird thing was
which is like you know I've always sort of like
enjoyed a good debunk video but like
his like special effects videos are the real
ream of the crop that's the stuff I really like
yeah yeah for sure
I always tell everyone to watch for one about the tape measure
because he just edits himself
oh that was so good
he removes the special effects
and he edits himself into the shot
setting up the special effects and like the wire rigs
and stuff and I'm like how the fuck dude
the other day
that one rules the other day I watched
the one about
it was a short one about
the trophy in the Great British Bake Off
you see that one and how they
oh yeah that's a good new one
I like that
I watched that I was like I can't fucking
believe he could just do that
I can't fucking believe this is real
that's another example of Americans
that was like a legal thing or something but like
American titles being stupid
very stupid very fucking stupid
we can't call it a bake off we have to call it like the cooking
the baking show or something like that
because Nestle owns the phrase Bake Off
I'm so stupid
fucking Nestle
is it Nestle it might not be Nestle
it was some I think it was
it was some company
someone owns the phrase
to bake off which is stupid in and of itself
terrible
nightmare
yeah
I think maybe I just checked and I just watched
the newest ones that had gone up since the last time
I had
scoped it out
you should watch every single one
I might have watched
all of you know what
I started to watch the one where he had
including his like talks his talks he does
are also like impressively good
I started watching the one about
his live shows like require so much coordination
and like setting things up
I started watching the video about
about the last Starfighter
I got bored
I like that one I thought that was interesting
I wasn't that interested in it
I like hearing minutia about
special effects so like I said that one
it did it for me
when people talk about things
they're really interested in
maybe I should give that one another try
I tried to watch the one
okay where he had
Beekman on it because like I remember
Beekman I saw Beekman's world on TV
as a kid and I was like oh my god it's
fucking Beekman but there was
okay I feel bad I feel bad to say
it about someone
esteemed as captain
D but I
when he was introducing Beekman
and they're getting really excited about
we should collab with each other
I was like it's too corny
it's too corny I'm cringing
I can't do it I had to
class that one
so I was
bored that one was a little like
I liked that he clearly had a good time
making it but I was like
he was like I can't believe
I've got Beekman on my show
and I'm like good for you
good for him you know I'm happy for him
now I fell so I was like you know
he clearly liked this one so
I used to watch Beekman
and it's so fucking
it's so weird to see Beekman but he's like 30 years
older now it's like oh my god
what the hell
what's happening
very very just
but that really
jogged a memory like oh yeah
Beekman's world
it was like Bill Nye but like Goofyere
yeah
cool cool shit
do people know about Beekman
surely some people just heard about
I'll be honest I'd never heard of him
outside of the Captain D
I wasn't aware to be honest
well okay
oh well
I remember when I was a little kid I thought he was like
Bill Nye but better
clearly people remember Captain D
he's gonna make sure all the new kids remember who he is
I thought he was funnier than Bill Nye
yes
I'm trying to think of like British equivalents
of like ooh science is cool
kids but I don't think we had
brainiac science abuse hosted by Richard Hammond
oh fuck that no
ham that's food
I remember that
I think we had like horrible science or horrible histories
but I don't think they were shows back then
we were just
Harry Potter
Harry Potter wasn't a scientist
he was the exact opposite
he was a sorcerer
from hell
he wasn't a sorcerer he was a philosopher
oh fuck
in America he was a sorcerer
and it made us really mad
do you know that the Harry Potter books in the UK
are entirely about philosophy
they're not anything to do with them
they cut out all mentions of magic
it's completely different like
setting
Harry Potter goes to Harvard and he thinks about things
I can't believe they localized
America they decided to turn it into magic
because they don't know what thinking is
nobody in England likes the movies because of that
because the English people are all wizards
the Nietzsche election
book one Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone
book two Harry Potter debates
Noam Chomsky
and so on
the Chamber of Nietzsche
Harry Potter and the Chamber of Philosophy
Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Philosophy
the Philosopher's Gewand
I want to hear what
Slaver shall we commission a dub of
oh I was going to say commission a dub of
Full Metal Alchemist but
every time they say Philosopher's Stone
get them to say Sorcerer's Stone instead
or like do a video review or it's like
I just don't understand what's going on in this show
what is a philosopher I don't get it
they localize it better
remember when Adult Swim
just aired Full Metal Alchemist
but they just dubbed a bunch of fart sounds
into it
I have always appreciated the really
stupid and like even unfunny
pranks that Adult Swim
has pulled just because I think it was a
you're never going to see another channel do anything
interesting I couldn't fucking believe it
I think it was an April Fool's joke and on April Fool's
they just aired the first episode
of Full Metal Alchemist but they just put
fart sounds into it
at like you know funny times
when like it was like ha ha ha
like during an awkward pause
like she farts like LeMalle
that was someone's job
at Turner Network
and it was great
I love it
I hope
I hope people
I hope networks do more things like that
what a
man that's like a
even exists anymore outside of Adult Swim
like a fucking network with like
editorial control
like that they can just like do stupid shit
and it's funny
that's what the internet's for now
that seems like such an outdated
thing that seems like so old school
like some dudes
running a magazine just like making a magazine
out of their garage or whatever
yeah TV doesn't exist anymore
I don't understand
do kids today watch TV
they watch TV in the sense they'll watch shows
on like a streaming service I guess
but I don't understand how network television
is still afloat
boomers
I guess all boomers are still watching TV
there's more boomers than there are kids
because as soon as you're like 19
you're a boomer now
they lowered the age of boomer first they lowered down to 30 year old boomer
now it's like anyone who isn't
you know people
people still listen to the radio
like the radio is not
like going away
radio has like a long easy reach
like it's really easy to broadcast
well it's not like super easy to broadcast things yourself
I mean actually it is pretty easy like I don't know if you know
like review bra like report of the week guy
he is like obsessed with like radio
he has like a radio show that he hosts and stuff
wait really no I
I did not know about that
that's very funny
he's an old fashioned kind of guy
he gave me a shout out on one of his shows once
really that's awesome
I knew I knew about his radio show but I didn't listen to it
yeah I only listen to it a couple times
but like it's just like interesting
like it's also weird that like a normal person
can have a radio show where you like play like copyrighted music
and stuff like I don't understand how the rules
about music on the radio work but there's like
some weird interesting shit going on over there
well you pay commission
like a little bit of money for each song you play
doesn't that sound like that
you can get like a license or something I really don't know the details
I don't want to speak and like say a bunch of bullshit
that's not true
like in the day they'd get like a check in the mail
of like here's how many times your song
was played on the radio in the entire world
this week and it's like well
billions and billions of dollars
now it's like your song was played
like 14 million times on Spotify
this week here's $20
yeah it's like nothing you get
streaming rights are like it's a whole fucked up situation
I'm not a musical artist so I don't even know
what is the pay
is actually pretty good
I think it's been getting better
someone posted how much money they make for each streaming service
and Napster was the most
what? how?
uh cause it's a paid service now
and some music artists
gets the most money from Napster than
any other streaming service
I can't remember who it was I did see that
yeah me neither
who the fuck like how is Napster still a thing
it was like a mainstream artist wasn't it
yeah
it wasn't like Drake or something was it
I guess it still exists but I can't go like
find a paid version of Kazaa and Limewire
uh
they couldn't cope with the changes
yeah what were you gonna say about review?
oh I was just gonna ask like what does
his radio show about
oh he just like talks about his life
and stuff it's not like
he's not like talking about like food on it
or anything like he's apart from like
I guess that is his job
my question
is like why
why do it on the radio?
why not stream it on like
why not do it a podcast where it would get way more views
that's just cause that's just how he likes
he just likes the radio like the technology
there's like it beams all across the
planets like people across in other countries
can hear it and he's like send they send back
people in other countries can see it on the internet
I don't
well a lot of he's talking about like
countries that don't have easy access to internet stuff
but yeah like I do know what you mean
I agree with you like it's very old fashioned
okay I mean
I'm genuinely curious like
does broadcasting via radio
give you like access to some
audience that like you could not reach
via the internet
yeah it does
I thought it was the opposite
unless it's like a global like network
or whatever like series or something
yeah I would think that if you were doing it radio
you would be like you would specifically
reaching like a local audience like
they would have to be like somewhat geographically
near he like buys
time slots with some fucking
company or something that broadcasted around
the world I really don't know the details so I don't
want to look into it yourself
not just you Ben and people I'm talking to but the
viewer or the listener listening to this right now
if you don't believe me look up I'm sure
you could find him talking about it on the
radio show because he's you know that's one of the things he's
interested in it's just an
interesting thing it's just an interesting that like
radio still exists
imagine being okay it's just such a
weird thing because like
if you're
review brah like the one thing you
don't have to worry about
is like how am I going to reach
my audience right
exactly like that's the one thing you'd be like
like that's settled like like your
method of like
reaching an audience is you got it
that's crazy that's crazy
I don't know
who's is to broadcast a radio show to I don't know
some like a few thousands
of people like people listen to the radio you know it's not
like some nobody listens to it but like yes
he literally has like millions of subs you could easily
have more people and get eyeballs on it
if you wanted I don't know some people just like
certain things I don't know
I sort of get I like some old technology I like
my old CRT TV
I'd be curious is it just
about like is it just
about like loving the technology
or is it about like
reaching like a different community like is like
the community of like the radio
listener like
his parents
I would have seen he simply does not care
who's listening
I think it's a combination of both those things like
he's happy to get the people who would you know
only listen to radio but he just he's doing it because
he likes radio like I really do think that is the main thing
like he just wants to do it that's his hobby
he just enjoys it
he like listens to other radio shows too
you know what I mean and like he's like
I mean most
most boomer for people just
you know if you're like a right-wing pundit
for instance you just do a podcast
but you just like pretend it's a radio
show like you just you have
you have the microphone and you set it up
the studio so it looks like
a Howard Stern like like like
broadcasting station or whatever you just you just
pretend you're on the radio and other what otherwise
do nothing differently
that's the easiest way to post your microphone
yeah that's the easiest way to do it
but I guess I think some
boomers authentic thing
that sort of ties in like boomers are
comforted by the fact that radio has like
barely changed like I remember listening to the annoying
shitty radio DJ
morning hosts when I was a kid and you can turn on the radio today
and it's the same exact annoying shitty banter
you know it's like exactly the same medium as it was
30 years ago and like longer back
than that I can have I guess
I can appreciate
I guess I can appreciate that
I wonder if I wonder if I'll be
the same with like
God I don't know
I was already having my insane boomer
moment about forums you know what I mean earlier
this podcast or someone listening
would be like what the fuck is these guys talking about
with forums these fucking crazy old boomers
what am I gonna what am I gonna have
my boomer moment about is it gonna be like
video game analysis
YouTube videos is that what I'm gonna be like
like oh they don't make up like they used to
come over here to me
come watch toki meki memorial
we've grown analysts we're just not gonna do it right
they don't put the cartoon avatar
in the bottom right corner anymore
how my arms aren't even crossed how do you know he's mad
how am I
they do they do they do do that actually
it's vtubers
the media hasn't been the same since rich got hairplugs
really rude on the show
I was um
I was thinking about vtubers
yeah vtubers is basically like
yeah it's it's kind of
the next step it is it is the next
logical evolution of like the little
the cartoon avatar in the corner
um I okay
I hate vtubers I hate them
um and the reason why I hate them
is because all right on the endless
war twitter account I
subscribe to like two vtubers because
they were slime themed vtubers
one of them was like a marshmallow
slime girl and the other was like a little slime
ball and I was like that's funny it
would be funny if I followed these slime vtubers
on the endless war account
so I did and now my feed
is nothing but vtubers they're all getting
recommended to me and I
I hate them I hate them so much
they are so cloying
and desperate and annoying they're all
just like oh other vtubers
what are you some relatable hashtag
relatable vtuber problems that we vtubers
have to deal with I'm looking for other
vtubers to please follow me and play
games with me and that's all it is
that's all I fucking see I hate them
just just just die alone
stop stop posting
let me just reiterate for listeners
Ben St hates vtubers because he
chose of his own free will to
follow vtubers that he didn't even watch
on his twitter account and now they're putting him on
fucking recommendations what the fuck no it's
not just the two it's not just the two
now I see like hundreds of them my whole feed
is full of all these other random vtubers
and like I don't want to see you I just thought
it was funny because these two guys were slime
I just wanted the slime but now
I have all this bullshit
and I just I just want to be pure
I just want to be free get it off my fucking
feed how dare these
fucking vtubers post about
collabing with each other on my timeline
I just don't want to see it I just hate
them fucking I just it's
it's just they're just all like oh it's like
haha we've got to be friends
you should use the other vtubers
to respond to all these being like would you just shut the fuck
up already please shut up I go
I go into all the compasses I'm like please stop
posting I don't know why I'm seeing
your post I don't want it on my timeline
please stop please leave me
alone I mean
Ben you could just block them
no
that's I know he can't do that then he wouldn't
be able to complain about it you them you turn off
retweets you guys are being uncharitable
to me I did not follow these people
these people because I followed these other
two these just all
just tons of others just just keep
appearing I think it's maybe
it's because those two like follow a bunch
of other ones and so I get like shown
them because I follow
your tweet wait do you not set your twitter to
only show like recent tweets
you're getting random recommendations I don't get that on twitter
I don't know
I didn't really fuck with the settings
I do everything I can to avoid getting
like random recommendations by the algorithm
I only want to see
tweets in chronological order yeah people I follow
and that's why I'm getting I'm getting recommend
it and it's all just like
and it's they all just
they all just want to they all just want to like
collab and like share one another's
audience there's and like play games with
each other and like build their they're all
like like a regular you super make
connection I know
they're just playing the cloud game they're playing
the cloud game like anyone else it's fine
I can't hold it against them just like
Lindsay Ellis I can't hold it against them
it's just annoying when I see it
Hey
do you ever think about how much money you could
make if you made like a failure vtuber and got
like a lady player I have
thought about it I don't know who I would get
to do it though I think I think about that
a lot with my characters and like fuck
I wish I had a girl voice
I do sort of just I was
for the record I was being uncharitable
on purpose to Ben and I want to say
I know some fair points
like there is some there is something very
like I there's already
a weird parasocial aspect to being a youtuber
okay but it feels like vtubers are like
aware of that and they're like leaning into it
on purpose yeah they feed off it
I don't I
I'm being I mean I'm being a little
you know like obviously I don't
have to read these posts but I don't know
so something about something about the
content creation plus
like an extra little visual thing
it not there are good ones
I've seen good ones I'm sure
the problem is that most of them are streamers
and that's just not content I'm interested in
yeah yeah yeah it's mostly streamers
and it's all
like it's all
it's all like the same like it's all the same product
but it's all
it's okay okay easier for me to
like see the appeal when it's like I'm only seeing
the highest quality vtuber moment and I'm only
seeing them animated by beautiful professional
like animation level you know what I mean like
like that's my only exposure to it because I'm not going out
there searching for
but I totally get we're coming there's just there's
just something a little a little weird to me about
like okay anyone who
can like you know it's like the barrier
to entry to be a vtuber is not that high
you can you don't
need like a hugely expensive
rig to have
what it takes to call yourself a vtuber and so it's just
it's just a little weird to see like so
many of them
all just kind of trying to do
I mean you know
there's there's there's there's not that much
it's weirdly corporate there's not that much
there's this weird thing about it it's not about being corporate
it's about the fact that like how like how different
can these be from
each other and yet they're all there's so many
of them right yeah everyone
just wants to be like it's not necessarily about
being corporate but everyone just wants to follow that model
and no one wants to like do really creative interesting
things like I mean you know I guess I can't blame
people for wanting to be a cute anime girl instead of like a
weird fucked up monster but I want to see more
weird vtuber there's just too many of them
to for me to be like okay
like like how many of them do they really
need to be how how many of them
do we really need you know it's I
yeah dude I
when member kizuna I she was like the only
one and everyone's like oh look at this new thing
and then you know there was like a new then there were a few
of them she was like the first one to mine
all I mean she wouldn't probably not the first ever
really blow up and then she just sort of fell off
because of some reasons I don't give a fuck
and then there was coronae coronae was coronae
the dog one and then there's like a couple others
that got really popular and now you're right now
there's a million of these fucking people and
like it's like impossible and like they're all there's
so many of them that have like a over a million subs and stuff
I have to say I am disappointed
in the NSFW like vtuber
scene because project melody
was also on there pretty early and got super
popular and she's got like this freedy model
and stuff and she does like porn streams
and I'm sitting here like
why are you not like
there are so many like
like fetish content
that you could be doing that because
you're like a cartoon character you could actually
do it like breast expansion
or whatever the fuck
and just no one fucking does it
it's like you're wasting
so much potential
like literally why bother
it's about the teas
she's got like the full
you have to deliver at some point
you have to deliver on the teas eventually
she's got like a full
body rig
like her rig is obviously
you know like not something
that your average schmuck
could afford to be doing
yeah it is a little
weird that like I don't know
I don't know there's something a little strange about
people trying to you know
foster this whole parasocial thing where you're like
but it's funny because it's like oh it's like nobody
thinks that they're really talking to a cute
anime girl like everyone's aware like everyone's
aware that like it's a shared
delusion right like
you know that there's a real human behind that screen
like that's the implicit understanding
because some people sort of lose track of that but like
that's my understanding right
it's like you can't like get mad at a guy
for simping over some vtuber
it's like his choice I guess I don't know
when you have
you know when the barrier to entry
is low to do a thing that
lots of people to do
this parasocial thing
and lots of people try to get in
on that action it's
it creates a
I don't know it just creates a vibe
of like
they're all just like
to the untrained eye
to a kind of checked out sort of
step back like looking at it from a distance
viewpoint it just looks like
the sea of like
identical creatures all just like
kind of like just yammering
yammering in the same
it's almost like they're inspired
by the anime industry
yeah
you looked at those seasonal charts
in the last few years
holy fuck
like when it was okay
on the one hand like I guess it's good
for things to be accessible
it's good for I like that the barrier
to entry to things is low
so I like that things don't have to be
corporate right because those ones that got popular
early on they were all owned by like
that one same corporation
I forget what it's called but like
you know hololive
like a bunch of those people are like
names and you know
maybe if the technology
is more accessible that's good
but I guess on the other hand
then it leads to this
this chatter this community chatter that is
so like so much
it's so much maybe we need
we need to keep more is what I'm saying
there's an underlying
air of like loneliness and desperation
of the entire vtuber fend
yes it's so bad
that's that might be what I'm picking up
on yeah
and I sort of get
what you're saying out with like the collaboration thing
like is like all these early generation
like corporate vtubers are popular
and they're all collabing with each other so it's just like
you know making even harder for newer people to get
a foothold you know they all have lore
and they all like exist in like a shared universe
and I mean yeah they have the same parent
company so they're all
you know they have these like
they're hooked up they're keyed in
it's funny they were
like so ready for this because it's just a new
version of idols you know what I mean I even have like
graduation ceremonies where they retire and shit
like it's literally just virtual idols at this point
like that's why they were so easily able to get
ready and capitalize on it Mary whether
he tweeted the other day that
like he never wants to graduate
and I didn't know what it meant
but then like in a tweet he clarified
it like in a reply he
clarified that it means
stop vtubing
and I was like oh
oh right right is that
from like an idol culture thing like when an idol
gets old enough they graduate because like it's
like you're too old now
it's literally just idol culture
I see I see you're too old now you're 20
you're 25 no one could ever
do they god 22
do they even make it 20%
because you can be an older
woman and be a vtuber and that's I think
it's a little slightly controversial for some
people because you know they get like docs and stuff of course
yeah cuz in Japan they don't want to fuck kids
apparently
I heard Corona was
actually like 35 or something
Corona based
yeah good for her
I legitimately think that's a good thing like the older
people can you know it's not just like
you know people don't graduate
because they're getting aged out necessarily
it's more just like you know you have to
keep your rare
they all just want
forever it would kill hype and they wouldn't
be able to pump the new ones as much I don't know
I'm not like a vtuber expert I'm really not
so I don't want to speak with authority like I really
know what's going on behind the scenes
that being the case I don't really understand
why they do graduate
because like what
if you're a popular vtuber
why would you stop doing it because
like why what
the only one I heard about
who got fired
or whatever is because they said something
like Taiwan is real or something
yeah uh someone
some big one retired
recently and it was like they're not
they're never gonna fire you they're gonna like
make you go through the whole song and dance of
graduating you know what I mean because
and you have to pretend that nothing bad is happening
they're totally not sending
you to the glue factory
it's so yeah it's such an ominous
thing or it's like it feels like a euphemism
like we're graduating it feels like they're getting
taken behind the shed and kills
the giver like
like oh yeah we're graduating them
like yeah we're putting them out
into the real world
are we yeah
we're sending them to a magical place
uh
creepy
um
I don't
I don't know how we got
how did I get here oh no
the brain fog my COVID brain
my COVID brain fog
conversations went
it was because
it was because you're talking about youtube
the cartoon avatars
right oh god
never went ages ago
the most popular vtuber in the world referenced
the cum zone I remember
wait really?
did she do it on purpose?
yes I was watching
her minecraft lets play because I was
I saw a clip from it and I'm like minecraft
I'm interested minecraft lets plays are usually good
like when they're first starting out
and it did I think her I watched
like the first like four vods four or five
vods before I got bored
um and yeah like uh she's like
oh I'm gonna put you in my chum in my
chum zone like wings at the camera
um and I'm like ha ha ha
I get it chum zone because she's a shark
that's funny
it's a joke
give her that it's an actual joke
and in recent
stream she has like a chum jar that has
like a miniature version of herself
ha ha ha ha
is she the most popular?
pretty sure she is
she's one of the ones that I see the most
for sure she's definitely up there
she's one of the most
English ones right
I think she is
I checked the subscriber counts of a few at the time
like a year ago and she was like shooting up
like past two million subscribers really fast
I recognize her so she's clearly
has some degree of
she's genuinely like
I think she genuinely has an extremely pleasant voice
to listen to it's very soothing
and I think she definitely has voice training
because she has very fine control over
her voice when she does little
funny sounds that go up and down in pitch
it's like very well controlled
her and Korone and maybe
Amelia Watson are like the three
that I probably have seen the most
Amelia Watson is like a distant third
um I watched
I watched some Amelia stuff too
I know the shark and I know
Pikami I know those two
Gargura is the shark
I don't know
I know Pikami because she has the funny face
I refuse to learn their names I only refer to the
the shark and the dog
I know one of them is a phoenix
that
I like this one's face
yes I know that one because she's like the tea kettle one
what
she makes tea kettle sounds
oh
her
she must not be a hololive
because she looks completely different
than all those people
yeah there are like independent ones
and I think there's like some people are talking about
forming their own little conglomerate
separate from hololive and stuff
and then hiring management to sort it out
for them oh no this one's really
cute look at that
look at that that's
precious
that's Pikami
okay well now
with the words
with the words leading VTuber podcast now
amazing
this whole segment was like
fucking hate VTubers
I fucking hate them now
oh this one's alright this one's not so bad
oh but she's so cute though
you know what it's because
I mean when you're a successful VTuber
you don't have to project that
like kind of desperate
air you have a desperate cloying
I feel bad because
I know it comes from a place of like
if you're trying to make it as a VTuber
you're in a really
tough spot and it must be really hard
and probably
basically statistically impossible
for you to ever claw your way up
to being popular from being
a nobody VTuber
so like I get it
but
I don't like but that doesn't mean I like it
yeah
well look at her go
why don't they all put cat ears on
and ruin their aesthetic
all the time this one doesn't
some of them do
okay well no wait no I just found a gift
of her doing it with cat ears on
people like cat ears of course there's everyone
to put on the cat ears at some point
it really paced me off when I saw the shark one with cat ears
it's like she's already a shark don't make her two things
here's a hot take
there's no such thing
as a anime girl with cat ears
that is good
the cat ears have never done anything
they're not good
they're not a good addition to a character design
ever never
that one in um
I don't like uh
what's that one anime
about the kid who fucks this
Aurora Borealis
oh Aurora
yeah it's like a
yeah ororaimu I don't like ororaimu
but that one cat
that girl with the cat ears is pretty good
isn't her name just
the thing about cat ears is like
do they have the regular human ears
below that do they have like four ears
it's just sort of like the
isn't it so cute to put cat ears
oh no it's not it does nothing
it does exactly nothing
it's completely neutral it just feels like
you're a fucking furry
I don't know
why there's such an infatuation with putting
cat ears on a person
I don't get it a real cat is cute
I think at a certain point they were supposed
at a certain point they were supposed to act
like a cat and like nuzzle up to you
and purr and ask for sex
real cats don't do that
that's why real cats are better
I guess I don't really
get why it's like the thing
I never like thought about it it's just like so
ingrained
cat boy is a cuter
you should like do it for more
the animals than just cats
and sometimes dogs you just have like turtle people
you have a turtle a shell
I'm a turtle girl
like it's a new idea
our entire like anime is based around
girls being different sorts of animals
I guess Japan loves
horse girl shows that have been a thing recently
where they have like horse ears
and all the animals are having big
horse dicks and I'm like yes this is good
more of that please
in America we have bunny girls
like the playboy mansion
yeah we invented
we invented that
as always we did it just like Disney
and Tezuka as always America did it
first and better
we invented furries
it's just something about like the
ubiquity of the cat ears as a
cute icon that I've just never agreed with
yeah I never I don't understand
like where did like they had to like come from
somewhere like the cat ears and just
spontaneously like they added
they added an armor attachment in Halo Infinite
which is the cat ears that you can put on any helmet
and it cost like
$15 to get them
it's insane and you better believe
tons of people are paying for that oh no yeah
I play the game and I see fucking like
20 people out of like 30
that I play matches with what the fucking stupid
cat ears thing and it's like you morons
you stumbags
genius move on their part making it 15 bucks
because they knew they could just milk that one
it's just triangle
it's true
it literally is just triangles
people be really loving basic shapes
get some squares in there
they love the kiki on top of the boba
oh I know that
I know that one
that reference
I suppose that's true
I'm stating only the truest facts
I'm getting hungry
it's muted
oh that's perfect I'm gonna make you hungry
I suggest you some food because my final topic
well actually it's the only topic
actually meant to bring on this episode
is I wanted to talk about some of the recipes
from cluster punk kitchens
especially the first one because it's actually
fucking delicious and one of the best things ever
I don't think anyone actually tried it
after I suggested it on the PCP
I can't remember it so yeah
please
it will rehash it for us
the recipe
it's two ingredients
and
Doritos
oh
and what you do is you put the English muffin
in the toaster you butter it up
and then you put like five or six Doritos in there
and you crunch it down and you eat it
and it's fucking delicious
and everyone's like oh it seems sort of okay
but I have made this for like seven different friends of mine
and every single time I hand it to them
they're a little skeptical if I take a bite
and then their eyes just light up
their life is changed take a bite change your life
and that's where it comes from is people
I made this
I invented this in like 2011
because I'm such a genius of just putting random shit together
and it is fucking tasty
it looks like a
McDuritos
fucking breakfast sandwich
and you know what it sounds like a meme item
if I just heard that in voicemail
because Doritos and Mountain Dew they're such like meme foods
but hey if you say it's good
I'll consider trying it out
if I ever see English muffins
I'll consider it
I'll post your pictures
but you're English
it's an American invention
they don't hold English muffins
we do have them
we have them in New Zealand too though
basically anyway you get crumpets
they'd be next to crumpets
they're always like sold next to the crumpets
like the worst crumpets that don't have the holes in them
they're basically like
the muffins at McDonald's
that's what they are
they're like really doughy bread
like all bread is doughy bread
but it's like
it's like doughier
not as fluffy it's more like
stodgy
more like stodgy bread
English muffins are fucking delicious
are they sweet or savory
the only time I eat them is when I have McDonald's breakfast
they're savory
I finish work at 6am
they're really good with butter
and Doritos
and you put them together and take a bite
change your life it's good
it's fucking delicious
everyone watching this try it at least once
you won't regret it
I promise
you're not allowed to hate it until you've tried it
I disagree I will hate it immediately
and forever
no
you gotta change my life
I've just been eating mozzarella cheese toasties recently
pancakes and I'm shit at that
that's another thing I failed at in my life
I don't
I can't cook
I can't do it
I get a canny soup
the thing about clusterpot kitchen recipes
takes zero skill
zero skill whatsoever
I think everyone was
macaroni and cheese with
honey barbecue fritos which I don't know if you can get them outside of America
but I just mixed the chips
into the mac and cheese and it was
pretty good it's not when you're as good as the Doritos
there are any recipes that aren't just like
make something and then put chips in it
um
I guess it depends on whether you like the chips
the third recipe was make spaghetti sauce
you know with like ground beef and stuff
but put saltine crackers in it
and use the sauce as a dip
so no every recipe is
just put chips in a thing
which is also pretty good
but the first Doritos was on the top of like
a chili con carne
which is good
what are we looking at here
we're talking about clusterpot kitchen
Ben
I said I was hungry and now Oblivion Fool
was torturing me
Ben you have to put Doritos in an English muffin
with butter it's so fucking good you have no idea
like
crumbled up or just
no just like 5 or
just like between 4 or 5
Doritos put them like in an English muffin
you can like crunch it down
I don't see why is that better
why is that better than just eating Doritos
it's a meal
it just tastes really fucking good
it's a feast
it's a meal
everyone I save is to Ben doesn't believe me
and then I make it for them I give it to him
they take a bite, their eyes light up, their life is changed
take a bite, change your life, it's real
so you butter the English muffin
what flavor Dorino
can you do any flavor
the nacho cheese works best
I've tried a few different flavors but the nacho cheese works best
or cheese supreme
I know what all those ingredients taste like
I'm imagining them together
and I don't know if they
do they really enhance each other that much
I don't know
they really do
I mean maybe you'll hate it
but I've given it to like 7 people
I'm sure I wouldn't hate it
okay I mean if you say so
hmm
well now I'm worried I'm hyping it up
I just really like it
it's like the best thing to have
it's the best way to eat both of those things
if I had all
if I had any, well I have butter
but if I had those three things
I would try it
but I don't
have you ever been at a low enough point in your life
that you've had paster and beans
that sounds like an English thing
paster and beans
paster and baked beans
all you got left
that's what you got to eat
I mean sometimes I just have
rice and beans
rice and beans is
filling and it's very easy
and I don't think that's too bad
rice doesn't fill me up
whenever I have rice I get hungry again
oh you're eating shit rice
you need to get that good rice
I don't know what it is
well rice
rice has the problem that most
carbohydrates have for me
which is that I can feel like I can just
eat an infinite amount of it and never
stop being hungry
so yeah I'm with you on that
um
paster and beans
like what kind of beans
baked beans like in tomato sauce
oh right
the English
tomatoes
because okay
if the beans are in tomato sauce
that sort of makes a little more sense
then like it's not like beans and molasses
like we would have here
that would be disgusting
yeah
more like that sounds gross
I don't think I've ever eaten molasses I don't even know what it is really
it's sugary stuff
I know it goes slow sometimes or something
isn't it sugary syrupy like super sticky
something or other
yeah the beans baked beans
but here they'd be in a can that have
it's sort of like a molassesy
sort of maybe caramel
not really caramel I don't know
it's like brown sugar it's like a thick
sort of brown sugary kind of
syrup
doesn't it go slow on a sundae or something
yeah it's very I mean pure molasses
is very thick
like it's like
it's thicker than
it's thicker than like peanut butter
basically it's like you can't even pour it
it's actually
I've tried I think
I tried like pure molasses
actually like gross
there's um
there's a scene in over the garden
is it over the garden wall
where they put molasses
they put molasses in their potatoes
and
and I'm convinced that that would be like vile
because like pure molasses is
like it is sweet but it's like
sickening like
sort of like powerful flavor
like you
you mix that shit
you don't just put a big dollop of it
on whatever you're eating
okay
yeah that's my molasses
rant
thanks for coming to
what's that about molasses
you would use it as like a baking ingredient
you could like bake it into like a bread
it's just sort of like a brown sugary
like dark
sweeteners
effects
anyway
the point is it would be terrible on pasta
just disgusting
okay I won't do that in the future
if I ever get a hold of it
instead of take a bite change your life
it should be
take a life
go to jail
that's it okay yeah
take a life get out of here
take a life
kill
a wife
kill people for no reason
take my wife please
take a life take my wife take it all
you take the good you take the bad
you take the rest and there you have
the facts of life
speaking of good and bad
should we move on to voicemails
we've been going for 4 hours and 10 minutes
oh my god
Ellie is our I'm so salty
maybe it's about time
we've gotten oh we've got
we've gotten two more voicemails
in the time
that we've been going so we should stop
because we don't we god we don't want any more voicemails
ugh I want to die
yeah
well you
well you've probably got covid so
maybe maybe you will so
don't worry about it
now
what a happy thought
you're welcome
okay
let me just scroll down here I will put
the voicemails in
the chat
first one is
okay the first one is like
it's an emo it's like an emoji
but like it's not displaying so I don't know
what it's called whatever
here's the voicemail
three two one go
what if your life is a computer
simulation and you are the only one
in it so everyone you know
is an NPC do you think
this is a real possibility
it's sort of like 12 year old question
is this
yes and no
wait wait wait
xkcd train car
that's so basic that's so basic
actually made me upset
I don't think it's a real possibility
it's a funny philosophical experiment
I just want to know
who is running this fucking private server
with one player on it when they're hosting an MMO
it doesn't make any fucking sense
this is a classic xkcd
oh yeah
this exact topic
what if you're the only real one
you are
we're just ghosts
okay go ahead
here's my answer even if you're the only real person
you should still be nice to the NPCs
because you know
just don't be a piece of shit
come on
being a solopsist
and having no friends
you really are the only one in the universe then
if I was in a simulation on my own
I would say like why would they put me in such
a boring scenario
whoever's overseeing this
sim
dungeon master sucks
I'm obsessed about these hypotheticals
they're like what if this thing
that even if it was true wouldn't really have any bearing
on your life
like who gives a fuck
unless I can break the simulation
what am I supposed to do about it
that's true
next
okay
here we go
next one is called
it's called over cooked vocalist
over cooked vocalist
three two one
go
I
don't get fired
resigned
boo
no
no no no
that's enough
thank you for the voicemail
I like that one
fuck you for the voicemail
okay next
it's more intellectually stimulating
for sure
that was nothing
you people are insane
this is really what happens when I quit voicemails
yes this is what I said
no more good voicemail
quality of voicemail
it's cratered
you were keeping the whole
market afloat
the capital that they pumped into the stock
to keep it afloat
and now we've lost it
covid is running ramp at the omega variant
I meant to say omicron
but sure yeah let's go with omega
it's fucked
this is what we gotta work with
next one is an image
next voicemail is a picture
okay
I was approached by an odd looking 30 something guy
that said fuck dude
how tall are you you're huge
I said five foot one with my boots on
he said want to join our yig movement
to stir up more shit
I took off my sunglasses
and glazed hard at him
and showed him my belt buckle
he screamed like a little girl
and ran off he knew an ass kicking beat down
was next for him
laughing crying emojis
where do you get one of those belt buckles
uh why is it blue
looks great though
I should make those
don't tread on me though
I'd buy one
this is the gadson flag
don't bend saint oh no
angels don't step on saint
angels sing
my coming
okay oh speaking of
the next one is called cummy ben
uh
here we go
there it is three two one go
please bring back gummy ben
keto gummies are the
best content you guys ever made
please ben I beg of you
I am sorry
but I can't
get the isomaltoligosaccharides
anymore
and it's the only thing that's good
I've tried other things that
everything else it's just not profitable at this point
to make them I mean
no I mean it was never not profitable
but you know it was never profitable it may saved money
for you in the sense that
it was a fit well I thought the whole point of making
gummies was you're like I don't want to pay these gummy
to sell me gummies I could make myself
it sort of was about that but then it became
more about the fact that they were just
good and I was just like I liked
that I could make them taste different ways
than I would normally be able to
get he was he was pulling a review
bra and just doing something for himself yeah
just like to gummies and
he fell in love with it because he couldn't get
his Chinese chemicals it's not that
it became too expensive that I
couldn't buy it it's that like just
like I can't
I think I've said this before but like I
can't find anyone who will sell it to me
in like a reasonable quantity
like I can only find people
that will sell me like a metric ton of it
then do it make a metric just buy
a metric ton of it it's like
I don't want to spend thousands of fucking dollars
it'll be like that episode
of the Simpsons where Homer has the pile of sugar
in his backyard
but it's isomaltic
saccharides for gummies but think about how much money
you'll save on gummies over the course of the next
20 years no it'll just get rained on
the rain will just wash it all away
just kill him
it kills for your precious
acids I'm sad
I'm sad that I can't just buy
like a normal amount of it anymore
but I have not been able to
find a new supplier and other
like substitutes that I've tried
allulose tastes like shit cornfiber
tastes like shit it all sucks
it's all bad IMO is the only
stuff that made any kind of decent
final product and
it's straight up
my source is gone a metric ton of
Igaluga mogulagasecharides would be a
good stretch goal for
a new Kickstarter if you ever did another
metric ton
yeah well
no I love the future
where Ben is just throwing in gummies with
every package it's the new stupid thing
that Ben needs but can't get it
honestly I would love
to make gummies
and give
those as backer rewards
or sell them to people or something
I would think that was really fun
dude you could
get a reputation as an art
comic convention type situation
you could be the gummy worm guy just hand out
gummy worms people would love you with a fire thing
everyone would be like oh check out the gummy guys stand
he makes a shitty slime comic but he gives out free gummies
yeah that's what I want everyone
to say about me
I wanted to get
a 3D mold I think
I talked to Smirig about this one time
and we never really went through with it
because I was still ironing out
the formula
but the idea at one point
was that I could maybe make
3D
printed gummy molds
of the various
fruits and vegetables that grow in
New Los Angeles city like dire apples
and
and phosphor poppies and stuff
custom gummies that's basic
custom New Los Angeles city gummies
that are like I could concoct
flavors for what each thing would taste
like and stuff
honestly I would
still do something like that I just
would need to get my fucking hands on
the other thing aside from not being able to get IMO
is that my kitchen now
is like shit
I used to have a slightly better kitchen
you know what that's not even that big
I could still do it I could just get
some new pots and pans and shit
and I could make it work if I wanted to
that's not really that big of a hurdle
stop getting this voicemailer's hope up if you're not going to return to the gummy arc
I'm saying
I wish I could return
I wish I could return to the gummy arc
honestly I kind of miss it
he likes gummies he just likes gummies
it's true
there's literally some PCP fan out there
who's just like god
Ben would make gummies again and talk about them
I would like nothing more
Ben talk about making roses and animal crossing again
that was
that was a mistake
that I should never
I should have never done that
at the end of the day there's just not that much
to say about it
listen it was like
it was like April of 2020
right we were all little
we were all a little weird
I
maybe it was
later than that but
no it was a time
some people transitioned
other people's made loads of roses and animal crossing
we
we all had to cope
some of us transitioned some of us made gummy worms
some of us made animal crossing roses
we all had our thing that got us through
it's true
next one
is called
uh
oh no it's actually called
it's actually called uh
okay three two one
go
Benjamin St you fucking grifter how dare you
release believe in the weeb
blue rays without my permission
you
mark
I was waiting for it
doid gazer is mad
I made doid gazer
you made
doid gazers
people should follow doid gazer on twitter
they're pretty funny
I like them
they have been they have responded to a few of my
blu ray posts
with some pretty quality
uh content
check them out check them out at doid gazer
doid gazers gets the angry
joe bad ass seal of approval in my opinion
is that a
that's a thing he does yeah that's what he gave
his favorite games yeah
it's what he gives every game
he gives like games like a score
and then sometimes a bad ass
seal of approval
damn
I would do anything
I angry joe am the bad ass
and I upload sleep on angry joe more
yeah okay I'm coming
around
uh
I watched that jar media
uh wait no did they
you angry joe on the jar
they have a series called
is this as good
as they say or as bad as they say
and they didn't have to know where they talk about
all of his content
I hate it
I hate everything
that's the one
I know whatever I don't care
I didn't even know he was in it
and I hate everything thing
until I had seen a few episodes
I hate everything is good actually
I don't I genuinely don't know
I don't watch it
I come on jar media I have not watched one of his main channel videos
in years
I only know him from being on a podcast with
YMS
that sucks
I haven't listened to it
I used to hate him because I hated his
weird angry cartoon avatar
but then I realized like it's easy
it has good branding
it's really ugly so it like you sticks out in
your memory like and I'm always saying
shit like why does everyone have to use a cute
cartoon avatar why can't everyone have weird ugly
looking avatars and there's one guy had that
and I'm like I fucking hate it it's ugly
yeah I saw the jar media
I think I probably started with the one about
the wall
and then I maybe saw one of their other ones about Doug
I watched their other one about Doug Walker
and then I think I was looking at their other ones
and I watched the one about angry Joe and I think that's the
video that's how I know most of what I know
about angry Joe I know from that
jar media video
which
those are good videos
those were pretty good videos
I like those boys
next
okay next one is called
the tale of the golden witch
and it's a vokeru
oh yeah I was going to ask
how it's longer than 130
yeah it's a vokeru
how do people even send those in
okay let's do it
3, 2, 1, go
hey there people
I'm the golden witch
the internet's favorite
rantin bitch
my videos are good
my channel is thriving
made some internet friends
and boy whereby been
here I am at the PCP
we're getting along
swimmingly
gonna hire this guy
who's fat and wears flannel
then burn all my bridges
oh god I am
the American dream
this is a truly
ingenious game
I've got a billion IQ
perhaps
gonna get rich and famous
of my shitty raps
then saint is
a piece of shit
he always ratios me
when I tweet
he makes me so mad
he farts cause he actually
makes some worthwhile art
and gib just makes me
squee
and fill up full
with jealousy
when I see her it makes me
wanna flee
cause she looks so much more
cuter than me
oh god I am
the American dream
I haven't lost any steam
now let's try the
best
and be homeless
so I went down and bought me
an RV
that was a lie
there is no RV
in with my folks
they don't know
that I am a massive joke
then as a final like
ability cleanse
I tried to trash
it blew up in my face
as everything does
now I'm seething with rage
but pretends to love
oh god I am the American dream
fool the PCP
really makes me scream
and I'll do anything
to get some yen
I'll lay away night screaming
fuck you Ben
oh god oh god I'm so fantastic
thanks to Ben
my brain's gone spastic
and my name is golden witch
watch me now I'll live in a dish
and my name is
golden witch
watch me now I have
purchased goods
and my name is golden witch
watch me now I'm gonna be rich
that was great
I still don't understand how
you only two types of voicemails
you have are terrible
and crazy
there's no in between
no one just
no one just like asks a normal
thought provoking question or anything
it's just like
they have to scream and like shit into
a microphone
I believe you that was you right
no I'm very proud
I don't sing
I rap badly
that was amazing
that's made my name
do we have any idea who that was by
well it's by the same guy
who is sending voicemails
under the name drydumpdecember
at dustydumps.com
he's been sending
that's all I know
just full credit to that person
cause that was incredible
I think maybe
Dusty Dumps is going in the voice
grail for that one
are we feeling it?
I'm feeling it
I'm thinking Dusty Dumps
buddy
congratulations
you made it
thanks for that voicemail
great stuff
next one is called
do you guys like Frank Zappa?
I like Frank Zappa
next one is called
British man is upset
3, 2, 1
go
hello PCP
now couple of episodes you go
you said you would put
Kringus Bingus in the voice
grail we did
now that sounded great to me
but I checked the google documents
and not a single trace
of Kringus Bingus' name
is on that thing
so this
makes me think
you
had something better to do
you were busy with stuff
I mean that is just unimaginable
so put
Kringus Bingus on the dock
right now
or I'll be cancelling my
subscription
to this show
not vaguely British man
we can't lose his paper
at Cluster Punk Kitchen while you're at it
you still haven't done it
still never got added despite the promise
was there a promise?
listen I promise a lot of things
when Keto Delito happened
everyone was
crying, everyone was screaming and laughing
and yelling voice grail
voice grail, voice grail
and then I checked the document and it never got updated
you know what that sounds true
I believe it
I'm in
voice grail
here we go
Kringus
Bingus
he's in
Dusty Dumps
Dusty Dumps is in
and
Cluster Punk Kitchen
of course Cluster Punk Kitchen deserves it
now Rip
posthumously
yeah
it'll go on the wall memorial
there we go
the document is updated
we can
we can finally rest
rest easy heroes
yeah
next one is called
Ejaculation Station
there it is
3, 2, 1, go
hey guys forgot to say this last time
just wanted to say that coming without ejaculating
is fine you know if you take estrogen
you can come without actually any semen
coming out but it doesn't hurt or anything
feels fine it's perfectly good it's fine
what?
oh high spork
guys we thinking voice grail
on that one
wait I have to
say something or spork is going to kill me
yeah
I promised I would mention this the last two times
I was on the PCP
I met spork IRL
they drove up to my place
I
wouldn't have a plan on what we were going to do
or hang out
they just kidnapped me they threw me in their car
and drove around the block once asked me where to pee
and I pointed them at a big lots
and then they dropped me off back at home
when I showed them road to rad con
and then they left
cool story
oh you guys like
you guys like live in like
you guys are both in the same state right?
like you just live near each other?
yeah we're like free hours
away I think
yeah spork just came by
we met
I spoke to her very briefly
we were like in the same area for like 20 minutes
and then she fucked off
she was just stopping by
as a pit stop on the way to somewhere else
hmmm
fascinating
neat
well I don't know
the only time I
come without ejaculating
is if I've jerked off so many times
that like I just can't come anymore
but I just keep going
so
but I don't think that kind of feels like
what it
we're ejaculating about coming
because that's happened to me
I don't get it
isn't that called pissing?
yes
yeah it felt like pissing
you know pissing is a very important topic today
I feel
in our modern era
oh okay
shall we go to
the next one which is called
X4
there it is
floating
damn
3, 2, 1, go
he is coming
indeed
still coming
without ejaculating
he just got held up in traffic a little
okay I'm glad to know
I'm glad to know yeah it's good
it's comforting
wouldn't want anything
to fuck it up
for him
okay next one is another
image
okay
here we go
I feel like this is an old meme
there's definitely been versions of this
okay the soy bensaint
has a year long beef with washed up youtubers
works on game that few will play
buy my comics please
spends his A.R.'s ring of people on twitter
covid makes his brain shrink
those boobs are too big
that's not true
that's the opposite of what I said
I'm saying that
big boobs need
more representation
the ones I'm seeing are not doing it
this guy fundamentally
misunderstands the character of bensaint
what about the last one
on your side though
that was it
spends his days arguing with people on twitter
do you want to read that one
okay I tried
I said that
yeah whatever
these are all true
yeah my brain did shrink due to covid
but it's just more efficient now
the chad nate bestman
makes you fail no nate november
with chad content
abandons his friends that don't generate him enough profit
only networks with people
larger than him
weird utilitarianism pilled
visits family even with covid
lives down on people less
successful than him
I think this person just hates both of us
yeah
I get to look down on nate
subscriber number
sub count
yeah
true
kill him
I can't believe someone with more subscribers
than nate bestman is on the procrastinators podcast
that's unthinkable to me
oh my god I kind of forgot
cyber shell is just
just one of the bullets
but you only have
guests more popular than you
you fucking scumbag
you
yeah but not on youtube
cyber shell is like two nates in a trench coat
with his subscriber count
that's true
but you know
my subscribers are sonic fans
so do they really count as like a mole
true
according to god
a sonic fan is only half a human being
if that
I was hoping we could get to three quarters
but I guess
three fifths
compromise
that was the real agreement
they agreed
when noah's arc in the rainbow
fans will be three fifths
and that's just been the law
ever since
of course
next voicemail is called
where is it here we go
more ways to humiliate tricksy
ideas for ben
oh my god
two seconds
okay three two one go
kill her
that would be hilarious
that would be a humiliation
that would just be like
ultimate break
that's like the business simpsons were homeless
thinking of revenge for net flanders
and it's like the leftorium closes
then it goes further and flanders is dead
and he's like no too far
yeah too far
it wouldn't be funny then
yeah yeah yeah
I think
it might be a little funny
alright next voicemail
is from
okay it's an image it's from big booby
ben at baba.buy
I like the sound of that
it's better be good
oh damn
those were good size
no objectification
without representation
not loot
this is great
no this
that is good squish
it is
I'm very
excited about how I came across
the huge forehead
my huge forehead
I appreciate it
I appreciate that you made me a girl
but you didn't just like take the easy way out
and give me like a cute
a cute girl hair
I'm a freak
I'm a big egg-headed freak
as a girl same as
same as it ever was
also I spy
I spy that soft tum
good detail
I see it
I don't like it it's making me
it's making me self-conscious I gotta get back on my diet
I gotta get back
when you have big boobs
you need a soft tummy to like
for them to rest on
I haven't been able to lift
in like two weeks because of COVID
because your boobs are in the way
my huge
image is too accurate to reality
more than you realize audience
it's upsetting
sad but true
next one
is that blue pills
oh
you weren't on
this episode we talked about
eating blue pills
and having huge tits
I thought this was about
when like
we were talking about
what's their face from that video game
we talked about the cover art
and booby representation
that was like the one before
it is a
continuation of that
the blue pills are
uh
related I don't know
I require people to draw
me with huge tits as well
just saying that
I'm just demanding that
yes whoever drew this draw a gib next please
next voicemail
Trixie will never recover
is not an RPG maker
expert
there it is
okay
3, 2, 1, go
hey
so I heard you guys talking about that RPG maker
I haven't really dabbled in it
much myself but from my understanding
if you want something done in RPG maker
then chances are someone has already made a plugin
for it like for example
simply having 8-way run is still
somehow not a standard feature
and it's absolutely the first thing you're
going to want to look for to implement
your game so many people
have managed to reverse engineer plugins
that work for RPG maker and a quick search
to hopefully find you one that works
and then of course it's just a matter
of debugging and testing to make sure
that you know it works
just for reference's sake
Life 2D has been a real game
changer for the hentai game scene
that should even work for the old
RPG maker not even VXA's
which is the new one just look up
any games made by Happy Pink I swear
they operate on black magic or something
as an alternative
you can try Wolf RPG editor
it's basically the same thing from my understanding
you know look up a bunch of plugins
they're probably already made
there's a Toho fan game called Genius of Sapphire
which is made with a heavily
edited wolf editor I think
it's probably one of my favorite RPGs
in general very heavily
inspired by the saga series
so yeah
indie RPGs have been
easier to make than ever before
crap out there but at the same time
there's some releases that put swear to shame
so yeah that's great
and all I'm not
interested in plugins
and shit
that's not real
I might be
maybe okay
could be some very good useful information
for someone watching
I learned a lot this past year
working on Phantom's Revenge
because I actually had to
code it with GML
I think if I
I don't know I can't even imagine
like a universe where
instead of that I like
found plugins and like
drop them into my game and like
modify it and like it's like oh does this plugin
work does this plugin
conflict with a lot of plugins
this sounds so stupid
I don't know
dumb
oh my god but I just reversed
image searched that
big booby ban image
see if maybe it's been posted
so I could find the artist
and all it says is did you mean objectification
yes
sorry related content
I did
just
okay
just don't be an idiot
just fuck around
with your coding language of choice
and just figure out how to do 8
just figure out how to do 8 way run yourself
just like don't be stupid
just fucking be like how do I do it
and think about it for a second
and then do it
duh
I don't think there's anything inherently wrong
if you just don't care about that shit
and you just want to like make a game
especially if it's just a fucking hentai game
then go ahead and use rpg maker plugins
but I agree with you in theory it's better
especially if you really want to make a game
just to know
actually make it yourself
if something goes wrong and you don't know
how it works you can't fix it
right
you don't want to be relying on plugins
you have no idea how they work
a hentai game
is a hentai game even a game
like if there's a loose state
I don't want to have is this a game
discourse on this fucking podcast
but like you're talking about like a visual novel
right
there's no if you have choices
it's a game
okay that's not what I mean but like
there's no
there's no like coding right there's no like
game design
involve
there's a lot of if this then that
so it's a fucking game
and it's easy to do
you fucking idiots I'm not
damn it I'm not trying to do a semantic like
that's not a real game yes I get it is technically
a game but like whatever
that's not like a game design
thing that's not something you have to
sit down and be like how am I gonna
how am I gonna achieve this like no
it's just like yeah obviously you can use plugins
absolutely can be
obviously you can use plugins for that because like
you don't need it to do anything
right
I don't agree
like I've
spoken to for eyes a lot about
like potential like hentai game
ideas and a lot of them like would involve
like actual game mechanics that revolve
around sex in interesting
ways
better not it's not just oh there's a
you lose and then you get fucked and it's just imagining
the most basic visual
awful possible and yeah to do that kind of shit
yeah you don't need plugins or anything but like
making basic visual novels yeah obviously
but like you can like make RPGs
and or things we have like sex
stats and I don't know
I
I'm not sorry enough to think of it but I
it's not easier to build that kind of game around an RPG
maker type framework than it is to like
code a visual novel from the ground up
okay sure I
guess I'm just like
all right it depends what kind of project it is
like for yeah for some
projects I'm sure that like just
putting just putting together plugins
to achieve a desired
prefab format
is like fine sure
okay
I
recognize a lot of the fucking plugins from
like Lisa the Painful like there's one
where like you go in a room and the light
like like shines around you and it's like
really weird because it's like the only room in the game like that
I was like oh I remember seeing that plugin when I was
fucking around with RPG maker
yeah
oh no don't tell me that a game
that I like use plugins that makes me
Lisa is an RPG maker game
and it uses plugins I promise you
in fact he lists plugins into credits
using plugins it's just a tool
he didn't personally hand code every single thing in that game
even before
I knew about the game when I saw screenshots
I could tell was made an RPG maker
I know it was made an RPG maker
I used it so much
I know it was made an RPG maker but like
okay fine I'm just okay
you know what here's what I think it would be
well if you knew how to
code he wouldn't make it an RPG maker
it would be a better game if he had
hand coded that light
effect
why?
no I'm joking
I basically agree with Ben's
advice that you should code
you shouldn't rely on plugins like he's basically right
I just want to say
it depends on the type of game
I'm being salty
obviously
I guess obviously for something like that
it doesn't matter
I'm just thinking about it
in terms of the game that I've been making
and I literally can't imagine
finding it useful
because I
understand my
I understand my game
like inside and out I know how
all the pieces of it work
and to like just take a big like
black box of code and drop it
in there and be like I hope it does
what I want it to do is unthinkable
it's sort of the equivalent of using
things that some people would consider
crutches in like drawing
like a stabilizer or whatever
it's just a tool that you can use or not
and it's fine
it doesn't make anything good or bad
it just depends on what the final product is
at the end of the day
I'm not arguing from like a
moral standpoint
I'm saying I don't think I could use it
to do anything
when an alternate timeline Ben who loves plugins
would have had phantoms revenge out like six months ago
I
I listen I want it I would
have taken shortcuts if I thought
it would achieve the
effect that I was looking for
but I don't think it would have
so
nobody else should use them either there
that's what I think
a little mouth
I need to use plugins for like After Effects
I don't I try to do everything from scratch using
the built-in things and it's slow
and painful making a game
game maker first of all
why don't you program it from the ground up Ben
like a real adult
game maker
why didn't I
why didn't I write it in notepad
why didn't I code my game in fucking notepad
why didn't you code it in an assembly
why didn't you code it out of raw binary
what do you mold it out of clay you weirdo
I don't know
I'm sorry
that's all I can contribute
I don't know anything about game development
yeah I don't even know anything about game development
so I can't even really have any insight into this
did you farm that silicone yourself for that chip
that's in your computer
did I mind this video
why not cobalt
did you ever see the video about the guy
who like made a sandwich himself like he
did everything like he grew the bread
yeah it was that episode of Spongebob
where Spongebob fight
he does the battle against neptune
and neptune like grows the wheat
he like divinely
makes the wheat grow and then he like
transmutes it into buns
some guy like did that
with like an actual sandwich like he raised the chicken
like he did everything himself
didn't he even like get the water from the ocean
and purify it I forget the exact details
but I wouldn't be surprised if he did something insane like that
and the point is like he did all that it probably cost like a thousand
dollars to do everything put together
and then he like ate the sandwich and he was like
that was okay
fine
and the conclusion this is why capitalism is good
because if you don't have it thousand dollars sandwiches
I mean yeah
markets are
effective
scale is what is the good thing
yeah that's true
scale does not belong to capitalism
it belongs to everyone
division of labor and all that
it's good
next voicemail
sorry I've lost track
here we go this one is called
let's just start from the top of voicemails again
yeah let's try again
cut out everything so far
huh
what
welcome to the procrastinators podcast
next voicemail is called
hypocrite is a leftist
sad 3 2 1 go
looks like we got another gem
from slow
biden first he wants to drink
water then he wants to take a piss
these leftist
hypocrites when will they
stop
I
I like it yeah I agree
wow
I like who he said
take a piss
you're welcome
did you I saw great
saw great twitter
posts from
libs of tiktok you know libs of tiktok
oh my god
sounds delightful
see see do you know what I'm gonna say
yes yes
I don't know
they put
the point of the account is to post
liberals taking
L's basically on tiktok
this post was
it was that girl
who makes like seven figures a year
pretending to be a dog
I don't
I am aware of this
she's like a fat
she's like a fetish
she's like a fetish actress
but I don't think I don't even know if she even
like gets nude but like she pretends
to be a dog right she just has a leash
and she acts like a dog
and people pay her an exorbitant amount of money
for this
and the libs of tiktok just posted this like
a gas
it's just like what the fuck am I seeing
and it's like
a video of this girl like
pretending to be a dog
and like barking at another girl who like barks back
and it's like
bro
these are not libs
these are porn fetish actors
and you are watching pornography
what the fuck did I just watch
fetish pornography
is what it was
um
the libs have really gone too far this time
the libs have gone too far that accounts great
because it will just post like pictures
of like people like committing crimes
and be like lol liberals
just like
there was one of like a bunch of people like smashing
a bunch of windows and like looting a store
and it's just like
like crime is just by default
liberal
be gay do crimes
you know these were liberals because they
broke into a store
you know they voted for Biden
like they loved Kamala
because she
that's why else would they be
stealing you know
I have a pee and drink water
I don't think anyone likes Kamala
who isn't like mmmmmm
are you joking
Kamala was the first woman to hold presidential power
while
Biden was unconscious and sedated
for a routine
colonoscopy and that makes her
a girl boss
that literally sounds like an episode of like veep or something
like that doesn't even sound like it should be
uh it is all
too real
okay next one is called
new epic voicemail
storyline the space epic
at pew pew dot com
uh oh boy here we go
uh there it is
alright three oh god it's a minute
three two one go
okay PCP
this is my new voicemail storyline
uh get ready for this to last
uh 18 voicemails
okay let's go yeah
um hey
here I am
driving around my spaceship yeah I'm in
space uh and it's fucking
sweet I'm driving around yeah okay
oh oh fuck oh pew pew pew
oh fuck I'm getting shot by space pirates
holy shit can you
pew pew pew oh my hole
it's a big hole uh
somebody's uh
entering through the hole oh my god who
is it uh hello there
I'm I'm new
iconic character
oh my god it's
it's a character that's going to
be a PCP staple for years
yes that's right
I'm um
Mr. Funny Man oh my god
Mr. Funny Man I uh
that is so cool that you came into my spaceship
are you gonna rob me he's getting his accents mixed up
no um we have to
try to find a way to get along
in this uh lonely space
just like in lonely space
oh geez man oh god
I don't know how this is gonna turn out
oh geez look
forward to the the following
episodes because this is
gonna get crazy guys
yeah I can't wait for a second
to do it
I was getting some too
boldly flea vibes when he was in the spaceship
that was my favorite part
I liked uh
when Mr. Funny Man made me
laugh
he was an iconic character
he lives up to his name
you can't beat an iconic character introduction that's like
look at me I'm an iconic character
you love me
it's like there's like subliminal
marketing at every time that's like
super liminal you love me
I'm great I'm iconic
oh my god it's true
yeah yeah yeah
there was a brief moment where I was like oh it's not funny
when you said Mr. Funny Man
but now thinking back on it I'm laughing inside
I kind of like it
in retrospect it was a good joke
nobody laughs but in retrospect
it was funny I can't wait to see what Mr. Funny Man
does next
I was chuckling
I can't wait to find out
uh alright
well uh it's gonna be hard
on top
that one obviously
but the next one is called
PCP
Presents
wait hold on
where did I uh
sorry
I thought I downloaded this
no I fucked it up oh god I fucked it all up
I thought I downloaded the voicemail
but I didn't download the voicemail
that's okay
it's downloading
how's everyone doing
I'm dying I'm good
nobody say anything let it be awkward for Ben
no it's too late I got it
I got the voicemail uh
bam it's called
Ben no PCP presents
the wall Ben life
dab
okay uh three two one
go
gonna grow up there
on my face
shall I ship more
on Beatrice
shall I get
into fights on
twitter.com
pay for the years
to engage in a scum
making games
good days learning sweet
new rates
turning cards great art
delivers it starts
I'm face lectures base
try dumping the waste
getting flanged as fuck
ain't love old stuff
yeah
there's no respect at all
on the PC
Ben saint?
more like base saint?
am I right?
wow
wowie
hope we don't get a copyright
slap
it was an elaborate long call
to get the video like strike
oh that's a bit we might actually
we might okay
oh is there a pitch it down two semitones
that actually
did happen remember with the Tom porn
yeah it did
it does occasionally
but it was funny
but I liked it though
I didn't realize you weren't allowed to
link to explicit things in the description
oh yeah
I liked the part where it was about me
same
I liked the part where it said
the shitting on Beatrice
that made me happy
yeah that is a thing
taking a dry dump on Beatrice
is that what I said?
oh yeah
that's what I said
it said dry dump
I remember it said dry dumps
I'm just combining the two ideas
you're just taking
that's called the juxtaposition
and that's the root of all
you're just seething descent
you're just seething
descent
you're just coping
descent right now
okay
next voicemail
is called
mystical hobo
three two one
go
I'm the mystical hobo
of Hoboken
and my question is this
have either of you
or any guests involved
tried meditation
and if not would you
what do you think about meditation
never do you think it's
fucking cringe
and bullshit
I think it's a valid way to soothe
anxiety in this modern age
let me know
I only
engage in negative meditation
which is like regular meditation
but I do it to get angry and pissed off about things
I never tried to meditate to calm down
that seems impossible
I feel like the boundaries
and the rules of meditate
I feel like it works for people who
I don't know
don't need specific instructions
but when people say just
feel the air around you
I'm like okay I feel it
I don't know whether I'm doing anything
right I don't feel it
I don't feel anything I can't do it
it doesn't work it doesn't make sense
these instructions are terrible
I can't get into it no teacher
has ever explained meditation
properly
I'll explain
what it is and what about it works
taking slow deep breaths
that's it
that's the part that has an effect
I don't know
I think there's a little more to it
than that
there's probably a little more to it
but that alone will calm you down
a certain calm
times, spaces
and locations usually
will calm me down
if it's like a nice sunset and there's a cool breeze
and I'm not bothered by anything
and I'm just sitting around
then yeah of course I'll feel calmer
but like I don't know how to
like
create that
when I don't have it
I think
that part of meditation
sometimes is about
imagining
yourself from the outside
like when you're angry
like thinking about
like part of it can be like
thinking about it from the outside
like from an observer
observing your own anger
and thinking about like
why are you angry
and becoming an outside
observer to yourself
and that is a great thing
to be able to do
and if you can do it it's very helpful
in a lot of situations
I feel like I do that all the time though
and that just makes me more upset
because I sort of
there's something different from what you're saying
but like I think to myself
like why am I angry, why am I so stupid
why am I like, why is my life so bad
um
maybe I'm like emotionally compromised
and I can't actually answer those questions properly
but I just end up like berating myself
like there's another version of me
just saying wow give you suck
and here's all of the proof
and I have the receipts and it makes sense
and I'm logically explaining
why you suck so hard
of course
I tried medification
a few times but I could never get like the fighting game
input down and pull off the move
and I kept dropping the combo and failing it
didn't work
I lay on the floor once for like 20 minutes
or maybe 30 minutes once in 2012
and I just lay on the wood floor
and just felt the floor and didn't think about anything
and it was calming
as I have mentioned before
I can only do the, no sorry
no go ahead
I was just gonna say I could only do that when I'm high
as I have mentioned before
um
when I used to do kendo
at the beginning of kendo practice
and at the end we would meditate
for like a few minutes
and the way that
the teacher would have us do that
is we would um
he described it as just sit there
and just deliberately
don't think about anything
and if you have a thought
imagine yourself like
like your mind is like the surface
of like still water
and if any thought disturbs the surface
imagine yourself like
taking the thought and throwing it away
like pluck it out and throw it away
and just like try to sit there
with the least disturbed mind
like no ripples
see I've tried
I've tried to do that before
like I've heard all these things and it's like
I just
I feel like
the metaphors they're using
to describe what you're supposed to do
I interpret them wrong and then I do something wrong
or I don't feel confident enough
that what I'm doing is the right thing
I've never really felt
like
like when I
deliberately tried to do a meditate
I can't do it
I felt calm before
but like I don't know how
the things people say to explain it
don't make any sense to me and I can't make sense of them
I get the feeling meditation is almost
one of those psychosomatic things where like
if you believe it it'll
have a perceived effect for you like almost like
a placebo kind of thing
that's probably a really mean way of talking about it
but to me that's the impression we've got
because I was doubtful of it and tried it
I fully believe that's what it is
it's that combined with the fact that you're probably
like breathing slower
and calm which does actually calm you down
whenever I'm agitated
I just take a deep breath
and that like helps
it's like a bit of that
it's not just about
being calm
it's not merely about
becoming calmer
from a state of upset
it's about like
I don't know I think if you do it right
it changes your
perspective a little bit and it gets you
it gets you into a
sort of a mood or a mindset
that is just more
focused and better
unless stupid
my form of
meditation is playing the first 200 turns
of a Civilization 6 game
and then going sleep
I mean
good breathing exercises
are also good for focus
I feel like if there's anything
oxygen flow to your brain
I think the only thing that's
like been consistently
a good thing to calm me down or focus
like if I'm having like
an anxiety moment
is to go outside only if it's like
really cold it works
and I just lay on like the earth
I lay on the ground on the stone
and I just become
really cold
I don't know why that helps
and then I come in and I'm shivering
but it's like now I can warm up
and now my brain is not
like I don't know foggy
I need one of those ice waterfalls
to sit under
one of them good old ice waterfalls
get that installed in the back garden
you need a
Joe Rogan freezing cold
flotation thing
is that like a sunbed
no what are those things
called where you lay inside of a thing
a sensory deprivation chamber
but like a cold
I'm sure you could make
I like the cool air
it's definitely something I appreciate
well that's the last voicemail
I thought we were going to go
for another 58,000 years
and I would die in collapse
no there weren't that many
but we are past the eight hour mark
so eight hours
no we really uh
sorry five hours
I meant five
well you heard him we have to go for another
three hours we were at five
hours and eight minutes on my
audacity and I fucked it up
I fucked it
you imagine ever putting out an eight hour episode
I have done that
well not a pcp but like
arm retrieval I think the last episode
was like almost eight hours
was it
god
dang
went all the way through the night and it was the sun was coming up
holy moly
by the time we had finished
that's a real ass
podcast
none of that is five hour bullshit
since we are since I imagine we're coming
since I imagine we're coming up on the end
I will take this opportunity to say
by plebe and the wee blue rays
link in the description
to check my tweet
where I explain how to do it
send me
$35
to paypal
at IASUcomic
at gmail.com
or 45
if you're foreign and not in America
because postage costs more
and that's it that's how you get it
get blue rays I have 50 left
and I would like to have zero
what a deal
what a deal it is a deal
it's not that bad
it's pretty
you can't afford not to
you literally can't afford not to
I can't afford you not to
please
but you the viewer could technically afford not to do it
no no that's not
what I that's not the right message
shhh cyber show shut the fuck up
okay
just reminding you
I just want to say if you're
if you're listening the PCP in 2022
but you're like
you got cash
I'm not a real PCP yeah I'm not going to buy
plebe and the weeb like who the fuck are you
honestly you're so right
you're so right like imagine
you'd be like you're listening to this stupid podcast
you're one of the like
10% of people
who are still here after all this shit
you're still like six years later
and you're like I remember
the plebe and the weeb red con too
but
am I interested in owning
an exclusive one of the kind
piece of that history
I'm ambivalent
like what's wrong with you
Ben now that you've said that
you need to check what this episode gets
in the first week in terms of views
and make a print exactly that
I think you're right
I think I
honestly I would expect someone
that's still invested after all this time
yeah I would expect the viewership to 100%
be like I'll pay anything
you viewers do you even understand
when you own this Blu-ray
you can just like hold it in your hand
just you owning that would make Trixie mad
like just existing
honestly
you got to do it like that live streamer
low tier god and say like I'm not even going to start
the stream or the podcast until you guys pay me
enough money to talk to you
the fact that they are all coordinated
like deliberately not
saying anything about it makes it really obvious
that like yes they are definitely
pissed off about it and it would upset
them a lot if
the more they got sold
you really would have expected some kind
of comment right at least be like
oh this is bad Ben shouldn't have done this
because you know he's profiting off my work
or something like I would expect
something like that
at least a diss track
I think I do expect something
but I think it'll probably get
maybe commented on and like avoid gazers
or something I think they will
I don't know
yeah they're doing that
they're doing a Q&A at some point aren't they
they'll probably mention at the end of that
I just find it impossible to imagine that she's not annoyed
like there's no way that she's just like
that's fine I don't care that Ben's doing that
you know what I mean
I know that she is because I know
that Riley would respond
to the tweets that I've made at him
because it's more engagement than he usually gets on twitter
there's no way he doesn't see them
the only reason he wouldn't engage with them
is if Trixie was like don't engage with them
please
like I just want to ignore it until it goes away
like she's told him not to
that's the only explanation
also they've been deleting comments about it
on their
on their channel so
that's amazing
I've seen a few comments that have
that have disappeared
the rise and fall
ah oh shit my headphones fell out
okay anyway
I just wanted to remind everyone
to please give me money
can I also
ask for money
I will ask to
you the viewer should
if you're not going to donate to Ben's saint
for whatever reason you should consider giving money to laserbot
because he could really use it
yeah I just
did you know Trixie is making like three times as much
as Tails gets trolled is
that sounds
that sounds about right
bad timeline
yeah
laserbot's making three times as much quality content
I know
we're getting money from
infinity
it's actually
I spit the inside of my mouth and I'm in pain
but I'm gonna sold drawn
good work
we actually need more money than usual
because we have to pay all the artists too
yeah I mean
we have to divide it amongst ourselves
well I'm not taking any but
that latest page
I forget what you said the artist's name was
like that person definitely deserves to be
paid for that
yeah
yeah I paid them
there's been some really good guest art
so yeah obviously
it's easier to pay good artists
than just to beg them to do free good art for you
yeah
that's the whole reason the Patreon exists
I would encourage people
to support
the ongoing
like you said earlier
Cybershell like
like wow
tails gets trolled is actually putting out regular
pages like that's kind of
crazy
it is honestly
it was over
it was dead
luckily CC
had to help revive it
with the help of laserbot
and Embergram and a bunch of other people
but CC did a lot
well actually
I guess this is a big deal to people
but laserbot actually came back
oh yeah I forgot
he probably even announced that on the podcast
yeah cause he like left the project but now he's back on the project
and you know he'll do pages
I didn't know that
I almost was going to be like
when you first announced he left I was almost going to be like
you know you could just not announce it
because maybe he'll come back someday
but I didn't want to
you should be transparent you should be honest
people would want to know why is
the art not his
but part of me was hoping maybe he'll come back
but I didn't want to jinx it and be like
cause you never know
I went along with those guys
I actually thought about that
I wish I didn't
say he was leaving because
5 million people retweeted that
and then I said oh actually he's coming back
like nobody
it's not as exciting to people who aren't invested
in the comic you know where he's always leaving
even if you don't know anything about the comic
you can sort of be like oh that's big news
I see
they wrote the whole article about it
on Know Your Meme
whatever
but what can you do
it'll be fine like he's going to continue doing pages
and most people
especially as the time goes on will that
announcement fade from people's memory
yeah I think it's already
started to fade because
people used to think the comic was cancelled
but I think most people
don't
also the Five Nights at Freddy's thing helped
I mean the Five Nights at Funkin
Friday Night Funkin
yeah
Five Nights at Funkin
you don't know about that Ben?
well I know what the game is
there's a Tails gets trolled mod
for Friday Night Funkin
do you remember last time
ages and ages ago I was like dude Ben
I don't have the most
viewed Tails gets trolled video on YouTube
and I have number 2 and you were like oh Pog
dude now there's like some Friday Night Funkin
video with over a million views
that like loads of shit
just search Tails gets trolled on YouTube right now
and you'll see what we're talking about
there's probably like multiple videos
oh yeah there's multiple videos showing off the mod
that all have more than our shit
yeah the first result
Friday Night Funkin versus Sonic and Tails
gets trolled 2.0
and Tails
okay
I can't get mad at it even though
it's introducing a ton of new people to comic
it's ultimately a good thing
as far as I'm concerned
but they are consumers
and they are cringe for not knowing
about Tails gets trolled already
well this is a shocking development
damn
I should have been on the internet for 30 years
like we were
oh you passed me Cybershell
the biggest
it's Friday Night Funkin with 1.4 million
and then you with just under 600k
and then my lecture
with 530k
and then after that is
Tails gets trolled is back
PCP episode with 22k
and then it's
chapter 1
part 1 of is it the audio
book after that?
I wish the audio comic book
or whatever the proper term for it had more views
like the ultimate Tails gets trolled
although that one is sort of split because there was an original
Tails gets trolled channel that uploaded the first
4 videos or whatever
and that one's got 180k
and then the ultimate Tails gets trolled
the latest one has 12k views
which I think is the most
maybe I'm not sure
I don't know if you can answer like an ultimate
but it's less
that channel's only got 8000
chapter 8 got 57k
so some of them are a bit bigger
ok
I still think
still more people watch the audio drama
than the
read the comic because I hear people say
oh you know the Friday Night Funkin' Mom got me to
watch the original
to watch the original
ah
it's the game of the anime of the manga
well I mean if you live on YouTube
maybe you just
just think
I guess if you've never heard of it before
YouTubers were all in creative endeavors that originate from
YouTube
well whatever
as long as people are enjoying
the content
you know
who cares if they watch it sub
or read the manga, watch the anime
so we're all fans
speaking of enjoying content
is this the longest PCP episode now
or are we still not beat that last week
it's gotta be close
I don't know
I don't know the exact count
because I started my audacity recording way earlier
so I'm at like 5.30
but I know we're only at like 5.10
5.15 is something like that
that sounds about right
that's pretty long
yeah I'm 5.20
if it's not the longest it's probably
I need to go get some food I'm hungry as fuck
the guests are overruling
you Ben the show is wrapping up now
that's fine
good that's what I wanted
ok
last words before we wrap up
apple
I said everything I wanted to say
well sort of
patreon.com
titty's
twitter.com
I'm not doing commissions anymore lol
just follow me
you can see drawings
just look at the fucking art you idiots
don't pay for it just look at it
you'll draw my girl eventually
you can take dot site to see the comics
that I draw
they're good
if you're seriously a PCP
listener and you're like
I've never been to
Redgiven's comics
what if you're like seriously
that would be pretty fucked up
fortunately I don't think there's too many people
like that I mean like a guy hope not
ok
good fucking
ok I guess that's it we've had enough
I've had enough
no more
enough
goodbye
I'm supposed to be working
right now
but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
we're not doing a whole fucking sing along
it's already gone it's already faded out
it's ended
we have to sink at the end
I'm not going to dive
Covid for it's finished