I'm going to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Cool.
Alright, let's just get right into it. Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm trying to be professional, and being professional is when you don't care about what you're doing.
So, whatever, I guess it's The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I guess we're doing a show. I mean, I don't need it. I don't care.
I've really got better things to be doing, but I'm on The Pro Crastinators Podcast and Gibbontake and Oblivionfall as well.
Hi.
Hello.
I'm a little tipsy from earlier today.
Yeah, tell me about that.
Let's explore that.
Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
So, it was a meetup of the Agoonary people, a few Agoonary people at the pub the day after we finished camp for the week, which is why I was not here last week.
It was an Agoonary camp.
Would you like to explain that for anyone who, would you like, let me see the Twitter, would you like to explain what the Agoonary is for anyone who might have forgotten?
The Agoonary is a scout camp for disabled children to go and have fun for a week with activities and scouty-ish things, but mostly just like low stakes fun activity stuff.
They sleep in patrol tents, they have a little patrol, and I go as a helper to help, and I apparently have been going for 11 years because I got a certificate this time.
Whoa.
Is it Boy Scouts related?
I mean, it's scout related.
It's like, it's actually, this year was the 75th anniversary of a Goonary.
So there was a big deal about, oh, 75 years ago the first Agoonary happened, and it was, you know, because the Scouting Association, initially it was Boy Scouts.
It was a guy, a British guy, who'd invented scouting by saying, I think young boys would like to do things.
I'm going to invent that, and he did that.
Because he was in the Army.
It's like, what if there was a low stakes like Army-esque thing for little boys to do so that they could feel like responsible and learn skills like tying a knot, making a campfire.
So he made that, and then the whole idea was to get to allow young people to have a sense of responsibility and autonomy and stuff.
So it expanded into Girl Scouts and all those other things, and then Agoonary was like, what about disabled kids?
Surely we can make something for them?
And so they did, and that's been going for 75 years, and it's great.
It's a lot of fun this year.
Had a good time.
Let me get that Twitter.
Yeah, show me the Twitter.
There's a site as well, I guess.
Yeah, goodery.org.
You may be able to see me in photographs.
Oh my God, how embarrassing.
That's so fun.
I may be doxing myself.
We're going to see you gooning.
You're gooning.
I'm going to goon.
Apparently a bad word or something, I heard, I think.
To who?
It's not like a slur.
I occasionally get tagged on Twitter by someone who's taken a picture of Phalia, my big booby succubus,
and they'll put text around her saying, are you a goon?
Are you going to goon?
Are you gooning right now?
Live a life of gooning, and I don't know what it means.
I'm scared.
The only goon I know is someone on Something Awful.
That's what the awful users call themselves.
Oh my God, give, I see you.
Oh no, where am I?
You're only five or six posts down.
I'm going to kill baking.
It was a Scottish day.
Yeah, we made kilts, and all the kids got to make their own kilts, and did Scottish things.
There was a cabot toss, and we had black pudding, and haggis, something or other.
Like haggis-esque meat.
I had a haggis once.
I've had a haggis many times. It's very nice.
I had haggis in like a...
Spicy minced meat, sort of.
Yeah, I had it in like a takeaway restaurant one time, and I ordered some over-the-counter
at like a haggis Taco Bell.
Damn.
Do you want to hear the origins of everyone's favorite transphobic slur?
I'm just realizing if people from a goonery find out that I am on a podcast, and the only things
the other two hosts have said so far is big boobies and transphobic slurs, I'm like, oh shit.
Maybe I shouldn't mix these cross these streams.
I don't know if it's technically a slur, but you know, that's where the word trune comes from.
It's from goons who were trans, you know, people on something awful.
So they just combined it.
Wait, really?
Yeah, it was a neutral term at one point.
So wait, what is a goon?
Someone on something awful.
Someone awful?
I don't know what the version of the word goon that I was referencing comes from, but it's probably also bad.
Yeah, I've never heard that before.
I'm gonna goon, like what the fuck does that mean?
I've never heard that.
I think I found some urban dictionary, but it's like it's stewing in the coom or something.
I don't know where the G comes from though.
Amazing.
I don't understand.
If you go to this Twitter, do not mention me at all.
Do not ever do that.
Don't let them know that this podcast exists.
I'm just saying, I saw some weird people using a similar word.
No, it's fine.
It's fine having like a podcast where we can say coom a lot.
But I don't mention, whenever people at that place, because they know me, they've known me for a while,
I talk about the things I do.
Oh, I'm making a comic.
I can show them my website.
Oh, I'm making a game.
Show them that.
You know, I'm doing this and that.
I never say my podcast ever.
Never would I ever subject them to knowing about the PCP.
This is a hard line.
That's fair.
That's a good line to never cross, I would think.
Yep.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm scrolling through more of the timeline here.
Yeah, this is a new thing.
Before the like social media, because a lot of the people who do...
Oh my...
...Gunaria, huh?
I'm sorry.
This is not strictly relevant, but I just noticed the...
Damn.
I just noticed the frickin' minimalist modern reimagining of the Scouts logo.
The Flirterly.
Oh, the Flirterly.
They got that too.
They got the fuckin' Scouts too, with that fuckin' modern minimalist corporate bullshit.
Yeah.
It's...
I was looking at like the old programs.
I was looking at the old programs, because every year there's like a little booklet you receive in the mail.
It's like, okay, meet here at this time to get on the coach to go to camp.
And here's what the...
Like, yeah, there's meat here.
You want to come over?
And they have like the symbol of the Gunaria and the Scouts symbol,
and then usually the symbol of the school or whatever campsite we're at.
And the more recent ones have this like really minimal Flirterly, and it's like, okay.
I mean, whatever.
I don't care for it, but it's pretty...
I like the purple color, but yeah, it's whatever.
The Gunaria style is iconic, though.
You can't minimize that, because it's just lines.
Wait a minute.
You mean that logo?
Or you mean that on the bottom the...
On the bottom, the style is like a...
Fence thing?
It's a fence with like what's called a style,
which is like a smaller piece of wood meant to allow...
To help people climb over the fence if they're going on a walk,
but animals wouldn't know how to use it.
So it's sort of like symbolic.
It's like, yeah, we're helping people...
Helping them over there.
Over the fence.
Oh, I see.
Hmm.
Confusing a double meaning of the word style there.
But, uh...
I don't know where it comes from, etymologically,
but I think it's pretty stylish.
That sounds like something we should go down a whole rabbit hole
to discover.
Oh, hell yeah.
I'm doing it.
I need more rabbits down my hole, if you know what I'm saying.
Oh, yeah.
You can just shove them in there, one after the other.
That's a little abbreviated for one of my topics later.
I got a new pet rabbit, but I eat it with my butt hole.
You're closer than you think.
It's something I found, but I'll talk about it a bit later.
Okay.
Yeah, on dictionary.com.
I don't...
Oh, maybe it's not with a Y.
Maybe it's S-T-I-O.
That's what it is.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, yeah.
Old English device for climbing or ladder
to climb, Germanic steak to climb.
Yeah, so style with an I.
And that's where turnstile is from.
I get it.
Because it's similar, sort of.
Oh, and you know what?
Guess what?
Hey, this is exciting.
Well, the style as in form of appearance,
design or mode type, whatever,
is from the Latin stylus.
So, meaning a writing implement.
So, we've got one style from the Latin,
one style from the Germanic,
and I've been watching a ton of videos this week
from a channel called Tolkien Untangled,
going into, like, deep lore of, like, Tolkien stuff.
And so now I know that he would have preferred
the fence meaning because he preferred Germanic words.
He liked when English words had Germanic origins.
He didn't like when they had Latin origins.
He thought that was stupid.
Lol.
Yeah, and he was right.
Isn't it funny how styluses and tablets
were a thing back in ancient Rome?
Yeah, like ancient Greece or whatever.
Didn't we talk about this on a podcast?
I think we did talk about the wax tablet.
Yeah, the wax, yes, the wax tablet
that you could wipe but wipe down.
With the stylus, which is just a stick.
Yeah.
They were making it full circle.
They were so close to inventing the Game Boy DS back then.
They had one half of it,
but they didn't get the other half until thousands of years later.
Ugh.
Yeah, back then it was just called DS.
Yeah.
This is why they died.
They made a Nintendo DS,
but they were like, hmm, what do we put in...
Do we put, like, a screen and microchips in this?
Or we could just fill it with wax.
Okay, let's go with a cheaper alternative.
I think we'd be fine.
Ugh, the gals are mad.
Ugh, the Visigoths are angry.
We did that.
They wanted the new DS.
But if we spend all our freaking...
What kind of currency did they have in Rome?
Like, drachma? No.
Coins?
I'm actually kind of curious what the...
I think they definitely had coins in the printing mechanism.
They had coins, but...
Oh, the gold aureus.
Aureus.
Yeah, okay, aureus.
But if we spend all our aureus,
you know, putting microchips in this tablet,
then we won't have any aureus left to spend on the grain doll.
And then we're fucked.
With a grain doll as a cornerstone of modern civilization,
and that was there, as always.
Communism was their downfall, as with all great empires,
so we know better.
We know better this time.
Their downfall was letting gay people fuck.
That destroyed everything.
Romans, one gay person fucked, the empire fell the next day.
That's what I learned.
Because of the cum blast, it was too powerful.
It shattered all of the infrastructure.
It's like we learned in that movie, the butterfly effect.
You know, one gay couple having gay sex across the world in China
can have ripple effects that spread throughout the entire world
and cause a tornado in California.
It's just...
It's just true.
It's just the facts.
I was imagining, like, ancient Rome,
like, oh, I'm an artist.
I have my Cintiq wax tablet
propped up on his stone marble desk.
He's like, ah, yes.
Drawing a thing.
You finished, and it's like, oh, well,
I don't know what to do now.
New tablet.
Oh, my God, I just...
I just learned.
I literally just learned what Orish Alchem,
or Orahalchim, is.
Or a calcum.
Yeah, because I guess they made...
I guess they made Roman orias out of it sometimes.
And I guess it's just some bullshit.
In numismatics,
which I guess is the study or collection of currency,
the term Orahalchim is used to refer to the golden-colored bronze alloy
used for the Cistercius and Dupondius coins.
It is considered more valuable than copper,
of which the az coin...
Az coin.
The az coin was made, which was a bronze...
They had fucking...
They had too many coins.
They're doing a stupid Harry Potter, like,
uh, bronze nuts and silver sickles and whatever.
There's too many. Just keep it simple, stupid.
I don't need all this garbage.
So wait, is Orahalchim like a mineral,
or is it just like a different percentage of something alloy?
It says it's just an alloy,
but it's a type of bronze,
and it says it's golden-colored and it's a type of bronze,
but it doesn't go into any more detail than that.
Well, that's stupid.
Those Romans should have wrote it down.
Yeah, yeah.
I guess we'll never know.
There's no way to determine these things.
Uh...
Man, so...
Yeah, I've been watching a lot of those Tolkien videos.
They're pretty good.
I've also, last week,
Simsie mentioned a channel called Explore With Us,
which is sort of, it's basically the same as Jim Can't Swim,
and I watched a bunch of those.
Those were wild.
You know the kind of videos I'm talking about, right?
Remind me, Jim Can't Swim.
I don't know if I've seen any of those.
It's like the Death Pig,
where they're interrogating Ben St.
It's like that.
It's exactly like that.
No, it's police interrogation videos,
but they're paused and then...
Yeah, this is why this guy's fucked right now,
because he just lied on camera.
Well, all the ones that I've seen
have less been about...
They've less been focused on,
here's how we know he's lying,
and more about this person is mentally ill.
It's not so much about...
I mean, there is some of that.
It's like, yeah, what their body language is saying,
but a lot of the ones that I watched
have had mentally ill people or autistic people or something.
Yeah, so it was like a guy who just admitted to the murder,
and they could determine from the way he was just saying everything,
and it was all factually accurate that he was insane.
Yeah, the big guy with the long hair, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I saw that one.
Yeah, that's the Jim Can't Swim.
These...
Some of the Explorer with us...
Oh, they have the interviews with the freaking Slenderman killer girls,
the ones that stabbed their friend.
That's fucking...
Oh, I've heard of that one.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but they're adorable.
I love them.
They killed their friend?
First of all, she didn't die. Let's not be hysterical.
I don't know the thing.
I just heard that they stabbed someone because of Slenderman.
Yeah.
Yeah, basically.
They thought they could become his proxies or his puppets
or something and live in Slenderman.
They wanted to prove themselves to him, so they went into the woods
and they did some fucked up shit and they waited.
Yeah, well, I've learned some things about it.
It was not really in the woods.
It was more in like a small little cops of trees in like a park.
But they both...
Oh, my God.
I was like...
I had watched a bunch and then like before bed,
last night I started that one up and I was so engrossed in it
that I stayed up way too late.
I watched all three hours of it.
I could not stop watching it.
They loved it.
They both...
It's these two girls.
One of them is schizophrenic
and I think bipolar
and the other one...
I'm not sure if she was diagnosed with anything,
but she was definitely not normal.
And they both basically seemed to think
that the other one was the one that really believed it
and they were kind of like...
No, that's not true.
No, no.
Well, they both think the other one was the one telling them
they had to do it.
Like neither one of them knows why they had to do it.
They both think that the other one was like,
it just has to be this way.
It just has to be this way and I don't know why
and I can't explain it,
but we have to do it or we're going to die.
Slender Man's going to kill our families if we don't do it.
Oh, no.
Yeah, yeah.
Man, what else?
I could say a lot about that one.
The worst one, though...
The worst one and this was so infuriating
was there was a guy...
It starts off, it's like...
This is a very unusual interview.
I'm not going to tell...
I'm not the narrator.
I'm not going to explain what is going on here.
Watch this interview and try to figure out
what's going on.
They sit this guy down.
He's got bruises all over his face.
They sit him down
and they found his girlfriend dead
in his house and he was in the house
and the guy seems confused and he's out of it
and he's answering questions
like only semi-coherently.
They're trying to ask him what happened
and he's just like,
I don't know, man.
I just want to go to sleep.
Five minutes and I'm like,
he's obviously got a head injury.
He's obviously got a head injury
and he's disoriented and he's not.
That's why he's answering all these questions weird.
He's got a head injury.
So the interview goes on for like an hour
and turns out at the end,
he's like, did you figure it out?
If you look closely,
you could see that he had a head injury.
Yes, that's it.
He'd been shot through the head.
The guy had shot him through the eye twice
and four bullet holes,
four open bullet wounds were in his head
and they just didn't notice.
He noticed?
The cops simply, they held him in the car
and then they took him to the interrogation room
and they interrogated him for six hours
because they didn't notice
obvious, visible, open bullet wounds
in his head.
Yeah, it sucked so bad.
Was there a blood coming out?
He had blood on him.
He had bruised.
He was bruised severely in the face.
I'm assuming he somehow survived
because if his six hours being conscious
with that,
I've heard of people getting shot
or a steam engine guy
got a train explosion
and he'd bar through the head
and his brain was cut
but he was like,
oh yeah, I'm fine.
Yeah, it was basically like that.
He was...
Okay, he had apparently been
in his house for two days
or something before the cops found him
so he'd already been just walking around
not knowing what was going on
with, yeah, he'd been shot through the head.
Then the cops find him.
They don't recognize that this guy
obviously needs to go to the hospital
not now but a long time ago really
and they just don't...
It was so obvious.
Instantly, he's obviously suffering a head injury
and of course, that's what was going on.
Yeah, so they waste six hours
during which he desperately needed
medical treatment.
They eventually figure it out
and get him to the hospital
and they get him surgery and stuff.
They try to put his head back together.
They have to remove part of his brain.
He does survive but he's never the same.
He has terrible seizures
for the rest of his life
and a couple years later, he does die.
Oh, that's so freaky.
I don't like thinking about that.
No.
Wow.
The guy's talking to him
and he's asking him,
do you remember what happened?
At first, he says,
yeah, we had bows and arrows.
We had bows and arrows
and he's like, what?
And then he explains what he means by the bow and arrow
and he's like, you mean revolvers?
You mean a gun?
He's like, yeah, revolvers.
That's what I said, revolvers.
The neurons are firing into the open air.
They're just falling out of them.
He keeps changing the story.
First, he talks about the girlfriend.
He says she's someone else's girlfriend.
Then she says he's his
and then there's another girl
and then there's another guy.
And then at one point,
just totally randomly,
he's like, oh, yeah,
so-and-so and his dad, yeah,
they broke into our house
and they shot us.
But I got to go.
I just want to go home and go to sleep.
And he's like, what?
They shot you?
He's like, yeah, where did they shoot you?
They shot me in the eye.
And the cop is like...
The fact that he knew
that that's where he was shot,
but he just didn't do anything about it
because he got shot in the brain.
He just thought,
you'd be dead if you got shot in the eye.
So obviously, that's not what happened.
But it is what happened.
It takes him a while for the guy to say it, though,
because he's having trouble remembering stuff.
I'm just f-f-fuck off.
This is made me really mad.
Apparently, and I didn't see this,
but apparently they took photos.
When they brought him in for questioning,
they took photos of him.
And apparently you can see
the open head wounds in the photos.
I guess they just didn't look at them.
We'll need that later.
Oh, man.
That one was f-f-ing infuriating.
I'm trying to...
I don't want to watch that.
I don't want to know about that.
That one's really troubling.
That one made me sick.
Yeah, I'm feeling a little woozy.
Yeah.
The Slenderman, though,
loved it.
I mean, I know they did a crime.
It's really horrible what they did to their friends.
But they both just seem...
They're both being melodramatic about it.
They're both...
The schizophrenic one keeps being like...
She keeps being like,
it was just necessary.
It just had to happen.
She says it in a melodramatic way.
She's narrating a movie or something.
I think, you know, I just wanted to live with no regrets.
Yeah, I just...
And the other one is like scared and nervous.
And sometimes she starts crying.
But then other times she gets really animated
and she starts just rattling off facts
about the creepy pasta wiki.
She just starts explaining to the cop
who Zalgo is and who Slenderman is
and who Jack the Killer is.
Jack the Ripper, you mean?
I mean, Jack the Killer, I mean...
Jack the Ripper.
Oh, there's only one killer in the world.
There are Jacks.
There's Eilis Jack I learned
and there's...
Shit, there was another Jack too, but I forget.
And it's honestly...
She says she doesn't believe it anymore.
She says that while they were on the run,
like while they were walking down the highway,
trying to walk to the woods of Wisconsin
to find the Slender Mansion.
Like apparently they start...
The Slender Mansion.
Yeah, they literally were walking down the highway
in the direction of what they thought
the Slender Mansion was.
And they like started...
They like broke down and started crying on the sidewalk,
or not the sidewalk, the shoulder of the road.
And apparently the schizophrenic one
basically like cried out in prayer
to Slenderman like save us.
And nothing happened.
And it like shattered the other one's faith.
It shattered her faith that Slenderman was real
and now she doesn't believe it anymore.
How old were they?
12.
I think they were like 12.
Yeah, too old, too old for this.
But they seem to believe it.
They seem pretty...
Well, no, that one seems to believe it.
The other one, the schizophrenic one,
it's a little harder to tell.
She seems really like detached.
Don't go on the internet.
Do not go on the internet.
I don't know much about this other kid
that I've seen like footage of.
Morgan was the schizophrenic one
and Anissa was the other one.
No, no, I mean like I've heard of a different one
that was like the inspiration for Cara in Undertale.
It's like a little girl looks just like Frisk
who is being interviewed saying,
like just admitting that she puts needles in her little brother.
Oh, I've never heard about that.
Yeah, this is like little kid wearing like a similar jumper
to Frisk from Undertale
and she's got like the little bob hair thing.
She's just admitting to this interview
that she does terrible things
and she's like, obviously doesn't care
about the consequences or the ramifications.
It's just like, yeah, I just do it.
It's like, it's really creepy.
Like she's like five or something.
Gross.
No, I didn't even know about that.
Scary.
Kids are fucked up.
We should end kids.
Bring back abortion, baby.
This is because they banned abortion.
That's why the Slender Man killings happened.
Yes.
They're just so chunibio about it.
They were planning to fucking kawaii
when they stabbed that girl.
They were planning it for like...
Oh, it's so awful.
They were planning it for like months.
They were going to have like a sleepover
and they were going to do it at the...
They were going to have these three of them
were going to sleep over
and they were going to like stab her in her sleep
and then run away in the middle of the night.
But I guess it didn't work out for some reason.
They couldn't do that.
One of them said...
The Schizophrenic one said...
Morgan said,
I'm going to set my alarm in my headphones.
I'm going to set the alarm for the middle of the night.
We're going to...
And I'll wake you up in the middle of the night
and that's when we'll do it.
And I guess she didn't set the alarm.
It seemed...
They both seemed to like not have really wanted to do it.
They both...
They both talk about it.
Like it's just this fatalistic thing that like...
Well, we just had to do.
There was nothing we could do.
And she...
I mean, I kind of understand like kid mindset
where like if one of them tells the other,
our parents are going to die
if we don't do what Slenderman says.
And they almost like,
Oh, no.
And they just believe it.
But I don't know.
The going that far seems abnormal.
I mean, yeah, for sure.
They both think the other one is the one that told them
that like Slenderman will kill our families
if we don't do this.
Neither of them thinks it was their idea.
Which is very strange.
They both sort of paint the other one as like the leader
and they were just a follower.
Yeah, but she didn't set her alarm.
She didn't set her alarm.
And so the next morning they wake up
and Morgan says,
Anissa was angry at me for not setting my alarm
so we didn't do it.
But Anissa says,
Morgan was being nice.
She let me sleep in
because I didn't want to do it.
So I guess they went,
they only went to the park and they were like playing,
they were playing hide and seek in the park
and they did it in like a,
in like a cops of trees.
Wait, this is great.
This is great.
They said,
Anissa said now and Morgan jumped.
Okay.
Morgan says that Anissa says now Kitty
because Kitty was like Morgan's code name.
Kitty says my code name.
You know, Morgan says my code name was Kitty
and Anissa's code name was Scorpion.
And she says that Anissa says now,
and Anissa says that she said now
and then Morgan said,
don't be scared.
I'm just a little kitty
and jumped on her and stabbed her.
Apparently they were going to,
her plan was to become,
when she ascended to the ranks of,
you know,
someone on the creepypasta wiki,
someone who lived in the slender mansion,
like killer name was going to be Kitty
and she was going to draw whiskers on her face.
But then that was going to be her gimmick.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
But then she says,
no, Anissa gave me that name
just because I have cats
and she says I act like a cat sometimes.
Like Anissa says that I'm Kitty.
It wasn't my idea.
It's really bizarre.
They both,
yeah, they're 12,
so they're too old for this.
But they act like,
they act like little kids,
like maybe like eight or 10,
which is not like super weird for a 12 year old.
Like some kids are just like that.
But they're acting like it.
While they're talking about like,
yeah, yeah, we stabbed our friend.
And apparently they,
Morgan did the stabbing
and then the one that they stabbed
is just kind of like crying out in pain
and like she's yelling at them like,
I hate you.
I trusted you.
How could you do this to me?
And then like crying because it hurts.
And they're just like, okay,
well, we're going to go get help.
You stay here.
But secretly they weren't going to get help.
They were just going to run away
to Slender Mansion and let her die.
She had to die.
It was all part of the plan.
There was nothing they could do.
It's so, it's so odd
because like the way you're describing it,
it is sort of like a little kid plan
to like steal from the cookie jar.
It sounds like they were all
talking about it like they were like,
they talk about it like they were playing a game.
Yeah, but like because they had read
what was the wiki thing?
The creepypasta wiki.
The creepypasta wiki that they just,
they thought that that was harmless
or maybe, I don't know, how do you,
I suppose if you've never like dealt
with like blood and death.
Yeah.
You wouldn't really think about it
until it's suddenly there and it's like,
oh no.
Terrible, terrible situation.
Morgan says that like,
oh, Anisa was the one that wanted to do it.
It was Anisa's idea.
But then when the time came,
she couldn't do it.
She made me do it.
She gave me the knife and said,
you have to be the one to do it.
I can't do it.
I'm too scared.
And Anisa says like,
yeah, Anisa also says like I was too scared.
I couldn't do it.
I'm too squeamish.
I'm too nice of a person.
I couldn't stab someone.
I could hurt myself,
but like if it was someone else's blood,
I couldn't stand it.
I couldn't look at that.
And that's like hours after conspiring
to murder her friend and stabbing her
in the cops of trees in the park.
It's unclear if Anisa did any stabbing herself.
It sounds like no.
But really is it really do be like,
don't go on the internet.
Don't end up on the creepypasta wiki
and get weird ideas when you're that young.
It's clear that these two are like,
there's something wrong with these two.
But also it's not like so profoundly wrong
that it's like this is inevitable.
Like they were like natural serial killers.
I think it was like a weird perfect storm
of like these two girls have something wrong with them.
And then they fall down this rabbit hole of lore
about, you know, these like sexy monster killers.
And there's all these like legends on the internet
that you can become one of them.
And then the two of them like fed off of each other
and like talked about it and like and validated one another
is like weird beliefs about it.
And then they said like, like they don't talk about
like they didn't ever want it.
They didn't even seem to want to do it.
They don't have any plans to do it again.
They never thought about doing anything like this
to anyone else.
They don't like kill small animals or anything like that.
It seems like like a really weird one up one off event
that just happened due to a bizarre confluence of factors.
Oh, I watched another one about a lady
who left her baby in the dumpster.
That was fucked up.
Yeah.
Some people found a baby in the dumpster and they're asked there.
That one was kind of sad.
I mean, I don't know.
The lady like she knows what she did was wrong.
She doesn't really have like an explanation for it.
She just she said she was scared,
but she doesn't really like explain what she was scared of.
Like she doesn't say that like, oh, I couldn't afford it.
Like I couldn't take care of a baby.
She apparently hid the pregnancy from her parents,
which might be maybe she was scared that like
her mom was going to be mad that she got pregnant
and she found out so she hid the whole thing
and then discarded the evidence basically.
And that's like, yeah.
This whole thing sounds like a real fucked up thing to watch.
I don't.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess I can see why it would be interesting.
Yeah, it's.
I mean, if I if I think the I think the there's a lot of videos.
I think the other only other one to watch it only watched a few
because I just started these like yesterday.
The last one was about like a girl like an emo girl
like a legit emo girl back in like 2008 or something who just
like just who just for fun like just to see what it felt like
like murdered her neighbor like her younger neighbor girl in like
the woods like strangled her slitter throat and then like
buried her and she has and she has the interview with her
grandma in the in the room.
And when she admits that she slipped the throat,
the grandma like freaks out and starts like crying
and screaming and stuff.
And like, yeah, that's fair.
I don't like hearing about any of this.
So I'm sorry.
Okay, the one thing I want to say about that is that
one's kind of that one's sort of interest sort of I want to say funny.
But that one's funny.
It's funny because she's like an emo girl and she has all these
pictures of her like Facebook or whatever that have like pictures
of her look an emo like she's got some like blood on her mouth.
Like she put on like fake blood and like posed with like her
teeth there like she's a vampire or something and they keep
showing these photos to show like what a what a person of
violent tendency she was.
But like it kind of just looks like any any emo girl might
have taken these anyone would like paint themselves to look
like a vampire and like pose like that.
It's not weird.
But I guess in this particular case it was.
I mean, it depends on who your audiences are definitely with
it.
There's definitely a type of conservative that's like we're like
having dyed hair or any piercings at all.
Like you're immediately a terrible terrible awful degenerate
person go away.
She didn't even look at you.
I mean, she had like kind of an emo haircut.
But she didn't have like blue hair.
She didn't have like a septum piercings or anything like that.
She's kind of had bangs and eye shadow.
I don't know.
They're scared eye shadow.
That's that's pretty extreme.
That's it's gone.
It's too far.
We've gone too far to even accept.
We used to live in a country, a real country.
We're we're we're sexualizing children by letting six year old
16 year olds put on eye shadow.
It's we have to return to.
We have to return to the ancient Roman days when they would
I'm sure they would use some weird fucked up shit for makeup.
Yeah, just like straight up lead.
Just metal.
They would have chrome faces.
The iron the iron mask.
They would.
Yeah, instead of they didn't have makeup, so they would get bolted
into like an iron.
That's reasonable.
Calcum all over.
Right.
But I've learned a lot about Tolkien as well.
I've learned I've learned a lot about horrific murders and
Tolkien.
And that's damn you.
You be tubing.
I'd be tubing.
I've been tubing this week.
I've been I've been working.
I've been working and tubing at the same time.
Incredible.
Yeah.
Here's a here's a fun fact.
In the movies.
Aragorn wears a ring that is never really explained what it is.
But in the books, he doesn't wear the ring, but he does have the
ring and there is like a long history of like who owned this
ring and where it came from and such and such.
And it's not a ring of power or anything.
It's just a regular ring.
But it's actually like made by the elves in like in the first
age and it's like it's literally the oldest thing like in the
world.
It's like the oldest piece of jewelry in the world.
It's older than the sun.
But yeah.
Because I get the heat.
Because I well, I guess when I guess in the early days of
Middle Earth, there was no sun and moon.
There were just the stars and the land was lit by these two
like magical trees, like a golden tree and a silver tree.
And I don't know exactly how the sun happened, but it's at some
point it was created and this ring was made like before that.
So Aragorn just casually has this like 10,000 year old
fucking ring.
He's got.
Yeah.
Also, also, did you know that Gandalf has a ring of power the
whole time?
No.
Yeah, he's got rings of power would corrupt would were
corruptive.
They are.
Is it just the one ring?
The one ring is worse.
They are they are all corruptive, but Gandalf has one of the
one of the he has one of the three.
Okay.
So, um, oh God, what's the name of the guy?
Guy who forged the airy rings.
It's not cuckoo lane.
Caleb Rimbour.
This guy Caleb Rimbour.
Sauron taught Caleb Rimbour how to make rings.
And so he made they made seven rings for the dwarves and nine
rings for the for men.
And then Caleb Rimbour was like, hey, I'm going to go away.
Thanks, Sauron.
Thanks.
Thanks for all the secret lore.
Thanks for the ring lore, Sauron.
You sucker.
And he went off by himself and he secretly crafted three
rings for the elves.
And, uh, I think, um, uh, Elrond has one.
And another guy in a du-
Galadriel?
No, Galadriel does not have one.
Oh, she was in the movie.
I remember that scene right at the beginning where she has a
ring.
You pretty sure it's her?
Uh, maybe.
Like three rings were gifted to the race of elves.
One.
Okay.
Maybe it was one of either her or Elrond had one.
Um, there's a ring of, like, I think it's a ring of air or
a ring of water and a ring of fire.
And yeah, um, this guy called, uh, is it Collane the Shipwright
or something?
This other guy, I guess when, when the Maiar who became the
wizards came to Arda, uh, they, uh, fucking, uh, what's,
what's his name?
Tolkien the Shipwrights.
C-Cyrdan.
Cyrdan, this is the shipwright.
He's this elven.
I guess he's a king of something.
Uh, when the, when the Maiar that became the wizards came to
Arda, I guess this guy Cyrdan, like, met them.
And he had this, this one, Caleb Rimbour made this one, I
think, Venya or Nunya or something.
It was the fire ring.
And he had it.
And he met all the Maiar and he's like, okay, yeah, cool.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks for coming to Arda to help out with like the work of
God or whatever.
Uh, but then he met, he met Gandalf last and Gandalf was, I
guess, he, I guess he was just better than the others.
And he was like, okay, actually this one's like, I really like
this one.
So he gifted him the, the ring, the elven ring of fire.
And he's like, here, just keep this just in case.
Um, and I guess when, when Gandalf is fighting the Balrog,
he's throws it, he throws out a bunch of like, he's trying to
like intimidate the Balrog and he says, I am so and so, uh, you
know, bearer of the, he says something like I am the bearer
of like the flame of the West or something.
And it's like, it might be that he's talking.
The flame of Arnor, I remember him saying.
Yes.
Yeah.
And he, I think he's talking about that he has this fucking
ring.
Wow.
Yeah.
But it's like,
That was just like a, like a, like a skill tree.
Like he knows fire magic.
Yeah.
Like he's, he's, he's specked into fire magic right now.
And, and, uh, despite.
One shot you bro.
And despite what you might think, uh, uh, Balrogs actually
are not resistant to fire elemental damage.
So you better watch out.
Sir.
Um, yes, I have, I have learned many interesting Tolkien
facts, uh, of that, of that sort.
Tolkien, more like token.
No.
We.
Damn.
Well.
A couple of weeks ago, I talked on the podcast about how
there was a remake of one of my favorite games that was
coming out and how it had a really bad, but then the new
remake looks better.
And that was clenoa.
And I played it.
And, uh, and, uh, it's, it's, it's flawed.
Um, I have to say.
Oh no.
I've seen, I've seen some looking screenshots of the
clenoa and it looks cool from what I saw.
I don't know anything about clenoa.
What is clenoa?
Okay.
I mean, I've seen the character.
Uh, read it.
Yeah.
Just read it.
So.
Is it a 3D platformer collectathon?
It's a 2.5 D.
What if a Sonic character was their own series?
No.
Hmm.
Well, okay.
So here, look, I'll just grab some of the comparisons that
I made today.
Uh, so like overall, like the new game looks good.
Maybe even looks better in a lot of places.
The, the, the problem, there's a couple of problems I
have for one, the controls are like clunkier.
I don't know how that happened, but, um, there's just
little details missing that just make me sad.
So if you look at the top, uh, left image, you'll see
in the background that you can see a waterfall with
some platforms.
That's actually level two.
You can see level two in the backdrop of level one.
And that's a cute little detail of it they put in.
Sure.
Um, and then the remake they just forgot is just a
waterfall with no platforms.
Uh, that's, that is, that's cringe.
That's cringe.
It's cringe.
It looks a little bit like a Kirby return to
Dream Mind or whatever.
Uh, it is, from other games I've seen, it is most
similar to Kirby, I would say.
Um, so like, okay, like, that's just, it's just
sad.
There's just a lot of like little things where it's
like, where they just forgot to put something in
or they forgot a sound effect.
Or there's like a cool sound effect in the original
and then like in, you know, you know, the new version,
there's just no sound effect at all.
Or it's just being replaced with like a generic
sound effect that like just blends in with everything
else that you, that doesn't stand out at all.
Um, little things like that that are annoying.
Um, the sound mixing is fucking awful.
Um, like some of the character's voices are
perpetually like way too fucking quiet.
Uh, Joker's voice is super quiet throughout the
whole game, but our character's voices are really
loud.
Is there no options for that?
It's so bizarre.
There's a voice volume option that changes everyone's
voices like linearly.
They're still proportionally
wrong compared to each other.
I see.
It's weird whenever that happens in a game.
Like, I don't know, whenever, whenever some
YouTuber is explaining like why some game is bad
and then he's like, this is not edited.
I did not edit this.
It actually sounds like this.
And then they play a clip that's like, you just
literally like can't hear characters talking over
like the background music or something.
I'm always like, I can't, I can't believe
things like that happen.
It's not even that rare, but it's like, how do you,
how does that happen?
It's so bad.
The original game didn't have any issues at all
like that.
It's, it sounded fine.
You can hear everything clearly.
Um, like during, during Joker's boss fight,
he has this like spinning attack where he
spins around really fast.
I'm the Joker's baby.
He's Joker.
Um, he, and, and the original game was like
a swish, swish, swish.
It's like this really like loud swishing sound
that you jump.
And then the remake, it's like negative like
30 decibels.
You have to like strain so hard.
It's like almost not even there.
Um, there's like one of the boss fights,
like over half the sound effects are just
missing.
Um, you just don't hear anything.
It doesn't have footsteps.
It doesn't have anything when it's running around.
It's just bizarre.
And that was just really weird and sad and
dumb, I guess.
Um, sound design is sometimes overlooked
as a very important aspect.
It's, it's one of the music, but like good
sounds like mastering and like
levels and shit.
It's like, um, it's like editing, you know,
the best editing is invisible and you don't
even notice it.
Sound editing.
Good, good, good sound editing you don't
even think about.
But when, when it's fucked up, you're like,
Oh God.
Oh no.
What the fuck is wrong?
Yeah.
So, so what I learned is that the reason
there are so many weird like changes that
didn't make sense or things missing is
because this wasn't a remake of the original
game.
It was a remaster of the Wii remake, which
was bad.
Um, hmm.
What was it originally on?
It was originally on the PlayStation 1.
Came out in 1997.
Uh, it looks so lovely.
Yeah, the small amount of pixels.
Yeah.
Perfect.
But like, has it been, has it been two weeks
since I, since I talked about Mega Man
Legends or was that last week?
Maybe.
I don't know.
I haven't watched, uh, I haven't listened to.
No, that would have been two, yeah.
It's been, it's been two weeks and I still
have not gotten around to playing Legends
too.
I wanted to do it.
You should.
I will, I will.
I just haven't found the time.
But anyway.
But yeah.
That's off topic.
I'd say most of the visual changes are
like lateral or an improvement, you know,
with the exception of these last two
screenshots, which are like, I don't know
why they got rid of like the really cool
dark colors and made everything super
bright Mario colors.
I don't know what's up with that.
Yeah.
I really liked, especially in the,
especially like the purple, um,
where you see the, the triple comparison.
I, I, I, I, I'm sad.
Oh.
So, cause that was a really pretty level.
Um, so the worst offense, and this is
a rant I have for all remakes.
Why do we get rid of pre-rendered cut
scenes when we remake games?
Cause every time I've seen this,
it looks fucking worse.
And I grab a bunch of comparisons,
uh, five, in fact.
Um, and it's just, it's just fucking
bad.
It's baffling.
Yeah.
They do it in engine because they
technically can.
We can do it in engine now.
And it's like, the original looks fine.
It wasn't originally in engine.
So, or, so like, why does it need
to be in engine?
Yeah.
Because we've moved on from that.
It's a new era of gaming.
Yeah.
Is it like, is the, is the idea that
like it needs to match and like,
it just needs to have the same.
I think.
Style to it.
I think it's, it's just sort of a
general sense that at the time full
motion video was like cutting edge.
It was a way to flex that you could
now you could put things on a CD.
You could have so much space to put
movie like video files and you could
you could animate better than what
could be done in the game normally.
Um, but now that games can do so much
more, it's sort of seen as regressive
to do like a thing because it's, oh,
that's cutting edge.
But for yesteryear and it's like,
it's like, now we do this thing.
I mean, like computer graphics and
animation has come so far, they could
still be cutting edge and just do like
an even better pre-rendered cutscene.
I mean, they could.
It's very time intensive because you
have to like storyboard it and like
think about it.
It's already thought about just do
what they already did.
Well, first, I mean, I mean,
why not just use the old ones?
Is the idea that they look too primitive?
I mean, what do you see on the left is
an AI upscale and it looks great.
It looks perfectly fine.
The design of the character is the same.
It's a fan-made AI upscale.
Why does he have Pac-Man on his hat?
Because Namco.
You see a gamer?
Oh, oh, I see.
It's Namco.
They put Pac-Man on his hat.
It's a little funny thing.
Oh, the second to last one is so egregious.
The guy's no expression.
Yeah, they just forgot to animate.
The first one, the first one where he's
snarling has so much more personality.
They lost so much.
Did that change?
That blows.
The little orb is so like
fucking geometric instead of
being a little like ethereal ball of light
like he was in the first one.
Yeah, some of these are just
straight downgrades.
Some of these, I think, and not even
in like a four of the time way, I would
just say straight up.
Some of these looked better.
Just straight up looked better.
And even technically, they don't look
like for all five of these videos
on a technical level, it just
looks better.
And the animation's better.
Like, for example,
in the final one, like, you know,
the flying fish, you see her actually
like swishing her tail around.
They actually put effort into animating
her moving gracefully.
And this one, it's just, they just
fast tween that are across the screen.
Yeah.
They just lazily just slapped it
together without any thought.
Yeah, I got to wonder,
like, obviously
time investment of making
like remaking a cutscene if they
didn't have the original like files or whatever
would take time. It's like, ah, we don't
want to spend time. That could be part of it.
Probably always is.
But like, how much of it is
the idea that
full motion video cutscenes that are not
rendered in engine is like
old fashioned.
We don't do them anymore.
But there's no reason
we don't do them anymore. It's just that they
are like a symbol of a different
era. I guess.
Like, do people, would the game studio
be like, wouldn't even think
to do that because, oh yeah, it's
we don't need to do that. So we won't.
There is one studio that does.
It's so frustrating that it's like
things that are invented
in video games and other
mediums, I guess, just
that they become
like.
They should be used as tools that you could
use forever.
But they get abandoned for
fashion.
Unless you're Final Fantasy
which still does pre-rendered
cutscenes and they look really great
and they still flex with that.
Yeah, Final Fantasy has always been good
with that.
Those big old things. I guess World of Warcraft
still does them. Every new
expansion. There's a film that is like a
really nicely animated
intro.
The most recent one is like, oh, that's
that's a nice little like short
film. Game looks
like it sucks because it always does.
But yeah.
That's life.
I mean, League of Legends is a good example of that.
They make all kinds of really fucking cool
amazing animations.
But the game is shit.
Yeah.
For sure.
25 years.
A difference.
And it just looks fucking so much worse.
I want pre-rendered
backdrops
to come back with static cameras.
I want pre-rendered cutscenes.
I think
it's like we couldn't do
such good cutscenes
in engine.
And so like the new flex
has been to do them in engine.
And now people are just getting
lazy with it and doing this
Klanowa thing.
They've forgotten where
who they are.
What are they fighting for?
Why go through
the trouble of a redo if you're just going to be
lazy about it?
If you're just like going to make it like
you're not going to even try.
I could see doing it if you thought
like, oh, I've got to, we could surpass
the original. We can make it look better.
But it doesn't really look like they even tried.
So.
I can't think of really any remake
off the top of my head that did
do it because they could try.
They wanted to try and make it better.
I think it's almost always
like, I mean we can cash in on the brand
recognition on this one.
Just do it again.
That's always how it is.
I don't know if Klanowa is
like a super hot license.
I mean, it's our license.
It's a thing people know.
And so it's easier than making an entirely
new game. I have heard of it.
Try to market that.
The one good thing I
can say about the remake is just
it is hurt by the mixing, but
the soundtrack sounds better
whenever.
Original composer still on the
still on board. I found his YouTube channel.
He does little remixes of Klanowa stuff
every so often. He just has a YouTube channel.
And that's sweet. He made
my favorite soundtracks of all time.
Yeah, the original composer.
Wow. Cool.
He just has a YouTube channel.
He's a cool guy.
I'll just link his channel, I guess.
It's
Kota Takahashi.
It's not
a remake.
It's more of a demake, but I decided
just to see what was up.
I decided to play
DOS PC
Mega Man games.
You ever seen those?
Oh, I have seen those.
I think...
Are they canon? Are they different?
I...
I guess I don't see why they wouldn't
be canon, because
they were officially licensed.
I mean, they're not mentioned anywhere.
They are very
strange. You could tell that
it was not made by the team.
The
bosses
have terrible AI. They mostly just
hop. They mostly just hop back
and forth and occasionally shoot off a bullet.
They do not look
like robot masters at all, basically.
All their
in-game
portrait sprites are just sloppy edits
of ones from the real games.
There's no
music.
There's barely any sound...
There are sound effects, but they suck.
And the game's too fucking hard.
I played it with...
Fortunately, the game has built
an invincibility code, so I just enabled
those and played through. And I still got
stuck at a couple of places.
Wily's Castle
in Mega Man 3, the robots
are revolting.
Actually, it has parts where the platforming
is so...
There's a part where you are
on these pillars, and you have to jump from pillar
to pillar over this vat of
green bubbling goo or something.
Looked amazing,
obviously.
But...
I don't know
what was going on, but the frame
rate of the game would change
depending on where I was standing.
So sometimes I would make a jump
and the frame rate would just double.
Just for the length of the jump.
And I would obviously misjudge the length
of the jump and dive because the frame rate
was inconsistent.
So that was infuriating.
And it took me an hour to get past
that part. No, maybe not an hour.
But even with
no damage enabled, I still
couldn't beat that part, and I had to
replay the level like a dozen times.
Because it was too hard.
Fucking...
Wait, let me show you.
Mega Man, the robots are
revolting.
Look at Shark Man.
Whoa, he's a
shark eating a man.
He's a Shark Man.
Who's the second on the left?
The blue guy?
Wave Man.
Because he's a wave?
I don't know.
I guess he's underwater, but a lot of the levels
are in water.
Torch Man is the bottom guy.
And his weakness is Water Wave
from Wave Man.
But when you fight Torch Man, his arena
is underwater.
But there is water in his arena
and you're standing in several feet of water.
So I don't know
what's going on there.
Anyway, these were really
bad.
They're really hard though.
Maybe if it was back in
1999 or whatever the fuck
this was released and all you had was DOS.
This would give you a stiff challenge
that would probably take you
days or weeks
to successfully get through without
that no damage code.
So I mean, if you're just looking for a
stiff platforming challenge, I mean
this would provide that.
Also the levels were really big.
I got you a stiff platforming challenge right here.
Not the first one, because there's two.
There's Mega Man for PC
and then there's Mega Man 3, the robots are
revolting for PC. And there's no two
for some reason.
But the second one
Mega Man 3 actually has
really big levels that you can
get lost in and explore. I think in
Wave Man Stage
you're swimming through these coral reefs
and it actually felt huge
and I was like, wow.
It's actually not
totally terrible. Technology sure is amazing.
There's one or two good
positive things I could say about this
terrible game
which I think was just made by one
American guy
who
must have had some
Capcom association
and they were like, hey, you're an American.
Make some fucking PC ports
of our franchise, please.
And he said, oh, okay.
And he did. And it was great.
Um, okay.
I'm sorry. I guess I will.
Um,
yes, that was funny.
Uh,
that's it.
The last thing I have to say
about this week is that
my stupid, evil,
terrible landlord
has ordered
fucking work be done.
All throughout the week
I have to deal with fucking people
in my house
like doing construction
stuff.
And they keep like,
they keep suggesting to me
that they're going to need to work in my room
and then not
actually doing it.
And I hate that.
They say,
what do they say to you to suggest that?
Okay. Well, a couple of times a guy has been
like, hey, can I come in? I need to measure your room.
And I'm like, okay. And he comes in and he puts
the tape measure up and he measures how wide the room
is and he's like, okay. And then he leaves.
And then he'll say like, hey, we're going to need to come in here
like soon or like one of these days
we're going to be in here. And one time he said,
yeah, we're going to need to work in here.
He said, uh, next week,
he said, next week we're going to be in here
to work on this room. And I said,
okay. And then
the next like, like the next day
a guy came and he was like, hey, we need to work
in here. And I'm like, the other guy said
next week. And he was like,
yeah, okay. And then he left.
And I was like, all right.
And then the next day, my landlord came
and knocked on my door and was like,
Ben, you know, when these guys need to
work in your room, you know, we need to
we need to, you need to be letting these guys
work in their room. And then she did, she did
the stupid thing she does where she, she like tries
to deflect and like she tries to
she tries to get her way by
using sympathy for other people. She says,
you know, I feel bad for these guys. They're just
trying to do their jobs. I feel bad for these
guys. They're just trying to do their jobs in here.
And they just, they need to, and I'm like, okay,
okay, okay, okay. And, and
I don't know. So I just
so she, she told me like tomorrow,
she told me like tomorrow, these guys are going to come in here
and I'm like, fine, like, yeah, fine.
It just, I just want to know in advance.
But so she told me, okay.
And then so
she said, like, keep this wall clear so
they can work on this side of the room. And I said, okay.
So then I cleared a bunch of
stuff and I moved stuff so the wall is clear.
And then the next day,
nobody came and nobody did anything
in my room. So
I don't know. You scared
you was, you were too powerful. I didn't do it.
Those, those poor little builders,
they, they were
intimidated by the big mean Ben St.
saying, okay, I was
ready though. Okay. I was ready
because I'm like, all right, well
if these guys are going to be in here and they're going to work in my room, that means
I can't do anything. So I'm going to take this
opportunity to go to the post
office and mail a bunch of packages I've been meaning to
mail.
So I packed up my bag and I'm like, I got
my bag ready as soon as they come and they're like, hey,
we got to work in here. I'm going to be like, okay.
And then I'm going to get on the bus and I'm going to go to the post
office and maybe by the time I get back, they'll be done.
And won't that be cool.
And then they didn't do it.
So like, I mean,
I got my bag still packed here.
It's got bottles of slime and stuff in it.
Undelivered road to rad
cons and stuff like that.
So I'm just
maybe, maybe tomorrow
they'll do that. And then I'll
go to the post office when they come
and work on my, they got to install.
Apparently they're installing, they're taking
out like steam radiators and they're
installing like,
you know, like the heaters that are like
a strip of metal across like the
bottom of the
corner of the wall. You know what I mean?
Yeah, they're installing some shit
like that.
They're updating the discussing
old-fashioned radiators that we got
in here. That's what they're doing.
Which is fine.
My stupid idiot
roommate who I hate
who sucks in his bad
and he asked me for money
for no
sensible reason.
So I'll never forgive him for that.
He walked by
and I think I've mentioned that adjacent
to my room is another room that has no windows.
It's like a horrible little
little cave.
Yeah, I've seen it.
Oh, that's right. Oh, that's right. Yeah, you were here.
Yeah.
So I don't go in there
but like this idiot
like I'm in the kitchen
and he walks through the kitchen and he's like
something
mumbles something and I'm like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And he looks in that cave
and he sees the
like they put in the fucking
they put the fucking new radiator in
and he's like, oh, that's a big improvement.
That looks like a really big improvement.
And of course I just
I hate this guy and I want to leave me alone
and I nod and I go, yeah, yeah, yeah.
On the inside, I'm like, you fucking
you mongrel, you've fucking
you what is wrong with you?
How could you look at this room
and say, oh, yeah, it looks good. Oh, yeah, big improvement.
No, you freak.
Trying so hard to make small
I hate
all I could think of was like, that is a radiator
in here and that's something
this is the guy I've probably
complained about it before. This is the guy who said
that one of
a guy who used to live here wants us
to send him money
to pay for utilities
like suppose like he said, oh, yeah, the guys
he's still paying the utility bill for this place
even though he doesn't live here. So like
can I have some money to like send to him
and I pulled out my gun and I shot
him. I shot him six.
So I pulled out a knife and I said, don't be scared.
Just a little kitty cat and I jumped on him and stabbed him
in the liver.
And then he shot him four times
through the eye.
Well, twice. It made four
entrance wounds and exit wounds.
Yeah, so two
Yeah, so two clean shots
in the eye, two shots in the eye
and it was clean kill, clean kill
or so I thought, but then he
but then he came back and he started
and he wandered around the place like a zombie
and he said, oh, hey, Ben
where's that bow that where that bow and arrow
you have before like where'd you get that bow and
arrow?
That's it.
That part was so odd like
to conflate a projectile
weapon with a bow and arrow
instead of a gun, which is so much more
common. Yeah, you would think be having.
Yeah, you would think and apparently
the guy like he owned guns
like this is not a guy who was like he owned
his own guns and yet
in trying to recall what happened
he mentions
Yeah, he mentions he mentions bow and
arrow before he mentions a gun.
He forgets what a gun is
like it's pretty interesting how the brain
works if you've got like a storage
thing of like, OK, so what should
stuff projectile weapons
and you've got a list and it starts
with bow and arrow and he just picks that
very counterintuitive. I like you have
like we in the modern day have such a
more visceral like
fucking experience
with guns.
I feel like
if your brain were like
randomly trying to pull
firing neurons and you were trying to
pull the concept of a projectile
weapon, you would more naturally
call something else a gun
than you would call a gun
some fucking weird shit
like a bow and arrow. Maybe
you was thinking alphabetically.
That's probably it.
Anyway, fucking
can't wait to send
cannot wait to send these packages. Some
of them I have owed people for months
and months and I'm sorry
I'm sorry
I'm sorry I
I'm almost
I'm almost done with the fucking
putting the files
together for this slime and punishment
book. The lady
the Alibaba lady is so
unhelpful. She takes
like
a day or more to get back to me
about very simple requests
for very obvious information
that I ought to have
and she sent me the wrong
template.
I asked for the page template
to set the pages up and she sent me
the correct page templates
but the wrong cover template
she sent me the template for a hard cover
even though it's a soft cover book. So I had
to ask her two days ago I sent her like
hey could you send me the right template so I can actually
finish making this thing and she hasn't gotten back
to me yet. So
that's not helping.
I'm
trying to make it clear to her that I'm almost
done. I'm almost ready to send your
company some money. So
if you could please help me
get there with it.
I used Alibaba
for the Lord of Ghost pins
and I think
just because there's so many
competing companies
of that type in China
that they probably
skimp on like
costs wherever they can. So like
the translation I'm assuming
is not like the best.
It takes a while for them to really
understand what I'm asking for them.
I don't know if that's the case.
This lady doesn't seem to have any
trouble like speaking or understanding
English. But I don't know.
She could be
having to consult
with an English speaking co-worker
between responses
to me. I don't know
it's possible.
It's going to be
different but at least for
pins. There was like so many
companies that make pins and they were all
yelling in broken English
giving me like I put my
thing up like I need
enamel pins of this size of this amount
and you get like
messages from everyone who's selling
that saying choose us choose us. Here's what
we have. You can do that.
You can like post a request for like
here's what I need made.
Yeah. Instead of
being the seller
of something you can
say I'm looking for this type of thing
and then you'd get DMs
from people selling that type of thing saying
choose me choose me. Huh.
That's what I did for the thing.
I didn't really know how I was supposed to do it
so that worked. I just
like I just like
I browsed products and I
found like companies
that were selling products similar to what I was
looking for and I would just I would just send
messages to them being like here's what I need
can you do it.
It's interesting.
Did you use you
didn't use the company that I used for
the DMs from them did you.
I don't think so.
I just I don't
remember asking you exactly what company
it was. Right.
I just found something
that was like it seems like good quality
cheap.
Like professional enough to be like
I could I could probably trust that they would
do it. They did actually get them very
quick to me which is nice.
That's not it took me I mean well
I mean when I did the rfck one I had to do
like they had like 20 different designs that I had
to yeah that would have been
a lot more different yeah
it took forever
hmm
what are we talking about. Oh
slime punishment templates yeah it's
pretty it's pretty close to being I've been drawing
the cover.
I've been drawing
me let me you know what
I'm sort of I'm sort of going
back and forth on what I think the cover is
going to look like but here's sort of
like this is kind of halfway
to being done
and like it's probably going to look something
like this I'm probably going to redraw a bunch
of it but like I think it's
kind of I think it's
alright I think it's getting there
I'm actually not sure about nightstar in
the background I don't know if we if it really
needs her
I think nightstar's
positioning is a bit weird yeah
yeah she's covered
yeah yeah yeah she's kind of obscured
in this it's you know what it is
it's because I put her in the I put her
in the sky and then I kind of
like moved phantom around
and then I added the buildings at the bottom
as kind of like a later
addition so yeah the
positioning does not account for any
of that so yeah this is not
also she would
probably have a different sort of like filter
effect on her
this is not final
this is not final yes yes
understood anyway but I've been
this is
one of the last things I need to get done is just finish
this
slime and or punishment please
yes yes right away
wishes my command
instead of trick or treating
you say slime or punishment
I ordered
I'm hoping it won't be some annoying
shit where like I order it
and then they're like okay I will send you the proof
copies and then
like I move in between
when they send it
like I'm hoping it gets here before I move
so they don't have to like
worry about it coming to the wrong address or anything
like that
could you do you not have the
p.o. box anymore I do not
no the old my old p.o. box expired
which is why a bunch
of a
a couple of not probably not that many but a
few of my
a road to red con and pleading with blue rays
might have ended up lost in the mail because
if I got any returns
past like February they would have had nowhere to go
because my p.o. box was expired
but
yeah I need I need to make a new one
but I haven't I haven't made a new one yet
also I'm not even
sure
they would send it in a box and I'm not sure you could send
a
you could it wouldn't fit in the p.o. box
but they would probably just keep it there and like put
a slip in the box and then you could
go and like pick up the slip and they would
find the package in a in the back room
or something I think that's how it works
yeah getting a new p.o. box
is just one of those things that I've needed
to do for a while and I haven't gotten around to it
oops
whoopsie
my gosh Ben is you should maybe should do
that for when I go
to the post office when they
finally get around
to doing some work in my room
whoa
what I think that was me
you mentioned you I heard
talking about sign punishment and it reminded
me of like an extra topic I'd forgotten about
oh you finished but I do want to bring
something cool up because I just type
something in and I'm getting crazy cool images
that you might like uh no I think I was
I'm pretty much done with what I had to
say about that
okay
surprise topic I just remembered I've been fucking
around with an AI
that recently became publicly available
called mid journey
yeah
I just put an image in chat of something I just
generated with it
you know inspired
by the rfck
colors
wait what did you put in
what did you type
well at first I typed
slime and punishment but the
result
so I'll post that result
that result didn't have the right color scheme
that looks awesome holy fuck
so when I'm like I need the right color
so I said green slime
and purple punishment
over slime city cathedral
and then I got the
first result there
these mid journeys
this is
it's just free you just do it
um it's the first
I think the first 20 are free
and then you have to pay
$10 a month and then you get like 200
I gave an ever prompt
a week ago this
I wonder if you could guess what the prompt for this
image is wait a minute this is
patreon.com
you're on the right track because of the
orange that's what I thought I was gonna say
it looks like um
uh oh god what's that
fucking video game
about space bloodborne oh
I don't know
could be a lot
the one about the procedurally generated
planets
out of worlds
no that's not procedurally generated
I don't know oh no man's sky
yeah
is it no man's sky something
uh no the prompt is
would you trust ben saint
so I was right
that is what they think ben saint is
because you're a saint
it gave him a halo because he's a saint
I guess
wait is it
is it orange because of my association with patreon
is that somehow
like a factor again
I have to assume
that halo looks
so
it kind of does look like the old patreon logo
honestly
it does kind of
what I've noticed from the journey
it can't be
gotta be coincidence
it is an exceptionally
exceptionally good
ideas machine more than anything else
because the results are always
going to be a bit funky they're always going to be a bit weird looking
but there's just some really cool stuff
I think
I was talking with four eyes
maybe a few nights ago
and he suggested
why don't you type in earth bound
these
I'm like
oh yeah
let's see how that goes
let me post
those results they were all very different
I actually
have the AI upscaled them because all four of them
looked so fucking cool
I'm just checking posting in the right order
these four images
that are loading
and there they are
it's just really cool
shit
let me see here
this is concept art for video game
this is like really really good
yeah quality
say goodbye
artists of human
yeah fuck artists
I knew we'd get rid of them one of these days
no
this is just another tool that artists can use
to like help them
think of more
ways to tackle their ideas
that's what they told
John Henry
about the train
train track laying machine
and he died
you ran over by a train
head crushed by a train
that's the guy
that died
to prove that he was a better railroad worker
than the machine
like he would lay track real quick
something like that
right?
he wanted to prove it
his big brain
could lay on a track and when a train ran over
his skull the train would be destroyed
and he would lay it off
I swear this is not
this is a real
well it's not a real thing to happen
possibly I mean
I don't have enough
I'm not getting enough information
it was a great victory for the proletariat
labor one
so there
the second one you posted is
like berserk
the what's it called
when
Griffith uses the behelit for the first time
the eclipse
that's like eclipse core
like writhing
massive flesh as the ground
and like towering things
it's like what
I wonder if this can do cute stuff
I feel like this is like a
like a vibe
that this is good at
but it couldn't like create a give and take image
I don't think
that's a great question
yeah maybe not
say goodbye ai you suck
you can't make my job
defunct
well I asked it to generate minions once
and it was really terrifying to be honest
ask it to do a realistic pokemon in real life
yes please
there's some more
rfck looking
rfck looking one like the bottom right quite a bit
just for slime
all over the cathedral there
I am
good stuff
I'm hastily photo editing
this one of me
because I like it
alright I can probably do better
probably do better than this later
this will do for now
this is going to be my new discord
avatar
hell yeah
I'll leave you with a funny one
to round that off so this is
great yellow minions devour the holy spirit
of the united states
oh I'm looking at some of these other ones
you posted previously
some of these are very hollow knight
like the big white skulls
with the holes in them
oh yeah maybe
those are all results from the earthbound
gigas
those ones
minions
what's going on
what's going on with these
I like the sort of weird smoke
in the first one
I don't know it's like
radiating off of this one-eyed
american shield
minion
captain america
yeah I think these are
definitely a vibe going on here
and I'm thinking that maybe this
program has sort of a
bias towards
painted
yeah it's a bias towards
like painterly surrealist heart
seems to be it's
you couldn't make
although I am curious
like if I typed in briska
what would it do
yeah
I could type in briska
briska circuit relaxing
after a long day of
being my girlfriend
that's a good one
you should make
you should make a visual novel called that
that's just briska like sitting in a hammock
and you just talk to her
explain like hi honey
how was being my girlfriend today
oh it was wonderful
I have to wonder
if the word
girlfriend is banned or not
they ban a lot of NSFW words
or anything suggestive
degeneracy
we can't let our children be exposed to
it says it's running
it says it's running we'll see
what happens with it
this is fucking elden ring them snakes
the roots of the heirs tree
the root of all snakes
it's true
these rfck ones I'm posting
in the community service
I can upscale any of them
this last one
please do
this last one of the two cathedrals
next to each other
the two cathedrals bottom right
right
that one on the right
I'll upscale that one for you
these rule
can you upscale the first
one too
I love all eight of these
I can upscale all eight of them
I'll do it
that would make me really happy
the top right in that second
thing the green one
reminds me a lot of
new lando ruins
in Dark Souls 1
I don't know why because it's blue in that game
but it just sort of feels like this is the underneath
this is like a secret
extra cathedral in the sewers
under
and Wacacom
proper
these are like
maybe it's the
you know as we know
from slime and punishment
the
the de-slimed alpha city was crushed
underneath
the re-slimifying beta
time line version
maybe these are the ruins
underneath of the old alpha city
where the slime from above
went back down
into it
it's Frisca there she is
she's got so many legs
she does
but does she have eight
wait wait
I gotta see this
I gotta tell the guys
wait a minute
okay
like obviously when you google frisca circuit
it would come up with different types of images
so this is like more bright
colorful I like that the color
is correct
with the orange
I can tell where
the source of things this would pull from
these are so
these are so weird and uncanny
yeah
AI is still a little difficult
it's difficult for an AI to like
figure out how to make a cartoon character
the multiple different artists draw
this thing cannot construct
a body
yeah
this thing can do
like organic shapes
and like symmetrical
creatures and it can do like
abstract sort of like
distance shots
scenery sort of
atmospheric
this is
did you
include the colors is it
like it knew the colors
frisca
it found complementary colors on its own
yeah
like again the text
to put above that one is exactly what I typed in
like you can type in like super vague shit
like scariest thing ever
and you'll like see really like creepy shit
and it'll just come up with stuff
it's just
this face
on the bottom right one
it's the one horn
smug grin
yeah the one macaroni horn
wait wait wait
shit how do we get to this thing
it's called mid journey
it runs on discord
there's actually a discord server
so you have to like
go to your website sign up
and then you can join your discord server
and the server has like a hundred channels
that are getting used by like a hundred people
each constantly
and it's a real cluster fuck
and it's hard to like find your images
because I get drowned out by everyone else's
you can like
if you pay them
like ten dollars a month
which is what I decided to do because I just have a lot of fun with it
you can
interact with their bot via discord dms
which is what I'm doing right now
yeah that sounds like a lot
more
less annoying than
the thing I'm being bombarded with
plus there is an arbitrary limit
which is nice to know
you know what
I do like
AI
like image creation
but I feel like on discord
I don't want to be on discord
I want to leave
leave server
I want to leave yeah same
why did you leave
server just don't
just leave me alone
go on
I can't stand
because there's no
it's never clear where you're supposed to go
you left my server
you traitor
you left me to die
I left your server because
it pulls me into like
annoying arguments
hell yeah
and like petty bullshit about tricksy
and I'm like you know what
I'd rather just never hear about anything
and it's great
I like to gossip
it's not even just you
it's just like the atmosphere there
that's the thing people do now
I like people in there
so it's not like a personal thing
I don't like that I keep checking
the server
because I get so upset sometimes
it's not good for me
I get it
some people in there like to just come in here
with like hey here's some really annoying
here's some really infuriating shit
that I saw
it's fine I understand
hang on
I'm applying more color filters
this cool portrait of me
that's my
I could like
try to have the AI just generate one
like dark robed
man with the power
of slime green halo
purple sky sort of thing
it could like come up with something like that
I mean
don't let me stop
I'll send it to you
and DMs when I do
it's taking a while to upscale all 8 of these
things from earlier
I guess
I'll just
I can bring up the last thing I want to mention
which is a YouTube channel that I
remembered exists
because
working on more
it's called Hippocrates
my favorite
this is a more obscure
less or known channel that
me and my friends stumbled across
on fucking new years
going from 2018 to 2019
we were all playing Minecraft
because I'm now sampling
older Minecraft recordings
for son of a glitch
and oh my god so
there's this channel
I don't remember which one of us found it
I haven't watched the recording in detail
because it's like five hours long but
we just found this YouTube channel that just has
a very specific fixation
I kind of like don't even know
like where to begin with this shit
so I'm just gonna
post images
of YouTube thumbnails that they
have
when Jason was
at the table I kept on seeing him look up at me
while he was
with that older girl
what
huh
giant pooping fox
three dimensional dogs
what's inside a dog's butthole
an educational
Minecraft video for kids
what the fuck hang on
in this kid friendly swear free video
I tell you and your kids what's inside a
dog's rectum
this video is fun for the whole family
oh
Steve from Minecraft
has a really nice house
uh oh
I don't like
I mean I can just from the context that
thumbnail is placed in
Minecraft fox buttholes texture
back
wow
fox
for oral anal unbirth
cock nasal
oh this one's got a lot of views
yeah
so this channel
somehow still exists somehow
being like destroyed for
some kind of violation but um
this is making me do the
the fucking um
Matthew McConaughey looking
at his phone while he
takes a drag on his cigarette with
a deranged look in his eye
face
so this person likes the inside
of canine buttholes
and he wants to live in one
uh presumably
and he put his Minecraft
skills to
to the test and built
I'm assuming a giant fox that he
can crawl inside and pretend he was
bored in Minecraft
and then come out the butthole
he's also a video game developer
hmm
and he's developing a video game we go inside
of dogs butthole
cool epic for game
um
so back on that new years
nearly you know
I convinced made to
download his game and play it
and it's an absolute fucking
it's an absolute clusterfuck
it's like an RPG maker style
game where you're a fox and you walk around
and it's like haha you found
rabbits xd lol
xd epic rabbits haha
put in inventory
and the inventory is your butthole
and so it's like you have 11 rabbits
in your inventory your inventory is full
will you poop one out to make room
is this by this is by the same guy right
this is by the same guy
and like the entire game all of the menus
and everything is hot little epic random
xd like it's all
so I was right yeah put rabbits in
your butthole yeah rabbits down your hole
exactly and we were
just like looking at this guy's fucking
channel and then made like played his video
game we were just fucking screaming
we were screaming
while he was playing it
um
fucking
epic random
lol cool epic
like that's like a
that's like um
a speak from a type of
god I can't speak
my throat hurts
um
drinks to stay
early 2000s I'm gonna
stay hydrate I'm gonna hydrate right now
wow you better
yeah
uh
early 2000s
like internet speak yeah
but like this is only
five years old so is he
associating that that kind of thing with like
like
I can has cheeseburger that means
and dog means here's what I think
this is a case this is what it what it means
to be a fox that is you talk like
you're from the early 2000s on a
forum here's here's what I think I think
this is an I think this is an adult
with this kind of arrested within
with an arrested development who is
talking in the way that he
maybe feels like a child
or a or a younger
person talks I think
he's doing it as sort of a like an
affect like a cute affect
just maybe for fun
so and but to him that's like oh yeah
that's the way you would the way
that a kid from 2000
and five would talk
right uh
so possibly
yeah
quite possibly
they're still they're still doing stuff
their last video was three months ago and it's like
you remat they remastered
their game they remastered it apparently
um
they're still going at it after all this time
sit
I just thought you should know that this person
exists and live with that
knowledge um yeah
well definitely like you're
coming soon
ah
mmm
nice I'm still I'm still applying
the perfect the perfect
color filters
gotta get the perfect color filters on my
sweet now
you know what it's fine sweet ass
sweet ass actually
you know what it's perfect just the way it is
uh
change avatar here we go
I just noticed you change your avatar to the
the AI
yeah I love it
you're a triangle man
or a diamond triangle man
triangle man
triangle man would you trust
particle man
I would yeah
I think he I think I feel
like he gets me
we're on we're on a wavelength
uh what is this
this is this looks like uh like
album you know album covers I'm gonna put this
in the chat just for um for
Eleazar to show what my new uh
frickin what my new at my new avi
looks like because I like hey
the video is pretty good
PCP viewers might be curious
what we're talking about it
ooh where do you
spiders come from yeah so
above the avatar of the spiders that stuff
I generated for my friend
iracubus she
is a vtuber friend of mine
who's cool yes a vtuber
ben you've met your match
um yeah
that's the thing the thing about me
is that those make me angry
it's
not yeah it's not true
this is a false
allegation against me I beat the charges
I just
wanted to make cool a spidery imagery
and these look
I
some honestly
some of these do feel like okay well
there's a certain kind of artist that is just
out of work now
yes yeah
Tony spent
yeah these do look
which ones I can't
I can't choose though the one with the
middle middle right
with the crown
rules oh yeah that's
a good one yeah the two the two
drawn to the to the bottom
middle right
just because of the
napkin that's bleeding pink into it
with the eyes
I feel like any one of these
that's like blown up it's like a vinyl
record album cover it'll be like oh
that's so fucking sick I wonder what
it is I'm gonna buy it the one the one
listen to it the one just to the left
of that one that it looks sort of like a
dead spider like set inside of like a
diamond and there's like human
blonde human hair flowing
down I have it oh my oh man
oh man
these are so good
give me
give me a break
okay
this is a yeah
for a certain genre of image this
AI really
he's really it's really
it's really delivering yeah
I guess like ten bucks a month there's
not that much if you needed to like a
commission an artist to make a thing
like like this take
time it would not take
like five minutes and it would take
more than ten dollars the thing to notice
about this is right now the upscaling
isn't great
for example I can
put a few of these so like in that collage
of all the spider imagery the top left you have the
the woman's face with like the
the crown floating above it
and there's like spider webs linking everything
together when you scale it all the
all the like the thin spider waves disappear
like the AI just like forgets what
they are and doesn't know what to do
with them you know yeah I'm opening
it in a different tab I'm zooming
in the
the closer you get to it the less impressive
it seems yeah
yeah
that makes sense still nice still
still good like for inspiration
it's very good for like inspiration
and it will
get better
which is better
or worse for us maybe I feel like
overall I mean for me
I'm always going to be drawing like bad
like comparatively
like my art style is like silly and goofy
and cute but I don't feel like
AI
is like it's like an industry
forwarded by people who
like that thing they want to make
the most realistic
this is what they're probably driving for
generally it's like
can we recreate a perfectly
human person
just with a computer in 2 seconds
they're not really wondering
whether we can draw like a stick figure
in the same time because it's easier
so I'll be alright
yeah I'll be alright because
every one of these AI things
across the board has like
no big huge boobies
no porn whatsoever
nothing the words fuck
and shit
and succubus
and boob all banned
all of them in the trash you can't type those words in
or we'll ban your account
I can only imagine
how fucking horrifying the results
of trying to make porn
with this thing would be
I think I would throw
I think cheesy was trying to make
porn with that
with Dolly
yeah
I did not have great results
but these would be
so much worse
I did things that they would probably
be able to recreate
typing in porn
I don't want to see what it thinks porn is
but like oh Bikini Babe
it could figure that out
and it could do like oh huge butt
like yeah that's doable
the faces were all fucked up
and you know
not really a thing but I could
choose one of those and be like
I could base of drawing off of that
that's not even that bad
I think you're right
it's the future
I'm the future baby
what time is it
it is
wow we've only been
hit with a wave of tiredness
damn okay
like I said I didn't sleep that well last night
because I was up
what's the word
just enthralled
by the slenderman
the slenderman stabbers
they are so infalling
I've been
I've been like tired
like fatigued
from camp
it's been a pretty
chill camp
all things considered because coronavirus
obviously couldn't do it
for a year
I got home
I got home yesterday
and I had a huge
nap
that I didn't expect I would have
and I woke up later that night
and I'm like you know
alright
I guess it wasn't night time
it was just getting dark
and then today
we were going to have the meet up
we went to the pub
we talked about some stuff
and then I came back
and I'm like
alright I'm gonna go
to bed
and I nearly missed the procrastinated podcast
that would have been
such a long time
that would have been really fucked up
hmm
yeah I still feel like my legs don't work
like I've been walking because we're in a field
you gotta
if you need to get anything
you need to walk all the way across the field
every time
there's a lot of walking
my legs hurt
well they don't hurt but they feel like
they have less power and I keep
losing my balance
hmm
I gotta sleep more
I gotta get a big sleep on
saw
saw a tweet
saw a tweet from
what's her name
that was like when I lay down in a comfy bed
you know I'm gonna be on my
me-me-me-me-me and honk-shoe
honk-shoe type shit
that's what I think you were
on
you know what I'm saying
I don't know what you mean
like cartoons, cartoon sleep sound effects
me-me-me-me-me-me
honk-shoe
shoe
me-me-me-me-me-me
yes
um
I'm hitting myself stop hitting myself
stop hitting myself
stop hitting yourself
I did
I did do you want to do
do you want to go to voicemails
sure yeah we've been going
for almost two hours okay
um sure
well uh let's uh
let me get them where did I where did I
put them where did I put those little guys
there they are
the first voicemail
is
okay well it's it's just a question
what if you and
no sorry
it's
what if you invite a former pcp just for one episode
I don't know then they'd be on for one episode
okay that that was terrible never mind
sorry
okay
I'm stalling
I'm stalling because I can't find the link okay here we go
uh
this one is called
about a meme
alright three two one go
so since this is probably
just the best use of my time
to talk about an already
obsolete meme with
um my favorite internet
micro celebrity uh Ben
about the garlic bread
meme
obviously the joke
although not very cool or original
is that garlic bread
is a more well endowed version
of the original
normal bread
just like the woman with the big titties
is a more well endowed
version of the woman
with the smaller boobs
even though I realize
that that is somewhat
sexist and
in keeping with gender
norms and why am I
talking about this
what am I doing with my life
I get it
no listen I get
that the meme was like
I don't know
I guess it was just pointing out like
girl
there's one thing
like you have bread and you have girl
a bread with
extra is garlic bread
girl with extra is big boob
girl so it's like
a big boob girl is like a girl
with extra
some extra goodness on there and like
I get it
I just think it's a very banal
observation to the point that it's irritating
to say it
it's almost like
saying I like garlic bread
like image finished
or I like
boobs
it's like almost a facebook
boomer meme
I think that's
pretty much how I feel about it
I did get it
I didn't like it
I thought it was a stupid
or it could be that they think the girls
with big boobs stink
I don't like them
I do like garlic bread
and I don't like big boobs
so I said no
that seems incorrect
they got it wrong
they fucked it up
next one
is called hypocrisy
three two one go
people always ask
where
is Nate
where is Tom Oliver
where is
Trixie
but no one ever asks
where
is Ben Saint
I want to
go kill him
it's a travesty
he's right
he's so
right
where are your fingers
and why are they around Ben Saint's
road
I
all I want to know
is where is the podcast
where is
I have still not uploaded
any more stuff
to the
apps because I still don't know
if anything there is to be done
about the fact that new posts
delete the old ones
I think we just
have it be the
latest episodes
that are an option
and if people really want to go back
they'll have to go to YouTube
you already
can't listen to the first 12 episodes
on
Spotify
and maybe Google podcasts
you can on the
website
you can on YouTube
and
I feel like the people who would go
back
people who get into the podcast
probably just find new episodes anyway
they don't think this is a great show
let's go to episode 1
maybe they do
maybe that helps everyone
if you did want to do that it's possible
it's just not on Spotify
whatever
you're probably right
the next one is
Slime times
weekend update
number 9
3,2,1
go
hello, hello, hello
welcome back gangsters
to the slime times weekend update
today is a little bit of a quickie
because I am too busy because of
rowdy rough house
fun fun fun party weekend
in lieu of fun party weekend
not because of it but
strangely related
there has been an update to the game
where fun has been added
to the game and the
prefix
which is normally exclamation point
can now be changed to fun
if you are holding a fun pizza
and you use the command
exclamation point fun
very, very intriguing indeed
furthermore the rough house
party weekend marks also
the end of the term of the 3 ring
leaders who will be giving up their
position and new elections will be held
finally some
interesting ARG figures
have appeared in the city among whom
are mysterious D of
strange seemingly former slime
corp employee and mainframe
a weird
AI computer
thingy magic
I don't understand technology
okay ta ta
yeah fun
I was aware that fun was added
to the game
I tried to have
as a stat
as a
it's more than just
a stat it's a way of life
I
was told to try to have some fun
to use the fun command
so I did I tried to use
the fun command
but I didn't have a fun pizza
so I died
even though I'm a king
which like
pretty much just was like a cataclysmic
offense
I don't been saying
the cop killer tried to have fun
but I didn't have a fun pizza
I don't know what I thought
was gonna happen
but they you know
listen I mean you know
they're working out the kinks but we're but
they're having a lot of fun with it so
it's good
I like that this yeah they're having a lot
they're having a lot of fun they were literally
having zero fun before
because fun had not been invented yet but now
the game
includes fun as one of its many
features so that's
big big
big things are happening
in rfck right now
the next level
of that joke is
for fun to be the most annoying
part of the game that nobody likes doing
but everyone feels obligated to
have fun don't be ridiculous
who would find fun annoying
it's fun that's what kind
of a killjoy would you have to be to
even suggest that fun
wasn't fun
uh
just
shit I'd fucking lost my
uh lost my mind
lost my mind lost my mind
okay the next one is just a question
Ben what do you think of the pewdiepie
twitter drama and uh
I don't know what that's referring to
I haven't I haven't heard a peep
about that so who cares
I think I did see
pewdiepie mentioned
somewhere and he
I think he was reacting
to
politician or something or he was reacting to
some
I don't know I don't know if that's what this is about
yeah I don't know what the drama is
next one is happy
birthday Ben
wait there's actually
an audio
with this one
if you will please load
my internet has been very bad
my fucking
my uh
slender man killer
interview videos they were
they were freezing
last night I was so
like no tell me more
uh okay
two one go
is that tim allen
thanks for the
thanks for the birthday wishes
um okay
next one is a question hey ben is
Nate done with making videos
uh no
I mean not like
totally done oh my god upscale
I'm gonna yeah I already
I already put the small versions
in rfck and in the community
service I will post all of these
full-size versions later
you absolutely
can
the fucking slime
exploding out of the cathedral is so
funny and cool these look
so good okay
that's oh thank you I appreciate it
you're welcome next
nate is not
making videos actually um
I talked to him
again
about the ova video
and he told me that he has
he has moved his
his uh his
schedule up he said he's gonna
he told me he's gonna start working on it
like like soon
like in a week or two
and he he he he he wants to do it
he wants to do it himself but he's gonna do it like soon
that's what he told me
so uh he
is making you have heard that before
I have I have heard that before
but uh we I don't know we talked about it more
extensively and
uh
I I believe
well I believe
that he
sincerely intends to do it
um
uh I don't know
I
mean
I don't
what else can you do
what else what else can I do
yeah
I mean he did he did eventually do
the uh the uh
the the the music video
on on that subject
um you've seen this
Gib drinking moth
who has sent in many a voicemail
in a fan art drinking drinking moth
has picked up a couple of uh
the dojin pages and has been
doing some of them and they look really good
I'm I'm I'm I'm impressed
I'm impressed I didn't know
if she could uh match
Ed's style and I would say
she did a great job so
I think I will maybe uh let her
do more if she wants
um damn
yeah Simsie is also working on one
he had sketched out like half
of one and I don't know how far
it is but uh
so yeah a few more pages done on that
it is getting I think there's maybe like
nine or ten maybe about
ten pages left to go after all that so
that'll be fun it's gonna be
finished it will actually be finished
and I'll I'll print it
and it'll have credits it'll have all the
writers credits and all the artists credits
on the inside cover probably and it will be
fun
I can't wait to
put that next to my road to
retcon book yeah yeah
uh
next one is called hey Ben
are you excited for Kimi no
Moa so Miki day
Saito D I don't know what any of this
means
do you do you know what this is
I mean especially not said like that
yeah
Kimi wa
oh is it that I don't think I've seen
an anime in a hundred years
oh Kimi no now
is
is the title of your name
the movie in Japanese
oh I've not yeah I've not seen
this so I yeah
why is it like the anniversary of its
release or something yeah I haven't seen it
Lamal
I've been following Masaaki Yuasa and he's been
like tweeting
like endless gifts of
these things from
that he's like little animations he's done
and like promoting the new film he's worked on
which looks pretty cool
cool
that's a thing Masaaki Yuasa
has good gifts on twitter
follow him
it's his claim to fame
like he draws like these little animations
and just post them and repost them
and it's like yeah I like seeing that funny
man do a funny little dance
it's nice it's nice on the timeline
cool
hold on I'm opening
I'm opening up all these upscaled
images for later
okay
the next voicemail is called
well it's just called
Hi Ben
let me post the audio
oh Eleazar could use one of these upscaled
things for like the thumbnail
I just realized
oh yeah I mean
that's a good thumbnail
put the logo I think
I think it would be cool yeah
fucking fruit fly I don't know where these fruit flies
are coming from I don't keep food in my room
there's no there's no nothing
for them to eat my room and yet
one or two is just constantly
in here and I don't know why
next one is called
oh wait I just posted it
Hi Ben 3 2 1
go
oh
is this is this some bullshit
is this
I forgot that
I forgot nothing
so I still have an appointment
the doctor came out and I followed it today
and the only thing
just covert recording of their family
that's great
that's fantastic yes
what are you gonna do
more undercover videos of unsuspecting people
like
they have parents
potentially
oh no
why didn't they tell me
they have parents
next one is called thank you
or it's called t y y y y y y
3 2 1
go
why
they're typing
they're typing their message
we have to interpret from the key clacks
but they're just
it's like
like I can tell they're just running their hand over it
okay great
this one is an image
but there's also an audio
so here's the imager link
right there
breaking train strikes
rail workers have been left with no choice
but to escalate industrial action
due to the NSFW
government refusal to commit to
safety changes and decision to get
to gut family and domestic violence leave
for rail workers
okay
my brain didn't read that
but I didn't understand anything
because I'm not thinking
so there's a rail worker strike because of
government
cutbacks
government doesn't care about human beings
and that sucks
the next one
here's the audio
3 2 1 go
they're just opening the gates
oh that's cool
that's uh very cool
very good, very base
uh
nice
heartwarming
the next one is called
the stunning
buffer effect
uh
yeah the stunning buffer effect
there it is 3 2 1 go
there's some problem that you can't really seem to
get over
and maybe their heads in the right place
or they just don't have all the details
instead of trying to address the problem
you just say ah you see
you're the stunning
buffer effect
you think you know more than you know
but actually you're a complete idiot
don't you think that's interesting
and you walk away
well the thing is
you're that guy that's you
haven't attempted to like make the
problem better
you don't bring it up in an argument
to win the argument
try to teach them anything
try to mend their misunderstanding
all you've done
is try and make yourself look smarter
than you actually are by
bringing up something completely unrelated
I don't think this works
I think this guy is done in program
himself
I just thought that was interesting
this amazing idea
the Dunning Kruger effect is most
it's the Dunning Kruger effect mostly
I agree it would be stupid
if someone is
talking out their ass about something
to be like aha I have
I got you now you see
you have lost the argument because
you are Dunning Krugering
you're Dunning Krugering so hard right now
I don't know that happens the most
but I've not even
that's not the context I generally here
I don't know
maybe it happens
I'm actually slightly disappointed
because
the real interesting thing about the Dunning Kruger effect
and how it's misunderstood
a lot by people who quote it is the fact
that the graph is different
explain
okay so
it's like when someone is new to a topic
they're just getting into it
they're like oh I'm starting to understand this
wow I know everything
oh you know they think they're real smart
and all that and then
the usual graph you see is one
that looks like this right
if we'll post it's like
yeah
yeah and like it's a useful
illustrative tool
but there's actually been tests
into people's confidence
versus their actual ability
because you can test that
you can like
quiz people on like
if they think you know this topic
or that topic or this other topic
and they'll give like a response
and then you can test them
let me guess does it actually like
rise in zigzags
pretty much
very subtly zigzags
this isn't quite what I was
wait a minute but okay
what's going on here
well the actual test score is going to be a straight line
because that's just 0 to 100
right
like
I don't know it sort of just goes up
um
but I guess
you know I've seen the second one
I do
forget that this is
because like
it's the
overestimation of your ability
versus the underestimation
of your ability when you're actually more capable
than you realize
that's the main thing
the real effect is that
everyone thinks they're above 50%
even
when they're definitely not
that's the real effect that you get from this
and also at the
end where people who are really smart
like under
sell themselves a little bit
those are like the real takeaways from this I think
and I think that's interesting
I feel like these
are not totally at odds
with each other
I mean
they're not the same
but like you know you have the bottom quartile
which like
they do overestimate themselves
by the biggest amount
and then that number goes down and down
until it eventually flips
to the negative
I feel like it's exaggerated
for effect but like maybe
it gives
a wrong impression
of how much confidence
people have when they're just starting out
because it's not as higher than
the highest
the first one is sort of a PragerU
like
what units are confidence measured in
in this graph
confidence is like
loudness of voice when saying
how cool you are
decibels
I mean the first graph
could probably be true
if you limited like
your test to only people
who like have super like
big egos
and think they're super smart
because
I guess the second graph is more looking at like
an average population maybe
because most people aren't
super cocky like that
but like for people who are super cocky
maybe the first graph would apply a little bit
but the first graph is more
just like an idea
if it's an average then
it would just mean that on average
people with
lower skill
would
more likely rate themselves
much higher
than people with higher skill
I'm curious like what this test was
in because I don't think
every subject matter
is something that like everyone thinks
they're above 50%
at
I've never looked into the initial
like papers on it
well I
I got it from watching this video which
I watched quite a long time ago
they might be more information
or maybe there's a source
I guess I'm curious
about the methodology
that generated this graph and like what
yeah like what the
what was being tested exactly
is there
ability to 360 no scope
like was it like
SAT
like SAT like language
and like basic like math geometry stuff
or was it like I don't know
some kind of specialized
field and was it was the test
done among people who were involved
in that field or was it done among complete layman
who literally like didn't know anything at all
about it period
I feel like that would affect the results
like for the results to be
as good as possible
it would need to be like as broad
a range but yeah I don't know
it would who did it's like two
people it would need to be like four people
they asked it would need to be something that like
even any anyone in
the general population is at least somewhat
familiar with but that there also
exists the possibility to become
like an expert in
like
maybe something like
reading people's body language
or something like that
this is overgraph I mean
the full studies that these are from
are not linked in the description
they're just named I guess I could
we could look into it
if we wanted to be smart
boys
but I'm
what's the confidence versus accuracy
I don't entirely know I'd watch the video
but then I'd be hearing audio
and not hearing you guys
okay Elia is our
we're all just going to pause the podcast
and watch this video
and you're going to leave it
you're going to leave it all in
I'll watch this later
I'll watch it later I need a refresher
dumbass Kroger
okay the next one
is
again there's an Imgur album
plus audio so let's
see the album first
my stands
it's a JoJo thing
crystal method
this is written in
Spanish
this is cute
I like this sort of stuff I used to do this
no this exactly but
these are JoJo stands
with
their stats
potential power
speed precision durability range
movement
movement energizes the limbs and heart
making it faster but too much burns the
oh these are descriptions of what each one does
these are actually really cool designs
I like the
the second guy's sort of face
they don't really
I'm not that much of a JoJo head
I don't know what stands are
I
I haven't watched any JoJo
not that I'm complaining
but why did you send these
to our voicemail
I don't know they're proud of it
I guess
put them on a fridge
that's fair enough
let's hear the
audio maybe there's a
elaboration
here we go
alright
3, 2, 1 go
a very fun idea
to draw
have you ever tried making
stands like in JoJo
JoJo stands
I drew my own on a
or a superpower
very specific or complicated
or stupid
you make
a humanoid type
thing
maybe with the stand user beside it
like
very abstract I really like
to do it
I have one idea
stand
he has
a catch of containers
that shoots a substance
that whatever the user is thinking
whatever food he's thinking
he makes whatever
he splashes out
the thing so like
he can turn you
into a cracker and break you easily
what
he thinks of a food
it turns you into the food
he has a catch up container
but it squirts the thing you're thinking of
so it squirts out crackers
if you think about crackers
you have like a ketchup bottle
and you squeeze it
and crackers come out
it says liquid
it says a liquid substance comes out
based on a food you're thinking of
so what part of that turns you
into a cracker so he can break you
into crackers
I think it's separate from the ketchup thing
he can think of you as a food
and then like eat you as such
like you are a hot dog and then he
bites you
I mean
pretty wacky
but if you to counter it
you have to just think of yourself as really
appetizing food and then you can't bite you
do you like hummus?
oh I don't know
I can't eat you now
you foiled me
but it's not halal
nope I'm not halal
I got pork in me
I can't be hummus
you reform back into a man
next one is
where was I
Ben's Weekly Reminder play delta room chapter 2
okay Ben's Weekly Reminder
ketchup to one piece I actually
really do mean to do that
oh I need to do that as well
apparently a big image
that I want to look at
I've been seeing a lot of Yamato fan art
on Twitter lately
Yamato is so fucking cool
I didn't really
like the idea of him joining
the crew like so quick
it seemed like it happened
really fast
I mean
maybe I'll change my mind
maybe because you read it all at once
I've been reading
1.0 like weekly and so it has been
like years since it began
maybe even
a year since Yamato was introduced
on the
thing so like
I guess it did come a bit abrupt
like
I want to join but it did make
sense because
he the fucking
all of the thing
with Odin going away
and seeing the world
is like paralleled because of the
they want to be Odin
near all that
and Momo is like
like capable
of protecting himself now
I
yeah I need to
I need to get I must be like
10 or 12 chapters
behind maybe more
oh remember you're still in the fight then right
I'm like at the very I think
yeah no I have not concluded the
the fight with
Kaido just yet
so
yeah I don't know what developments
are going on with that yet
but I do
I feel like I feel like I'm missing out
by not being caught up
you should because like
I mean it's always fun
after the big events to see how the world
reacts there's some big
shit there's some big like
oh my god
I'm pogging for one piece
I can't wait for more
I think I saw some spoilers
but I forget them so
yeah whatever yeah
I don't remember what it was I saw
next butler had the one piece
the whole time
yeah
next one is called
till I draw again
but seriously scroll back
and share to Gib
uh
here's the
fuck
fucking
mouse scroll back and share to Gib
anyway
art
I don't know
I mean there's no link
there's no art link
here okay three two one go
hey Ben
I don't have any images
to share with you this week
as everything I've drawn at work
contains spoilers to the comic
the comic that is
about Gib and take visiting you
I'm sorry
until next week
oh fuck
don't forget to show Gib
these pictures
please and thank you
I don't know what they mean
aren't they
talking about the ones
I've seen the ones that happened on the podcast
I didn't see last week
was there one on last week
oh
I don't
there were ones of like me lying down with my butt
showing
the bow
oh wait is this it
I see an image or album
the first ones were Ben
but I started thinking about monkeys
yeah I don't think those were about
you
there's your butt
I will
restate again
that the new
the artist knew
if you would like to draw
anything for the
I would be overjoyed
to let you draw
a piece of it
I believe I saw their
YouTube account
make a comment
I forgot to mention it
I saw an account saying
new and I'm like oh that might be them
but I forgot to message them
so a couple of podcasts
back maybe you'll find it
maybe I'll go hunt
just to see
uh
yeah
the next one
is called
Mega Man Legendary
Characters
there we go
3, 2, 1, go
there's this guy in Mega Man 64
and if you talk to him
he's like hey did you know
and you say yes he's like oh
so you did know
if you say no he's like
oh I guess you don't know
and I think that guy is the coolest NPC
in video game history
I don't remember
I don't remember such a guy
but it sounds like
I think I've seen that
like a screenshot of that
cause that sounds familiar
I talk to
I talk to NPCs
I don't remember a guy saying anything like that
was that in Legends
64 is Legends
Legends was on the PlayStation
64 was on the N64
oh is that them
I found the comment you referenced
but there's no links
to any pages or anything here
yeah an enigma
hmm
yeah I mean
seems like if
he's got the same name so
yeah it could be
anyway
I don't know
I love you new I like your work
if you want to draw some
some of the dojin
we'd be thrilled
next one
I would have to agree
next one is called
fuck
it's called
slime times weekend update
breaking
3 2 1 go
breaking news
I say breaking news
then saint aka the cop killer
has killed himself with the fun command
and repeat he has killed himself
with the fun command
he did not have a fun pizza as per requirement
while using the fun command
and therefore perished in a horrifying manner
he then also lost
all of his kingpin slime
for an extended period of time
and the rowdies were more on top than ever
this has been an absolute win
for not only the rowdies
but for rfck in general
thank you and goodnight
hey
at least I had fun
it doesn't matter had fun
yeah yeah yeah yeah
fun had you
you know fuck slime
you know what fuck slime
I'm all about fun now
frankly there are more important things
like having fun
and that's just what I did
damn it
next one is called
slime times apologies
there it is
3 2 1 go
we at the slime times weekend update
redaction would like to
offer our sincerest apologies in our role
for the death of Ben saying that
the hands of fun and fun pizza
because we did not get
to him in time
with our new information
as to not only the introduction
but also the mechanics of the
fun and fun pizza
that being said
get wrecked
plus L plus ratio plus purple
it was
it was sabotage
damadunk who is a rowdy
try the fun command
okay
I don't know if he knew that it would kill me
I'm not sure
I'm not clear on that part
but it was all like rowdy versus killer
things was completely
ended with a little prank
a little joke
with a fun little prank like well
the other guy is dead
okay next one is
it's a vocaru link
no sorry it's not
the next one is called the joker
and batman has a chat
okay
wait
the joker
and batman has a chat
there okay
3 2 1 go
I slip and fell
on a banana peel
and the banana peel went right up my ass
except it wasn't a banana
it was a dildo
society is conspiring
to make me gay
you're wrong the joker
you put the dildo there yourself
you're gay the joker
I'm not fucking gay
shut the fuck up
then explain the cat boys I found
on your browser history
you literally fuck a cat batman
she's a pussy the joker
she's a pussy on multiple levels
that just makes you a furry
I literally dress up
as a giant bat
I'm comfortable with who I am
will you impress your true self
that's why you're the villain
I'm not gay
he's right
I guess
we can all learn something
you know what
putting a dildo up your ass isn't gay
I
it's just an accident
it's just a
it's just a prank
it's just a prank bro
dude I pranked myself
I put a dildo up there
it was so funny