Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am the best
guy ever. And today we're joined by Digilomatic Ben Saint. There he is. The slime I can hear
bubbling up deep within my veins. Munchy. Oh wow. What's now? You know. Oh wow. We've got
Tom. Tom Oliver. I'm here. Good. We've got. Oh, okay. We've got Letharora Mage. There's
a cat on my table, so excuse any cat noises. No furries allowed. The pussy is present. Yeah.
And begin the pussy jokes. And the digital booboo boy. There he is. Hey, I'm here. I'm
trying to recover my mind after a really intense 420 celebration slash Evangelion viewing party.
Oh God. It was 420 yesterday. Yeah. Indeed it was. Indeed it was. Did you see that thing
that I tweed you? A clip from Armored Shoebaccon 3 with a filter over a digi? Yes, I saw that.
I saw that. Very nice. It was looking good. But nothing about that. Oh shit. Where are they?
Where can we find animals? What are their culture? What can we learn from them? You can find
typical animal over on Dictionary Urban Dictionary.com. Dictionary Urban was my favorite
child detective novel as it's set on the mean streets of New York where Dictionary Urban. You
guys know what I'm fucking talking about? There was a cryptic, I remember that, yeah,
from that ancient children's book story. There was lots of mysterious clues left about dipping to
the whip and I had to open up my dictionary urban and find out what the fuck was going on in there.
Listen, this is terrible. Let's get down to our real shit. Is Nate breaking up or do my headphones
just suck dick? Your headphones suck dick. I bet you've got like a $5 one you'd be like oh this
will work. No, they were like 30 bucks and they're garbage. Anyway, I'm derailing. Let's fucking get
in that urban dictionary. The interest for the audience is Ben has been doing the PCP just by
turning his speakers real low this entire time. I've just been turning my speakers really low so
that my mic doesn't pick us up as an echo and it's worked brilliantly. None of you knew. None of
you knew. I fooled you all. You're not wrong. All right, here we go. UrbanDictionary.com. It's
furries, guys. Furries. So here is the top definition of furry. All right, here we go. This is a
fucking literary piece on this. Furry. There is no piece for you. There is no one single definition
of what a furry is. Even within the furry fandom, people cannot always agree on just what makes a
person a furry or not. Okay, so this guy's breaking it down. Some would argue that to be a furry,
you must think and talk like one, i.e. use furry specific words and phrases. Even if you go to
conventions, wear a food fursuit, draw the art, write the stories, etc., but don't talk using furry
lingo. This is one of those things where only within that community would they even... Would there even
be a question? Yeah, for any outsider, it's just like, do you have any interest whatsoever in
watching animalized stuff? It's like my old standby. It's like I always say, I may be attracted to
robots, you know, have had sex with a robot, fucked a robot in its tailpipe, you know, be married
to a robot and be exclusively interested in robots sexually, but at least I'm not a goddamn robo-file.
Unlike some people. I scroll down and like so many of these definitions of furry are like
incredibly extensive on Urban Dictionary. Because they're all in there trying to do PR damage
control. A constant state, a decades long state of society-wide damage control. There's a simpler
one here. I just skipped, some of these are short. Listen, furry, simply one who has interest, small
or large of anthropomorphic animals, animals who have animal colonies, be it simply talking or
having a human-like body. The next one, in the same one it says, one who has interest in
anthropomorphic animals, does not mean wanting to have sex with them. What do you mean it doesn't,
they don't want to have sex with them? That's wrong. This is just incorrect. It's like saying that
bronies don't want to fuck show people. It's the exact same correlation, the exact same thing is
like, bronies don't clop, it's not sexual. As hard as it is to believe- As hard as it is to believe,
this is an extremely poorly worded entry on UrbanDictionary.com. To say that it does not mean
wanting to have sex with them, it implies that it means inherently a furry does not want to have
sex when the fact is you can or cannot. It doesn't define whether or not you're- Is that true?
Is that true? Is what true? They're furries who don't want to have sex with animals.
Do furries exist who go to conventions where fursuits but have no desire to-
Yes, absolutely. Of course there is. Is that true? Yes. Okay. I bet the proportion of
asexuals in the furry community is astronomical. I don't believe in asexuals, but okay, go on.
Okay, okay, let's say our stances, let's say our stances, because this is-
You heard me. You may think- What if you just- Nate, that doesn't make any sense, but okay.
I think everyone who says they're asexual is fooling themselves. That's what I-
What about- What if you don't have sex, then what? What's your counter-argument to that?
Are we describing it as a thing that you do or like a state of mind, like a personality trait?
Are we talking about- Oh, fucking hell.
People who don't want to have sex don't exist? Are we talking about that?
Are we talking about literally munchy? Okay, we'll get back to this. We'll get back to the
asexuality question. I hope we don't.
All right, munchy, you have some experience with furries in the world. I do.
Tell us your tale. Tell us your stories. And mind your words.
Oh, I will. My stance, my angle that will be integral to this entire episode, here's my position.
Furries were a joke. They were just a fucking meme that you would punctuate friendly conversation
with your friends with. It would be like, oh, you know, I'm getting a sick frag. I'm killing a
zombie right through his goddamn head. Oh, this is just like what I would do to a furry if I were
to see him on the streets. And it was a great time. It was an excellent time. And then due to
circumstances too unlawful and sinful to recreate or reproduce with my words, I was thrusts into
situations where I would be able to not be able to. I was forced to examine furry culture
and lifestyles on like a every other day basis. And it made me realize,
wait a second, furries are real and not like a fictional construct made to make other people
laugh at what furries are. And so I had to like examine the furry culture for a while on Twitter.
On Twitter, I made a tweet about how I was going to try and become a furry. And by that I just meant
join furry discords and see what they do. Not to bully, not to bully, but to understand, you know,
like, like, what's this all about? What's going on here? And I have come back with the data. The
data is that I am a fucking genius and that furries are all terrible except for the furries that are
great, which are all of them because all furries are great. And I'm a fucking faggot except for
the ones that are shit. And I'm so conflicted and nuanced. I'm so nuanced. Kill me. I want to,
I just want to go back to furries being jokes. I wish they were jokes again. I don't want to think
about them. Dude, this guy got, this guy got nuanced out the ass. This guy got achieved maximum over
nuance. I got strapped. I can't even, I begged my fucking daddy not let me walk and then he
lowered me up with his nuanced knowledge. That's what fucking happened right now.
So yeah, needless to say, like, there's things going on. There's things going on these days as
society progresses and more degenerate elements of society are able to survive on the backs of
people who can actually do things with their lives. Like, like all this kind of shit is just
getting more and more prevalent. You know, what's, what's the deal? How do we, how do we end them
once and for all? Let's go through all our stances. I mean, do you, do you guys all have the lay
queries are bad? No, I, but a little bit. I'm pretty, no, but kind of ambivalent. My position
is pure ambivalence. I don't, I don't care for it too much. And in fact, I find a lot of the
aesthetic to be pretty, pretty unappealing. Like, like I've, I've seen, I know people who are furry,
so I've seen lots of art and like, how can you not see furry art when you're on the internet?
And like, I'm definitely much more and like, not into it sexually at all, obviously, but, but in
terms of like the aesthetic of like anthropomorphized animals, I definitely swing more towards like,
I like the like Disney sort of thing where it's like, like the classic Disney movies where they
add like humanoid features to animals, but like the weird like furry art where it's like a human
with like paws, that like creeps me out when like it's uncanny valley. Yeah, I'm talking about like,
so, so you prefer that, that like Lion King moment where Nala looks at Simba. Oh, so sexually.
Those aren't even fun. Lion King's not even a furry movie. They're just animals. Yeah. Well,
where's the, that's a good question. Where is the little anthropomorphized? I mean,
I mean, literally your movie sucks. Like that's his third favorite movie on the basis of he wants
to fuck Scar. So like, I would say it's a furry movie on some of them. Wait, wait, why? No, it might
be a movie with furry appeal. It might be a movie with furry appeal, but those characters are, I was
saying the Lion King, the YMS considers that his third favorite movie out of his desire to fuck
Scar. Well, you know, unlike YMS, why? Because he's getting the furry before he is a before, you
know, Hitler liked painting. That doesn't mean that painting is a Nazi thing. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah, just because YMS likes to fuck Scar doesn't mean I can also want to fuck Scar. Yeah,
you know, yeah, he could not be labeled a damn dirty furry, you know what I'm saying. Get ready
for this hot JoJo reference. It's like just because Kira from part four of JoJo finds the Mona
Lisa's hands incredibly sexual. Well, I mean, no, not really. It's just that like the bad guy does
find Mona Lisa's hands like overtly sexual and arousing. But that doesn't mean that like it's
an erotic image inherently, like this is him bringing that to the table. Sure, you can convert
anything to any degree if you try hard enough. People have people up there, you know, sexual
all right, guys, indeed, we're kind of getting we're getting off. When are we going to get
poly procrastinators? When are you gonna get like, like, like, like, like polygrams? No,
you mean shipping subreddit? That's what I mean. Oh, you mean like between us? Yeah. Oh,
that's why I'm not surprised it hasn't happened right now. Yeah, I'm sure it hasn't happened.
You have set it in motion. We're not. We're not sexy. We're we're losers, you guys.
I don't know what you're talking about. You know, gay. Yeah. Okay, okay. Here's some facts. 99%
of all procrastinators fans are transsexual. Another one percent are gay. There are no other
do the graphics. That is all basis. That is truer, like, like you say that as a joke, but yeah,
it's true. No, that's actually the truth. Yeah, I know, I know. I mean, I mean, I'm sure there's
there's a lot of trans people. No, no, no, 99% and 1% those are the only those are the only
percentage, you know, there are rounds, which is strange why why we would choose to be you know,
you know, I'm so glad that the privileged class of trans of trans women have, you know,
have thrown their lot in as allies of the, you know, of the downtrodden PCP, you know,
we need the famous alt-right comedy. You know, it shows a lot of magnanimity.
Well, we're having a great time. Stop that. We got to talk about.
All right. Yeah, let's continue this expressing our general thoughts on furry. So here's my thing,
and this will not surprise anybody, but I, everyone, anyone who's like judgmental of what
somebody is into sexually can just fuck off and die. I actually am probably way more,
I wouldn't say that I'm pro furry, but I'm 100% pro freedom to do whatever the hell you want.
I'm pro bestiality. I'm ironically, there's, there is an argument to make there, I suppose,
but I am like, I'm a pro bee ball. I'm a pro bee ball. I know you guys on several,
some people here, I don't remember exactly who have argued with me. I've debated that like,
yeah, if you're like a furry, and you go to conventions, dress up in a fur suit, like,
okay, like that's a little strange to me, like it's not something I would do. But as long as you
continue to be a productive human being, and it's like something that you do just out of fun,
then I don't see a problem. But if you stop being productive, if you put that pick down and stop
mining for slime, then you're going, you're done. If you, if you start to become like, if you start
to be like a dependent, and you start to like be like, Oh no, I need to spend all my money to like
make myself feel okay about the fact that I'm a furry by getting like increasingly elaborate
fur suits, or buying all this porn supporting these artists. So of course, mom and dad, I need
you to pay my rent for me so I can like, I'm not saying that furries do this, but like if somebody
has that attitude about anything, that's a problem. That's not a furry problem. That's being a broken,
irresponsible human being. Okay, okay. This is the thing. All of my complaints with furries are all
in character for me and not relate to like the core of what a furry is. Nothing has to do with
like the animal side of it. It all is in character complaints that I've complained about in other
situations before that all culminate in this fandom. It's not inherent to all members of the
fandom, but, but why should we ignore? Why should we ignore outliers? Why should we ignore the face
of the fandom? Why should we know? That's an excellent point. And like, you know, for example,
bronies as a group, as a movement, get lambasted because many of them, maybe not even a majority,
but many of them are obnoxious and annoying. So like in the same way, like, have you seen
Foam Adventure? That famous- Yes, of course. Of course, I've seen Foam Adventure. That's a legendary
video. I wish I liked anything. I wish I liked anything as much as they liked their foam.
I was a little judge, honestly. I like Foam Adventure as much as they liked their foam.
It's just, it's just the tale, if you haven't seen it, it would probably be in the show notes,
but like it's just the, it's a day adventure of two furries going out to get foam in order to make
fursuits when they, when they come back home. Is that what it was for? Yes. Yeah, I thought they
just wanted to like roll around on it. No, no, no, it's for fursuit. That was just a side benefit.
Okay. So they needed it for something. Well, all right. And like, they don't like do,
they don't hurt anybody. They're not really that annoying. It's just when you just,
when you witness this little slice of their lives and you imagine being like,
within three feet of them, it's just like, oh no. Imagine living like this or adjacent to this.
But the thing is though, with me, I'm not trying to land best furries or anything. It's just that like,
a lot of it just seems childish to me. It seems very like whimsical. Like, yeah, we're going to do
this crazy thing. Oh, okay. I completely agree. Does anyone else want to give their stance? Does
anyone fucking, does anyone care? I can go. Okay. Yeah. What do you think, did you?
Well, as, as we were all in the Brony community, obviously there's plenty of overlap between that
and the furry community. Yes. And, you know, I know a whole bunch of people from that community
who are furries, especially from being on the pub crawl, because like pub crawl has always been
like a, on some, on some level, somehow it's always been a furry show, I feel like.
I didn't know that. Okay. I mean, like Cider is heavily affiliated with the furry community,
and a lot of the guests we had on there would be into that stuff. And because like,
the nature of the show early on was we got shitfaced and talked about like weird,
like laws and stuff. Like we were always talking about things like what animals are surprisingly
legal to fucking what states.
Gee, that's not a red flag that it's a furry show. I don't know what it is.
And I mean, obviously we, well, I mean, during the pub crawl, we would have somebody in the chat
who just would routinely every show, which is constantly post pony porn, you know,
and like, we were all okay with that because we saw it as like, this is a real outsider program
here. Like this is not, you know, we're not expecting anybody who can't handle pony porn
to be listening to the fucking pub crawl, which was like a 2am show on an obscure pony network,
you know, but like, as a result, I ended up talking to, you know, just like hearing
second hand. And it's amazing how much of it is just like furry to me, furriness,
there's like a whole culture is next to godliness, you know, it really is. There's definitely like,
I think to them they are almost another, well, another species in a way, but like,
more like another race of people, like they like furries act the way that like, you know,
when you go to like a rest, like an Asian restaurant or something, and like the family
who runs the place are all like talking in Chinese and making fun of you, because you
can't speak Chinese, that's how I feel around furries. It's like, they've devised their own
language, and they're kind of like, making fun of every like, you know, there's like, whatever,
we're over here, like, we're using our language so you guys can't understand us, or we're like,
in our own other world, you know, but like, it's mostly a sex thing.
So what you're telling me, Digi, is that, so these people are not exactly human, and my
loyalties are intense, but extend only to human. So, and since they're furries, and they identify
outside the normal human spectrum, they're more bestial, they wouldn't mind, they wouldn't object
if I put them down like a dog, is what you're telling me. That's, that's my, ends on the kink,
I guess. I certainly wouldn't mind. So, but there is a distinction to be, or, I mean, I'm asking,
I guess, because I'm not really an expert. So like, furry, yeah. Furry is not equal to otherkin,
is not equal to like, someone who's intubitial. If we, if we're, if otherkin, if otherkin's
part of this, that just, I mean, so many memories, so many memories of trolling otherkin. It was a
great time in my life. That's like, I mean, I, I mean, I don't, I mean, I imagine that the otherkin
percentage number is higher in the furry fandom, though it's not an integral part to it. There was
the time, there was the time I pretended to be the meta, the metatron, like reincarnated and talked
about and gaining literal superpowers and was like, hey guys, I'm gaining literal superpowers
because my angelic power is manifesting. There was the time I was a mind flayer. There was the time
I was a mind flayer. There was the time that I was the spirit of my own fat and I was also a feeder
who was determined to become as fat as possible because I identified so strongly with the, no,
it was on likeotherkinforums.com or whatever it was back in like 2010.
Okay, okay. Damn.
Unnerve me, I don't particularly like them, especially like fictional other people where,
and like, there's like the subculture of people who take other people's OCs and kin with them
and it's super uncomfortable. Oh my god. There's, there's copyright issues there,
guys. Jay, I just got to pay to play. Like that guy who was kin to like that one Digimon character
from season two, like the blue haired guy. That's not even, that's not even like, that's like
kinning with a show, but like, I mean, like taking people like such as like, let's say me or like
any other creator that they don't have anything published or whatever. They're just one person
on the internet. They take their character and they kin with them. Well, now, Maj, is your,
is your complaint there on more of a, I don't know, I'm not trying to dig into it, but like, is it,
is it more of like a, like a, this is your character. What right does this person have to like,
define themselves by a character that, frankly, they don't even know, because it's not their
character? Like, why would they do that? Or does anyone ever really know anyone?
It's kind of like that, but also like, my characters are in a way also a small extension
of myself. Like they don't necessarily represent myself. They might not have anything in common
with me, but they are a part of me. Like I put a little bit of myself in them, you know, and like
then someone takes my character and then assumes them and then like,
So if someone, if someone kins to a character of yours that is an extension of you, that's
basically rape at that point. So we got to, we got to tap down on this across the board.
Literally, literally, literally. Yeah, you're right.
It just makes me really uncomfortable. Like it hasn't happened to me, but it has happened to
a few artists I follow. And it's just like the thought idea is just, is just really uncomfortable
to me. I mean, that's a fair point. But aren't there people who other kin as like, not even like
dead people, but living people, like I personally am a Kanye West kin. I feel, I feel, you know,
a con kin for sure. If I, if I bought into the whole kin thing, I don't understand people who
kin with people who are still alive because I thought the whole idea is like reincarnation or
whatever. Yeah, I don't know. Maybe these people don't believe in the linear progression of time.
So that being said, they could be a reincarnation. Just like how there's theories that every electron
in the universe is the same electron. No, they must, they must be adherence to my,
to my famous church of transubstantiation, wherein a single spirit is reborn throughout
time and space as every individual living thing that ever existed. Time means nothing to a
transubstantialist like myself. You know, major's right. If that's true, then we're all just kin
of everybody. And that's, oh my God. Yes, it's true. It's true. Yes, we're all kin. We're all kin.
It's not, Ben, Ben. So it's, at that point, Ben, it's not other kin. It's every kin. We are the,
we are the Omni-kin. Oh, yeah. This is the word for this, but you're not, that's the name. That's
the name for this one universal spirit that reincarnates. It is the Omni-kin because it is
kin to all fictional and non-fictional alike. Wait, wait, wait, stop, but you crossed the line.
No, no, we're going right in this train all the way to the station. Well, I guess, I guess if we
include the multiverse theory as a part of that, then it is literally every character. And of course
we do. Of course we do. But then technically nothing is fictional. So the problem's off.
In the nation, you can be kin with anyone that you want. That's ever existed.
Yeah. And so you shall, and so it shall be. Amen. Well, okay, all right. Let's focus back on
furries. Now, I want to ask, like, so we said before, there is a distinction between a furry
and like an other kin, but like, what is going on with a furry who dresses up in a fur suit?
Like, what is, what's going on there? What's the deal? What do you mean?
They would like to have sex in the suit made of fur. Is that because they feel like they
are that creature or is it that they just like to pretend? I mean, there is a difference there.
Like, I know a few people and like, from them personal experience, nothing all furries, but
from them is just, it's kind of like cosplay in a way. They just like to dress up and,
you know, go to conventions and have a good time. Well, that makes sense to me.
I scoffed at this as you should scoff at this because I, I have a small sample source and I
don't even believe what I'm about to say. But I have been told that it is a sort of performance
art in the sense that they assume a character with a costume and then they portray this character
at conventions. It's not inherently sex thing. There are actually different types of fur suits
that are, it's like, if you were to watch the footage of like YMS will go to furry conventions
and like just take a bunch of footage and post it on his side channel. And yeah, like the fur
suitors always seem to be putting on like a cool cat-esque like character of like over the top,
you know, like kids show, hey, I'm a big fur suit man. Like we're going to run this convention
and it's going to be a great, uh, convention into the ground. Are you saying that YMS is
attracted to cool cat? That's not impossible. That is like, it does not look too different from
your normal fur suits. Well, I know that YMS identifies as a horse, but he is interested in
big cats. This is some deep lore that I'm not aware of. Well, that's fine. I mean, this is all
very strange, but like, I just want to, like, all the weird porn I watch is pretty strange too.
So I, I don't know, in no way am I trying to disrespect Adam or like anybody who's a furry
out there. It just, you know, it's interesting and funny. I only know all these things because I,
like, part of why I got into YMS was that I was really fascinated that he was an openly gay furry
and willing to talk about it like very matter of factly. Like, yeah, why the fuck do I care?
And I was just like, yeah. Are there any other big name furries out there? Who else is a
representative of a community? I can't, I can't think of any like, respectables. I can't think
of any of the people. I know. I mean, yeah, I have lots of friends who are in the furry community
and people who are like, I know, but nobody who's like giant, nobody who's as big as, as YMS.
Yeah, I guess, I guess, I guess all the big, all the big furries are just big in their little
puns. I, I want, I want, I need, I feel like I feel the need to separate church and state
you real quick because if we, if we, I just want to put the kibosh on this real quick. Being a
furry does not inherently mean that you are sexually attracted to furry creatures. Now,
on that side of that, that's not a huge part, right? But I just feel the need to separate that
because I have no problem with the sexual component of it. Okay, I'm going to level
this through real quick. If furries were just a cult of, of red robed, you know,
Luminati fucking, you know, Burning Man type cultish freaks whose soul, you know, a tenant of
their, of their personality and religion is that they love to fuck like turtles. I would have no
problem. My, my, my problem. And when I, I should specify my problem is my, my specific, I don't like
them opinion, opinion, like danger, like red alert, Lee Sirens opinion, uh, is with their culture
and their culture is truly disgusting to me for in-character reasons that have been honed outside
of the furry fandom. Yeah. We've been, we've been magnanimous and, and dancing around the issue,
but let, I want to get into the shit. I want to weigh into the, the, the, the, I wanted to bring
up, it was funny that Munchie mentioned, uh, Burning Man because Dick always tells us, uh, Dick,
of the dick show. So it's the story of, uh, going to Burning Man and going to see the furry
tent. And it was like the only one that was like this fully realized, like the almost futuristic,
like technology tent where they had like built an entire hut with like TV and they'd gotten
cable and shit out there. Like it was just an orgy dome. Like it was just a place where they
like literally would just have a gigantic furry orgies. However, they had the best and like most
fully realized tent at Burning Man because the furries are, are, are geniuses. And, uh,
they're an entrepreneurial community. I really do think that furries, first, I don't know what
the connection is. There seems to be some connection between furries and engineering. And like that.
Yes. I've noticed this too. Because the, because the suits maybe, because they're complicated.
I, I think it's probably just they're both things that nerds do.
That's definitely a huge part of it. And I gotta tell you, I was just at this convention called,
called Torah Khan, which is at the Rochester Institute of Technology, really huge engineering
school that's been around for, for like a hundred years or something. However, they've been around
forever. They have, they're, you know, pres, fairly prestigious, but they have a gigantic
anime convention, like a 3,500 person con at the school. And it's because the school has enough
of a weeb population that there's not only nearby the best manga store I've ever been to,
with it like a block away from the school. One of the best tabletop game stores I've ever seen
in my life, like within a block of the school, like everyone at the school is a fucking nerd.
And while we were there, not only are there furries in fursuits all over the school,
like, like think about this, these people go to school here, like almost everybody at this
convention is somebody who goes to school here. And yet they are willing to walk around in fursuits,
like in front of everyone they know, because the school is just so full of nerds and there's such
a huge furry population. Well, that's true. I mean, they were all hanging out just among the
crowds. Well, okay, we're talking about a school that has like, like, uh, dive, like diversity
and inclusion, like messages everywhere. But the moment that really got to me was even like,
we're at a convention and there's furries everywhere, whatever. But I saw that this,
there were posters up for a cosplay formal dance. This school has cosplay formal dances,
and it depicted in the picture, like two, two, like a couple of like anime drawn characters,
like in, in, you know, gowns, like dancing, and they both have cat or they both have tiger ears,
because the school's mascot is a tiger. So all of their like branding, they just have like anime
characters with tiger ears as like their mascot characters. So it's just a furry school is basically
what I'm saying. Here's a question. If I, uh, if I own a local coffee shop and I observe a pack of
furries walking into my establishment, here's my question. If I refuse to serve them and demand
they leave immediately, uh, because they're creeping out me and everyone else around me,
not that this has happened. I'm just saying in a hypothetical, uh, is it a human rights issue?
Yes, of course. But, but, but they are not human. They are subhuman, you might say. These are furries.
They do not, you know, they don't fit. Uh, that's, that's my joke. Okay. That's the whole extent of
it. All right. But anyways, what were we getting into here? Oh yeah, Munchie. Munchie was gonna,
was gonna go into his deep hole. I want to give one final last disclaimer, not for the audience,
but for you guys, because I, I have been trying to be, you know, you know, passe and be nuanced
and be, you know, you know, I'm trying to put on the kid gloves and say, you know, you know,
I'm trying, I've been trying to defend furries. I will continue to defend furries, but make no
mistake. All of you are fucking idiots because I hate furries more than you could ever, ever
possibly understand. And I hate them for, for, for, for nuanced and on point reasons. My reasons
are on fucking- The furries are calling right now, dude. They've got a problem with this. They,
they want to talk to the manager. The phones are ringing off the hook. So, so, so while you guys
are being like, oh, fucking aren't whales gross or fuck you if you'd like horses. I'm over here
with the real fucking raw actual shit. Point one of why you would actually hate furries,
aka, it's my opinion, and I'll have like a reveal later and it will be narratively catharsis and
coon, coon, spheric. Point number one. Okay. This, obviously, the sex and not as in like, not,
not as in the like, you know, I want to fuck a horse. That's completely fine. That's completely
fine. Go, go at them. What I dislike is the openness. I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna coin this term
that will be used at the entire thing. Unearned smothering kinship. So this is unearned smothering
kinship where, when you were part of a community, keep in mind, I've prowled furry forms, you know,
I, I, I've brought in the work. I've done the fucking work. This is true. The furrio stereotype
is not inaccurate and it is true. The, the, the sense of like, it's, it's like the Ben and Jackie
College fund. You enter, you, you, you enter, everyone's super nice. Everyone's super like
unbelievable, like, touchy and like, feeling one another and everything's soft. And it's,
it's this feeling that I've described over and over again throughout this podcast. It's when
you're in bed and you're in, you're in bed, it's winter. You want to get nice and cozy.
Then after a while and you're in your hop and you're like, this is too hot. This is too much.
Like I need to get, I don't have the covers. I need to be cool. I can't be in this fucking
softy, this fucking touchy, this feely, too up in, too up in my fucking grill, this cobbling,
fucking overheating, a din, this cesspool of sex and fucking villainy, the openness that these
people have to do, to do lewd and perverse and, and not even just like strictly destructive, but
like, like, nay, I think I'm trying, I'm struggling to come up with the words, but like, you understand
like, like how niceness, I know exactly what you're talking about. And well, the problem with,
the problem with communities of inclusivity is that to some degree, humans are both physically
and mentally, we're designed to be beasts of burden and we are expected to have psychological
loads and not have just everybody say how great and wonderful we are all the time. We're pack hunters.
Well, whatever, you know, we followed our many umbrellas here, but, but here's my point. Like,
the reason I prefer to hang out in communities that are like overtly in the opposite direction,
like on 4chan, where everyone is incredibly vicious and cruel to each other is because I just see more,
like, usefulness to come from that as opposed to people just placating me all day about like,
you're perfect just the way you are, there's no need to improve, like, and like, there's an,
that's of course important in some measures, like we want to not shame people for just being weird
or different, but to say that like every choice, now back to how much we hate furries, being a furry
is a fine thing to do. But if you walk around in a fur suit and people know who you are,
all I'm saying is I am not casting judgment, but I am telling you, there will be social
ramifications of doing so. Yeah, you'll have a lot of great sex with like-minded furry people.
That's that's what you have to look for too. Congratulations. Did you speak on the subject
because I want to know if you're, I mean, more on the openness about the sex thing. That's what I
care about. It's like really, it's really, yeah, it's intense, like, furries because of the fact
that they have that culture of like, understanding each other, I guess, um, yes, like, it's the
over the window dude. It's because it's because they can do, you know, it is definitely over to
windows. Yeah, they're all freaks and they allow themselves to do degenerate things. And so the
overall, like, you know, how, how much can you touch your friend? How, how much, you know, how,
how much weird flirting can you do? All dialogue, all dialogue between furries is
flirty. It's all, it's all. Yeah, in my experience, that is true.
Yo, yo, let's listen to this. Okay. Here's, here's the real shit. There's a word that I think that
has been lost to the ages a little bit. And I think it is such an important word. I don't know,
maybe people would disagree, but the word is classy. I like things that are classy. And you
know what? In my humble opinion, what is not classy is like talking overtly about sex, open,
like you're involved with it all the time, digi, like bring up sex when it's not relevant. And
like, like, it's, it's, you, you are allowed to do it. You are, it's fine. It's not a problem.
But I don't want to hear about it. I'm not interested in how much sex you are having,
like the weird things you get up. One time, like a neighbor of mine, when I was growing up,
like I asked her for a ride home, just told me like, I can't give her a ride home. I'm going
to a threesome. That happened to me in my real life. I would have said the same damn thing if I
was going to a threesome. I mean, that was totally fine. But like, you got to think, what was she
trying to do? She was like trying to like shock me or something, because she knew I was a fucking
gay ass twink. Like she could have said, I'm just busy. She chose to tell me she's going to a threesome.
She wants to brag about getting to go to a threesome.
Don't get me wrong. That's totally fine. And I, again, I respect her right to do so.
All I'm saying is classiness. Her classiness took a hit when she told me that. That's, that's,
that's all I'm saying. I have no attraction to the classiness that you speak of. I can tell.
I have no, I just, I don't, if you're, but it comes to like sexual stuff, I feel like, I mean,
you, I know you agree with me that like, we need to be more open about sexuality for our,
for our culture's sake. And I don't like, I do think that maybe the furries are like an over
extension of that. And I'm sure that has to do a lot with the fact that there's probably a fucking
near one to one autism ratio in the community. I've done the numbers. It is high. It is not
more than half, but it is high. Okay. I am on Nate's side. Like, I don't, I don't like on solicitors
at TMI about your sex life. Well, did you, did you is right though? I definitely agree that I
think society as a whole will be better off once we're at this place. But it's just that,
it's just that right now was like, there is a difference in your face about it.
I mean, that, that's true. I mean, I like, if, if we lived like, like fucking Star Trek, for
example, like there are just planets you can go to, like on earth, like people are relatively
conservative about these things. But if you go to like literally like the sex planet in Star Trek,
like it's like, then you can just talk about fucking anything you want all the time.
If there is, let's say a furry convention and the furry convention is just a big orgy,
I'm okay with that because it's just a bunch of furries, like everyone's going there knowing
what it is. There's definitely something weird about, for instance, at BronyCon, where every
year I would hear that there is somewhere a BronyCon orgy, like every year at BronyCon and
some hotel room nearby, a bunch of furries get together and have a huge orgy. And this is like,
this is something you hear about like floating over the crowds at BronyCon. And you see people,
you see furries like, you know, in fursuits with shirts like down to Yiff and shit like that.
It's brazenly sexual on some level. And then you're like, but this is a My Little Pony convention
where like, there's also six year old girls around. And it's like-
Well, okay, did you-
To a certain degree.
There are also six year olds at furry conventions.
Well, I mean, okay, you're not wrong. I want to speak on-
Some six year olds are furries and want to get into that orgy, I guess.
Like there's definitely some crossover between like, for example, like the gay rights movement
and stuff. Because like a lot of it is, it's about like being proud of who you are and like,
not allowing society to like, shame you and repress you. But like, I mean, you know, again,
there's a context for everything and there's degrees of doing different things. And like,
if you're at like a gay pride parade, like there's kind of, you're making a statement,
if you just like make out, if you're a guy and you're gay and you just make out with a dude
publicly, and it's like sloppy and just like, like just celebrating being gay, like that actually
has kind of like some utility. It's like, you're like challenging social norms and stuff. And so
like, I get it. I mean, and you know, now it's legal. So like, things have changed and it's
starting to get a little passe. So how about we shut the fuck up about that?
I'm just kidding. But like,
I'm just kidding everyone. Come on.
It's like taking potshots at all the fucking quote unquote repressed groups. So he's just like,
I got a really flag. I am currently defending all of them by saying that I totally understand
the desire to like, feel that you can express your sexuality just in general. And I think,
I think just that leads to a little bit of overcompensation is all I'm saying. Again,
like I agree with you guys on all of this. I think there's, there's a lot of like, I feel
shame. So I'm going to hyper like accentuate this in response, which is logical to a degree.
Sure. I think that the same time though, that becomes, I don't want to say obnoxious. That's
where the stigma comes from though. Right. You're, you're, you're, you're, you're being
more comfortable in of yourself and you're probably winning allies, but you're also
creating enemies you wouldn't otherwise have at the same time. That's true. There's a difference.
There's a, there's a big social problem with confusing tolerance, with like acceptance,
like, like people tolerate things even though they don't like them. And that's what we should aim
for. Like right now, everyone, you don't have the right to be loved by everybody. Well, that's
for sure. That's for sure. And there's a huge difference between fighting for tolerance and
fighting for being loved. And I feel like a lot of people have that problem. Right. Right now,
I still get shit occasionally. This is pretty rare for me, but it's like people will
at me and like give me shit about the fact that I even liked my little pony at all,
despite like never being in any way like a creep or like weird about it. I simply like a show.
And because it's associated with like things happening with other people elsewhere,
you know, even maybe touching into the furry community to some degree, obviously, like then
that there's just, there's a social miasma that just swirls around these things. And I mean,
it's around every community. You know, there's, there's bad things about every single community,
which is why I'm so anti-identitarian and think everyone should just be their individual self
and be judged on their own merits. Yeah. This will be a thing later. Word. To all viewers,
you may like think, ah, these fucking guys, what the fuck are they talking about? They just don't
want people to be nice to one another on their own fucking discord service. What's in her new
guys? Well, that's the thing. You fucking dumb ass slut. You fucking drink up, come you fucking
bitch. Is because I have opinions and I have been forced to think about my opinion on this subject.
As you all know, in a little podcast named Armour Fucking Trevill, I discussed extensively how much
I dislike the characters for exhibiting overly sexual and creepy, disgusting, perverted dialogue
constantly without any respite and how I dislike the overall, you know, jovial and cheerful and,
you know, hug, boxy nature of the characters in that. So don't you come fucking tell me that this
is some like, you know, oh, I'm just hanging furries for no fucking reason. Oh, my son's a fucking
foreigner. He's taking ten cocks up the ass. You know what the fuck you're talking about. Well,
you know what, maybe I don't, but am I not allowed to feel things? Am I not allowed to have a soul?
Am I not allowed to have my heart singing? All right. Well, what else you got, Munchy? What's
point two here? Or may I say something? Well, I actually wanted to sort of shift the topic about
your opinion about life personas and stuff. Yes. Yes. Oh, I would love to get in this, please, please.
Like, oh, like specifically, would you guys like to have personas or just
I'm, please define. Wait, wait. In major, in your own words, please define a fursona.
Well, basically, you that is like an anthropomorphic animal.
We literally all have those because we were all, we all have brony so.
Yes. I kind of, I kind of like put the brony part away from the furries. I have no interest in doing
that specifically with like an anthro animal man, man boy, or, I mean, it's just like, what, what,
what is the end game of having a fursona? If you just really like. And you want to be a person,
it's just natural. It's just, I think it's just a way of participating in the community. Like,
the same reason we all had horse characters. Yeah, that's true. It's the exact same.
Science, do you remember? I did like some sketches like a way, way back ago before,
before Munchie was even born. Oh my God.
Of like several of us members as like animal characters. Like, I think.
Yeah, that was for an RPG that we were going to do. Yeah. Yeah. I was a spider lady and.
Yeah, that was great. I remember those. Well, okay, but you're calling it a fursona. To me,
it's almost like just like fan art of a sort, you know, in a certain way. I think a huge part
of the existence of fursonas has to do with the fact that like fur affinity and like artwork is
such a big part of the furry community. And so people just kind of have a character so that
there is a vessel to have art. Like, like YMS, for instance, will regularly buy commissions of
just his like other artists he likes drawing his horse character. And since, you know,
commissions, they can charge whatever they want if it's a good enough artist. So like these people
are willing to pay to have their fursonas. So like it's just kind of a part of the culture is like
this this weird dropping all your money on like bronies were like this, too. This is also part of
for other levels are like they just spend lots and lots of money. And I do think there's an
element of like, uh, I think a lot of like, well, furries have disposable income is what I'm
saying. Sure. I want to stress that I have literally seen a person on Tumblr that like is
poor and could barely pay rent by $80 commissions. Like like he spent literally, literally like all
of his money, all of his written money. I'm not fucking joking. Like seriously. What would you
say? What would you say to someone who came back with this, like someone who's maybe like a member
of the trans community and would say that like, but Munchy, don't you see he needs to invest at
least some maybe that's too much money. But like he feels like like he doesn't belong in his body.
And he feels like he needs to be depicted as this persona in order to feel okay about himself.
I don't think that's not the point of them. But I would say no, that's not all the point.
Maybe that's the other thing. I think that what Munchy is describing with this guy,
this is something I've seen a lot of, which is just some people get locked into pleasure spending
and literally just spend all their goddamn money. And it's a big thing in these communities. Like
my, uh, my ex-girlfriend was not really a furry, but she was big into like buying plushies on Deviant
Art and like literally would just like spend all her fucking money on that and then ran out of money
and like had no money anymore because she would drop like $500 on a plushie, like a custom made
Etsy plushie like every fucking week. And eventually you don't have money anymore. So that's what
happens. It's advice like anything else. Yeah, go on Munchy, go on. Did you side topic real quick?
I was really listening to the horse cast for various reasons. And in the first episode,
like 20 minutes in, you're just like, hey, can I just like bring my ex-girlfriend into the call?
And she's like, uh, okay. And then she's just there for the rest of the episode. Is that true?
Just like in the background, just sometimes chiming in. Damn, I never noticed that. I must have not
listened to that one. Very funny. Very fucking funny. Well, I think I made my point. So, I mean,
well, what I was going to say was like, you could, I, that is a good point, did you? I totally
think that's a reasonable thing to say. It's just like, I don't know what I said. That was like a
pet, like none of what you just said would reconcile with the thing that I had said. Like, no, no,
well, I mean, no, that's what I'm saying. It's like, what I'm saying is like the most defensive
position that like someone who's like trying to like explain this behavior is like a necessary
thing somebody needs to engage in. No, no, I'm not trying to say that at all. I'm just saying that
some dumb motherfuckers just like to blow through all the goddamn money. That's what I'm saying too.
It's not defensible at all. This guy's a fucking idiot. He just doesn't know how to spend money.
You're right. I'm just recognizing that as a fair counterpoint to what I was saying. And like,
it's really hard for me to like know what that's like. Like, once in a while, I absolutely do
just waste some money on like a new video game that I really don't need that I want. But like,
to this degree is unfathomable to me. I can't imagine doing that. I don't know, man. I guess
these are just, I think these are just irresponsible people if you, if you do something, you know,
to that degree. You know, I mean, if I, if you, if you're not an artist, I can understand what
wanting to spend tons of money getting like art of your character made. I feel blessed. I feel
blessed to have the skills that I can just do it myself and turn my nose up.
Yeah, but that's your goddamn privilege. It is my privilege. And I'm fucking, I'm never checking
it. But you learned how to draw, Ben. I don't accept that as a privilege. No, I was born with
this ability. I never worked a day in my life. But there's like different art styles out there
and something you can do and maybe you want to see in a different style. That's true. That's fair.
Yeah, I'm not saying I do understand, I do understand the drive to like commission art.
Like it makes sense. I hardly ever do it. I sort of, I sort of share it. I guess it's a bit of an
ego of an artist. Why pay for it if I can do it myself at the same time? I want to, I want to
support my fellow artists and also I like other art styles. So I have commissioned other artists
to draw my characters a few times. It's really fun. It's really neat. It's just, it's kind of,
I guess it's kind of paying, like paying for fan art. So it's kind of sad, but at the same time,
to see the art in the end. I want to discuss OC's and not just, you know, original characters,
like Ben, you wouldn't consider like a magda in OC, right? This is, I'm very interested in this
discussion of what is an OC. And yeah, yeah, I think technically anything you make up yourself
is an OC. But I think that, but I think that if you talk like that, it doesn't make any sense.
I think you might, at that point, you might as well just call them your, you know,
I have a definition. I have a definition. Okay. For this discussion, I want, when I say OC's,
it'll be short for NC's, which is narrative-less characters. These are characters you can create
just for the purpose of having a character. See, see, that's a little different to me.
I mean, avatars is a word I would use as well. To me.
Because you can have multiple avatars, you know, and these are just the ones you cycle between,
if you even used them that way. But like, yeah, it's, it's really fascinating the way that people
will like project themselves onto an illustration they didn't even make up. And then like, be like,
this is who I am now, and I spend all my money on this character now, like. To me. Yeah, it's
interesting. An OC, like I always felt like the best definition for an OC is a, it's a,
it's a character, but it's a character that exists within like another canon that you don't know.
Correct. Like an OC is a character you make up that is in like My Little Pony or Danganronpa or
whatever. That's an MC most of the time, fan character. But like, I mean, the terms aren't
interchangeable. It doesn't really matter so much, but like specifically that would be a fan character,
like in a fandom. Fair enough. What about a character that exists outside of any fandom?
That's just like, those exist. And those are what I would call NC's narrative.
That's what I would call OC's because I always create a narrative for my characters,
even if they don't have a fandom. Well, I mean, okay, okay, if you create a narrative for them,
and like you create like a comic or something for them, then like no one can, like, like,
I know I understand super pretentious here, but I totally do. And I can't deny that I put like,
characters in a story above characters without a story. I think we can all understand why,
because you need narratives to get like greater insight into the characters and gives them a
purpose for existing and allows, you know, themes, narrative plots to come out of them and make me
care about them. I do not care about narratives. But aesthetic is a narrative. That's true.
Okay, hold on. Wait, this is important.
Thanks for interrupting me like three times. Sorry.
To make a character, I think it's important to know why you're creating the character,
what purpose, and for what sort of universe or whatever, even though like a lot of my
characters lack description and deviant, and I'd be like, Hey, I made this boy, isn't he cute?
And you know, I don't put any information, know that I still think about the information when
I'm drawing like, what's the purpose of this thing? So the audience, though, how do they know
any of this? It should be conveyed in the design, I would think, you know, the design has to be
informed by your ideas, because it has to have some sort of consistency with whatever you're doing.
I mean, by that definition, then every character ever drawn, like there has to be some thought
into why they are what they are. So, you know, is it really true? Because you could have the
decision of like, this guy's wearing this chain, because it will look cool on this outfit. Or
you can think like, this guy picked up this chain from his dead grandma, and like, it has a
fucking secret resonance. And also, it's like how he uses his soul play. You know what it is?
If your character exists in any narrative, then they have to like have like a history and a
story. It's like, it's like, when you try to observe an electron, that's when it like chooses
a placement. It's when you try to observe a character in any narrative, like their history
develops instantly. But until you do so, it does not exist. Shrodingers. You know what I mean?
I think that a character doesn't need, okay, I mean, I think that you can like plan out your
characters like history and backstory and personality and relationships and all that stuff.
I wouldn't say that you shouldn't do that. But I think that you totally can create a character
with like very little history or like prethought and like put them in a story and have a character
kind of emerge out of that. Totally. Totally. That's not what I'm arguing. I'm kind of arguing
against mage that like that kind of like pre narrative like character creation is like it's
not always necessary. Alright, enough of whatever the hell we were just talking about. Munchy,
get to the business. The point, the point here that I dislike OCs for is because I feel they are like
basically inherently shallow without other characters or a narrative or plot to speak of. I
feel that they are shallow and cannot reach like the same level as like, you know, a fucking
anime comedy. Wait, wait, wait, wait, you're talking about a furry in real life? No, I'm talking
about an OC. I'm talking about an OC. Oh, yeah, okay, okay, okay. So this ties into real life
because most of the first suits are the OCs that people have created. So I am willing to binge
a little bit and allow people to say, you know, it's a performance art, you know, these people
are performing a character when they put on the costume. But if it's a shit character then. Yeah,
but it's a shit character is my point. It's a shit character that is shallow.
And okay, there's a difference between a sona and a character, but yeah.
No, no, I'm aware that there is, but a lot of there are first suits that are not for sonas.
It's not, it's not, it's not. Is it, is it a faux pas to go up to someone and say,
you're boring and I find your real life narrative shit? Because like, is it a faux pas to come up
to someone? I have done that and it was a faux pas. It was definitely who would have guessed.
Because that's basically what Munchie is advocating here with the furry community.
Your narrative is garbage. You need to revisit why am I advocating going up to people and like
shoving them down to the ground and like, well, why am I doing that? Because you're a white nationalist.
When I was in high school, I told a girl she was cliche and she did not take that very well.
Damn girl. That's pretty, that's pretty like, that's called a girl that's like, that's like,
that's like that part in American beauty where the guy tells the girl that she's boring and ordinary.
Oh yeah. My favorite part because I'm like all women. Am I right, man?
Smash. Smash the matriarch.
What else is worth though? She was like the only female juggalo I've ever met, so she wasn't that
Whoa!
Wildly recontextualized the story. The only female juggalo I've ever met was Jackie.
So like, yeah, I mean, you know, she's always down to clown.
I want to shift to point two of why I hate furries and by why I hate furries,
you all fucking know, I'm not going to put on the fucking killings a little more.
It's a fucking joke. I'm supposed to be hyperbolic in order to maintain comedy.
I don't actually, you know, it's, it's not, I don't actually have that much ill will.
Why hate furries? Two fursuits. I hate fucking fursuits and here's the thing.
They're ugly, man. They're ugly.
Here's what all furries, all furries have jumped up their ears. They're the little cute tail ears
have perked up and they're buying a mean comment right now. You guys have only seen fucking mass,
you know, mascot costumes. You haven't seen the real Rasha. You're just taking the worst of the
bunch and, you know, making fun of them. Not all fursuits are the same, my friend. Sick.
But here's what I have to say to you. The best and the worst fursuits, I hate them for the same
reasons. That's what I say when I say that I don't like anime style or like furry style.
It's not that they are literally the same. I just hate them all for similar reasons.
That's why I say that I don't like the furries styles because there are things about, you know,
commonly, you know, generic furries styles that are all like similar among different artists.
Yeah. And this is the same for fursuits, obviously. There are good fursuits and there are bad fursuits,
but they're indistinguishable to me because they both have the same trapeze. I've seen autumn
fallings, yeah, fucking names dropped, I'm a partition. Yeah. Get on my fucking level.
They're still bad. I got to back that up. You know, sometimes the artwork is well-crafted,
but like aesthetically, furry art is fucking repulsive. And I'm not even going to knock them
for that because obviously a lot of the shit that I like would repulse a lot of people. Like,
the porn I look at, if you showed it to your mom, she'd just fucking die instantly. Like,
knowing that, literally knowing that someone jacks off to this would kill a lot of moms.
The thing about the furry aesthetic that gets me, more than, I mean, I don't like it,
but more than just that I don't like it is that it's incredibly samey and it's all very like
self-reflective, you know, like it all looks like itself. Yeah, it's very incestuous. It's literally
tons and tons of the same. It's all so insular. It's a bunch of young artists copying old
artists that all copied fucking Don Bluth. Right, you know, or that it's that kind of scenario.
The thing that makes, I think, furry stuff like not as good as like anime is that like,
anime, like there's an anime style that like anyone sees like that's an anime,
but there are things like just for example, one piece that does not look like a normal
anime. There's for just like that. I was just going to say that I've never seen any furry art
that like actually looks like that. Oh, no, no, no. There's tons of... I say that, but then I found
this online, but then I found this image and I knew that I had found true love on this day.
Where is this? It's in the main chat. It'll be in the show notes, everybody. You're going to want to
see this shit. There's this one that's undeniably beautiful here. I have to find this. You guys
keep talking and I'll be listening. We're getting derailed.
Tom, what do you have to say about all this? You're a known degenerate. What do you think about
all this? Definitely. I don't know. I don't really find fur suits all that aesthetically pleasing.
I think my biggest problem with fur suits, and there are some that dodge this problem,
like the ones that are done like immaculately well, they all feel very lifeless. Like the whole
idea is you're trying to portray this cartoon character, but there's just very little emotion
in the face or anything and it feels very dead. It feels like you're wearing some cartoon husk.
Let me tell you a little story that's somewhat relevant to this. I went to Chuck E. Cheese not
that long ago for Jackie's birthday and Chuck E. was there. The man himself. Damn. He was quite
short. He was quite short. He only came up to my nose. I went to give him a high five and he's
looking down with his big stupid mouse grin and he's waving at the kids that are all jumping around
and grabbing tickets out of his hands. I went to give him a high five and he totally whiffed me.
You know why? I realized later, it's because he could not see me because he could only see down
out of his mouth. Well, here's here. Well, I guess that makes sense. This is supposed to be children.
Yeah. He can only see the kids below him, but here you see the world of adults that lives above.
This is kind of going off track, but I can kind of pull it back into something relevant.
That's terrifying. Is that look at this one, everybody. It's a Pikachu fursuit. All right,
I get it. The show notes. Check this out. Yeah. That's a good one. Damn. Dude, she's thick. Dude,
this girl. Have you seen the Celestias? No. I don't know. But Ben, Ben, I'm surprised they
still even have fursuits at Chuck E. Cheese because the current Chuck E. Cheese mascot,
he's the size of a regular mouse. Yeah. And here's the question. Is the current Chuck E. Cheese
mascot a furry anymore? He's just an anthropomorphized character and not a furry because he's definitely
a delineation. He's riding the line. He's getting more and more mousy, but I think he's still on the
side of evil. But the current character is the size of a mouse. He's like this tiny little
mouse running around wearing a shirt. Well, not when he's in a fursuit. He's not. I get it. That's
weird to me. I found the fur yard. That is weird. That he's an actual mouse or something. I found
the fur yard. That is good. And I'm about to post it. This is by Glitched Puppet of the comic
Floraverse. This is like the one piece. This is like the one piece. Floraverse is that one that's
nice. Floraverse is that one that's pretty cool, but it's got the like secret porn side. Yes, yes.
It's got the secret porn page. I remember I mirror Way Back when you discussed that. And then I was
like, huh, how interesting. Floraverse is actually pretty cool in a lot of ways. I found out about
it myself. And I was like, oh, this is the thing that Ben talked about. And I had the same conclusion
that you did. Yeah, it's like, it's cool. I mean, but it's also a little like, eh, it's a little
squeaky. This looks great. I mean, this looks really nice. I wouldn't even consider this
furry art. This is the one that you said that the artist also does like porn, right? They have two
patreons, one for the like the main comic and one for like the porn side stories. If this artist draws
porn, I need to get on that immediately. They do. I'll leave it to you right now, my friends. Now,
I don't think this is the case, but is this like there is one, it's not really furry, but there
is a, uh, a comic that features a unicorn that all of 4chan regards is extremely sexy. Like she's
like, oh, I know exactly the one you're thinking of. This is not that. Wait, wait, wait. Okay. Okay,
I guess not. I don't know what you're talking about. It's, it's the, I want to blank that blank.
And it's, you know, it's that old meme. Indeed. Well, uh, okay, dope, dope. I mean, we've done it
guys. I guess, I guess furries are somewhat saved. We've redeemed them. You're always trying to
in podcast, you're always trying to close. That's your main occupation is podcast. No, no, no,
much. You don't understand. I'm going for the fake out ending. I want everyone to think that we
resolve so that you can blast their assholes wide open with the truth at the end of the, it's like
the post, uh, credits, uh, final sequence. So let's, what else you got for us? Well, okay, let's,
let's get meta here real quick because this, I'm about to launch into a thing and this was,
and this was made, I have not scripted this like I usually do with notes, but this is on top of
my head. But this was intended, this idea was intended to come after a long section of me talk
about how I dislike, you know, the, the, the niceness and stuff, but that came at the beginning.
That's all fine. So just know that, uh, the impassioned rant I'm about to go on is totally
unearned within the context of the podcast. Only makes sense in my own mind, but just make sure
that this is just, no, for a fact, this is all genuine and not fake. And this is all is true.
The reason why I dislike that all this fucking gross ass, gross,
melty, hug box bullshit is because I was fucking there. Digi knows on fucking Tumblr,
I was in the most perverse and disgusting parts of the Brony fandom. And I was surrounded by
hug box, gross fucking openly sexual people all the time. And it fucked me up and made me sad
all the time being around all these people who are so freely open about, about their sexual
impulses and about, about all their, you know, trying to be all touchy and feely and all gross
all around me. It made me a disgusting person because like, because I couldn't hold back on
like, unlike my, you know, my urges and I turned into a weird fucking gross ass.
Oh no. And it was completely awful experience for everyone involved. And so, and so I grew up
and I, and I knew that I couldn't be like this anymore. Due to this group right fucking here
at BronyCon, I was a fucking bitch. But then I hung out with all view fucking people and I turned
to not a bitch. Simplified. But that's fine. That's fine. So the first time we met, you were,
you were deep in the shit, huh? Yeah, I was deep in the shit. Damn. And, and, and, and due to hanging
out with you guys and, and, you know, other friends, I slowly regained my humanity and renounced,
and renounced being a fucking carpet munchery, fucking, you know, like foreign, foreign browser,
you know, is this the, is this the off discussed like role play lifestyle that you mentioned?
My role plays came, my role plays were super innocent and just like I was like a kid on the
internet doing Pokemon. Sure. It was like home stuck. You were like Nepeta. I gotta pounce.
I gotta go on a thing here because I'm looking at this forbidden flora.com that munchy.
Man, the furry porn. So annoying. I think I've realized that the only thing that makes me not
a furry is that furry is defined by like the certain aesthetic and like
characteristics, you know, because if it was anime porn, you could draw any, like, you could
draw me a furry fuck and I will look at it and like it. Monster girls, man. Of course. I love,
love monster girls or any, just any type of like animal, human, hybrid, like the game Juan
Koto Kurasa, which is just about fucking like girls who are literally dogs, but they're like,
they look like human girls. Like, I mean, and even like, I look at tons of poke porn, but like,
and I was looking at this forbidden flora and I'm like, this would be my thing. Like, I think
this artist is really good. I think they have, they draw good porn. The only problem is that there
are little subtle things that make it extremely furry feeling. And those are the only things
that turn me off about it. Like, otherwise it'd be perfectly fine, but I just look at it and I'm
like, Oh, if they didn't look like fucking furries, this would be really hot. Well, see, that's,
that's what I, that's what I think about. That's why I'm so strident in my defense of like all
these people. Cause like, I have jacked off to every kind of porn there is, and I will do so
again in the future. Furry, scat, well, not really a girl or anything. Well, not, not even that much
scat. The scat kind of turns me off, but it doesn't matter. The point is, like, I don't want to
limit my freedoms. I mean, I was watching, I was watching, not resort, Bowen, uh,
like Aerogay, it's this whatever thing. And then like, all of a sudden there's just a shitting
scene and I was like, what the fuck is happening right now? Uh, it does matter. It happens all
the time in porn, especially like pissing is near constant in anime porn. If you watch enough
anime porn, if you watch enough anime porn and you're not into pissing, it can be difficult
because it's just going to happen. Like, I know we've all seen Oni Chichi and I know there's
pissing at least once in that scene. I don't even know what that is. What are you talking about?
I guess, I guess I'm not as degenerate as you all thought I was. No, Oni Chichi is like the most
popular hentai, like, ever, other than Bible Black. It's like the one that everyone's seen.
Is it about Chichi from Dragon Ball? No, it's just about some blonde girl getting
fucked by like her stepdad, I think, but like, they made like 80 episodes of it.
Hit up my boys on hentai gasm to see that shit. That's the real shit. Yo, all right,
we earlier discussed about TMI. Hentai Gasm is a good site. I'd like it.
But all I want to say is I am so absolutist in my viewing of like, all this is fine.
Like, I don't want to shame anybody. Do exactly what you want to do. It's totally cool.
But like, I think keep it in the privacy of your own home. Like, I do degenerate shit and I talk
about it here because it's funny. But like, if I was just hanging out with my friends and I started
talking about my weird fetishes, then like, there's an audience. You got to consider your
audience is all I'm saying. And you will creep people out if you start talking about the shit
openly. Like, thinking about it from their perspective, they are all furries. They all
do this. Why would they not discuss what they that even if I was a huge furry? I like, yes,
there's like the emancipation element, like, we shouldn't be ashamed for this. Like, yeah,
we're going to talk about rah rah. But on the like, it's right the path. I don't want to,
I don't want to hear about heterosexual sex that my buddies are having. I'm not
interested. I mean, I think that's, I think that's kind of unique to you though, Nate,
because I think it's fairly normal for like locker room talk to be like, yeah, I fucked
that bitch last night and put it in her ass. And it's not the same thing. I think it's,
wait, what is different about that? What do you mean it's not the same? Well, I mean,
if it's open the door, it's different to hear about my buddy plowing his girlfriend night
after night after night, as opposed to, yeah, at one night stand with this girl who you'll
never meet. Those are two different situations. I guess, I mean, I also see it as like, I mean,
me and my friends, fair enough, me and my other, you know, my offline friends, we even talk about
porn all the time because we were all just huge porn fans. Like, so, well, you know, I'm into
porn. I mean, all day, whether it's a girlfriend or a one night stand. Yeah, I kind of don't want
to think about my friends having sex ever, you know, that's where I'm coming from. That's where
I'm coming from. But hey, man, if I'm the weird one, fair enough, I accept it. I don't think you're
gross for doing it, but I think that thinking about it is kind of gross, you know, you know.
Class, man. Yeah, I know that we disagree on this topic, me and Digian, probably other people here,
but that's that's what comes down to for me. I think about everybody having sex.
Thanks. Well, okay. Yeah, yeah. I just wanted to say to watch any, you know, potential uprising
here, people are probably going to be like, munchy, like, like, like, I'm like, you Nick,
where I think you can do whatever you want sexually and you can do whatever you want.
Like, basically, you know, I'm pretty into, you know, freedom and, you know, do whatever you want.
It's your life. But like, I'm, you know, I'm an alt person. I'm living the alternative lifestyle.
I am not, I am not, you know, following society's normals. Why should I impose society's rules?
Like, why should I pick and choose the ones that I choose to follow? Like, you know, not protect
the freedoms, protect the freedoms of people who disagree with you people because one day
they're coming for your shit. Exactly. So I'm, none of this is meaning to intend like,
furries, stop it. I don't like furries. In fact, I wish that they didn't exist, but they do. And so
I'm not going to make any attempt to make sure that they stop being real. Right. And that's the
difference between my opinion and that's the difference between tolerance and like loving
that I was talking about earlier. Yes. Correct. And now there's an elephant in the room for this
whole conversation, Munchie, that I've deliberately avoided mentioning until now.
How big is the dick on that elephant? Cause I am, I'm getting horny thinking about all this.
Is it, is it, is it appropriate to bring it up now, Munchie? Or are you, do you want to,
you know, wait? I haven't asked the other party if they, I don't think they would fucking care,
yeah, whatever. Well, okay. Here's the deal, people. Munchie is dating a furry right now.
He is dating a big ol' fursuit furry. Yeah. So that's the context of this whole conversation.
It's not even a moderate, itch. She, she can't, Cassey, link, link in the description.
It's not even like a moderate furry. Like she's, she's real.
But see, but see, that's the thing, man. Tolerance, right? Like you, you're not into it, right?
I should also mention that she is not, she, she does not exhibit the behaviors that I have described
here. Well, yeah, there you go. She does not role play or anything. Proving that there are good
furries, you know, basically. Yeah. She does not exhibit the overwhelming, you know, heat,
and unbelievable, you know, warmness of, of unearned kinship. She does not exhibit that.
Yes. Yes. She's one of the good ones. Thumbs up. There you go.
Um, but yeah, uh, furries are all great. They give charities. How many charities have you
donated to, motherfuckers? Furries are all about charities. Do you, do you consider furry
patreons a charity? If so, they are the most generous organization in the entire universe.
That is also, that is also a good thing about furries, is that like, like, even though we can
make fun of them for spending so much money on commissions, and we should, because that's not
smart, uh, they do like support artists mad hardcore. Well, I think the reason that furries
support artists so much is because, like, because their fandom has no, like, canon material,
you can't just go buy the official release of Furry. It's just, it's all community driven
material. So if you want to, like, spend something, you can't just go out buy the
Blu-ray of Furry season one. You've got to support artists because that's all there is.
You know, I bet, I bet that is a ton to do with why they're so vocal and like fervorous in their
little community because it's so like shunned by, I mean, that's probably true of everybody who's
got a community like that, you know? Oh, I've, I've definitely, this is definitely true. Like,
the more that you voice opinions against furries, the more they will come away brazen in their
attitude. I honestly think, I think that on some level, I don't know how deliberate this is, but
I definitely think that it's understood by a lot of the furries that a lot of the outlandishness of
it, I think, is deliberate to keep people away. Because like, no one, yeah, no one fucks with
furries because everyone thinks they're disgusting and crazy. Like, furries, like-
You got your, like, Mr. Medicurys and those kind of guys who, like, deliberately try to, like,
you know, go out and start shit with these people. Yeah, but like, for the most part, I feel like
furries, like, the sign on the door is like, this is, this is how fucked it's gonna be in here,
so is that something you relate to? If so, come along and like, if you make it past that barrier,
it's like you're already, I think that's why there's such a hug box is that, like,
you've made it past this incredible barrier of, like, sacrificing your own conception of
your social normalcy. You're not wrong. You're not wrong. I mean, you're basically saying, like,
I am committing to never being a normie again. Like, something similar happened. I mean, at least
while you identify, it's not a complete transformation. That is true. Yeah, I mean, and you can, you
can stop being a furry one day, if you so desire. I'm just possibly burn and bury all footage of
you having been a furry. There's probably plenty of pictures out there, because these are cons are
all well documented. Yeah, social media. But like, I just think that there's, there's an element of
the fact that you even are willing to call yourself a furry is enough to give you some
camaraderie that, like, you are willing to, you know, stand in this world that, that where furries
are literally the bottom rung of society, they're everyone's punching bag. And yet, like, if you're
willing to call yourself that, then it's like, all right, you've made it into the herd, you know.
I think furry is, I would, I would give furries the, the immaculate distinction of being
the lowest level, like the lowest rung of society, that it doesn't quite make sense to, like,
deliberately mock or shame. Like, and like, when you get to, like, other can right below them,
at that point, it's like, well, okay, now that's open season, like, these people are insane.
But, you know, unless they're, I guess, they're playing around, whatever. By the way, by the way,
I just, I namedrop Mr. Medeker before, he actually is more charitable towards furries,
and he's just harder on, like, other can. So I just want to, like, I don't like hate the guy,
he's not like insane or anything, just, just saying. People might be like, why do we feel
the need to come on this? We are not furry experts. We, we, we, people like this are all the time
where they're like, oh, you don't know everything there is to know about physics. How dare you have
a nihilism episode? What the fuck are you doing, you dumb bitches? But, but, like, are, like,
are we not allowed to comment on things as we see them? Because it's not, it's not like we are
forming them out, out of the ether, purely from, like, going into fortune and hearing
secondhand information. We've all seen furries. I mean, it's also not, it's not as though at the end
of a PCP episode, whatever conclusion we've come to about, like, how we should all think about
this. We press a button and now, like, it is so, you know, like, oh, I've, we've, oh, we've concluded
furries are bad. I press this button and now that's what the world is from this point forward.
It's like, there's no consequence to this show. Well, this is, this is a comedy show, everybody.
It's just the conversation. And like, that's, I guess that's the interesting part is like,
because for everybody who's like into the furry thing, being like, they're missing so much the
important nuance, like, there's also people who are outside. If you feel that way, please look
at what we're like, this is how even people who are close to furries think of them. So if we're
wrong, this is your PR, motherfucker. Like, you gotta do something about it. I think we've been
pretty magnanimous here, relatively speaking, I think. I mean, I mean, at the end of the day,
I don't have any ill will. This has happened before on other episodes, where I am a fucking
knowledgeable saint. And I will just say what I say if you'll be like, you missed this, you didn't
factor this into your equation. But I did know that fact, and it just wasn't important. Like,
you can say a bunch of shit in the comments about how like furries are like all grain stuff,
or even about how they're all bad. And I will have considered them because I think about this
literally constantly. I know everything that you could possibly say. And this is my opinion.
People like, like the reason I feel the need to comment on this isn't just because I want to be a
funny people with my friends. I don't want to be, I just want to be funny people. No, it's because
I have to think about this. This isn't a joke anymore. This has reached a stage where I could
no longer deny that furries exist and go on with my day just treating them like, ah, they're just
fucking like elves or like trolls. No, furries are real. And I have, I have to, I have to acknowledge
them. It's suffering. I don't like this. I want them to go back to being jokes. I don't like this.
You know, I wonder if like you said at the beginning, and I just remembered my thought,
I thought of the comparison to like the flat earth thing where like that's definitely started as a
joke and a troll, but it just started gaining steam because I don't know, people just like,
we're like, you know what, that's actually not a bad idea. Let's, let's get in on that. And I'm not
trying to shame furries and saying there was craziest flat earthers or anything, but you know,
just, just saying funny comparison. The conclusion I've come away with from this podcast is that I
am a furry. And the only reason I haven't identified it is that I am too much of an
elitist when it comes to the art that I masturbate to. Like if there were furry artists who just drew
anime style, I would be all in on this community because I want to fuck a Pikachu just as badly as
this first suitor does, but she is doing a terrible job of making it look attractive.
Sure. Link did the show notes. We already mentioned I think this.
Indeed. That's the thing. I think like all of us, like, like if some like, you know, guys,
if God gave him dad, it's like, Hey, I'm going to make something to peel us to your taste. It's
just going to be like an anthropomorphic animal. Like it's that cool. So you would probably be
like, yeah, sure. It's not the actual like animal part of it. Like I don't think any of us like
cared that much. The furries, the furries specifically are into that, right? Isn't that what
makes them furry as opposed to like, I've jacked off to tons of furry porn, but for me, it's always
just like, that's a hot girl and oh, she's a dog or whatever. I mean, that's fine. I'll deal with that.
No, what I'm trying to say is that like, it's not like particularly the fact that it is an
anthropomorphic creature. It's just the way that it's always depicted. It's the culture is the
culture of society. Indeed. Indeed. It's the context in which the images exist in.
All right, are we going to move on to questions then? I think it's about time. I think it's about
time. I just want to quickly say, if it wasn't clear enough by this point, because it probably
isn't because it didn't speak much. But you know, overall, I, I like furries in general.
And I like the art, say for work art mostly, I like the character designs a lot. Like what
really interests me about furries is like, they take an animal and they like make a character
design and like the really skilled artists, whenever they like draw like a furry character,
is just like, I don't know why I just, I just really like art. Can my sexuality be art because
I really like art? Well, Mage, here's, here's my question for you. You know, we, uh, we haven't
really addressed this, but, and I think I've asked you personally before, I forget the answer off
hand though, would you consider yourself a furry? You like your anthropomorphic, you know, animal
boys and whatnot? I, I don't know. Like the thing is like, it depends on other people's
definition of furry. I myself am not involved in like any furry communities. Uh, I don't talk to
that many furries. I have no plans in the future to have a fursuit or I'm not even interested
in having a fursuit. I do have a fursona, but that's because I like character designs and
I like making characters and it's just really interesting for me. It's just like, for, for,
people trying to say stuff like, just because you like like MLP or something that like makes
you a brony or something, or just like, I mean, I just hate all the stuff of like, because you
like thing or are generally interested, you like now are considered a member of a community. Anyone
putting a label on you that you don't put on yourself is disgusting. I couldn't agree more,
could not agree more. Yeah. It's, it's like saying everyone who likes a toke is a furry.
So if, if you don't, if, if all those other Ken who refuse to believe that they're human,
guess what? We have no right to call them human. We've lost our, our, it's, it's over. We're done.
He's right. We fucked it up. Yep. We've all learned something today.
All right. Well, I guess that's it. Let's, let's head over to our questions. We're all
furries. We admit it. That was the point. That's who we were building to. We all admit it. We're
active members of the community. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. There's something
huge. Okay. What animal would you be, Nate? Like, what would your persona be? What animal would
you be? Well, I mean, okay, sure, sure. Uh, everybody always tells me a pig. Sure. That was,
that was the old animal design she did for us and Ben and I were orcs. Um, I mean, everyone says
I'm like a dog. My girlfriend says I'm like a dog. I think I bear a lot of resemblance to a
dog. It works for me, man. I think I'm a dog. I bear a lot of resemblance to a dog like currently.
I resemble a dog. Apparently I look like a German shepherd. I know how much Michelle
like dogs. So that must be, that's pretty good. That's pretty good. It's good for the old romance.
Michelle's a furry for sure, but just for dogs. Oh, it even goes with the best guy ever because,
you know, what's the best compliment to a dog? The best boy. A good boy. He's a good boy. Yeah.
Works for me. I think I could be a dog. I think you can make a strong argument for a dog. I think
it could also be a raccoon or an owl. I would definitely ban a raccoon is fucking perfect.
I was going to go with sloth. I was going to go with sloth. Especially because a raccoon has got
like kind of an edgy like design and everything. No, you're all missing the most obvious point.
Raccoons dig through everyone's trash. Yeah, exactly. Yeah. It's perfect. It's perfect.
Pensacoon for sure. It's got it. I mean, you know, raccoons are actually nasty. Like they're
actually idiots. Yeah, exactly. Deeply unpleasant creatures. I know you're saying all the right
things. All right. Have you seen their hands? Have you seen a raccoon's hands? Oh, yes, grimy.
They are. They are. They have nasty little like gremlin skeleton hands. Just take a raccoon and
have a vape pen in one hand and a, you know, a tablet pen in the other and you got yourself
a Ben St right there. All right. I would be a Hopkinsville goblin. That's what my
What the hell is that? Here. That's some other kinship. That is some other kinship.
It's this way right here. If I, oh god, why are Google image like links so unbelievably big?
Why is that the case? You just got to go to the actual like image.
But that's technically not an animal. It's like, no, it's an animal. It's an animal.
This is other kin. This is other kin, Munchie. Crippid. Crippid or whatever. Bigfoot is real.
So the Hopkinsville goblin. This is just like the time I told the furries that I was a that I was a
mind flare. I didn't know that fucking Dungeons and Dragons invented that. Well, wait a kink
shame, Ben. I would definitely be like a normal type Pokemon. I would be like some sort of like
bear or like something big and fat and doesn't give a shit. Or like, you know, you know that big
like fairy normal type bear that was a tank and like sun and moon. Beware. Beware is pretty good.
And he's a very Munchie. The way that that Pokemon is portrayed in the TV show is like a Munchie-esque
character. That's true. A power. Because all he does is show up and beat up people and carry them
around basically. All right, Digi, what would you be? Oh, I would be a walrus, probably.
A walrus. I'd like to be depicted as a walrus. Yeah, okay. Well, I already have a fursona,
but I just before I made her like she's a gerboa. That's like a like a little
right mouse thingie. That's a Raichu is right? Wait, is he? Oh, yeah, I think Raichu is one of
those based on it. No, don't you boas. You know, Mew is actually more gerboa-esque than a cat-esque.
Oh, yeah, that's true. With his weird old legs. Yeah, okay. Even the tail. And he'll like, yeah,
gerboa, hopping mouse, whatever. It's cute little hoppy legs. I love it. But before I made her,
I was heavily debating between like a unicorn or a deer or a bunny because I like this
something cute ones. And but like none of them like had all the things I needed because I wanted
a long tail and that I also wanted to like be sort of fluffy and cute and long years. Yeah,
long years and long tail and like I couldn't I couldn't have that with any of those properly.
So, yeah, then I found gerboa and then all my prayers were answered.
Well, if there was ever evidence of God, there it is, everybody. And Tom and Tom, I think I'm
thinking guerrilla. I'm thinking a guerrilla. A powerful beast. Oh, I think you're on the right
track. I think like a like what's the what's the long monkey? There's like a long monkey. There's a
long monkey. What's a given? A orangutan. You know, I could see Tom as like a lemur.
Okay, I don't think I don't think orangutan hits. Well, okay. Well, what does Tom think though?
I literally never thought of this before. So you're all in floor informing me very deeply right
as like a dust skull. I'm not I'm not I'm not dust skull. I'm not opposed to lemur lemur would
be kind of cool. I was all I was going to say was my favorite my favorite animals are crows. I
find crows fascinating. I can see ravens and crows are cool as shit. I can say you'd be a raven
because that's like the fucking raven that's so like fucking big. Yeah, I like the bigger versions
of crows, right? I think crows are bigger. Oh my god. Guys, this literally looks like Tom. Hold on.
This is Tom. That I mean, I see a result. I opened up discord and saw the heart Hopkinsville
goblins. Got it. All right, let's get on the fucking questions. All right. Okay, draw us as our first
is everyone. Yes, please. All right, yo, Twitter at TP Crasnators. Follow us for announcements
of stuff. And yo, here's a question. Hashtag ask bcp. Send questions using the hashtag. Okay,
here we go. Now here's one that was reading and I like this one. Okay, here we go. It's at chaotic
sloth an old patron of mine. What's up, buddy says up in your own opinion. Do you have to like a person
to be able to like their content? And for some reason, he adds animations don't count. I don't
know why he would throw that in the trash. Throw that in the trash. Yeah, what is different? What
at all is different? Okay, mage, what do you think? What do you think? The reason he mentioned is
because of the recent controversy in the anime community with Princess molestia getting her
own anime at a long last. It's like the guy who made that really cute over Rony Kenshin or whatever,
right? Like it was just a sugar cube. All right, sorry. I'm more recent one. Like, oh yeah,
I'm a mo junkie. That anime. Oh, what did he do? What did he do? One of the directors, like, I think
he's like confirmed to be an actual Nazi. And he's denying an actual Nazi for what? Yeah, I mean,
I get in, he's denying the Holocaust. Oh, who hasn't denied the Holocaust? You know what's
interesting about that? That is so weird of a thing to even know about an anime director. Like,
how many anime directors do you know any element of their personality? Because the controversy
was so big it reached me and I hate that. There was a huge Twitter snap. He publicly just kept
doing it on Twitter. Even if this is a thing that happened, I still don't see why it merits an
exception for animation. And Ben means the Holocaust. I'm not surprised about this. So,
is it the anime director and not like the American? I'm not surprised that an old Japanese man would
deny the Holocaust at all. I'd be surprised if most of them even know what it is. He's not that
old. It can't be that old. I mean, the Japanese and the Germans were allies. That's like saying
your best friend from back in the day killed a bunch of Jews. I'm looking this up. I mean,
how do they know? Nobody fucking knows anything. I don't know. You know what's funny about this,
though? It's interesting to note that, by the way, it is the director. It's Kazuyoshi Yaginuma.
But it's interesting to note that at long last, it seems like anime maker people
like the people who nobody has given a shit about in the West, Japan's a pretty right-wing conservative,
especially with immigration and stuff and race issues. At long last, people are starting to
care about what they think and they're finally facing some backlash. I think I had a moment
actually a while back where I was like, you know, I'm really excited about the fact that
all these animators and everything are on Twitter and we have more open communication.
But this cannot take long before this leads to something like this. And I just didn't expect
someone to come out as a fucking holocaust to die. Well, let's do this. Listen to this. Okay,
quote from Kazuyoshi. Here it is. One bit September 8th, 2012. Have you looked into
whether Anne Frank's diary is real? Oh, no. I mean, I haven't. I haven't.
I love you, Jesus Christ. This guy's a big Utermilk hotel fan, for sure. Well, that's something.
Jesus Christ, I love you.
In the airplane over the seam, I do. I had heard of this, but I haven't looked into it very much.
And I just want to say that like, just because you deny the holocaust does not actually make
you a Nazi. I'm just putting that out there. You could be an anti-Semite. You can hate the Jews.
I'm not putting that on you. But also, Japan, if you recall, everybody, Japan had a pretty
cozy relationship with the Nazis back in the day. So they've been across the board pretty forgiving.
I feel like holocaust and Nile is probably pretty rampant.
It's probably rampant across a lot of the world outside of America and Europe.
They did Nan King, man. Yeah, Nan King was like a nightmare.
The Nan King incident, as they recall.
Fuck, I forgot what I was going to goddamn say. I kept talking about the fucking Nan King shit.
Well, I mean, regardless, I think once this Pandora's Box open and we start to actually judge
like Japanese creators by their opinions, I think that is Pandora's Box.
I was going to say, to answer the actual fucking question,
yes, I think you could enjoy art regardless of the creator, but it really depends on the
piece because sometimes you feel like the creature, like sometimes I look at something like Ruroni
Kenshin. I don't think the original manga is even all that good, but like the offshoots of it,
clearly there's no influence of this guy's being a fucking pedophile on Ruroni Kenshin,
other than maybe there's like a couple of cute younger characters. There's not even really
any lollies in it. There's a couple of minor ass characters. They are cute though, but like
the series, you don't have to think about that when watching Ruroni Kenshin. It's not going
to strike you. You're not going to watch a scene and be like, oh, this totally reminds
me of the fact that he was a pedophile, but there's other stuff like some music, for instance,
where the musician is so baked into the song that if you don't like them as a person,
it's unavoidable when you're listening to the music that you're being hit with their
personality basically. It's going to remind you of the things you don't like about though.
Yeah, you also have to keep in mind that a lot of mediums are made by more than just one person,
for instance, that anime that I said. He's just a director. He's like a whole
slew of people working on that anime. Just because he's, let's say, a scumbag, doesn't mean
no, you have to shame the anime. That's a fair point. That is a fair point. I haven't seen it,
but I believe you. A lot of people have said that it's quite good, and the main character
reminds me of you. The director didn't make the source material of it anyway. It's not his story.
It's fair to criticize the man himself if you strongly disagree with him,
and you can choose to not want to. Well, that's the thing. But are you supporting him so much?
If you are supporting him by supporting his work, and if so, does that support his belief
structure? I honestly don't think it would even be possible to support that guy by buying the
work, because for what it's worth, first of all, it's not how anime works. If you buy a
Blu-ray, it doesn't just put money in the director's pocket. And second of all, that
dude's probably going to get fired and blacklisted at this point. Who knows how Japan works with
stuff. Japan is just very anti-PR at anything. The fact that he has bugs around him is the
problem. It's not what he said. It's that you can't be a controversial figure.
The question, I think the answer to this is obviously, yes, you can enjoy work. But that
doesn't mean that you always will be able to or even want to. If the politics leak into the work,
and you don't like them, it's going to be hard to ignore. At that point, you hate the product,
not the person. Who did not just use you, for example, did you? Sure, your anime essays could
be those standalone, but they do require people to know about you and lead to you, the person.
I mean, it really depends. I mean, I've always kept the main channel relatively clean in certain
ways. I don't run around saying nigga constantly on that channel. The way I see it, I want people
who wouldn't be okay with that to be able to enjoy my videos so that I can cast a wider net,
so that I can make more money. When you come to the side channels, I don't give a fuck, because
ultimately, I would rather just do whatever I want than be an acceptable artist on any level.
In order to maintain making money from a larger amount of people who I am deliberately dooping,
like I'm deliberately not showing them the entire picture of myself, as most people don't. Most
people don't show you everything about themselves, even if it's something that is public about them
in another way. On the internet, all those things kind of bleed together if they're all under the
same name. And you can call that dooping, but really, no matter what situation we're in, there
are things that we choose to offer and choose to not offer in a given situation. Would you not call
that dooping? Well, it's more just withholding information that you don't need. People who
watch the Otaku Gaza Journalist channel don't need to know that I'm a guy, a white boy who says
niggah all the time. That is irrelevant to those videos that I'd prefer they just not think about
it. I'm not saying that it is dooping. I don't think it is, but I would think that Nate would
think it is. I'm surprised that he doesn't. Technically, you could call that dooping,
but it's just if you call that dooping, you have to define basically every human interaction as
also dooping to some degree. Didn't we talk about how you consider every human action deceit?
Yes, and this is exactly that issue. I think what he's saying is that the word dooping would
lose meaning if we applied it to all. Then why is holding an open the door for someone deceit?
We're talking about degrees here. We're talking about degrees. Is this the part of the episode
where we have to splice in all of the weird utilitarian episodes? Please splice it in, everybody.
God damn it. Well, okay, I think we've basically covered this question. So,
chaotic sloth, thanks for the good one. That was a juicy one. That was a hashtag,
not bad question from Twitter. Hashtag. This is from the Patreon lounge. Donate any amount to
get into the Patreon lounge and you can answer the exclusive questions. Patreon.com is like
the procrastinators. Yes. This is about Julian my Julian. How do we get closer to PCPHQ? What
does the roadmap look like to that? Well, the roadmap is wait for digits to move and then it,
yeah, throw money and just wait. Yeah, I mean, like some of us are just already like,
I'm moving very soon because I have to move at the end of May. Like there's no question about that
and my plan is move to Boston because I mean, at this point, I like it's too late to even change
plans. So, so we're going to Boston. Make the best of it. Yeah. And I mean, Tom's already there.
Munchie's already planning to go there. You know, it wouldn't be hard for if Nate decides he's,
you know, ready to finally leave his job, then that's probably where he's going. So like,
it's just kind of a matter of time. But if you want to grease the wheels and make sure that it
actually happens and nothing fucks up, keep throwing money at us because we need the money to
make it happen. I mean, PCPHQ is entirely a financial issue. Yeah, that's correct. That's
correct. Yeah. I mean, yeah, everybody, I don't expect anybody to go way out of their way. And
like, I don't, I generally dislike the idea of like giving money for like future projects that
aren't specifically being promised. Like I certainly wouldn't give it. I mean, you got to think of
yourselves as a production committee and are you willing to take a risk on a product you want
to see exist? Like if you spend that money now, you're making an investment towards the idea that
a type of content you think you want, at the very least, might come to fruition. Will you be horribly
disappointed? It's possible. But like, yeah, sure. I mean, that's a perfectly fine way to think about
and like, again, everyone's making a personal decision, whether they give to a patron or not,
and for what reasons. And we have specifically stated that like one of our intentions is to make
PCPHQ happen. If we had more money, we could start making steps in that direction. I'll tell you
right now, for me, the thing that is holding me back from currently going charging all speed ahead
is purely like the need to or like leaving my job is the thing I need to do and being financially
stable. So when I can earn enough money to make sure that's safe and frankly, I'm probably going
to depend on that like whatever whatever that income is, like the portion I get from the PCP
and the portion I get on my own, like that needs to be at a certain level where I think like,
okay, I can I can do this. And you know, it's become a reality that like I'm pretty pretty,
it's not that I'm comfortable at my job, but like, it's got me in a situation where I'm making
enough money that I can keep building up my savings for a while. So to me, I think the logical thing
to do is either my just income on YouTube stuff just goes way up and looks like it's going to stay
that way for a while, or I like work for a while longer, save up more money so that I can take
that risk and you know, jump out there and I'd like to do it as soon as possible. It's all I'm
saying. Do you have any timeframe just for art? I was really hoping it would be in 2018. Looking
at the math, I don't know if that's actually exactly right. So I guess I'd say my hope is like
early 2019. That's my current thoughts, but I have to play it by ear. I have to play it by
ear. All the other questions in the patron lounge are like terrible. How about this question from
Bobby Meow 13? Here's the question, freemium games pay to win mechanics? Question mark?
Um, yes. Yes. Exactly. Yes. Thank you. What's your persona? Wait, okay. Here's one. Here's
one that Cyrus asks, do you think Kanye West is a furry because he always portrays as a bear in his
old album? It was embarrassed by it and didn't read it out loud. There you go. I just wanted to
say Kanye because he's a good boy. I'm looking forward to the new album. Hurry up, boy. This is,
I'm looking at the list of questions. Yeah, I know. It's really upsetting. Giffy thoughts on
passivism. Moving on. We got a question from Hippocrite. Where's Carcat? He's right here.
Carcat, why don't you say something? There's no reason we can't just all have three questions
at the show, right? Like, we can just do that. You know, he's right. We can do whatever we want.
Fuck you guys. Ask him better questions if you want to be read on the goddamn show.
That's perfectly good. Perfectly good. Why is it every episode the proof becomes more and more
evident that you can have wit and you can have, or you can have money, but you can't have both?
Yeah, well, fair enough. I think they just try to rush to be like, to like ask as fast as possible
without like, I mean, the reality is they've got an hour and a half. Yeah, yeah. Bruh on it for
a while, guys. Maybe they think we ask right before we start the section or something. Yeah,
we should clarify that for everybody. Just so you know, if you're asking a question either on
Twitter or on the Discord, you have at least an hour for when the message goes out to form
like, because we do the whole episode. In fact, you're actually probably, you're better off waiting,
because if you respond to our tweet right when we post it, we're not going to dig back and see it,
because we're only going to ask a question. It's better to wait like an hour and a half at least
before you respond to it. At least an hour. Well, I mean, usually we take most of our stuff from
the Discord, but like, they do usually like the first 10 minutes after we post a question,
a bunch of shitty questions get posted that everybody shuts up and it's like, well,
that wasn't helpful. Let me ask you about this, guys. The Q&A is like almost always terrible.
No, I disagree. I totally disagree. Yeah.
I was going to ask, like, what's the point of it? It's funny and entertaining is the point for me.
I think we always choose good questions. They're just rarely our ones to find.
Okay, when there are good questions, it is nice. But I feel like every episode is just like,
look at how bad these questions are. I mean, we always say that while we're looking for good ones.
This is why we need to do questioner rules. We've talked about this a few times here and there.
Why are we talking shop on the middle of the show?
At TP Crasnators, that's the Twitter. Check it out for announcements and all kinds of stuff.
Patreon.com slash TheProCrasnators. One dollar gets into the lounge where you can get your
questions in and we'll fucking see them more likely. And $5 gets you all the bonus episodes.
There's like 12 now. There's a huge library being built. And they're all pretty fucking great.
To clarify, there's 12 and you get them all. I don't know if everybody understands this,
but when you have a patron reward, you get all of it. So like when you patron DigiBro,
you get like hundreds of hours of commentaries of me and DeVoo watching back all of my videos.
That's enough personal shilling, you fucking bitch. I'm definitely editing that out.
Oh, excellent. But that's it, everybody. Thanks for joining. We will see you next week
and stay tuned. Everybody give us money for the new bonus episode. We'll tell you about it next
time. All right, thanks for being around and we'll see you next time. Bye.
I am a furry. I love Anthrocon. See you at Anthrocon. See you at Anthrocon. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.