Hello everyone and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Uh, I'm sorry darling, I'm listening to the PCP right now. It's so interesting. It's so
arousing. It's so exciting. It's so- what's- fuck how does it go? It's so something. Haven't
heard that song in a while. Hey, shout outs to Pro Sasuke for that tune. That was you right?
Oh god, I'm almost certain. Anyway, uh, welcome to the pro solo Bencast. It's here guys. It's
here. The day has arrived. The day has arrived. I'm in charge. I'm in charge. I own the road.
I can do whatever I want. And no one can stop me. I'm here to say thanks for listening.
And if this excites you, if the thought of the solo Bencast is titillating for you, as it should be,
you can get more on patreon.com slash ben saint where I do one of these every month just about
me and myself. What's going on? So, hmm, I don't have a plan. I never come into the
PCP with a plan. So what am I going to talk about? Let me talk about what's been going on with me.
Just very briefly, um, Vapors 2. It's coming out. It's getting printed. It's in the process right
now. Very exciting. Fulfillment shall begin. RFCK, Endless War, just got a big update. I wasn't
really involved in making it. I'm not much on the coding side of things anymore, hardly at all really.
But the pins, the pin kickstarter, those are also in production, entering the final stages. I should
have the samples of all the pin designs tomorrow. That's what UPS tells me. Very exciting. Uh,
that's great. That's cool and all. Good shit going on. Um, but enough about that. Let's talk about
the absolute state of the PCP. Um, just yesterday or was it the day before? I don't remember.
They all blur together. There was some Twitter shit. I went on Twitter. I went on the Procrastinator's
account and I said, it's, it's maybe time. This was, Tom had said that like, we need to start
thinking about what if the videos don't come back? And yeah, I agree. It's starting to seem like maybe
they won't. Um, YouTube keeps emailing us back. Whenever Nate sends an email, we get an email
back saying, thanks for reaching out. Thanks for your patience. There's still no update. We're working
on it. Um, meanwhile, like, you know, my, my close personal friend, Maryweather, who this is not
anything against him, I'm just using it as an example because I happen to notice that he had a,
a, a video get, uh, you know, falsely copyright flagged and it got taken down. He said so to
Team YouTube on Twitter and he got a response within like a day and his video went back up.
Hmm. Could it be that he has 10 times as many followers on Twitter? Could it be that he has
10 times as many YouTube subscribers? Hmm. Probably not. I don't see any correlation there.
And I certainly don't think that correlation implies causation. Heavens, heaven forbids
to Betsy. Um, so, you know, they, they're just God, they, I'm gonna, I'm gonna look at the fucking
Twitter because I'm so mad. I'll just tell you what happens. If you don't, if you don't look at
Twitter, that's fine. Um, I'll, I'll give you the blow by blow. Um, because this is infuriating.
Uh, you know, I said, um, you know, email us if you have the streams, right? At this point,
it's like, okay, we got to think about, are we, do we have to reupload? Um, if anyone has, I know
at least some of the streams were saved by, by one or two people. These were the people who,
they contacted us during Radcom when we thought we lost the streams and they had saved them.
So somebody has them saved, at least some of them. Some of them could be lost forever. I don't know.
Um, but at least some of them have been saved somewhere. So I sit in the tweet like, uh,
our content's gone. YouTube's really being sluggish. Email us at the procrastinators mail
at gmail.com. If you would be so kind, if you have a copy and can provide it with us for a
potential reupload in the future and fuck in team YouTube. Thanks for the follow-up. We're
still working on your case. We understand that this can be very frustrating, but rest assured that
we're doing our best to recover the deleted content. Appreciate your patience in the meantime.
Okay. Thanks for that, I guess. And then follow-up. We also recommend deleting your previous tweet
as it contains your personal info, email address. This is so that you can restore your privacy.
So you can send secure your privacy and security at all times. Hope this helps. Oh yeah, team
YouTube. That helps a lot. That's big. That's, that's a, that's doing a lot for me right now.
And I really appreciate it. I totally didn't think that gosh, if I said the email, someone might find
our email. And then who knows what could happen. Thank you. I'm sure you don't just want us to
delete the tweet because it's embarrassing that you made a fucking clerical error or, or a deliberate
decision, maybe, at this point, who knows, to just fucking destroy our content for no reason
and not even explain why. You know, it couldn't be that you just don't want us saying that on
Twitter. No. I'm very mad. I'm very mad about this PCP situation. That's it. I, what, you know, it
must be the moon. It must be those damn witches that cursed the moon. I don't know if you've seen
today. This is a trending thing on Twitter. Apparently someone says that some, some witches
did a blood hex on the moon and now it's bad. I don't know. I hadn't actually read the original
article, but I believe it. You know, I don't know the evidence, but I buy the premise that the moon
is cursed and we're all feeling the consequences. It just seems, it just seems, it just seems plausible.
You know, it just seems like something that it feels true is what I'm saying.
Oh, man. What else thing to update about the fucking procrastinator podcast?
You know, this, this shit is all happening. This content deletion has occurred. We're uploading
on the website. If you're listening to that on the website, hey, good job. You found me.
And, but we're still, we are still making some progress on the, on the rad con stuff that we
didn't deliver on yet, like the, the OVA and stuff. We are, we are chugging along that we've made a
little more headway on that. It'll, you know, when we'll be done. I don't know, but it's gonna get,
it's, it's getting there. It's, it's progressing. Oh man. I don't know. It's the solo Ben cast. And
you know, you've all given me a very easy out. This time, let me just, uh, the pro you've all
given me an easy out because I have been less censurious, censorious, um, with, with voicemails.
I think people are liking it. I think people are liking it. I'll play anything. I'll do anything.
I'm crazy. Uh, I mean, I'm Antifa. Um,
so I've been getting a lot more voicemails, so maybe I'll just jump into voicemails and see
how long that, that takes me. By the way, that guy, um, that guy who made the don't support PCP
or Digi Bro because Ben is Antifa and Digi is a quote unquote degenerate. Uh, that guy
privated the video. However, I did have the foresight to save a copy. I have a copy of that
video saved. And I think I might, I'm, I'll, I'll, I'll ask around and see if anyone else,
if there's a problem, if I do this, I think this should be fine, but I might re upload the video
just to Patreon, just as like, if you're a patron and you miss that video and you want to hear
all the reasons why, you know, the PCP hates America. I might put make that
just a little patron bonus exclusive thing since, since, since our, our friend has decided to redact
it publicly. Um, but you know, you put it, he put it, he put it out there and you know, he said it,
you know, people saw it. Um, anyway, so I might do that. Patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Uh, but let's jump into voicemails and just see where the night, where the, where that leads.
Um, the first one is a hip hop is bad. You guys were talking about Kanye being the,
like running for president and shit. And, uh, you were mentioned the statement from a guy who said
that like, uh, hip hop sucks because they all just brag about stuff. And, um, yeah, bragging
in raps is like bad, but like the reverse is good because like I saw this other quote. I, uh,
it was like rap stopped being good when they stopped rapping about being poor and started
rapping about being rich. And, uh, I feel like that is actually true. And the rap that is about
like being vulnerable emotionally or financially or just in any way is better. And then like rap
where they're talking about how great they are and how they have money and bitches and all that
shit like that. Um, and that kind of just applies to any music. Like if you're, you know, talking
yourself up, it's kind of cringe, but if you're like, you know, letting you open in the doors to
your heart and shit, that's, that's epic and based every single time, even like all the music, you
know, right, right on. Um, I think, yeah, I don't, I'm like, I can understand the appeal and yeah,
not just rap anything, anything that any piece of media or whatever that is like bragging about
your success, bragging about how rich you are. It's like, okay, seems like the base appeal of that
would be like other rich people would like that. Cause like, yeah, I can relate to it. Like who's
going to, like no one's going to relate to that except other rich people or people who, or maybe
just people who overestimate their own success, right? Those are two things, but like there's
more poor people than rich people. Um, so I don't know. It's just based on the numbers game. I don't
get it, but apparently I'm wrong because people do seem to like rag raps. That's people don't
generally have a problem with it. As a fucking communist, uh, you know, I'm just inclined to be
like, hmm, wealth doesn't seem like a thing to be bragging about. If anything, I feel like you
should be embarrassed of it because you're hoarding resources and that's bad. Um, but I mean, obviously
not everyone feels that way. So yeah, uh, the, the, the, the quote, I remember quoting, I think
was Benjamin Dixon, he wasn't saying like bragging, rapping is bad. He was just saying that like the
rap culture celebrates capitalism and monetary accumulation, which seems from an outsider's
respect, as someone who doesn't, isn't into music at all, from an outsider's perspective,
that feels true. Um, but yeah, uh, good point. Next one is from stop recording.
Please stop recording unless you have at least four people on, because it's just, the podcast is
only wasting my time now with just two hour episodes that are shit. Um, like make two hour
episodes that waste my time and are funny again. Stop making shit. Okay. You dumb, you dumb motherfucker.
Okay. Listen, if you don't like, if you don't like episodes that have fewer people on them,
I guess that's fine. That's valid and you're entitled to your opinion. But why, like what,
what would you gain? What would you gain if we decided no, no, no, anything that doesn't have,
let's say four people on it shouldn't exist. We won't make it. What's the benefit? I, why? Like,
I could under, I could, if you, I don't see what's inherently worse about something that has, like,
here I am on the Ben Solo cast, like obviously I have a vested interest in this concept, right?
I don't see what is inherently worse about it, about having fewer people. I could understand
that you're having a preference, maybe it tends to be lower energy, or maybe it's just less likely
that, you know, your favorite guy or whatever is going to be on it. Fair enough. Why would we stop?
Why would we stop? I don't get it. You haven't explained it to me. You haven't convinced me.
Owned. Next one is from Thank You, Nate.
This message is from Nate. I saw your high school, the dead video recently, and it inspired me to
make a big change in my life. For years, I've been trying to win the affection of this girl by
trying to communicate that I need her, trying to appeal to the fact that she's my friend and she
cares about me to get her to be with me. That doesn't work, lads. You have to do the opposite.
It comes down to your dignity or your crush. Pick your dignity every time. That doesn't mean
never admit you're wrong. Just only do it when you actually think you are wrong. Even if that
trade-off works, you do not want to be one of those guys that's married to a woman that doesn't
respect him. You have to be okay without a woman for her to respect you. The thing I always got
caught up in was that I'd never met anyone who I wanted to spend my life with, like this girl,
and I don't think I ever will. But that doesn't matter because you don't actually need to be
with them. You need to work for something that you care about so much. Then even if it's all
you have, all alone, you'll be okay. Maybe this girl will come back to me someday or maybe I will
be alone. But if that happens, I will be okay. Thank you, Nate. You were close. You swerved a
little at the very end there. Surely, I'm going to give you the benefit of the doubt and assume
that surely, in hindsight, you can see that maybe this girl will come back to me or maybe I'll be
alone is kind of the wrong lesson. If you don't, like you said, you don't need anyone. You can be
self-sufficient. You can be happy alone. That's called valuing yourself, having, I don't know,
dignity or whatever. It's a component of that, right? If you can do that, then surely, surely
you must see that it's not the logical extension of that is not, okay, okay, so I can be alone.
And the only alternative is this girl. You've gotten there, kind of, but you're not quite at
the finish line. I haven't seen High School of the Dead. I haven't seen Nate's High School of the
Dead video. But yes, oneitis is bad. You will not, you will, that's, if you know, that's when
you are obsessed with one girl and you're like, oh, this is the only girl for me. That's bad.
That's not healthy. And the idea of like appealing to them is like, oh, you're my friend and I care
about you, right? It's like, you can't, you can't like, if someone doesn't like you, you can't,
you can't appeal to them on the basis of how much you like them, right? Like, no matter,
no matter how much you like someone, that's not gonna make them like you. Like, so there's no
point in appealing, like either they like you or they don't. And maybe there's no, there's no use,
like, there's no end, like the more you try to work on it, like you can't like be like, okay, okay,
well, let me, let me try and fix that. Let me do something to make them like me. It's like, well,
if you're, if you're, if you're deliberately working on that as a project, like it's a bad look,
right? It's like, you shouldn't be, you shouldn't be working on that. You should be doing your thing.
And if someone likes it, they like it, right? So the thing is, so there's no,
there's no fixing that if they don't like you, you just got to, you just got to do your thing.
And if they, maybe, if they change their minds, maybe they, they probably won't,
because you shouldn't be doing anything radically different. You should be doing your thing.
All times, you should be doing your thing. And if you keep doing your thing,
then the people who are into it will be down for it. And they're in, and they're out, and they're
out, but down, and all around, like the Heffalumps and Wuzels. Okay, woo, cool, good, good, good
story, guy. Next one is from Nate, quote, full-time YouTuber and quote, best man. Let's hear what he
asked to say. The other day, it just dawned on me. I'm a full-time YouTuber now. I've kind of been for,
you know, nine, 10, 11 months now, 12 almost. Yeah, how many, and how many videos came out in
that time? Nate, full, I'm reading into the intention of these air quotes here. It's like,
okay, full-time, yeah. Glad, I'm glad you don't have to work a wagey job. But I'm not alone in asking,
where's best anime ever, Ghost in the Shell? Where's Gits, Nate, full-time YouTuber best man?
Give me the content. I want the content.
Oh God, I hope these aren't all about Nate. The next one is called, for real, is Nate sexist?
Let's fucking do it, lads. You know, guys, I don't know how to feel about Nate these days,
you know? It seems like he really hates women and like makes fun of them all the time.
I'm genuinely wondering if he's sexist. Mr. Bestman, do you care to comment?
I'm not sexist. Thank you.
Well, there it is. You mean you heard it. That's it. There's no, there's no more. There's nothing
else to say on the matter. We have the word of God, and that's it, end of discussion. Cool, simple.
Next one is from Margar, who famously has been the last person to call in
a few times in a row now, but not this time. We've got more. We've got plenty more after this.
Let's hear from Margar, shall we? Margar here. I'd like to question my status in voice jail.
Has it been abolished? Am I set free? What happens to a person when there are no police,
but they get arrested? Do I still exist? I still want to send voicemails every week.
It's, I look forward to it now. I have made a pattern of it. Don't put me in jail. I've done
nothing wrong. I like it. Don't do it, please. Well, that's for a judge to decide. I can tell,
okay, the status is there was disagreement about whether voice jail was the proper course of
action. And so your trial was held up. You are currently caught up in red tape. You are being
processed by the system. The system is working. The process is working. It's in the process.
You are being put through the machine. However, while you are not technically in voice jail,
which was not technically about, we did not fully abolish voice jail with the charity stream,
but effectively you are detained and unable and lack your freedom while you are in the
processing phase. And frankly, I intend to use it, do everything in my power to make sure
that the process takes, never comes to completion. You are never brought to trial,
and you are never free. But that's just me. So I hope that answers your question and you're welcome.
Next one is called BLM. Okay. All right. Hey, what's up again? I'm here again talking about
everybody. The last two weeks, I've been trying to get a hold of Nate Bestman because he's a
fucking coward and won't show up on his own show. This is the whole point of him using the N word.
Don't really appreciate it as a viewer and a listener. So he does fucking stuff for that.
Again, and also stop talking over the voicemails. It's really hard to listen
when you're talking over. Okay. You have a limit of 90 seconds. Okay. I got 96 to talk
when I apologize. I deeply, deeply apologize for talking over the voicemail. That's my
bad friend. Nothing else up with me. You know, just chilling right here. Okay. Nate to respond to
this message. Okay. I'm sorry. I can't, I can't, I can't raise all right or
issues of the N word and his reason. Okay, bro. It's not cool. Okay. You wouldn't even say in
front of an African American. Go fuck off. All right.
I, oh God. Yeah. I mean, I'm, I'm, I'm with you. And I think I would mostly agree.
I mean, I know Nate's said it before. I mean, I've said it before. I can't, I have. I just,
it's happened. Ingest always, but I have. So there it is. I don't think it was a good idea.
I'm not like saying like, no, it's fine. I don't know if it is fine, but, but it's happened. So
I'm not above it. But Digi's explanation of why her, what she said. Okay. I hope I'm not
misremembering, but like her explanation is that like she grew up in a school that was like
very much black population and a lot of people there said it all the time and she said it and
it was like a part of growing up in her culture. That doesn't sound completely ridiculous to me.
You know, if you grew up and everyone around you said it, sure. I, I would,
I mean, you wouldn't say it. I don't think did you, or I don't think anyone would say it in
front of like, I know she would probably say it in front of like certain people that she knows,
you know, black people, maybe certain people who she knows is fine with it. Probably she wouldn't
say it in front of just any random person, black person, that would be like real fucked up. So,
I don't know. I personally don't think that I should say it. I don't, you know,
even, even as a joke, I don't necessarily, I don't stand by the times that I've said it in the past
before. It's bad. It's, you shouldn't say it generally. But I'm not here to police anyone's
language. I'm not here to say like, you can't say that. I do think, you know, I might not agree with
it. I might think that generally probably white people probably don't say it, but I'm not gonna,
I don't have the power to enforce that. And I don't think that I can say you can't,
that's just me. It's everyone's, the words you use, ultimately, it's up to you, myself,
I don't think I should say it, but I can't speak for anyone else. But I did not disagreeing with you
in thinking that probably don't say it. So that's my opinion. I don't like it, but I'm not a cop.
Yeah, I think that's what I think about that. Okay, next one. A question people might hate.
Let's see about that. Did Nate stop showing up because there's drama or just because he's cringe?
I mean, Nate has given no explanation why he stopped showing up. He did just move.
I don't know why. I mean, I don't think moving would explain not being on the show for, you know,
like six weeks or whatever. It doesn't take that long to move. I don't think any drama did it,
like I don't recall any particular drama occurring before Nate stopped showing up.
Other than maybe like the,
Nate had had Nate stopped showing up before the channel, the content got deleted. Did he like,
did he like recuse himself out of like shame or something or a general upset about like,
you know, what's happened to the channel? I don't know. I don't know what the relation,
if there's any relationship to that happening here. I have no idea. Short answer, no clue.
No clue why Nate doesn't show up anymore. It doesn't make any sense. Seems really weird to me.
But you know, here I am, the only one still here. So, so clearly I'm the weird one.
All right, cool. Next one is from Doon Koon. My man.
PCP. This is Doon Koon from Procrastinate is Anonymous.
And I demand the immediate release of All Dye Corporation from The Voice Jail.
I am invoking my voice grail status to free my nigga All Dye. Do it or we'll kill you with guns
in Minecraft. Oh God, okay. Hold on. I gotta check something. I gotta check something
real quick here. I'll die. I mean, was not released, was not one of the ones released
from Voice Jail during the BLM stream, right? Let me just make absolutely sure of that. I have the
jail image saved here. Yep, it was. It was Mozilla Fennekin, a well-researched thesis,
and Japanese man Yuta who were freed. Still in there are lol pussies out here eating with spoons,
Lost Tape Archive, All Dye Corporation, Oopsie Bobo, and Fuck Dye Buster.
Those are the ones still in there. I'm pretty sure eating with spoons is TNCP.
Hope I'm remembering that right. But, but,
Doon Koon, I don't remember you being in Voice Grail, but if indeed you are in the Voice Grail,
then we have stipulated before that like Matter and Antimatter, Voice Jail and Voice Grail
cancel one another out and mutually annihilate one another in a burst of pure light that extends
in a time-space cone throughout the fabric of reality. So, if indeed if you're not pulling
one over on me, if you're in the Voice Grail, then there we go. All Dye Corporation, you're free.
You're free, fucker. Congratulations. Pussies out here eating with spoons, Oopsie Bobo,
and Fuck Dye Buster are the only ones left in Voice Jail since Margar is still being processed.
He's not technically made it into his cordoned off cell yet, which why I have specially prepared
for him. He hasn't made it there yet though, so there's only three in there. So we're closer
than ever to abolishing Voice Jail, which obviously I'm conflicted about. Obviously,
I'm of two minds about that. On the one hand, cops bad. On the other, prison labor, highly profitable.
So, I don't know. Let me just, just for reference, let me,
let me make sure, let me remove him from the image so that I won't forget. There we go.
This, it's Canon now. It's, it's Canon. Done. Okay, next up, semi-normie guy. Hmm, I don't like,
I don't like the cut of this guy's jib. Let's see what he's got to say for himself.
About a year ago, I sent in a voicemail to you guys about me considering joining the military.
At the time, I thought it was the most effective and accessible way to help and serve people,
and I thought that it would develop me as a person in ways that only that career path could.
But I was still torn about it, so I asked you guys's advice. Now, one year in change later,
I look back at those thoughts and my frame of mind has just shifted so much on so many issues,
including but obviously not limited to the military. And so I'm almost embarrassed that I even sent
in that voicemail. I just think it's crazy how much people's perspective can change in such a
short amount of time. Anyways, question I'm leading to is, can any of you remember a time in your
life when you looked back and had this similar experience that I'm having now where you're
cringing at your past self for being just fucking idiot? And what was it that you were being an
idiot about? Thanks. Um, well, I think my answer is going to be kind of boring. But like around
like last year, when I fell down the communism hole, I look back at my I look back at my dumb,
confused, milk toasts, no real convictions about anything, you know, sort of vaguely
liberal, centrist self. And I'm like, absolutely disgusted, like how embarrassing,
how embarrassing to be like that. I don't know. So that's that's me. That's this the most obvious
example. Um, um, what else? What else? I don't fucking know. Um, the military, I don't begrudge
anyone serving in the military. I do think that it's probably not. Yeah, I don't think it's
necessarily like a super helpful or heroic thing to do. I don't think like the United States
military is like a force for good in the world really. Um, but you know, you got to do what
you got to do. And they claim to give like some pretty good like veterans benefits, but then at
the same time it seems like they kind of bend over backwards to find loopholes to deny their
veterans benefits. I hear that all the time that it's actually real hard to get the benefits
you're supposed to have and stuff like that. So, you know, I don't know, but um, you know,
an individual who does it because it's like that they're their their quickest path to like
economic security or whatever. It's like, I get it. Um, but also I'm kind of glad you didn't do it
because I don't think it's super, super great, but whatever. Um, it's not necessarily super
really. It's fine. It could be fine maybe, but probably not. That's bad. Don't join the military.
It's stupid. Uh, ACAB, uh, lol. Uh, next one is from who Ben St. really is. Hmm. Terrible.
Guys, I've finally done it. I finally understand who Ben St. really is. Think about this. Ben
is just Chaz Princeton from Yu-Gi-Oh! Who? Chaz Princeton.
Chaz Princeton. Uh, okay. Well, I like his fashion sense. I like his, I like his look. I like his
vibe. Um, he's got, he's got better hair than I do, but I mean it's, this is Yu-Gi-Oh! So that's fine.
Um, uh, let's, let's read, let's read about Chaz Princeton from the Yu-Gi-Oh! wiki. Chaz Princeton,
known as Jun Manjome in the Japanese version, is an arrogant duelist who serves as one of
Jaden Yu-Ki's rivals throughout the Yu-Gi-Oh! GX series. Chaz is considered Jaden's primary
rival in the same, in the same effect that Setokaiba is the primary rival of Yu-Gi mode.
Okay, so I'm the edgy rival of the GX series. Okay, that's good. They do have dueled one another
total of seven times throughout the seasons of the anime. Through his evolution, he goes from
being a duelist who only respected powerful cards. Is that a thing? Is that a thing in Yu-Gi-Oh!
That's like, oh, even weak cards are good. You gotta love your fucking Pokemon. Just battle with
your favorite. That sucks. That sucks so bad. He only respected powerful cards to a duelist who
believes that there can be effectiveness in any card, specifically shown in his use of Ojama cards.
He becomes a marked threat after becoming the North Academy representative, but after that
becomes more and more a comic relief. Yes, it's me. It is me. It's perfect. Uh, in the manga,
Chas serves much the same purpose as in the anime. Very good. Um, I want to know what are these
Ojamas. They're like nasty little goblins. Um, like, what's, are they like little weak
creatures, but with like funny goofy like side effects or something? I don't know. Uh, it's
yeah, you're right. He, he got it. He did it. Um, next voicemail is from
Nat. These are all caps. Naz, question mark, greater than Chas. Well, we just found out that Chas
Princeton is base. So I hope you're not gonna, I hope you're not gonna shit on my boy, but I think
this is talking about the Capitol Hill Autonomous Zone, I think. Um, I don't know what Naz is, but
let's, let's find out. We're entering a new era, a golden era for the PCP. No more Chas. We are in
the Naz, the Nate Autonomous Zone. What do you guys think? Let's air some grievances, shall we?
Why is Nate so bad at communicating? Why can't he like, you know, let us know he's moving and stuff?
Um, he wanted to move at the end of the last month, but he didn't. Okay, he's moving now,
and that's fine. But what the fuck is up? Where are you at, dog? He's canceled a bunch of streams,
and he hasn't been on any of the episodes. Okay, maybe. Let's say, hypothetically, he's editing
some videos. That's fine and all, but is an hour or two to come hang with you guys really that big
of a time sink? I don't know. I don't know. I don't, I don't know. You know, I don't, I don't have the
answers. I don't have answers to these questions. It really makes you wonder. Uh, the Nate Autonomous
Zone, that doesn't, no, it would be like, because Nate, it's a Capitol Hill Autonomous Zone,
then the Nate Autonomous Zone would be an Autonomous Zone located in or around Nate,
so that doesn't work. I don't know what you would call it, but I understand the point.
Uh, yeah, we're free, we're free of his tyranny, the tyranny of his, of his, of his ledgers,
um, and his, and his fucking, his, uh, his, uh, his devil, his devil's advocate centrism. We're
free, everyone. Uh, we've made it to the other side. Uh, no one can fucking stop me. Um, uh,
and here I am. Here I am, you know, speaking truth to power. And, you know, I'm proud of myself.
I'm proud of myself to stand up to bullies. Yeah, yeah. No, no, uh, I don't know. I don't know
what the fuck his deal is, you know, whatever. Uh, he doesn't want to explain himself and that is
his prerogative. Um, next up is from Slyther Slacker. I think I know who this is, but let's
hear him, shall we? Quick clarification. Slyther Sean is also me, a.k.a. the voicemail god.
Also, the reason for that was I rebranded my channel to fit more with my theme. I'm going to
be doing a big ol' UgeoGX lecture in the future. And also, question for y'all. How many notes
or how long were your notes for your lectures? I'm currently sitting on a Google doc at 21 pages.
Um, um, my notes, uh, okay. Well, I'll speak for myself. My, I didn't take that many notes.
My first Sonichi lecture, I didn't have any notes. The only, like, my main notes that I used
were on the board. Like, the board was my notes. I had my phone open to, like, quickly look stuff
up and I did that a couple times in the lecture. Um, in the Unicorn Jelly lecture, I think it was
the same. I didn't really have any, I don't think I had any notes other than what was on the board.
I think, I don't, I don't, I don't remember, but I'm pretty sure. In the Sonichi 2 lecture, which,
I'm sorry it's not out yet, but I'm waiting until, um, after I do the Slime and Punishment
Finale, which is almost done. I have, like, one more shot to make. It is, like, almost
fucking done. Uh, yeah, baby, yeah. Um, uh, in the Sonichi 2 lecture, I did have notes,
not that many. I just kind of, like, I had, like, just like the first one, I had, like,
chapter names on the board and a couple of highlights, but then I, I sort of had a little
bit more elaboration in my little, in a little, little notebook, just a small, little ledger
notebook. So I, my notes were pretty, probably, like, four, like, mini pages, four or five,
like, very mini pages. It was the equivalent of maybe, like, one and a half, like, full-size pages
of notes written at normal size. So, minor. Um, I, I found it, I found it mostly adequate to just read,
reread through the material, since I was already familiar with it, reread through it,
write down notes, sort of highlighting what I considered to be important moments, and then
kind of pair them down to what I actually wanted to talk about, and then just sort of distill those
into bullet points and put them on the thing. And mainly I was able to, like, okay, oh, bullet
point, oh, I remember, and then kind of go on about the details of what the bullet point, um,
was referring to. So yeah, I'm not a big note guy. Uh, and I'm pretty sure that the other guys were
the same. I don't think any of us had, like, a ton of notes. Um, so yeah, for, for me, and I think
for the rest of us, not that much. Uh, next one is from Ben, you ruined my life. Well, I'm ready
to answer for my crimes. Let's go. All right, Ben, it's your roommate, Joe Swanson. I could not
find my legs, so I broke into the kitchen and I took your room, and I took your worm oil,
and I drank it all because I was running low on nutrients, like Paul Blart, Ben. You understand?
I understand, like Paul Blart, yes. I hope it wasn't too important to you, but I would not
recommend you make any more, unless you would like to become a worm as well. You see, on top of not
having legs, I now no longer have arms because I lost them drinking your worm oil. I am now a worm.
It's syrup. It is your roommate, the worm. Don't even know what you're drinking. Good night.
Hey, okay, worm. Uh, is this a reference to In the House of the Worm by George R.R. Martin,
which is a, I haven't read it, but I like know about it. It's like a story that he wrote a long
time ago about like a space colony that has this cult, and they worship this like, sort of dune,
sort of like, worm creature, I think, but like the priests of this worm god, they cut their arms
and legs off to basically make them into, like, resemble a worm. Is that, is it a reference,
or is it just a happy accident? Um, listen, Joe, worm, buddy. Uh, yeah, it was important to me. I
spent like over $100 buying 11 pounds of isomolta oligosaccharides, aka insoluble tapioca fiber.
It took me all day to convert it to, to, to cook it into syrup and bottle it.
It took hours and hours to cool down. It was, it was, it was molten hot and it does not give off
heat. It was like the labrea tar pits. It was, um, just, just a nightmare. I had to put a little,
I had to put it on the, on the living room table and put a note on it with a skull that said,
heat death, don't touch. Um, but, but you, you didn't listen. Um, and the thing about it is that
it's delicious. You can, I'm, I would love to just drink it myself. It's, if it weren't earmarked
from, it's drinkable. You just take a big spoon of it and eat it. It's like honey. It's like a
agave nectar. It's wicked good. So good. I hate you. I hate you, Joe. How could you? You've ruined
my life and I will not be bullied. Um, I will, I will persevere. Um, I will make more worm syrup.
Um, and I will fucking cook you in it. I will, the thing about it is, Joe, if you take that,
if you, I'm trying to experiment, but like how, how much should I cook it down? I bought a candy
thermometer and I'm seeing, and I'm taking little, little small batches of it and cooking it to,
because like the lower the water content, the higher the boiling point, because you know,
adding fiber to it in a solution increases the boiling point. So as you cook it and water cooks
off, the temperature increases higher and higher. This is how it works. So I'm experimenting with
seeing like how hot should I cook it to get it down to the point where it has, I think I want
like the minimum water content possible while still making it like able to be like poured and
work with and added to a solution. But if you cook it way down, like to about 140 degrees Celsius,
it becomes like amber. It becomes like this syrup that once cooled becomes like rock hard and you
can like crack it with a hammer. So what I'm saying is that I'm going to encase you in it, um, and
keep you like Han Solo in, in fucking carbonite hanging on my wall as a trophy. That is your
fate. You brought this upon yourself. Live by the serp, die by the serp. That's, that's, and also,
Eleazar put up a picture of my fucking the syrup that I made on Twitter. It's, it's funny. It's
cool. I'm very excited. Delicious. Next one in this, in this charade. We've got a message from 522.
Oh god, I wanted to burp, but it didn't work. And now my throat feels gross.
522. What's up, buddy?
Ah shit, what game is this? Is it, is it, is it Chrono Trigger? No, it's Earthbound. It's Earthbound.
Where, where, where, where is this going? Where, where is this going?
I mean, it's, it's nice. What a, what a relaxing time. You know, this is just like the solo
Bencast vibe. It's just, you know, just floating through, floating through a, a, a void. But it's,
a vaguely sinister void. That's, that's what this feels like. That's, that's, that's what,
that's what listening to my voice sounds like. And that's what this song sounds like. So it's
very fitting. Appreciate the contribution. You fuck!
Well, um, voice jail. Voice, I'm gonna submit another applicant. You, you're going into processing
along with Margar, 522. You are, the paperwork has been begun. You will be incarcerated at our earliest
possible convenience after we, after we refund the police. Next up, Snowman. What's up, my dude?
Hey guys, I'm a longtime fan of the show. I just wanted to say thanks for making it. It makes
me happy. Bye. Thank you. And you, you see, who was it that said that dumb shit? Who was it that
said, uh, stop, stop? You see, stop recording. People appreciate what I, me, personally do. This
is now a solo effort. I have successfully privatized the PCP. It is mine now. I own it. Uh, this is a,
this is a one man show. Um, and frankly, this was the plan all along. Just make the PCP environment
so toxic, so uninhabitable that all other members would just be forced into, into retirement.
And I would be left, you know, with the spoils. That was the, the treasure, the pot of gold at the
end of the rainbow. I, I made it. I made it through the wilderness. Somehow I made it through. Uh,
it's good. It's good to be the best, but it's lonely at the top.
What's up, the Joker?
I had a vision, a world, world without insane PCP ground out a little profit and YouTube
trying to, trying to shut them down one video at a time. And it was so
great. I've had a change of heart. Speak up.
Should I, should I have all the fun?
Let's give someone, give someone else a chance. If Ben St. isn't cancel pencil in 60 minutes,
and I blow up PCP HQ.
I'm genuinely not sure if that like glitchiness was intentional. I'm leaning towards yes,
but I'm not a hundred. I'm not a hundo on it. Um, blow up the PCP headquarters. We have no need
for it. I was planning to burn it down anyway. Now that, now that it's my show, we don't need
this big office building. It's just taken up space. It's just rent seeking, you know, burn it down.
You know, give it, give it back to nature. You know, humans are truly are the virus.
Um, I think, I think you and I can make beautiful music together. The Joker.
Uh, let's hear from
Drumpf off a bean. Yes, please.
What, what, what? One more time? One, one more time? Hmm?
Defund PCP, execute Ben St. Drink Mountain Dew Game Fuel.
Something, okay, execute Ben St. Drink Mountain Dew Game Refuel. I, I agree with one of those two
things. So I guess I would say that I'm kind of a centrist on this voicemail. I'm, I'm, I'm
semi-pro, semi-against. I, I think, you know, I don't agree with everything you say,
but I will defend to the death. You're right to say it. Mr. Mr. Drumpf, sir. You are a disgrace
to the office, sir. Have you no sense of decency, sir? Uh, military budget approved.
Okay, here we go. Suggestion from a black fan. Oh, no, it's, oh, no, help. Uh, okay, let's hear it.
Crossover episode idea, the PCP with the N-double-A-C-P.
N-double-A-C-P. Nick is angry about Caucasian people. We ain't never going to make it.
You guys like Charlie Brown's Christmas, Charlie Brown's Kwanzaa most offensive video?
It's real good. It's real funny. It's very funny. Racist? I don't think, I don't know. It's just so
fucking whack. It's so wild. It's so out there. I find that it takes a refuge in audacity and
it's, you can't take it seriously to the point that I don't really see, I don't really see it being
that offensive. Maybe that's just me. I don't know. But that's my thoughts on it. Also,
no hard R. I'm safe. Don't cancel me. Um,
because then, because that would just be feeding into the Joker. No, the Joker said we had 60 minutes.
I'm not canceled. I'm not. The Joker did not win. He, he still has to blow up the PCPHQ. He has to
do it. That was he agreed on it and I'm not canceled. So he has to do it. That's part of the
agreement. We live in a society. You gotta keep your promises. Thank you. Mwah. Um, next up.
Poopsack. 25 seconds. Baby.
Howdy. It's me. One of your fans who is not an involuntary celibate. Just wanted to speak up and
remind you guys that you do have fans that are adults with children and careers out there
that do enjoy the constant ramblings of the procrastinators. Keep up the good work, gentlemen
and mage. And remember, there are more like me out there. Cheers.
I mean, I, I, I appreciate it. I, I was just reflecting today on how much I hate kids and
teenagers. They're stupid. They don't know shit. Anytime they do anything good, it's by accident.
They're just, they're just animals, you know, going on instinct. They can't,
they don't, they don't have agency. You know, it's not their fault that they like us. It's just,
you know, an accident. So it doesn't make me feel good. On the other hand, an adult with like a
family, like that seems kind of normie. And that's pretty embarrassing. And frankly, I, I don't know
if, if, if I'm comfortable having you listening to the show. Being that way as you are, I think
that maybe, I think that's a little weird. And I think that maybe you've probably some kind of like,
some kind of like, some kind of like MAP, pedophile, a global elite, adrena comb drinking,
fucking Democrat or something. And frankly, I won't have it. I won't have it on my show. I object. I
don't like it. Well, fuck, man, we're done with the, we're done with the, the voicemails.
We're done with the voicemails and we're not even an hour in. This is unprecedented.
But then this, this, this length is unprecedented. It would be unprecedented for me to end the show
now. But on the other hand, everything about the Ben Solo cast is unprecedented. We're entering
a new age, a golden age. This is the Ben Saints show now. Everyone, there was a secret,
I snuck a secret clause into the contract, into the PCP contract that we all signed in blood
all those years ago that said, if ever an episode happens and it's just Ben, Ben owns the podcast.
It's all, it all, it's all his. It was a, it was like a taunting, you know, that episode of the
Simpsons where it's like, you know, the last one to die gets the art and it's, it's down to, to
Burns versus Grandpa. It was exactly like that. And now here I am. I, I, I did it. I killed all
the other ones. I destroyed them. I drove them away with my toxic personality.
And, and now here I am at the end. Here we are in the future. And it's bright. I own everything.
The, the, the ultimate reward of the PCP. I did it. Remember that? Remember my little pony?
Remember, let's take this moment, this moment of transition, a moment of change, right? Nothing
will ever be the same after this. Let's take this moment to think back to where it all started,
with my little pony, the little, with a little blue horse named Phantom Horn. He never thought
he would see the day when he'd become a big, fancy CEO, corporate executive, head of the
procrastinator's podcast, highfalutin, emailing with the YouTube staff, getting, getting deals,
cutting deals, making, making flip, canceling people, getting canceled on and on. We go round
and round. But here we are. You know what? I'm tempted to try and stretch to an hour, but like,
fuck it, who gives a shit? Thanks for listening, everybody. You're welcome. You're welcome for
being the guy who shows up to deliver this quality content directly to your ears and
for being, for having the good taste and the good sense to make it just as long as it needs to be,
just, just, just perfect, the optimal length, the ideal format. Here it is. And it's me. I'm the guy
who did it. If you want to hear more bonus episodes of the PCP with other guys, I don't know why you
would want to hear other people, but if you, if that seems like something you would consider,
patreon.com slash the procrastinators, you get access to all our fucking bonus episodes.
There's like 40 hundred of them right now. That's a fucking deal if ever there was one.
patreon.com slash Ben St. If you want to hear more solo Ben casts and hear me answering questions,
that's what this is. On the solo Ben cast, Patreon Q&A, people put type questions in the comments
and I answer them. And usually I go on longer for each one because they're more,
generally people ask me things more specifically about me that I have more to say about.
It's better. What am I, am I saying that the Ben St. Patreon Q&A podcast is better in every way
than the procrastinators podcast? And yeah, as a matter of fact, I am. Sue me. Send a voicemail
to speakpipe at, is it at the procrastinators mail at gmail.com.
Wait, no, that's not the, the link is teespring, put gumroad, redbubble, speak, speakpipe.com slash
pcp voicemail. Always fuck it up. Send the voicemail. And I'll read it. I'll listen to it,
because as you see, I don't curate anything. I'm an anarchist. And, and I don't believe in censorship.
And I, I'll just give it over to the fucking, I'll throw, I'll throw the shit to the fucking wolves
and let them devour it. Anything goes. It's chaos. Fuck the police.
Um, and I guess that's the perfect note to end on. Thanks for listening, everybody.
Thanks for being a pet. Hey, fuck YouTube. Hey, YouTube, die. Hey, thanks for nothing.
Hey, thanks for fucking our show for no reason. And then just pretending you're going to fix it
when you're not going to. Thanks for everything. You're really fucking nailed it. You're really
cool guys. It's really like fair and good and nice. And you're a good company and you,
and it's cool. It's great. You did it. Thanks and have a great day, everyone. See you on the next episode.