I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Uh, what's up? That's the intro.
Hey, Ben.
Welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. Hey, Gibb.
Hey, it's me.
Hey, Cheesy.
It's Cheesy.
I'm back.
How y'all doing?
How y'all living?
Uh, well, good news, everybody.
I got the vaccine. I got the booster.
I got the bivalent, covalent, COVID shot.
Nice.
Yeah, pretty nice.
Made me real sick for a day.
Oh, Pog.
Felt so bad.
I was so shitty.
Uh, Tom.
I got it in the flu.
I got COVID, I got COVID and flu shot at the same time.
I was, it was a nightmare.
Uh, tell me, Ben, what convinced you about the big lie?
Um, why do you now believe in the big lie right now?
Um, it's just because women wouldn't date me because I was a conservative.
So to open up my dating pool, to get those blue-haired sluts, I had to, I had to get the jab.
Nice.
I had, that they had to stick me so I could stick them if you know what I'm saying...
Wow.
Hacha-cha.
And how's the, is it working?
Would you recommend it?
No!
So that knocked me out two days ago.
I was tossing and turning...
Oh, it was feverish, fever and chills and body aches all night.
night and then I woke up and it was mostly okay so that was fun nice it was
nice it was nice so you should say for well another week until the there's the
new variant comes out they've been working on it for a long time I keep
seeing I saw an article that's like oh there's a new variant coming out of
China it's like well okay just in time just in time for the Omicron booster
all right you gotta admit those Chinese are effective they um they just keep
they just keep pumping them out they just keep they just they can't keep getting
away with it if there's one thing you can't take away from the Chinese is
their workman like attitude and always on schedule for it us you know they're
they're humble wisdom they're down to earth home homey mystical powers there's
various spell their various spells and enchantments yeah you can't you can't
stop them you're describing the Chinese people from the fucking
Gremlins movie I'm described I haven't seen Gremlins you haven't seen
Gremlins no I've never no I haven't seen it a long time I can't remember it a
Chinese family wait there was the guy who had the he had the the Gremlin the
the ancient Chinese guy with the gremlin and you mean Billy Peltzer no it's
like the little little boy goes into this this ancient Chinese gift shop and
there's a gremlin in there and he's like oh don't feed it right that's what
happens don't think that's the plot of the movie yeah and how I understand it
he says don't feed it and the little boys like why and then he then the guy
says oh because he's currently working it's not his lunch break can't eat right
hmm
um iconic scene the the China what do we try I think China thumbs up okay hey
political news Liz trust is dead yeah finally let's trust is cute I think she's
cute I like why did you put why did you do that why did you think she's cute
I like her I mean if she were if she were like if she were like 20 years
younger she'd be she'd be assault she'd be a solid a solid six out of ten which
is a 10 out of 10 in my opinion why why would you say it why would you do that
why would you do this like her face just like her face look I've never heard
her speak I don't know anything about her that would ruin the illusion if you
just think I just think she's I just think she's neat I just think she's
cute confirm something for for us before you continue all right if less
trust was a POC women would she still be attracted to you attracted yeah so
trust was it was a POC was a POC woman yeah I mean it would change it would
change her appeal would change her appeal that's very diplomatic way of
saying that insane very very political answer and the topic is politics after
all so you're not you're not off topic but you might be off you might be off
colored in other words you know really much another that I have to say about
the Liz trust thing being gone it's just that like some last episode of talking
about it and then I think even before the episode came out she was gone so it
was out of date yeah so someone I saw a tweet that was like as an American the
concept of a politician resigning because they fucked everything up and
everyone hates them is like completely foreign and that's that's exactly how I
feel like wow she left just because she failed and ruined everything like what a
what a concept yeah amazing it's it's I mean I don't know why it's different I
think it's like you can resign whenever you want but like to save your political
future like you can get bullied out by say by all the other politicians saying
yeah we're gonna we don't like that and what future do you have what what
political future do you have when you take over the part of the as prime
minister and then you're like oh fuck I have to stop being prime minister
immediately is a prime minister like the endpoint you know everyone's trying to
be prime minister or something you know it's pretty good yeah get big money you
get big money for it even after you she saw the view from the top from the top
of the world she's like never mind I like it here I think the only reason she
stayed as long as she did was because of like ego like it was like oh but I'm I
would do such a good job if only everyone in the entire world would just agree
with my idea it's that scene from the beginning of Dark Crystal when the
emperor is dying and the Chamberlain tries to take his staff or whatever he
said I am still emperor and then he crumbles to dust kind of like that scene
at the beginning of the Dark Knight Rises where Bane steals the plane Liz
Truss is the plane in the scenario exactly yeah exactly right because I
haven't seen that one actually you haven't seen the Bane movie no I haven't
seen the Bane movie just watch the first five minutes and that's like the best
part of the movie yeah the first five minutes that plane seemed iconic can't
believe they whitewashed Bane it's okay so mad look so mad that they erase a POC
voice yeah exactly that's true I've heard I've heard people say that he's like
Mexican right he's original or yeah he is Mexican look I remember reading that
comic like years ago you know what I'm you know what Bane's like original like
origin story was I forget it was um he was born in a prison and then he I mean
that kind of happens oh he was born in darkness molded by it well he was kind
of there was like a there was like a teddy bear that told him that you should
kill Batman and he's like oh okay I'll do that I'll go murder him right now I see
and he and he devised a team of other a very diverse team and there was a guy
with a lasso on his team that was very important he had a guy with a lasso on
his team to confront Batman because you know that's amazing in case Batman
through he can't get away he's in ropes and my understanding is what you're
telling me that his origin story is that as a child a teddy bear told him that
he should he should assemble a team to kill Batman kind of it's a very I'm
giving you a very rough version but I know at one point his teddy bear told
them was it the teddy bear from Dengan Rompah yeah he was a big anime like all
Mexicans persona five or three like all Mexicans Bane was a really big anime
and he modeled he modeled his like that's why he got all swollen he saw Goku he's
like oh I gotta get big and then he's like and then Goku he fights strong
opponents and Bane was like I gotta fight the biggest guys around and who's
bigger than Batman Superman yeah but you know you gotta start you gotta start
somewhere you know right had a sensible goals if you were to you know yeah you
gotta take on all the justice like you gotta start with Batman first he is he
is human after all
yeah exactly he just has gadgets and if you have a guy with a lasso on your team
you could like catch his batarangs in midair hmm yeah right easily it's the
effectiveness so now it's like rock-paper-scissors lasso beats
batarang right right right you guys um you guys up for a quick for a quick
little game yeah I love games okay I'm gonna post an image filled with filled
with colorful characters and I want to see how many of these characters you can
name oh should we just shout shout the names out what a time I suppose yeah I
just I guess from left to right it's like a lineup of characters and if I just
want to see how many can name I've been asking a lot of people this question I'll
see if I can name one I'll count how many I can name without naming them all
right cool see if you name this lineup of characters can I name this I gotta
zoom in the resolution is a bit shit one two three okay some of the some of
these I've definitely seen before six seven yeah from just that wait these are
um these are 10 more mostly spider-man villains right yeah the majority yeah
majority of our spider-man villains please like the most popular he has the
most popular villains right yeah this does a lot but it's a wide range of
Marvel villains like almost all the popular heroes have at least one villain
represented in this lineup okay miss Mysterio there's the Rhino there's Dr.
Octopus kingpin there's like is it just a lizard skull which one Venom Venom Dr.
Doom the green goblin who's that purple guy Thanos with the chin that's Thanos in
the back is that is that with the gold juggernaut behind him yeah juggernaut
yes yeah like Magneto Magneto yeah the is it dark is that storm or just Phoenix
the color I think you just call her Phoenix there's a low key there's the
red face man in the green rhino hobgoblin yeah that's it no that's wrong
okay whatever there's Mysterio on the left and that's I'm done that's all the
ones I know the lizard guy on the front I know he's a spider-man villain I can't
remember his name is he just the lizard yeah his name is just the lizard oh
guy with the wings is called the vulture right yeah the green guy on the left
there's two there's two guys with green wings in this lineup yeah this is Dr. Doom
I don't know who that guy right in the back is I think that might be a green
lantern guy but I've never read that wait which one but right in the back behind
Dr. Doom and Venom with a big like like weird head thing that's that's hella
that's hella she's a she's a forward character she was in the third movie
I haven't seen any movies that's that's fine so I saw the first two only only the
first two or wait the first I saw the one with I saw the one with green
goblin I saw the one with doc doc who's the hobbit with us with a snooka queue
right there that one that is 3d glasses but they're both blue that that's the
mole man you just gonna hit you with a stick like most of these guys I have
seen before I just don't know their names mole man's whole gimmick he was
actually the first supervillain the fantastic four per fought and his whole
gimmick is that he could control Kaiju's he had like a he um he was like
ugly and everyone's everyone's all like it'll get away from you ugly and he's
like okay I'm gonna run off and live on Monster Island where he controls he
controls the species of like little yellow mole people called the mole
Lloyds and and he doesn't those glasses are they're like I think they're kind
of glasses like Inuits would wear right oh I know what you're talking about yeah
the one with slits in them to limit sunlight yeah and that came I think he
just has that because he's like he just needs a cane because him he's like a
short little he's a short little hobbit well hunchback yeah exactly and he's
all like I hate humanity I gave up my humanity I live among the Kaiju's now
and he sends out his army of Kaiju's to destroy the world truly remarkable I
iconic that's kind of that's kind of been saying it maybe like five years it's
been saying now that's been saying three years ago I send my army of Ben fans out
to the world to destroy humanity oh shit I just realized the huge face in the
back that's the big ultra mega man that's like that's like I know that's the
yeah that's that's mega man yeah you're right like Lord of the universe or
whatever the fuck okay so that that giant purple guy that's Galactus yes and
the and the guy with the green wings with the with the back green wings that's
Annihilus and okay I never heard that and the blue guy in front of him that's
apocalypse that's the list I knew it's not Thanos
Thanos is the purple one with the chin and he's got both arms out oh oh like
he's grabbing the blue oh no no no who's who's the one who's just the giant
head that's modoc okay it's like a one-piece like giant baby that's some
that's a that's big head his name is big head and the the fat guy next to him is
big body their brothers there's a big guy with a big body it's not true yeah
that's kingpin that's kingpin that's kingpin the big body of the big head
there they're one half there they're a team they're a duo the big face guy
looks like that one like sea creature in one piece that Jim Baber friends he's
just really big and funny look oh isn't he the guy who could like keep inflating
himself make himself huge and huger yeah he's like a he's like a fishman sea
creature that is like a balloon fish I forget forget his name the guy with the
fish wool for his head his name is his name is go fish one piece fish man what
that's me that's him let me get a picture of what that's me the guy with the face
on fire his name is ah because he's on fire all the time he looks like this he's
like a Pokemon he says his name yeah it's this guy oh yeah this guy kind of
looks like um the one bear from Animal Crossing was his name the one that
everyone says is ugly bear like like gay and no no not not bearing gay but I bear
it's Animal Crossing so he's an actual fucking like bear oh yeah yeah that's so
obvious I don't know why I thought whatever oh they kind of reminds me of
the twig from Animal Crossing oh it's because he's like gay it's like that
fin boy bunny it's um it's funny when people draw the whole like thick Animal
Crossing characters when they all just have like like oval bodies no one really
has like so no one really has like defining like body types in Animal
Crossing well you mean like when they draw like the characters torso it's just
like the cutesy animal crossing shaped torso but then they have huge thighs and
a butt yeah when they um when they gave a like on the fat pussy with a fat butt
or the fat tits the rest of herself is just sort of like cartoon yeah you got to
give it up to the Japanese they really like made objectifying women into an
art you know hell yeah somebody had to do cuz here and I'm here in the West like
when we objectify women it's like oh she's got fat tits fat ass and she's like a
sex sex slave and she does she does anything you want her to do right but
in Japan it's like oh this woman was turned into a like a flesh light and
she's slowly losing her like consciousness as you're fucking her I don't
wait I don't get it what was your first statement related to that sound pretty
similar no and no no and one and sure and one she's like one is base she's
being degraded and the other one she's literally turning into an object and like
in a way like in a way like dying but in a like almost like existential like
abstract way wow like that yeah it's horrifying they're like I really get
upset when they do the thing where it's like haha she's having so much sex and
now let's cut her arms and legs off is not when do they do that when the fuck
do they do that like oh like get get her just so that she's just a torso and
you can fuck it I'm like why would you do that I don't I don't I don't know
the bed you ever I mean I like I never I like never see that I've never I mean I
can imagine it but like that upon it often enough to know that it is
definitely a trope a trend yeah I see that I see that before too I mean
upon some gross stuff usually it's not like that it's not like like gore
sometimes it's like oh I have like attachable legs and arms I can take
them all off haha and like their stumps now it's my hentai that happens in
clown milk but now no one will know isn't clown milk isn't clown milk still
available by special order it's available and pre-order you can get
pre-order right now gamers the yeah the the the the clown milk the clown milk is
real tell tell us tell us what you've learned tell us what you've learned from
your Kickstarter experience yeah let me out before before anyone rushes to point
out every little thing that I could have done and yeah in retrospect let me I
already wrote down a list of things and if I then list something down you tell
me later as I go through the list of things but oh but the most I mean yeah
I'd like to hear what I'd like to hear your observations well first first and
foremost everyone wants me to kill myself that was that was mistake number one
obviously I could have told you that I think number one was promising people
three thousand dollars that's probably a big mistake eat the artist hang on
yeah when you say I mean I mean I mean I would phrase I would phrase that
differently it would say I would say like the goal was too high the goal was
too high I do agree and yeah could have been there should have been a deal about
like percentages or like oh we'll get to I mean the thing is that nothing was
like ridded and stowed and it's all like good faith among like three friends you
know yeah really I mean ultimately if I if I pulled like a dick mood and didn't
get it no one paid you know that would reflect poorly on me and what like if
you just if it if it had hit the goal and then you had just like skip town well
yeah and in a way right that would you want to make sure that the artists were
paid and that was like a big part of yeah yeah yeah yeah and I think it's still
a good thing I think it's just sort of like maybe it was like like what was
would that be like a normal paycheck for the work they do I was that a higher
paycheck I hear that like cuz I'm like in the industry like in the big two I
think three thousand is not like too much I think like people get roughly paid
more than that yeah it in the indie stuff no one's ever paid like three
thousand up front right and I was talking to I was talking to my buddy Eddie
Adams creator of pinky and pepper forever and he was telling me that yeah
straight up like I've never been paid three thousand up front and I'm like okay
well that was kind of high and I mostly picked that number because I was I was
talking to a buddy about joining the anthology before they they couldn't and
I asked him like let's say like I was commissioning you for a comic how much
would you charge for something in between like 15 to 20 pages and they said
three thousand and I was like oh well they want three thousand dollars for a
15 page comic 15 to 20 that's like that's like isn't that like $200 a page you
ever made a comic I mean some people are worth that much I mean when it's like
when you're paid to do something I mean that the thing is like I would probably
multiple pages is a lot of work yeah it's really good art because it can
cost a lot because I'm also asking you to create I'm asking you to create a
original story too right and that's like a whole other thing right I mean yeah I
understand that if you're talking about like in turn like an hourly rate yeah
sure you could easily spend 10 or 20 hours drawing a comic page if you wanted
and then it's like well $200 is like that's $10 an hour it's not that much
and like yeah true but also like you said like no like no indie comic artists
is commanding numbers like that right right yeah yeah it's too high agree but
also a part of me was kind of like seeing it as a gamble because think of it
like this I mean I know it's failed now but let's say there's an alternate
universe where it did succeed right and let's say like the numbers of like how
everyone like paid for it were like just like just like good you know like there
was never like everything like lined up good and everyone got there like 3,000
that would like yeah that would look imagine being the guy who was able to
get people $3,000 right you I mean you would be the guy people you I mean you
would be the guy that people would want to work with right because like oh like
cheesy has gotten people $3,000 before I want to work with that guy right sure
right sure yeah ambitious it isn't it is ambitious and I mean it bit me in the
ass and I bit that I mean here's I guess here's what I think about that it's
like you know obviously in hindsight we can say the goal was too high I think I
think for an all or nothing I think the all or nothing I know that's kind of
just how Kickstarter is but I think I think going for like okay we're gonna
make costs plus $3,000 per artist or or nothing is like kind of a mistake yeah
yeah I agree with that I agree with that yeah luckily for me I never like signed
anything or never told them that like yeah I'm gonna get you the 3,000 with
like one at once you know they're they're still gonna get the 3,000 is
just gonna now gonna take like a year what do you mean they're gonna get the
3,000 there's like so as because I'm gonna be selling the book like the book
could could still be sold how are you how can you how can you guarantee how
can you guarantee that that those those guys will each get $3,000 in sales
residuals because I'm just gonna sell the book you can't what what are you
talking about I'm not gonna like I'm not gonna give the 3,000 at once I mean
sure I mean sure like if you were to say at one point the book like I can't
guarantee that the book will continue to sell and that I reached 3,000 right it's
like what you're saying yeah yeah okay okay I mean I mean to make that to make
that happen I mean I don't know how much you sell them if you sell the book for
$20 then you would have to sell you know to make $6,000 to give these other two
guys 3,000 each you have to sell 300 copies and that's if you had no take
for yourself or to cover your own costs is that where you're I'm well you know
mine I'm also like this is gonna make it I'm just gonna make it seem even more
impossible is that I'm also like getting a cut like it's getting like three ways
you know yes I know I was very conservative in my S right right right
now I get you I think it could be done it just has to be like cuz I have I have
I have plans I have plans and people in places what does that mean I got trust the
plan then where we go one we all then yeah I mean now I mean my language I mean I
respect the the dedication I guess to pay the artists for the work they've
already part of a part of me doesn't want like I hate the idea of like oh you
remember when I promised you guys this much well not anymore it's like well are
you are you so hang on here's here's what are you saying that you told these
guys that you would pay them $3,000 if they drew like a 15 page like a 15 to
20 page comic for this anthology yes why cuz that's what one guy asked for and I
was like oh to make it fair everyone should get that amount I mean I mean make
sense at the time no it didn't I think it did I mean how could you you it had to
make sense at one point for me to agree to it okay hang on okay so you're so
you're saying what I'm saying you're saying that you have an agreement with
this guy that you now owe him $3,000 for this comic that he drew for this
anthology and it will be well both of these guys but okay I mean I'm gonna I'm
gonna be perfectly honest okay if if that's I mean if that's the deal I think
that maybe I think maybe the thing to do is cut and run I think maybe the thing
to do is call it a sunk cost and cut and run I don't think I could I could do
that maybe I could lie I mean I could potentially I mean I'm talking to them so
you owe this so you so you told this guy you get him $3,000 but not but just at
some point in the future well not all at once and like you know segment they're
getting like once all these pre-orders are done they're all getting like you
know they're part in it it's not gonna be three thousand three thousand but
gonna be part of three thousand so you're just gonna owe them money until it
you sell all yeah so it's all paid I guess I would have added a stipulation in
the original agreement but if the Kickstarter doesn't do it you have a
different arrangement ready yeah but I mean there was there's no there was
never an agreement to like that they would get that the green ones that'll
get three thousand and never said like that they that they wouldn't get it in
parts
sure but like there should have been like if the Kickstarter doesn't succeed
you can get like a percentage of the sales of however many we end up selling
boy I thought that's gonna happen that's what's gonna happen with the pre-orders
they're gonna get a percentage of the we're gonna like it's gonna be sweet
three ways but you're not also you're not also owing them like a an ultimate
like some right and I guess that sucks a little hope you get enough orders I mean
I guess in theory well the thing is I'm not I'm not gonna die when the pre-order
deadline is is up you know I'm not gonna like be murdered unless I am and this is
like the last recording of me in okay first I mean three three thousand seems
like a lot in but in in theory I guess if you if you manage to make if you
manage okay how much you planning to sell the books for 30 okay 30 right well
how much okay just how much is how much was like for one book how much is the
cost to print one book and then ship it to someone that orders it just for the
one would be like just yeah just like her book last quote okay so I'm not
ordering in bulk is what you're saying I'm just ordering one well you would all
I am I assume that you are gonna print in bulk the price the price goes down as
you order more I mean but you already know yes yes so okay but you okay but
you're saying that you but you haven't printed them yet so you don't know the
yeah I don't know can you okay can you give me like a rough ballpark I mean I'll
tell you I'll tell you how many pre-orders you got so far sure okay look at
the Google form okay we got four we got no we got 40 pre-orders I remember one
guy canceled and it had to refill up we have 40 orders so far right and if I go
to if I go to my printer and I type in like how much that's gonna be Lincoln
we'll put a link link in the description for anyone that pledged to the
Kickstarter or who wants to get the book by the because it would you have like a
hundred or you have like a hundred and something pledges right to the key to the
Kickstarter we have like I'm gonna check that too I think it was like under
was it okay yeah maybe a hundred bucks no I wouldn't have been that I think it's
a hundred bucks fail it was only a hundred bucks if all my friends is donated
$1 hmm okay I'm gonna I'm getting the quote right now okay no it was 91 90 91
backers so if I look if I order if I order 40 books that's gonna be around
like 264 okay so that's what like I'm so and I'm like I'm like six like six six
dollars a piece to print $5.15 okay and so let's call it $5 and what about
what about shipping what about shipping what's the cost to ship
domestically inside the US I mean it's it's gotta be five bucks five bucks all
right let's okay so let's say 10 let's just say $10 ship printing and shipping
so out of that $30 10 that's $10 goes to cover costs so you got $20 profit
leftover and then splitting it I mean let's let's assume assuming that you
don't take any additional cut other than what covers the cost of printing
that's let's say that's $10 a piece to each of these other guys so so you've
got to sell 300 so 300 copies will make the the 3k that you owe these two guys
and I guess if you could do that then thereafter then thereafter you own the
anthology and you don't have to pay any additional cost you could like continue
to sell it right um a part of me like because the thing is they still own the
rights to their story why they made a story I'm gonna lose my mind you pay
them $3,000 and you don't even get the rights that's just for their work oh my
god I the thing is like no this is under a fucking contract so I don't like pay
them right the fuck away you know I just think it's all really like what's the
word like a verbal cons a verbal contract a verbal verbal agreement yeah and
like I don't have to pay them all at once listen let me let me just let me
ask you okay let's say let's say a year from now a year from now you've sold
300 copies you've paid you've paid each of these guys the 3k that you said you
would pay them for their for their work and then you're like okay cool done I've
paid down I've paid down Tom nook for my house you know my my dad is covered
then the next day you go to a con and you sell some more and you sell some more
copies you sell some more right copies of of clown milk what do you do with the
profits I mean if I haven't like bought the stories off of them I would split
it like three ways with them still that just seems like you're really getting
screwed here sure but I'm not too worried about it because I have my own
comics you should be worried about it you should be worried about getting
screwed I mean okay I'll tell you this if I were to do this all over again I
wouldn't I wouldn't set up these parameters I mean sure right right and
the thing is that like I think the one thing that's not making me freak out is
that there's no deadline for the 3,000 yeah I mean like that's that's good I
mean it depends on how these two that's why I like about about that I mean are
they free if they like freak out I mean none of them have freaked out on me yet
yeah right they're very super chill about it and you know like they both are
very like chill about it and have other ways to make money I don't think they're
worried about like I mean they told me that like they put the fucking what what
what's that crazy shit that people do with their houses like oh yeah mortgage
they put their houses up they flip their house upside down and they're like
she's I put my house upside down to get that 3,000 like down screwed now the bank
is coming after me yeah I just think that like you're you're gonna split the
profits three ways from the pre-orders until all three of you get 3k and then
the profits will if they continue you'll split it three ways as well it just
sort of feels like there is no 3k it's just sort of like the profits will
continue from whatever you sell you just split it three ways that's that's
ultimately like if I keep ever decide to keep selling the book after we reach
the 3k I mean there's no reason why not right I mean the most of what I'm aside
from the labor you have to do to me the fact the fact that you you know agree
there was an agreement with these guys like I will give you 3k to produce a
comic a work of intellectual property I feel like what then is like okay you
paid me to make this thing now you own it because you commissioned me to produce
it for you I have done labor to produce a work that is now your property like
there's no obligation unless you've mentioned in your like verbal agreement
there's no obligation that they get like residuals beyond 3k so you don't have
to I mean a part of it's kind of like what if like what if like the right
push the right person pushes the book at the right time and then it starts
selling gang busters and like after I don't know the 3k right and then what do
you mean then like what if the book just becomes extremely like popular after
you mean like if one of these get if one of these get are you are you saying
that you want these what if the book makes way more money have an incentive to
push the book I mean that could be a way that's the way to like to look at it I
mean mostly because I think like you know I I feel like it's fair that they
keep getting a share you know well I don't I mean I would want people like
cuz the thing is like if there was a way where I mean they just keep getting
like royalties off of it and they get like passive income I think that's great
you know I mean sure but you would need a higher cut because you're also the one
organizing the printing and sending though of them and they just they've drawn
it they don't need to do anything more so like beyond the 3k you should be
getting a higher cut for extra labor in the process of continuing to sell the
books I was originally the Kickstarter because the labor costs was gonna go to
me and me and my partner because we're gonna be the one who was actually gonna
like put the books in the envelopes and like print out the labels and whatnot
right so I was ultimately gonna get like a bigger cut I mean no I mean I get
that I get that I mean like yeah that's a yeah I should be getting a bigger cut
for like sending and shipping it out but I think I'm think right now I want to
like just focus on just getting the the books out and like getting the word out
you know I've like little I've like little things I've like little things to
kind of like I guess the idea is to like because you know I've done like
pre-orders before and when you do like a pre-order for the same book again in a
couple of months you usually don't sell too much like you did in the first run
right yeah so like I have um I have little little ideas little plans in
place to um to keep some momentum going you know okay I mean I could I could see
like if you table that a con or something I could see selling selling some
copies at a table I do have I do have like I do have a con lined up like okay
yeah there's there's a con that's gonna happen where like I could sell the book
at so yeah that's a that's a that's in mind I think I'm just not too worried
about the one thing that's making me not worried about like the 3000 and why I
don't really I'm not that freaked out about it is because ultimately there's
like no deadline right I understand that right as long as like I mean up with me
as I feel as long as they're getting the the money in a reasonable amount and
in a reasonable like you know yeah an amount like over a course of time then
it's not it's not like too worrying you know I wouldn't want like oh by 20 by
20 30 finally they all got in the 3k you know I wouldn't want that but like you
know I feel I feel like it could be possible by next year I feel like it
could be like I really do have that much faith they buy next year they will all
get their money that was originally promise what if what if what if you what
if you just don't what if you just don't sell that many books I mean I'll just
find other ways to pay them my pocket see yeah here's this is like this is like
you're like you're the one shouldering all the risk I mean I hate in this in
this situation you're the you're the one shouldering if I mean they've received a
promise of financial compensation you're the one who is running the risk of what
if I have to pay out of pocket if like sales don't cover the cost that's why I
feel like it's fair for you like once the fee is paid you own the rights that's
the risk versus reward calculus I mean that could be an agreement I
talked to them about well no it's too late
nothing nothing in stone it's always like just what do you mean there's
nothing in stone I'm gonna I'm gonna throw myself on a fucking way for the 3k
nothing's like in stone what what what do you mean a side of the 3k that's
that's the whole deal I don't get why you're mad I'm the one who's gonna get
anything why are you mad I'm the one who's got to pay them 3k I each I just
don't understand I just don't understand okay well I just don't understand
what's going on here and it makes me angry when I don't understand things all
okay all right well I I just I just I just okay I guess on the one hand they
do they do they do they do run the risk of like okay this guy wants me to draw a
comic I'm drawing this comic with an agreement of future payment and there's
a chance that this guy will never come through and I will not ever be paid for
it that is that is a risk so on their end on your end if if you are if you are
committed to falling through and paying the 3k that was agreed to then then the
risk is is all on you like what if what if the book doesn't sell and I have to
cover it myself so on that end it's like well there's there should be some
reward on your end for for risking that I agree with that I agree with that I
mean I'll talk I mean that's a good that's fair point I'll bring that out
but I'm just saying at this point at this point it seems too late to call it
like if you if you said hey man what are they go galactic be and who's the other
one super spell super so on galactic be if you if you call them up you bring them
up on the telephone you say hey galactic be so I know I said that there was a
through there was an agreement of $3,000 in exchange for work you have done the
work now I owe you the $3,000 now hey what if instead of you can what if instead
of you continuing to receive residuals what if instead of that we didn't do
that I don't know like what what what are there what are their expectations do
they have expectations do they know what's going on yeah they know what's
going on okay do I mean do they do they expect to continue to receive
residuals into the indefinite future no I haven't told them that part exactly I
mean I'll say that much I'm told that part okay so they don't expect anything
in in addition to the 3k so why would you give them any more than that I mean I
think I just I mean nice person yeah I mean nice person shut the fuck I'm just
it's I mean I don't know there's being a nice person and then there's just and
then there's just shooting yourself in the foot I don't know I just I just feel
like there's no you know this is a this is a business arrangement that you
entered into here and so I feel like it's it's everyone everyone it's kind of
everyone's individual responsibility to max to max to maximize their own profit
and if you're do if you and if you're like well okay the expectation was that
I would only pay them $3,000 but I can meet that and then I can choose to
exceed that if I want to I mean that's just charity I just paying for the cut
like you know for like you know no the three thousand was their cut no the
agreed the agreed upon 3k was their cut you'd be paying extra money anything in
addition to that is literally just you giving the money for free that's
royalties no it's not royalties royalties are agreed upon no royalties
would be a royalty agreement would be I won't pay you anything upfront but if you
make this if you make this work and I publish it in this book I will continue
to give you a cut of future sales into the indefinite future that's royalties
yeah you could you could pay them a fine and then they get also royalties like
that's why option cheesy I here's it here's I just feel like we're approaching
this I okay I think I understand okay that you value the idea of paying these
guys more right and that's and that's admirable okay I understand you I
understand the appeal of that however I just think you should be focused on like
your own bottom line first here and I really think that yeah I really think
that you have a reasonable expectation that like these proceeds should belong to
you and and I don't understand why you seem to want to be rid of them I I guess
cuz like I mentioned before there's no like that line to it and I would
understand okay I would be mad if I would I would probably be very upset with
myself if this was if my Twitter like handle wasn't like working on like five
other if I didn't have other projects to like that like that's not that's not
about your overall thing it's not what I'm talking about the agreement you made
did not include royalties so you have no obligation to do that that's what I'm
saying that's what I'm saying it sounds yeah there's no obligation for such a
thing okay I mean I guess it just wouldn't kill me to do royalties it
wouldn't like end my life this is so I I don't I don't get it yeah I mean by
that logic I mean anything you make in excess of like what you need to like pay
rent and buy food it's like well it wouldn't kill me to just you know give
it to someone give it to whoever I what I give help please I think ultimately
the goodwill I get off of that's gonna be more valuable to me I don't know all
right I'll tell you what okay here's what I think I think I'll just I'll just I'll
I think if I'm if I'm one of these guys and I'm like I agreed to do this work in
exchange for $3,000 to be paid in the indefinite future and then maybe a year
or whatever from now I received the $3,000 I'm like yes and then and then the
guy who gave me the $3,000 like hey by the way I'm gonna give you even more I'm
just gonna keep giving you even more than that like it's like I don't know to me
that doesn't earn you any goodwill that just makes you look like a sucker like
you wouldn't you wouldn't what do you I would I would appreciate I would
appreciate the money and I would shake my head and think what a sap why is this
guy still paying me I'll mean I'll take it but I don't respect it that's just me
though you don't you don't think so yeah do you feel that would you think I'm
as if I kept giving you money after like a comic like would you would you think
I'm sort of fucking sad I don't know if I 100% I think I think when it comes to
like respect and goodwill honoring an agreement is like that's good yeah like
if you eventually get these people the 3k they should be happy with you honoring
your the agreement you had extra money is just sort of like oh cool like I
wouldn't really I don't know whether it would be like oh my god she's so
cool yeah you are giving me free money but like I think on some level I repeat
work would feel more right like oh cheesy follows through on promises they get
you the money they promise you so I'll work for them again the extra money I
don't think is like a necessary part of that it maybe it's nice maybe maybe if
there was like if a network executive calls you up on the phone one day he's
choppy cigar and he says hey I got to get this cheesy manfredo guy on the
phone we got to make a clown milk Netflix adaptation we got to get him if
that if that happens then and you make a million dollars and you receive a
residual you and you receive a million dollars in your bank account then I
could maybe be like you call up these guys and you're like hey guys I just got
like a huge windfall from this work and like as a token of goodwill I'm gonna
give you each like ten thousand dollars or something here you go God bless like
something like that I think would be understandable I just I just wouldn't
feel good about you like selling yourself short in a sense I feel yeah I
feel like you're selling yourself you should you should like if it's not in
the agreement like you don't you shouldn't feel the need to do extra yeah
just do what you said you did you would do and that that should be enough that
will be enough well I I mean it wasn't kind of the whole goal with the
three thousand dollars didn't you want to give yourself like three months to take
off of work so that you could just draw instead of working right right so yeah
I mean there you go money is time so you should you should you should you should
you should want to hoard as much of it as you can to use on doing the things you
want to go that's it I don't say I'm not like I'm just not freaked out about it
it doesn't I don't know because ultimately I mean these guys are like my
friends too and if I could like I understand like do you would you not
want your friends to have more money like I don't like if they thought well sure
I will share I want my friends to have more money but I'm not digging into my
pockets to like shovel it out to them but I don't want them to have more money
more than I want to have money myself I mean we can I mean the thing is that it's
all just like still for one I could talk to them about it right because like
there's some things in this conversation that are making me rethink some some
approaches about it right okay okay that being said it's not the worst shit ever
you know that it's not the worst shit I just talking about I think that it's not
it's what are you talking about I'm not like very like very least the barest
minimum is that beyond the 3k you definitely get a higher cut if you
continue to pay them like you get I don't know half of it and then well wait
how'd you split it this three I don't know I can't know I can't numbers but
you do it more so that you're getting more out of it after the 3k that you've
promised them because it's you didn't promise them anymore and if you want to
give them something that's you know you are in with it within your rights to do
so it's just you're the one doing the extra work by continuing to go to the
printer and print them mail them out so like the very least you need a higher cut
I think it I think that's get give you know what you're you're you're
negotiating with the terrorists right now you're giving you're giving too much
I really think so give what you there's no like you did you did a chapter you
did a vaporette for Vapor 2 if I go to if I go to a con and I sell I don't know
20 copies of Vapor 2 I'm not I'm sorry I'm not I'm not giving you any of that
I already paid you sure yeah that's that's your prerogative yeah yeah that's
your prerogative right but think of it like that's fucking right it's like
fucking prerogative think of it like this think of it like okay but like let's
say um I don't know let's say um you're you're you're you're you're an artist
right and then uh then Ben saying approaches you for a vaporette and I
call I duck under my table I call the police yeah let's say let's say it's
like oh you want to you do a vaporette but then let's say cheesy Manfredo comes
in and is like oh you want to do you want to do a clown milk story ultimately
which which job are they gonna take which one seems like you're gonna pay me
more well here's the thing right even though you may if you do the residuals
thing you may have like a history of going beyond the agreed upon amount of
money that doesn't necessarily mean that every time a great an agreement is
made you're going to go beyond I mean like let's say like I would say there's
a good one the agreement to be like you know the amount I expect let's say
maybe hope yeah I could hope that you would give me like residuals even though
you didn't say you would but like that wouldn't really influence my future
decision-making on who I would like to be working for when it should go back
to the company that keeps paying you more well only if it yeah but like there's
no guarantee like if it's not in the agreement if you if it's in the agreement
that you give residuals beyond a paid thing then I'm like oh that sounds like
a better deal the only thing in this situation is that the agreement didn't
involve that and you're doing it anyway yeah so so like as a as a as a decision
making factor if I see the agreement like say both of you have identical
agreements for a number of pages and a payout and cheesy may like is likely to
or potentially could give me extra money on top of that I just I don't know I
don't think I would like that would sway my opinion yeah you don't think so I
think I just I like things in writing I like things to know exactly what I'm
getting myself in for I to me it seems like oh this oh this cheesy manfredo
guy he just gives free money over and above well he's he's gonna he's gonna
go bankrupt his business is gonna go under he's gonna he's not he's never
gonna make it in this town he's NG yet he's NGMI because he's sucker not I
want to work for this guy because he pays more this guy's this guy's sunk
because he he can't because he because he's just bleeding money I know that's
nice to be nice to your friends but like in a business arrangement it's it's a
little different I mean I'll tell you I mean I mean most like the most I could
tell you is that I'll continue to talk to these guys and we'll arrange some
arrangements like I'll tell you that much right what what what arrangements oh my
well I will fucking like what we'll talk about like how residuals will work you
know like I got there are but okay but there is no expectation I have to I mean
yeah but there could be but why would you want there to be like I like I want
them to keep getting paid like what's what's wrong with that like I don't
fucking I there's I can't I can't do it there's just no there's that we've made
no progress we've made no progress here I I mean I don't I don't I don't want to
tell you I mean I'll talk to these guys and that's between me and these two
other guys right I don't have to expel every single little thing I agree with
these guys on this podcast unless I have to unless you were expecting me that
like to go for every little fucking little what give help give help you
already you already said it was like a verbal agreement yeah right and then
there's no deadline yeah exactly um that's why I'm not fucking worried if it
seemed if it seems like it was fucking ruining me yeah I'll talk to them I'll
rearrange things but it's not ruining me well of course it's not really cuz you
haven't given you haven't paid them anything yeah what's going on I don't
tell you even even if I like I don't know I even think I don't know I don't
tell you I been seen breaks down on the idea of not looking out for number one
but fucking fucking Ben sell Ben sell break seeds at the idea of your cheesy
your NGMI okay I'm sorry be your NGMI okay that's that's that's that's that's
my takeaway okay well I'll I'll end GMI here let me right I have no I mean I
have no I have no power to compel you to do any anything I don't know yeah that's
nothing more to say at this point I think it was a little bit of a sloppy
initial promise that relied on and it's like it's causing problems down the line
but if you're not worried about it then I guess we can just move on a different
topic yeah I'm not worried about it I mean in retrospect get the fucking
Kickstarter work as a pretty decent advertising for the pre-order it's
right yeah everyone loves everyone loves a comeback I'll tell you that much you
know and that's so that's that's the first thing on my list of what I did
wrong wait I have to pee I'll be right back I want to hear I do want to hear
the rest of this but I gotta pee I also gotta pee I'll be back all right okay I'm
back yeah what's what's up gamers are you sound excited just to hear from me all
right are we on to item number two give us not back yet oh where'd she go she
want to go she went to the where they call it there she went to the Lou oh she
went to the short to the crapper good I guess okay how can I take this only take
this opportunity how can I get through plot plot plot twist turns out big Twitter
artist guy too nice too nice for this world
and back yeah all right all right all right let's let's all right number item
number two let's go let's go I should have done way more promotion for the
comic okay okay yeah sure yeah like a lot of stuff could be um like could have
been a lot of stuff that I did later down the line I should have probably done
earlier the whole you mean like the the clown girl ads and stuff oh well I mean
here's the thing that maybe that probably wasn't the best thing for me to do
because um why cuz I cuz like okay so on paper like oh I have like a clown
milk like a porn comic I have a clown porn comic right I have that yeah who
do I get to promote this well oh there's clown girls out there that have only
fans I get them to promote yes right that seems to make sense on paper right
cuz they both have clown in the word right but the one thing that I kind of
noticed is that like every time one of these clown girls would make a post like
the pledges never seemed to jump like I didn't seem to get more pledges after
their posts right and that could be like okay it could be like one maybe it just
wasn't enough clown girls maybe I should have gone with a couple more right maybe
five because that's kind of like the thing with advertising you gotta see
something at least five times before you like give it a chance right that's that
a thing that's what I heard that it's gotta be at least five times get seen at
five times before you really consider giving it a chance okay like you know
before it breaks you down right or two makes make sense the people that kind of
like drawn like clown porn aren't the same kind of people who want like IRL
clown porn you know yeah maybe yeah that's cuz it could be a disconnect there
too right and even though like there's like a klusi means a bound doesn't mean
that like necessarily it's popular it could just be um what's the word for it
when something seems more popular than actually is
I'm not sure but yeah basically so the fact that a paper tiger clown paper tiger
like like like mate because I remember like a couple podcasts ago you mentioned
something about it seems like the clown real stuff is popular right now but I
could just because I follow cheesy man Fredo and he's the one mostly retweeting
right yeah it could just be that you're just following me and it seems like it
right it could have been I feel like there was that that ace attorney character
that just blew up and I saw everywhere mm-hmm yeah yes yeah it could be it could
be it could be that or it just could be that maybe these people just didn't make
maybe seem like the major the people just didn't like gel well with like my art
style I know like I had someone tell me that they didn't they didn't like my
art style for when it comes to porn so that that could be a more common take
with a lot of people I mean that's why there's like different artists on the
project right not not much you can not much you can really do about that right
you know let's say I get better at drawing porn but easier not not easier
done but that takes while before you know so so what's the takeaway if you did
it again would you not do any clown girl ads would you more clown girl I think
what I what I what I notice is that because later in the middle of the
Kickstarter I had the idea of like there was like a handful of people there was
two there was two like NSFW artists who I talked to about making like like if you
could draw a piece of art that promotes the Kickstarter I will just send you a
free copy of the book right and I noticed that when they drew their pictures
there was like a boost in pledges right which makes me think that it's the
audience that like enjoys like cartoon porn is more close to what I'm hitting
than the audience that enjoys like IRL clowns right yes yes so I probably make
sense to me yeah I probably would have gone more that route I would have probably
talked to way more like NSFW artists about doing promotion for it right yeah
yeah like maybe like maybe at least like 10 figures some sort of deal out with
right I think I feel like maybe this got discussed in my discord at some point
but like if you had maybe yeah done like instead of instead of IRL like only
fans girls if you had gotten like NSFW artists to draw like pieces for the
comic and like you could put them in the comic but you could also they could
also serve as like ads right now that makes yeah that makes sense right so
because yeah I mean it's it's a little like weird intricacies of marketing you
know like I mean like you know oh they both say clowns there must be an
overlap like oh well potentially like not really maybe right mm-hmm yeah yeah
that's I mean that yeah next time just do way more promotion or like really
think about who who's the kind of person who's consuming this right like you
know cuz I think only a handful of people that are like fans of my porn
stuff are like very clown centric and the majority are just kind of like oh I
like seeing drawn just humorous just humorous right exactly that's fair like
cartoon right but you target the coomer market the coomer market is bigger
than the clown market because the classy mark that's true so you are not so if
yeah it's reasonable okay okay that's yeah you got an item number three okay
I remember three is probably should have gone with more special rewards right yeah
I'm gonna kill you about the reward no that's not true I had some I thought the
rewards were a little weird yeah they were I thought that I thought that the
Commission tier was very strange I mean I the only reason why I set up the
Commission's like that because I asked like these guys how many commissions are
you willing to do for the Kickstarter yes I understand right this number should
have been zero because it doesn't make any sense what about it doesn't make any
sense well I mean if someone wants a commission they can just they can just
commission them to draw something yeah instead of instead of what does it have
to do with the Kickstarter right exactly what is yeah what it was after
the Kickstarter so what you're saying is okay the Commission should have been
lower no there should not there should not have been a Commission tier it's a
nonsensical tier like if it was lower that incentivizes you to like want a
commission out of here I mean it should have been I can't I can't believe how
much you're misunderstanding what I'm saying right now like the idea of rewards
is that you add value to the product that already exists and you charge higher
than the work you need to put into it so that you actually like make money off of
it mm-hmm so like a signature doesn't take really any work at all and it can add
value like and it can make like individual pledges a lot more an entire
commission is like work that costs a lot yeah that's yeah that's the thing it's
work it's like it's it's like it's additional work for the artist on top of
what was already done to make the product and so if it's like a bad it's like a
bad value proposition for for you the person behind the Kickstarter yeah
because you can't charge the whole price of an entire commission on top of all
of that because it then it might get too high for people to actually want to
pledge so you'd have to make it like a cheaper alternative but then the work
still needs to be done so you're losing money ultimately
mm all right I hear you that's why on the Lord of Ghost thing I would do I would
do doodles but they they're not like supposed to be good they're just sort of
a little asset they're not take too much time out of you right yeah I've heard of
I heard a very similar thing I just I guess in my head it was like oh you know
it's better than a doodle commission right and then it made sense then but now it
I mean from the point of view of you in this position of like I need to make this
Kickstarter hit its funding goal it does make sense right to offer to offer the
work of these to offer commissions from these other guys as as rewards as a way
to like artificially boost the number but I mean but like to me that's that's
what that is I'm bullying you cheesy I'm bullying you all right okay
why is too nice cheesy I like that about you it's nice definitely 100%
yeah so yeah that that's what I'm saying I from that angle I understand the desire to
do that understand the the the purpose of it but uh yeah um that's all I want is
understanding I just want people to understand where I was coming from you
know I don't want to be a thing I'm in a way I do in a way I do um but uh yeah I
think like kind of the point of the Kickstarter is that you've already done
the work and you are selling it now and you don't and you don't want you don't
really want uh reward tiers that incur a lot of additional work for yourself so you want to do
things yeah think things like paper crafts bookmarks posters stuff that stuff that you
can mass produce and include in the package you can put lipstick on and kiss each book or something
right I um but um there was one tier in the in the rewards I don't know if you saw it and I
mean I didn't really talk about it much was that one of the tiers was getting a video from pasta
the clown and he'll monologue whatever you want I did I did see that it's it's an interesting idea
it's kind of got the same problem as a commission in that it sort of involves the whole separate
production it the the the thing is that like um it's actually not that hard to think I mean yeah
you could you could mass produce that would not be like do all the makeup and set up the camera
but then you can do all of them at once right and yeah exactly yeah boom boom boom right right
after right so it's not that hard actually and I and I like and I love I I'm talking I love I gave
me an excuse to put on the makeup please well fair enough but did anyone go for that tier uh no I
didn't really talk about it I guess I didn't really talk about it because like I felt I felt I felt
sad I did you felt sad I felt sad why why did you feel sad because the Kickstarter was failing
that's okay but um sure um yeah I mean like I probably could have like lowered that tier
I want um here's the thing I oh I was like 200 okay um I think also I mean someone like mentioned
I saw one comment like in one of the videos a couple of videos ago where someone said that
she's gonna have enough of the reward between like the the physical book to like a commission
yeah new new made a comment yeah yeah and and a part of me like is like well I mean a I wanted
things to be simple and in retrospect that it's like shooting myself in the foot and I get that
but but then B is like a part of me is very much like I don't like doing that like I don't like
I don't really like fuck with like buttons or like or like kind of like making stickers and
shit like that you know and like uh I get it I get that it's a hassle but I I do think that's
like that probably would have helped me right yeah a little little like stuff like stuff like that is
stuff like that is I is good I mean I mean I got I got to thinking and tell me if tell me if you
agree with this um that like the people that when you do that you're I mean you're like you're adding
more value to the thing right yeah right because like well the thing is people don't and you and
you do that because like you know people don't value you too much right or like what wait hold
what do you add you add the extra value because you need it right uh sure I I guess right because
that that implies that they that they don't value you too much right because if you need to add the
extra value they don't value you I think it's just a little extra because like like people did buy
my comic without the pen because it's like they wanted the comic I mean people got like my comic
without the um it's it's it's not necessary it's just like you can you can you can I um
like the pins very cheap to mass produce they don't actually add as much value as I charge for them
so they're like they're like a very easy simple little way to like make a lot of profit out of
out of a little thing and it's I I feel like I feel like it's like um every person that comes to the
campaign who is interested in getting whatever the product is they've probably they've probably
got sort of like a soft limit for like how much they're willing to spend on this thing and stuff like
you know uh posters uh bookmarks pins you know little bonus value editions are basic are basically
they're basically just an excuse for them to like justify spending as much as they want to spend
on this thing yeah right like it has to be in small enough increments if you go from like 10
to 50 to 200 then like people are not the people who could who would be willing to spend 35
would just spend 10 because they don't want to spend the whole 50 you know
right yeah like you like you want you want like at the $20 tier for someone who just wants the
book and they've only got $20 to spend but for someone who's got 50 bucks that they're willing
to spend you want yeah if you don't have the $50 tier then they're gonna go for the $25 instead of
the $100 so you've missed out on the whatever they're low-key excuses but like um they're
they can be nice i think my little ghost pin is really cute
they're they're i mean they're excuses but i mean they it's they're not i mean they're they're um
like the pin is not i don't know how much how much extra did it cost to get the pin from the
lord of ghost kickstarter like 10 extra bucks or something like that like i can't remember i it was
really low to to have like 100 or 200 something pins sent to me it was it was yeah probably around 10
10 pounds 10 pounds uh right but i mean i think people know people understand that like this pin
was not did not an individual pin does not cost like the 10 pounds to reduce they're not really
getting like 10 pounds worth of hard value from it but it's the fact that it's associated with this
like exclusive timed event yeah and also the whole thing of like technically anybody could go to
like a pin manufacturer and get whatever pin they want but like it's a big hassle to do that and
if they just receive a little funny thing with their thing they buy and it's like ah cool there's
the the value of the exclusivity of the item there's the value of the fact that you're just
they're just supporting an artist that they like is yeah yeah so even though you might not fuck with
bookmarks uh it doesn't hurt to add them right it's got there's gotta be a way for me to circumvent
books it's gotta be a way i mean i am anti bookmark i like all the bookmarks what's what else i mean
what else was there something else you would you would do instead um fidget spinner um i would
i would um and i would say maybe at $50 you get a music stand with your copy of clown milk like
i'll send you it a music stand yeah yeah music stand like where you know where you put the sheet
music on isn't that like a big bulky thing am i having a stroke wait wait hold on wait i'm not done
so you get the music stand right and you put the book there making it easier to masturbate to the
while you're reading and that's a funny idea but that okay like buying music stands it was a joke
it was a joke i'm not it was a joke i'm not gonna fucking do that what the fuck are you crazy you
think i want to get a motherfucker music stand you insane you think i'm crazy you think i'm making
insane decisions you've lost it you've lost it you've lost the plot you think this is a psycho
you think i think you're a little bit of a jester you think you think i'm a funny little guy you
think i you think i'll pull a little clown maneuver like that maybe should i just should have
done the music stand tier like higher you should get like a at 300 you get the music stand you
should call it like a masturbation a masturbation yeah yeah yeah if that's the point or you could
you could have like a special tear where you cram the comic into a tiny car a tiny clown car and
send that and then you open it up and this like all crumpled and ruined but it's inside a clown
car so it's funny if the if the if the if the uh the campaign hits a hundred thousand dollars we
will invest in a clown car that will go door to door across the country and stop at every
individual backer's house and uh clowns will will pile out of the tiny car deliver their order yeah
i think it i think it could work fuck it we'll go we'll go we'll go um international too and
then someone orders a copy in ukraine you gotta take the clown car all the way in ukraine
is there a big red target on the fucking map okay so item number three is more more tears
more moichindizing i am moichindized yeah yeah is there is there a fourth is there an item number
four um i'm looking at what i listed as um potential items number four uh they're not like
they're not like major issues just kind of grievances or things or me retrospective grievance
persons yeah i have some i do have some grievances against people like cuz um okay let let let just
say i'd like to say a handful of people i realized like didn't really have my fucking back on this
like it worked me right me um he's talking about me i'm i mean i'm i'm down to say the names i just
need ellis are to like bleep them out cuz uh yeah please bleep every single one tell us who didn't
tell us you didn't have i was uh ellis are i'll give you i'll Venmo your 10 bucks if you bleep
all the names you don't need to venmo and he'll it'll just do it why yeah for fuck's sake
he's ellis ellis ellis ellis are ellis are gonna cut himself in the middle of this thing like oh
jeez you you can say you can send me the 10 bucks jeez it's okay you can send me the 10 bucks it's
fine so are you gonna tell us you're gonna give us the names or what uh like okay so like um i've
probably mentioned this before but fucking uh i ghosted me there this whole thing like um because
um so basically he has he has a podcast right and it's it's doing pretty good actually he's doing
like pretty good in numbers and it's a really good podcast like i've never considered being a
patron of a podcast until this podcast now mm-hmm right uh their podcast which is a really good
podcast and um they he and they have mentioned me on the podcast before like casually like almost
every other episode they just casually mentioned me right so i i dm them saying about like it's
basically the whole proposition of like if you guys could just promote um clown milk i will send
both of you guys like a free copy right okay and he just didn't reply back to that email right
yeah and then and then um i um i dm them on like uh twitter like a week later
right and about like hey did you get my email and he's all like oh we got a lot of emails um
well which one was yours and i i reiterated the offer to him and he just didn't he just didn't
say anything to it right yeah and then like then like another week later i tell him like look dude
the kickstart is not doing so well can you at least like retweet it and he he just didn't reply to
that and i i don't know why i don't know why and i mean this might just be a paranoid but it feels
like they're not like casually like mentioning me anymore on the podcast right uh and i i i don't
sound like they just this is not a not a good value proposition for them i mean if he if he told me
that if like because i didn't i mean i did offer him money like do you want do you think you need
to get paid for this because like i'll be down just like you know maybe buy some number because i
told him that like that that i could pay him um but like he just i guess they just were interested
i mean um if i were to kind of like guess why is because um they're about to shoot their own
patreon and i guess they didn't like want to ask their fans for money for another thing
and then they're gonna drop their patreon you know yeah kind of kind of makes sense
i could i could explain it i yeah or i mean another thing that could have explained it was
then maybe someone else like has um tried a proposition to him about like promoting something
and he said no to that and to be consistent he has to say no to me maybe maybe it just feels so it
just feels just so it just feels so weird like i don't know why because he's promoted my other
stuff before like i've asked him like it because this wasn't this isn't like the first time i ever
asked him to like can you retweet like a thing for me right so in this case like i just don't
know what the deal was and it's not like he is not like he's he's not the kind of person that's
scared to retweet porn because like he's like commissioned porn artist and he's posted it on
his like twitter right so it doesn't like i don't know it doesn't like um it doesn't like
make sense you know and it i don't really yeah it's hard hard to hard to say hard to say and
i'm not gonna lie because like i thought i was like decently close to this guy you know and i
was really bothered by it like like no joke i wouldn't like stop thinking about like what
was the deal like why like like like you think you think you got you think someone's got your back
and then it's like i don't know that sucks i mean i guess i guess you you were just i don't know
asking for more than he was willing to give you i guess i mean if he told me that i wish he would
just told if that was the case i wish he would have just told that they're like hey yeah i don't
know is he uncomfortable the thing is i've mentioned clown porn to him before and he's like oh let me
see that i'm sure i'm sure he's not i'm sure he's not like has an issue with clown porn i'm sure
that's not it i i just don't know i just don't know what the what the deal is you know i and i wish i
knew i wish he would have told me right because i because it's not the first time i just been
ghosted by someone and it's not like he unfollowed me on on twitter any like he so follows me but
it's just so like well what what is it like am i do i just pretend that this didn't happen the next
time i you probably there is going to be a next time i would say the Kickstarter was going to fail
like i give help i i don't know i mean i guess there's the there's technically room from just
have not noticed every single time that that could be it yeah you should mention it to him at least
so you know for sure if you want to talk to him again about it i mean i mentioned like probably
like i feel like i'll mention it when i'm in a better headspace about it i think because right
now i think you should probably assume that he did see it and just didn't feel like it and then
i'll just i don't know part of me just feels kind of weird pretending it didn't happen you know
i mean i i mean is it is it now that okay just don't ever ask for this don't ever ask anything
from this guy ever again like don't like don't ask for maybe because because i would hate like i
i would hate like if i like because i have like other Kickstarter plans and other projects and
it'd be i'd be kind of weird if like he like now i like see him retweeting those and then it's like
okay well what was the deal then you know i don't know i just i just uh i i don't want to come
i mean you're not i mean you're not you're not owed you're not owed or retweet yeah i i agree
i'm not owed anything but like you you know like i i that am i friends and did i think i'm
did i'm fake i'm more friends with this guy than i actually am
like that could be a thing but like i don't know the guy's been on my podcast twice
yeah like he seems to like like my shit i drew a picture from one of his like cards
right yeah i did oh i didn't know that like for the first wave i drew a picture of one of
it one of the cards like he asked me to huh yeah so what card um i did a big homo
oh well it's weird i haven't i haven't i hadn't seen that okay that's really yeah well i don't know um
i don't know maybe he just maybe just maybe he just wasn't a fan of the project for one reason
or another and who knows i maybe has beef with the two other artists that i have on it i don't know
i don't know it could be that's a there's something i'm kind of like
realizing more and more about myself and this should have been more obvious is that um
like it's it's not normal for people to go into other people's DMs and ask for retweets
that's not a normal thing apparently um
because i think more people are i think more people are scared about doing it
like it's it's a very scary thing we would do it's not normal but i mean it's not really normal
to be like a content creator with like a product to market yeah if you are that then i don't think
it's like particularly shameful or problematic to to do that i i think it's um i just i guess
because in the back of my head and i guess not everyone sees it this way and i still don't get
why no one still sees it this way is that retaining something does not take anything away from you
yeah ultimately you know but it feels like people think it does like they lose a little bit like
either their finger breaks pressing the retweet button or they lose a bit of their soul they're
well i mean you retweet a lot yeah i do retweet a lot right i think well i mean i think if a if a
twitter feed is like a if a twitter feed is like content then you you want to retweet
the the fewer things you retweet the more like a spotlight you put on each individual thing
true but i still gotten like my personal stuff like blown up outside of the concert retweeting
right yeah and and the thing is like i feel like people will still see the same number of like
tweets even if you didn't retweet so much you know maybe i i haven't like seen an argument like
against that i think that i think there's an argument to be made that like every every every
retweet you do sort of like takes a little bit of value away from all your other retweets if
someone like actually like brought it like down to me and told me this is like this is the deal
like this is how many like retweets and then i don't think like twitter is ever gonna say that
because it's the thing about they don't want someone to like perfectly game the system right
because that's like what youtube does as well they don't tell you exactly what are the things
or you do or not supposed to do because then like that's how you get like the else of spider man
videos well i mean they i don't think there is like a formula i think it's just like depends on
what people are looking at i because i also saw people say that like you know how they say like
oh if you if you add like a link to like a patreon or kickstarter commission in your tweet
it like makes it makes your twitter tweet seem like you get less people looking at that tweet
yeah yeah yeah yeah right but then i hear people say that that's not true like that's just
yeah people it's not it's not true it's mostly just people hyper focusing on that tweet so
they notice when it doesn't like i yeah i i think the the experience of using twitter generally
is just scrolling down and occasionally slowing down when you see something that's interesting
and so like the amount of retweets it only really becomes like apparent when you're on
that person's page but most people don't go to a person's page they just go to like twitter home
and they scroll down i feel like most people click they go to media tab first if they click on your
page uh yeah if you if you make like knowings yeah yeah if you yeah yeah that that is always
kind of a thing where it's like oh this artist made this really good thing i want to see what
else they do i click on their thing it's like 90 percent retweets of like memes i'm like okay i go
to the media tab and it's also got memes in it and i'm like i just want to see what they do
that is a frustrating thing if you're if you're an artist with a twitter you probably i can
understand why you might have like an an art account and then like a personal account because
like yeah if you want to see someone's art and you go to their twitter and you don't see the art
it's like well what's the point it's it's a balance to strike i don't think uh i don't think um it's
necessarily wrong of somebody to not want to retweet something for any reason i just think it
should be more normal to say no i don't want to do that instead of ghosting instead of saying nothing
saying nah nah i don't i don't want to clutter my page up with that like it that should be more
normal just admitting that that you don't want to do something i i mean i think it's um i mean
i think it's fine if people say they don't i just they fuck my body's stopping me from saying
like i think it's fine if people say no to a retweet my body is my body is physically stopping
me from saying that your mind understands but your heart can't can't it's process like okay
if someone like the thing is like i i feel like any if any mutual goes into my depending on like
i mean depending on what they want me to retweet i would say yes to anything like to any retweet i
don't care right yeah i'll retweet like there's there's people who are like former mutuals who
don't fuck with me and don't like me but i still retweet like their stuff specifically like mission
sheets because like they they need money like shit like i don't fuck with you anymore i mean if they
really like if they really like piss me off then i won't do it but if like they didn't if they're
the one who ghosted me like you know hmm right me i'm not gonna stop i'm not gonna stop retweeting
because i do think they're fine sure right sure i mean i usually just i get that i usually i i
never really think to like go to somebody individually and say hey could you retweet
this thing i usually just post and hope that it gains traction naturally because i i'd rather
i'd rather not converse with people i would do that i would maybe do that if like
i would do that if i was like doing a kickstarter or something i would maybe reach out to like
people who i know on twitter and be like hey you know i'm doing this thing like if you would uh
that's uh that's a little bit more time sensitive you know yeah yeah i didn't do that for my
kickstarter i maybe i should have it's the thing is it really doesn't take anything out of people
i was in um i was in this one discord server and um one of the one of the people that runs
that discord server like posted like two pieces of art in one day and they asked like they asked
like a more popular person there if they could retweet they asked them to repeat retweet the
first one and then when they posted the second one they asked they could do retweet the second one too
and this this person was really like he said like he he was like oh come on dude i already
like i already retweeted the first one and it's like it doesn't break your fucking arm like i was
about to fight this guy too i don't know i was like i was like i was an absorber about it but
like i was i was willing to like fight this guy on this but it's like why he gave he gave a retweet
the second retweet doesn't hurt it doesn't hurt you doesn't break your fucking fingers
well so what the guy wasn't obligated to do the first one and he's not obligated to do the
second one either but but but if they did the first one and like the second one shouldn't have been
that big of a fucking problem oh come on like if it's your buddy like if it's your friend
yeah i i if your buddy is like i don't see how this would be like okay i mean if this is a
total stranger and this is a total fucking i get if it's like a mutual you've never talked to before
and the first thing you when you pop into their dms is this that you know i get that
but this is like this is someone you talk to back and forth you're super casual and friendly
you're like why not like you know it doesn't fucking
it doesn't you know the fucking like end your life i understand i understand i kind of understand
and wanting to keep your feed clean
because if you're if you're if your feed is if your feed is content you want the content to be
good or you want or you want it to be uncluttered you want it to be focused i i understand i i mean
i would i would retweet i would retweet stuff that a buddy made i would definitely do that
but it doesn't mean i'm gonna retweet everything that they make i'm gonna do it if like i think
it's something that they would appreciate it enough that it's like okay the cleanliness of my feed is
not so precious that i won't do this for a guy i i get it if you're the kind because there's some
artists out out there who just never retweet anyone else they're just like constantly reposting
their own work yeah like i get that because there's no point in asking those people to retweet
something because they just don't yeah right yeah um but if you're not that kind of person and you
are like i mean the thing is like if you're willing to retweet uh a picture of someone who you're just
a fan of right like i i feel you should take the the offer for the retweet is is usually more inclined
because it's a buddy you know i mean sure yeah i am if if a buddy you know remember remember when
uh remember when nate wouldn't post the newest pcp on his channel uh even though like he like
got our channel hacked remember that gib uh yeah why did we end up putting it that would
that was i think i think trixie might have put it on her channel i think or something
uh yeah i remember yeah i i thought it was pretty i thought it was pretty uh stupid that
nate was like no i won't uh i won't host an episode of the pcp on my channel because like
the cleanliness of my feed uh lamal but uh so i mean i kind of get it i don't know there was
she was embarrassed about the pcp yeah probably i mean i don't know that was a joke i don't know
how true that it is but i mean like i i get it when it's like your brand or whatever it's like
high quality videos very infrequently and then to put a podcast on there it'd be like oh you're
doing these now like maybe some viewers would be turned off by that um i mean if you just what it
was just one episode right it wasn't like and it's your pot it's your podcast it was it was yeah
yeah i feel like it wouldn't have been a problem but like i can see the the mindset that would
lead you to i could i could see like feeling i feel like see i wouldn't have put it on hypocrite
but i'm totally fine putting it on gib and take because gib and take is just a grand bag of stuff
you know sure right i guess i guess um checking the general real quick
why am i looking at this
that's what that's what happens when you retweet something so when your big art is
that's what happens to you uh you become like you become a moldy Voldemort sad but you become a
little a little fried up fetus i think it's a banana or something it looks like as tea yeah it does
look like it has teeth maybe it's like a little yeah it's the root is it like a root of a plant
the legs look like banana peels almost like the leg i don't it kind of looks like maybe it was
been edited because it looks like that little hands there is too much of a hand the hands on the feet
look very like deliberate this is what a fetus looks like on the fourth month this is a banana fetus
the banana fetus i call it i call it the fried fetus yeah i have to pee again and i'm gonna go
do it no one can stop me you gotta go abort that fried fetus right now man all right um
uh you got any more insight for me gib uh on on on what on retweeting whatever
this is really sweet yeah sure uh well my policy has always been that i retweet things that i think
are cool and that maybe my followers haven't seen so it's like do that too it's like oh
this is a cool art and this is from this this cool art i have been notified because i follow
someone and they liked it and it's got it's only got 12 likes um but this is really good
so i retweet it and like it and be like i'm glad to share that cool thing with people i do occasionally
do like the the sort of obligatory retweeting for awareness um even though it's like you know it's
just sort of like a friend thing it's like oh it's a gotta let people know you know gotta let
people know about this even though my followers aren't this is not that many of them uh like
generally speaking i don't think it's i don't think i've ever really had like a problem retweeting
something that maybe my followers are not interested in okay i'm back but i'm also not like that big
of a twitter user like it like i don't have so many followers that i don't i probably wouldn't
even hear about like negative feedback about a thing i retweet anyway so i don't know it's
just sort of like a doesn't really come up my day-to-day twitter usage
hey did you guys um you guys see that's the jorts the cat drama on twitter this week
genuinely cannot comprehend any of it what the fuck are you talking about uh it was the
word it was the word it literally the worst thing ever literally the worst thing that's ever happened
wait is that the so angry that the grubhub one uh more or less yeah i think you're thinking
about it you run that because i saw i saw you guys talking about it but i didn't read it because
you guys were talking a mile a minute yeah uh all right i'll try and some i'll try and summarize
uh and i'm gonna be as and i'm gonna be as neutral and i'm gonna be as factual as possible here
all right so what what happened was this lady uh with a not huge account but like a big-ish
account like 10k or something um made a tweet about how men can't shop and every time she gets
a mail instacart shopper they fuck up the order so one time she tracked down the man that was shopping
for her and found him standing in the aisle of the supermarket looking at his phone this was this
was the tweet yes i remember that and this and this cat this gimmick he is apparently a pro labor cat
this is like a cat account who retweets like union efforts which is great i guess
this so this guy just so this george the cat gimmick account said idea get your own groceries
or idea buy your own groceries now what do what do you think happened after after george the cat
said this uh i know people got mad yeah that's all i know do you know why because he's a cat
and cats can't be involved in human life because he's able is yes that's right
see on the face of it that always seemed a bit silly because if she tracked him down
she clearly went to the store and she's in front of the groceries which she could then buy
yes it's not like she was unable in that instance to get the groceries she just like the convenience
which is what the app is for that's right and then what happened i mean i mean that's the the the
fear the fear was you know a lot a lot of accounts tweeted that george is ableist because uh because
he said get your own groceries i thought that was and if and if you said that to a disabled person
that can't get their own groceries that would be really bad but what if you said that to someone
else and it was in a worse context maybe you think ever think about that i i i don't know i don't know
um this listen i'm minimizing it i'm minimizing the the irreversible psychic damage that has been
done to me this week i i will i swear i will never be the same this is this this this this has broken
me this has tipped me over the edge i am less of a person now than i was before see i didn't look
into it but like it seemed like a huge deal i was sure there was more to it than the ableism
that no it's it's literally like people it's it's literally disabled people said like
this this is about me this is this would be ableist if you said this to me and now the fact that you
said this to someone who isn't disabled is now people are gonna say this to me also and that
and how could you do this to me george how could you do this to me george george the cat used to
be an institution you could trust and now now that's been stained okay um uh it's just i i i just i
what is the it went on for like two days people were angry at george george for being ableist
for telling this woman and then like and then it kind of evolved because people people were
people were saying people were talking about how much they need instacart right and it literally
is like totally beside the point because it doesn't matter how much you a disabled person
need or rely on instacart literally irrelevant to to what happened and but people kept making
these posts about how i'm disabled and i need instacart i'm disabled and i rely on instacart
and if an instacart gig worker got my order wrong it would financially devastate me or whatever and
like great first first of all i i use as someone who has used instacart i know that you can just
fucking report a like wrong order and they will just refund it you can just fucking complain to
them and they will give you your money back it's it's totally deranged to be like it would
financially devastate me if my instacart shopper got my order wrong that would never wait wait
whose side are they on then i thought they were mad at george for saying get your own groceries
but they're also mad at the idea of a guy getting the groceries wrong there's there's two sides
well yeah yeah yeah because because this woman because this woman is right to stalk and harass
her gig worker because if she had been disabled and this guy had got her order wrong that would
be abuse you see that would be abuse of the disabled it's it's the two sides it's uh it's
the you know it's the people who like are mad at the grub hub worker keeps fucking up the order
and then the people are kind of like if they keep fucking up why don't you just get the order
and then i'm super abled that evolves into the oh well what if i'm disabled and i'm like what if
the grub hub worker is disabled like what if the grub what if what if the shopper's disabled
bro what if i what if the shopper's disabled what if i go into your house and fucking kill
what if i slit your throat while you're asleep what the fuck about that people you never consider
that as an option and people started posting their stuff and there were there were a few
very weird ones that were like i have adhd and therefore i can't shop in person therefore i have
to therefore i need i need a gig worker to do it for me and and also i reserve the right to stalk
them if they do it wrong i you know this woman was right this woman was right to stalk to stalk
her her gig worker it's he was abusing her i know um what else did i
i'm glad like i haven't really thought about it in the last couple days but like when it was going
on this was like i was i was i'm glad i'm glad i have some distance from it let's just say i'm
glad i have some distance from it because i could i could not deal with it yes it was so infuriating
trying to think what else yeah but she do she do got a point though men suck at shopping though
she's right she's right about men men do be men do be failing at shopping they do be failing at
shopping right that's really the whole like literally the whole point of the original post
was like men suck oh the whole point of the original post was men suck and then
and then and then jorts dammit jorts i i i thought i could trust you i i thought i believed in you
jorts and you let me down he he and he apologized he made a full apology for his boneheaded post
that hurt so many people and and he said like oh yeah me and this woman we've reconciled like
donate to her go fund me uh you know uh of course she ended she ended up being a turf obviously
ended up being a car but it doesn't matter because the uh because the fake disabled
bullies demanded demanded blood and even and even after and even after even after the apology
people were still posting like it's not enough jorts it's not enough to set off the harm you
call it would you please please work with the disabled community to continue to like to like
undo the irreparable harm that you've caused with your thoughtless comments jorts has to go like
to the school to school talking about why being uh able is there is there is no there is no appeasing
some people there's no appeasing some people and you should never apologize you should never ever
apologize for anything it's because you'll it'll never be enough that's what i've learned he posted
jorts jorts will never there's nothing jorts could do to to to wipe the stain of ableism off
of him now it's too late that's so true ben just like i'll never apologize for for being too nice
and giving people all of money that i can't promise them i will never apologize ever the apology
you will you will perish you will you will you will you will perish you'll be wiped from the
face of the earth hypocrite ben got him that's me you actually you will fail you will the free
market the free market will devour you a more ruthless a more ruthless uh uh artist will fear
the market will take your place in the market is what will happen to you my friend i'm so scared
you well i well guess what ben guess what ben guess what guess what i'm disabled so i'm gonna
need you to like no i'm disabled no i'm disabled oh yeah from myself down the stairs it's sort of
like beat top that it's sort of like you imagine somebody just posting a tweet saying i had a
really good run today and then somebody said um i can't run so yeah that's funny this morning i saw
people were reacting to like some lady posted about how much she liked sitting in her garden
and how much she loved her husband oh yeah people were like um not all of us can afford gardens or
husbands yeah or husbands yeah it's just sort of like okay i i you're reading into my non-tweet
like non position so many positions i have i have i like i have i and i and i don't think anybody
has anything against like anyone who is disabled and relies on like a gig to like do their grocery
delivery like it's fine and like literally nobody is mad about that but they they they they this
totally unrelated thing a certain kind of person saw this as an attack on them yeah personally for
some reason and made a big discourse about it that lasted like three days and i hated it
was so angry it really it was like the worst it was it was probably the worst twitter discourse
of 2022 if i had to if i had to put my it really had to gun to my gun to my head this was the worst
i mean it's a funny thing to say because like twitter discourse is so vapid and so like nothing
that i completely forget every single one of them i don't even know what happened this year on
twitter i'll never forget i'll never forget where were you when george said get your own
like can you even name a single other twitter discourse that happened this year
there's there's so like like you know in the moment and they think is that they tend to repeat
they do they kind of tend to repeat and go in cycles i am i started some discourse in in cell
discourse men aren't men aren't having enough sex that one comes up every now and then
nice um what else i don't know uh i don't know some careful careful shit careful um
me when i when i decided to go after bendy and was labeled in ableist because it turned out
bendy was disabled me no me oh bendy yeah oh that blue guy yeah blue guy was he disabled no
who was like he was like in his thirties or something is that like the i guess we
know that well that's that's a disability that's a disability yeah bendy the the
fucking indie horror game mascot um so there's bendy the and the ink machine that's the video
game and then there's bendy fan one two three or something like that he's like his bendy fan 1488
on twitter bendy yeah and uh and i know i know the horror game you're thinking of but that's
that's a different he was like uh he was like a adult larpy and i was like a 13 year old oh yeah
bendy fan 13 i was and he was like oh wait i remember the blue yeah the blue guy yeah yeah yeah
and like i went once it was revealed that he was like an adult and um had was posting such
shit in in the week that he was active um i made a tweet like uh like shitting on people for drawing
fan art of him because in my head i thought like okay well these things come in cycles right like
people people love the guy and then everyone starts shitting on him so i'm going to jump ahead of the
line on the whole shitting on him but no it turns out people still love them even though it was he
was like i come i remember i'll be honest i never really saw that guy around i i saw like yeah
but that's how that works always right like i never saw any of the george the cat shit
it wait wait so you just you just decided to like get out ahead of like you were like this is a
popular guy i'm sure he will eventually be exposed no he was already he was already exposed so i'm
going to be the first hater i'm going to be the the primordial hater of this guy so when he
eventually the community turns on him i'll be the guy that everyone looks to and be like this
guy knew it this guy called it no no i he was already exposed by the time i made the tweet
but i guess the news did not reach around that fast what was the expose what was he was he was
just that he was older he was large his whole plan was that um he made this account where he was
like pretending to be 13 and he would like draw his shitty like bendy oc's and he would like
go around and like pretend to be a cringey 13 year old and then one and he would do the thing
where it's like oh can you draw my character and someone actually did it and it blew up and he
became super popular really quick right because everyone was under the idea that he was just some
13 year old like just trying to try and just trying to make it on twitter right and and just
trying to make it but then people like trying to make and he's only been around for like that that
guy's gmi yeah you should you should learn a thing or two from that guy yeah i should i should pretend
to be 13 and then be like hey guys i started a cloud point kicks whatever um you're a minor uh
you can't be doing that what's um for what happens if a minor like draws porn um they immediately
teleport to jail i have if a minor wants to draw a porn go ahead just don't post it online
you shouldn't post any of your is it like is it like illegal for a minor to like draw a porn
and post it no it's not there's no law it's just sort of like it just shouldn't be encouraged i guess
because the there'll be it's weird because they don't really know what they're doing it is very
weird and but i feel like there's so many people out there who encourage it yeah i i see um i've
never i've never seen like a minor posting porn i've definitely seen minors posting some kind
of itchy stuff though yeah um there's like a there's like a i don't like there's an art style to the
that crab girl there's there's someone there's someone with an oc that looks exactly like
the villain in that meme in mimi ori's comic yeah you know you you know the oc i'm talking
about the girl with the crab there's like another guy would have there's another guy who has a
crab girl oc but he doesn't drop yeah he's he's not a minor anything to draw porn as far as i know
hmm well there's one well there's there's one person who i thought was a minor who has a girl
with crab claw hair and and he and he draws and it looks like it looks like uh frickin uh craig
mccracken cartoon but bad um but there's like butts this it's it's definitely it's definitely itchy
it's definitely the most like the most like pop the most like fame infamous of the minor she drew
porn was um ink plasm you know i'm praying you know ink plasm nope um no he kind of has this
kind of like almost like imagine like adventure time characters but thicker like they have big
hips and big tits that's kind of like the art style for the miners who draw porn if you're a
minor you draw like that you probably draw porn like secretly oh i i've seen um this oc
okay it's like a lizard girl anyway that guy yeah that guy would draw very suggestive things and
people would get mad at him but he would always be like oh okay i'm just oh guys i'm just a minor
guys guys i'm just a minor as i'm just a minor don't be mad but then it got revealed
but then it got revealed that he he would secretly do nsfw commission it's like he would keep it under
like like he wouldn't tell anyone yeah so he was doing that the whole time being a minor that got
him a lot of like negative attention but i mean but i mean why would you mention that he's not him
that's gonna get in trouble for it wouldn't it be the people that are doing something wrong it would
be the people commissioning him but he at the end of the day he's like a bigger name that them
than them so he's gonna get all the attention for it right yeah yeah um yeah like i think i think
you're a minor and i think there's just like very like what i mean people are really what are you
gonna do the whole like call the cops yeah yeah he's doing it again he's drawing he's drawing big
titty lizard girls yeah he's only 13 see 13 no no i'm joking but okay okay i i i have no idea how
the guy was when i know he's like 18 now he's not he's not a minor no good for him so retroactively
all the stuff he did was is a okay now it's all okay now yeah because now he's 18 it's all good
yeah it's just it's like a discussion to be had about like the prevalence of not safe work
imagery on the internet and how easy it is to get but like i don't know how different that is from
how it used to be it just sort of like now social media means that you you're more able and and
encouraged to post whatever you make on the internet for everyone to see i i don't and people don't
people if they can't tell based on your art skill how young you are you just get away with lying
yeah i i don't i try never mostly to never follow any minors um because like i'm really like a
pose of a minor being popular on the internet who needs that yeah like i i think that's i think
that's not good for people and the minor if you shouldn't be popular and if you're a minor i think
that fucks you up yeah you shouldn't be on the internet until you're 28 i yeah exactly i i think
like you bird out a lot quicker if you're popular as a minor you know you know how people complain
about how like oh because kids nowadays have easier access to like digital art program so they're
learning art skills at a way faster pace that's why you get like minors who draw so well but but in
retrospect um because they're minors and they're so so susceptible to like trying to be popular
online they bird out quicker and they usually delete their account at a younger age yeah which
is pretty base and then that leaves us the adults still around your mentally sound and be like ha ha
minor minor couldn't cut it it's meant to be bad so they couldn't cut it stupid big baby you should
have been so good at r u motherfucker i sure hate it when somebody young is better than me at something
so i love it when they die yeah i don't die inside and i say grow up into a ball i say what the people
want to say you know i i say the things people actually want to say you know i don't sugar
code i'm not a little pussy bitch you know you know i'm me and me and george george the cat we
got a lot in common actually you know george the cat he betrayed me he betrayed me i had i believed
in him you were the chosen one i thought he was based but he would he ended up being a friend she was
grand yeah yeah can't believe he caved can't believe he let me down so sad so sad hey while we're
uh sort of on the topic of arts and stuff um i got new commissions i've got a new commission
thing oh that's right i'm doing more i finished all of the old ones and now i'm doing more
nice you've been you've been getting better you've been getting better at art give i really
thank you um i thought i thought you were gonna i thought you were gonna be uh working on Clarissa
i am um it's actually it's funny i was talking to my therapist about like ah jeez these commissions
taking so long ah shit ah fuck and she was sort of like encouraging me to you know finish them
and then like like do more because i was worried i was i was worried about like oh people was i took
so long on those last ones what if people hate me and they'll never commission me again and so
she's saying for you should you should do it again like for peace of mind see what see what
happens because you if you worry about like potential bad things happening in the future
based on like zero information um you're just going to be worried forever so like actually
just do it and see what happens if people don't want to commission you anymore then you know
you have more actual real reality information that you can base future decisions off so that's
why i'm doing it it's like uh it's a it's a it's a i don't know testing the waters because i do
worry about things without like like i think of the worst possible outcome and i worry about that
when i don't actually know what's likely to happen because i haven't tried anything
so that's why i'm doing it and i think it's gonna go well i've already started one
and it's looking great i've been very more productive recently uh just good also on clarris as
well very nice very nice it's pretty nice i sent me to um get you the script for the guest comment
for my alien girlfriend yeah also that is happening that's happening to give is gonna do a guest
comment from my alien girlfriend um by the time this video comes out i have i'm working on a little
halloween special for um my alien girlfriend um it was going to be called um it's called no it's
going to be called uh my demon girlfriend doesn't know i'm a demon uh cool right is it so and it's
basically just a remake of the first episode but um instead of aliens you're demons
i've still got a like i i've caught like bits of of the alien girlfriend
comic but i haven't read the entire thing i think i've like skipped a few accidentally
gonna have to reread it just go on webtoons i mean it's it's there's not too many at this
point so you could catch up pretty quick yeah um and like at least one third of it is like guest
comics because like i've been focusing on a bunch of other things i i do have other things i'm working
on oh but in uh but in good news and you're gonna love to hear this ben um Mimi or Mimi already
DMed me recently and she's saying she's um she put all her other projects on pause just to get extra
souls finished and she is pumping out the pages a lot faster oh that rule yeah yeah she's sending
it to me and they look really fucking good so so uh so even so even though there was no expectation
of uh residuals on that for me you know because i i did fund i did fund it but i said uh you don't
have to pay me royalties after after all i want is my initial investment back but you know you're
you're gonna give me you're gonna give me residuals anyway right even though i there's no expectation
of them okay um i would have before this podcast but after this podcast i don't think i'm gonna do
i mean not not because not because like i wouldn't do that for anybody else but because um
you're mean specifically mean yeah mean yeah i like you yeah you're meanie you're a big meanie
head and um i'm gonna starve you by not giving you money i'm gonna starve you whether yet
you look at it could i get residuals in in the form of uh shout outs and retweets for for my guest
comic it's like every 10 minutes you retweet one of my posts you know i give you know like yes and
also um open wide i'm gonna dump with this barrel of free estrogen down your mouth just wow yeah
ben ben doesn't get any though no none for ben hell yeah what the fuck ben ben just gonna get
you missed out and this is i don't be like balding ben but it's fucking
i'll be like that's all you two i'm yeah i'm two months i'm two months into my uh into my uh
not finasteride what's the other if i just into my minoxidil application so another month or two
and we'll see if uh anything happens there and then we'll have and then we'll have the last laugh
maybe what would you do ben if only one hair grew a lot and it was like a one really long curl at the
top you would kill him i don't want to cut it what the fuck he would make a it would make a rope out
of it to hang himself yeah what if he had exactly enough of the hair to make the Homer Simpson
you were gonna say what if like there was one hair but it was like really thick like it was like a
whole like inch in diameter yeah like like a twisted realm like a like a a rope that's horrible
that's too scary to even think about um uh the the the what shit i feel like i'm gonna say something
else about extra souls um the only yeah the only residuals i need are that executive producer credit
just um all right just just print just print just print that print it with print it with executive
producer ben saint and i'll be and i'll be more than happy it'll be on the cover and i'll be bigger
than the title yeah actually actually instead of like a traditional cover just put the tie just put
just in in times new roman right or in like in like typewriter font an aerial not aerial just
just have it look like a screenplay and just say extra souls executive producer ben saint and that's
all and then you can have the cover page on the inside the title is gonna be ben saint presents
a ben saint production a ben ben saints extra souls that's what's gonna be the title i just
realized i don't know what extra souls is what is this oh what maybe i know what that is is it
do you want to explain it i'll tell it okay so extra souls is um it's a comic it's that i wrote
based on a short film that i was working on years ago and i had to cancel
and um i rewrote it as a comic and i've been talking to several different artists about drawing it
and twice it twice it fell through like two artists couldn't like finish it they couldn't
like they like lost their interest very quickly and then i finally um got me me already to do it
and the plan was that like uh we would like do the whole pre-order things on the on the comic and
she would get like 800 the first 800 would be hers by the fault um then i told ben about it and
ben just offered to give her because well because maybe because mimi already said like she wanted
to do it yeah but she like couldn't justify like taking the time to do it on like the promise of
future payment well she was gonna she was gonna do it she was gonna do it already before you came
along it's just that yeah but it was like down the price it was like down the priorities list so like
who knows when it would have ever actually gotten done right yes that's true so ben ben came along
um executive producer ben to say um that's right came along and just gave her the 800 and she's
been i just i just said i'll just i'll just pay it now i'll just pay it now so you can start doing
it now and then you can when you sell the book later you can pay me back uh uh cool anyway i
didn't hear any i didn't hear about it for a long time but i guess you asked her recently and she
said she is back at it so that's cool yeah she it was like yeah because um she's just she kind of
her life has kind of changed since like the last we started right i think she moved to whole new state
and started a new job but um she's taking priority in the book now so she's still speaking of
speaking of speaking of uh comics i'm still waiting i'm still waiting for i think simsie has
probably dropped that one page that he sketched i don't think he's gonna finish it at this point
should i give him the clown note deal uh royalties forever bad no no um
um kai kaiju asked me like a week or two ago
he like asked what was left and i told him he's he he was supposed to draw the cover
and there's like one other page he was gonna do and i haven't heard back from him but he'll
probably get it done at some point and new new i know you're listening you sketched two you
sketched three pages and then you finished one and i and i sorry i DM'd you back late but uh
whenever you finish those uh i want those other two please do them thanks they look really good
by the way the sketches look really good i think that's it and i i think that like
like two more pages from new and like two more from kaiju and one that i think simsie was gonna do
but maybe i'll have to find someone else to do it and like that's that's it for the the dojin
crazy yeah i know new can do it i just offered him a comic for um that volume two and he says
gonna take that who uh new new yeah uh well good for him uh well uh well nevertheless that's
that's the plan the next week next time the next vapor's chapter comes out i'm gonna drop the next
clown milk snatch up everybody for the minute did i um did i already say did i already say
that i know i said last week that i might have the video done this week but this time i really
mean it guys like really for real this time uh yeah yeah well i'm saying it again um i i should have
i had yesterday i honestly i like could have finished it yesterday but i didn't uh uh i like
like like all i have to do for it to be like done is basically just watch it through and just like
make and just like go into the file and make any corrections because like sometimes there's
like a gap in the footage or sometimes like an image got like moved at some point and it's in
the wrong place and i have to just like find those and just move them back to where they should be
and and um i'm like i'm like two hours through re-watching my eight hour video and uh it's
hard and i don't like it i'm sick of looking at it i don't want to watch it anymore but i just have
to put like there's another i just have to get through it i have to get through it and then
it'll be done and then i'm post it so i i'll probably post it this week i'll probably post it
before this episode comes out so i hope it's out by the time this episode is is published and that
will be fun that'll be fun this is gonna be your eight hour um rebuttal to uh two unique
name of source is eight hour in the pentagonist tea video right yes um there's like a hurricane
going on outside like suddenly there's like a loud thunder and now it's like there are leaves
like pelting my window at like a hundred miles an hour nice i can hear a little bit of it yeah it's
cool i don't hear anything this is really like amazing actually there's another thunder dude i got
to film this i'm gonna film this wow just all out of nowhere huh yeah she's got to get distracted
like that i don't know where um wait how long are we even going are we at three hours or two
two two hours and 20 minutes um uh i'm trying to think if i can mention there's some more
things i could i could talk about um sure yeah i go i've been talking to eddie adam i also want
to shout out eddie adam again is he still on twitter no good okay good he's smart he's he's
on instagram oh okay the idea for instagram i'm a shout out to like eddie adam's i gotta tell you
there was like a there was like a handful of people out there who like who are who are friends of
mine who just did not who i really had to fucking convince to give me one retweet on clown milk
right yeah i really had to like i'm not gonna say any names oblivion fall i'm not gonna say any names
but um um eddie like eddie does not like clowns eddie does not fuck with clowns
okay like right but eddie likes me and so eddie like did at least like three posts about clown
milk on instagram well good good ol good ol eddie and eddie's a real eddie's a real g for
doing that eddie like i i appreciate eddie a lot all right sorry i'm back uh it was it was like i
was in a car wash so fucking so much wet are you gonna post the video i will eventually it's annoying
getting stuff off my phone i'm at the edge of my seat you can't you can't just put it in discord
i i probably can hang on put it in discord posted in the general sometimes the videos are too big
yeah discord who knows sometimes let me try speaking of videos being too big i rent i test
rendered a 720p resolution version unfinished version of the video it took like 30 hours to render uh
i uploaded it it's on my channel unlisted just to see if it would catch any like uh copyright
claims it did not so that's good um uh so that's it's gonna oh my god but i have to render it in um
it's it's filmed in 2k you know like like a 222 uh what's the resolution thousand kilograms
it's it's 225 60 by 1440 so not 4k but it's like higher than higher than hd uh so that's gonna be uh
that's gonna take like 60 fucking out so actually you know what i said the video would be out this
week no it won't it'll be done this week but then it'll take an entire other week just to
render the fucking video so uh sorry about that you should make a you should make a live feed of
it rendering so like people could watch that yeah i wonder if anyone's ever thought of that just a
live feed of a video rendering just watch the bar i feel like it would slow down the render though
having to process and then send out the footage of it so if you hate if you hate the person you
will watch the stream to slow down their rendering um yeah so um the reason why i mentioned eddie
adam's earlier is because i've been talking to him about him because eddie adams mostly publishes
stuff through a through a publication called silver sprocket and um they're pretty um there
there's they're like what i like is that they're like big enough that they can get like um their
books like across like the country in different bookstores but also that they're small enough
that they still look at like smaller indie people right yeah so i was talking to him about like um
potentially getting extra souls published through uh silver sprocket and he laid it down to me and
it sounds um it sounds pretty it sounds very fucking doable it sounds really fucking incredibly
doable um and i mean to just kind of give you an idea of like what kind of stuff they do um
silver sprocket is the is a publisher that published the complete collection of mr boob
so yeah yeah that's the kind of that's kind of caliber we're trying to get to you know
and i feel like it's possible i feel like um we get um we get uh does um this remi boy del
published through them too um i don't think so i think remi goes through image comics
oh okay yeah or the i mean the pervert was publisher image comics i remember that
okay um there's a handful they have a whole other website they have like the whole list of people
they've worked with um you know i see uh yeah i mean i've heard of them i think i i mean they
mr boob is a good yeah yeah right we're gonna um we're gonna outshine mr boob we're gonna blow
his ass out of the water hmm i think this will work oh my god new video by gibb and take video
on google photos oh i'm watching it oh it's a video oh it's oh hell yeah oh hell yeah there it goes
whoo getting getting a big old thunder lightning flying through the window yes there it is the flash
oh my god she's in this video wow that is some wet that's some big way there that's some
damn i'm feeling damp just just looking at it it's um
and yeah it reminds me of it reminds me of my window but it's also been damp and wet here
where i live hmm you live in california right yeah yeah but the rain the rain season starting
pretty soon right yep it's right after the forest fire season it's uh it's chili it's chili over
here it's getting chilly it's beanie weather i wore my signature beanie for the first time in the long
time the other day the iconic ben beanie when i walked to mcdonald's because i got sick because i
was sick from the vaccine and i was having a fever and i was like i'm gonna die i feel like the
worst so i went to sleep and i woke up the next day and i was still kind of sick and i'm like oh
i'm gonna be sick all day so i ordered so i said um so because i'm disabled i was disabled by the
vaccine so i had to use uh i had to use door dash i had to use a gig app and so i ordered i ordered
like uh five guys and then i ordered pizza but then like i like by the time it got there i wasn't
sick like i i i got over it in like an an hour after i woke up uh but then the next day i just
wanted mcdonald's so i walked to mcdonald's just because i just because i was on a streak just
because i was on a streak i was off the wagon so i wore the beanie and that's my story
and i hope you enjoyed it did you get your adult happy meal
yes which one which one uh no i did not i no i did not actually get the adult happy meal
damn did they have because i watched because i watched the report of the week
review the adult happy meal and i was not impressed by what i saw
this the deal though just falls apart i don't care about the fucking meal itself i um i wanted
the little toy that i put it looks it i thought it was it it just it looks it it looks like a
regular happy meal toy but just to say it just looks like dog shit wait i guess it's like designer
or something but like it's just like i mean that's what people want they want like dog
shit plastic well not like i'm not me i'm not people so i guess you're not an adult then then
this i guess you're not a human yeah yeah i'm not yeah adults want the adult happy meal if you are
not then what are you even doing here i don't know geriatric happy meal um i ordered like five
things i i had looked i had looked at door dash to get mcdonald's delivered and i was like oh it's
gonna cost like 12 dollars for what i want plus like another five dollars or more for delivery
fuck that i'll just walk there because like a 15 minute walk so i walked there and then i was like
oh i want everything and i spent like 20 so i ended up spending more just buying it in person
um because i wanted like five different things and then i ate that i ate it all immediately
i didn't even save it for later hell yeah but it was so good but it was so good though okay well
you save your mcdonald's food sometimes well i mean if i get more than i can eat right away
fries are never good if you save them i didn't get any fries oh well so there you go what what did
you get my i got i'll tell you exactly what i got i got an apple fritter i got a cinnamon roll
which was bad don't get the cinnamon rolls the apple fritter was good the cinnamon roll was bad
um i got a big mac i got a no i didn't know it was breakfast menu
no i got a uh i got a chicken biscuit um i got an egg McMuffin and i got ah the steak the steak egg
and cheese the steak egg and cheese sandwich at mcdonald's incredible the best the best breakfast
sandwich the best fast food breakfast sandwich money can buy order now order now yes i am sponsored
uh so there you go that was that would and it cost me like 20 21 dollars and it was stupid
hey but i wore the beanie that's the point the only point of any of this is just to say
that i wore a beanie that's great ben i'm proud of you so now it doesn't even matter it doesn't
even matter that i shave my head because i just wear a hat finally back back on brand
yeah it all it all comes full circle uh i i got to mention uh the live gig will be as of the release
of this episode on the friday 28th tomorrow i'll be at that thing where i'll be playing some songs
with my dad's band for a parkinsons charity relief thing so that's saturday um yes i see well
should be should be cool same links this last time uh thanks to the few people who did donate
even though they'll never make it because they're in america it's very far away
you'll have to you'll have to yeah the money's gonna take a long time before it reaches there
yeah so far away by pelican putting the mouse pelican the the bird how that goes
you'll have to tell us how that goes the next day you're gonna be you're gonna be there right
on the podcast i'm i'm yeah book my ticket oh wow use my freaking flyer miles
nice what a pal i think it's gonna be good i'm gonna play some songs and it's gonna be
not terrible the the only thing i'm worrying about what more to ask for what outfit i wear
because obviously i'm the dad's band dad's just gonna wear dad's clothes there's gonna be like dad
rock dad stuff but i'm not a rock dad i'm uh like i'm not that you're a rock chad i'm a rock chick
um but uh i don't know i don't really have like a stage out a brown brick um i don't really have
like a stage outfit i just want to have clothing i want to look cool but i don't want to look like
i'm trying too hard you know i spent i went to that uh i went to that vintage clothing store near me
and i foolishly spent 60 on a like dark gray like lab coat i don't know it's like kind of a weird
item of clothing i guess it was kind of neat looking it fit pretty well i don't know when
i'll ever wear it it's like a it's like it's not like lab coat fabric it's like a niceish fabric
but it's a lab coat and uh i guess maybe i could wear it as part of some sort of halloween
get-up i don't know just wanted to break from rick and marty it's not the right color um i don't
know i just went in there and i was like i found something and i think i would have bought it no
matter how much it cost because i just wanted to buy something you said you had a lab coat right
it that is the item i described yes okay well obviously there's only one carry there you should
there's one character that ben shank ben saint should obviously be and this is a throwback
waiting for the punchline remember this character yeah that's right well as i have explained now
multiple times that is a dark gray lab coat it is not white well i don't care just just one one
say no okay fine i will even even if you even if you were to do an accurate doctor and say no
outfit people would still not know who the fuck you are so it doesn't matter they can be well it's
okay yeah spoonie's got the got pretty nice teeth pretty pretty decent pretty decent set of teeth on
that guy he's a youthful boy that's true yeah where is he now is he dead he uh yeah he's dead
live streams on his channel uh every so often more frequently recently i'm still subscribed
i just never click on them because then they're very like low-key sort of streams nothing nothing
like his over-the-top ostentatious like persona in his videos it's very very quiet very like a comment
every so often it's like yeah it's not really for me no way antweiler is still uh his patreon is
still he's making silly videos 79 patrons 285 a month 285 they have that that's right it beats me
by a couple of a couple of bucks he's making bank true true you pay rent in arizona without money
yeah did i um oh my god his his his patreon blurb i'm i'm sure he just hasn't touched it in a while
and just hasn't thought about it but like it still references like projects he was doing in like 2012
the cinema snob movie press start to continue suburban nights and to boldly flee are all on here
that's fucking funny as hell you gotta put the you gotta put on the classics you know up there
the most recognizable works you know suburban nights internet classic did i say last time
that like i think that i'm like restructuring my patreon i think i did talk about that i mean
yeah yeah um i'm hoping i'm hoping i'm hoping i'm hoping i'm hoping i can see a bump in my patreon
from the new video and like i'm offering some new i'm offering some new stuff on there in the hopes
that it the sort of gets me back gets me back to like where i was like a year or two ago that would
be nice once i knew once i knew video drops i will offer fans i swear i'm offering value
once a new video drops and uh you you ask for merriweather for that retweet
i'm not gonna ask merriweather for the retweet they're gonna ask merriweather for the retweet
i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna mention i'm gonna thank him i'm gonna thank him for
encouraging me to make the video i'm not gonna ask him for the retweet and you're hoping that and
and you know what i i genuinely don't think it matters if you retweets or not it's like
it would be nice i don't i don't think i don't think a retweet from him would even like do anything
would get me like a couple thousand views who cares that's a couple thousand you didn't have
buck him you're like no ben i saw you talking shit about my my ugly bastard come
i wasn't though i'm very generous i was very generous i swear no i i swear i wasn't
no no i wasn't look i compared just because i compared it to dar man i meant that in the
most complimentary way possible um all right what are we talking about what are we doing
oh wait okay check check this out tell me what you think of this
it's a triple eel it's a triple eel wait what is it a mash up of
is this the eel it's the eel from the super mario and there's three of them there's um there's
like one of these to combine two enemies this is just three of one enemy kind kind of it's it's
mostly just cash catchy um there's there's a in super mario bros too there's like a tree
head snake so i'm like oh i should make like a tree headed something else oh yeah i remember that i
remember that snake of course this is a mash up of this snake i'm not gonna lie i would say like
maybe like one third of these ideas are just like this is just a mario enemy i wish existed
like i i think would be like interesting to have i'm trying to think of like looking at this guy
like how how useful really is he as a predator having three heads what if they get distracted by
different mice what if they what if they go in different directions and they all pull and then
like slam like that's how you stretch back and hit themselves in the head and they that's how you
heard of that's how you heard of it that's how the boss fight he's one of those bosses where you
have to make him hurt himself you have to spread gossip about one head shit talking the other
and they bite each other yeah some of these um some of these are just like kind of like i i just
think this would be an interesting idea for a mario enemy like this shy guy isn't really a mashup of
of any two characters is just like oh what if you just draw on the shy guy's face yeah like that
mm-hmm mm-hmm it's just it's just cute you know what if there was a shy guy but they had huge
tits though whoa whoa calm down there buddy i'm just i'm just slow down slow down whoa what is that
a fusion of um uh shy guy and the big booby that's not mario enemy uh you're you're thinking too
limited you're you're stopping short of greatness with that with that attitude okay um people have
been asking me and by people i mean one person one discord server asked me to when am i going to do
a bowser fusion and that's actually going to be the last one because i have a pretty i had a pretty
good idea for a bowser fusion uh barrio will you tell us or is it a secret bower yo it's a secret
um like they'll just say i i fuse bowser with um a very evil character ever a very uh like
very malicious character is what a character that a character that that has um that predates
the mario franchise but very evil uh bonky kong wait i know who it is i know who it is
who do you want to guess you have to guess is it the villain no oh never does is it satan
uh maybe maybe it's satan okay maybe maybe it's satan from from real life or from ghouls
and goblins satan for real life you know satan by neighbor
huh what do you mean ghouls and goblins what are you talking about goblins and ghosts what's that game
the little guy of the night super ghouls and ghosts goblins and goblins ghosts and goblins
ghosts and goblins yeah yeah ghosts and goblins that's satan it satan is uh the final boss in that
game yeah if you said there's there's bosses called the devil and then there's one called satan
or let's see the way around there's like uh there's a little red guy firebrand who's my um
who's my uh my kin a kin firebrand literally me
is that a pony is that a pony's name firebrand firebrand wait a minute wasn't that josh scorcher's
pony who the what who uh oh ben what are you talking about
shh gosh is josh scorcher you ever everybody knows josh scorcher the fiery joker
josh scorcher is that the josh scorcher is like the name of the of the alter ego of ghost writer
that's not a real person ghost writer also known as josh scorcher the fiery joker
josh scorcher the pony reviewer who was in the military technically yeah because he scorched
he scorched palestinian children uh wait i just remembered this was the last thing i saw before
i went to sleep last night michelle DM'd me to show me a new turkey tom video about bronies
and i didn't watch the whole thing but she highlighted for me a part where he plays
the first episode yes the first episode of analysis anarchy oh and my yeah phantom horn
is there wait uh check yeah check this shit out check this shit out um i'll post the link to the
video turkey tom yeah um and it's at eight minutes at eight minutes and 40 seconds she said yes
at eight minutes and 40 seconds phantom horns debut his first and last appearance and analysis
anarchy 43 minute video this feels like it's 10 years too late yeah i agree why don't you time
stamp it hey guys did you know that bronies are a bunch of losers and they probably are petafite
well i mean some of them oh i'm scrubbing through i'm seeing i'm seeing the phantom horn i'm seeing
the funny like uh tune critic discord or skype call remember that yeah you know i think it's a
lot of this is about that guy oh wait that there i am no wait you too is it in the analysis anarchy
just in an analysis anarchy like screenshot or whatever it's like give and take the the tf2 spy
facepalming yeah i i can't you know what i mean analysis anarchy is cringe it is terrible
yeah deserves to be made fun of so like what i can't even i can't i can't really complain
oh there's digi oh where oh god near the beginning like five minutes in um does he say anything
i'm not watching the video i'm just i'm just looking at the scrubbing through the the thing
seeing the little thumbnail that comes out i i don't think i would like i don't think i would
like this video i think turkey tom seems like kind of a bitch i know yeah i don't fuck the turkey
tom um so yeah it's just gonna be a lot of like tired things yeah i i think um i seen some turkey
tom but some of the recent ones have been like way better about like topics i don't believe it
i don't believe it but like his a bunch of like i've heard i keep hearing him say like
these bunch of little very stupid things all the time um he believes in the whole like twitter
being the public square so you shouldn't ban anyone off of it which is the most dumb ass take
ever heard it's funny how that's his take and he's a big destiny fan and that destiny is like
hate when people say that twitter's the public square and people shouldn't get banned off of
there turkey tom's a destiny fan oh yeah that destiny had been very popular with like reactionary
types recently yeah it makes makes sense um man what's what's the point i mean i'm okay this the
scandals of andrew tate uh roblox degenerates tarik nashid who who gives a shit man i i don't
care i don't like i don't like what i'm seeing um the disappearance of animated james how he makes
so many of these they must be terrible because he makes so many they must be awful yeah i mean
it's it's one of those things where he pumps out like an hour long video of week they can't possibly
be good i'm not i think there's something with like the subject matter being so negative like
exposing a terrible horrible thing and that's all the content creator does put a soyjack on a
roblox and then i'll talk about a bunch of how people oh really are people on roblox cringe
are there like pedophiles playing this children's game oh i can't tell me more educate me i mean
people tell me about the pedophiles there's there's there's another channel that i've seen that is
so like overtly like negative like this just sort of focusing on like the worst things ever
and that's all they make it's just like exposing this and exposing that and i'm like
sure you know exposing exposing things is like a good thing to do i guess but if it's your entire
brand and i just i'm just sort of put off hanging around there i don't like it
yeah this is a whole this is a whole type of channel
oh man they upload a podcast a week there's no they upload a three hour podcast every week
there's no way this is good there's just no way yeah that's right i wasn't being uh sarcastic
when i saw that was my my true opinion my true all right let's all right let's do voicemails
i've had enough i've had enough wait how many voicemails is it i don't know
let's go to speakpipe.com slash pcp voicemail and check out what we're looking at okay well in that
case i can't i can't stay for a while but i gotta go all right fair enough all right jeezy it's been
a pleasure bullying you uh it's it's it's it's fine it's fine but i i'm gonna prove you wrong
ben saying i'm gonna i'm gonna prove you wrong you're gonna come crawling he's gonna you're gonna
be coming to my knees coming to me oh come on your knees you'll come on my knees you'll be jerking
off i'm like you're saying oh please let me do a story in clown mode volume 24 heart please
i hope you're right um uh uh uh link in the description though um yeah link in the description
buy buy a copy of clown unironically people should buy a copy of clown milk yeah yeah they should
they should all right all right sweet all right later jeezy see yeah okay the first one is called
tldr how carbon offsetting works three two one go we should take the teeny bottom and push it somewhere
yep just push it i
next one is called winging about a oh my god
there's three emails and they're all over a minute long or voicemails
all right winging about a ir at part one three two one go
well it's already monday so i'm definitely missing the next episode recording uh which
has already happened by now but i just want to weigh in anyways on the whole a i art business
because the whole thing annoys me in general far too much to not open my big mouth so first of all
um it is not actually i think the main issue uh that a i art is plagiarism because that only invites
the counterargument like ben kind of uh intimated that um well artists also copy each other's styles
and if an ai is just doing it more efficiently then that is not really um plagiarism that is simply
well you know the artistic process as much as you can argue about whether or not that's true
like psychologically the real point is that it is wage theft and labor exploitation like a capitalist
factory owner who uses his laborers labor and the value that it generates in order to buy machines
that put them out of work the same shit happens to artists whose art is literally used to put them
out of work well yeah okay should i listen to part two yeah i i just think that like i agree with
this guy like it is wage theft i guess that's what i meant really when i meant plagiarism
like like the the problem with the plagiarism is that the artist will get less work because of a
machine the the problem is not trained to to come like to do their art can maybe make them lose work
and they didn't get the the permission to take that art and put it in the machine
yeah it's the the problem is not simply that it can well i'm not sure if this is even true but
if even if it were true that like the ai could just produce a better product than a human for less
money like that in and of itself would not be the problem uh the problem would be that it's doing it
yeah that it's doing it in a way that is uh it's basically stealing value from human artists
that created the the the work in the first place okay anyway part two three two one go
and then secondly uh as much as i agree with ben about the the idea that if something simply
becomes easier for people to do be it creative or otherwise productive that that's a good thing
in principle as much as i agree with that i do not think that ai quote unquote art is the actual
answer to that or is actually a good development because of that the reason being that ai art
eliminates like the most vital aspect of the artistic process and of what makes art valuable
in my eyes which is not in fact that it takes struggle or strife or pain uh and time to create it
but rather that it is created through an intentional process you know through both mental and physical
faculties that you know actually gives rise to a person's lived experience in a very tangible
and physical way that you can trace back to how they did it and appreciate that that's just
impossible with ai art it makes art into just product and it's shit it's garbage and i hate
sorry i agree again
um i remember the problem you had with like the show and tweet that it was like in your eyes um
uh glorifying hard labor for its own sake yeah and yeah i i think i think i think i was basically
saying the thing i said before that like the artistic process is valuable um in and of itself
the end product is like one thing but like making it is valuable for the person doing it and
in context of viewing it no wrong i don't agree at the end of the day product is all is all that's
left uh all all that is all that occurs as a result of the artistic process is a product
and anything else that you think about it when you look at it is just is just uh is just fan fiction
yeah but like like but like if it is fan fiction in the sense that like once the art is made
um you as the audience sort of create meaning from it however you interpret it yeah and i think
knowing that an art was made by a real person with purpose changes the context of how you
interpret it so it's valuable in that way it's at least at the very least variety because if
everything is made by computer you're like ah like you i think you would really just stop
feeling anything because you you can't relate to any person or any experience you just know
that a computer squished it together and maybe you like the look of it i think i see what you're
saying but i don't know imagine if you had like two identical paintings and one had been done
by an ai and one had been done by a human why why would why would the one done by the human
be better just because you know that a human did it i don't even think it's about better
i think it's just about variety i i think i i would rather live in a world where i can get
lots of different things from art rather than what ai essentially does which is like
like builds various like samey things or like weirdo things i like ai art that's like insane
that nobody would ever make because the computer doesn't know what is like expected of it i saw
i saw i saw a tweet this week that was like oh ai art doesn't understand doesn't understand
ramen did you see happen to see this tweet no well it was um it was four ai images and they
were things like the girl it was an anime girl eating ramen and in one like she was like eating
it with her hands like her she was grabbing noodles out of the bowl with her hands and in other ones
like her fingers like became the chopsticks that she was eating the noodles with and in other
ones like there were too many chopsticks like there were like four there was like a whole
like cluster of chopsticks in the hand that sort of became the noodles and then the fourth one
was a girl's like head in the noodle bowl and like her hair was the noodles and that was awesome
it looked so cool yeah it was great oh i i don't i don't ascribe like ai art equals bad stuff
it's it's merely the um i i i want like real art to continue to exist and in some ways this could
push artists away from you know being able to to live off their work and so less of it might exist
it's a lot of hypotheticals it just sort of it it it and creates a lot of like
like like this shitty future in my head okay but what's shitty about it
because it's all it would be all the same at some point well that just seems like a
that's sort of like a that's just a technical concern like what okay well what well what if
ai art were more advanced and it could create stuff that didn't all look the same which it
kind of it kind of already does i think um since ultimately i'm the one who decides how i feel
about something you would need to change my mind about how ai art appears to me for me to like
like be okay with a world exclusively of ai art that can completely like um like replace all human
art okay but who i who is the sort of thing who is saying that ai art should completely replace
human art no one but like that's the sort of thing that makes me dislike ai art on a like an
emotional visceral level i see things that are cool and then i see things that are like this is
not weird and wacky and ai aesthetic it's sort of like this looks like some human drew it like
a really good human artist even though their hands a bit fucked up but it's like i could see i've
seen paintings and drawings by people that look like this because they purposely made a thing
and now the ai art is so good at recreating human art that it doesn't have its own like flavor
anymore it's just sort of like doing human art instead of humans doing it and so i extrapolate
that idea further and it's like well what if all humans are pushed out of art somehow
i don't like that it just sort of they won't be i mean they won't be but why are you so sure they
won't be why why would they be i don't i don't get it i forget the point that we were arguing ai can
um i mean i mean look at what it's doing okay it can't like it can't but you you were the one
you said okay you're using you're using two you're using two separate arguments that are like
completely at cross purposes with each other on the one hand you're saying that ai art can't be
like human art because it lacks ideas and it's not original but on the other hand you're saying
but it would be bad it's bad ai bad because what if it replaces all human art but like
if one is true then the other can't be true i don't get it i don't know what you mean if ai
art does not replicate the kinds of creativity that human art is capable of then it's like
it will then then it will never replace human artists yeah but like i'm also saying that
the knowing that something is made by a computer changes how i feel about it
i mean i get that hypothetically if if all ai art um does replace human art like in
terms of quality or whatever you want a metric knowing that it's made by computer i will feel
bad there's it's just an emotional response when i hear that i think oh so you would be okay
with living in a future where all ai art where all art was generated by computers but they just
didn't tell you that that was true uh i guess hypothetically that could already be the case
so yeah right if i didn't know um it's like oh we're living in a simulation but nobody
you there's no proof you'll never find proof is like oh i guess i wouldn't feel any different
because i it could already be the case okay i mean yeah okay all right that's fair um i just i just
don't see it i just don't see my general point i don't i don't really see it replacing traditional
art sure yeah yeah i i don't i would want to live in a world where
uh there's not like this there's multiple like conclusion like like main points and i'm not really
like making anyone at the say at the at this like there's the there's the capitalism problem
people losing work that upsets me just generally i don't like the fact that some artists could
have their work wage stolen like their their labor taken without their consent put into a
machine and then the machine makes art that looks like their stuff that the machine operator or
whatever can profit from i or just or just like real lower the amount of profit that the artist
could make off of that same style that's one thing uh the other thing about like all i ai art
replacing human art is more of like a an existential sort of emotional response which is not really
related and then uh then the other thing is that i prefer i prefer ai art that looks like
a weird dream nightmare and i don't like ai art when it's just normal i prefer it when it's
fucked up because that's funny and cool yeah this girl's head in the ramen bowl you know i mean
i think a human could have drawn a human could have drawn something like this yeah you would just
never think to i mean they could but you know in this case you in this case an ai came up with it
and like you know good good for good for them good for the the ai i guess i like it um the labor
argument i mean yeah it's bad when people lose work but to me the like oh ai will cost artists
their jobs argument is an art is an argument against capitalism more than it's an argument
against ai in my opinion sure um as there are some people who wouldn't understand that but i
definitely understand it's an anti-capitalism position as as for it yeah as for it replacing
like as for ai art like becoming the norm it's i just don't i mean in i think it might
in certain applications where we like wouldn't notice the difference and if we don't notice the
difference then like i guess who cares i mean the line has been blurred in certain fields already
like textures in in like video game development yeah it used to be like photographs that you
would edit now like you can kind of just ai generate based on like a bunch of inputs google
images and then you can come up with things like that like simple things that you're not supposed
to look right at but they they're they're they're ways of like skipping ahead um in the process of
building something different or like uh you know you need a pose for a thing and you you want to
you get some inspiration you want to get some inspiration and you want the ai to generate some
like prototypes of a general like description instead of drawing them all yourself so the line
has been blurred already it's i don't know yeah yeah uh okay i think there's a there's a third part
so let's just let me just listen to the third part three two one go
okay i said i was gonna shut up but i thought of one more thing that might be important to say
before uh that has to be explained by other people so yes of course you can use ai uh
quote-unquote artists in a like not morally wrong full way like of course that's possible it's
possible with any technology but like that does involve like deeply changing both how it's how
like the ai works and is like made and how it is like employed so like of course like give kind
of mentions in this episode like you can use it for ideation you can use it for just like spitball
and ideas and then just making your own thing based on that uh you can just use it for that which is
fine and you can uh use it for like uh background purposes you know you can use it for at least
producing art when you really only mean to create a product i guess uh but then it's still a question
of first uh addressing the whole database issue and the issue of what data what art goes into it and
whether or not yeah i mean i agree with the and it's just morally dubious to try an art like the
art of consenting artists professional artists who's you know the intellectual property is being uh
robbed did you see there was like a different stable diffusion but from music but they they
they explicitly said we're not going to put copyrighted tracks in there because we don't
want the legal trouble which just goes to show that the music industry has ways of protecting
their artists but the art industry does not and so they feel totally fine with stealing art from
every artist who posts their stuff online but um they're scared legally of of what the music industry
could do to them so it's like very obviously a problem there yeah that that does speak to like
the fact that one is like more regulated than the other uh for sure hmm that's interesting
i forget the name it was like stable dance or something i didn't i did not see that but uh
should we should we have a i mean
okay but i mean i those are is that what are they gonna put like you know un unlicensed like sound
like random sound cloud musicians in there like who's probably whose music are they gonna put in
there that that's the thing it's like you know they're still they're still gonna steal the music
just not from anyone who can do anything about it that's like oh that's the track that fucking
i don't know who's a big studio atlantic records is the first thing comes to my head like oh they
take a fucking led zeppelin song put it in there and make something that sounds like led zeppelin
the lawyers involved will destroy the ai um company they'll be killed they'll be murdered
in their sleep can't do that hmm i mean i guess a similar thing would happen if like
an ai started producing images that like were provably derivative of like i don't know
dc comics image stuff i guess or if it like
made jokes in the style of saturday night live or something
we made an ai to steal jokes i saw a thread this is off topic but i saw a thread of um
it was from that twitter account called like weird medieval guys
yeah uh i saw a thread of like medieval jokes they sucked they were bad they had bad jokes back
then all of the jokes were like the punchline is like oh the priest had sex or like oh this woman
her husband had anal sex with her or like none of them none of them had like a punchline that was
like a subversion of expectations that was like set up in the joke all of their all of them had
a punchline that was like it was it was it was a merely a subversion of like social convention
like one of the jokes was literally like a guy said like oh i'm going down to the whorehouse and
the other one was like oh say hi to your mom for me and like that was literally the joke
that was a good one trap good good one you got him
they talked funny back then how could you how could you definitely like explain that joke like as a
quip it was so wordy how could you do how could you do that joke in real time yeah well i mean
these were um these were trans translations into modern english uh yeah fucking um i mean here's
the thread here's here's the here's the thread and there's a bunch of um jokes or length here
let me read a piece of this shitty stupid this this is a joke a young florentine was going down
to river arno with one of those nets in which they wash wool and metafrolics and boy who out of fun
asked him what birds he was going to catch with that net of his i am going to the brothel's outlet
replied the youth to spread my net there and catch your mother mind you search the place carefully
retorted the boy for you will be sure to find yours there also this is dog shit this
i like it it's something it's something about it the sort of the flowery over explain over a
descriptive i would say boy is a good phrase i like frolicson i would say that this thread
is proof that the technology of humor has improved in in in the time since then we understand how to
construct jokes better these days uh it's ultimately it's just sort of like hey loser what are you
gonna net yeah you maybe i'm gonna net your mom i'm gonna net your mom you're gonna find your own
mom at the brothel you dumb fuck no i'm gonna find your mom but i'm not gonna find my mom no
you're only gonna find your mom and not my mom if you're gonna find your mom you're gonna need
a bigger net bitch that's good see that's good that's an improvement um uh yeah if if the if the
retort was no your mom that sucks but if the retort was well if you're gonna find my mom you're
no you're gonna need a bit if you're gonna it's just a mother a cell phone yeah you're gonna need
a bigger net who are you gonna net with that net i'm gonna go down to the whorehouse and net your
mom oh well you're gonna need a bigger net that you high five them yeah no that's a joke um
i i just wanted to own i just wanted to roast these uh these medieval comedians
they just didn't understand what we understand today about jokesmanship um uh god uh where are we
the next one is an image yeah god help us it's it's here are my original characters
synthia cutlass and kin if you see someone draw similar characters that person is a copycat
kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill
i like this this is cool oh it's kin oh i get it the other half of pump kin pump
there should be in yeah i'll share kind of well they share a share okay i can join
by the why is synthia cut why is synthia cutlass have a gun i feel like that goes against her
yeah cringe yeah i just her whole identity her whole character identity down the drain
with that gun um luckily my characters are slightly different so it's fine yeah yeah that's
right so there's no so what's what's there's no no no overlap whatsoever mm-hmm uh the next one
is called hair cast three two one go welcome back to the losing my hair podcast i'm losing my hair
today we have special guest ben saint ben how's it i believe i already mentioned that i'm on
i'm around month two of my minoxidil routine and they say that it's a if it if it takes effect
at all it doesn't do it in about four months so two months from now we'll see if uh anything
has happened at all there or uh whatever that's that's my report thank you for asking uh next
one is an image oh boy
oh
ben saint i'm coming to kill you at your house
los angeles no in real life
um the the the the saturation on that first image is is a lot
hmm look at my goofy my goofy ass i've never seen that second that second munchie picture
before i don't know what that's from um i think it's probably from the same video
just a still that's been fucked yeah yeah probably it's got the hat
hmm this looks uh i look i look terrible here i hate i hate how i looked at rad con two
three three three this is the the ten paces and dry yes yes um next one is called gummies at
ben saint three two one go gummies it's so sour this is me this is how i sound every day
not patented by ben saint that's true
um what do you say he's saying he's very very sour
not patented by ben saint these gummies are very sour i see and he's absolutely absolutely
correct next one is called am sick three two one go is the paladin motive or aesthetic more of
killer or rowdy thing what i didn't understand the beginning of that
killer or rowdy aesthetic uh rowdy please
e the paladin motive or aesthetic i don't know i can't i can't parse it um next one is called
there's an image this one is an image oh it's you speaking oh god mark my words munchie before
this day is done i ben saint will capture a nazi i mean this is you as papyrus
pate pate pate true and what's the pun of like put papyrus and patreon
papatrion papatrion papatrion oh god uh hey i'm glad to see this guy making uh i'm glad to
see this dude back in the voicemails i've always like like this guy's drawings so that's cool this but i
don't like that you're making fun of me so stop it
well what's to make what's being made fun of here um i just don't like papyrus your beloved
character in undertale i just don't like the tone i don't like his tone it's like he thinks i'm
i'm not gonna capture a nazi but i will see next one is called ben saint more like three two one go
ben saint more like ben paint
it's mario paint
as a reference to mario paint cool cool uh next one is called is your stuff cool three two one go
you know it's a much better cancel culture just never use twitter and if you ever meet someone
who uses twitter cut them out of your life it's so much more fun cancelled culture than being on
twitter all the time i'll be a much more interesting person i came i i i actually was like seriously
considering like do i want to just delete my twitter account this week i really was thinking
like i kind of think that twitter just makes me a worse person and it makes everyone a worse person
and uh i i think i'd be better off without it true so i agree it is it is a dangerous drug
yeah it's not it's when it when it when you get on the wrong side of it and you use it
in the way that like just makes you mad all the time i mean yeah the the stand the standard
response of using twitter is just being mad all the time so that's great and then i mean
worst case scenario i saw someone made a tweet that was like uh twitter twitter is like when you
post a take on twitter it's like you're pulling a slot machine but you can only lose like the only
jackpot you can win is like everyone hates you uh so yeah next one's called wakame three two one go
what's your opinion on portal it's the best video game of all time in my opinion however i think
portal two sucks um this is like a conversation that's been had on the pcp before probably remember
portal two is fine there's some sort of discourse around like how portal two is oh was this the one
where we talked about like the original and how i said the original is better just by virtue of being
the original yeah something like that because it's yeah i still feel that way uh i like portal one
i think i i think i appreciate portal two just because it's more fun puzzles and i like puzzles
yeah i mean i think most of what's good about portal two is the same stuff that's good about
portal one uh like the the the new mechanics they added are are fine and and good and all
um but i don't really think they like improved that much on like the core formula of it
it's basically just more portal one so i wouldn't say that portal two sucks i don't think it sucks
it's fine nah um bands we clear reminder play delta room chapter two okay bands we clear reminder
catch up to one piece okay at this point they're not reminding you they're just sort of like
you don't even really think oh yeah i should do that you just see you see this again you're like
okay isn't uh isn't delta room chapter three out or am i crazy no not yet oh being worked on but
i don't know when it's coming out okay okay um
i will i will do both of these things at some point i promise you that much it will probably
not have anything to do with how often i'm reminded in the voicemails but i mean whatever
next one is called bayonetta three voice actors update three two one go
yeah i just you probably already know this but um with the bayonetta three voice actors
shit like it's sort of it sort of looks like she lied and shit and instead of being paid just four
thousand dollars flat it looks more like she wanted to be she was offered to be paid god damn it four
thousand dollars per session which looks to be about three to four to five different sessions
which comes out to a lot of money and that the actually the actual voice actors wanted uh around
six figures uh just for paying that and um so it so it looks like she was a little bit facetious
about that you probably already know this i just want to let you know um yeah and like in hindsight
thank you very much like you don't just get what jennifer hail is the actress for placing her in
spainetta you don't just sort of just come across jennifer hail money if you're not willing to pay
someone four thousand dollars flat so it looks like she actually is just being facetious not to
mention that uh i don't remember her name but facetious actresses like a total like huge turf
and like a like a thin blue lion type of deal um or something like that so yeah it seems like she was
sort of sort of lying about that trying to trying to use the fans saying to boycott the game even
though it was all bullshit anyway i'm gonna go jerk off to uh the last was part two uh sex scenes
so bye all right good boy smell um uh i did not hear about the like that she may have lied about
the number i did hear that she's a turf uh fuck it yeah i don't know i mean i just fuck it i mean
i'm not i'm she did ask the six figures you know what based um the everything after that is not based
yeah i mean uh people should be paid for their work that's good people should not be turf said
should not be thin blue line that's bad however those are two separate issues but uh yeah i don't
know i don't really care about bayonetta honestly uh so i don't give a shit about any of it
other than in general i think work should be compensated uh whatever fuck it not interested
next one is called the comic progress oh this is probably some more vinny stuff
ben saint ben saint in red yep true angrily posting on twitter it's angrily angrily angrily yeah
ew like you do you scalp yourself my scalp off did i oh did i say something about like um i might
have said something about like dead skin on my head i think i said something about it says here
ben saint's usual normal cycle on the pc was newly acquired bald head same normal amount of dandruff
expelling from ben saint gross gross why are you smiling at the last one you scalped yourself
and you're still on twitter that's disgusting bs the hedgehog and gib and take the goth sheep
these are these are pretty good pretty good yay uh these are is there a nice way to say that they
are like sonichu side characters and i mean like like parentheses complimentary i mean a
sonico seas are all kind of like that aren't they the son sonichu specifically like like sonichu
yeah like you know in sonichu there will be well no like actually no it gets insonic also there
are just like random like animals that don't look like the animal they're supposed to be
yeah yeah no that's actually sort of the whole thing about sonics so never mind yeah
um i like my pose i like my green yeah you got a good pose that's a good like good pose
taking a shit but like not actually i'm wearing one of the shirts that i can fit into again now
that i'm not fat anymore so that's pretty neat ah ow oh head oh headache ow oh that dandruff
oh gotta scratch scratch scrape my head again i'm gonna take one ibu one ibuprofen please
om nom nom nom ah delicious um next one is called uh was page three of the comic huff did we see
this last time i don't think so i don't remember page one and two maybe if i went back i think it
was when i arrived yeah because this is like i've got my guitars when i arrived in the airport
who am i battling here some bully i think is a police guy the oh he's got a gun he's got a gun
did you melt that cop yep our ride is waiting let's go jesus christ man the skeleton
um what a bizarre welcome to welcome to america no oh god big johnny he's dead
oh my god a piggy pulled carriage yep error rari gave me a great deal
recall error rari's voicemails you know i remember there being a pig but i don't know
what is driving that wagon i think it's one of error rari's um twitter abominations
you know the art because she draws the like fucking insect monster people
oh is that what it is uh that's my best guess ladies first what was that besties first lol
thanks auto autotuned lol page five the rest of it will have to be done at work i've got way too
much overtime i need to pay bills so i can't prioritize it at home ambitious yeah wait a
minute on page four we're coming out of the main terminal but it's spelled like main the state
i don't know if that's intentional or not that's probably intentional it's pretty hard to misspell
main yeah i would think so um hell yeah i remember yeah error rari's voicemails they had
some of like weird characters with weird voices and the little bug thing is saying an autotuned
lol because of the weird voice oh yeah i genuinely can't remember the storyline
i was beware the bear was that how it started yeah i and then it evolved into like
some incomprehensible saga carriage i think there were piggies involved yeah probably i remember
all the details it's hard to remember all the details though uh okay well good good stuff good
stuff uh next voicemail is ben gibb name your favorite clown have cheesy judge you i couldn't
name any clowns for you it's when it comes to clowns i really know like i know of some there
was a very there was a pretty there was kind of a there was kind of a hot uh uh only fans clown girl
on twitter called bouncy clown so i guess i like her i feel like that big boobs i feel like that's
like but she's not a real clown she didn't go to clown code she's just she's just she's just pretending
to be a clown she just put on the makeup she's she's just wearing clown face she's just wearing
clown face and it's offensive like when i think of clowns in media i'm thinking of like characters
from stuff rather than like personas online and i'm remembering like that weird clown in the dream
in the brave little toaster movie but he's creepy and he's ugly and i don't like him so i don't know
if i have a favorite clown the best clown is oh wait gamsy but he's a juggalo there's not really
a clown i feel like juggalo's i feel like it counts quackered quacker jack from dark wing duck
obviously quacker jack from dark wing duck is the best i guess he's more of a jester are jester's
clowns does the joker count as a clown i feel like yeah i feel like yeah the joker is a clown
joker is pretty good um what other what other clowns what other clowns um
there's the clown from steven king's it which i haven't seen oh you oh you mean it
oh you mean the titular it yes it no his name is penny wise penis wise yeah um
that's it that's all i got quacker jack wait um uh z from cycloneals she's pretty good
clown oh yeah there's a lot in cyclone there's a lot of good clown designs in cycloneals
this is my favorite clown in cycloneals i like the one lady it would probably be z honestly
i like z's clown face yeah it's pretty pretty edgy pretty cool but there are a lot of like
background clowns i like dance that's that's all right that's a good one yeah i could probably go
through and pick out some good ones if i wanted to but i don't uh cycloneals is pretty high-grade
clown media i i feel like i feel like cycloneals deserve more attention than it got i feel like
it got like no fanfare at all and i feel like it deserved at least a little bit yeah it was it
was not bad it was i think just people assumed bad things for some reason yeah the the the the
disc the homestuck discourse has turned decidedly negative these days maybe that's just in the circles
that i'm in like i know i follow the i follow the homestuck hashtag on twitter like you know when
it says like um when they do like uh here's a topic you might be interested in you can click x
so just like okay we won't do it anymore i always click on a homestuck one because i want the
algorithm to show me pictures of homestuck as often as possible so i see fan art a lot
and fan trolls and stuff sometimes is brisker and that's great you know what i did that i did that
for mega man actually yeah i i got recommended a mega man tweet and i clicked like yes continue
to show me mega man stuff and i've been seeing mega man stuff so i mean i guess the system works
um yeah uh all the like youtubers that i'm aware of have nothing nice to say about homestuck and
like you know good for them i guess i don't know it's my favorite yeah i'll just keep saying that
because it's true it didn't change it's still the same comic i would i would i would i guess i would
consider myself kind of a homestuck defender even though i am like very much willing to admit that
like actually most of homestuck is bad objectively it's funny because like that was always the line
it was just sort of like you know homestuck's trash right and the homestuck fans like yeah
and they continue to enjoy it that was always like the the funny like thing you would say yeah
like i love my trash comic um well now i mean now that it's done we can look back and be like
yes in hindsight most of it sucks
sad but true um but it's still what's good what's good there is really good and worth
deserves respect um next one is an image let's let's look at it shall we
what is what is going on it's the pcp and there's mage in the middle
and mage is a huge brain and we are all huge brain we're all fucking around
and we're all dumb except for mage i guess that's me with the sonichu medallion
and the twitter and the patreon in your head oh it's all of us as um you know like the like no brain
soy no brain yeah yeah
i like that i'm the the one with the long neck you know that one and i gotta like i've got a
punk ducky oh oh yes the the long neck and the like gross like adam's apple
yeah yeah okay i you can't really tell because like your ducky is like covering up
the neck but yeah i see it i thought the neck was going around maybe it's my arm
yeah it reads as an arm holding it to me i guess i'll post this here in chat i wonder if this guy
knows that that mage drew uh like i asked mage to draw a riska a not a riska a a punk ducky image
he did yeah we never made it into a pillow though for some reason it was something i think something
would like i was there was a time when like this company was saying oh do a small video and we'll
give you a free uh thing ducky macro i'm like hey free shit and that's cool i never had a ducky macro
before so i got a couple from that and i wanted to do another one i wanted to do a custom one with
punk but then that they didn't respond to that one even though they did the same thing like i will do
a video and uh and you can have the the thing they just never sent the the part of the punk one
so mage drew that and i still have it but never turned into a pillow
hmm is is that digi as the bong why why does it have blue hair
does she have blue hair no well let's see there's not like that kind of blue ever
there's cult corona there's tom there's nate there's devu on her head i i nate nate torso
head is great it's actually like very very good i think that's probably the best one although i
i like munchies face munchies like screaming oh that's munchie yeah i think so
so silly these are good these are these are good i've never seen the the soy jacks that some of
these are based on but like it seems like they mostly are well i don't know i like it it's good
and i appreciate it let's move on to the next uh voicemail there's another image yeah hey hey
apple bloom going to the city that's fine just remember what granny said about them crime rates
never relax sis i get it racism racism racism big city racism
apple bloom remember we in the apple family are alpha males we're scared of big cities
won't even drive through them anymore crime rates are too high and so are taxes uh
next one last one is called we was poke tubers three two one go
hello ptp i was wondering do you think that pokemon scarlet and bile are gonna be good
no you think they're gonna be bad yes i was just thinking about how with the regional forms of
pokemon they never made one into a bug a type you know and i guess that kind of makes sense because
you can't like change the biology of something above why not but yeah why but now they're not
doing regional forms anymore they're they're doing two things one is they're doing like
if you if you saw wiggler no wiggle it wiggle it it's not diglett it just looks like daily but
it's an eel because you can't evolve into an eel from a mole and now they're gonna do that with
tentacle i to mark my fucking words they're gonna make tentacle into a bug type and it's not gonna
be tentacle it's gonna be some other shit um that's all i had to say i can't oh wait the other
the other thing they're doing is um future paradox and past paradox pokemon i'm gonna have i don't
know make of that way well um check out the pcp minecraft server that's all i wonder if i can
say it's got we got so much it it's really cool um come on down anyway have a nice day thank you i
love you and why that is true there's a lot of cool shit on the minecraft sir i know i have i have
not been uh we we we would we've been saying we should do another stream soon yeah and we will
i just uh finished my super video um what is it what is it about tentacle they're gonna
release he thinks he thinks they're gonna turn tentacle into a bug because of wiggler because
why did i i didn't make him think that because wiggler is not an evolution of diglett it's just
a completely different pokemon i guess i mean i mean the regional variants have always been
that like role picks ice version you can't evolve into a nine tails fire version yeah like it's
yeah yeah yeah like it's um a regional variant basically is its own pokemon
in all ways that matter i guess i would like a new i would like a bug tentacle
tentacle and tentacle are really cool designs or at least tentacle is i don't i don't really
understand what the like evidence for that claim is but i'll assume that it makes sense uh
oh did you see uh they're they're doing um first of all the game will not be good they
don't make good pokemon games anymore they're they're against sure that goes without saying yeah um
they're doing a they're no you're your your player no longer has a gender you don't like
pick boy or girl you just have your avatar and you can dress them boy way or girl way or whatever
yes i like that it's cool i think that's good i think i mean honestly even even in a even a even
in a non woke way right i just think that makes sense because like you have something the same
fucking model no matter what the like the base the base model of your character doesn't look any different
like you could just take the same uh a 3d model character and just give it different eyes different
hair just makes sense it's just it's just more it's more a sensible design why why do you have to
pick one it's it's more you could literally just change its hairstyle and like the difference
it's it's like same difference i think i'm i haven't played a pokemon game in a long time but i'm
pretty sure when you like in x and y or any other 3d ones uh the model between male and female is
more than just hair and stuff like is there like there are like different leg shapes and
noticeable breasts on the female ones because they're not like children unless they are are you
are you but are you talking about like the player character when you when you choose one or the other
that like the female one looks more feminine on a structural way in the 3d one too but yeah i think
so okay that might be true that might be true but i'm remembering like x and y doesn't need to be
the case at all no it doesn't yeah it it i mean it'd be cool if you could like you could like
change body parts as well but like that's a little too involved for a child's game i feel like you
could put um you would i don't think you'd need to change the the body i think you could just pick
different outfits and different outfits could just have different shapes that could sort of imply a
body shape underneath and like that would be basically the same so yeah to to to me yeah to
me it's just like it's just like cleaner design to just have a base character who is not you don't
have to like lock yourself into one of two sets you just have a base thing and you can just make
it you can just uh have it wear whatever you you want just makes more sense um
uh but the game will still be bad in spite of that so it doesn't matter
yeah um yeah i think that was the last voicemail well thank god all right
i got a little frustrated i got a little frustrated today i was a little bit mean to our
guest uh and you know what but he deserved it so it's fine um uh i'm i'm i'm uh i'm in a dark
place but it's okay uh uh once the video is done probably i'll feel better i'm in that i'm in that
stage of like i'm in that stage of like it's basically done and now if it's just like feel like
like a never-ending series of minutia to to to do before i can finally wash my hands of it
and it's very frustrating uh so maybe next week i'll be in a better mood uh
uh but hopefully not hopefully not hopefully hopefully yeah hopefully you'd be a good old
cantank respensing everyone likes to see me suffer i know that's what they come here for every day
um i don't know what else uh what else do we have to say i just want to reiterate i'm doing
commissions if you're interested in me drawing anything i'll draw fucking anything until i
until i say oh that's a bit i don't want to do that but i'll draw anything not safe work
safe work black and white commissions 30 bucks 30 bucks starting price
if it's like two characters is it 60 no two characters an additional character is just a
10 buck extra so be 40 bucks if there's two characters well so you gotta play you gotta do
the i can't afford not i can't afford not to add a character uh oh yes yes finally the end of the
episode it's i'm free uh i'm gonna get back i'm gonna get back to her i i i as i was saying
before the episode started i wasted yesterday yesterday i was supposed to finish and i didn't
so today is the day actually and i actually mean it this time i'm really gonna do it i'm really
gonna do it so i'm gonna get you to do that as soon as this episode's done uh i have nothing else to
say all right patreon.com slash the procrastinators for bonus episodes yes billions of bonus episodes
yes we should do another one at some point i don't know what kind of topic we would do
but uh maybe we should think of something uh yes we should okay uh bye good uh speak pipe
dot com slash the procrastinators and um no it's slash pcp voicemail pcp voicemail links
descriptions okay that's the end the end goodbye good night goodbye