Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Radcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
Hello, welcome to the show. We're here to let you know.
Time is running out, there's something running out. Remember that song from that movie?
No, couldn't possibly in any way.
It's the pony movie.
What? There was a song?
It's the pony, it was the two, yeah, the one with the rock band.
With the sirens.
The only thing I can remember is that one Aladdin scene because it was so out of place with the cat.
What? No, no, no, not that pony movie. I'm talking about the Equestria Girls. Equestria Girls, two rainbow rocks.
Oh, yeah, that's sad. Why do you remember any of that?
No, you're wrong. That's the only Equestria Girl that's kind of good. That one's kind of okay sometimes.
The other ones are terrible.
It was mediocre. It was like, this is not enough classic rock for me.
They got guitars, but where's the solos at? Where's the Jimmy Page shit?
That one has its moments. That one has its moments.
Moments of pure devastation on the part of the viewer.
Yeah, I mean when you're right, you're right.
So how's your week been, Gib? What's been going on over there across the pond?
It's been fine.
Oh, wait, well, there's a news thing.
I don't really want to, I mean, it's like a thing happened.
Oh my God.
It's just that I have an opinion on it, but it's kind of a stupid like making it about me opinion.
But there was this lady who got murdered by a policeman or something.
Or like the police didn't help or it was like it was really tragic or something.
I didn't look into it too much, but I did see that there was like a memorial service.
The vigil.
And the police came to that and they pushed everyone around and said,
get the fuck out of here, you're not allowed.
And it's like, I guess they're not allowed. It's true, but it didn't look good.
Super bad.
And there was a lot of stuff on BBC.
And I was just like checking BBC every so often just because whatever.
I don't get British news from American pundits.
So I just have to check myself.
And there was a lot of women talking about how they are mistreated and they're not listened to
and that men are evil and well, not evil.
They didn't say that.
Yeah.
And there was all that stuff going on.
And the only thing I could think of, I mean, obviously there's always like a problem with misogyny and stuff.
But the only thing I can think of is that that could so easily turn into hardcore turf bigotry.
And I was just thinking about...
Everyone in England is a turf, Gib.
I know.
All of your people are like that.
I'm like, true.
Women, they don't feel safe to walk the streets at night.
There's some parts of London that are very dangerous and it's not good.
But at the same time, I could so easily see like if I spoke out or if I was involved in any way that I would be potentially sort of attacked or like...
You wouldn't be taken seriously.
I would be...
Yeah.
Like, I don't know.
I mean, there was nothing in the news that indicated that like trans issues was any part of the discussion.
But I'm just wary of it now because I'm just...
It's so obvious in other parts how transphobic the UK is.
Ah, just pissed me off.
It didn't piss me off.
It just made me a little, ah, jeez.
Ah, jeez.
Ah, jeez, Rick.
Well, ah, jeez, Rick.
You're saying we got to take a whole 23-minute episode, go to the Wizarding World of Harry Potter and kill JK Rowling.
Ah, jeez.
God, they should do that.
They might do that.
They might...
They were making a fucking...
They made a Gamergate reference in the last season.
It was really like late on that issue.
I could see them saying turf.
I could see Rick saying turf.
Like, you know what Morty, it's cool to be hating turfs.
I know how influential I am because of Pickle Rick Morty.
I'm going to teach the kids how to kill the turfs.
Ah, fuck.
Guaranteed plotline.
Can't wait.
It just rolls...
I mean, it's just such a natural...
It's just a natural thing.
Rick is just so interested in social justice and in making people's lives better.
He won't let any injustice stand.
And he's probably just...
I think he would probably just wipe Great Britain off the map.
I think it would probably be the simplest solution.
And then everyone would be happy.
No losers.
Okay, okay.
That brings me a little bit to...
Some people in my Discord were talking a little about the Kiwi Farms thread.
About the Trixie thread on Kiwi Farms.
And I read some of it.
And I...
There were a couple funny things about it that were worth noting.
But there was one post in particular that made me lull so hard.
Let me... hold on.
I think I...
Okay, I have a screenshot.
So, like, the context is that all the Kiwi Farms people, a lot of them are like,
Oh, fuck Trixie.
Fuck the PCP.
But Nate, though.
Oh, but that Nate guy, though, he's kind of like a trad chat.
And I'm like, I have daddy issues and I will latch on to anyone as a role model.
So, like, hmm, maybe this Nate guy's all right.
I don't know.
I don't want to, like, put that on Nate.
It's not Nate's fault that these people are idiots.
But this...
I'm going to read this out loud because this is so fucking funny.
On a side note, I hope Kantent dies soon.
Let Nate go.
He's a meme lord, but will never ever trune out or even joke about doing so.
He thinks buff males are peak aesthetic for men and likes women with fat tits unironically.
Guy is straight as a board.
Wait.
What does trune out mean?
He's straight.
Okay.
That's kind of a slur at all.
Oh.
Okay.
Nominally.
In theory, in theory, a trune is a fake trans person who's just doing it for attention.
But in practice, every trans person is a trune to these pig fuckers.
Right.
Okay.
So, I just love the like...
What sort of person is like...
Nate will never go trans.
He's straight.
He's fucking straight.
What a strange thing to say.
I know.
This is my favorite.
This is like copy pasta worthy.
Dude, unironically likes fat tits.
Bruh.
He's just like me.
You know, that argument doesn't even make sense.
Because if he were trans, he could still like men and women with fat tits unironically.
That could still be true.
Yeah.
But like this person doesn't fucking understand anything.
Such a strange reason for content to die is that Nate is not trans.
I can't believe how straight he is.
Trixie is too much of a bad influence.
Too much of a degenerate influence on Nate.
Like the two of them are like oil and water.
Like they must naturally repel from one another.
For them to have a show together is like a violation of the natural hierarchy.
Oh, is that why they're saying it?
I don't know.
I mean, I think this person just has distaste at seeing the two of them together.
I see.
Because they respect one and hate the other.
I think that's the point.
That's more what I would have expected from...
At first I was thinking, why the fuck is Nate here?
Get the fuck rid of Nate.
He's not trans enough.
He's too straight.
I hate looking at Nate.
No.
That doesn't make any sense.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not it.
Yeah.
I like the part when he says he will never trun out or even joke about doing so.
Is this guy...
And I just wonder what this guy is gonna...
What is the cop gonna be when the OVA comes out?
Lol.
Oh, no.
He would never even joke.
He would never even joke about being a girl.
That's just how straight he is.
And unironically, this is like pre-transition Chris Chan being like, I'm straight.
I have a subscription to Playboy.
That's the feeling here.
But it's not even about himself.
It's about someone else.
I love this.
This is the new meme.
Insane.
Guy is straight.
He thinks buff males are peak aesthetic for men and likes women with fat tits unironically.
Guy is a straight...
Guy is a straight as a board.
Okay.
That's a jewel.
That's a jewel I had to...
I just had to share it.
Well, that's over.
What next?
Oh, Bitcoin.
Oh, no.
Bitcoin.
It's going to the moon.
I guess it's a good thing, but it's like the continuing arc of like, oh, did you know
coin went up or down?
Well, it went up.
It went up.
It went up past the previous peak.
That's the news.
Yep.
It's up.
It is at...
It is just over 60K.
It went up to almost 62K.
It's down a little bit, but like it's still up overall.
I am waiting for it to hit 64K.
If it hits 64K, I will have recouped everything that I lost from GameStop.
So that would be...
That would be very nice.
That's what I'm hoping it happens.
Also, I'm still waiting for...
I was kind of expecting it to jump when people started getting stimmy checks.
I haven't really seen that happening.
I know some people are saying they're getting their stimmy, but it's not...
I don't know if like most people have gotten it yet.
So I'm still waiting to see if there's a jump.
No, about like the...
I mean, obviously, I don't know nothing.
I don't even know why I started speaking, but like there's a lot of big...
There's a lot of big investments from big business people being like,
oh, Bitcoin is good and they're pumping money into it.
So I think that's what's causing this spike rather than like individuals getting into it.
There's a whole lot of like, oh, we've got to make sure it doesn't crash.
Keep fucking putting money in it or something.
Maybe you're right.
I mean, I'm looking at it and like early on the 13th, there was like one...
Like couple of minutes there where it just like shot up like crazy.
And like, yeah, that has to be some like big company being like,
time to dump all our assets into Bitcoin.
Got a dumb pass on this Bitcoin.
A dumb pass on Bitcoin.
We've waited far too long.
The investors are clamoring for those Bitcoin gains.
Well, they'll get them in the short term anyway.
I do think it's going to crash again.
I just don't know when.
Yeah, whatever.
But great segue, great segue to Psycholonials,
which also has Bitcoin shenanigans involved.
Oh, it does.
Yeah, it does.
So you're caught up to Chapter 5 now?
Yeah.
I've caught up to the current Chapter 5 of Psycholonials.
I would say it's great.
It's like...
I love it.
I love Psycholonials.
It's like the sort of hype that you get from a homestuck with a few flash.
Well, I guess there wouldn't be flash.
It's just like movies, cutscenes, if you will, of stuff happening with music.
And the writing is cool.
The characters are really good.
And it's...
Yeah.
They are.
They're actually good.
How's he actually wrote a thing that's good?
Yeah, yeah.
In fact, put this audio before we talk about spoilers.
Go play Psycholonials.
It's very, very good.
It's a visual novel.
Hussie written.
Extremely good character development.
Would you believe it?
Everyone was so skeptical.
Everyone said, ah, Hussie, he's a washed up old dish rag.
He's never...
He fucked up with Hive Swap and now he's fucking dead.
Nah.
I was very optimistic.
I was like, oh, this is him.
This is him untethered from any weird corporate shit or monetary expectations of like, oh,
I have to write this thing for Hive Swap.
Oh, I have to deliver on these Kickstarter expectations.
He's like, no, that's a separate thing.
This is just a thing he felt like making and he made.
And that's what I'm interested in seeing.
And it's good.
Zee is really cool.
She's a literal cop killer and they call her that and she wears purple.
So it's pretty good.
Very like super Bencore.
She is super Bencore.
I think, do we want to...
Do we care about spoilers or...
We can talk about spoilers in a little bit.
I just want to say that the whole Hussie washed up thing.
I don't ever think it's been because of his writing.
Because like, the epilogue was extremely terrible, but like it was written.
I didn't read it.
So I don't know.
I didn't read the candy side.
There was the meat and the candy meat.
I read purely so that I could see the finality of what happened with the Lord English battle
and what happened to John Egbert for real.
Canon.
Now I know.
John's dead.
He's dead.
And Roxy is trans and various other things that are interesting and good.
But like it's tied to Homestuck and the whole, you know, Homestuck has a lot of baggage with it.
So like, you can't make an epilogue to Homestuck work exactly.
Like you can't make it like satisfy everyone.
So he just made it kind of as unsatisfying and ridiculous and stupid as possible.
And it was kind of funny in that sense.
But also I didn't, yeah, it was whatever.
Then there was Homestuck too, which is like not really written by him.
And so that's not really a, it's like plot points and various some things are written by him, but not all of it is.
So the only thing I've really seen of his post Homestuck writing wise is his authors notes on the latest like Homestuck books.
The physical print versions.
I've enjoyed those.
Do you own those?
I own Act, let me check.
I've got my shelf here.
Yes, I have books four, five and six.
Book five is Act five, Act two, part one.
Book six is Act five, Act two, part two.
And I don't think it gets to Cascade.
I think that would be the next one.
All I wanted was like Act five and Cascade.
And Cascade is like still not, it's so much pages, but the author notes are really good.
Very insightful, very good analysis stuff.
And since it's written like more modern times than his previous book commentary was,
I get to understand a little bit of what he's going through right at the moment as he's, you know, like after Homestuck is finished and seeing the author notes and like that that's pretty cool.
So I was never under the impression that Hussier has like got bad or shit.
It's just that he didn't like Homestuck.
You didn't want to work on it anymore, but it was sort of like yeah.
And that's why I was like, oh, this is this thing is not Homestuck.
Like, yeah, Homestuck had so much baggage.
I was like, oh my God, and non Homestuck property.
Like finally, like I've sort of, I've wanted Hussie to stop making Homestuck for a while now and just do something else.
Did you, did you play Hiveswap?
I guess there's two Hiveswaps.
I don't know.
Oh yeah, the second one is out.
Is it?
I think it is.
Yeah, I played the first one.
It was all right.
Here it was all right.
Yeah, it was all right.
It was just a point and click like puzzles run that interesting and it was quite short.
I'm just not that interested in like exploring the like troll culture, which seems like a lot of what Hiveswap is about.
I don't know if that's accurate.
That's just my impression.
The first part is like half in Joey in the mansion, like the human world.
And it's a mansion that is tied to Jake English grandpa or Jade Harley or something.
It's like tied to those characters in some way.
And then the troll stuff is like after her Imperius condescension left troll land.
No, this is before.
This is, I can't think of what the, I think it slots into Homestuck somewhere.
It's like before a lot of stuff happened, but it's got a different Empress and it's a different Empress and a bunch of trolls.
And there they are.
I don't know.
They never gave a shit about any of them.
They had that fucking fucking talking game where you talk to a bunch of troll OCs and you learn about them and I never had any interest in that.
Nice.
I should probably play it.
I mean, they're short, right?
Everyone says they're short.
Hiveswap?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
It's like not a shit game.
So, okay.
The branding on Psycholonials or like the blurbs about Psycholonials that I could read before I started playing it.
They emphasize that it was like about some kids trying to like start like a media brand.
Yeah.
I feel like it didn't talk about like spoilers, by the way, all like the murder and the cop murder.
I mean, that was a surprise.
I wasn't really expecting it to go away.
No, I wasn't expecting that.
At the end of chapter one, I'm like, oh, it's that kind of story.
All right.
Yeah.
It's like it starts off because the first Homestuck was like ostensibly.
Obstensibly, it was a thing.
It was about like four kids and, you know, Homestuck, like they're stuck at home.
Like they are not old enough to leave home.
They are not old enough to venture on their own.
And it is a coming of age story in a way.
You're saying that that's what you thought it was?
Well, there's lots of like theming of like, I'm trying to like wrap Homestuck up in like one description.
It's kind of difficult.
But like, it's about four kids who are kind of young.
They're like 13 stuff.
And the adventure they go on is in part about growing up and also about the way the internet works.
And the model of, you know, how the comic is portrayed online with GIFs, with Flash, with, you know, HTML is like, and all of the mannerisms of like the trolls are like, it's like a web comic about the web.
On the web.
And it's a comic.
It's like a new thing.
It's like an interesting idea that hadn't really been done before.
And so this, I feel like Psycholonials is like Hussie finding is another interesting way, like the internet has changed.
And this, you know, the way culture has changed.
Homestuck doesn't really make sense anymore.
It also is broken in a lot of ways.
And you can't exactly experience it the same way.
And like Psycholonials is clearly his, like he's interested in the way that it's changed.
And he's telling a story with that as part of, part of something.
You know, it's not finished yet.
And I haven't seen it a little bit.
But like, I get the feeling that that's the reason he was interested in this idea is that it takes place in the real world.
COVID-19, 2020.
And people are, you know, they're not just human beings.
They also have brands and everyone's trying to make their brand good.
And these two girls are influencers.
But also this shudder guy.
Hmm. Yeah.
I mean, do you think Hussie just like wants at all times to be writing a story about what the internet is like?
No, I mean.
This is just like the newest iteration of that.
No, I think it's just that like maybe to move on from Homestuck, which was that is like deliberately showing that like Homestuck is not that Homestuck is old or whatever.
But like the internet in the way that it's portrayed in Homestuck is very outdated.
And people are different in the way they interact with each other is different social media and all that.
They just found that interesting.
And also he just wanted to write another clown story because he's been like clowns is like the every single comic has clowns in them.
Every single one, every single thing he's done has clowns except for maybe that.
Yeah, the wrapping.
Homestuck was like the least clown thing he ever made.
Well, I guess close.
It's close.
Problem Sleuth has clown like a clown race in it, but they're not that forefront.
They're sort of just a funny little extra thing.
They're just kind of there.
I mean, I mean, Homestuck has like all like the gamsy stuff is like pretty is juggler stuff.
But I mean, he's like one character out of like, you know, 400 or whatever.
Yeah, this is like the clowns clowns are back their front and center back with a vengeance.
His his like his like Instagram posts of like himself in like the E boy clown makeup.
Yeah, it was the E boy cast that in like a funny new new life.
He had those the E boy like looking funky fresh out in the world taking pictures doing silly poses in front of stuff and horses.
And like the the sunglasses with sports on them that Z wears he has those and has taken a picture of those.
I recognize that was like a long now.
Yeah.
Yeah, that was another thing I was going to say is like it's very clearly a reflection of his.
You know, experiences being extremely influential creator that has been canceled a few times and it's like a little bit of that mixed in.
To the story a little, I mean, a little bit, a little bit someone.
Munchie told me that he he hadn't read it yet, but he I asked him if he was gonna and he said that he heard somewhere that someone had like told him that like the story was cringe because it was all about cancel culture and how and how bad cancel culture is.
And I'm like, I don't know who told you that but like that's totally wrong.
No, I guess there's a little bit of that in there.
Yeah, it's it's like it's using counts, counts, council, cancel culture, so culture.
It's using cancel culture, culture, culture as as like a like a plot point.
You know, it's just a new way that somebody something from your past can come back to haunt you is another is it's a cancel culture is just a modern way of saying that sort of thing happened.
Like you did something fucked up and people remember it and that will haunt you forever.
I mean, the fact that it's like can cancel you is like the fact that she doesn't really get canceled at all.
Maybe she will in the future, but like that it's it's more of a storytelling device just like a contemporary way of telling a thing happened.
She she got canceled in the past, but we don't like they allude to something that happened before that made everyone hate her.
Yeah, but like they we never find out what that was.
Yeah, it's just like it might not even be important.
It's like saying, you know, it's like, oh, this story sucks because it's about a backstory.
And that's all it's about.
It's like, well, I mean, backstories exist in all sorts of things.
This one just happens to be cancel culture related.
I don't really I don't really think it is cancel culture really.
I don't know.
Well, the whole like the whole everyone hates her now is like it's so vague about like what it's meaning that like I wouldn't call it.
I wouldn't call it.
I wouldn't really call it anything.
Well, yeah.
Who fucking knows what it is.
Not a cancel culture.
It's just the words they use.
That's what I was getting at.
It's like this is a normal thing that happens in a lot of stories.
It's just got the words cancel in it and it's like, oh, that's a modern thing.
I guess.
Yeah, I guess so.
She I don't know.
I don't know where the story is going.
I mean, I can see the where it's at now how like the brand combined like the brand people liked it.
And then the news broke of the cop murder and that was like completely on brand for it and it only like propelled the brand to greater heights.
And then it turned into like this kind of tertiary social movement that sort of piggybacked off the George Floyd stuff.
And now there's like a militia on Nantucket.
Yeah.
That all makes sense to me.
That all seems like a pretty natural progression.
I have no clue.
Well, like what this is like what the end is going to be.
I I mean, I asked, you know, like the clown God, the Jubilee God.
Is he real?
Is it real entity or is he just hallucination?
Yeah, like, you know, Hussey has had things that seemed real and then didn't be real in like problem sleuth started off as like, oh, it's a like a video game private detective thing.
And then it spiraled out of control and something completely insane.
Homestuck similarly, people will be wondering if this is the same sort of thing.
Is it actually like supernatural or is this just like a psychological manifestation?
And I don't know.
It could be.
It could go either way, which is why I'm interested in finding out.
I guess go play psychological on steam.
I was I was going to say time.
Let's timestamp this moment right now because it's after spoiler, but no, it's not done because I want to spoil a little bit more.
I'm really wondering about like, will will Z will Z be like redeemed?
Like, will she like, will she come out on top of this or not?
Because it seems like she's kind of evil, but also like all the things she says are like good and like Hussey agree.
I agree with them and Hussey agrees with them.
Yeah, like she's kind of like a folk hero, even at the same time that she's like a complete sociopath.
Yeah.
And like getting into some people killed.
She's a psycho and and but she's also like a rad socialist and a crazy juggler and that's a goth girl GF like sort of that's kind of cool.
It is kind of cool.
And like, I don't know.
I'm rooting for her.
I don't know.
She got her she got Percy killed though.
She did seem sad about it.
So it was like, I feel like she didn't seem that sad about it.
She seemed like performatively.
She seemed like, I mean, it was an intense moment.
She gives him she gives him the kiss and then she seems like she's like moved by the moment, but not in a way that it's like, oh God, what have I done?
This innocent person is dead.
No, yeah, she's too deep in it.
This is such high drama like like things are coming to such a such a cataclysmic head like yes, like I'm feeling like the drama of the moment.
I got to give him a kiss because that's just what you do in this situation.
That was my read on it.
Yeah, I it's I think it's more that to show that she's not like completely lost her humanity that she does feel sad, but like she's too deep in it now to like turn back.
She's going to continue war.
That moment made me think that she's like lost her humanity even more than I thought she had like that.
Like she immediately she's not even she's not worried about Percy the person she immediately starts like mythologizing him is like this is like the this is the first martyr in you know in the Jubilee war revolution or whatever.
Yeah, maybe hadn't thought about it like that.
But I but I know that like.
But still, like, I like what she stands for and I think Hussey does too like she's she's not like completely villainous.
I think it seems like maybe it's heading for like a like a hubris like a like a like a hubris down like a Lorax.
Yeah, exactly.
Like like this is like a good person with like some tragic flaws that will eventually lead to their destruction.
That seems like the trajectory, but I don't know that the whole the whole Jubilee cosmic clown god thing could perhaps could perhaps have some impact on the direction.
The story too.
I don't know.
That's that's just a possibility.
I think the fact that there's like psychic damage and she's like clearly has like mental issues that the Jubilee clown is more likely like a like a mental problem.
But like that we can see a cool space god thing.
If I had to bet right now, I would say that this story is not actually like a supernatural thing that the God is the clown is just a thing in her mind.
That's my that's my I'll bet all my Bitcoin on that.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
And then it will keep going up.
And then I'll have lost even more.
My losses will just keep compounding forever.
Yeah, never, never sell, never sell Bitcoin give you all only buy.
Oh, it goes down by it goes up by because it will only ever go up never down.
But if it does go down, definitely buy.
I like looking at the long term.
I don't care about Bitcoin.
I'm trying to talk about psychologials.
Although, yeah, the Bitcoin stuff in there was funny.
The whole like, like, I forget the name of the other girl.
What was there?
Abby.
I like the whole like, you know, the super billionaires and then Z has this ingenious plan to steal all of their money.
And flirts with Abby's mom.
Gross.
It was it was really like through emails and then gets Percy to do the voice.
And it's such such a elaborate.
It's such the such an elaborate plan that I couldn't even imagine thinking of it for a character to think of in a story.
You know, I I thought it was weird that like there's like a throwaway line about like how Abby.
Graduated Harvard by fucking all her professors and Abby's just like, lol, true.
And like, I just thought that was a weird detail.
I understand that like sex isn't bad, but like, I don't know.
That doesn't.
I don't feel like that's like a good.
I don't feel like that reflects well on a person still.
I don't even think I'm approved to think that.
I mean, the fact that I don't think Abby is like an angel.
She's no angel.
She's like, she heard she hears about like the fact that Z like shot a cop.
I mean, admittedly, it was like.
In self-defense in a way, but we saw that it wasn't exactly when you get shot at.
Yeah, like she's these these these gaslighting us, right?
Like was these keeps saying it's in self-defense, but like she's definitely.
It wasn't completely.
She jumped at him, bit his arm or something, took the gun and then shot him a bunch of times.
Yeah.
It's like.
He wasn't even really aiming for her.
He shot her thing.
Honestly, she but she says it.
She says so often and so confidently that like it was in self-defense that like I started to believe it.
And then I was like, wait, and I had to go back and check and like.
She fooled me.
She gaslit me.
It's manipulator.
So yeah, Abby sort of buys that.
And I guess that's just her being a good friend, but it's also like covering up a murder.
So like she's not.
It's kind of covering up a murder.
And she's totally okay with I mean, it's interesting because it's like.
The literal what she's okay with.
Like stealing all of her parents' money and then tricking them into having a divorce.
It seems to be.
It's good for them, obviously, but she's sort of like it's good for her parents as well because they're not in a happy marriage.
And she's like.
I don't know.
It's hard to say that Abby is a bad person for going along with all that because there's like reasons why.
That they sort of those billionaires deserve what they're what's coming to them as well.
The billionaires deserve it.
And like if she thinks that like the cop murder was in self-defense, like that's totally reasonable.
Yeah.
Abby is like, yeah, like Abby doesn't really know.
So like I just think it's it's kind of no.
Okay, go on.
I think.
Well, yeah, I think she leans towards being the innocent sort of person in this.
I assume is going to be a tragedy.
I think Abby might be killed in this war, which will just feel Z to do even more danger dangerous blow up stuff.
Yeah.
I just think it's a little weird and I don't really know what to think about the fact that like.
I know that Hussie is like a cab kill cops and like loves clowns and like his the hero of this story is is like that.
And yet she's kind of being portrayed as like this this dangerous like a sort of mentally unhinged like manipulator at the same time.
That's what he loves, dude.
I guess I created risk and he loves her more than any other character in Homestuck.
What you make an excellent point.
It's it's it's it's interesting because it's not just like an idea that you can root for like, oh yeah, like a cab like fuck the police and there's like a character that's just doing that and they're perfect in every other way.
It's it's not an idea it's a flawed human being which makes it more difficult to root for them even though you want to and that's why characters like that, like people really latch on to.
Like the fact that Vriska was such a horrible person, but so right so often is like why is she so controversial and why I enjoy like her in so controversial and yet so brave and yet so brave.
Literally.
Good point.
I fucking.
Cyclone is so good.
I want more people to play it.
There's like no.
There's like no tweets about it.
There's like there's like six pieces of Psycholonial's fan art that you can find on floating around Twitter if you Google for it or if you if you search for it.
It's like very much like an on.
I hadn't looked into it.
But I would have assumed.
Oh, it's the new Hussey thing like loads of people would be into it.
Maybe they were all waiting for it the story to be over and there's silently hype.
I don't know.
I actually have like a half drawn picture of Z that I started doing and then kind of never quite finished.
I should finish it and just post it somewhere because I really like it.
Her clown makeup is pretty good.
Yeah, it is pretty good.
That's pretty good.
It's pretty good.
I kind of for a minute there.
I was thinking about making a clown so now just a little bit.
Why not?
Why the fuck not?
I don't know.
I'm not really I'm not that into wearing makeup and painting my face or anything, but I guess I could do it for a laugh.
And then repeatedly every day until you die.
Because it would be really funny.
Clown gender based horse gender cringe.
Yeah, the horse gender aspect.
The horse gender is so like like it's so dumb and it's I don't know.
I don't know whether to think that Hussey is dumb for even including the idea or are the characters dumb for for doing it.
I think it's part of like the cat because it was Abby's idea and then Z was like, no, it's perfect.
Well, I suppose you have a point.
I like the idea of it being stupider.
So I'll make it stupider for you.
Abby just has like this stupid idea and Z is like, yeah, she is like, okay.
You're my friend.
So, okay, I'll make my sit my ideas dumber just like because you would like it.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, the triangle of genders with the clown at the top coming together.
It's pretty good.
It's pretty fun.
I don't know where I would put my side.
I haven't really considered it.
In a way, I don't care.
I guess like it's weird because like non binary, like being perfectly in the middle non binary would technically be like quite clown gendery in the sense that they don't necessarily ascribe to one or the other or care so much.
But I guess they care about being in the middle.
It's like, how do you care?
How do you be a super non binary horse gender?
How do you be extremely both?
You're like, you're extremely neither.
You're like a militant, a militant rejector of all that is.
But that's, I feel like that would be clown gender.
Like a complete, like, I guess the clown part is like it doesn't matter.
I think clown gender.
If you can do whatever.
If you're clown gender, you can do masculine things, but it doesn't make you masculine.
It doesn't mean anything because you're just a clown, right?
Yeah.
Where I mean, it sounds like horse, horse non binary would be, yeah, would be, I guess you could do like a very deliberate melding of masculine and feminine, or you could be a very militant rejection of all this.
A horse, a horse gendered non binary person would be like half, they got a beard like half the side of their face and like long hair on the other side.
And like they wear half of a dress on one side and then it's like completely split down the middle.
Sounds like a contra points character.
Yes.
But I was going to say something else about the the whole the clown gender thing is like the Psycholonial's version of like the shipping grids.
Yeah.
Pussy loves stupid graphs that I mean I do as well.
Just find take some take some concept that like clearly defies that like obviously defies like rigid categorization and then like very like very sort of bluntly like place it in a in a graphic form and then adhere to that graph.
Religiously.
Yeah, it's like inherently funny.
The idea of flooding gender on a specific graph and then clown also involved.
And clowns are also just inherently funny.
So, there you go.
The whole the pranks.
That was really good.
Pranks is pretty good.
I think I like I understand it intuitively, but I couldn't like describe pranks to someone like it's it's like doing stuff.
I think it's funny.
I think it's just I mean it's just it's just it's just being a it's just it's literally just being a socialist clown is what pranks is and also you you you fuck with people in ways that are funny.
I don't know.
Pranks is a funny name for a pretty for a pretty a pretty common sense concept I think which is fine, which is fine.
I mean, Bitcoin, Bitcoin fraud.
Bitcoin fraud doesn't strike me as as pranks is but that just kind of strikes me as just, you know, theft, which is fine.
It's particularly funny.
It's like Robin Hood.
I guess the way she's doing it by seducing Abby's mom is pretty funny like that.
That I might consider pranks like getting amateur porn and then Photoshopping the face of the guy she thinks she's talking to onto the amateur porn and sending that to her.
Nudes is like that that's the prank part of pranks is that it wouldn't be funny if you just stole the money.
You have to make it extremely embarrassing.
I like I like hearing Abby, I like Abby's disgust at like her dad, her Republican dad.
I'm like every every time Abby talks about that.
I get like a little I don't know.
It's I know he's a fictional character, but you know, imagining this imagining this piece of shit like his daughter fucking like just duping him just duping him for being like a like a Republican fuck and just using that against him while like loathing him the entire time.
I'm like, yes, it's fine that you fucked all your all your professors.
Abby, you've redeemed yourself.
Yeah, it is a lot of it's it's like it's very cathartic because like obviously a militant clown uprising probably wouldn't be the best way to do socialism.
But like for like seeing it like appear before you in this in this in this game this visual novel.
It's like, oh yeah, God, if only I wish, you know, yeah, yeah.
Um, I had one more.
I have one more thing I was going to say about clowns, Bitcoin Republicans.
Fuck it's gone.
Okay.
We're going to say about like the how they switched to supporting Biden just because they
Oh, like in their pockets or whatever.
I was just going to say that I feel like when I read Psycholonial's like in the very first chapter it talks about like it talks about like the elections and stuff and like cycle when I read Psycholonial's
I can feel that like Hussey was feeling angst about like the state of politics, American politics.
And I'm like I even though it's not even though that's not like a super.
It's not like a super important like story beat like it comes through in the writing and the way he talks about like current events and the times and I'm like, Hussey, I feel a connection with you through through this work.
Yeah.
If you remember, if you remember like Homestuck had the Obama stuff and and the the future ridiculous future where Violent J Shaggy too dope and Guy Fieri will like took over the White House and and like took a shit on the Constitution.
And it's like that stuff is so like ridiculous like wow crazy.
But then a few years later, Trump and it was like, oh, it's kind of true.
It's like it was a little bit of a little bit of to it would be like not even that satirical to make a joke like that in Homestuck.
Was that was that pre Trump was the clown was the clown was the twin clown president stuff pre Trump.
That was definitely pre Trump.
I don't know if Homestuck ended before before Trump was in office, but I know that that part was already there because I caught up to it before 2016.
Wait, wait, what if.
Okay, just hear me out for a second.
I got a great idea we should we should go back and we should fix Homestuck and the way we fix Homestuck is that you insert up.
It's on the day that Trump was elected.
You have a panel where John Egbert just looks directly into the camera and says so here's the thing.
I fucking hate Trump.
He embarrasses me every day.
He makes us all look like backwards idiots and frankly the fact that he got elected means that we are all backwards idiots.
You know what I'm referencing.
Quinton reviews.
Yeah, that's the Quinton just have John just deliver that word for word.
It missed missed opportunities, though.
Yeah.
I'm thinking, I don't know.
I mean, I'll have to finish it and see how I feel.
I think I would like to maybe make like a video or something in which I discuss.
Psycholonials like after it's over.
Yeah.
And I've read the whole thing.
You should do a PCP again and just ask Hussey to be on.
It'll be like, okay.
He's, I mean, he's getting no love for Psycholonial.
So maybe he'd fucking do it.
Maybe he would.
Yeah.
No, you got to stay optimistic.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Yeah, you're right.
We should do some pranks on Hussey.
We should invite him on the PCP and then.
That's the best prank of all.
And then steal all his Bitcoin while he's not looking.
I think that's how you do it.
I wonder if I wonder if Hussey has Bitcoin.
Probably has a little bit.
Who doesn't want to have a little bit of Bitcoin?
That's true.
Everybody's got to have some.
Because when the United States implodes and fiat currency is worthless,
you better hope you have at least a little bit coin just to cover the necessities.
It's the hardest form of money ever invented, don't you know?
Harder than diamond.
Oh, no.
It's under 60K.
Oh, wait, it's back over 60K.
Okay, it's fine.
Few.
60026.
It was down.
It was down to 59985 or something before a minute there.
Incredible.
It's wobbling.
No.
It's wobbling around the 60.
But it's wobbling.
Oh, 60.
41.
Why do you watch something that updates so much?
I literally watch the like minute to minute, like by the second update.
The app I have only updates by the hour and even then it's not accurate,
so I usually have to wait anyway.
I mean, I go to, I use Kitco.
I use kitco.com slash Bitcoin price charts, USD.
Don't go there.
Don't go there every few seconds.
The link not in the description.
Okay, all right.
But I just got to know.
If it's updating once an hour,
like hell, 40 minutes ago, the market could have crashed
and it could have lost 40% of its value.
And I would, and I would never know.
I'd have to be a sap.
I'd have to be a sap not to watch one that updates every minute.
This was the problem the first time.
No, it's not that this, I don't, I don't look at it like all the time.
For a while I was looking at it all the time.
This time I like, I'll check it like once a day, like twice a day maybe.
I don't actually like watch it going up and down.
I mean, on the PCP, I'll keep it open continually.
Oh, 23.
Oh, down to 22.
Are we going up or down from here?
It just had a killer minute.
The last minute it rose from 59915 to 60038.
That was all in the space of one minute.
Hovering at 60022.
60023.
We're up.
We're up a dollar.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm closing it.
I'm closing the app.
I need this.
I need this in my life.
What else?
Oh, now is the time.
Eleazar, link in the description here for, for cook, put, put a link to where you can
skip the Psycholonial spoilers.
Because I genuinely, if people want to not be spoiled on Psycholonials, I don't want
to spoil it.
Yeah.
Because I think, I think a lot of people should, I think people should be encouraged to read
it themselves.
Yeah.
In fact, put this audio before we talk about spoilers.
Go play Psycholonials.
It's very, very good.
It's a visual novel, hussy written, extremely good character development.
You will not want to be spoiled for it.
And here's Tom Oliver.
I'm here for my dollar.
I'm here for the dollar I earn.
Here's Tom Oliver.
Just in time for us to stop talking about Psycholonials.
Oh, good.
The game I've never, is it a game?
Is it a show?
I don't know what it is.
It's a game.
I've never heard of it.
It is a visual novel.
So it's technically a game.
Oh, all right.
Well.
By the most, by the most generous definition, it is a game.
Yeah.
It's good.
Cool.
Sick.
Keep playing that game.
What's up?
Okay.
We will, we will.
Next, next update comes out on, was it like next Wednesday or there might be an off week?
No, there's an off week.
The next update comes out on the 24th.
So.
Plenty of time for people to play it.
True.
Maybe I'll listen back to this episode and see if you can convince me to try it.
Probably not.
If you don't care about spoilers, you can listen to what we said because it's, it's good.
All right.
Um, what if we, what the fuck?
Yeah.
What's going on?
I'm just vibing, hanging out.
Yeah.
I was just on another podcast that was supposed to start at noon and it didn't start till
two.
And I was like, well, I can't be on two podcasts at the same time.
Or can I?
You started a Mrs. Doubtfire sort of like two discord accounts open in two different windows.
You just flipping your microphone back and forth from one to the other, two pairs of
headphones, one in each year.
Yeah.
Imagine the antics.
Laptop open on one with a microphone attached to there, desktop, the other one just kind
of flipping it back and forth.
You know, I wasn't thinking.
They should, they should remake Mrs. Doubtfire, but it's about being in discord calls in 2020
in the, in the pandemic.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
I got a zoom, I got a zoom thing with like a family and I got a discord school in a Skype
poll.
And it's, and it's about, and it's about being trans.
It's about being a boy motor and like you got one call with your family because like,
oh, my family's having their zoom call because we haven't seen each other.
And the other one, it's like, oh, my cool, my cool zoomer friends, like, oh, they think
I'm a girl, but my family still thinks I'm a boy.
That's, that's Mrs. Doubtfire for the modern age.
That's true.
That would be.
Send me a check, Hollywood.
That'd be pretty powerful.
Go, go on and sell that idea so Hollywood can fuck it up and make it really insulting.
I don't care.
As long as I get paid.
As long as you get paid.
It's fine.
Pay them a bit point.
Please.
It's going to the moon.
As we talked about NFTs yet.
I can't remember.
We talked about NFTs on the podcast.
Oh, we talked about them that one time.
We didn't know what we were saying.
We had just heard about it.
No, it's under 60.
It's under 60 K.
Oh, God, my life is over.
You said you closed it.
You closed it.
I lied.
I lied to your fucking face and I could do it again.
Did Bitcoin hit 60 earlier today?
Yesterday, I think.
Oh, really?
I didn't even.
It almost hit 62, but it dipped a little bit since then.
I like was getting excited about Bitcoin going up.
And then I realized I have so little invested in Bitcoin.
It would have to hit like 120,000 for it to do any significant amount of gains for me.
Well, the solution is to buy more Bitcoin.
In fact, that's the solution to every problem in life.
My plan right now is every time Nate sends me a PCP payment,
I just immediately I'm going to put into Bitcoin.
Are you actually?
That's what I did last month.
I don't know.
That's why I have Bitcoin.
I'm holding for now, but I think a crash is coming.
I really do.
I mean, it has to eventually.
It has to eventually.
Brian's smarter than both of us combined.
So I trust him with my life.
Absolutely.
By far.
I mean, this is the first time it's been so high.
We haven't seen a crash from so high.
So maybe it will never.
I don't think it will crash.
It's too big a fail.
It will crash all the way back down.
But it could drop 20K easily.
It crashed like that percentage before.
Yeah.
That's when you capitalize.
No, I think that like eventually it will crash back all the way down to like 20K
or maybe even low at some point.
Like it's.
I am.
I don't think it's thinking about Ethereum though, because Ethereum is what's
powering all this NFT stuff.
And I feel like that's to explode once NFTs really start taking off.
I don't think NFTs are going to take off.
No, they totally will.
I think they're a stupid meme and everyone hates them.
They're a meme in their current form, but I guarantee you that like the entire
like Zoomer culture is primed to be like bragging rights, digital ownership.
Like it's going to be big.
There's going to, it's going to be.
I don't, I don't think that's true.
I don't agree.
I think it is.
It's like, it's like patently, it's patent nonsense.
Like what, like an NFT is like so manifestly, like a worthless thing.
But like we do, we spend money on worthless things all the time.
Like, you know, like you can buy a baseball with a signature on it.
It's worth like $10 trillion.
That, that, that weird illogical sense of like connection to something is, is there
in human psychology.
But that's not true.
But like an NFT is something that like anyone can just make like out of, out of the ether
can just generate it.
Like there's no supply and demand.
The supply and demand curve is just, okay, all it needs is a few people who know how
to make NFTs and suddenly everything in the world can be NFT'd.
And, and that's that like fucks up the supply demand curve.
Well, that's because I don't think that's how it works.
It's not, it's not just making an NFT.
It's about, it's about tracking where it comes from, right?
Like if some random person tried to mint an NFT of like a famous YouTubers like content
or something, that wouldn't be worth anything.
But if the YouTuber themselves minted the NFT, it's the connection between like this
is an NFT made by this person.
It's attached permanently on the blockchain to their initial source of ownership.
And just like signing a baseball is like attached to a famous player.
Once a celebrity like attaches it to that, it's just a digital version of that same
sort of collector mentality.
But it's gonna stick.
I guess that makes sense.
I'm wondering though about how you can, like how visible and obvious that would be.
Like, like if, if.
As far as I understand, it was like, there's like a, the ledger lets you know where it's,
where it's been, where it's come from.
Like you track of sales so you can see where it originated.
I'm just thinking of like smaller people, smaller creators, not super celebrities.
And then like people who like make accounts that have similar characters in them, but
like instead of an eye, it's like an eye with a slanted thing at the top and they could
just pretend like, I know it like for the largest, like huge things like a, I don't
know, Johnny Depp took a picture of his himself taking a shit.
And that's like a thing.
And then that's like, oh, it's a Johnny Depp original from his phone.
Like this is the one, like people would pay attention, I guess, pay attention to like
something that is big celebrity.
But like, there was a lot of people talking about how it's the future of like, like just
art in general, just anyone who wants their art to be like.
I don't, I don't think, I think it's gonna be just like anything else where like,
most people won't get anywhere with it, but there's going to be a few people.
It's just going to be another way for like you to leverage the cloud you already have,
you know, it's not like any random schmuck is going to be able to mint an NFT of like
their DeviantArt account and make billions of dollars.
Like you already have to have some social currency in order to make your NFT valuable.
But I think if you, if you already have a brand and NFT is just going to make it more
valuable because I think one of the most interesting things about NFTs is that
the smart contract attached to them gives you residuals.
So like, let's say, Ben.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Okay.
Ben, Ben, let's say you mint an NFT representing like, like the first issue of the Vapors,
right?
It's like, there's, this represents the first issue of the Vapors that I made and you can
buy this NFT and it represents it, right?
And you put it up there and people can buy it, but part of the contract, like part of
the thing of the NFT is like, you can set a percentage.
So every time it's resold, you get X% of that sale.
So let's say someone buys that NFT off you for like $100.
Let's say the Vapors blows up and gets fucking huge, like when like, you know, like issue
five or six, whatever comes out, like it does gangbusters, whatever reason.
The NFT's value goes up and someone's like, I want to sell this NFT now that it's worth
money.
I'm going to sell it for $60,000.
In that contract, you get $6,000 from that sale.
And then if someone sells it again for $100,000, you get $10,000 and in perpetuity, every time
that NFT gets resold on the market, you get a kickback, which is better than a collectible
because a normal collectible, all the money goes to the whoever acquired it.
And that's an interesting idea.
That is an interesting idea.
I mean, is it like in the form of like some Ethereum that just like appears in your wallet
or whatever?
I believe it's all done through Ethereum right now.
And then you can obviously exchange that for real currency.
But the idea that like you can have a digital equivalent of like a collectible and then
in perpetuity, you can keep making money off of its reselling.
I think is a really interesting idea even on a small scale, right?
Like let's say when you release the Vapors five, you mint like 15 NFTs.
Like the first 15 people who buy this, they get an NFT attached to it.
You know, you get the digital file and you also get an NFT.
And then if somebody else in your audience wants to buy it for like 20 bucks, you get two bucks.
You know, like that's kind of cool.
The biggest problem with NFTs is the environmental impact, which I think is definitely a problem.
Ethereum is saying they're changing the way that mining Ethereum works.
It's not going to be done based on mining starting next year, which could severely reduce the energy problem,
which could be interesting.
I don't know.
I just think that there's something about like an NFT is just not as attractive as like, I mean,
the obvious parallel here is like the fine art world where some like rich idiot pays like $50,000 for some painting.
But at least that's like a thing that you can understand what it is and see and look at.
An NFT is like most people just don't know what it is and it isn't really anything.
It's literally just like a handshake of like, OK, we both know you own something now.
But the same reason, I agree, and I totally think you're right.
I think the problem is that there's just...
I feel like that's a problem for adoption.
I feel like it just doesn't have that as much social value attached to it because people don't understand it.
I just think there are people out there because there is, people have bought NFTs for $70 million.
This is a thing that's already happening.
But I think there's just people out there who are like, the reason they would buy a fine piece of art is for the clout,
like for the bragging rights.
And an NFT gives you the exact same thing.
Like even though you're not getting a tangible item, it's still the underlying reason is the same.
The thing you're bragging about is not something that as many people can appreciate what you're telling them.
It is that you own.
I think people our age will think it's stupid.
I think younger kids who have grown up with an iPhone in their hand and everything has been digital
and microtransactions and buying digital goods is a part of their psychology are going to be way more into it.
And I think that's why it's going to be viable going forward.
I don't know about that.
I think that growing up more exposed to the internet might just make you more likely to be like,
so it's just like some random data that you both agree represents a thing.
Obviously, that's worthless.
I feel like the younger people might be even less likely to take it seriously.
If I think of the parallels to reality, if you've got a big old mansion, you're like,
I want to show off my art clout, my taste.
I'm going to buy some big old paintings and put them in here and people will come around for dinner parties.
And they'll look at them and I'll say, haha, I'm rich and I bought this and I have great taste.
And this is the clout. You're impressed, aren't you?
Right.
The equivalent of that in the digital space, I don't know where you would show off that you have it.
You would just have to make a platform.
It's the same way that back in the day, you would customize your MySpace page and put all a bunch of memes and images and songs on there.
You would acquire things and put them on this space to represent who you are and to show to the world who you are.
And NFTs are going to be the exact same thing.
They're going to be platforms, but they're already a platform so you can show what's in your wallet, what you own.
And it's just a way of like, I guess flexing, I don't know.
I don't personally think it matters. I think it's dumb. I think society's going to like that.
Sure, sure. I'm just trying to think of like, if it's a flex and obviously if you want people to see,
it needs to be in a place where people can see it.
If it's a new social media that is just for flexing, nobody's going to go over there to look.
It'll need to be on like current social media or whatever integrated.
Like you go to someone's Twitter.
Or it could be built. It really depends.
I think we're still a few years out from it becoming mainstream if it ever picks up that kind of steam.
It's not going to happen like tomorrow.
Say for example, Elon Musk buys like the founder of Twitter's first tweet or something.
That sentence you just said just made me want to throw out.
It's already going for two and a half million dollars.
It's fucking stupid, but say that he wants to show off that he did that.
He could pin a tweet saying he did. He could put it in his description or what?
It's so very volatile right now.
If they become big, they'll be integrated into platforms and new platforms will spring up to facilitate the system.
I don't know. I just feel like ultimately where the people are is where this is the most useful.
I think the thing is people don't really, at the moment, because it's hype.
They don't really care about the art itself.
They buy these things under the assumption that they will appreciate in value and then they can sell them on.
If that's the case, I don't see how it's going to stick around at all.
The market that's there right now I think is going to crash eventually.
It's too big and people are just riding high and it's going to be just like the internet.
The early 90s web boom, it popped and the same things that happened in NFTs.
How exactly do you display that you own an NFT?
I think there's some websites like OpenSeenRarable where you have your wallet and if you go to your profile, it'll show all the NFTs you own.
On the record of the NFT, it shows who the current owner is.
If you go and look up a people NFT, it'll show whoever owns it right now.
I suppose it's not that different in theory from buying adoptables.
People are so fucking stupid.
My little sister was showing me a video yesterday about a YouTuber who spent four months trying to get number one on the leaderboards for the world's fastest pencil sharpener.
Unassisted, like tool-less pencil sharpening.
Tool-assisted?
This strat is task only for sharpening pencils.
Well, that's the whole thing. There was a leaderboard for drills and no drills on this.
I'm just thinking if people are stupid enough to chase that, why wouldn't NFTs make sense?
You laugh, but that's as valid as any other field of human endeavor.
It's about attaining excellence for its own sake. You're just a hater.
I saw a video about a guy on his journey to the top of the leaderboard.
It was such a small thing, and then he made his video, and then it became a big thing, and now everyone's doing it.
I was at the iCarly one?
I have no idea.
I saw that.
But that's my whole point. People are doing this just because A, for the meme, and B, because I can be number one on this.
It's chasing that pseudo-glory, I guess.
And I feel like NFTs tap into that same kind of part of your brain where it's just like, I want to own the thing for the cloud.
It's too much. It's too similar, because it's also an environmental drain, because all of those pencils get destroyed and used.
Oh, sure.
Get all those trees. There's no trees left.
Yeah, that's the big problem with NFTs right now, is that the whole market is so unsustainable, and so environmentally unfriendly, because it uses so much energy.
And that's a problem that's going to have to be addressed.
To be clear, I'm not endorsing NFTs.
I'm saying, I believe they're going to happen.
Just like everything else that's bad about the internet has happened, despite me not liking any of it.
I don't know. I understand. They just seem so backwards and counter-intuitive.
It kind of takes us a huge step backwards in terms of what the internet enabled, which is access abundance.
We've artificially introduced scarcity again, which can be beneficial in some ways.
Being able to make residuals off of tokens from your art and stuff, that's kind of cool.
I do kind of like that idea, but it's going to enable so much worse things than just that.
A better idea is just getting rid of the need to make money. That's probably a better idea.
That's never going to happen.
I saw people were saying, OK, Sean on Twitter made a tweet that said,
we can't solve climate change under capitalism.
He was roundly attacked from so-called leftists who claimed that he was being a doomer
and saying that there was no hope to fix climate change then.
Obviously, the implication there is we have to remove capitalism.
We need to become socialists. That's how you solve climate change.
His bio said he was a socialist. This is like a streamer or something.
This is a socialist guy who's like, you're just making people want to give up.
Saying you can't solve climate change under capitalism, that's just so doomer.
This is just accelerationism.
I don't know. I think there's some people who just want-
You fucking idiot. Don't you not like capitalism? What's wrong with you?
I think they're projecting. They are the doomers
because they think that capitalism is so difficult to get rid of
that it's not even worth trying.
They're the doomers because they're the ones that will never abolish capitalism
or at least not within our lifetimes.
Maybe they're right about that, but I don't know.
I believe that we probably can't fix climate change under capitalism.
We will have to move to socialism.
If you believe that, then it's not doomer to just acknowledge that
because then the hopeful thing to do
would then, even if we can't achieve it in our lifetimes,
to try to move towards it in whatever ways we can
because that's what leads to long-term improving the situation.
It's not doomer just to acknowledge that if you think it's true.
I really hate the attitude that a lot of people had about calling it-
It's like you don't even understand what words mean.
A doomer would be-
You get it. You understand.
Yeah, it's just like the-
It's what Sean's saying, and I haven't seen the tweet itself,
but based on what you said-
I think I said it or made him.
It's not mutually exclusive.
You can understand that capitalism needs to go before climate change is completely possible,
and you can combat climate change under capitalism as well.
You can do both of those things.
I don't think what Sean's saying is implying that you should try not to do anything under capitalism.
You can both try to get rid of capitalism and then also climate change.
He totally was not saying that, and yet tons of people read that into it
and criticized it as though that was what he said.
Very, very frustrating.
I hate Twitter.
The left has always been very bad with language in general, so it doesn't-
That's true.
It's sad but true.
More like shitter.
Oh, I want to mention about the Noida stream that I did on Wednesday.
I have some things.
One, it was really fun to play Noida and tell everyone about the game.
Two, I don't understand why it had all these problems.
The game lagged in ways that it never lags before.
I closed all my other applications.
I was cutting off CPU usage.
I couldn't get it to run at its normal speed.
I don't know why.
It was very infuriating.
I beat the game on stream.
It was very satisfying.
And then a guy, a guy who was in chat, I guess he was just so chuffed that I beat Noida.
He bought me a fridge.
What the fuck?
A fridge?
This Chalupa-kun is his name on Discord.
He was like, yo, congrats on beating Noida.
Let me buy you a mini-frame.
And he did.
And I have it.
I have it here.
Right now, it's an $80 mini-fridge.
What a madman.
That's literally what I said.
I said, absolute madman.
It's a 1.7-foot cube.
Cubic.
It's a galan's.
It arrived from Amazon.
It is currently holding many bottles of flavored seltzer water.
So I just want to say that this is just what happens when you're a pro MLG gamer like me.
You make dividends.
You reap the rewards of pro gaming.
You put all your energy drinks in there.
Your gamer fuel.
I'm all out of Summit Gridlock.
In fact, I'm out of almost every source of caffeine.
I've had to brew coffee.
Ugh.
I've had to do it like the cavemen used to do.
Yeah, I had coffee earlier today.
I had moved entirely to Gridlock in pills.
Oh my God.
There's no joy if you have caffeine pills.
That's half the fun.
Half the fun is getting caffeine and enjoying the process.
Not, you know.
It's the most efficient.
You say it like that.
I don't know.
I enjoy having a nice beverage.
I think I'm going to try moving back to Gridlock.
I just got a bunch of red thunder and it's just not nearly as good as Red Bull.
I'm just like, ugh, it just tastes terrible.
Maybe I'll try Gridlock again.
I don't understand how a person ever stops drinking Gridlock once they start.
It's simply the beverage champions.
The last time I had Gridlock, I just remember being like, this is like monster but worse
because I don't even like monster that much.
But it's so cheap I have to give it another shot.
I would agree.
It is like monster.
It is maybe slightly worse than monster but not like, notice, not much worse.
And I like monsters.
So to me, it's like still good.
Right, right, right.
That's just me.
That makes sense.
Nice.
Very nice.
Too many, too many seltzer waters.
Oh, Tom.
Project Blue.
Yeah, the Windows version of Astropad.
Do you like my starter there?
That was a good one.
I don't know.
That was like skipping a stone.
Project Blue, it's like a, I got my iPad on the assumption that eventually this thing
would come out called Astropad.
It took way longer than I told you it would.
Yep.
But it's fine, it's whatever.
But my tablet that I've been using for my computer for a while, like my bamboo is broken.
And I just wanted a way to like draw on my computer, my PC.
And this thing apparently-
You can draw on a computer?
I know, it's weird.
You get a crayon, you shove it in there and you draw.
No, very nice.
And now I can get my iPad, my Apple product, and compatible with Windows.
And I've been drawing a little bit.
It doesn't really seem to work with pen pressure on Photoshop.
I don't know why.
Maybe it's an older version of Photoshop and it doesn't recognize it or something.
It works on some other things.
Yeah, I looked into Windows Inc.
But I couldn't figure it out.
What version of Photoshop do you have right now?
Let me check.
How do I check?
I'm hovering over the icon.
Photoshop CS6, CS5, CC.
I don't think they added Windows Inc. support to like CC.
Like the older ones.
Like the older ones don't even have high DPI support.
That's like the problem.
That's why I don't use Photoshop anymore.
I have band in that motherfucker.
CC 2018 is what I have.
It should have Windows Inc. support then.
That's pretty new.
That's new-ish.
Well, I don't know.
Whatever.
I'll try and figure it out.
Just yell at them on Twitter until they respond to you.
Yeah.
But yeah, it's cool.
I just like that finally my iPad can be used for the thing I bought it for.
Even though it's been great for drawing with Procreate this whole time I've been drawing.
The only annoying thing with drawing on an iPad is having to transfer my files.
Because I haven't found a really smooth, simple way to do it.
I've just been like sending them to myself through Discord and then opening them in Discord on my PC and then using them there.
The file manager on iOS still is not great.
They'll never fix it because they're like, you just need to pay for iCloud Drive storage.
That's what we want you to do.
I'm just like, no, I refuse.
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
So what's Project Blue?
It's the thing where I kill you.
Okay.
Yep.
I'm dead.
Sorry.
Got to listen back to the podcast.
Okay.
I would never listen to this hog swallow.
This corn swash.
It's a public beta of a company called Astropad.
They started by making an application that let you hook your iPad up to your Mac and use it as a waycom.
Like a waycom sensitive sensor.
And they finally released their public beta of using it with Windows because Apple two years ago they added that feature natively to macOS.
Basically stole their idea, bundled it in there and fucked them over.
There's actually a term in the Apple community.
It's called getting Sherlocked because they made a feature called Sherlock that copied something back in the day.
But yeah, they do that all the time.
They'll pilfer the best ideas from their community and then copy them and fuck their developers out of money.
So once that happened to them, they're like, well, I guess we got to go port it to Windows now so we can keep making money.
Okay.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
Sounds good.
Ben, you've not...
Should I invest in it?
Should I sell my Bitcoin and invest in Project Blue?
You should give me your Bitcoin so I can invest for you.
Okay.
Thank you.
I expect returns at an undetermined point somewhere in the future.
On my grave.
You can have it back.
Okay.
It's basic.
But yeah, the Apple Pencil version one, at least.
I've really enjoyed using that.
It's a great little stylus.
It's surprisingly good.
Sort of little rubberized tip with the screen.
It feels so much like an actual pencil on paper.
I was super...
There's no way this is going to work.
It doesn't have a cursor.
It doesn't have float support.
Like a Waycom thing does.
You can't see where the cursor is and then it's like, oh no, it's just so good.
It just works like a regular pencil.
It just feels like a real pencil.
It's so much easier to transition from physical to iPad.
I like it.
I think it's good.
It's pretty good.
Well, la di da.
Yeah.
Well, I just thought about it.
Okay.
You don't have to kill me.
Yeah.
Well, you shouldn't have.
Please don't kill me.
I do have to do that.
I'm sorry.
Some of us try out Project Blue.
Some of us get a free mini fridge.
You know, lives take different paths.
You can't do both.
Something.
Okay.
Fair.
Well, my replacement Cintiq since my last one broke recently is doing great.
Thanks for asking.
Hell yeah.
Why'd you get a replacement from?
Did you buy it?
I think I just bought it on eBay.
I think I bought one on eBay.
How much?
It's a Cintiq.
Well, I mean, Cintiqs are old now.
This is, um, I think it cost me like 200 and change.
Okay.
Like not that much.
Uh, I had to, I had to get a new pen though because I had an, okay.
The story is my old Cintiq was a, um, hang on, let me, let me look at the back of the,
of the monitor.
It was a, I might be able to switch things around.
I think the old one was a DTK and then they had basically made an updated version of the
DTK that was identical, except it had like a slightly different button layout and a slightly
higher, like pixel resolution.
And that was the DTZ.
I might be switching them, but whatever.
So the DTZ was basically identical, slightly better.
The old one that I had, um, um, somebody gave me as a, just as a gift and that was a DTK
and those ones were like over a decade old.
The new version, they made, they redid it that the DTZ like a few years later.
So this one is like slightly less old, but the DTK eventually just the screen stopped
displaying.
Like it would still like know that I was drawing on it and it would take input, but the screen
just was dead and wouldn't show anything.
So it was like too old.
I don't know.
So I got this one, which is, um, basically the same model except like a slightly newer
iteration of it.
And yeah, I mean, these are old machines.
They don't, uh, they were like thousands of dollars when they were new, but now they're
just like a couple hundred.
This one came, but it came with a, even though it's like a newer, even though it's like a
newer, uh, model, it needed like a different thing, even though it's like the same item
as the previous one, I just, I needed to get a different stylus, uh, which is irritating
because the first time I had the original one, the original one, I had bought a newer
stylus and tried to use it.
And they were like, no, this model doesn't work with the new styles.
You have to use the old stylus.
So we got that.
And then I get this one and I realize I've lost the other, the other stylus that I originally
bought that didn't work with the other model would have worked with this one, but I lost
it.
I don't know where it is.
So I just have to buy another one, but a stylus is like 70 bucks or not even that.
Let me be like 50.
So like, it wasn't that big a deal.
Just annoying.
Uh, but I mean, that's all in the past.
That's all in the past.
It works poifically now.
Poifect.
And it's better.
It has more buttons than the old one too, which is nice.
And also the old one was like dim and like the colors were a little bit like tinted red
and kind of dim and they didn't look the same as my normal monitor.
The new one looks much closer in its color display to my regular monitor.
So I think it's a good upgrade from something that's like 12 years old to like eight thumbs
up.
And that's my story.
Wow.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Uh, I don't know if you guys got anything else to talk about, but if you don't, we could
move on to voicemails.
Um, I guess the only other thing is I've been playing minesweeper a lot.
Getting into that.
Oh yeah.
Oh God.
I guess I got to practice.
I've been practicing.
I've been getting so good.
I can find the mines.
Damn.
Find those mines and sweep them.
I can sweep those mines.
Against the average idiot, I would feel pretty confident that I could win minesweeper, but
if you like actually, you play pick cross and you're practicing minesweeper.
So I'm going to disadvantage.
I'm going to have to, I'm going to have to study up.
Yeah.
You're going to study yourself.
I'm going to have to study advanced mine, not Minecraft, sorry, minesweeper theory.
But I mean, I'm a pro Minecraft player, so like the skills are probably transferable
in some way.
Dude, what if there was like minesweeper in Minecraft?
Yeah, like there's mines in some blocks and you have to, and like they tell you the number
and you have like, yeah.
That would be funny.
Somebody, somebody should have made that mod.
There's TNT in the game, so.
You'd have to have like a minesweeper craft.
You'd have to like get a code that like plants bunches of TNT all over the world's generation
in every biome.
Oh, here we go.
I think, I think there is minesweeper version two in Minecraft.
This is a video posted on September 8th, 2011.
Let me, let me get it here.
Here we go.
It's real.
September of 2011.
It's so old.
You can't, there's no, not even hunger.
You can't even run.
Wait a minute though.
Okay, I think this is too, I think it's a 2D game just being played in Minecraft.
Like the minesweeper game.
I would be cooler if it were 3D.
You know what I mean?
Like, like if the mines were not just on a 2D plane.
God, when's it gonna hit the, when's it gonna hit a mine?
This is such a great podcast as reacting to a video that nobody can see.
It's really uninteresting a video.
I thought, is he just taking it himself?
No, don't play the video.
It's not even worth it.
I'm waiting for him to hit a mine.
Show me the mine.
He's not even, it's not even a mod.
He's just like placed blocks and put dirt on top of it and he's just digging them.
He knows where everything is.
He put it there.
This guy's a fucking liar.
Is this, no, is this just a single minesweeper map?
Yeah, I think it is.
Okay, that's lame.
That's so lame.
Oh, he did it.
Yeah, he's going.
He's dying.
Oh, it doesn't even kill him though.
Well, that's, no, it's not good unless it like generates a random map.
That's the only way that it's okay.
Disappointing.
Wasn't there a minesweeper in RFCK?
Yeah, you would have to play like a mines, a version of minesweeper when you were mining to get slime for a while.
I think they took it out because it was like really annoying or something.
Imagine like tech space, like click on this square, put flag on this square, like it's be so slow.
I never like saw the game.
I never saw like what that looked like.
I think it's like, it's a weird thing that I know existed in the past, but I don't know what it looked like.
And I think I want to leave it that way.
Just like leave the mystery.
But yeah, there was minesweeper in Endless War for a little bit.
Voicemails?
Uh, yeah.
Oh, wait, we're gonna do the bonus episode.
Uh, we should record the minesweeper bonus challenge this week.
Yeah, I could, I think, I think I'm gonna lose, but it's okay.
I want, I want it poker.
I want it poker.
Anyone who subscribed to the Patreon knows about the time that I beat you and Nate at poker and I took all your money and it was really funny.
Yeah, but you didn't take all my money.
You took like most of it though.
Didn't I, didn't I like clean up?
Didn't I end up with like the entire pot?
No, I think, I think the idea was like if you lose, you don't lose like 100% of your earnings for that episode.
Yeah, it was some, maybe it was some, some like funny because I knew I was not going to win.
So I didn't want all of it to be gone.
It was very, very good though.
Very funny.
Um, yeah, we'll do, you can do that this week.
Uh, I, man, I would maybe, I would be willing to do more Noida streams.
I just wish they weren't so plagued with like technical bullshit.
Like, like too, too much of that stream was me just like trying to under, like figure out like why the CPU was chugging so much.
You just need a better computer.
I know it can't be true.
It's always the answer.
What is, what's your computer specs?
They always be the answer.
What's, how old's your computer?
What, what are you running?
What's that hardcore band rig?
It's not that old.
I, I, this is the computer that I bought from the GoFundMe that I did when I was living at, at Trixie's house in like 2017 or 2018.
So it's only like three or four years old.
Like it's not an old computer.
That shouldn't be terrible, I guess.
The definition of old changes with time.
I guess, like, how high end was it at the time? That's the question.
It was, it was decently high end.
I think I spent like, I spent more than like $1,000 on all the parts and stuff.
Like it has like, it had like a graphics card that was like very new at the time.
I mean, you can't even buy a new computer right now anyways.
Everything's so fucking expensive because it's all out of stock.
That's true.
So you're kind of fucked.
Nothing to be done.
Yeah.
The graphics card that I bought two years ago for $180 used right now is going used for $550.
Oh my God.
I don't know if you, I don't know if you guys remember, but there was a whole thing when I got this computer that was like the GoFundMe paid for.
Somebody told me, like, somebody gave me like specs of like what motherboard to get and what graphics card to get and all these other parts.
And I was like, okay, and I got the, but someone was like, hey, you can get this different motherboard for like $50 less.
And I was like, I want to save $50.
And I got it.
And that motherboard ended up being a complete nightmare.
And it, it made the computer like unusable for like six months while I was like taking it to repair shops and like sending the parts back and waiting for replacements.
That was like the worst 50, I think I ended up just not even getting, I think I ended up buying the more expensive one in the end.
That was like so annoying.
That was, that was the worst.
You don't really want to cheap out of any component.
It worked.
Like on paper, it looked like it was perfectly good, but just for some reason, it just didn't do it.
There's like different tiers of motherboards.
They have different chip sets and you never want to get the lowest end chip set that's designed for like potatoes.
If you want to do anything more advanced through the computer, you want to get at least a mid-range motherboard that has like decent capacitors and shit so it won't die on you instantly.
Tragic.
It really is.
Just tragic.
Okay, voicemails.
I think it's time.
All right.
All right, we got them.
We ready?
Okay, hold on.
Let me get to fucking speak pipe.
Man, I should have skipped this back half of the podcast, not the first half.
You're all floundering here and I am offering a way out.
I'm offering an escape from this and you're all treating me like I'm-
If you don't want to go to voicemails, then just don't flounder.
Guns blazing with a great topic.
All right, it was high energy.
Everybody loved it.
Yeah, it was a good-
No, it was a good topic.
Hey, it was a good topic.
It was a good topic, but it's over.
It's time has passed.
You got to live in the present.
I know.
The present is voicemail.
How unfortunate for us all.
It's true.
It's sad but true.
The first one looks like this week is called Roger Roger.
Are we ready?
Yes.
Tom?
Yes, I'm ready.
Okay, Roger Roger.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, guys.
In the last episode, you were talking about maybe getting a 12th member.
How about more logic, the Wonder Bread guy?
I mean, he's kind of a weirdo, but he's kind of a fun weirdo.
He's got a good sense of energy to him.
I think it'd be a good fit.
I mean, if you want to, of course, if you want to, but I think it'd be a good thing.
Anybody call me back?
Call me back.
Never.
That wasn't a Star Wars episode one battle droid reference.
I'm very upset.
No, like what's up with the name?
I don't know.
Merlogic is my best friend and we go out for salads twice a week.
Next one is called Ben's weekly reminder to catch up on one piece.
Three, two, one, go.
Fun fact.
Alec Robbins, AKA Mr. Boop is caught up on one piece.
How about that?
What's your excuse?
Damn.
Okay.
That is embarrassing.
I can't.
I want to be like Alec.
Okay.
There's more reason than ever to catch up, I guess.
Next one is called intro three, two, one, go.
Y'all look, I'm supposed to be working right now.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
No, I ain't working.
Shit.
I'm doing nothing.
Damn.
My dick.
I'm jerking and myself.
I'm sucking.
Oh, I am an asshole.
Damn.
You are a stupid.
I got a deadline, but don't want to do it.
I mean, pretty good.
Not a lot of production on that.
Needed musical accompaniment to really sell it.
Needed musical accompaniment.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Maybe just a little clap, like clap it along.
Maybe just clap those cheeks along with it.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Hey, send me some, hey, send me some twerking videos.
Don't say that.
Who, who was the, was it Onision who like asked, asked people for twerking videos?
Was it pyrocynical?
I think it was onision.
I don't know.
No, Onision was the one who like had the like underage roommate that like him and his wife
or husband were having sex with.
Well, I didn't need to know about that.
Now I do though.
Who was the one who was asked for twerking videos?
It doesn't matter.
Bad people.
I saw the video about it.
It wasn't, I don't know, whatever.
Who cares?
Next one is called Greg.
Three, two, one, go.
The lesson in all of this is to never trust a woman to deliver a man's lecture.
Lol.
True.
Sad but true.
That's just, that's just biological.
That's just genes.
You know.
Am I right?
Am I right guys?
Can I get a high five?
Can I get a high five here?
Under duress.
Oh, okay.
That often high five where you're just like, ugh.
I must mention that I've been delivered a burger and I am eating it.
What the fuck?
Gusting.
How did you do that?
How could it be?
Last night, I was really craving chicken.
I caved and I bought some buffalo chicken and I ate it.
I went a little over my, I went a little over my calorie restrictions just because I really wanted that sweet, sweet wings over.
I almost had bad food yesterday, but I resisted.
I went to D&D, it was really fun.
I threw a fireball at seven cultists and they all died at the same time.
It felt great.
That's pretty good.
Nice aim.
It was a good hit.
Rolled high.
Good damage.
33 points of fire damage on one fireball.
Oh, wow.
They must not have made their reflex saves.
Only one did, but then I immediately killed him next round.
It was great.
It was a good time.
Okay.
Excellent.
I'm glad.
Next one is called, I recorded this in my car and people near me heard it.
Three, two, one, go.
Like an absolute fiend.
Pump that crocodile right into the base of my cock.
I'm like Arnold Schwarzenegger and pumping iron.
Cause every time I play risk of rain two, I'm coming.
Just like I'm coming over to your house to give you that companionship you so freshly deserve.
On this cold, dark nights when you cry out for the warmth of a woman's touch.
You know what I was doing?
Getting fucking cracked on the stage with my boys in risk of rain two.
I didn't like risk of rain one.
I don't know if two is good.
He made a compelling argument.
Risk of rain two.
That bit about the woman's touch was very, very compelling.
Risk of rain two, I think is in three Ds, three dimensional games, completely different.
So maybe.
What?
Yeah.
I was surprised.
I was like, they made risk of rain.
You just platforming side to side.
Survival game?
They should have saved that for risk of rain three.
Risk of rain three D.
When are they going to make a risk of rain?
Rogue like third person shooter.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
That sounds pretty cool.
But I mean, I'm a little hesitant because I thought the original risk of rain sounded really cool.
And then I played it and I thought it was bad.
So I might look into it.
I might look into it and check it out.
Okay.
Came out late last year.
No.
No, it came out in early 2019.
This is old.
This game is old as fuck.
Okay.
I'll look into it.
Might be cool.
From now on, Ben will only play games that came out after Noida, which unfortunately
means he forfeits Minesweeper by default.
That's true.
It's too old.
It's just not relevant to the young people these days.
People these days don't care about Minecraft.
They're all about Picross.
Next voicemail is called soon.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, Benjamin.
That's me.
I am in the process of acquiring a certain picture from three men in Aqours, Georgia.
Do you know what that picture is been?
Yes.
It is that picture.
That picture which you have tried to hide from us all these years.
Picture of three men.
That picture of your butthole, a gape, so supple and so inviting.
Yes, Ben, soon, very soon.
Dude, I'm trying to eat.
I will have seen your butthole.
You could have just asked.
Three men in Aqours, Georgia.
What does that have to do with my butthole?
I don't understand.
Listen, if you find it, Godspeed.
Next one is called I Have DLC.
Three, two, one, go.
The whole big lip controversy is fucking stupid.
Do people seriously think that black people are the only ones in the world with big lips?
I'm an Asian guy and I have huge lips.
I've been made fun of it my entire life, but I'm not going to cancel people on Twitter
just because they want to draw big lip characters.
I don't find it offensive, nor is it meant to be offensive.
It's the whole same thing with lollies.
There are petite women in the world, too.
Are you just going to deny these people's existence just because it doesn't gel with your own personal tastes
or you just want to be some moral guardian?
People who just want to get offended on behalf of everyone, you're actually disgusting
because you're not doing this for the sake of other people.
You're just doing it to make yourself feel better
and you need to fucking stop because it is actual cancer.
No one was really getting canceled over it, though, is the thing.
No, it just been.
Yeah, just me.
It really wasn't a big deal.
That's why I'm like, eh, what was even the point?
What was the point?
I don't think that it equates so well to lolly stuff, though.
I don't really think that's really...
That's kind of apples and oranges, too.
Yeah.
Some of them are just women who are small.
He said lollies, but then he was describing adult petite women.
Adult petite women.
So he's conflating some things.
Absolutely.
Lollies that are supposed to be cute.
To be fair, people do conflate those on the time on Twitter anyway.
Children.
Sure, whatever.
I mean, I think if you're drawing, if the character is an adult,
even if they're small, then they're not a lolly, right?
Or is a lolly just an aesthetic and how they look?
I'm not entirely sure, honestly.
Okay, whatever.
Whatever.
Next one is two deaf punkers pitch about a weekend at Bernie's.
Three, two, one, go.
There we go.
Did you catch the question?
I'm not going to lie, my brain completely ignored all of that.
It was a little difficult to grasp what the words were.
I don't know.
Something happened.
There's a shark involved.
I sure hope the shark's okay.
Once it goes to shore, we'll know for sure.
Were there any reason for...
I can't hear the last word.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't make it out.
I didn't feel terrible.
But I can't do it.
I'm doomed.
Nice flow, though, as always.
Next voicemail is called a desperate plea.
Three, two, one, go.
Release me.
You.
No.
No, definitely not.
This bondage.
I am trapped.
Oh, good.
Monty.
Betray us.
Turn his back on us.
Easy.
Just listen to yourself.
Nothing could be simpler.
Okay.
I don't know.
I think if Monty betrays people like that,
it reflects well on him as a person.
Thanks for the voicemail.
Next one is called investments.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP, you get a lot of financial advice lately,
but it's really boring, so I want you to consider this.
An investment, right?
It's something that you set aside and it comes back stronger.
Literal definition, right?
Stock market is gambling and a distraction from the real shit.
Let me give you this first tip, diversity.
Feel like you missed out on Bitcoin or GME,
early Google, those golden gooses.
Well, don't be, because you don't have a crystal ball.
You can't know if that shit's going to explode.
What you do know is that over time,
stocks rise and fall while the market always grows.
Don't bother searching for that needle.
Just buy the haystack.
Diversity.
Secondly, you want to get a Roth IRA and cap it yearly.
M1 Finance is a good service for this.
Consider you put in 6K a year into one of these accounts
for 30 years.
Once you put in about 180K with proper investments
and diversity, your total is going to be at around
a million dollars for doing fucking nothing.
Once you're 60 years old, you can withdraw from this account
tax-free and live a good life.
If you need money short-term, this is, of course, less useful,
but if you have 6K a year, you can put aside
and don't expect to die before you're 60, this is what you want.
I have a Roth IRA.
I didn't cap it last year.
I'm like stunned at just like the extreme change in tone
when someone who actually has a brain between their ears
speaks on the show.
I'm like, whoa, where am I?
I'm afraid.
I need an adult.
But the adult left the voicemail.
He didn't say it into an auto-tuner though.
How am I supposed to take this seriously?
You know that's fair.
He wasn't playing the piano.
This is, I mean, the diversity thing, like that's similar
to the index fund thing that Doublecast said.
This is great advice, but I make less than 6K a year total.
So I'm very polling.
How do you make less than 6K a year total?
Because I make $300 a month on Patreon, like $200 a month on this show.
Add that up times 12.
That's what I make per year.
Tragic, tragic.
The index fund, well, the index fund is just a single fund
that is tied to the market.
Diversifying is like different, but similar.
I mean, that's pretty much what Minerva said,
was the market always grows and an index fund is like how you get in on that.
I have been saying that I want to do that for like months now,
and I have not actually got, not months, a month, a month and a half.
I don't know, sounds reasonable.
Thanks, Mr. Investments.
The next voicemail is called Kringus Real.
Three, two, one, go.
Oi, basically, it's me, your friend, Kringus Abengus.
Oh, there he is.
I know that voice anywhere.
I wanted to talk all about Kring and bugging that this week.
But first, I want to bring this up.
Someone called in on the voicemails pretending to be me,
and how do you fall for that?
I don't know, how did that happen?
You're a smart guy.
I just was so caught up in the need of the moment.
But it is not a big deal.
I just, I was hurt a little bit by it.
Listen, if you could just, just listen to me like,
I apologize.
What if I send you a mini French?
Let me get to my week.
This week, oh man, let me tell you,
I cringed so hard at the US government.
I cannot believe what they're up to.
It's crazy.
It's real bad.
Anyway, are you suggesting that this is not the Kringus bingus?
That we know and love?
I can't tell for sure.
It's fantastic.
That's a serious accusation.
It's pretty great.
That's what I did this week.
I'll tell you what I cringed and bugging that next week.
So keep it up.
He said it again.
Kringus bingus, a pleasure as always to hear from you.
You are a light at the end of a dark tunnel of each week
of being a member of the PCB.
Right now I'm doing the Philip J. Fry shifty eyes look face.
That's slander and libel that you would make that face
even in private.
Well, sue me.
Do it.
The court, the court, the court, the court will hear the case
of Kringus bingus versus give and take.
All, all rise.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called the monopoly man.
Three, two, one, go.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
Here's the monopoly man.
Oh, I love money.
It's me.
What do I also love?
Bribing politicians.
If you're in the league of Nate Fockers, send a voicemail
and become president.
I will sponsor you with 2000 Dutch coin.
This is 2000 Dutch coin for the best voicemail.
Ho, ho, ho.
This was the monopoly man.
Okay.
Humble beginnings of a new character.
What's dogecoin at right now?
Is it, is he saying dogecoin?
A little under six cents, or at least it was.
Uh, yeah.
Oh, it's kind of just, it's kind of just hung around at like 50.
Yeah, it's up to, it's up to a little under six cents.
So 2000.
So what is, what is 2000 dogecoin worth?
It's worth about, that's about $100.
What, wait a minute.
What the fuck?
I just went to Google calculator and there's like a,
a sparkly little pie symbol that you can press.
It's because it's pie day.
It's March 14th.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's like a little like game or something where like it types pie in for you.
Uh, one, four, one, five, nine, two, six.
Did I get it right?
One, four, four, one, five.
I know all the digits of pie.
Oh, it like, it wants you to type the rest of the digits and it will like give you a little like red button if you hit the wrong one.
Okay.
Very cute.
Very cute Google.
The digits of pie are 3.12.
Prove it.
Nope.
Okay.
Yeah.
Next voicemail is called pick cross at work.
Three, two, one.
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't see that one.
It's on the next page.
You don't?
Yeah.
Oh, lol.
We got more of these.
Three, two, one.
Go.
Gib, what do you like do in pick cross when it's a square that you have to guess to solve?
Like it's either each corner or the other corner.
Like you lose.
I can't get my dick hard when I'm forecasting at work and I just can't do these puzzles.
Damn.
What do I do?
The unfortunate reality is that with a randomly generated puzzle of pick cross you stand to
sometimes have to guess and it sucks when you do.
Just like minecraft.
I've gotten mine sweeper.
Mine sweeper.
You mean?
Minecraft.
Like you just play the game and then you get right to the end of a 25 by 25 pick cross board.
You've done everything perfectly and it took like three hours, not three hours, but like
a while to think about all the numbers involved and then there was swirling around your head
and you were thinking like, ah, squares and numbers.
This is very intellectual.
And then you get right to the end.
You have to make a coin flip.
You fail and you just die.
That's what happens.
That's what you do.
Beautiful.
Inspirational.
This is why Sudoku is the only like perfect one, but it is a little, you know, I'm tired
of Sudoku.
I'm too good at it.
Because there's no, because there's no guessing in Sudoku.
There's never any guessing.
If it's, I mean, I think it's impossible to make a Sudoku that can be like fucked up
because all the numbers have to fit.
Yeah.
This is why Pokemon, the competitive Pokemon is the ultimate sport because there's never
any random chance.
There's never any guessing.
The winner is always the better player 100% of the time.
Stone edge always hits and that's just a fact.
Next one is called riches beyond your wildest dreams.
Three, two, one, go.
All right.
I gave this a little more thought about that financial advice I was giving earlier and
I realized it's bad, disregarded.
Oh, shit.
Here's the thing.
Here's the real advice.
No one comes to this fucking podcast for financial advice.
They come here to hear Ben St. talk about how he lost a million dollars again every
single week.
So I wasted my time.
I wasted your time.
I wasted all of our time.
I'm very sorry.
He should be.
Fuck you.
He's trying to ruin the podcast.
He's trying to ruin the podcast by making me financially solvent.
You see a future in your mind's eye of like Ben St. saying, ah, yes, my index fund, my
special money thingy has made me more money.
Haha.
My 401k is taken off.
Yes.
Everything's going up.
No house for me.
Ben St.
My money's doing great.
How am I supposed to guilt people into giving me another mini fridge?
I earned that mini fridge.
I earned that mini fridge by achieving the end.
By achieving the end of Noida, all those hundreds of hours I've put into Noida, we're
just training to win that mini fridge from Chalupa Coon.
Doing the math, you made like 16 cents an hour earning that mini fridge for all the
hours you put into Noida.
But you know what they say?
You work, do what you love and you never work a day in your life.
And for me, that's playing Noida for a mini fridge.
So jokes on them.
Next voicemail is from Ren, three, two, one, go.
Do I have a speech impediment or are microphones just fed?
This thing costs 70 EU credits and I still don't recognize my voice.
It's like a stranger, we call it this.
And neither my neighbors nor the traffic in front of the house are helping.
If by speech impediment, you mean your German accent, then yes.
You kind of sound like you have a lisp and that could be the microphone.
So I don't know.
How does a microphone create a lisp?
I don't know.
Maybe just made it sound fuzzy.
Yeah.
Well, he said he seemed to be suggesting that he does not have a speech impediment and yet
he sounds like he does in the microphone.
And he did kind of sound like he had a bit of a lisp, which is that maybe that's what
he's talking about with the microphone.
Or maybe he just has one and he's just in denial about it.
I just don't know.
It could also be the recording location if there's cars driving by and you're like noise
removing that would fuck up a little bit of stuff, deleting noise removal can fuck
you up.
Scrubbing data from it.
Try recording inside of a closet where there's dampening clothing.
Try put that like foam egg crates up all of your walls to suck up the extra noise.
Make a pillow for it and record in there.
Record at midnight when you can scream as loud as you want and wake your parents up.
The only time where you can scream as loud as you want is when you will get in trouble
for it.
Got to live on the edge.
Next voicemail is called cross browser extensions three, two, one, go.
What are some browser extensions that you use and that you think everyone should use?
None.
Well, I have an ad block and that's the only one that I feel strongly about.
Oh, no, wait, I have two that I can recommend.
First one is sponsor block for YouTube.
It's a great extension.
If you're sick of hearing ads for RAID Shadow Legends, this is like a crowd aggregate thing
where they'll automatically mark where sponsor segments are in YouTube videos and automatically
skip them.
Super great.
That's actually based.
Sponsor block.
Super good.
The other one, better Twitter.
You can block retweets, you can block ads, you can block all those things and just get
all the bullshit out of your Twitter feed so it's just original content from the people
you follow, which is why I'm there in the first place.
Holy shit, that's so good.
That's super good.
Okay.
I'm tempted by that one.
Aside from ad block is speed dial, which is just like when you open a new tab, there's
like all of the websites you frequent in like a little grid and you just click on them.
I've actually used it that much recently though.
I've taken to like opening a new tab and then typing the first letter of the website I want
to go to and then it auto completes.
Yeah.
Like if I type why it goes to YouTube.
So really nothing, get nothing, get what Tom said.
Did you guys see that like they're making another Simpsons episode that changes Homer's
teenage years?
I was just looking at a tweet.
They moved.
Okay.
They've moved it up.
This is the current year the Simpsons were born in, Homer 1985, Marge 1987, Bart 2011,
Lisa 2013, Maggie 2020.
God is dead and we need to die too.
So I remember there was like a when we were young Simpsons where it's like Homer Marge
and they're listening to Nirvana and it's the nineties or whatever.
Yeah.
That was the most recent.
So they already did this once.
Is there another one?
Like new one.
There's a new one.
Yeah, there's a new one.
Yeah.
Are they playing Minecraft?
What are they doing?
Well, I mean, it would be in the nineties.
So no, it wouldn't be playing Minecraft, but like Homer's got like hip hop posters on his
walls.
He's got posters for the Humpty Dance and Naughty by Nature, which is fine, I guess.
They should just go full insane and like implied that the Simpsons is now taking place in
the future and like Homer and Marge were Zoomers.
This is so bad.
I don't know.
Like fucking the whole like the Homer's mom's backstory like doesn't make any sense if she's
not like a hippie.
So like what the fuck is this?
It's all not canon anymore.
It's been uncannonized.
The Simpsons is like a Abe Simpson is like is very is very like obviously like a greatest
generation guy.
And now he's now he's like Gen X like fuck, no, it just doesn't work.
It just doesn't work.
I'm sorry.
Simpsons right now is like if you copy paste something like a billion times like it loses.
It's like it's sort of like a facsimile of the original thing, but it doesn't make any
sense.
And it's just sort of lost a lot of like JPEG artifacts all over it.
You know that when you like copy a video, you download a video, you uploaded it like
a hundred thousand times.
It becomes like a weird blob.
Oh, yeah.
Sure.
Yeah.
It's like they it's like they think like we need to set.
We need to change the time it's set in for it to continue to be relevant, but it's not
relevant.
I think there's the unfortunate thing about it is that it implies and it's probably true
that people who watch the Simpsons on TV will not have time nor the inclination to watch
all of the Simpsons.
So why would we keep continuity?
There's no reason.
And now now people may not have a reason to go back and watch the parts of the Simpsons
that are good.
I guess the whole point is that it's a parody on like modern family interactions.
And so by having them be 20 years older than what an average family of their age is supposed
to be, it loses relevance.
But I feel like the Simpsons have been around so long, like they've kind of become characters
in and of themselves and shifting them to match the current times almost feels like
a betrayal of the legacy of the characters.
I guess it's a fair question.
Like who is the average viewer of like the new episodes of the Simpsons in twenty twenty
one.
And it probably is like it's probably not like people who have been watching since the early
nineties.
Yeah.
It's a new audience watching the same show.
And like there's so many episodes that there's it's like not a given thing that somebody
who gets into the Simpsons will want to go back and watch everything.
So they're not they're not treating it like it's something that needs to do that anymore.
See, they should have just had Bart and Lisa grow up and they should be the main characters
now as adults.
And then we could have just had a continuing timeline of all these characters actually growing
and changing and evolving.
Well, well, that wouldn't be relatable because canonically Lisa grows up to become president
and Bart grows up to become chief chief justice of the Supreme Court.
So that would be like a really fucked up show.
That'd be like the West Wing.
We can't have.
Damn.
You got me.
Yeah.
Sorry.
I've owned you at Simpsons trivia.
I wonder though because like I've seen like three episodes of the Simpsons so it's not
hard to beat me.
Really?
You haven't.
That's fucked up.
That's so fucked up.
I was a big Simpsons head.
I watched it all growing up until about until I went to college and then I pretty much fell
off it.
Which which episodes were they actually?
Do you remember?
What do you mean?
The episodes that I've seen.
Yeah.
I think I've seen the one where like everyone thinks Mr. Burns is an alien.
That one was kind of cool.
I remember that one sticking out in my brain a lot.
Oh, yeah.
Remember that one?
The one with the Mulder and Scully guest stars, right?
Maybe?
It's been so fucking long.
I watched these like at like 12, just like they happened to be on after like cartoons
and I would just keep watching until my parents like this isn't for you and they would turn
it off.
Oh.
God.
Okay.
I don't know if I even remember the specifics of any other ones.
There's like one Krusty the Clown episode like I remember the itchy and scratchy show
coming on a couple of times in some episodes, but I don't even remember the general context
of these episodes.
Just remember bits and pieces.
Simpsons is like so good at it's like the reason it's gone on so long is because it
had such a good string of seasons early on.
So I would encourage anyone who's not gotten into the Simpsons to like try some earlier
stuff.
See if there's like a few because like as a as a teenager or an adult, there's so many
things that are like clever funny jokes they pick up on for when you're a kid, maybe things
would go over your head.
Maybe you'd find the physical humor interesting like there's so many clever so much clever
writing in there.
It's really good.
I watched a video earlier this week about it was a it was like a moderately big YouTube
channel who people might have heard of.
I don't remember, but it was he he he ranks every Simpsons episode like every single
one like all 600 plus of them.
He goes through each one in order and like gives his thoughts on them.
And then at the end he ranks them.
The channel was like LS something, whatever, it was like a pretty no, it wasn't like a Simpsons
channel.
It was just like a general like, like, like culture, like cartoon, culture, commentary
Oh, hold on, ranking every Simpsons episode.
It is the channel is, yeah, LS mark, who I'd never heard of before I saw this video just
popped up in my recommends and I was like, that sounds like a good way to kill six hours.
It's okay.
I think I was working while I was listening to it.
So it's fine.
It was a decent video, though, it was good.
I recommend it.
I recommend it, but he gets he gets really fed up.
He gets really fed up with the show.
Probably even like earlier, like people say this show got bad around like season 10, but
he's like, he's starting to get like fed up with its bullshit, even by season like, I
don't know, like seven or eight, I think, lol.
And then there's the end then there's like so much left to go after that and he like just
hates it.
It's pretty solid.
Anything for the cloud.
I mean, it's a solid concept for a video.
Wish I'd thought of it.
You wouldn't have finished like you stopped for your Winnie the Pooh series.
I did.
I'm too much of a bitch.
I should have made one big 10 hour video where I like ranking every episode of Winnie
the Pooh.
That's true.
That's the way to do it.
It probably would have been better for views.
You could still do that, I guess.
I still kind of intend to finish the at least season one of the Pooh videos just because
I said I would.
I don't know when I'll do it, but like maybe after I finish a couple other things, I said
I would do it and I feel bad not having done something that I said I would do.
So I might just bang some out at some point just just for the memes.
I don't know.
Every now and then I still get a comment or two on those videos and I'm like, how are
they finding me?
These are people that are completely removed.
These are people I've never heard of before.
They're not PCP viewers.
They're not like Chris Chan people.
They're just like, they're just some hardcore Winnie the Pooh fans who just like, I need
some dank Winnie the Pooh content and they just find your shit.
Where's that poo?
Yeah.
They're poo heads.
I need that poo.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess that's why I made the videos is to get people like that.
But like it didn't, since I got so few of them, whenever one pops up in my comments,
I'm like, really?
Really?
You're here?
Why?
No.
You're all alone.
Yeah.
I like Winnie the Pooh.
I'm Gen X.
We exist.
Next voicemail, by the way, is called spiral three, two, one, go.
Do you guys know the name of the ice type gym leader from Diamond and Pearl?
I can't remember her name.
From Diamond.
Help me out.
Ice cream.
Weird that you confused our voicemails for Google.
Wait, there's got to be some joke here.
There's got to be a joke, right?
Let's see.
Ice type gym leader.
What's Gen 4?
Is it Hoenn?
Yeah.
No, no.
That's Gen 3.
No.
No?
What?
It's Sinnoh, right?
Sinnoh's Gen 4?
Oh, okay.
It's Candice.
It's the gym leader of Snowpoint City's Gym, officially known as the Snowpoint Gym.
Her name is Candice.
It's got an ice pun in there.
Great.
I guess.
That's what a voicemail fucker.
If he had titled the thing nuts, it'd be like Candice nuts, like Candice nuts.
I don't know.
I don't know what he was going for.
Maybe.
Fail.
Epic.
Yeah.
Epic fail.
Next voicemail is called Advice for Custodian Bro.
Three, two, one, go.
If you're looking for a new direction in life, maybe a new line of work, if you have low education,
low skills, I would definitely recommend looking for employment in a bar or a restaurant
as a server, a waiter, a waitress.
Well, this advice doesn't work for everyone, but I can tell you that being a server in
a restaurant is actually a great job.
It's one of the few jobs where your boomer parents' advice of knocking doors and shaking
hands actually fucking works.
Get a haircut, groom yourself as best you can, put on a shirt with buttons and some
nice jeans, and then literally walk into every restaurant in your area.
Ask someone there for the manager, and then ask the manager if they're hiring.
Give them a resume and fill out the application, and I can almost promise by the end of the
week you will have a job.
Being a server, it can be tough work, but it's easy to pick up and learn, and you can
make good money.
The nicer the restaurant you work at, the more money you make, so walk into the nice
ones first.
Walk into your fucking local PF chains or whatever.
Then once you're in there, ask if you can move into the bar.
You can bar back to start and then move into bartender.
I was bartending with low education, low skills, and I was clearing easily $1,000 a week because
I was in a good spot.
Just something to try.
Hopefully, that works out for you for anyone looking for a new job.
Good luck.
This is ... I mean, I guess it's true that maybe someone might want to change things
up for themselves and get a new job and stop being a custodian and become a restaurant
server.
Maybe, but that's such basic advice.
Like, oh, if you're looking for a job, walk into restaurants and ask if they're hiring.
Yeah.
Maybe it's so obvious that it bears repeating just because some people wouldn't think of
it, I guess.
That seems like basic advice to me.
Yeah, sometimes what people need.
I'm not impressed.
I guess so.
I mean, I think I would hate to be a bartender, but I'm sure for some people it's a great
job, but they would enjoy a lot, so whatever.
I'm bad with people, so I'm glad that I studied the arts and I could maybe do that instead.
Something that allows me to avoid talking to people is good.
Additional advice, this next one is called Additional Advice, three, two, one, go.
And if you're sitting there thinking, oh no, I don't have any experience with that, there's
no way a place will hire me.
I promise you, a ton of people, their first job is being a waiter in a restaurant.
If you've been a custodian and are working 12-hour days, every single restaurant manager
will want to hire you.
It means that you are willing to work hard, you can take orders, and you're not afraid
to do gross things to get a job done, which sometimes as a server, you have to do when
you have to do extra cleaning and clean bathrooms and shit.
I feel like this guy is assuming a lot, this guy seems really confident that the custodian
guy would much prefer to work in a restaurant than to be a custodian, and I don't think
that's necessarily true.
So you can make new friends and you can potentially find a roommate there.
You can get you out of your parent's house.
Also regulars at the bar and restaurant, if you're there long enough, you get to know
them.
I've had plenty of job offers come from regulars, I come into my restaurants and bars.
So you can pursue other options off of that, you don't have to be a tip slave for the rest
of your life if you don't want to be either.
Good luck out there, man, it's tough, but I know you can do it, I know you can make a
better life for yourself.
You're working hard right now, you just got to put that hard work in a slightly different
direction.
You got this.
Okay, the thing about working in a restaurant, like you need more people, that was like
surprising me uplifting at the end, I was like, whoa.
I guess he has a point there.
Yeah, I mean, it may be obvious, but sometimes you just go through life and you miss all
the obvious advice, and then you just don't know what to do.
I mean, when you're in your own shit, it's hard to see out of it.
This voicemail is called A Request, A Recommendation, 3, 2, 1, go.
Despite the current state of the PCP, you guys should still do some extracurricular PCP
video game content, whether it be a pick, cross race, or a minesweeper game of attrition.
Even if it is just Ben, Gib, and Tom, it would be fun to watch.
Ben, you like roguelikes, you should play Tower Climb, Gay Rights, Trans Rights, BLM,
AKF, you get it just.
Cool.
Tower Climb, I've never heard of that.
I wonder what you do in it.
Is it the opposite of Downwell?
Hmm.
All right, I got the Steam page up.
It's the sequel to Downwell, Tower Climb.
A roguelike platformer, five years in the making.
I mean, from first glance, yeah, it looks like the kind of game I would enjoy, so how
much does it cost?
$15, highway robbery.
Even Noida was only 10.
Wait, no, Noida was 20, lol.
All right, I'll put it on my wishlist.
Next voice.
Wait, as for gaming content, I mean, is it spoiler to say we're going to do the Minecraft
thing?
I mean, the minesweeper thing?
We've already said it.
I think it's...
Oh, okay.
We're going to do a both episode minesweeper.
Minesweeper challenge, challenge run.
Who's going to blow things up?
Who's going to blow up on social media?
Who's going to get viral?
Who's going to get coronavirus?
All of these questions are one or the other.
Okay, next voicemail is called folk punk album recommendations, three, two, one, go.
People who eat people are the luckiest people in the world, rogue taxidermy, death and hatred
to mankind, the city isn't big enough, probably nothing, possibly everything, gay rights,
but that's not an album recommendation.
Okay, thanks for the album recommendations.
I've never listened to folk punk, but I will probably forget everything you just said.
Is folk punk like go go bordello?
It's probably just the aesthetic of punk, but without the electricity, acoustic guitar.
I think it's probably punk rock, but with an aesthetic tinged with some kind of flavor
of some kind of folk musical tradition or something, go go bordello is the one that
jumps to mind.
It's like that music, like the ukulele with a xylophone, like ding ding ding, happy advertisement
friendly corporate bullshit, but then there's a guy screaming like fuck everything.
Like Borat, bing bong bing bong bing, right?
Yeah, exactly like that.
Yeah, nice.
I've never heard of any of those albums, lol.
Okay, next voicemail is called Trying If This Shit Works, 3, 2, 1, go.
You're a fucking criminal.
You're a fucking criminal, you know that?
It's literally just a test.
Voice jail, voice jail, voice jail.
This is serious business, you're fucking it up, you're fucking up everything.
Oh my god, we have so many more to go and that wasted 30 seconds of my day.
There's not that many, there's like 100, nah, okay, we're good.
Next one is called Fuck'em, 3, 2, 1, go.
Okay, Ben, I just checked out the Twitter account of that person that tried to cancel
you, and it's pretty much either like apologizing for stupid microaggressions or trying to cancel
people or the stupid microaggressions, and I just want to say these are the people that
you're trying to appease, and I want to tell you to stop because you can't, fuck'em.
I don't know which person you mean, if you mean that one, if you mean the one I'm thinking
of with the pink display picture, I wasn't trying to appease that person, fuck that person.
I don't apologize to that fucking white snowflake for anything.
If you mean someone else though, I'm not sure.
I, a bunch of them were shit, but I think some of them had a point, and that's what
I did, and that's what I, and that's fucking, I'm not appeasing anyone, I'm being true to
myself and my spirit.
I don't think getting canceled is a good excuse to not take responsibility for the things
you say, just because some people are really shitty about it.
I don't know whether this guy meant that by saying fuck'em.
You could just be these specific people, but I don't know, I see that idea a lot, they're
never gonna, like they is in like a large random assortment of people, very vague, just
like, oh just don't worry about doing all this stuff that pisses them off, don't ever
apologize no matter what, it's like, well sometimes you do say the wrong thing.
The fact that some of them are shitty, I mean doesn't mean that those shitty people are
wrong about everything.
That one though, that one really pissed me off, it's the one I think you're talking about,
but um.
Yeah some people definitely are like way too into the cancel culture mode on Twitter, they
just don't do anything else with their time on there.
Um, okay next, wait a minute, next, what the fuck is this?
Next one is a link, ah, this is gonna give me a virus, this is a link to an mp3, okay
I will just put this, I will put this in the chat for you guys, here we go, it's called
UwuLilliaStrikesAgain, it is uploading, give it a second, okay here we go, why don't you
just leave a fucking voicemail, oh my god, alright, uh, three, two, one, go.
Oof, me, wait, um, listen, we need to talk.
I'm not actually an anarcho-capitalist, just to be clear on that.
No, no, uh, we're fine, it's just that I'm, you know, lately, cooking Michelle just hasn't
really been doing it for me anymore, oh well, so um, I thought, you know, displace things
up a little bit, I'd bring a friend.
Yeah?
Okay, alright, he's just totally cool with it.
Which member of the league was that?
Was it Mike the Microphone, or uh, Mike the Microphone's a Brody, oh, no, there's also
those were all the voice clips from the ComeZone video, Welcome to the ComeZone.
Oh, okay, yeah, okay, so I don't actually know who did that, I don't know if, I don't
think it's OblivionFull themselves who said this, uh, man, just, uh, cooking Michelle
just isn't good enough anymore, okay, I see, go on.
Okay, guys, Nate's back, he's back on the podcast.
Wait a minute.
Nate's back and he's getting fucked.
You can't say, no Nate, no watch this week.
There he is, there he is, uh, what's his name in the comments.
Now we'll know if you say it, if you say it, you didn't watch the whole episode.
Well, I respect that guy in the comments who every week comes back, I respect the dedication,
I've got, I've turned around on him and I'm pro that guy, uh, where is the, uh,
Same, honestly, it's, it's like, that he never like, like blossoms into anything bullshit
like extra, it's just like the same thing every time, if this is the case, then I will
say this.
He's on message, he's on brand, he's consistent, he's not trying to link his like social media
underneath every post, you know, don't give him ideas though.
He's just a pillar, he's just a pillar of the community.
Next voicemail is called speediest voicemail, three, two, one, go.
Uh, R-I-P-C-P, May max clutch, cars run like shit, I think I just got a speeding ticket
early tonight.
Ah, let's do this.
No, oh god, oh dear, this is awful, I hate this, I'd like to think he's just sitting
in his gamer chair playing like Forza Horizon right now, I'm scared, I'm scared there's
going to be like a crashing sound, that's 100 miles per hour, 160 kilometers per hour,
uh, when's the last time you're absolutely reckless, all right, I gotta get out, I gotta
get out of this cool side, yeah, there's one, I was reckless, I was reckless just yesterday,
no it was Friday, I was reckless on Friday, I went out, I left my house, in the middle
of a pandemic, I risked COVID-19 to hang out with people in the Boston Common, uh, in
the fresh air, the poisoned air, uh, I hope I don't get any viruses, uh, oh yeah, you
were with Munchin Kazian stuff, and Azcan, yes, yes, uh, it was nice though, it was nice
though because Azcan picked me up, I thought I was going to have to, I wasn't going to
risk the tea, I wasn't going to risk that, but I thought I was going to have to get an
Uber, which is like, I mean that's not that risky, it was a little, it seemed a little
eh, but I didn't have to, Azcan picked me up, uh, I don't know, I didn't go near anyone,
we just went to the Boston Common, hung out, and then came back to my house, and I was
fucked around my backyard, like we usually do, uh, so that was me, that was uh, if I
die, that's why, that's what did it, it's Munchie's fault, lol, what about you guys,
have you been reckless lately, have you drove a hundredth of any school zones, nah, I don't
be reckless that often, yeah my life is boring and uninteresting, if you're not, if you're
not at least, if you're not at least a little likely to get COVID-19, then what are you even
doing, what are you, then what are you thinking, I mean I went outside a little bit, ah there
we go, but it wasn't like that reckless, I went on like the train and I just had my
mask on and I kept it to myself and it was fine, I went to play D&D yesterday with five
other people in a tiny space and none of us were masked up, I guess that's almost reckless,
I really don't want to go on the T until I'm vaccinated, like that seems like, that seems
like a super bad place to go if you want to like avoid, like going out in the common like
it's like, it's outside, outside's not that dangerous, the T seems like the exact place
that like tons and tons of people are constantly shuffling around, breathing on shit, I know
people don't consistently wear their masks, because I did wear, I did ride the T one time,
it was when I went to that George Floyd March thing, I rode the T that day and the fucking
guys on there weren't wearing their masks and I was like, I don't know about this, so
I don't want to avoid that until I got this shit in my arm, but I'll fucking go out to
a park, I mean that's fine, that's fine, I am like not a very much of a risk taker, I
get cautious feelings when I was like, oh no, I could be doing something bad, what if
I get hurt and I'm far away from people, I should go, I should head back, you know that
sort of feeling, I feel a little guilty that I'm not epic, but at the same time I'm alive,
so I don't know, I don't know how to feel about it sometimes.
Being dead is the least epic state of being, but I don't really seek thrills.
I guess there's like a pressure to like, oh if you don't seek thrills you're not, you
know, cool or whatever, I'm like, well I guess I don't and maybe that's bad.
Cautious feelings should be the title of your debut album, I'd never release it, it'll be
too reckless of me, yeah, yeah, too embarrassing, next voicemail is called Advice, 3, 2, 1, go.
Kill yourself.
No, that's the most reckless thing of all, that's the feckless thing to do, what if you
fucked up and you're just paralyzed for life, that's what I think about when I think about
killing myself, just make sure you do the job properly, that's not, that's not worse
than being dead, that's not worse, I would say it is, I mean they both, they're both
unfortunate states, I think being dead is about the worst state.
If I was paralyzed I would ask for mercy killing.
I probably wouldn't.
I would, absolutely.
You should ask for robot legs.
I mean I'm already like partially crippled and I already think about suicide, like man
this sucks, I don't like this, I don't like being able to, not be able to run anymore,
the zombie apocalypse happens, I'm so fucked, I mean that's an outside possibility, that's
an outside chance, you're worried about, this is nonsense.
COVID was step one dude, it's happening.
You, hey, fuck you for telling me your feelings, they're not valid.
No, that's fair.
Yeah, you're white, get fucked.
Next one is called Let's Be Frank Ferda, three, two, one, go.
I am in the center of the Shepi, Bingzirk and PC or Turkey, go.
To explain, a long time ago you and me had this row where we talked about creativity
and ideas, specifically, we had no plans or like any idea of how they would actually
work, the existence of the idea was funny enough, for me, that was why YouTube series
was all about war, I was going to combine more and more of a footage of Sonic, I said
yeah, yeah, didn't know how to do it and really didn't have any plans to do it, you obviously
didn't hear it, my mic was terrible and my mobile phone quite a bit.
I hate you.
Why did you double it up?
I could barely understand that.
I feel like that was an accident, it had to be an accident, right?
I also think it was an accident, I thought it was on purpose at first, but I decided
it was an accident.
There was nothing funny about it, it was a legit question, there's no reason to echo
that.
There was nothing funny about the echo and also why did it cut off there?
I don't understand, it seemed like the voicemail ended before the question was done.
Didn't we have a voicemail about this project before?
This sounds familiar, sad AM over something that's ringing a bell in the deep recesses
of my brain that still unfortunately can't let go of voicemails.
It sounds like he did make a voicemail about it before, but he said his mic was bad, so
maybe we did hear it.
Was that the joke that the mic was purposely bad this time?
I don't know.
I genuinely didn't understand anything that he said.
If you think a thing would be funny, you should make it and post it on YouTube and maybe it'll
go viral, that's my...
And I'm sorry about your microphone, please don't do this to me again.
Okay, next voicemail, I don't even want to listen to it, but I guess I have to, it's
called It's Okay Ben, I know that you're not racist, lol, 3, 2, 1, go.
Konnichiwa.
This was Summoner-san.
Benno Sento-san.
You have been cancelled for racism.
Noto Teru.
Benno Sento-san.
Noto Resisto.
He treated you.
He communist.
He corrected of a baby for skin.
But noto Resisto.
Thank you.
Benno Sento-san.
He know that despite being only 13% of the population, Usapu make up 50% of the
imperial down population.
Really make you think.
Okay, until you next time.
Sayonara.
This reminds me of somebody who was talking about it and someone else posted it in my
discord.
A video that was played at CPAC of a Japanese guy calling Donald Trump the last American
samurai and saying how honorable he was and how he wants to... wait, Gabe, have you seen
this?
Yeah, I was talking about it last time.
Were you... oh, that's where I heard it, I'm so stupid, lol.
I actually, someone posted it in my discord and I watched it and I just thought, American
samurai, whoever heard of such an outlandish thing.
You say, as you stroke the Kawasaki scrolls.
Yeah, I mean, I mean, I'm Teru Teru, so noto samurai anymore.
Cancel it again, can't use that accent.
No, it's funny, it's funny.
That voice is based on offensive stereotypes because it's how Japanese actually sounds in
real life.
Next voicemail is called Jebediah Prickinson is still alive, unfortunately.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, this is me, Jebediah Prickinson.
I'm here to say done.
Can't kill myself anymore.
Though, I guess, did Jenae slash Trixie's live an asshole bitch now?
Okay, release the groaning lecture you weasel know.
Oh dear.
Alright.
Okay, thanks, Jebediah.
Sorry you can't kill yourself anymore, but thanks for the voicemail.
Next one is called No More Lies, a league of n-fuckers.
Oh wait, I think this is- it's asterisk asterisk n, so I don't know-
It sounded a little bad.
No, three, two, one, go.
I will really, really, really, really react to it.
Okay.
Shit.
Shit, I didn't mean to give consent, but I did.
Oh, damn.
We all know that once consent is given it can never be withdrawn. It's open season on my asshole
The gates of hell have been thrown wide open if you know what I mean
Next voicemail is called the real question pulling back the curtain unveiling the three two one go
Hey guys, I just wanted to know what is the ratio between normal porn and hentai? Do you guys usually
Consume on a weekly basis. They're asking for myself. Goodbye
Hmm
Normal porn to hentai ratio
I
Mean I don't think I yeah, like define nor did they just mean like live-action? I would assume. I think I think he means live-action
Okay
Yeah, it's it's more hentai than it is and I suppose
Yeah, I mean
Zero like zero to one. I think it's probably more hentai because I just like I like a
Manga the I like the comic form for it and I I go for that a lot of the time more so than than for
videos, so
Man's probably my ratio is probably like
three to one
for for hentai lol
Tom I'm trying to think this is a very important question
Yeah, it's probably probably similar to your answer. I think I think it's probably
Wow, maybe like we're all we're all in the same two to one three to one something like that
I mean, we're all art people so like you can appreciate the artistry at the same time, you know
It's like it's like a dual
That's not what I go to fucking that's not what I fucking jerk it to know like oh line with the line weights are so dynamic
I don't know once you're once you're done. You can reflect on it be like, you know, that was some pretty good line
I mean, I
Mean there is definitely there are definitely art styles that are like
Bad to the point that I'm like I this is this is impacting my enjoyment
for sure and there are some artists who I think are good and I think is sexier
But whatever I don't think about that
but on
This looks like it's the last voicemail. It's called is my going to finally to you turn on on the brony lecture three two one go
To those waiting with baited breath for that favorite media catchphrase the u-turn I
Have only one thing to say
You turn if you want to
The ladies not for turning
Margaret Thatcher
What the fuck is she talking? I don't understand what any of that means. It's I don't know too much about that speech
But she was a asshole. She was a
Conservative fuck over the poor sort of lady
Yeah, yeah, her and Reagan best buddies
The yeah, I don't get it
Okay, then there's a dumb
Here's the context. This is a Wikipedia article on this the ladies not for turning was a phrase used by Margaret Thatcher in her speech to the
Conservative Party conference in 1980 the term has been applied as a name to the speech in its entirety
The phrase made reference to Thatcher's refusal to perform a u-turn in response to opposition to her liberalization of the economy
Which some commenters as well as her predecessors
Conservatively that Ted Heath had urged because unemployment had risen to two million by the autumn of 1980. Oh
Okay, so
All right, all she's saying is my critics say that I should stop
privatizing industry
Just because it's destroying the economy and making everyone unemployed and to that I say the lady is not for turning
We're going forward. No u-turns here. So to that I say no
based as fuck
No
Yeah, exactly
Some people say I should do something and I say I will not
God what a powerful speech
The Margaret Thatcher really had girl power is all I'm saying. She was a girl boss of her age of her time
Absolutely the girl boss if you if you will the first woman ever
The first woman ever to ruin Great Britain
Yeah
Oh, we just got another one we just got another voicemail. I would you know I've
Sorry, but it's called. Let's be frank further
three two one go I
Sent in being Zerk as a way to lament my cringe voicemail
I happen to have seen all of dirt gently sees one and the gut steam from the Zerk 97 sound fitting at the time
Apologies to Gringis Vegas. I was panicked and short on time because I procrastinated
I wanted the drama the name seppy by the way
I put my name in the voicemail because I thought there was a separate space for the title
My shower speed run personal best is
417.71
To be fair, I have a hard to damn cool afro
So I prefer to be in a different division if like a ball what what
You go cut off
What was the division cold?
Thanks for the voicemail
Different afro afro division like afro percent
Yeah, because I am at I
Am it probably does make it harder to shampoo if you have an afro. I believe it
Um
Well shit, I guess that's I guess that's the end of the voicemails. We we made it
Just closing
Any closing thoughts before we wrap this sucker up?
I don't like it when the PCP is too long and I get tired
Yeah, it's it's not it's not that long. We're under three hours. It's not it's just the voicemail
When the voicemail is dragged because I was only here for two hours and I already feel wiped
That's true. I feel white all the time. Oh, no
Bad that's that's bad
Okay
Go to speak pop comm
Slash PCP voicemail if you want to leave us a voicemail, but not too many
Cuz there's too many of them
Leave a voicemail if you're stupid
Definitely don't do that
and go to
patreon.com slash the procrastinators to pledge five adoradoo for bonus episodes, which will include
That other one you can hear me beat these guys at poker and also soon you will see me beat at
Mine Sweeper not minecraft mine. I'm gonna win. No win the day man
Victory victory will be mine. I promise and
Anything else?
Nope
Good night everyone sweet dreams and God bless us everyone. Bye. Bye
You