I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello, hello, hello America. Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast again. It's Sunday.
When we record this, we record this on Sunday.
Hello, everybody. It's the show. We're both dead, it sounds like.
Yeah, I just stayed up all night last night and then I got like two hours of sleep.
Not for any reason. I just didn't want to go to bed.
You like you do sometimes. So now I feel like shit for no gain, but that's okay.
That's okay. It's good actually.
No, it's not okay. I feel bad. I feel icky and sicky and sad.
Are you COVID free though?
Well, I think so. Yeah, I don't see any reason to think I wouldn't be COVID free at the moment.
Are you COVID?
No, completely avoided COVID.
So that's nice, although it does mean that yesterday, last week, yesterday, last episode, yesterday episode,
where I said, oh, I would be in the air. I could have flown. I just didn't know that I didn't already have it.
So I could have had fun in America with friends and instead I was depressed crying all the time on the floor.
I played Jack 2 on my PS4 and that was alright.
Jack 2 though. It's a great fun little game until you get to like one of five missions of the worst thing ever made.
I got to one and then I rage quit. I couldn't believe it. I couldn't stand it.
I was so tired of seething in real life. I didn't need to see that a video game as well.
I love Jack 2, although it's been a long, long time since I played it. I played the whole. I love the whole Jack series.
What a bizarre series. What a bizarre progression of games.
When I was young, it felt normal because I hadn't grown up with like, oh, the normal thing to do is to make Mario 64 and then Mario Sunshine.
When you're a kid, they can convince you anything's normal. Any fucked up shit. They want a big hand off to you.
So like going from a Banjo-Kazooie style collect-a-thon in different worlds to a GTA, Tony Hawk, free roaming city, murdering civilians and being like,
I'm Shadow the Hedgehog now. Bit weird. But it works.
It really does. I mean, it's got the same basic mechanics, right? It feels kind of the same to just run and jump around.
Kind of the same.
Spin dash and whatever.
I think the platforming doesn't have much of a role to play, obviously.
I think the hardest platforming comes in like, bits that you have to do with the jet board.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh yeah, the jet board. You have to fucking grind. You have to fucking grind every shit.
You can grind on railings. It's Tony Hawk GTA Banjo-Kazooie.
And then Jack-3 is just like that again, but bigger.
Yeah. I can't remember.
In Jack-3, they gave the big like dune buggy like vehicle. The huge driving areas, yeah.
Which was probably my favorite part of that game. They had the whole light eco as well, which you could fly and there was time stuff.
They had all these gimmicks built on the first game and the second game.
And they're like, okay, well, to make a third game, we have to build more gimmicks.
But I think it sort of got to a point where there's too many, too many different things.
I think they just needed to have the cars, the dune buggy stuff. But I don't know, whatever.
That's what you do when you're making a video game and you don't know what to put it.
You just put in big, big cars. That's what they did with Banjo-Kazooie.
Not some bolts, right?
Oh my God. They did.
It's the oldest trick in the book.
And then the Crash Team Racing. The dad with Crash Banjo-Kazooie as well.
Sure. Diddy Kong Racing?
Everybody goes in a car at some point. Even Mario. Mario got a car.
He did. Good for him. Good for him.
Yeah.
The mission I was playing, it might not be that hard for some people.
But it was like, you're in the drill platform, which is like a giant drill,
drilling around in the ground. And you can look down and it's down there.
And you're on a platform high above spinning around because the drill is spinning,
which is kind of fun as a cool level.
But this mission is you get into a little turret thing on a rail
and then you have to shoot these Crimson Guards jet pack guys.
And there's like a wave of 40 of them and they come from all around you.
And using the analog stick, it just sucks.
And I looked it up. It's like, how do I do this?
And it was like many forum posts of like, this is the hardest mission in the entire game.
Oh, I don't want to spend like three hours on this.
I'm going to go do nothing instead.
Man, I did.
Yeah.
And then there was a one after that, which...
That'll show those developers.
Yeah.
Fuck them.
I'm not going to get their fucking trophies.
I'm playing on the PS4.
I'm not going to 100% your shitty game suckers.
On the PS4 port of Jak 2, it's kind of terrible.
Not like the games fine, but it's just sort of like buggy and extremely laggy.
Like way laggier than the PS2 would be, which is sad.
Because eventually the PS2 will stop working.
True.
And the PS4 is relatively okay.
Yeah.
I guess I can emulate it. I think PS2 emulation is decent now.
Used to be like really...
Probably.
Really shaky.
Yeah.
But now it should be fine.
Whatever. Who cares about Jak 2? Me. That's who.
That's right. That's correct.
I just want to complain about the weather.
It's so fucking cold.
It's been so fucking cold here all week.
It's so cold that the cold is like seeping through my windows.
And my radiator and my space heater aren't even enough.
That sounds dreadful.
It is a little dreadful. It's down to like almost zero degrees.
And my...
I just build a fire, get some lugs, get some cold, build a fire on the floor.
My window's too big. I just want it to stop.
Just like stop. Just stop having the properties of glass you fuck.
Are they like shitty windows? They're like a single...
Well, they're not great. I don't know. Probably.
Yeah, they probably are shitty windows. I don't know.
Everything in my apartment is shitty.
But yeah, they're letting the cold in real good.
And then my radiator...
And then my fucking radiator.
Sometimes it gets so excited that it just starts clanging like really loud.
Like it sounds like it's exploding.
Like a loud clang noise.
Like a few feet away from my bed, so I'm just like...
Wakes me up at night.
I think I've complained about this before.
I probably will for the foreseeable future.
Is that for that be like water hammer?
Water hammer?
Where like a bubble of air is in the pipes.
And something or other causes like the water to slush around.
And like that movement.
The water goes really fast and then smashes into the end of the pipe.
I don't really know what I'm talking about.
And I'm...
Water hammer.
Because it's the sort of thing that would make a loud clang.
That's not as loud as it gets.
But you can't hear it?
Okay, well it's going.
That's not as loud as it gets.
Well okay, there is...
Water hammer is a phenomenon that occur in any piping system where valves are used to control the flow of the steam.
The result of a pressure surge.
Yeah, it even sounds like it.
That's interesting that there's a word for it.
Hydraulic shock colloquial water hammer is a pressure surger wave.
So like if...
I think there was a time where there was something like that in the plumbing in our house.
So I had to like...
The plumber had to come and let air out to the top.
He had to go to the top of the house and let air out.
So that there wouldn't be so much slushing around.
I don't know how that fixes it, but...
I guess if there's water everywhere, then water can't like accelerate and then stop suddenly.
Yeah, you fill in the air bubbles.
Yeah, I think so.
Did I mention that like a few weeks ago, or maybe like a month or two ago,
I had water leaking out of my fucking apartment ceiling?
You did, yeah.
I guess that wasn't really a saga because it surprisingly did get resolved fairly quickly.
That's the kind of thing that I can't like...
That's the kind of thing that you can't ignore.
That turned out to be...
I mean, you know, you see that and you're afraid that like a pipe has burst
and like some fucking sewage is leaking somewhere.
No, it was like condensation from like one of the radiator pipes.
It wasn't like too too gross or anything.
Just a bit.
I haven't had that happen anymore though.
Don't condensate.
The radiator does work.
It's just loud as fuck.
It's annoying.
You know, speaking of cold,
I've been watching Game of Thrones like I said last week.
I've been watching it.
I'm on season six now.
There's so many scenes that are like...
They're like north of the wall.
They're in the snow.
They're like white walkers in the wildlings and all that.
And they don't have...
They just have their coats and they're just walking and then they go to sleep
and there's no fire.
They would die.
They would just die if they didn't build a fire.
How do they even do anything?
It doesn't make sense.
It feels like a little stupid, a little silly.
Do you think that they shot it in like...
It wasn't as cold as it seemed?
Like they made the shot seem colder somehow?
I'm sure they were in cold locations.
But like, you know, the actors, they act and then they go to a warm like tent or trailer or whatever.
And they warm up after their shoot.
But like, in the story, like characters will just be like,
oh, there's no time to build a fire.
We just have to huddle for warmth.
In like the super cold, the winter, the definitely icy...
Like how the fuck?
Can that even be done?
I thought you would definitely die of hypothermia.
I think so.
Yeah, I think so.
I don't know, I didn't see any later seasons.
Maybe they wouldn't surprise me too much if they get sloppy about that kind of thing.
That seems like the kind of thing that Preston Jacobs would lampoon in a review.
Maybe if it's like possible.
I mean, I can buy, like if a character is supposed to be like super hard and they can take any amount of weather, it doesn't matter.
They're just a social badass, they can just do that.
Like a wildling leader, I can buy that.
But like Samuel Tarly, chubby boy, very unprepared for the world.
Fat little baby needs his fire not to die in the cold.
Little soft bitch.
He doesn't know how to build a fire, so he can't and he doesn't.
And he's not like shivering the next morning, he's fine.
He's talking like he's not going to die.
Yeah, he's talking like he's not going to die, but he's totally going to die.
Yeah, it's just sort of like when I feel cold, such as in winter, in real life, I'm like, dang, I can't stand this.
I feel like if you know to go outside when it's cold, it's probably just that they fucked it up and didn't think about it.
Your instinct is probably correct.
I feel like they would need a fire in this situation.
I don't know.
Well, they would be at least like the cheeks would be redder, the nose would be like icicles hanging off it or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think I, what did I watch?
I don't know.
I think I stopped watching it at some point and I got all my, I got all my Game of Thrones from Preston Jacobs reviewing the new episodes.
Yeah.
Is that the one I'm thinking of, the person who does like the books with the full size of the video and then it becomes one third size of the video and then other things.
And then it ends up with a large map of words and pictures relating to the topic he's talking about.
That's, I'm not sure if it's that exactly.
It's like, oh, what the hell is up with Varys and he goes into like.
You might be thinking of Alt Shift X.
Oh yeah, yeah, I recognize that name.
Yeah, Alt Shift X is the, Alt Shift X is the mainstream sell out Preston Jacobs.
I'm proud of knowing that person.
Yeah.
Norminess is next to godliness.
That's true.
Preston Jacobs, I guess he wrote a novel.
It's like a pseudo historical novel.
I think it's called like, I think it's called like of wolves and Indians or something like that.
It's really, it's fun.
It's funny because like all of his video, it sounds like a title that he would give like one of his like series explaining something about Game of Thrones, but it's just the title of his book.
I don't know.
It's, it's, I'm not interested in reading it.
It's, it's funny.
It's funny to me when a YouTuber is like, I did something other than YouTube and I'm like, shut up.
Get back to the, get back to doing the thing that I came for.
Get back to the, the click minds.
Get, get back to the, you get back to the video factory.
You sap, you slob.
That's why I had to, that's why I stopped doing videos so that people wouldn't, wouldn't yell at me when I did things other than make videos, like make a video game for instance.
Yeah.
Very good.
Very classic.
It was all, all calculated.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I didn't want to get typecast.
I didn't want to be too successful.
As the, as the sonichu Winnie the Pooh poker streamer, put a Nuzlocke guy.
You can't really have like a single thing going on with your channel.
You can't pin me down.
Yeah, that's, yeah, it's true.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess the, like the sonichu lectures are what most people know me for because they're like the biggest things.
But you know, like I only did two of those.
So, yeah.
Everything, and everything else got modest views.
Then the Nuzlocke's and the Winnie the Pooh stuff, they're all pretty, pretty modestly viewed.
None of that was a huge runaway success or anything.
Sad, but true.
Oh well.
It's funny that, like, I really remember the Nuzlocke's, but I think the, the main thing I remember from them is just, you're playing the video game.
And then when you get a new Pokemon, you draw them.
And when they evolve, you draw them and it's like the little picture changes.
And I was like, oh, I love that.
I like the little picture changing.
I sure would like to see a little picture change again.
Oh no, they died.
The little pictures changed though.
I mean, I'm entertained by this.
Yeah.
I like doing that.
I am sort of mentally preparing for another Nuzlocke at some point.
I kind of want to do another Nuzlocke.
I have some ideas for gimmicks for it that I will, I will, I think I have to do it at some point.
I don't, I'm not, I'm not ready to do that like right away, but it's definitely a thing that I, certainly a thing I want to do.
Yeah.
Although, like, I don't know.
I want to do it and I guess that, that means I will do it.
But also like, you know, I say that knowing that like, I guess my old Nuzlocke's got some views.
They got some viewership.
Maybe they got, I think the biggest ones might have like 30k views or something, which is not nothing.
Honestly, honestly, you know what?
Now that I think about it, a Nuzlocke series would probably get viewed more than say the Poo videos did.
Yeah.
It is a genius move, actually.
It's definitely what I should do.
I got a gimmick for you.
Yeah.
Instead of a Nuzlocke, you do-
How about a less nuke?
No, you do a lock nuts where all the Pokemon wear chested belts and you lock them and their nuts are locked and you lock nuts.
Yeah.
And then what?
And when they die, they can finally release.
There's an edge lock.
It's an edge lock.
All of the, all the Pokemon are edging the whole time.
And then when you've knocked out and they finally come, they have to go.
They have to leave.
They have to leave the show.
Yeah.
I mean-
Yeah, they're not dead.
You banished them because they finished edging.
Yeah.
And like, well, guess you-
You're no longer pure.
Guess you should leave now.
Goodbye.
Sure.
Only virgins on this Pokemon team.
Only virgins.
And if you lose your virginity, if you have an orgasm for any reason, under any circumstances.
Super virgins.
Just like, oh, like the super straight thing, but it's super virgins.
And it's like, not only have I never had sex, I've never even come.
I've never even, I've never even felt anything.
So based.
So chase.
So based and chase, baby.
Yeah.
USA.
Classic USA.
Sure.
Classic USA moment.
I'm trying to think of the word.
It's like-
That's like wordle.
Wasn't it, was it Isaac Newton who wore like a Chastity device so he wouldn't like jerk off when he was like sleeping?
That doesn't, well, I don't know.
Or was it like Kant or someone like that?
Isaac Newton was a perma virgin.
Funnily enough, you know.
He stuck all those needles in the back of his eye to see colors and he didn't get any puss.
No.
What the fuck?
No, nobody fucked him.
Nobody fucked him even though he literally invented the rainbow.
He invented the prism.
He made light from the sun.
He invented light and the rainbow, giving him a monopoly on leprechaun's gold.
Wait, if he invented the rainbow, maybe people thought he was gay and that's why.
Oh my god, that's right.
He was typecast.
He invented the pride flag and everyone was like, oh, I see.
Well, this isn't cool yet.
We don't like this at the moment in society.
I'm not so cool with what I'm seeing here.
And he was like, no, no, it's like science.
No, look, look at this.
You can make telescopes and stuff.
Microscopes even.
Look what happens if I shoot it through a clear rock and everyone was like, shut up.
Gay.
No.
Not away with you.
Away at devil worship.
Yeah.
Something, something game of thrones.
Something, something.
Renly's rainbow guard.
Ha, ha.
Faith of the Seven.
Rainbows.
Lamal.
Ha, ha.
Duh.
What part of the show did you stop watching?
Do you remember?
What part did I stop watching?
I think it was maybe right after Euron shows up.
Oh, so that's the beginning of season six.
That's where I am.
Did I watch, did I watch all the way to season six?
Maybe I did.
Okay.
Spoilers ahead, but I'm going to say the big thing.
Uh-huh, sure.
The end of season five is where Jon Snow dies.
Oh, yes.
Yes, I saw that.
I did see up to the, I actually know that was where I stopped watching.
That was the last one that I saw.
Yeah.
Euron appears in like episode one or two of season six.
Okay.
So I was, I was basically right.
Yeah.
That was, that's, that's the season where the, the books, there's no book stuff.
The season five was like largely book and then it sort of stopped being the books near the
end of the season.
That's the end of the, the end of the, is it the, the end of the fifth book is just
Jon dies, right?
And same with like the end of the fifth season is Jon dies.
And then it's like, well, now, now what?
Yeah.
Okay.
I, man, I don't, I don't like, I've said this before.
I don't like watch enough shows.
I don't read enough.
I don't watch enough stuff.
I don't consume, I don't consume enough media.
Way too much of the stuff I like consume is like reviews and like critical stuff about
other things.
Stuff I haven't even played.
I've watched so much like Elder Scrolls criticism.
I've never played an Elder Scrolls game.
It's sick.
It's, I'm sick in the head.
I'm sick in the mind.
I think it's, I think it's a sickness in society.
Not me though.
It's society's fault.
I guess so.
It's, I guess the reason review content is more approachable is because it's free and
it's right there and they explain everything completely so that you don't have to be wondering,
am I wasting my time playing this game?
And then you watch review and they explain why this game is good and bad and you're like,
okay, well now I know.
And so that, that inherently is more appealing to start with.
But if you never go on to play or watch the thing, then you end up just seeing reviews
of stuff.
I watched the new, do you know a channel, the channel called Bob Vids?
Nope.
It's not a huge channel.
It's most known for, he did a bunch of videos about why CinemaSins is bad and he did a few
videos called Everything Wrong With, Everything Wrong With, in which he would do like dings
of CinemaSins.
I think I saw one of those somewhere.
Yeah.
Well he made a new video, like just like a few weeks ago, I think, where he sort of
does like, okay, it's been four years.
Has CinemaSins improved on anything?
And the answer is no.
Oh, why would he?
Yeah.
Well he, yeah.
I mean he said, he said they won't change and then he was like, well did they?
I was right.
He was talking about their review of the newer Suicide Squad, the one with the giant starfish.
And he shows like, he shows like the climax of it.
He shows like the final moment.
I haven't seen the movie, but it's the bit where like, there's like a flashback of like
that girl talking to her dad about like, why rats are just like us.
And like, if rats can be useful, then so can we.
Like they're the lowest creatures just like us, you know.
And it's like a, it's like, and it's like a touching little moment.
And I was, and I was like, oh, wait a second, wait a second.
That seems like kind of like a good, was that movie good?
Are there good movies?
Is that a good scene in a mainstream film?
Oh, fuck.
It just changed everything.
I'm gonna have to go watch.
I know the feeling of like, oh shit, I don't watch it.
I don't consume enough media.
What's wrong with me?
I used to be all about consuming media.
Now I don't.
Well, like, I don't know.
It shouldn't be a job.
No, it's just, it's not like, it's not like I feel like I don't do enough like for a job.
I think I feel like because I don't consume enough media, I think I don't have enough like things to like think about.
I think I don't like have enough like new stimuli that is like making me think about stuff and giving me like things to discuss with people.
I mean, does that, does that void have to be filled with like media?
Could you not fill it with a hobby instead?
Like, oh, I'm gonna learn wood carving so I can carve a little wood thing.
I guess, I guess you could.
I guess you could, but like mainstream media is like a, is like a shared cultural thing.
Whereas like wood carving is like an endeavor one generally embarks upon solidarily.
No, there's probably wood carving reddits and communities.
Well, yeah, sure.
There would be for any craft.
I mean, yeah, you're, you're right.
Like you want to go to the water cooler and be like, oh, did you watch the latest Housewives in a pit episode?
Housewives in a pit, the new.
Housewives in a pit, they're going crazy.
They're going crazy.
They haven't given them any food.
Yeah.
Margaret like, like Margaret like clawed her way pretty far up the side this time until,
until George, George yet, you know, she got her hands on the, on the shovel and like,
and like knocked her down and like broker femur with like the blade of the edge of the spade.
And then that put that put it into that.
Oh yeah.
Very exciting episode this week.
Yeah.
So you go around like, you know, the cultural consciousness, you talk about the thing.
You go to the water cooler and say, look what I made, look at this wood, like a wooden ring.
It's like a ring made of wood.
And look at the carving on that.
Yeah.
And they say, cool.
Sure.
Yeah.
I think, I think what annoys me a little bit is the insistence that you've got to be hooked
into whatever bullshit is being made.
Yeah.
I don't like it most of the time, except when it's really, really good, like Game of Thrones
or Breaking Bad or something like an HBO drama is usually something fun to get into because
it's quality, as well as culturally significant.
Like, I don't even one slight tiny piece of a shit to go and watch anything on Netflix
ever, or like, or like a Disney plus, or any of these streaming things where it's like,
it's not immediately available.
Well, I don't care.
Yeah.
Mandalorian, when you go away.
I think I'm, I think I'm just, I think I'm just thinking about like, I think I'm just
thinking about like, how do, how do I, how do I, how do I make more like connections with
people?
How do I connect with people more in life?
Is, is movies, is movies what I'm, what I'm missing?
I mean, it's a, I mean, if you're not interested in them.
Yeah.
I doubt that they would be like a springboard for like a super interesting relationship on
its own.
Maybe it would like be an icebreaker.
Like, have you seen that movie?
Yeah.
I guess that, that's what it could be.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Shit.
Hell, I don't know.
I just thought that rat, thought that rat scene was pretty good.
Bob Vidd said that rat scene was pretty good.
And then he showed it.
And I was like, Hey, yeah, it was pretty good actually.
Good job.
Suicide Squad.
Did they say, I'm the Jane Rat that meets all the rules?
No, no, no, no, no.
They were just regular sized.
Unfortunately.
That was a good, Bob Vidd is good.
He doesn't really make like content.
I mean, his only like, I think his only like regular content was that everything wrong
with, everything wrong with, and he only did like six of them.
And then I think he was kind of just like, Hey, I'm done.
Fuck it.
And now he occasionally puts out like a little like five minute shitpost or a little like
joke video or something.
Now it's making everything strong with this wrestler.
But he came, but he came back for one last, for one last, one last word about the, about
Cinema Sins in 2022 when we needed it most, when we really needed to be told that Cinema
Sins was bad in case any of us had missed the memo the first time.
Yeah.
Geez.
I don't have any shit.
I don't have any notes.
I don't have any notes for stuff to talk about this week.
I think I'm thinking about like, maybe I should watch more movies because this is another week
where I'm like, well, what do I, what do I talk about?
What did, what did I do?
What did I do this week?
If I'd watched a movie, I could talk about like a cool movie I watched at least.
Yeah.
The idiots that listen to this would surely love to hear my thoughts on God, I don't know,
whatever is out now.
Smiling friends is out.
I haven't seen that yet.
Oh, um, you know.
That's the, the Zach Hadel and, uh, uh, Kusek, Michael Kusek collaborative show.
Yeah.
Um, I was seeing that all over the place and I kind of meant to actually go check that
out, but I, I forgot.
So I haven't seen it.
I, I was on like adultswim.com and I said, um, you don't have the right IP address.
Uh, maybe, maybe you should use today's sponsor, Nord VPN.
You can get a million dollars for free.
It would, it would take me like 20 minutes to circumvent that, but I just couldn't be
bothered.
I will watch it though.
Cause it, it, I've seen clips and those are funny.
I've seen a few clips that seem pretty, pretty good that I heard people, you know, I didn't,
I didn't see anybody like, I didn't see anybody saying like it sucked or it was overhyped
or it wasn't as good as everyone was saying.
I only saw people being like, this part was really funny.
I liked it.
I was like, okay, cool.
Yeah.
They got the, the sick animation guy that does a voice and maybe some animation as well.
The sick animation.
No, I don't think so.
Uh, yeah.
Nate likes him.
He's like a weird animation guy who's done some small things for adultswim before.
They mostly are on YouTube.
Uh, how do I explain it?
Sick animation.
Like it is sick.
A lot of it is like grotesque, but not like in a, you know, I have no idea how to explain
the body of work of sick animation.
I mean, I'm seeing some images here.
I don't, I don't know.
I don't recognize this at all.
I don't think I've ever seen this before.
They're, they're funny.
They're like, uh, they're like alternative humor, cranked to absurd levels.
Hmm.
Okay.
I think that their, their latest one, Michelangelo was about Michelangelo, the turtle, but it
was trans.
And there was a, there was a, this was an altercation at work where somebody misgendered them.
But like that's the plot of a lot of their animations.
It's just sort of like.
Somebody's trans and then they fight about it.
No, no, no, no.
Not the trans part.
It's just sort of like, it's a relatively mundane situation with weird characters involved.
And then they do weird things and it ends abruptly.
It's hard to know like what the joke is other than it's absurd.
It's absurd and it's great.
And I like it.
There's a lot of ones I like.
There were, there were like so many, there were a lot of voices that I recognize.
Like Mike Stoklasa was in the pilot.
Yes.
I remember that.
That's funny.
Okay.
I, okay.
I heard different people saying that the, the angry video game nerd was in it, but like,
I saw a disagreement about like what he did.
I saw someone say that he voiced Satan and I saw another person saying, no, there was
just like a still image of his face in, in the episode somewhere, like he, what his voice
was not actually in it.
Yeah.
I mean, you could check that with the credits surely.
If James Rolfe was in there, you know, I saw the, I did see the credits and it did say
James Rolfe.
I just, um,
Under what?
Like voice acting?
Yeah.
It was listed as a voice.
Okay.
I think it, someone said it was Satan, but then somebody else said no.
So I don't know.
I probably could just check it if I wanted to.
I think I was thinking, I would just watch the app.
I think I was thinking I would just watch the episode and listen for when I heard him,
but I haven't done that yet.
So whoops.
Yeah, it's, it's definitely the sort of thing cause Zach, like a new grounds guy is like,
has been for years, like in, with like internet culture, more so than industry stuff.
So there's a lot of like deliberate like, oh, let's get this person, let's get Mike
Stoklasso.
Let's get like this and that.
Yeah.
Get in our show.
Cause they can.
That's great.
It's inspiring.
I think for a lot of people who like make things on the internet, like, oh, there's a show.
They worked hard.
They made a show about it and they made all these stupid references that they had and
like their, their let's play.
And it's like, oh, you can, you can just be in a let's play and make stupid jokes and
then make a show eventually if you're good enough and put them in there.
And it's like,
Can you though?
It's, it's, it's an unrealistic, like a goal cause that never happens, but it's nice to
see it.
Yeah, sure.
It's fun.
Like, I guess, uh, I don't know, obviously, yeah, it's not an attainable goal for most
people, but like, I don't know, I guess it had to be someone.
Why not, why not these internet guys that, that show whatever seems like it came out
good.
It's all, it's all good.
Uh, I'll, I'll probably check it out.
I'll make a show.
I'll make a show and it'll be better than this show.
I'll put it on all the television channels and the streaming services.
That's right.
That is what I'm going to do.
Yeah, that is exactly, that is exactly correct.
It's going to be called Ben St.
Uh, it's going to be, it's going to have a logo that says Ben St.
Patreon.com slash.
Oh, you know, I was thinking.
Somebody, one or two people, I think, asked me, uh, if I was going to make Blu-rays of
the Nuzlocs, like the old ones.
I saw that comment.
And I, yeah, and I remember, like, I've said this before, years ago, I tried to do that.
I tried to make, like, DVD menus for, uh, uh, I think it was Genocide, the first one.
And I got fed up with the software and I was like, fuck it, this is stupid.
But now, you know, I got the Pleeve and the Wii Blu-rays, uh, buy the Pleeve and the Wii
Blu-rays, DM me on Twitter, uh, send me money, send me $30 plus shipping to, uh, IASUcomic
at gmail.com, uh, please, uh, thanks.
Um, and, uh, oh, I said, I, I, I made a joke tweet that they were canceled and, like, tons
of people thought I was serious.
Like many multiple people, like, thought they were actually canceled, like I was actually
canceling the Blu-rays.
I saw people thinking, like, oh, he must have got a DMCA from Trixie or something.
Like no, I, I thought I was really clearly joking, but like, like half a dozen people
were like, oh, they're canceled.
Why?
Was there a DMCA?
I was like, no, no, I made a joke about making it into NFT, um, anyway.
It's too close to, to serious posts they've seen.
I guess so.
The world is, is funny now.
There is no such thing as, as a joke.
It is just funny.
Yeah, sure.
Uh, but no, they're real.
In fact, I had, I had like a dozen more to burn yesterday.
I think I have like four more to burn today, uh, a few more.
Um, but anyway, yeah, I could, if I wanted, I could just get slobed on, on, on Fiverr.
To do, I would just have to get the files together and tell him like, yeah, make me another one.
And then I would just have, you know, I have some extra discs left over.
I could, if I wanted to, I could make, I could make Blu-rays of the, of the, of the, of the
Nuzlocke.
Yeah.
Nuzlocke, Genocide and Nuzlocke.
And I was thinking, you know, since I want to do another Nuzlocke, I think probably what
I'll do is when I do that, at the same time, I will like, I will make, I will just make
a blue, like one test Blu-ray of the old ones and be like, yeah, hey, you could fuck it.
You can buy Blu-ray DVD cases for all, all of them.
I made them.
Why not?
I got this, I got this fucking printer.
I got this fucking printer that prints on discs.
Yeah.
I guess if you got all the equipment.
I got all the equipment now, paid, paid for from the, from the profits of the Blu-ray,
of the, the Pleeve and the Wee Blu-ray.
So I have all this stuff now and why not continue to use them to produce stuff?
Right?
I don't know if that many people would actually want the Blu-rays of that, but like maybe a
few would.
And like, I don't have to make a lot.
I could make like 10.
I used to make like 10 copies and sell them of 10 people on them.
Yeah, it's, I mean, it's, I feel like people would like it just for the, the, the novelty
of having a Nuzlocke from Ben St.
Honestly.
On physical media.
I will probably do it just even, even if, even without, without any expectation of like
selling any at all or very many or anything.
I'll probably just do it just because it's, it would be funny.
It would just be funny to have done it and be like, yep, it's on a Blu-ray.
Everything's on a Blu-ray now in the, in the year where everything's becoming an NFT.
I am like a decade behind the curve.
I'm, I'm making the jump to Blu-ray, baby.
Yeah.
I don't know.
So that's.
No, it's cool.
I'm just thinking.
So that's the plan.
I guess.
I don't know.
I'm thinking about like, I've got my, my Redman comics now.
I saw, I saw those.
I saw those on Twitter.
They look and feel great.
They're a nice little small book.
You can have it in your, in your purse.
How big, how big are they?
They're like two 10 by two 10 millimeters.
Two 10 by two 10.
So like smaller than a mouse mat.
Hmm.
Let me, let me, let me pull up iRuler.com.
iRuler.
Uh, okay.
200.
It's just pictures of emperors.
Oh, okay.
It's kind of a, oh, it's bigger than I thought actually.
Uh, yeah.
Gotcha.
Okay.
So like.
I think, I think it's that big.
Seven inches, eight inches.
Yeah.
Seven inches.
I'm looking at the, I'm looking at the iRuler and 20 millimeters is about eight inches.
Or sorry, 20 centimeters, a.k.a. 200 millimeters is about eight inches.
I typed in two 10 by two 10 millimeters and I got lenses.
No.
Oh.
That's wrong.
No, thank you.
Well, whatever.
I know what they are.
They're over there in the, in their box.
So I don't want to take them out.
Yeah.
But yeah, I got those.
I got the, the spine with the little red man on the side.
And that was, that was my favorite part.
It's in the tweet.
Let me, let me, let me go take a closer, let me go take a closer look at that.
Uh, my, the pleb, pleb and wee blue rays have the night.
They have the funny little, funny little, uh, Digi and Jesse little, little guys on the,
on the, on the spine.
Oh yeah.
That's actually kind of to the same.
That's where.
Yeah.
Digi bro is, is just sitting down at the bottom of the, of the blue ray spine.
There he is.
He's just hanging out.
That's great.
Yeah.
It's, it's cause it was like one red man comic per page.
Um, and I did like a hundred of them.
I didn't even realize that's how many I've made.
Are you, are you wearing some kind of like fluffy pirate shirt?
No, I'm wearing like a hoodie with a zip.
Oh, okay.
It just happened to be outside.
Yeah.
It's, it's cool.
The third picture here, it looks almost like you've got like, like a white cuff and then
like a big puffy, like puffy arm.
Okay.
Just, just check in.
Uh, but yeah, those, uh, those are nice quality and I have those.
The Lord of Ghosts books are also printed and they will be with me tomorrow as we're
recording on Monday.
Um, and then I'll have to buy a bunch of, uh, envelopes and boxes to size so that I could
fit both of the comics and the plush and whatever else in the pin.
And I can be like, okay, I needed this many envelopes at this size.
Then I can start fucking sell it and mailing them out.
That's exciting.
It is.
I'm, I'm almost ready to start.
I have a big stack of about like 48 DVDs or blue, blue rays here and I'm, I just have
to make like the last few more and I have all the envelopes addressed.
I haven't put the, I haven't put the things in the, I have to put them in the envelopes
and then, then I can take them to the post office.
I'm going to take them all in one go because I don't want to make multiple trips.
Frustratingly, there used to be, before I moved here, apparently there was a post office
like right next to my house, like like one street over.
I guess they closed it due to COVID or something.
So now I have to take like, it's like a half an hour bus ride.
I mean, you know, and include wait times to take like a fucking like two buses to get
to a, a damn post office.
It was very inconvenient.
It sucks.
It does.
It's too bad.
It's just, just too damn bad.
But anyway.
Yeah.
Mail-in.
I can't wait to, can't wait to get my, what did I, I got the Redman book.
I got the Lord of Ghost book.
I got the plush.
Did I get it?
Was there anything else?
You got the pin.
Oh, the pin.
Yes.
The pin.
Of course.
Yes.
Very, very good.
Very exciting.
There's still, there's still the matter of the, the ghost costume I have to make.
Oh yeah.
And, and oh, and, and the doodle inside the book.
I think you had, you had like the maximum tier size.
Yeah.
So you have everything.
So you get a doodle.
I will doodle something in the book for you.
Please.
Sign it.
And thank you.
Oh yeah.
So, so if, if the, the Lord of Ghost books are with me, I will have already sent out like
a questionnaire for people to send their addresses and what they want doodled if they were on
that tier.
So I guess if anybody who is listening to this had backed the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter,
who had pledged enough money, remember to tell me, because if I don't know what you want
me to draw, it'll just take a while for me to send it.
I'll, I'll leave them for last.
And then if you never respond, I'll just draw something and then send it.
Can I tell you right now what I want you to doodle in mind?
Yes.
Draw me, draw me, just draw me a picture of Phantom Horn as he appears in Phantom's
Revenge.
Phantom Horn.
That version.
That version of Phantom Horn.
Yeah.
With the sword and the, and the raincoat and, and all that.
All right.
Did you, did you see my, my, my promo image, my Phantom's Revenge?
I did.
That was very cool looking.
I was so, I thought that came out so good.
I was enamored of it.
You ever, you ever draw something and you just really love it and you just stare at it for
like a really long time?
Uh, there have been moments.
Yes.
I had, I had a moment like that with that.
I was just like, ah, I was, I was in awe of what I have created.
The, you know, sometimes, you know, the muse just works through me.
You know, I'm not responsible for works of genius like that.
They simply happen through me.
Yeah.
That's true of everything I do, actually.
Anyway.
Loved it.
Yeah.
I was glad, glad you caught that.
Somebody, somebody was asking, somebody was asking me if I would make a plush Uwupati
for, for the, for the eventual Kickstarter for that.
Uwupati.
I guess I could.
And I'm, and I'm used like, what if, what if I made a gummy, a little gummy Uwupati?
Oh my God.
Cause, cause like it's got, um.
It's, that's a perfect gummy thing to make.
Yeah.
Cause he's a slime boy.
It's made of goo.
And it's got, cause you know, his, um, his, his, uh, most distinguished, I mean, he's got
the, the, the shape, the general shape and the cute eyes, but then like the brain, like
the visible brain, like floating in his little like membrane bubble.
And I was like, what if I made like a, like a carrot, like a caramel brain or something,
like a chocolate brain and I like encased it in like a, in like a sour green apple,
a, a gummy or something.
I don't know.
That would be unbelievable.
It would be unbelievably delicious.
You mean.
No.
Yes.
It would be.
Well, I feel like a chocolate thing inside of a slime goo would be a bit weird, but.
Yeah.
That's, that's a striking image.
Right.
That would be like a, like a, what do you call it?
Like a, not gourmet, but like a, a candy thing that took a lot of work to make.
Oh, like a, um, what's the, what is the word?
Um, like hand handmade?
Is that the word?
Like a hand crafted, like a, like a patissier?
No.
There's a word to describe like the, the fine artistry that goes into a single chocolate
treat, a confectionery thing.
Yeah, there is.
Hmm.
Oh, I'm drawing.
I'm drawing a blank.
Bass is the word.
Uh.
Dude, bass is five letters.
That could be a word.
Oh.
Oh, I got it.
I have, I was spoiled on yesterday's word.
I have not been spoiled on today's word.
So have you, have you done it yet?
No.
Should I do it right now?
Do it right now.
All right.
Have you, have you done today's?
I have.
Yes.
All right.
I'm going to start.
We're going to walk through it.
I'm going to start with my, my typical starting guess, which is a aches.
I like, I like that one.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, okay.
We got the A and the S.
Um.
All right.
So I want to do, I want to guess a word that has an A and an S in the middle.
So what about?
Hmm.
Uh.
What about like rat?
Rass.
Raisin?
No.
Uh.
Rass, raspy.
I got the R.
Hmm.
Nothing in.
No greens.
Okay.
So an A.
An A, there's an A in, in column three and four or three or four.
There's an S in column.
Well, one, one, two, or.
Oh no.
No.
Uh.
Hmm.
Okay.
Can't give anything away.
I can't say anything, but it is very quiet.
Yes.
Uh.
Oh dear.
I didn't realize this might.
This might require like extent, some somewhat extended periods of silent
contemplation.
Um.
Uh.
What?
Okay.
I'll just, what if I did?
Because I want to try another one with the A and the S and the R.
I just rearranged.
So.
How about.
Hmm.
So.
Uh.
No, not sauce.
That's not.
That's not gonna work.
Um.
So.
Uh.
No, not sauce.
That's not.
That's not gonna work.
Um.
So.
Okay.
What about, how about, um, slay?
What's another?
What's slay?
Sleigh Queen.
I've already guessed, I've already guessed why.
So that would be a way.
How about slack?
I already, I already guessed C. How about in slake?
I already guessed E.
Slah.
Slam, because this is exactly what goes on in your head when you play.
Oh, slit, slew, blit, blue, green.
Yeah, trying to like, trying to like, force a word.
Finetically figure it out, even though a lot of the times the word
phonetically does not sound the way it's spelled.
OK, you get fucked.
What if it OK, what if I went with like slow?
No, there's no there's no O.
It's got to be an A and an E.
I'm sure those are the only two vowels.
Slaw, slaw wheel, Ryan.
Slah, sledge, slah, slacko, S-L-A-K-O, slab, I'm just trying to find a combo
that doesn't waste any letters.
Oh, oh, oh, wait, wait, OK, OK, what about no salt would have an A
in the same position as before?
Damn it.
OK, OK.
Oh, wait, no, I've only found one.
I've only found one vowel.
So it could have like slow, sloy, no, slo-
Eliezer, could you put a graphic of this on screen so people can look at something?
So like the first word been guessed at the top.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, but what about like a loan?
Well, that would have an S, loans would have another.
What about, oh, what about no, loser, loser would would have the S in the same?
Just don't want to waste any any information.
Low, low, no, it would either be loafs or could do loafs.
No, I know, like bread.
No, it'd be a VES.
I think I think loafs is a word.
I think loafs is a valid is a valid word.
I don't think so.
But maybe maybe it's another Americanization.
Those damn Yankees, they fucked me.
Yeah, with them was it's favor favor, right?
They have no honor with a U.
It has a U in it.
Honor, honor, honor, damn.
How about Maros?
Joy, no.
America.
How about Tart?
No, I can't do Tart.
I can't do Tarty because it's got I already guessed why in the last lot.
Tart, tar, tariff, is there two F's in tariff?
Yes, damn it.
Well, there's two R's to I know.
Yes, no, it's T-A-R-I-F-F, I think.
How about OK, OK, I got it.
How about Tal?
How about how about Talon?
Wait, no, there's no R and no S in that.
Fuck.
Did you guess it already?
No, I'm going to do it.
OK, the L, the L is good.
Wait, no, no, I repeated the A.
I repeated the second slot.
Hey, I'm so fucking stupid.
Oh, whoopsie.
I know I just realized this kind of annoying.
What's this?
Wordle has six letters.
Yeah, some word.
Someone got rid of this discord was like,
why didn't they make the name five letters
like like the whole game is about?
All right, squirtle.
OK, mo, mo, mollar, mollar.
Oh, my this might be it, actually.
No.
OK, it's pretty good.
Oh, it's solar.
OK, got it.
Got it.
Got it. Got it in five, baby.
I got mine. I could have got mine in three.
Well, I'll I'll I'll run you.
I have never gotten one in less than five.
I have five in five and three in six.
So I'm not that great at this, actually.
Not going to three.
No, I got three in six.
I got five in five and three.
Oh, I see. Yeah. Yeah.
That's what I meant to say.
The the trick is is like
never guessing if you would repeat a letter.
Yeah. Or if a word like.
I don't know. Never never make a guess.
I mean, well, I don't know.
I guess I never make a wasted guess.
Yeah, that's why, like.
It was a waste.
It was a waste to guess Talon because that I wanted I knew
I wanted to have an A in a new spot to find where the A goes.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's there's definitely like a like a strategy to
yeah, like getting each new each new guest to give you
like the maximum amount of information it possibly can.
So like ice, that's the strat to always win.
But maybe not always to win in like few guesses.
I don't know to win in a few guesses.
I feel like you kind of got to like maybe maybe going with your gut.
Maybe going with your gut will get you more like wins in three,
but also like will risk you just like fucking up and failing.
I I usually don't have why I say usually it's always I never have.
A strategy for the first word, I just think of one.
So I put in pride for this one.
P R I E D like you pry it open.
Oh, yeah, from that.
And then I thought, OK, the R can't be in the second slot.
I'll try the thing that begins with R and I put roast.
And I gave me the O and the A and the S and the R all in different places.
So from there, I struggled, but I've eventually figured out.
Oh, so now I put it in, but is the wrong middle letter?
If I if solar, if I had just thought a little harder,
I would have realized with my guest molar that wait a second,
I know there needs to be an S in the word.
So, like, yeah, I could have just guessed solar right away
if I thought about it.
But I but I but I didn't oh, well.
Oh, well, that was that was how much.
How long did we just make the listener listen to me?
Oh, well, we're at all.
They love it. They love it.
They're playing along with like a week old.
They fucking better. Yeah. Yeah.
There's got to be some app that lets you like play old wordles, right?
There aren't, but there are
like wordle adjacent games that are basically the same thing
that just make random things you can play.
Because what I want to do, yeah, is go back and play the other
like 200 wordles that I missed.
Like if I'm going to pay DLC, honestly.
Yeah, they should just do that if they want to make a million dollars.
But who wants to do that?
I think the the thing with it.
Is they don't want because, like, obviously,
you can just look up the answer
and they don't want people to have access, easy access to the answer.
But like, but you can already have 24 hours.
Yeah, like look up the answer.
So it's like, I don't know why I disagree.
I think it's annoying that that you can get your wordle
like based on your time zone, like Europeans get it before I get it.
I think that's dumb.
I think they should just have one universal time when it turns over for everybody.
It's stupid that like it's stupid.
It's stupid that like some people have the new wordle
and they can solve it and post their solution.
Well, other people like have to wait.
I just think that's like bad design because because wordle,
like the whole point of wordle, like the puzzle is fine.
But the point of wordle, the innovation of wordle,
the things it makes successful is the virality of like the emoji
sharing mechanism and the like the communal aspect of everyone's
posting their results and comparing the results.
So it just makes more sense to if it turns over at one time for everybody,
then everybody can be there at the same time and be like,
oh, new wordle just dropped. Let's all let's all do it.
I kind of agree.
But I feel like if it had that quality,
some people in the world could do a wordle
and then five minutes later do the next wordle
while everybody else is asleep on the other side of the world.
And then they'll wake up like it's exactly the same problem
that you could see other people's things before you'd have a chance to do yours.
Well, I mean, it's always it's always going to be a problem.
No, it reduces the problem, though, because then ever everyone has it available.
Everyone has the same window to be spoiled in.
There's not like some people that are more spoilable than others.
I don't find it. I mean, maybe I'm just I'm not really worried about the spoilers.
I just it's not so much the spoiler thing.
It's that like when if like like like other people in like, say,
my discord server, they're doing the wordle.
So like the Europeans are all like doing the wordle, comparing their guesses.
And then the Americans just got to be like, all right, cool.
Well, I'll let you know how it went for me seven hours from now.
Slame, it's dumb. I like it.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I guess.
The the the instant communication is not possible in time zone stuff.
Yeah, I think I think I think it's I think it would be it's more.
I don't think much would be lost
if like the new wordle doesn't appear at midnight for everybody.
I think it would be OK if for some people it appears at midnight
and for some people it appears at 5 p.m. and so on and whatever.
Because it's still because everyone still gets one every day.
Yeah, that's not those are my those are my wordle thoughts.
That's my criticism.
That's my that's my advice for the wordlers.
Get it get it together.
Yeah, I mean, I've I find it to be quite fun,
but it is mostly the communal aspect.
I was playing on some of those other sites where you can just do randomly
generated wordles words, but it's not wordle.
It's just exactly the same thing on a different website and it there is no one per day.
So you get a random seed, you got a word and you got to figure it out.
And I'm like, OK, let's try this.
And then I realized that once I finished it, I can't tell anyone about it.
And right, I realized that the game itself is too luck based
to be like a compelling strategy game.
There's there's some strategy to it.
There's some strategy.
But it is a guessing game.
That yeah, the first word you use
is like it determines quite a lot.
And yeah, and another thing is that you can use your information
of past wordles to be like, OK, well, it's probably not going to be the same word
as yesterday. So like, yeah, like if you remember a bunch of them,
it's like, well, it's probably not any of those.
But I mean, how much does that really narrow it down?
There's still like 100,000 words that it could be true.
But if you if you like guess and you get a bunch of yellow letters
and you're like, OK, I could arrange them in this way.
But that would give me a very similar word, a letter, a word from like two days ago.
And I'm like, well, it's probably not going to be that one.
So knowing that I could think what other word could it be?
And it's like, I don't know.
If there's more strategy with the the wordle game, if we assume
that the list of wordle words is is not purely randomly seeded
but is curated by someone, then I think it's probably true
that you wouldn't expect to see like two very similar words back to back.
Although you might. Sure, you might.
I mean, how it's been to 111.
How many five letter words even are there?
I think I looked it up and there's like 168,000. That's OK.
OK, we're all right.
Yeah, we'll be OK. Yeah.
We'll keep it going for a few years, I guess, few decades.
Yeah, I mean, it's it's a good it's a good little puzzle,
but the the share button and the emoji.
That's yeah, that's where the real fun is.
Yeah, because if I want like a real.
Puzzle.
I like having all the information and my disposal at my at my use.
So like if I can have all the information and then it's like figure out
the answer with all this information and like, oh, let's hmm, let's hmm.
And it's like a puzzle. It's fun. It's it's brain tingly.
It's engaging with wordle.
You can just get fucked by having a bad guess on the first one.
It gives you not enough information to get the word.
I feel like there's probably I feel like there is probably some
like optimal strategy that is pretty much that you'll never lose.
Yeah, me either.
It's it's like if I let oh, you say quidjibo.
And that's like the word that the letters that are perfectly
tailors to be like of all the five letter words.
These are the ones that come up the most often.
And there is for you should put them in there.
So I don't I would rather not know what that is.
Yeah.
And even then it won't work every time.
I wonder, I wonder, I wonder if
with an optimal strategy, you would be guaranteed to always win wordle.
I I'm going to define when, you know, to always I feel like in six guesses.
I feel like in six guesses, it's always possible.
I think there's kind of enough to fail.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think most likely if you use like different letters on each word
and each word is a real word, then I think six is enough every time.
This would make a good I haven't done it in five yet, I don't think.
You haven't done it in five.
Oh, let me check my let me check my stats.
Wait, you've you've done it in three, but not in five.
Statistics. Oh, no, I have done it in five.
I've done it once in five, three times with four and then twice with three.
That's funny.
I'm just too smart, you see.
Too smart, too smart for too smart for five, but also too stupid for five.
I just go above and below.
I can't get that perfect sweet spot of smartness.
Yeah, wordle, wordle, great, great stuff.
Like every time I type it, I type wordly instead.
No, worldy, worldy, worldy.
Well, that well, that's over.
What? I don't know.
What else? What else is going on?
Hang on, I got a P.
I'll be back in a second.
All right. A few moments later, a.
Hello.
And we're back and we're back.
And we're back.
Pleab in the wee blue rays, 30 fucking dollars.
Patreon Venmo me at Ben St.
Capital B, capital S.
If you don't have PayPal, you could Venmo me if you want to.
You could send it to my Bitcoin wallet.
I got a Bitcoin wallet.
I posted it on Twitter.
Why would anyone send to a Bitcoin wallet?
Surely their donation will disappear immediately.
Um, this Bitcoin will change value.
It would fluctuate.
That's true.
But if I if I withdrew at the same day,
it would probably be more or less secure.
I don't know if if all.
Listen, if all you got is Bitcoin,
I will accept Satoshi's in my Bitcoin wallet.
If it would just be just, I mean, I think it would be pretty funny.
I think it would be pretty funny to buy
Pleab in the wee blue rays with a Bitcoin.
Uh, right, right.
Come on. Come on.
It's just that's just funny.
That's just that's just comedy.
Posting posting my posting my Bitcoin wallet in the server.
Right there.
Oh, yeah, there it is.
I'll send little little Bitcoin gremlins to come and steal it.
You can you can now.
No, digital like skirmishes digital like a rating party.
You can share your wallet and it just means other people can put money in.
They can't take money out.
And by money, I mean cryptocurrency, which.
I get, I guess it's money.
I guess it's sort of money.
I don't know.
I guess the only other thing on my on my topic list is
covid house since my dad had covid.
And yeah, it was like, oh, probably like too risky to fly.
Maybe it wasn't risky enough to fly.
It wasn't risky enough.
Yeah, yeah, true.
But like, you know, whatever, staying in my room,
staying away from dad.
How is he doing?
Is he is he sick?
He was coughing and spluttering, but it appears to be all right.
He had the double vax in the boost.
So OK, too much damage going on.
He seems fine.
He's walking and talking and stuff.
Yeah, we have to talk across the room.
Sure, sure.
Oh, yeah. Oh, my God.
Sorry, you can continue.
But I just I just remembered I got something.
Let me show you what I just ordered on Amazon that just arrived at covid.
That's fucking right.
It's fucking covid, baby.
No, it's some fuck.
Well, yeah, and yeah, I was just going to say that.
It's been.
It's been like a little it's been fine.
It's been fine.
I thought it would be worse, but like nobody else in the house has got it yet.
Even mom who's been spending time with them.
She's been wearing a mask, but like they've been in the same room.
I think it's just because like everyone has the vax.
So like transmission is difficult for the virus.
It's it's more difficult, more difficult.
Yeah, it's yeah.
So luckily, hopefully dad will test negative soon.
It's been like eight days and he's been positive every day.
Oh, how much is a how much is a test over there?
Because they're like expensive.
It's like it's like 15 bucks for a fucking test over here.
It's annoying.
We haven't been doing the tests every day.
It was like on day six or seven, if you test negative twice in a row,
you can stop isolating because it's thought to be gone.
But if you don't test twice, two days in a row, then it's like you still have it.
Yeah, if you don't test negative.
So on the sixth day, my dad started taking them one per day.
It was looking like it was going to be gone.
But then on the eighth day, it was there again.
So whatever.
OK, I found this is not the exact model that I got.
But actually, it's it's pretty close.
Yeah, I ordered one of these and I got it now.
It just arrived.
And you know, is that like the the you like doing paint work?
Yes, like sawdust.
Yes, it is.
Yeah, it's for like industrial applications.
I wanted to buy one of these last year.
Just because I think they look cool, but they do.
I kind of meant I just kind of assumed they would be really expensive.
They're not there.
It was like it was like forty five bucks for like the mask and the cartridges,
like the filter cartridges, because the pink things on the sides are replaceable.
I can I just assumed it would be expensive and I didn't look into it.
And I think I also was kind of like.
If I get a mask like that, it's sort of like, I don't know, it feels kind of like
I don't want to be that guy who's like super paranoid looking.
Yeah, like I don't want people to think that I'm like some kind of like prepper freak,
you know, I don't want people to think that I'm some sort of like
anti social weirdo who is like going above and beyond like doing
like taking unreasonable measures to isolate myself from society.
Like, you know, a regular if a regular mask works,
then why wear one of these unless you're a psycho?
Right. So I talked myself out of it.
And I think I think it was also kind of like it would be sort of giving in to panic
to to to to to do to go this hard.
But that was when I thought it was expensive.
Turns out it's not so it's actually fine.
But like I always I wanted one and I think I wanted to look like that.
I want to look like Bane.
I want to look like a monster.
So I didn't do it.
And then it was to my eternal shame.
So I finally I finally pulled the plug.
I'm not pulled the plug.
I finally pulled the lever, hit the hit the switch,
pulled the whatever I did it, and I think it literally like arrived
in my house like today and is like sitting in a box upstairs in my foyer.
Probably I haven't checked yet.
Do you have one with green filters or do you have like rowdy pink?
Tragically, they only come in pink.
I wanted purple ones, but they don't know.
Yeah, you would think if they make them in like that bright
day glow color, like you would think maybe they have them in different colors.
No, they just only come in pink for some reason.
I don't know why, but a bit disappointing.
I guess I could dye them or paint them or something.
I don't know you spray them with paint and then plug them up.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, that'll work.
That'll work.
Yeah, I can't actually breathe in it anymore, but it looks amazing.
Looks incredible.
You should you should wear like a like a big fireproof jumpsuit
alongside that and a backpack with a flamethrower attached
and hold a flamethrower and go around with a flamethrower.
I should just I should just I should just have a bubble.
I should just live in a bubble, live in a hamster wheel.
You should have a 10 rewb to like bubble.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, those guys never get COVID.
If I would, if I could.
Yeah, so anyway, I'm pretty excited about that.
Don't know when I'll have the chance to wear it in public.
You know, I bought the gator.
I bought the neck gator that had my face, but in like RFCK colors
with like the bright green teeth.
Yeah, did you wear that or were you chicken?
I did. I did wear it a few times.
The thing about that, though, is like this is this is not just all all
gators like that.
Like I've seen gators that have like a face printed on them
and they don't they don't actually look like a face when you wear them
because like they're warped and stretched over a surface.
Like it the illusion is not.
It's not convincing.
Like your brain does not see it and think, oh, it's a it's a guy
with like a creepy smile.
You think like, oh, it's a guy in a gator.
Wait, what's that printed on the gator?
Is that oh, it's supposed to be like a mouth.
OK, whatever. Right.
It's just it's unfortunately just not a very convincing visual effect.
But I did wear it a few times.
So this is my new that this is the new one.
It's like, do I have the do I have the guts to just go out in public?
Looking like a.
Well, here's what will be I don't know.
What do you think?
Would people see this and be like, this guy's a freak?
Or would people see this and this like, this guy is flattening the curve.
We should all be more like this guy, this guy's a hero.
I think I think they'd think both of those things at the same time.
Hmm.
And you know what?
This this freaks flattening the curve.
This just this sick fuck.
Yeah, I'm glad I'm not a freak like that.
But like, God bless him, he's flattening the curve.
You know, good for him.
Keep on keeping on.
But like far away from you got to have
like an ensemble that works with it.
Yeah, this guy in this picture.
Just wearing the fucking Polish.
It does not look correct.
No, we're wearing just a shirt.
He's not he's not he's not prepared for when life attacks.
He's putting on this mask as a lark.
This is a joke to him.
He looks like he's joking around.
He's dead eyes.
He's he's he's laughing at us on the inside.
Man, I never I never posted a picture.
Of myself wearing the the I have covid shirt.
And now I don't have covid anymore.
Oh, did you take a picture?
Well, no, I didn't.
I meant to because my dad regifted me the I have covid shirt that I got him.
He just he just gave it back to me for Christmas
because I had covid on Christmas and I just thought that was really funny.
But I never took a picture of it.
So, I mean, I like I could just put it on and do it now.
It would be cheating, of course, because I don't actually have covid.
I could go out and get covid and then just for the bit.
Like it really just for the pick. Yeah.
You like cough mid like picture take.
Somebody I hate I hate to call them out.
I hate to call them out.
No, no offense or anything to comment or Gary Hackett.
But I did see your comment on the last episode asking us to please quit talking
about covid and I just got to say, man.
Hey, man, we're living in the real world.
We're dealing with it.
You know, this is not a game.
This is not a joke.
This is this is reality.
We're talking about things that exist.
I'm sorry, covid.
I wish covid quit would quit talking about us.
There are lots of terrible things.
Honestly, I wish people would stop talking about NFTs.
We're talking about NFTs before.
Wish people would stop talking about those and they would go away.
They haven't.
No, Ben, we're about to talk about NFTs.
We've got to switch.
We've got to change topics.
Right.
But that's all I think about.
How about like covid then?
Yeah, they have a covid better than NFTs.
I saw a poll on Twitter like which would you you could you could destroy
one forever, NFTs or or covid?
And I was like, it's actually covid.
It's actually kind of hard.
Is it?
I don't know.
covid covid is making everything in the entire world bad.
OK, it's slightly.
OK, here's the the question, I guess, is yes.
Like obviously right now, covid is a bigger problem for me.
But will covid eventually not be such a huge problem?
Whereas NFTs will exist and continue to make the world a worse place forever.
Right.
If that's the case, I think maybe there's an argument for NFTs
being worse in the long haul.
Sure.
I mean, you don't know what's going to happen with covid.
It could be a new variant that is 10 times more deadly than the Omicron.
It's it's bounced back and now it's going to kill everyone again.
Oh, yeah.
Did you see there was like a news story I saw that was like.
This is like a parody.
This is like a joke.
Like I couldn't believe this was real.
It was like, oh, oh, we found it.
They found a a mutant strain that's like covid and Delta like merged into one.
No, no, no, no, sorry.
Omicron and Delta merge into one.
They're calling it Delta Cron.
It was like, shut up.
You know, they're not calling it.
Who's calling it?
So one guy who's actually you, you, you're calling it this.
You're calling it that and making and pretending it's news.
New York Times or the the sun or whoever.
Shut up.
Stop it.
Where's the like the scrotum variant going to come out?
That's not a Greek letter.
Yeah, well, Greek people have scrotums.
I guess some.
Oh, there is.
Is it up Salon that has like it's like it's a little W.
Wait, Greek.
There is one that is a little like round W.
Kind of looks like a ball sack, I guess.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, it's lower lower case omega.
Lower case omega.
Add total nuts, total and totally nuts.
There it is.
So there it is.
Yeah, Omega variant.
Omega lol, Omega lol, Omega lol variant is on is on its way, I'm sure.
I didn't hear about most of these variants.
I guess we must have gone through a bunch that nobody heard of.
Oh, well, whatever.
Yeah, death, you know, the world pandemic cares.
It is it's pretty it's pretty boring.
I mean, it is boring, actually.
It is it is it is what's what's the word I'm looking for?
Drury Drury.
Yeah, sure.
Droll, not Droll.
Droll means funny.
Droll, actually.
Droll means funny, actually.
I thought Droll was like a dull.
No, it just sounds like it sounds like it means that.
But it actually went.
OK, I think it's because I heard music.
Yeah, jokes on the Simpsons where someone would say, how Droll?
And like they say it like that and they say but they say they mean like, oh,
this is funny, but they're like a boring person with a British accent.
As all as all British people are Britishism must have been an old person term.
Yeah, the oldies would say that.
Yeah, the only time I ever heard it in pop culture was someone just someone boring,
describing something that is boring, but they're saying that it's funny.
So I think it's like why I got that mixed up.
Yeah, how how Droll?
Right.
How Droll drills you in the head.
How Droll?
Hmm, corn cob.
Don't. I say to the drill instructor,
don't put on the news that I that I got mad.
Huh?
You know, the drill, the drill, the account.
I was thinking of the tool.
No, that's that sucks.
The AI version of drill.
Can't wait to wear my AI generated drill tweets.
I've seen a few.
I think there's a couple different like drill AI accounts.
How is drill?
How is drill such a genius?
How does he just put banger after banger out every day?
He just has like a different mind, a better mind than the rest of us.
It's good. It is good.
He just does things the rest of us can only dream of with language.
We can't we couldn't do what drill does if we spent a million years practicing.
It's the way he is.
Just it's the way he says nutsack and shits out my ass.
That it's really like I guess.
Yeah, he puts it.
He puts those words in the perfect context.
Sure.
She's his his his his trade his trademark words.
Uh, man.
All right, I guess stop looking at Twitter.
Twitter's dumb. Twitter's bad.
Uh, there.
What else happened this week?
I'm floundering. I'm floundering.
I'm struggling. I'm struggling.
I'm struggling to fill time.
Hey, hey, audience.
This is me, Ben saying, admitting that I'm just filling time.
I'm just killing time.
I'm just here for a paycheck.
Listen, I don't want to be here.
I know that you, the listener, don't want to be here listening to this.
Why don't we just call it?
Why don't we just as a mutual as a mutual favor to one another?
I'll stop recording this podcast and you can stop listening.
Why not?
I saw on the last episode just came out
people like, oh, thank God, five hours of PCP content.
I'm like, Dan, they really, really want those long episodes.
They do. We've been recording.
I get it. Oh, no, not even two.
They're going to kill us. They're going to crucify us.
Genuinely, yeah, when we now, when we do a two hour episode,
everyone is like, what the fuck?
What the fuck? What am I supposed to do on my commute?
What am I supposed to do on my?
Yeah, drive quicker.
Yeah, yeah.
Make the train go faster.
Uh, yeah, they, they, they, they love it.
They love it. But why?
Why not? Listen, save us all the time.
Just just go pledge to the Patreon
and then just click unsubscribe and just forget about it.
Just forget we exist. All right. Listen, they'll save you the time.
We won't have to make them anymore.
Just just pledge and forget your pledged.
And we can all just we can all just go.
We can all we can all just you give me money
and I give you the freedom to not listen to the podcast.
I give you permission to stop listening.
I tell you, it's OK to quit. Yeah.
That's that's the curse.
You're you're you're you're not you're not actually allowed to stop listening
unless you have pledged.
It is a it is a transactional transaction.
It is a it is a deal.
The deal of a lifetime.
I mean, I guess the one thing.
The one other thing you give me five dollars a month,
you get you receive your life back, your freedom.
Breaker of chains, yeah.
Uh, the other thing that I've been thinking about recently,
because I've been watching Game of Thrones is like a world building.
And what about the worlds that I must build?
For my stupid comics that suck? Sure.
Oh, wouldn't that be great to have all that? Absolutely.
And I'm like, I go I go on like fantasy map generators
and I generate a bunch of like, oh, there's rivers here and there's a coastline
and we've got all these places and I can name them.
And I'm like, cool, the tools in my disposal to create this world
in such detail as George R. R. Martin creates his.
What a wonderful world I live in where I can I can make all these things.
And I just sit there looking at it and like, OK, well, any moment now,
I'll just make the I'll just do it.
I'll just make that world.
What do you have like any second like a drawing program open or something?
I got like a drawing program open.
I got like documents.
I'm like, OK, so what are the kingdoms called?
You know, yeah, you know, what?
You know, I can't probably think of anything good.
Let's never do anything.
Let's never do that. Let's never think about that again.
Absolutely.
Why is it so hard?
Why is it so hard to just to just create like a vast network
of interconnected like kingdoms and empires and and factions
and characters and and lore and history?
How's that so hard?
Why is that? So I kind of be easy.
Well, I kind of be snap my finger and it's done.
Oh, it is easy.
Oh, yeah, it is. You're just dumb.
That's all.
No, you're just you you're just uniquely bad at it.
Everybody, everybody has their own world and the lore.
And they've all just like, oh, yeah, you know, I I just didn't want to show anyone.
I made three of those before breakfast.
What? What are you talking about?
Everyone's got them in their drawer and they're just like,
yeah, I don't want to show you and I don't feel like I need to show you.
And you just have to suffer as the only person in the entire world
who is bad at doing that one thing that everyone else knows.
Damn.
Well, you see, it's it's actually because covid shrank the part of your brain
that is good at making maps and thinking, oh, well,
well, you better not get it or it'll be even worse.
Maybe that's why maybe my maybe I need that brain shrinkage
to increase the efficiency of my neurons.
Right. You've got too much.
You've got too much unnecessary padding in there.
It's it's keeping the world building my brain.
Deep record with covid.
Oh, just put the new one to each other.
And it just becomes like a fucking neutron bomb.
It's just dense like a neutron star.
That's that's what all those like a galaxy brain things mean.
That's what the image is of is if somebody right.
You you don't you don't want a big brain.
You want a small dense brain.
You want it to be you want to be compact is streamlined aerodynamic.
Sure. What? Why not?
Oh, that makes me you.
Uh, how is the I won't say any details.
How is the secret project going?
You kind of put it aside for December, right?
Have you been I put it aside for December
and I was going to I was going to fly out to America.
But there have been there's been time to work on it a little bit.
Yeah. So it may come out before February, probably in February.
OK. And it's looking very good.
It's it's it's it's based.
It's epic. I was I looked at a tweet by Tom
who was like saying, oh, it's cool to have like a big project
that you can release in secret, but it's shit for the algorithm.
Oh, I saw this tweet and I was like, it's true.
I probably would have more like interest in what I'm doing
when I release it, if people already were expecting something
like in you, what they were expecting to release.
I'll be honest, I'll be honest.
That tweet that tweet annoyed me.
I thought I think it's a wrongheaded attitude to take about it.
I I I feel similar.
But how am I going to drip feed for the algorithm?
Who cares? I generally agree.
Because the algorithm is like it's it sucks.
Even when it's good for you, it's it's never like you're doing.
It just happens.
You know, you know, it's more important than drip feeding the algorithm
having a fucking project that you finished. True.
That's like 10,000 times more important is making making the thing
not not hurting the thing into a drip feed of algorithm pleasing.
Yes, or whatever. Yeah.
Well, that aspect of like using it for the algorithm is is one thing.
But like, I think it's like otherwise generally true
that like or at least it gave me pause to be like,
should I have like announced this earlier?
Should I have like given somebody given people something?
Because I don't think anyone in the entire world is waiting
and with bated breath about what my secret project is.
They just know I've said it a few times.
They're like, yeah, come on, Gabe, just that nobody cares.
Well, I think it's yeah, I mean, why would they could they don't know what it is?
They don't know what it is, except a few patrons
who have listened to the Money Spenders podcast, where I explain it like
that there's no like images yet.
Here's here's what I think.
I think I think it doesn't really matter.
I think what matters is that when it's out,
people will like it and be impressed by it.
That's like so much more important than
than whatever, you know, that you
that you drip feed at it or something.
But it's not that I want to drip feed it for algorithm.
It's just sort of like, I don't know, sometimes it feels like.
I'm looking at it and I'm like, this is great.
This is amazing compared to like what I ever expected it to become.
But then I'm like, what if it's not amazing enough for anyone to give a shit?
Maybe we should work on this for another 20 years and never talk about it.
No, we shouldn't do that.
We should release it soon, sooner rather than later.
Release and like, I guess I guess I have the same sort of thoughts
about like Phantoms Revenge.
Like, I think it's I think it's great.
I think it's a masterpiece.
But is it like?
But is it? But is it like such harsh critics?
Well, OK, they see something that you worked really hard on.
And they don't know about that.
And they just sort of like, well, I'd rather play this other game that came out.
Right. Yeah.
And like that.
Yeah, it's kind of bad.
And I'm like, oh, that's going to happen to me.
It's not. Of course it would.
It's not that I'm worried that people will like say it's bad.
It's that the worst thing would be if like people are just like,
what is this? I don't get it. I don't care.
You know, if it just if it just gets no attention, which is like,
yeah, that could happen.
Yeah, it could happen.
Uh, I think I mean, I think it's good.
I think it deserves.
I think it deserves some attention.
And I think if I just if I just, I don't know, I'll just talk about it a lot.
I'll just like, I'll put it in front of people to the best extent that I can.
And I think and I think it's good enough and cool enough.
And there's enough in it that even if it's not like a smash hit or anything,
which like it won't be, but like, I don't know.
I think I think I think some people will will take notice and be like,
hey, this guy made a pretty good little video game.
Which, you know, what more can I ask for money?
Well, yeah, yeah, money, please.
Yeah, that's that's the my secret project is like, I don't know.
It's it's just closer to being releasable than it was before.
Sure. I'm going to be working on it tomorrow.
I have been I have not really been doing any work on Phantom's revenge
because it's it's basically done.
It actually needs what it needs is work done on converting it
to an HTML version that can like play in browser.
Because when I try to play it HTML in browser, it like is is
fucked up and broken for some reason.
And I need to figure out why that is.
So that's kind of important.
Yeah. So that's kind of important.
But then also, I've been making like an itch page for it, you know.
And so that's something that that's like, I think that's like mostly done.
Yeah, the page is basically looking fine.
Yeah, I got I'm putting off the fucking HTML.
Port, because that's like, it's going to be really fucking boring.
You're really fucking boring work that I don't want to.
I just don't want to do it.
I don't like I have no idea what's broken about it.
So I don't even know like where to start looking.
And I'm like, God, I hope it doesn't take me like two fucking weeks
of like work on it, just like just to make it work in another application.
Like that would suck.
But that's sometimes how it is.
Yeah, and getting things to work somewhere else.
I'm just really confused.
Like it's breaking in like weird ways that don't make any sense.
And I'm like, why?
Like, why are you doing that?
For instance, in this is just one problem.
The title screen, the title fades in from zero opacity to max opacity.
Right. That's it.
It just it fades in.
On HTML, it fades in and then it blinks back to zero.
And it starts like kind of fading in and then blinking back and fading in
and then blinking out and fading in. And it's like, are you joking?
Why are you literally like, why do you not know how to count?
Why does the function not know how to count in HTML?
What the fuck?
Just very bizarre.
So I'm not looking forward to it.
OK, anyway, the sort of thing you never think about.
No, I need the assets.
I need the code and the things to work.
No, I kind of thought I kind of thought it would just work.
Well, sure. But like, yeah.
There's so much about game development that's like invisible.
Yeah, like hours upon hours to make sure that when you press the menu button,
it does, in fact, open the menu. Yes.
It's true. It's it's sad.
But and then and then people aren't like impressed by that.
They're just like, they want it to work.
And if it doesn't work, they're going to piss their pants and scream.
Because of course they should.
Was that I think I think I think Brian Leo Malley on like form spring or something.
Someone asked him he was just answering people's questions.
And he said like he said something like
like like comics are really hard, like they're a lot of work.
Like every time you finish a page of a comic, it's like you feel
like you did so much like they should throw you a parade
because just because you finished one page.
But like, of course, nobody does.
And you just got to finish the next bit.
You got to make hundreds of pages before you're actually done.
That's how it feels. Right.
Game dev stuff, you make you make you make
you take a menu and you add like one more option to the menu.
You make you make the menu scroll.
And it's like I deserve a fucking monument built in my honor
in the in Central Park for this.
This was this was the hardest thing in the world.
But it's but it's completely invisible on the user end.
It's it's it's it's, you know, it's if it's designed well.
They don't even notice it. Right.
It's invisible. Yeah.
But I mean. Yeah.
I guess I guess all I can hope for is that, you know,
to typical rubes, typical laypeople will probably
will probably not appreciate all the effort that goes into making a game.
But I mean, and how would they? Right.
How would they know? How would they know? No, it's silly to expect them.
But you feel it in your gut when they like
when like a tiny problem.
Yeah, is the thing they they like, oh, that's terrible.
But you like you spent so long to try and get it even to that point.
It was so much worse before.
So many so many difficult things that go unappreciated.
But the final product is the only thing that really matters.
It does.
But I guess something that I can hope for is that maybe other people
who make who make their own games might see the game and be like, oh,
well, there's there's like, you know, I understand how much
how much must have gone into this.
Like this is more complicated than it looks.
Yeah, there's a lot of like art people who are like
impressed with other art people who follow art people.
And they're all talking about art and knowing about how it's created.
And sometimes it's like there's so many art people, especially on Twitter.
It's like, are there any like normal peers or any like normal people? No, no.
Any any rubes, any any lay people?
Yeah, any any filthy peasants who don't know how to hold a pencil?
Hey, if you're a rub, DM me.
Any rubes, rubes in the audience hit me up and
tell me about tell me about that.
Tell me about your Rube Goldberg machine.
Man, Phantom's Revenge, Big Effort Post, Big Effort Post.
Worth it? I don't know.
I just I just don't know.
Maybe perhaps one day, perhaps one day, I will have achieved something in my life.
And I will look back and say, oh, yeah, you know, things really turned around for me.
I think it was after I think it was after I spent a year making that game and I released that game.
And, you know, through some through some through some series of consequences of having done that that at the time I could never have foreseen.
You know, things really started to look up and change change the course of my life.
And now I'm and now I'm like and now I'm now I'm worth something.
That would be nice. A man can dream.
I think I mean, it's easy to be cynical about your own achievements.
But I think I've already kind of done that when I like made Balejape because it's like before that I was like a hobbyist artist.
I drew occasionally. I used to draw at school, but I was making videos.
I was like, I'm going to make a videos forever.
I feel like if I had stayed on that path, my life would be cringe.
Maybe I would have loads of subscribers or maybe not.
And maybe it would be like the same amount of money, maybe a lot more.
But I feel like I still would have eventually realized I didn't like it.
I'm glad I'm glad I have, you know, a comic under my belt already.
People like it and they remember it and they like the character and it's like, that's great.
There's parts of it I don't like.
There's parts of it that are stupid and bad, but like that, it's a good moment in my art career.
They decided to do that and now I'm doing comics. I'm doing things like that.
It can lead to bigger and better things right now.
Nothing has come of it really.
Nothing like substantial life changing.
I like the direction I'm going, I guess.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I feel like...
What's this thought that's coagulating that I'm trying to express?
It's like, I think...
I guess I already feel like I can make anything that I put my mind to.
I don't feel like I'm not where I need to be artistically or anything.
Not that I couldn't grow as an artist or anything like that, but I don't feel like I need to grow more before I can do the things I want to do.
I'm there. I'm good enough for everything.
All that's left to me now is to just continue to do stuff, make things that I want to be making, whatever those are.
That's all sorted.
The only other thing to think about is power, accruing power to crush my enemies while I continue to do that sort of thing on my own.
To get a big break?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't know. Heck, job storyboarding for a show or something.
That would be cool.
Something like that.
That's probably the only way that I could get some sort of big break.
Storyboard for a show or something.
The kind of artists that I know of who have gotten storyboarding gigs were way more successful than I am.
People someone might have actually heard of, someone like Ryan Pequen got a job storyboarding on a regular show.
You either got to have industry connections, it seems, or you actually have to be not zealust like Ben St. Famous.
And I say that word with disdain.
I spit that word in that contest.
You have to have a real following.
You have to be like a real guy.
And frankly, I'm just not a real guy.
I just can't do it.
It's all been for nothing.
So you think simultaneously that you can do anything, but that you're nothing as well?
Ability-wise, I can do anything.
Clout-wise, power-wise, I have nothing.
That's how it feels.
I'm held back just because nobody knows who I am.
That's the worst thing.
You've got a million-view video. Some people know who you are.
It's just not, I don't know.
Okay, the Sonichu video is fine and all.
Yeah, some people know who I am because of that video.
I don't think that video's existence earns me a lot of respect.
You know what I mean?
It's a Chris Chan video.
And Chris Chan is literally the lowest hanging fruit on the whole internet.
I think I would be lucky for someone with connections to be like,
Oh, Ben St., you mean the Sonichu lecture guy?
Yeah.
I'm neutral about that, right?
I think that's, you know, you know what I fucking mean.
I know.
I mean, I can't really relate because I've always had less clout than anyone.
I don't feel like I have much clout.
That's what I'm saying.
I just don't feel like I have clout.
I need it.
I need it to hurt people that deserve it.
I don't know.
Go to the clout mines.
I guess.
Chisel some out.
I don't know.
Oh, you gotta feed that algorithm.
Yeah.
Gotta drip feed that content.
Drip feed game dev vlogs.
Game dev vlogs.
GIFs dev vlogs.
I don't know.
I feel maybe it's because I haven't had like a large clout.
Exactly.
I've had like a middling sort of size and it's like, that's pretty cool.
I don't feel like I need to be like big.
Of course, money is always nice.
So that would be good.
I need to be bigger, but I don't want to do any of the things.
Well, same.
That's why it's like, oh, in order to like maximize your chances of getting all this clout,
you've got to do stuff that makes you miserable.
I'm like, God damn it.
No.
Honestly, I don't even know.
Honestly, I say that like, that's not even true.
I don't even know.
I don't even know like what I would need to do.
If I wanted to sell out and get clout and become a big guy,
I genuinely don't even know what I would need to do.
Well, you got to have a clear like thing you do.
When people say Ben St, they think of what?
Exactly.
That you got to have a very clear thing and then do collabs with people in the same field
until it's really like that seems to be what people do a lot.
Or they just get lucky and people find them anyway.
Yeah.
I don't know.
So I don't know long story short.
I'm just, I think I've had the same spiel before.
Just about how mad I am that I'm not more powerful.
You got to lift.
Oh, I haven't lifted in like three weeks.
That's the, that's the feeling.
I stopped for COVID and I have not resumed.
I mean, I do have to lift.
If I can't have social power, then I'll become physically more powerful.
I mean, why not?
I had, man, I was almost, I was almost up to deadlifting 300.
I'm sure I've lost like a ton off it now.
I'm going to have to reset down to like some bullshit, like 250 or something.
Maybe even lower.
I don't know.
Oh, well.
Oh, well, I'll get some fun.
I'll get some fun easy gains getting back to where I was.
I'll be, that'll be, that'll be a hoot.
I still have those sort of naive, like youthful imagination moments where I'm like,
oh, what if, what if, what if, what if Clarissa became like a cartoon and she was on TV?
That would be fucking sick.
Oh my God, people would like Clarissa.
And then I would go on to rule 34 and I would find rule 34 for her.
And it would be like, I've made it.
People are doing that of their own volition.
Yeah.
I don't really, I wouldn't really be, I mean, God, if someone came up to me and was like,
hey, Ben, this thing you made, we want to make a fucking TV show about it.
I mean, I'd be like, great.
Amazing.
I wouldn't really be like, I don't know, I wouldn't, it wouldn't feel.
You wouldn't talk about it?
I mean, I wouldn't, but I wouldn't be like, oh yeah, I want the thing to be on television.
I would be like, hey, if you want to do that, like it's not my thing, right?
Cause it's like, I wouldn't be making the show.
I guess maybe if they asked me, like, we want you to be, to work on the show,
to produce it for television.
I mean, I wouldn't, I wouldn't be like, oh yeah, I want the thing to be on television.
On the show to produce it for television.
I'd be like, sure, yeah, I'd do that.
And then maybe I would be excited about the product because it's like, okay,
this is what I am thinking.
That's what I was thinking.
I would have my Clarissa character comic books and it's like,
we want to turn this into a thing and maybe put on Netflix or whatever the fuck.
And I'm like, oh, oh yeah, I'll be the director and I'll tell people what to do.
And I'll look at, I'll say this voice actor would be great for this character
and say, okay, we'll see if we can get him.
I can't wait.
It's definitely going to happen in my head, in my fantasy.
Can we get Frankie Muniz as the bandit king?
Yes?
I don't know who that is.
I think I'm saying his name right.
It's the kid who played Malcolm in the middle.
I say kid, he's probably like 30 now.
I can't remember his voice.
You know Malcolm in the middle?
I do.
I've watched it many a time when I was younger.
He's 36.
That sounds about right.
He's got like brain cancer or something or he's got some kind of like,
he's got some kind of like brain problem.
Too big, probably.
He needs COVID.
Okay, but has he tried it though?
Don't knock it until you try it.
True.
Man.
Well, that was a tangent.
I don't even remember how we got on this topic.
Talking about projects and stuff.
Oh yeah, talking about Secret Project in January and whatnot.
I guess that rules out my Secret Project being a Clarissa television show,
if I've said that now.
It's not that.
Damn, I said I hoped to maybe get Phantom's Revenge released in January.
And with like the HTML version being all like, fucky, I just don't know.
I just don't know if it'll be possible or not.
Like I have no idea.
I won't know how long that's going to take to fix until it's fixed.
But, oh well.
In the meantime, I have been selling,
I have been selling Blu-rays.
I've sold maybe like, probably like 55 or something.
In total?
Something like that.
Probably, yeah.
I made a few more, I think I made a few more.
A few more people asked me for them after the last PCP came out.
Like a handful of other people messaged me.
So, pretty good.
It's definitely justified itself as an endeavor.
Like I said, I've got a big stack of them right here.
And as soon as this episode is over, I have to get back to,
I have another one in the burner and burn.
Yeah, I think I got like four more to go or something.
Okay, suddenly unlocked a memory of like every computer in the house
burning a DVD for something because we were making DVDs.
Were you like converting like VHS tapes to DVD or something?
No.
It was, okay, you know the agunary thing I do?
Yeah.
Haven't done it for past few years because of COVID.
Yeah, true.
But for a while there have been like, all the scout camp leaders,
they get like a little digital camera and a little video camera
that they can record things with.
And we used to make DVDs for the camp mates to like,
oh, this is what happened on all these days.
And here's some, so a slideshow and a thing.
Yeah, sure.
And we were making DVDs for everyone.
And that's a nice memory for some reason.
All the houses is like, okay, mom and dad got a computer,
I got a computer, gotta get all the computers,
make a bunch of DVDs with them.
Man, just imagine how shit it would be
to have someone, to be like a caregiver for like,
someone who's like, you know, learning disabled
or like mentally impaired or something.
And like, you have to like, you have to like take care of them
like through COVID and like keep them like,
Oh, god.
You gotta make them comply with fucking CDC regulations
and like explain shit to them.
And like, they gotta deal with it.
And you gotta deal with it.
Wow.
It's terrible.
It would suck.
It'd be so fucking bad.
I'm sure like carers have like,
they're allowed to visit the houses of people they give care to,
like elderly people or people with disabilities.
They should wear a mask and isolate with them or something.
Of course.
But it would be very, I mean, I'm sure when it was like
lockdown in the UK, you couldn't go anywhere.
You couldn't go outside unless you were exercising
or shopping for food.
And it's like, that would have been the worst for everyone,
but especially disabled people.
Man, lockdown was awesome.
We should go back.
Lockdown was great.
No worries.
Never had to worry about what you were doing.
Never had to worry about looking like a loser.
You were doing nothing.
Never had to worry about looking like a loser
because you got no plans on a Friday night.
Now those were the days.
Well, it's the same as normal.
It's just that nobody expects you to have plans.
Right, exactly.
I mean, yeah.
It's like, what are you doing this Friday?
Oh, you know, interesting things and stuff
that you wouldn't possibly understand.
What I'm saying is back during lockdown,
nobody asked that question.
And that was just the way I liked it, actually.
Every time somebody says,
hey, are you doing something later?
You should say, yeah, I'm going to kill you.
Yeah, I'm going to.
Yes, I'm going to kill you.
You're going to die.
Hmm.
Fascinating.
That's another way to make people stop asking.
Hmm.
Well, yeah, I'm lost in the sea.
Lost at sea.
I'm also lost at sea by Brian.
Leo Malley.
Not Brian Clevenger, Brian Leo Malley.
Not the same.
Very different.
You know who Brian Clevenger is?
Nope.
He was the artist of the Sprite comic called the 8-Bit Theater.
I don't know if you've ever heard of 8-Bit Theater.
I don't know what it is, but I think I've heard it.
It's a Sprite comic with the Sprites from the original Final Fantasy.
There's Black Mage and Red Mage and Thief and so on.
Right.
White Mage.
It's those guys.
It was fine and all.
He wrote a book.
And because I read his webcomic, I bought his book.
And his book sucks.
It was called Nuclear Age, I think it was called.
It was about a superhero and it was fucking bad.
Even as a kid, I was like, wow, this is bad.
This is like a bad.
I'm not finishing this.
Give me a break.
Yeah.
Do you want to go to voicemails?
Yes.
Run out of topics.
Yeah, let's do it.
You just ran out of the unimportant ones.
They're keeping your synapses far apart.
Making it take too long to think.
Alright, let's do it.
The first one is an image link.
Let's see.
Alright.
It's okay, I got to look at the big version.
Ben, we need to talk.
It's Tom and me and Ben.
Sure, I look so happy.
Gib and I are thinking of leaving the PCP.
Okay.
Huh, you're not mad.
Why would I be mad?
I don't want to keep you here against your will.
Then it's settled.
The podcast is over.
Over?
The podcast will go on.
I'm not sure what...
Wait.
What is this?
Is it...
Yeah, probably.
The nostalgia critic camp, so it's probably...
The podcast will go on.
Those eyes, those little eyes of mine,
that's my face when the podcast will go on.
No matter what.
Sure, I'll keep the podcast running until I'm dead.
What else am I going to do?
I appreciate this.
This is funny.
This is nice.
It is funny.
I like that I have a color.
Ben, your color is black.
Tom's is gray, I guess.
Should I make Tom red?
Tom's color is red.
Tom's color is red, but...
I don't see him wearing red.
You just turned into a skull.
And Tom turned into...
An old Chinese man?
Yeah.
Sure.
Just like in real life.
Well, hey, another fucking masterpiece of a voicemail.
Okay, the next one is called...
What is that noise?
Three, two, one, go.
Do you guys remember the yellow argument?
Good times.
I don't know.
Is it like jacking off or something?
It didn't sound like anything.
It just sounds like you're hitting something.
I do remember the yellow argument.
Sure, I remember the yellow argument.
Stupid.
The thing I remember most from the yellow argument,
from my perspective, is that I tried to play cold play yellow,
but I didn't know how to play it.
And I fucked it up.
I thought it would have been funnier if I had played it better.
Oh, like you're talking about on the episode?
On the episode, I brought out my guitar and I started playing cold plays yellow.
I'll be honest, I wouldn't recognize that song.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, yes, I would.
And it was...
Yeah.
It was for you.
And it was all yellow.
Yeah, I might not have recognized that song if it was just on an acoustic guitar.
Yeah, it was probably inaudible.
But I remember being like, oh, I'm so embarrassed.
I didn't figure out the chords quickly enough.
I didn't want the moment to pass.
Oh, it was so bad.
Alas, alas.
Well, road's not taken, traveled.
Next one is called Ben St. at Night.
Three, two, one, go.
It's just a scratch.
I don't get it.
Again, was it was it jacking off?
Was the sound jacking off?
Everything sounds like jacking off to me.
It doesn't.
It was just like somebody rubbing like a piece of plastic against another piece of plastic
or some sort of rough surface.
Well, the first one.
I don't get it.
The first one was rubbing, but then at the end there was a little like...
A couple little smacking sound?
I don't know.
I don't get it.
It's too subtle.
This comedy is too subtle for me.
Absolutely.
Delight like most comedy.
Next voicemail is called Hi.
Three, two, one, go.
Is it incredibly quiet for you as well?
I could hear something?
It's like a mouse taking a bite of a cookie.
That's the sort of sound it was.
All right.
Well, thanks for the fucking voicemail, Joker.
Little mouse.
Next one is an image.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, okay.
Low energy talking, true.
Oh, it's me and Ben, low energy talking.
Ben and Tom, doom and gloom talking.
Everything is fucked.
I believe that's true.
Gib and Tom, very nice episode without Ben's bullshit.
Unfortunately, it happened only once.
Yeah, true, true.
Ben, Gib and Tom, PCP at its peak.
All annoying hosts are gone, not including Mage.
All right, Mage is right.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, master risk.
Yeah.
Ben, Gib, Tom and guests, what the PCP used to be.
Just Ben, shit episode, but seeing him alone is extremely funny.
I listen.
I agree with most of these.
I do agree with, I mean, I don't remember the one that was just you and Tom.
I have no opinion about that.
My bullshit is great, actually, and you'd miss it.
You'd miss it if it was gone.
I can't remember what we talked about on that.
I think it was mostly about art stuff, which is, I guess, my favorite conversation topic,
because I'm always creating.
I'm always thinking about creating.
I think what the PCP used to be is just anytime we have a bunch of guests,
like a bunch of guests, like Cybershell, Oblivion, Fall, Fisnaker.
It felt like the old PCP, because I was like,
When we have like seven.
Okay, I'll say something now.
Oh, wait, no, I can't speak.
There's too many people speaking over me.
Okay, I'll be quiet.
Yeah.
I'll wait.
Classic PCP moment.
Classic magical moments.
All right.
Yeah, good.
It's true.
It's all true.
All right.
Next one is another image thrown up.
What is this?
Okay.
It's okay.
Oh, this is about the logo.
This is about the Shekels for Heckels logo.
Right?
Oh, okay.
Sure.
Alpha Libra.
It looks like an F, though.
That's why I put it for the F.
Oh, I see.
I never even thought about it.
I never even thought about it, but...
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, I...
Yeah, okay.
I mean, he's got a point, I guess.
Hang on.
But they changed the Euro to be the E.
But it looks more like a C, which is why I put it for the C.
But they didn't replace the other E's,
or the other L with the Libra.
So what's the choices?
What's the choices?
Yeah, all the S's should be dollars.
All the E's should be Euros, I guess.
It should be like a typing quirk.
Really hard to read.
All the L's should be whatever.
Libras.
That would be a pretty good typing quirk
for a greedy capitalist troll.
Every currency symbol that looks like a letter
he just uses in place of that letter.
Oh, the Yen would be a perfect Y.
Exactly.
Pokedollars, of course, would make a great P for pounds.
I wonder how many currencies of signal or signs there are.
There's ones that aren't used anymore, like the Frank.
There must be...
I don't even know what the sign is.
Right, right.
There must be so fucking many.
I wouldn't be surprised if you could fill most of the alphabet with them.
There's probably a few that they don't have.
There's probably none that's like an X.
No, maybe.
I don't know.
There's probably some crypto that's X.
Oh yeah, XRP Ripple.
Yeah.
Just use Ripple.
With crypto, everything's possible.
Oh my god.
Blockchain technology.
Okay.
Next one is called...
Is it update on an old friend from an old friend?
That's the next one, right?
Yep.
Yeah, okay.
3, 2, 1, go.
Oh, the new Davoo video.
Yeah, Davoo put out a new video.
Did you see that?
Oh, I did.
I did.
Good for her.
But I'm extremely jealous of how good her voice is,
and I couldn't watch it.
I felt bad.
Oh, really?
Made me feel bad.
But it's not her fault.
It's no hate.
I was just like, oh god, no.
She sure does sound different.
It's true.
Completely different.
Although she talks really slowly in that video?
Or now maybe she just talks really slow now?
There was a part that made me roll my eyes where she claims like,
yeah, before talking in my old voice,
it always made me feel like physical pain.
And then I realized that it was because my voice was too deep.
Shut up.
No, it didn't.
There's a certain aspect of transitioning where once you feel gender euphoria,
because you've never felt it before,
you suddenly realize how much you didn't like everything previously.
You had a general level of unhappiness going on,
and it's invisible to you because that's all you've ever known.
I can imagine that it feels like that way,
but it is maybe a little over the top to say physical pain.
You know what?
I'm paraphrasing.
She said something like it...
I think she said it caused her pain or something like,
yeah, whatever.
I'll buy it.
I felt similar things to similar stuff.
I was surprised.
She talked really slow.
At least threw a lot of it.
I think that video...
You know, it's a video about Fival American Tale, I guess.
It sort of claims to be a review.
It's not a review at all.
It's basically just like some light commentary about some things in the game.
I'm pretty sure that it's basically just like a soft, sort of coming out video, basically,
but doesn't call itself that.
The purpose of the video is to come out,
hey guys, I'm trans now,
but it's not calling itself that.
No, it's a video about Fival.
But in it, I will take a brief aside to be like,
yeah, I transition, this is my new voice, blah blah blah blah, whatever,
which is fine, which is fine.
I should probably just message her to ask how,
like what she did to train it,
just because I don't know.
Perhaps.
I would like knowledge about that.
That's fair.
That would be a reasonable thing to do if you want to know about that, I guess.
I don't know.
What can I say?
Davoo, I guess I'll get into it.
Davoo messaged me before putting that video out,
like a few days before, maybe a week before or something,
and said like,
Ben, I'm thinking about,
I'm thinking that maybe I might,
you know, sort of come back to the internet a little bit.
Like I made a Discord server and everything,
and I'm like, okay.
And she said like,
but I wanted to tell you that,
I actually just want you to know,
so you're not surprised,
that I don't agree with what you were doing
with the paying people to unpledge from Trixie's Patreon.
So I just want you to know that I don't think that,
I'm not for that, I don't think that's right or whatever.
And I just like,
I don't know, shut the fuck up.
Shut the fuck up, go away.
Piss off, I don't fucking care.
You idiot, you fucking moron.
You're a fucking rube.
Davoo messaged me all the time to tell me about how much,
how bad Trixie was to her,
and how much she mistreated her and stuff.
And then I'd be like,
well you should say something about it,
and she'd say no,
no I can't,
because what if something bad happens,
what if somebody got mad at me,
I can't say anything about it,
but you should keep saying it though.
I like what you're saying,
but I'm not going to say anything.
But actually, I don't agree with,
you shouldn't mess with someone's income, Ben.
It's wrong to mess with someone's income,
even if they abuse me or whatever,
whatever I said, I don't remember.
That's too far, that's too far, I don't agree with that.
Shut the fuck up.
I hate Davoo, fuck Davoo.
That's my statement about that.
The end.
Any thoughts?
Incredibly transphobic Ben saying that again.
True, true.
What can I say?
I'm just, I'm the product of my society.
Alright.
That's all I have to say about Davoo's new video.
Next one is called,
VVV Saber Dub, please?
Maybe.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello again, Benjamin St.
Hello.
SaberSpark64 has released yet another video,
reviewing Halo Infinite, it looks like.
Okay.
Would you mind telling me if it's narrated by Tom or Saber?
Why would you ask this?
I don't, I still.
Don't even want to click it, don't want to chance it.
Still went on the dub of that one video,
but like, I'm still going to listen to the ones that are like,
primarily with Tom.
That's all.
I'm confused.
What, what dub is he talking about?
I think he left another voicemail a while ago,
asking you to please dub over or have Tom dub over at SaberSpark 64 video
where SaberSpark was speaking, cause he didn't like hearing SaberSpark.
Right.
I also don't like SaberSpark's voice.
I don't like the way he talks in his videos.
It's a common affliction with YouTubers.
He's one of them.
Yeah, man.
I'll get right on that.
Right after I, right after I get the HTML board of the game.
You should do dubs of all the SaberSpark videos.
Yeah, just start a new channel.
I'll start a new channel.
It's called, it's called SaberSpark 64 dubs.
And it's, I just re-upload every SaberSpark 64 video with my voice.
And then I make a fucking blu-ray about it.
Oh, if you're so, if you, if you like it so much, why did you make a fucking blu-ray about it?
Uh, I guess I will.
I can do that now.
Now that, now there's how you gain clout.
Now there's a move to get, to blow up on social-
The blu-ray guy.
Oh, blue saint.
Now there's a drip feed for your social media engagement, whatever.
Um, next voicemail is called Rod Serling, Life Without Enemies.
Three, two, one, go.
Imagine if you will, a world in which tricks of the golden bitch had never existed.
Ben Sainz is on this cathedral throne, lethargic.
He opens up Twitter on his phone, but who is there to even talk shit on for the third time this week?
He fancies that he should do something productive, but wears the grievance that nemesis from whom to draw the motivation of pure spite which sets him about his projects.
When is Radcom five?
What is even the point when there is no subject for jokes about deleting one of the lecture recordings?
Finally, our saint decides to try and get himself some bitches on Tinder.
He cannot.
The connection he makes remains an entirely shadow.
He finds himself to his despair, unable to even remember love.
So to everyone with an anime, you'd better treasure that golden bitch,
for without villains, no revenge, not even a phantoms, soon available on itch.
Oh, nice.
Hey, that was great.
I liked that a lot.
And it's true.
I like the idea that if, like, Trixie existing means you get bitches on Tinder.
Yeah, if only Trixie had not existed.
Okay, it's the bad timeline.
It's the bad timeline.
Wait, oh wait, no, in real light, yeah.
Because in this alternate timeline, no Trixie, no Blu-rays, no Radcon, no bitches.
Yeah, it's true.
It's the worst possible future.
Good thing Trixie is all too real, and the bitches all too plentiful.
Very, very good.
I have nothing to add.
You nailed it.
Okay, next one is called, next one is X3.
Three, two, one, go.
He is almost here.
Oh, development.
Oh, almost.
This is just Lord English.
Something's happening.
Next one is called, it's a minute long, and it looks like it's a real question.
It's called Christian YouTube Censorship.
Three, two, one, go.
What's up, PCP?
Dusty Dumps slash The Wall Guy here.
Yes.
Last week, I sent a, PCP presents The Wall.
I saw you commented on the last one.
But I realized that the lyrics were pretty hard to discern as I was going through COVID at the time.
I mean, I still am kind of.
Oh, bummer.
I was like, okay, I'll just post the lyrics in the comments.
That'll be great.
People can sing along at home.
It'll be a good time for everyone.
But whenever I would post the lyrics, they would, the comment would be automatically deleted.
So I was like, what's the deal?
So I tried experimenting on a bunch of different videos, commenting different things.
It seems to me that YouTube now automatically just like auto-deletes a comment with swearing in it.
And not just swearing, even like illusions to swearing.
Even if you like try to.
Use like an asterisk.
Like censor it or put in some sort of like censor marks or just like take out the word.
YouTube just like automatically detects, oh, you're trying to swear here, boy.
And deletes your comments.
Did you know about this?
What's the deal with that?
I mean, I've seen comments disappear seemingly randomly.
So I mean, it doesn't surprise me that much.
I mean, I guess it's hard to notice when comments have not been showing up.
Because you don't know that they should be there.
I mean, I feel like they've seen swears though.
There are definitely swears in comments.
I think unless something changed and I haven't been paying attention.
Could it be like your account settings, maybe?
Could it be just like a you thing?
I don't know.
It could be blacklisted.
Maybe.
It's definitely a thing YouTube has the power to do is to know your user, your Google account.
Say, oh, that person.
Like, why?
I don't know.
No, nobody knows.
God, I hope you figure out how to swear in the comments.
Everybody in the comments say a swear word.
Cuss in the comments.
Let's figure this out.
Just say the most vile shit down there, please.
And thank you.
OK, next one is called Fucking with Trixie 3 from PJWorthman at Hotmail.com.
Three, two, one, go.
All right, Ben.
So you got the book, Road to Radcon Finish.
You got the plebe and the weed, blue rays, out.
There's still one more thing you can do to fuck with Trixie.
Is it Cus Omega?
You got to do the Brony Lecture.
I mean, it can even be the Brony Lecture Lecture where you just talk about all the dumb bullshit that surrounded it and why this dumb video about ponies never came out.
I think it could be fun.
One last way to fucking get at them.
And then every Radcon obligation is finished.
Pretty cool.
Also, is there a way I can get the plebe and the weed, blue ray and the Radcon book together as a bundle?
Shipping to Canada isn't cheap.
PCP forever, Tom will never die, call me back.
I think I might have said this before, but yeah, if we ever did some sort of Radcon 5 or equivalent, I probably would do a Brony Lecture Lecture.
It probably wouldn't be very long, but it would be pretty funny.
Yeah, I probably would do something like that.
It's a very funny idea.
No, you can't buy them as a bundle because they have to go in separate envelopes.
I have to ship them separately.
I'm sorry.
I know international shipping, especially on the blue ray, is kind of shit, but I'm sorry.
They charge me $15 to send a fucking DVD box anywhere outside of the United States.
Wait, are they not flat enough?
They are not thin enough to be considered envelopes.
They are too thick.
They are considered packages.
It varies, but it costs between $13 up to $19 to send it depending on the country, which is a bit lame, but I don't know.
That's what they make me do.
Inside of the US, it's not so bad because they have a program called Media Mail, which is basically just...
If your mail is just books or recorded video content or a small list of things like that, you could just mail it cheaper.
They just will give you a discount on mailing, but it doesn't extend internationally, so I have to...
Sorry about that.
I'm sorry.
There is no bulk discount for the plebe and the weeb and the Road to Radcon.
However, if you are a patron, you do get $5 off of the Road to Radcon.
And of course, if you backed the plebe and weeb Kickstarter and you show me a screenshot of your pledge at the $40 tier or higher,
I will give you $20 off that.
If you didn't, you're fucked.
Sorry.
Anyway, yes, good voicemail.
Next one.
ASMR, I said it wrong and I'm not re-recording.
My break is over.
Three, two, one, go.
Can I request a view of a longer-form video?
I'm working 12 hours every day.
Sorry, this is a mere two-hour, 30-minute podcast.
12 hours of an AMSR friend simulator.
No, fuck you.
You're no friend of mine.
I said, yeah, buddy.
Going forward, we're getting through this.
You won me.
Yeah.
I need something to get me through this.
Yeah, well.
Oh, you sound haggard.
You sound destroyed, defeated.
Boy, damn, you really could use a friend, huh?
Well, oh well.
Next voicemail.
No, here's what you do.
You play the procrastination podcast like normal and you turn the speed to 0.5 and then it takes longer.
Listen, Mr. ASMR, as Trixie famously said, I don't have to listen to you just because you give me money, all right?
So fuck you.
I'm assuming you're a patron since you want to be our friend so bad.
Best way to become our real-life best friend would be to draw $5 in the Patreon, in my opinion.
It's the first step of a 1,000-mile journey.
Next voicemail is called Kyle and Funny Man.
The Space from TheSpaceEpic at PewPew.com.
Three, two, one, go.
One name's Kyle, the other is a Funny Man.
It's Kyle and Funny Man in Space.
Yeah, that's right. This voicemail storyline was no joke.
This is literally going to go for 18 episodes.
Yeah, continuity.
Now it'll be like an epic five-minute one,
paying off all the storylines and all the epic lore and stuff.
I hope so, or else what was the point?
Stop in.
Don't waste my time.
Get ready.
I'm ready.
Hey, Funny Man.
I don't watch movies, but I listen to these voicemails.
I really got to use the toilet because I get some real nasty space stew.
Taco Bell? Okay.
Okay.
Yep.
It'll do it.
It might take a bit longer still.
Why is that funny, man?
Are you having some diarrhea in there?
No, it's actually quite the opposite.
I'm having dry dubs.
Good for him.
Oh my God, Funny Man.
You would have referenced that.
Oh my God.
That's it.
I'm showing it for life here on the space station.
This is good.
This is great stuff.
The audience at home, literally probably when I said that,
because that's the thing that people in the PCP,
the audience remembers.
And we're going to go for...
Remembers from like two weeks ago.
And oh my God, I get so excited for the future because oh my God,
we're going to go into the funny fucking adventures.
Oh, this is so fucking good.
This is the beginning of a beautiful arc, I think.
This is on the road to like Voice Grail.
It's getting there.
All it needs, I would say at this point,
all it needs is a like 15 minute long,
like fully musical finale.
Like you're there.
You just got to bring it home.
You've built up the bond with the audience.
You just got to stick the landing.
And we'll have a classic on our hand.
You got an intro song.
You got a guy thoroughly explaining the point of the thing immediately.
It's all the ingredients.
Front loading before the actual show begins.
All the ingredients.
So people are all like on the same page.
All the ingredients of greatness.
Next voicemail is called Endless Wordle.
Three, two, one, go.
Day five in Wordle office, RFCK.
I can't see anything.
I'm looking for the updates.
I'm looking for what's being updated on the game.
I'm looking for if there's possible bugs I have to take account of.
I can't see anything.
I can't fucking see anything.
I have to scroll through 100,000 fucking moon runes of little baby blocks
being built up from the top down down to a fucking pyramid.
And I can't fucking understand anything.
And then I find out that they're not even fucking playing the game.
They're not even playing Wordle by posting that.
They're just updating each other on their fucking progress.
It's...
Wait.
Does this guy not understand Wordle?
Has he just seen the tweets and not thought to Google it?
I guess this is an Endless War dev and like Endless War...
Is Endless War being flooded with Wordle squares?
Perhaps.
That would be funny.
I would support that.
The Endless War kids gotta get a fucking education.
They need to learn to spell.
About time.
Next one is Tony.
It's Tony.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, this is Tony.
So the last voicemail message I sent,
I was talking about how I always skip the voicemail messages being read in the podcast.
So I've never heard my own voicemails being read.
And I would like to, but I don't know how to solve this problem.
Because I don't know what episodes I...
My messages are in and I don't know what the timestamp is.
So I guess I'm just kind of fucked.
Yeah.
That's all.
Well...
Episode 2...
Wait, what is this?
Is this 291?
Gib?
Okay.
She's muted.
Whatever.
I think this is episode 291.
Episode 291.
Gotcha, buddy.
You're in there.
No problem.
Alright.
Next one...
I'm just gonna continue.
I'm just gonna go ahead.
So this one is a Google Drive link from Solaru, I think?
It didn't work.
The copy-paste didn't work.
Did I have to leave the underscore off the end?
Unfortunately, I'm getting a...
Sorry, the file you have requested does not exist.
I am sorry.
Well, if this is from Solaru...
Oh no, I'm bad at this.
At home sick.
Well, you are bad at it.
I'm sorry, the link didn't work.
I'm sorry.
Try again, maybe.
Alright.
Gib said BRB and I...
The next one is for her, I think?
So I'm just gonna...
I will just hit the bathroom for a second.
You know what?
I don't even have to say this.
Just cut this out.
We'll just take a pause.
LA's are.
Just cut this part out.
I'm just gonna go and I'll be back in a minute.
And maybe Gib will be back.
And this is not for anyone.
This is not for the audience to hear.
This is secret.
Alright.
It was just in time to see you unmute.
Okay, good.
Sorry, it was a matter of fecal urgency.
Okay.
I suddenly needed to shit and I had no time to explain.
Acceptable.
Acceptable reason.
Okay, well the next one was a Google Drive link, but it didn't work.
I couldn't get the link to work, unfortunately.
Uh, Google...
Wait, there are two dashes in the middle of that.
Are they supposed to be there?
Are they not supposed to?
I don't think dashes exist in files.
Oh no, I got rid of them.
It still doesn't work.
Yeah, I tried getting rid of the underscore at the end and that also didn't help.
Sorry, that's too bad.
But anyway, the next one seems like it's for you.
It's an image from Giant Gazongas Gib at Girl Gamer.
Oh, base.
Alright, here we go.
Whoa, this is like cool.
It's like a real drawing.
Wait, what is this?
Actually, me taking my entire online career was a bit, a ruse, a Kafka-esque,
meta-allegorical critique on houses.
Is that supposed to be Trixie?
That, I think, is supposed to be Trixie.
It's a very flattering portrayal of her hair in particular.
And the People's Choice Podcast Award for the funniest joke goes to Miss Bonte.
Miss Bonte.
For the iconic line, you give them an inch, they'll take my splinge.
Who could forget?
Oh, it's iconic only because it was a tag.
It's such a nothing coming out of it.
Total afterthought, but now it's our tagline.
Now it's the title of this episode.
Maybe not, actually.
It's not very Google-friendly.
This is really nice.
Look at those Pozongas.
I'm looking respectfully.
Is that the People's Choice Podcast Award for funniest joke?
Is that Bill Clinton?
I don't know who that is.
I think it's just a guy.
I'm not sure who it's supposed to be.
This is a really nice drawing.
I'm going to save that to the fan art folder.
This is great, yeah.
Actually, me and me tanking my entire online career was a bit a ruse.
A Kafka-esque meta-allegorical...
She doesn't know what Kafka-esque is.
I don't...
I'm trying to think if I've ever heard her use the freight.
Probably, I don't know.
She's probably heard people say it.
I'm sure she's never read any Kafka.
I read one Kafka.
I read Metamorphosis when I was like 13.
Maybe even younger.
My dad got me to read it for some fucked up reason.
I'm going to get anything out of that when I'm a fucking kid.
Give me a break.
Anyway...
Pozongas Gib Girl Gamer.
Naming the file.
This is great.
Thank you.
I think we've just got one more...
Yeah.
Just one more image from Pick at COVID Daredevil.
Sure.
Oh.
COVID Daredevil versus the Thousand Lung Man.
When...
I don't remember the COVID Daredevil.
I also...
Was that a thing when I wasn't there?
I'll be honest.
It doesn't ring a bell.
But just because I don't remember something doesn't mean anything.
I do remember a joke involving like COVID not actually being bad.
In fact, it gives you super...
No, I do remember.
Oh, yes.
The COVID Daredevil.
Right.
It makes you lose your sense of smell and taste, but it boosts your other senses.
Yes.
But I think the COVID Daredevil was also blind for unrelated reasons.
She just happened to also be blind.
And she's a big titty lady.
And guess why not?
I get...
Yeah.
I'm sure.
Thousand Lung Man.
So wait.
Is this implying...
Is that a vaccine?
Or is it like...
I believe...
The Daredevil is using COVID to defeat the person with loads of lungs.
Yeah.
It says Omega variant, so it's not the vaccine.
It's COVID.
The COVID Daredevil.
Because, I mean, she has COVID, right?
And it's good.
It's the source of her power.
Her inability to smell things.
If her sense of smell were to...
If she were to not have COVID and her sense of smell and taste were to return.
If that part of her brain were to grow back.
I mean, her other power, her many other powers would just dissipate.
In the middle of battle, she would find herself unable to compete in the free market.
I don't know.
These lungs are disgusting.
They look like the funny chins on that King Goblin or King Troll in the Hobbit movie.
I didn't see any of the Hobbit movies.
There's like a...
The Goblin King, and he's got like a big nut sack, ball sack chin that's flabby and gross.
Hobbit?
Oh, I gotta see this.
I'm sold.
Is he the Great Goblin?
I forget his name.
He's like a king of something.
Yeah, he's just got a big sagging jowl chin.
Well, that's gross.
Good for him.
At least he doesn't have COVID.
But at least he can smell, idiot.
Yeah.
We did it.
That's it.
I want to quickly clarify because I feel bad for accidentally saying the image that I looked at was like,
oh, it's like a real drawing.
It's not to say that other drawings are not real drawings.
It's just like clearly like a higher level of like artistic skill, you know?
Oh, I don't want to clarify.
I want to clarify.
Like I didn't mean that the other ones aren't drawings.
I just mean that this one was good and those ones were bad.
This one was like markedly gooder.
It does.
It does have anatomy.
It's definitely got anatomy.
Yes.
It's got anatomy.
When you're drawing big bazongas, there's only two ways you can go.
Anatomy or large circle, very big.
Large circle, comma, very big.
That's, you know, wait, wait, did you know that Ernest Hemingway was once challenged to write the saddest story in the world?
In only four words?
And he wrote large circle, very big.
No.
That's not a sad story.
I like that story.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, he failed.
He failed the challenge.
He lost.
The most erotic story, large circle.
Large circle, very big.
Excellent.
All right.
We have, we have done it.
We have, we have recorded it despite, despite everything.
We have recorded another podcast this week.
Despite everything.
It's still the PCP.
It's true.
It's truer now than ever before.
We're in fact more the PCP than we ever were.
Heck, I got nothing else to say.
I'm done.
I'll see.
I'll see you all next week.
Yeah.
Have a good week, you fools.
Have a good one.
Don't get, don't get Omicron.
Don't get COVID.
And if you do, hope it gives you benefits, boosts to your other senses.
Of course.
Yeah.
Don't, don't get COVID.
But if you do, buy the shirt.
Yes, definitely.
Buy a fucking, buy the Bane mask, buy the Bane mask.
I expect it's going to do great things for me.
Hell yeah.
Okay.
That's it.
Peace out.
Nice.
Thanks for listening.
Bye.