Get out of me swamp. Welcome everybody. Get out of my swamp. It's the PCP. I'm the best
guy ever. We've got Ben Saint in his swamp. I'm here. I'm showering in mud and farting
to kill fish. That's the thing. And Tom Oliver. I'm still sick post-radcon with not coronavirus
and it's pretty annoying. It's pretty fucking annoying. I don't feel like sick. Like I have
a disease but I feel like really tired all the time. Yeah. I'm back to 100% feeling and
my only issue now is I need to start exercising because I know I'll feel better. I will probably
feel better if I started exercising again. I just feel like I wake up early. I've been
waking up early lately and then like three hours later I'm like, man, can I go back to
bed again? And then I just feel like that for the rest of the day. It's based. Exercise
would probably help. Probably. Real recommendation anyway. I called my doctor and they were like,
it sounds like you have a sinus infection. Go get a sinus infection medication. I'm just
like, I don't want to go to a pharmacy. That seems like the worst place to go during a
pandemic where all the sick people go. Just wear a mask. Put your scarf over your face.
No, I'm a scared populist person who watches too many scary things. I mean, I don't want
to go outside either, but like I have to go out for like groceries and stuff. I'm a go
to the grocery store probably. Wait, have you been using Instacart? Yes. How? I've tried
to use Instacart a bunch of times and they're all like, oh yeah, there's no deliverers available
not for like four days. Probably because you're in Boston and I'm in the middle of nowhere.
Wouldn't that, I feel like that would make me more likely to be able to. No, because
there's more demand. There's more supply, but there's way more demand because you're
in a city. I guess that makes sense. They're legitimately not available because they're
busy. I mean, maybe it's just that they're too busy and not that nobody wants to do
it. Right, right. Yeah, it could be. Like when I order Instacart, it's like, hey, your
order will be here by 2pm, like okay, and then like it'll be delayed like four times
and then it'll get there like seven at night. Right, right. You know, I should do that.
I want to, I'm working from home. I'm working on all these Radcon videos and stuff. I should
just fucking Instacart. What do I do? Well, apparently Instacart workers are organizing
a strike soon. So maybe I shouldn't, maybe I shouldn't strike break. My friend works
does Instacart and he showed me like the payouts and they're pathetic and terrible and bad.
And I was like, why are you doing this? Yeah, why would you do it? I'm sure they're bad.
Fringe to the max. I've just been going to, I've just been going to Whole Foods, you know,
looking like a fucking wasteland warrior, wearing my like scarf over my mouth with my
fucking dyed hair and shit and like a, my coat. I'm the only one who does it too. There's
like old people who are wearing medical masks and then everyone else just looks normal and
I'm like, I'm like all mouth covered and stuff, feeling like a freak, but I'm convinced that
I'm right and everyone else is wrong. When I was coming back from Radcon at the airport,
I saw a bunch of people in gloves and a couple of people in masks. That was like pretty much
the highest. Yeah, I wear gloves when I go into Whole Foods. I put gloves on. I don't
touch anything. I would never, ever, I'm never going to touch that keypad. Sure. Wear gloves
the whole time. It's based. Makes sense. Makes sense. Yeah, I'll probably do that if I end
up going up. Hey, speaking of going to stores. Hey, big news guys, I know you've been waiting
to hear this, but it's, I'm sorry to say it's true. GameStop sales have dropped by 26% in
the fourth quarter. Oh, wait, so sorry, everyone. Sorry to let you know. What's dropped in the
fourth quarter? GameStop sales. Are you not aware of the saga of GameStop and what they've
been doing in the wake of this crisis? I mean, I know that they're bad. What have they been
doing, Tom? I don't actually know. Oh, so GameStop in response to like everything closing
down, they tried to make the case that they were an essential service and should stay
open. Oh, yeah. My gamer score, Tom, my gamer score. And then like they didn't provide anything
for their employees and they actually like sent out an internal email to like the managers
and they were like, if the cops come, give them this number to call because you can't
close even if the police come to close you down. Bro, when the bombs drop and it's us
against us, the only currency that's going to matter is gamer score. It's important.
That's an essential function, you know, society. You're right. I guess GameStop Corporation
knew the correct shares thing all the time. Yeah, you know, I just happened to see a thing
before this that said that like, oh, they're closing 300 storefronts this year. Okay, which
obviously isn't bad. But do you know how many GameStop stores there are too many nationwide?
As of googling just now, 5,500 stores. So that represents what like a 5% maybe maybe more
than that 10%. Yeah, a little over 5%. It's like six, six and a half, 7% something like
that. So obviously the trend is down. And I mean, I you know, I have some sympathy for
like or some some attunement to the argument that like, you want to own your physical media
because I fucking hate patches and shit in in a sense that games are being wiped off the
earth because you can't get creators make little George Lucas esque tweaks and the fuck
things around. I just want the classic original. Her name is Eris. You can't tell me her name
is Eris. I will never submit and I will never surrender. But but why the fuck would you go
to GameStop? Would you just download the game? I mean, that's, you know, I don't get it. I
like never buy games in physical media. I mean, I just I just order them from Amazon.
They're usually cheaper or just get them used from eBay. But they have to wait like days,
several days for it. But I don't have to get out of my chair. And that is definitely worth
waiting two days. But I don't have to get out of my chair if I go on the switch store and download
the game directly on there or steal a game from the internet. But then the bad people win because
then you don't own your media anymore. And when your switch console breaks and you can't port
any of your shit over to the new replacement system you buy, because Nintendo is living in
the Stone Age when it comes to internet, you're fucked. Okay, I'm happily in the valley of it
feels like this is the way things are going. I would love to for things to not necessarily go
this way. But I can't do it alone. So I give up. And I'll just do what's convenient. We could have
been brothers in arms, but you've abandoned me. In some ways I am. But the convenience argument
is too strong. It's far too sounds like you're part of the problem, Nate. The most No, I think
I'm part of the solution. Convenience is everything. It's all I want. It's all I have just like a
capitalist bootlicker going for the convenience over fucking anything else. How sad. That's true.
I mean, why would you ever buy a video game? Which of Maslow's hierarchy of needs does it
serve? Why would you even buy video games in the first place? Truly the worst thing to do.
Can you eat a video game? Can it shelter you from the elements? Depends on how many you have, I
guess. You can't build a shelter out of downloads, but if you have enough jewel cases, you can.
So clearly I'm in the right here. Yes, Ben. I want to see you collect that vapor,
you spew from your fiery gullet and try to make a shelter or live off of that. You degenerate.
I believe in the miasma theory of disease. I don't believe in bacteria. So by filling my room
with vapors that smell like cotton candy or blueberry or blueberry cake or mango sorbet,
I believe I will be protected from infection, yes. Okay, well said. Well argued.
It's like, wait, no, it's the opposite of what Digi said with Destiny that even if you make a
bad, if you make a good case for a bad argument, Digi said, no, you lose. No, he said you win,
whatever. Oh god, I can't remember. It was too confusing. I'm sorry to bring it up. What a nightmare.
Well, that's it guys. Game stop. That's all that's on my mind. You guys all, you guys quarantined?
Still quarantined. You know, it's this, you know, the joke, the joke going around on the
internet is everyone's like, haha, I never leave my house anyway. And that's true. I am not, life
is not very much different for me personally under quarantine than it was at any other time.
And yet, and yet, it feels worse. It feels because now you have to, you're not doing it
voluntarily. I don't like that. I don't like that. I guess so. I guess that has to be it.
But here's a silver lining, Ben. Here's a silver lining. It just feels more stressful because
I'm seeing people like talking about it on Twitter and like people on Twitter and stuff are like,
oh boy, I'm cooped up in the house. This is so bad. And I'm like, and it makes me self-conscious,
like, oh no, me too. And now I, but now I feel bad about it. Well, no, here's the thing. The thing
is that like you realize, oh, I should feel bad about it. My entire life for the last like 10
years, I've been living like I was in a pandemic without realizing it. Yeah, kind of. That's pretty
fucked a little bit. Yeah. But but but the silver lining guys, the payout, the payout was approved.
We're getting $1,200. Oh my god. That's true. Yeah. You know, hey, that'll pay rent for one month.
That's not bad. But here's the thing. For us specifically, they're saying unemployment works
for a gig economy and like people working like like independently. So we might actually be
able to get a couple months of unemployment as well. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yeah. What? What? Yeah, dude. What? Yeah, I don't, how? How? That doesn't make any sense.
I want to believe it's true. I mean, let me pull up the article again. Someone sent it to me. It was
like, Hey, does this apply to you? For self-employed 1099 creatives who have lost employment due to
COVID-19, everyone is fixated on the one time $1,200 check. But for the first time ever,
freelancers are eligible for unemployment pay plus $600 per week through the end of July.
Per week, baby. Let me, let me for no particular reason point out that those
uninsurance protections were included in the bill specifically because Bernie Sanders pushed for
them to be there. So if we all get $600 a week, we have Bernie to thank for it.
That's all I have to say about that. Based. But I heard that like, we don't get paid out until like,
I heard that those checks won't be going out until like May, which seems like a little.
I don't figure that as well. I mean, I'm not sure if that's true, but that's what I heard.
To cover. To do those.
Okay. So that's not good for people who are literally living, you know, paycheck to paycheck.
But I guess I like to think that most people have enough money to, you know,
dig into their savings until that comes to account. Most people have no savings.
A lot don't. A lot. What is it? What was it?
Yang would always throw out the statistic and so would Bernie that like 40% of Americans
can't afford like a $500 emergency or something like that. Right. Right.
So that's pretty bad. Pretty bad. Rent strike. I mean, that's rough. That's rough.
Rent strike. Damn you Nancy Pelosi holding up the bill. Curse you. Curse you woman.
The, you know, for one day, I heard that I heard that Canada, Canada is getting $2,000 per person
for four months, as opposed to our one time $1,200. Well, pretty cool.
We just, we just used, you know, 75% of that money to bail out everybody but the common
person because that's much more important. That's, oh, that's after. So we gave them 1.5 trillion
out of the $2 trillion and then we also gave them $1.5 trillion a couple like last month
to jumpstart the stock market for 20 minutes before it crashed again.
Yeah. So, you know, you know, about that first bailout, I did learn that it's not,
it's not as simple as we just took $1.5 trillion from the budget and just gave it to companies.
It's more like, it's weirder than that. It's like, they basically just went into the government,
the government computer like fund and just like edited the number to say,
we have $1.5 trillion more than we have. And then gave that as like sort of a short-term loan
to those companies to like liquidate assets. And then they were given back the money,
the quote unquote money, the phantom money, and then it was like deleted again.
So it's not like, it's not as simple as they just gave them $1.5 trillion,
they just invented $1.5 trillion that did not exist out of whole cloth,
pretended to give it to some people to fix the, to try and fix the economy,
and then unpretended it. So I don't know. I don't understand that at all. Money is,
money is literally fake. Money is a spook. It's made up. The government, the government has as
much money as they say they have. You know, it occurs to me that all our current,
I forget the word for it, but this whole system, capitalism, we have an entire country that has
expanded itself to a very wide degree on the back of, I mean, this is just basic economic theory
of capitalism or whatever, on the back of like, there's all this money in play that can be promised
here. It's like your basic loan thing. Your bank has money and it loans it out. That money
doesn't actually exist all the time, but there are expectations of earnings and whatnot,
so that when the machine grinds to a halt, like there is nothing there to support it,
and then it collapse. I mean, this is just your basic fucking bubble theory or whatever.
I don't think I would have done that if it was me in charge. That seems pretty irresponsible,
but maybe it's not. I don't know. I've been against fractional reserve banking ever since
guys two fucking red-pilled me on that shit like 15 years ago.
You lost me there. What are you saying you wouldn't have done?
I don't know. I can't express it any better than I did.
For fractional reserve banking, for every dollar that comes into a bank, a bank is allowed to loan
to $10 out because of the way the system works. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, gotcha.
So when something happens and they call the debt or whatever, the problem we're having is not
specifically a run on the bank, though. No, no, it's a separate issue. I mean,
it just occurs to me that I mean, all this stuff is intertwined in the underpinnings of our broken
fucked up society. So when one thing fails, it all fails. Sure. And now the big thing this week
was like Republicans calling for this cure is worse than the disease. We got to get everyone
back to work because like, sure, people will die, but like, we can't let the we can't let the economy
crash. You're right, because the economy, unlike everything we just explained about why it actually
is important for our overextended world, we can just let that collapse. And it'll be totally fine.
Don't worry about it. No one's going to get hurt as a result of that. I mean, I mean, the economy,
I mean, as as a elaborated upon in the example of the just made up a bunch of imaginary money,
the money in the economy is all fake. It's all it's all a dream, a whisper in the wind.
But but but but further than that, further than that, the problem with that line of thinking,
okay, maybe maybe you do believe that there will be like a like a measurable like cost of like human
life, specifically from a from an economy crash, right? Well, like maybe maybe if you if you believe
that, you could try and weigh it against, okay, what is the what is the cost of allowing COVID-19
to spread versus crashing the economy? And that's a reasonable line of inquiry. But like,
yeah, if you're saying like, oh, we got to get people back to work, we can't we can't let this
virus stall the economy. That's bad. Well, like, okay. But if you people go back to work and they
stop self quarantining, then the infection will continue to spread. And like, that just
unsolves the problem. And we're going to have an economic crash anyway, from like,
millions of people dying. Like, that's like, that's going to be way, like, not only is that I think
a bad way to go about it, it doesn't even like on it doesn't even solve the problem it purports to
solve of preventing the economy from crashing. Well, you're totally right. If that happens,
I mean, yes, it would be it would be not only would it be bad, then it would kind of be have
pointless to have even done anything that made the economy go bad in the first place,
which is obviously foolish that likes the worst of both. It would all it would also undo the
utility of everything that has been done. Yeah. Yeah. So what's the right answer? Oh, God, I'm
too stupid. Professional epidemiologists who seem to agree that mass quarantining for a period
is the right way to go. I believe that works for South Korea.
Is that what they did? They they they did mass testing really quickly isolated everybody who
had the disease quarantine them and now they're kind of doing better. Yeah, I saw that like their
curve was like, flat AF. Yeah. Damn. I mean, you know, yeah, sure, this would spread the disease.
But like, why not have like, the young people are mostly fine. Maybe there could just be like,
the people who are the higher risk are self there's a bunch of young people now.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, first of all, the proportions of people infected. I mean, you know,
listen, young people can die of it. But sure, furthermore, it's the point of quarantining everyone
is that the infection stops spreading and the virus is killed. Like, yeah, young people mostly
don't die of it, but they can still spread it. Well, sure. Listener, fair listener. None of us
know what we're talking about. I just finished watching this awesome video by cold fusion,
one of my favorite YouTubers about the virus and like the cures that are being worked on right now.
It's fucking great. It's a LinkedIn in the show notes. Watch it, subscribe to cold fusion,
one of the best YouTubers on the platform. Really good shit. I'm looking at, you know,
I'll be honest, the biggest thing about this is it's fucking boring is what it is. It's
fucking boring and I don't care and I'm really bored and I just want to do other shit and I'm
sick of everybody talking about it. Fine, be quarantined. What would you be doing? Yeah,
I'm going to say, are you not in the boat of like, I would just be home anyway? I mean,
I definitely am. But I'm sick of it dominating everyone's thoughts. That's what annoys me.
And look, I get it. It's a big deal, but I could also be bored of that. Here's the thing,
though, the fact that we're all saying like, Oh God, the fact that like everyone's talking
about COVID-19, it's so boring. That just shows that we're too glued to social media. We have all
this free time to just go do actual productive things or just watch anime. Like I started
watching Olive Shirabako. That was much better than just being on Twitter reading about COVID-19.
Go use your time wisely, people. Go do something fucking cool.
I'm no goddamn Twitter animal who's on Twitter all day reading about this stuff. I'm just saying
that in the feeds that I already follow, there has been certainly a shift toward this subject
matter. Just block coronavirus and COVID-19.
You're not going to get any like vital information about the outbreak through Twitter anyways.
I mean, I use Twitter for cute anime girls. That's what I use Twitter for. So that's not the
issue, Twitter. It's mostly like YouTube videos. Thank God, 2D waifus can't get the coronavirus.
They're safe. I'm looking at this flow chart.
Uh, or I'm, man, can I do this? Can I file for unemployment insurance?
I mean, I haven't been fired or anything, but I don't know. What are the conditions?
Is it just if I don't make enough money, then I qualify for unemployment insurance?
If that's the case, then maybe I would just get unemployment insurance.
That would be pretty sick. I don't know.
I want to roll the dice. I want to try. Why not?
Well, nothing wrong with trying if you want to.
I guess I should look into it.
Like I'm so fucking poor that getting even just $600 a month, not even a week, would double my
income. Oh, dude. Oh, dude. Hell yeah. Please God, let this work.
What is this about a SBA paycheck protection loan? It says to apply for. I don't know what that is.
Thank you for this infographic, Tom. I will be looking into it shortly.
If you figure out anything, let me know. I'm going to start looking to it as well,
because I want to get to the bottom of this shit.
Let's do a left turn here. I've got something else to discuss.
And it's that. Okay.
So there are three PCPU lectures coming out, or already out, sorry. There's Ben's,
Tom's, and Gibbs. They have been very well received. And mine, by the time you get this.
Tom's is literally, it's accelerating in views. It is not flattening. It is gaining views at an
increasing rate. Did you guys see what you guys think about your experience of getting them out
so far since we talk about them so much? And I'm really happy with the response. It was funny,
because I was in this morning in the Radcon for Discord, and someone was like, hey, a few days
ago, some guy uploaded an Animorphs video and was like, oh, yeah, it's beginning. Was it just
intolerant or something? Yeah, the video was pretty shit. I didn't like it, and I don't like the guy's
channel. I have seen that guy's channel. It's, by the way, it's James Tullo. James Tullo. I saw
that today, and I posted a comment in the comments saying, because in the video, he says, like, oh,
I could, if you wanted a full explanation on this, on the lore of this series, that would take me
forever. And so I commented like, oh, if anyone wants that explanation, there's a link to exactly
such a video. Got four hours free. It's funny, I almost did that as well. But I ended up forgetting,
because I'm dumb. And I was too busy watching COVID-19 treatment by Cold Fusion.
So I mean, yeah, what do you think? What are the odds? This guy published two days ago.
He says in the video that he had been meaning to put out an Animorphs video for a while.
Okay, I believe it. Yeah, he's a book guy. He just talks about books.
His whole channel is him just talking about like fantasy books, mostly.
I wonder if he feels cucked that you got yours out right before he got his.
I mean, he has 50k subs. So his is already like catching up to my video, despite being
out for like a third of the time. So I'm pretty sure he'll do just fine.
But his video, his video was not good. The production values were basically non-existent.
And he was just like, Animorphs was so weird. Lots of stupid shit happened. Man, the 90s were
dumb. I heard he had a very negative take overall on the series. It was pretty bad.
Fair enough, I guess. He basically just lists off the five weirdest things.
They're not even the weirdest things.
Anything that you didn't touch on in your video.
Yeah, there was some of the filler books that I've left out because I just want to
write a general plot. There's one where Rachel morphs into a starfish, but gets cut in half.
Oh, yeah, that's right. My favorite one is how canonically El Fangor founded Microsoft.
Is that true? Yeah.
Why and how did that happen?
Well, he didn't found Microsoft. What he did is like, well, he was a human nofflet.
He's like, he goes through a general human education, but he's an andalite. So he's super
fucking smart. And like he can easily get his PhD and whatever because it's like baby shit to him.
But there's one offline where he's like, yeah, I helped my friends, Steve and Bill
start their companies and it's Steve Jobs and Bill Gates. And it's just like cheeky.
What the fuck? That's really funny. That's really funny.
Hey, by the way, speaking of Microsoft just reminds me, are you guys aware that not only is
Bill Gates like in a hard quarantine, like in a boat offshore because the world may or may not
be ending, but also like he did a TED talk just like exactly predicting exactly what COVID is
right now. Have you seen that? No.
Yeah, I watched it just the other day. Or most of it anyway. I mean, he's just talking about
exactly what we're going through. And this is like two years ago. It was like two or three years ago.
And are you telling me the Bilderberg group engineered COVID-19 and is this all a big
experiment done by the deep state? Because I believe it. Maybe, maybe. But he's mostly like,
guys, please, let's make sure we're prepared. Please God, there are things we can do. No,
but then we didn't. Oops. Sorry, Bill. I popped into, I popped into a Pantsu party live stream
the other day. Those things are popping off these days. Where I don't, is that sarcastic?
I don't know. No, no. Maybe it's getting some good people on there. Didn't she
get like channel, get like shadow band or something? Yeah, I think it did. Somebody said
that it did. And like her side channel too, I think. They were discussing how COVID-19 is a
Chinese bio weapon designed to thin the population. I mean, some aspects of that,
some aspects could be true because they, it may have come from a lab. And then I mean, you know,
I mean, I went and I googled it and I did not see any credible information. I found a bunch of
articles being like, here's how we know that it did not come from a lab. No, it is not a bio weapon.
I mean, I'm not gonna, I've been in the air a little, I'm not going to claim that like that's
hard evidence of anything, but I haven't seen any evidence that it is a bio weapon. So,
if anyone's got any, I guess I'd be marginally interested in seeing it. Kind of sounds like
some crackpot shit to me. Certainly could be. I mean, this is, I mean, the coronavirus is,
it's just like a new version of like the same thing that caused SARS. This isn't like a new
invention. Yeah, I mean, for me, I'm much more concerned with the cover up China did after
it was already loose and that's not so good. Yeah, sure. That's just China being China. I'd be more
surprised if they didn't cover it up. If it turned out it was a bio weapon, I would be concerned,
but I don't know that, you know, whatever. I don't know. I'll just, I just need to see evidence
of such a thing. Of course, I agree. I agree. I think a lot of people just don't trust the Chinese
government too much. And so maybe they're a little tempted to lean on, they're bad boys,
which they are. They're doing some genocide over there. Let me complain about, let me complain
about something. Everyone, there was a, okay, first people got mad at Trump for calling it
the Chinese virus. And then there was a reaction of people like, why is it racist to call it the
Chinese? It's not racist to call it the Chinese virus. We name things, it's just where it came
from. We name things after where they came from. Ever heard of the Spanish flu? Did you see them
update the Wikipedia article on the Spanish flu to remove that it's called the Spanish flu?
That was pretty funny. I did not. I mean, I mean, I heard some people talking about that. I don't
have the facts, but let me, let me, let me, let me see if that's true. Spanish flu, Wikipedia.
I believe it, it's called something else now, but I think the Spanish flu also known as the 1918
flu pandemic wasn't unusually deadly, blah, blah, blah, blah. Thing about the Spanish flu is it
did not come from Spain. It came from America. All right. Why is it called the Spanish flu?
Maybe just it got there and that's what's best known for being. Honestly, like, okay,
I'm not an expert on this, but I have heard it said that like people called it the Spanish flu,
like specifically to like, oh, okay. I guess it was first reported in Spain,
but it didn't come from, but it didn't come from Spain. All right.
I think it's more just like the zeitgeist of culture, you know, like, like the coronavirus is
obviously associated with China because that's where it fucking got its start and shit.
People are like, oh, it's not, but it's not racist just to call it the Chinese virus.
And like, I agree. It's not in and of itself racist to call it that. But like,
the point is it's weird. It's weird. Don't you think that like it was called the coronavirus?
They've been calling it that for months and then all of a sudden Trump and other people,
they just, they pivot. They start calling it the Chinese virus. Did you see that picture?
There's a picture. You can see Trump's speech and he literally used a sharpie to cross out
coronavirus on and wrote Chinese virus. I saw that. I assumed it was fake. It's not fake.
He really did that. Can I get a source? It just seems, it seems so, like, if anybody would do
something like that, it would be Trump, but it just seems so ridiculous to me that you would,
why would you need to scribble it out? Couldn't you just remember? I mean, maybe I don't know.
I don't know. The thing is, the thing is, the people are mad, people are mad at the,
let me fucking finish, the people are mad at the libs for being like, okay, oh, it's not racist.
It's just calling it what it is. Okay, whatever. The point is not whether that phrase is racist.
The point is that calling it that is, like, clearly a manipulation of the thing. It already
had a name, but they've decided we need to give it a new name to transpose blame for the situation
onto China. That's clearly why they're doing it. And I don't appreciate it.
I agree. I agree. I think, I think in the case of Trump, if he did that, then yeah,
I think someone on Twitter just calling it the Chinese virus.
No, it was, I mean, it became a thing because Trump said it in the speech and then Trump said
in one of his speeches when like some lady asked him, like, if it's racist, he said, like, no,
I mean, clearly one of his motivations here was that he said that the Chinese government
attempted to spin this as actually an American virus that was like leaked by the American
government. And clearly he was very annoyed by that. And he's like, no, no, no, this is
a Chinese virus. Is that true though? I mean, that's what he said. I mean, why would you believe
anything is he says it? I mean, that doesn't prove it's true. But I mean, I've never heard that
fact disputed. I've just heard the fact. I will not believe I will not believe anything just
because Trump says it. It's just that I've heard no pushback on that point. I don't care other
points. I mean, that's not him saying it is not evidence of it being true. I'm not I'm not
asserting that it is definitely true. I'm saying that I'm saying that there's no reason to believe
it even could be true simply because he mentioned it. Also, a lot of people seem hung up on like
this is giving a bad name to the glorious Chinese people. I mean, I can sort of see that. But
isn't really the intent here to smear the government who is responsible for managing the
situation? I mean, I mean, I read it. I don't I don't think the attempt is to deliberately like
demean the ethnically Chinese. It's definitely like a political thing. Right. I mean, I mean,
to be fair, the Chinese are trying to pin this on the US by saying that the coronavirus started
in America and we're saying it was US military. I've never heard that. Is that this is the first
time hearing of that? If it's true, then so be it. A couple weeks ago, that was the Chinese
government's position was trying to shift blame to the US and saying it was like a military operation
that brought it in or something to that effect. So this is the government's doing the governments
pretending to be brainless when they're all working in a big interlocking system where
they're all at fault and they all need to be called. Just to give you a fact here, a data point,
I'm reading an article in The New York Times that says, this is just the title, China spins
tale that the US army started the coronavirus epidemic. So I don't know any more than that.
It's The New York Times seems reasonably credible. Well, then well, then maybe. Okay, whatever. Yeah.
The point is, I'm going to keep calling it the coronavirus because that's I mean, that was its
name. It's perfectly fair to me. Okay, Trump definitely calls it the virus just to annoy China
and I don't feel a particular need to do so. So I don't care. The actually people saying it annoys me
because people say like, oh, we name things after what they're they come from. Well, actually,
the World Health Organization says no, we don't do that anymore. Because sometimes we're bringing
it back, baby. Our official naming convention specifically preclude doing that.
So no, wrong. I'm sorry, we are bringing your fancy laws to the streets where we call in the
virus, you know, what it what it really is. I'm just, you know, I'm just I'm too by the book.
Ben, let's call it what it is. It's the kung flu. It's the kung flu. I know. Look,
in my heart of hearts, I know it's the kung flu.
Hey, hey, okay, but but I was also curious, we talked about the dang lectures. I wanted to
hear what you your debacle about your lecture about my trauma you sucked. Yeah, it was because I
I guess my headphones are bad because we had two. There were two audio tracks. One was from
the two floor mics. And the other was from the the lapel mic. Yeah. And I listened to both of them.
And like quality wise, I didn't hear that much of a difference. But this baffles me.
But for some reason, the that you guys talking was actually quieter relative to me speaking in
the floor mics in the lapel mics, you guys are actually like relatively louder. I don't know
how that could possibly be the case. Yeah. And yet it is. So I was like, well, since I don't hear
much of a quality problem, I'll just go with the floor mics, because like whatever, it doesn't
matter. So I released it. And, you know, in hindsight, actually, the quality of the lapel
mic is actually a little better. It's a little less tinny. But even, but it's not like a deal
breaker. However, I guess for some reason, the two floor mics were like out of sync with each
other. Like, yeah, waveforms were like, yeah, they were just like one frame off or whatever.
And so listen to in stereo, it didn't it sounded okay. But if you listen to it on mono,
the two signals because they were out of sync, they would like negatively cancel or I forget
what the phrase is, you know, the two waves would like cancel each other out. And so people said
it sounded like they were hearing me like as though I was speaking underwater or through a wall or
something. So, you know, most people didn't have it. And a lot of people were like, why are you
reuploading it? It's fine. It's fine. But like some people were like, this sounds like terrible,
like this is like unlistenable. Yeah, I couldn't I couldn't use the the mics for the audience,
because for some reason, as the lecture went on, the those ones desynced from
in my case, the video was very weird. In my case, and this is very frustrating,
in my case, actually, the lapel mic desync, it's not very much. But if you watch at the end of the
Kokoro wish lecture, you can see that like the audio is desync from the video by like,
a quarter of a second, like it's very minor. But if you pay attention, you can kind of see it.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, the whole last third part of my lecture, the audio drops in quality even
further, because I guess the lapel mic for the third recording just didn't work. So it was just
the camera audio. So it's just like, okay, it's just bad. It's not going to be good. It's gonna
we're gonna have to ride on the performance and the information because clearly the production
value is not you got him in for the first two hours. I mean, most people will coast. I ended up
I ended up I contacted our old friend oblivion fall to do I was like, first I wanted him to like,
hey, could you fix this like, this like phase issue that is like causing this cancellation?
And then he kind of did but then he was like, you know, the lapel mic sounds better. And I was
like, well, okay, can you just apply the lapel mic? And he was like, well, I want to do some
cleanup on it. I was like, okay, and then it took a while but then he did it. And then I got it up
and that was how that happened. But very frustrating, because the second release
did not get as many views as the first one. It did not it did not spike. I think it killed
some of its momentum to re upload it. It lost like, you know, like six 6.8 thousand views
that it had on the first one. Kind of a bummer, kind of a bummer. But whatever, what are you
going to do? I think we should do this. Shut the fuck up. I'm fucking talking. Oh my god.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Holy shit. It's fine. No, I love you. I love you.
On the first release, on the first release, I did I went and I posted it on like every
fucking subreddit that it was even marginally related. I posted it in my discord, I posted
an rfck discord, I posted the link to the first one everywhere. And I don't know if it made that
much of a difference, but it clearly maybe made some because the first one got got a percent
more views by a bit. But I don't know if I have the energy to do that again. I don't know if I feel
I just I feel like embarrassed. I would feel embarrassed to do it a second time. I know what
you mean. I don't know how to pin it on the audience because people were complaining. I went back and
did this. He's fucking entitled viewers. Where where would I plug such a thing? I was thinking
like what what subreddits would I even post this on? The PCP subreddit. Yeah, it was already there.
It's already there. But like I went and the webcomic subreddit, the cringe subreddit. I did that.
I did that too. I posted on like 15. The based subreddit. Yeah. Is there a based subreddit?
There should be. Okay. I don't. Where do you plug a thing like this? I put it on 4chan.
I don't know. I just posted. I've made a thread on 4chan about it.
Go to our college and just be like, here's a university lecture for you guys.
There is. There is actually a subreddit for video lectures. It's not that big.
Wait, regardless, our slash lectures. I don't think about any of this because I'm a fucking
idiot. I mean, to be fair, it didn't make much of a difference for me, but like
this is the kind of thing that I worry about. I like to watch numbers go up. Indeed. Same.
You want to know something disgraceful? Yes. You want to know something disgraceful about
our friend Gibb and take? Oh no. Yeah. Ream him, Ben. Do you know what he's doing right now?
Jerk in his little dick. Worse. He is streaming ratchet and clank.
He's streaming right now. He is streaming right now. He must have forgotten. That piece of shit.
You know what it is? He keeps thinking, okay, yesterday he like pinged everybody two hours
before the meeting and like, hey guys, it's time for the meeting. I think his like clock or alarms
are just wrong. How fucking hard is it to fix that? I don't know. Well, I think he probably just
something got screwed when he like changed time zones when he came here or something. I have no
idea, but the boy needs help. It's gotten to his brain. It just seems like a very solvable problem
to me. We could. We could add him right now, but it's too late. I guess. Yeah. Yeah. It's possible.
I'm not gonna. You know what? You know what he should do? We didn't add everybody. We should.
Oh god. Oh, we didn't add everybody. Whoops. We should get him on the podcast right now, but he
should have us, our audio be audible on his stream. We should have this episode live on Gibbon
Gaming. Um, potentially doable, I suppose. Guys, here, I'll just add everyone. I got,
I got the best fucking comment right now on the Kokoro wish lecture. It is from Mike Smith.
Do you want to know what it said? Yeah, indeed. It said, Christ, you people are ugly.
He's not. Oh Christ. That's death.
My favorite comment on the Animarse lecture so far was just someone like yesterday say,
I know what you're going to say. This is the most unfunny thing I've seen in a long time or
something. Oh, I thought you were going to say the one about the circus, the four skins. Oh,
that one was great too. That was a nightmare fuel. Tell us that one time. Yeah. So somebody
commented yesterday on the Animarse lecture saying like, Oh, so you're saying when, when
everybody morphs back, all of their non-genetic injuries are healed from their base form. So
that means that all the man and male animorphs got their foreskin back, right? And I'm just like,
and all the women got their FGM reverse. I guess so. I guess so. I can't say you're wrong.
Female genital mutilation. Oh, right. My favorite. Yeah. Okay, cool. Cool. My favorite thing to
watch. Let's play is up. I can't cure this damn autism or this damn one-itis, the deadliest
mildest motor man. Shit. If only. Listen to purple glasses over here, making more misogynistic
comments. I'd never say the word because I hate women so much. Well, I mean, true.
Well, hey, so I'm, I don't wonder if you guys have done the same because I've been going through
my big ass long lecture and I have been, I'm going to go through it. I'm like, I'm, I'm getting pretty
close to being done. I should be done editing it two day. So it should be out by the time people
hear this. We know how my predictions go, but feeling pretty confident about this one.
And end of the month, people, end of the month. I've been doing that. Well, that's only two days
from now. End of the month, every month. Well, uh, uh, oh, so I've been going through the entire
thing and putting in images. I've really, this is almost my penance. It's my penance for, I feel
so bad about both the Kingdom Hearts and Final Fantasy lecture, not adding in images, just things
to give context. I've maybe gone a bit overboard. But my, it's, yeah, my policy, I have been doing,
I did the same thing for, um, Kokoro Wish and I'm doing the same thing for, uh, Chris102.
My policy, and I haven't stuck to it a hundred percent, but like, my rule of thumb is I don't
show images of events. I just show images of a character or like a thing. Yeah, when the character.
And I have a general rule that's mostly, it's like the first time a character is mentioned,
I show them and that's generally. If there's something that you would need to end up to
visualize, like to, to understand what I'm talking about, I show that. But generally, I don't show
like, oh, this is, if I say, oh, and then this happened, show the panel where it happened.
No, I, some, sometimes I do. Because you want people to wonder and to use their imagination
a lot of the time. Yes. What things look like. Yeah. I have been, I have been considering,
like, should I do, should I do Chris, should I do Sonichu101 Remastered where I just put images
on screen? I thought of that too. I thought of that too. I don't know. Like, on the one hand,
like, one, would people care? Two, like, would it actually like, help anyone with understanding
what I'm talking about? Would anyone watch it? Would it like, yeah, I don't know. Well, the interesting
thing is that. It's a thing that I would like to exist, but I feel like if I were to release it
and nobody cared, like, it's, I wouldn't, there wouldn't, like, what would be the point?
Sure, sure. One of the things that I didn't expect would be so well received, because I just
blatantly copied it from the RFCK lecture, was having little audio cues when images popped up,
because I didn't even consider that people would just like tab over and do something else.
Oh, they will, no doubt. But of course they would. I consider that as well. There are too many
images, so I'm just bailing on that idea. It is a good one, though. It is a good one. Oh, the,
the dings? Yeah. Yeah. Yes. I decided that there were too many images, and I wasn't going to ding
for everyone. The first render I did did not have the dings. Then the RFCK lecture came out
in between, and I already had an error I needed to fix. I was like, well, I might as well put
them in. I don't have any excuse now, so I did. That's smart. That's smart. I've also, as I've been
going through the whole thing, I have like my audio up and like, I have everyone else muted
for optimal audio quality. And then only at times when the audience speaks, I raise the audio of the
ambient noise and then lower it once they're done. I've done that through the entire thing so far,
and it's pretty much the most time-consuming thing of the whole project. But yeah, that's why I do
stick with it. I'm not sure if Oblivion mentioned wanting to do some of that. I don't know if he
ended up doing it. I didn't think that it, I don't think it was that big of a deal. It's going to be
a classic overproduced best guy ever video, no doubt. Yeah. The audio in Sonichu 101 is like
bad, and I get quieter and louder when I face the mic or away from the mic. It's bad, but it's got
a million views. Nobody gives a shit. It's true. It's true. I was looking at the lapel mic audio
for the Sonichu 102, and there's one side is clearly louder. The left channel is louder than
the right channel, and there's probably a really simple way to fix that or compensate for it.
Maybe I'll do it. Is rendering audio through Vegas bad? Does that make it audio bad? Should
I render the video in Vegas and then get the audio from another source and just apply it through
another program? I generally do that stuff in Audacity, but I've never been sure it's actually
necessary. I wouldn't, I mean, I don't think so, but I've always used Audacity like for this
purpose, so I can't tell you exactly. Yeah, but you can't render a video in Audacity. Oh, right.
Do you then put the audio into Vegas and render it in Vegas? I mean, sometimes, but only for
things that I don't really care about the quality of, just because I've been afraid it'll be worse.
So is what you're saying, that you do the audio in Audacity, you render the video in Vegas,
and then you apply the Audacity audio to the video through an external program? Yes, I have
done that many times. What program do you use for that? Well, Audacity. Audacity in Vegas.
No. What I'm saying, do you... Oh, you're asking how do you strip the audio from the video?
Yeah. I can't remember offhand. Well, if you want to get audio from... No,
you just said you do it. What do you do? Well, I mean, it's been a while since I last did it. Maybe
I did render just the MP3 or the like the FLAC file or whatever in Vegas to get the best quality
possible and then edit it in Audacity because I do that fairly frequently. No, stop. That doesn't
make any fucking sense. How would you render a video file in Audacity? No, everything I'm talking
about in Audacity is that I've stripped audio files from other projects in some way, like such as
rendering a FLAC file from Vegas or whatever, then you import into Audacity where I do lots of cleanup
stuff, then I move it back. Move it back? How? To Vegas? Move it back. So you put it in Vegas
and render it in Vegas? I mean, yes. Okay, thank you. Oh boy. All right, cool.
Just for future reference, you can save a step of rendering out a FLAC file. If you install the
FFmpeg extension for Audacity, you can just import video files and it'll just automatically grab
the audio file from whatever video you import and just dump it in there. That's the sort of thing.
Can you then put that audio onto a video file? No, you have to save it as an MP3 or WAV file and
then sync it back up. Oblivion Fallhead, I forgot what he said, the software, Oblivion Fallhead
software that could just take an audio file and just swap it into a video, like just just
something an audio guy would have. Just apply it to a video file without re-rendering,
which is pretty convenient, but I don't think it's free software though.
Anything's free if you know where to look. Maybe. That's true. Maybe.
Well, after this, I've got one more lecture to end. Well, I guess I'll just say, I mean,
I have been charged with the heightened responsibility of getting Brad's esteemed lecture
done, which won't that be a fun thing? He's got lots of useful information,
everybody, so stay tuned. Won't that be fun? Look in your sub-box in the old PCP.
What is the next lecture coming out? Whose lecture's coming out next?
I really think it's going to be mine, because I'm almost done.
Okay, cool. I am really looking forward to the response to Digi's lecture. That's the one that
I'm like. Yeah, that's going to be juicy. That's going to be juicy.
That's definitely true, but I'm the most hyped for Munchies, because Munchies was so much fun to
listen to, and it's fucking great. I mean, true, but also, have we said, should I say what it is?
Yeah, you said it. He's announced it. I wonder if people will not want to hear about real history,
as opposed to like- We need to sell them on it.
You've got to have a really insane title. Like, the French Revolution is the best anime you've
never seen, or some really dumb shit. That's pretty good. Honestly, that's probably the way to go
with the title. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I mean, he starts saying, he says, what does he say? He's like,
oh, history's boring. Actually, no, you're an idiot. I'll kill you. He says history is anime.
It's like the tagline, right? Yeah, he says it, yeah. That's why I said that.
Oh, right, right, right. Spoilers, Teehee.
Bring it out, Munchie. He probably pawned it off to a sweatshop laborer, Ethan, again,
and took six months to get the shit out. Maybe. He needs to be disappointed.
Munchie needs to be working on the Vaporette. That's true. We don't need this lecture. We need
the Vaporette. It is- Okay, Nexus is working on his. Jade Moreau told me yesterday that she was
going to work on hers. Don't know what's going on with Munchie and Kazes, but God, I hope soon.
I hope they'll be done soon. Who is done? Are there people who are done?
Cheesy Manfredo and Hippo are done. Good man, good man. Yes, yes.
My money is sitting somewhere. I've got- I want my product. I just want to give,
I just want to give these artists money. I just want to pay them for their work.
I just want to consume the product so I can clap and start waiting for the next product.
Yeah, true. Hey, you know, Ben said before, he wasn't thrilled with how his episode, or
you know, having to repost and whatnot, and that got me thinking. Maybe we should do a thing
where we sell DVDs of the lectures as one big box set after all of ours come out,
and people can fucking buy them and watch them. I think that's unironically a good idea.
One time, boy, that's a weird, weird to imagine, and yet I can't help but think it probably is a
good idea. Yeah, yeah. One time I downloaded some software, some DVD, like design software,
and I tried to, actually I probably made some progress with it. I tried to design a DVD menu,
and like a DVD design for the Nuzlocke genocide. Right, right. And it was really hard,
and really frustrating, and I think I abandoned the project. I don't remember how far into it I got.
I don't know. So, yeah, I mean it's a thing. It's a lost start, the DVD menu. Back in 2007,
I played around with iDVD on my Mac constantly. It was super simple. It worked great. I made
tons of DVDs of like all my pirated. Did you really? What did you put on them? I just put all
my pirated TV shows on DVD, so I could watch them on my TV. Did you make like menus? Yeah,
they had a quick, you just drag and drop some menus, you put some images in, and they just work
like, it was an Apple thing. Back when Apple was actually cool, and it was the easiest thing in the
world. Oh man. I want to make my Naruto DVD playing in the end, with a sick Naruto versus
Sasuke background. You could do that. It was super easy. You're fucking sick. Oh, and to press play,
you have to like press the showering gun on Sasuke's eye to start. Fuck yeah. I use using a
program called DVD Architect. Damn. I didn't enjoy the process very much. The Virgin iDVD versus the
Chad DVD Architect. No, I think it might be the other way around. Basically, it's cringe. Both
cringe. Yeah, yeah. I can't remember where I saw this. I just saw a video the other day. I mean,
I haven't fucked with a DVD in years, so it would never occur to me to create one. You know what
it was? I just watched Cinemassacre, the angry video game nerd, made a video about like, I forget
what else it was, but it was, among other things, like the lost art of the DVD menu, how they used
to be set. It was in the context of some bigger video. That sounds pretty cool. I feel like it's
completely about like a Blu-ray, and then I think it expanded to all his Blu-rays, and how he was
fucking sick of these awful, like basic bitch. Oh, I think I remember this video. I don't remember
what it was talking about. I don't remember which one it was, but I know I remember this point,
because he's saying like, it's just like a static screen. It's really boring and dumb. And they all
use like the same format, and it totally sucks. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to do a scan real quick
in this channel and see if I can find it. All right. What if we had a DVD box set or a Blu-ray
box set of the lectures, and then for like bonus content, we could have like, like the commentary
on the lecture. So like, if you already seen it. Commentary. Yeah, like commentate on the lecture.
Sure. Sure. Although some of those are pretty long. That'd be a long commentary track. Oh,
god. Like we would like record like a new like commentary track to play over it. Yeah.
It'd be a big ask, but it would be pretty cool. I mean, we're in the lecture. We're asking questions.
Yeah. They have actors do commentary on movies. They're in all the time. This is standard DVD
Extras 101. But like, we were doing the commentary in the video. We're there raising our hands and
saying stuff. Ben. Making comments. Ben. It's a joke, Ben. No. It's supposed to be funny.
Yeah. Well. Oh, wait. I got it. I got it. I'm sorry. I found the video. It's the top 10 reasons
Blu-ray sucks by Cinemastaker. That's the one. I will post. I can't wait. Get ready for our Blu-ray
box set, guys. Cinemastaker disapproved. No. We can put some stank on that menu. We can like
Munchy asks a question in the lecture and then in the commentary is like, yeah. So when I raised
my hand, I was really like, I was really concerned about a certain thing. You know, I'd heard, I'd
heard like, maybe we can provide one additional piece of content in such a DVD or Blu-ray box set
or something to like one secret bonus lecture. That would be a good place to float the short
lectures, like the remedial class ideas that we were talking about forever.
True. But like, we don't, we haven't made one yet. No, we're not doing one.
Remind me what the remedial lectures were about. We were just, we were just talking about like
trying to do short, like half an hour, 45 minute lectures that were just like, not a four hour
monster. Next, I want to do one big lecture. I've already got some ideas and I want to do
like one small lecture, like deliberately, intentionally, like 20 to half an hour minutes.
I was thinking, if we were going to do that, I was going to do this in general, but now they
were talking about the box set. Maybe I put on that like a mini lecture on the Animorphs TV show,
because it's so much different and it was so shitty, like a half an hour thing going through
that and being the changes and how like the budget fucked it over and all that crap.
You know what, Tom? I think someone said this, but I did think this was an amazingly good idea.
I don't know the, I'd have to do research. Maybe you're a better student for this, but a lecture on
all of the doom lore, because there is extensive lore of doom and it's fucking crazy.
Eternal, eternal canonized like everything, like all the dooms of one storyline now,
it's pretty ridiculous. Yep. I don't know, even analyzing retcons and stuff. The thing is,
my first doom, I mean, I played doom one back in the day, but like I didn't pay any attention to
the story. My first real doom was like 2016. So I mean, the story in doom one is like,
there's four paragraphs. Yeah, yeah, you're right. You know what's fucked up, man? Your rabbit's
dead and you're really mad about it. We were playing doom the other day or like a while,
a couple months ago. Why is the font so fucking horrible and impenetrable and impossible to read?
Like all the letters, the kerning is awful in the original doom and nobody talks about it,
but that's the real reason why that game is a zero out of 10. I can't read shit. Because a VGA
monitor when it came out was like high tech. I don't give a shit, man. Also, you don't give a
no excuse. Check your 2020 privilege, dude. Maybe I will. The banjo tui, which I played as I was
prepping from like the big banjo smash video or whatever, like the kerning again, of the font
at the beginning of the game, as it does like the text crawl, like telling you the story so far,
it like the letters are literally over each other. It's a nightmare. Why did they do it that way?
It's it was actually hard to read. I couldn't believe like this game is so good. So much love
and craft was put into every aspect of the game. But then these letters are like impossible to
read. It's a fucking nightmare. I want you I just want to show you what I was talking about before.
Look at the this is this is these are the views on the Animorphs lecture. Oh, there they go.
All right. It is accelerating. As I'm taught, it will reach infinity. You could say it's going to
the moon. If current trends hold, we will it will actually circle back around into infinity.
You know, on the lectures in general, in the next month, I've really been trying to
take stock of which one succeed and, you know, beyond others. I really think just the best
formula is like unexpectedly cool or unexpectedly interesting stuff presented with like a certain
reverence, and perhaps, you know, some some jabs of the thing, but with like a sincere love for
the thing. I mean, that's why people didn't know about. I mean, that's why I think that
the Kokoro wish lecture is the best lecture in why I should be doing these Iron Man numbers,
not you. I deserve those views. We got it. Yeah, we got to pump those numbers up. Well, Ben,
according to that one guy on Twitter, the Animorphs lecture was your win just as much as it was mine.
Oh, yeah, somebody said somebody's because I posted that I was like feeling bad on Twitter,
and someone responded like, but hey, you've got the animal, you did the Animorphs lecture,
and someone else was like, actually, Tom did that, and the guy responded like, yeah,
but Ben was like really contributing. I mean, it's not wrong. You could choose to see it like
that. Ben's Animorphs lecture really was success. There's no doubt about it. Ben's debut role as
the TA was really well done. Hashtag Ben's Animorphs lecture. Get a trending. That sounds good.
Everyone in the comments of the Kokoro wish lecture is like, I thought this was going to be
cringe, and you all said the same thing too after that. You were like, I thought this was going to
be cringe, but it was actually based. I can't believe it. It was actually cool. Yeah, I totally
stand by that. Yeah, I completely think that. The second year in a row, you've done that.
Last time with Tales of Gets Troll, we all thought that was going to be done, but it was actually
fucking lit. That's true. Tales of Gets Troll was the same. Although it's time to ask the hard
question. I think that perhaps there's a reason. Okay, Christian is obviously exponentially more
famous, but I think that there's a certain thirst for blood. I think the people, in a
sense, they want to see the person shit-talked. They want to see them reamed a little bit.
I think there's a certain hunger for that. I'm just not that interested in doing that.
Sure, sure. I go on every now and then I'll check the CWC thread on Kiwi Farms. I never went on
Kiwi Farms, but back in college, I would check the Something Awful forums, which was where the
hotbed for Chris discussion back in the day. Kiwi Farms seems basically similar, maybe a bit more
mean-spirited, but it is so boring. It is so lame. Here, let me fucking peep some right now.
Okay, sure. This is the state of default, just negative shit-talking. It's like,
oh, Chris is a lulcow. I'm going to misgender them because they're hypocrite or whatever,
and they're bad. This is moralizing. Okay, god, there was a...
There was a... Oh, god. You're losing me, man. I'm really... I know. Okay, here we go.
Someone says, oh, for sure. No sapient being that's even remotely in their right mind, in any
dimension or reality, would ever enter willingly into a loving relationship with Chris, not even
his hedgehog abominations. He has nothing to offer anyone, so unless they were being blackmailed or
were enslaved or forced into it some other way, every one of them would run far, far away from
Chris. That's arguably Chris' biggest delusion, and they're talking about his marriage to his
tulpas or whatever. Right. And then something about the idea, guys. I agree. That's why I just
can't feel pity for Chris. For the most part, he has only himself to blame for his situation.
It was his shitty life choices, laziness, will for ignorance, stubbornness, and forcing away
anyone who doesn't kiss his ass and humor his delusional crap that brought him to his current
situation. What was the idea, fags, did to Chris shitty and cruel? Yes, but it was Chris who chose
to ignore reality for comforting lies. This is the state of Chris Chan discussion as it is now,
and I want no part of it, because not only is it like gross, imagine 1500 pages of a thread
that are like that, just like pointing out, here's what, just like just stewing and like,
I hate Chris so much, let me just say over and over and over again what I think is wrong with
her. Yeah. Right. It's boring. Not only is it mean spirit, it's boring, and I hate it. It's definitely
boring. I don't want to fucking do it anymore. I don't want to be a part of that. Well, I mean,
I think the good, the great thing about the lectures, and I think the reason why they
resonate so much is that they come from an authentic place for all of us, like we all
choose topics that we're legitimately invested in, and it's not like an ironic, like, haha to he,
which is why a lot of the times, you know, when people make great suggestions for lecture topics,
like, I don't act on them because like, I have no reason, I'm not into it. Like someone's like,
oh man, this is like such a great lecture on anamorphosis, you got to do K Apple Gates
Everworld series next. I'm like, yeah, never read it. Never read it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And it's
just like, like, like, it has to, it basically has to be something that like we're already interested
in that we've already spent like our life, you know, thinking about and reading about and we,
you know, like, to do a lecture, I mean, I guess you could just like go look up something you've
never heard of, like, like do some research and present a lecture on like you could do that.
Yeah. But like, it wouldn't be different. Yeah, we totally know what makes the lectures
are like good is like the tangible details. And a lot of those, I mean, we were saying that the
other day, it takes a lifetime to prepare for a lecture, and then 30 minutes to like, you know,
arrange the board, or whatever, you know, actually hours, but you know what I'm saying.
And like, it's the tangible details that like, for example, I mean, I'll just say I'm doing one
piece, you'll be out by now, you'll see it. Like if you hadn't read the SPS's, there's so many
amazing details that like as I'm going through an editing right now, yeah, that's like, that's a big
little details that people don't know. Like the fact that Sanji doesn't get burned by his fiery
Diomeli Jambi technique, because canonically, while his leg is hot, his heart burns hotter. So
that doesn't even make sense, but it's the exploration. And it's great. Yeah, that's the
kind of shit in my mind that makes the lectures good. Definitely. Man, great stuff. I want,
I want the Kokoro Wish. I think Kokoro Wish is just as interesting as, say, Tails, I think
Kokoro Wish deserves to do as well as Tails gets trolled. It might not because of like comparable.
It might not because of lower name recognition. Would you say Kokoro Wish doing well is your
Kokoro Wish right now? Yeah, I would say so. Yeah, I would say so. Definitely. I don't know.
Shit, I feel like I had more to say about that, but I've kind of, I've kind of lost the thread.
No matter. No matter. I don't know. We've been talking about that for a while. We can go to the
voicemails if you want. I was gonna say about the mini lectures. I feel like people tell me to do
Oolulilia. I would do, I had kind of thought maybe I could cram in Oolulilia into Radcon 4.
It didn't work out, but I think that that would be a short lecture. I think it might be under an hour
because, I mean, I focus on like the work that they've done. Like, I can talk about Oolulilia
and how he's like a weird guy with OCD and all these like strange personal habits,
but it doesn't really take that long to explain. I would mostly be talking about his books,
and he's written two books, and they're pretty simple, and they wouldn't take like a huge amount
of time to like summarize. You know, they've got their funny moments. They've got their funny,
funny bits in there. Yeah, that's the stuff people want to hear. I think it's worth doing.
Oh yeah, yeah, I would do it, and at Radcon 5 I probably will, but it'll be short. It won't be
like a two hour lecture. I've heard suggestions for like a budget. I mean, I'm interested in what
people are, you know, want to hear and stuff. Like somebody the other day, because I think I was
on stream and I just said, I was talking about how much I love Legend of Dragoon. Someone's like,
do a Legend of Dragoon lecture. I was like, okay, I mean, first of all, Legend of Dragoon does have
some cool lore. We're talking about one game. Yeah. And there is some cool stuff about like,
did you know, I just learned this the other day, that apparently Dart was like the next character
being considered to be included in the PlayStation All-Stars right before the game got like canned
and they stopped making like new characters for it. That would have been wild. That's too bad,
because that was the one character I was really hoping to see is maybe a preference to like a
revival of the series, because I really do love that game and stuff. But I mean, and then there's
other ones like, I mean, Metal Gear, people have suggested, now that would probably be better,
because there's lots of crazy lore in there. And like the real life drama and stuff,
that could be pretty interesting. But I mean, yeah, it depends on how you want to do it. But
I mean, who knows the real lore of like the first two Metal Gear games, something about Gray Fox,
you fight him, Big Boss, Zanzibar, I don't fucking know. Metal Gear is a good, is a pretty good one.
It's a good idea. Yeah, like the thing about the lecture, I think the lectures are, they benefit
if the thing you're talking about is something that you could, that you would benefit from additional
context for other than if you just, like if you just play a Dragoon, you would know everything
there was to know about Dragoon. Like Kokoro Wish and stuff, it's like, well, there's like,
there's context about the author that helps, that is interesting and informs the work.
Michelle just made the best fucking tweet I've ever seen in my life.
Did she? What is it? Did you see, yesterday I posted a tweet that said three stage evolution,
and it was my three faces from the three radcons. Yeah, yeah. And how I've, I look way different
in everyone. She just tweeted three pictures of a spinel. There's like pre, pre, like happy
spinel, like sad spinel from the garden, and then like, like evil spinel. Yeah. That's supposed to
parallel my journey, and I think it is pretty much accurate. That's good. Way to go, Michelle.
Okay, okay. I think I'm done. I think I'm done talking about that.
I'm pretty, I'm pretty tapped in general. We could just move on to voicemails now,
if you want. We got them. That's fine. Yeah. Okay, let's do it. Let me see. Got them pulled
up right here. Okay, everybody, of course, you know, go down and click on the link to the speed.
Wait, I want to very briefly, I do want to expand on something that I mentioned last time.
Last episode, I said some stuff about how I thought makeup was cool. On reflection,
I think what that is, is that I just like the idea of being like an edgy goth teen and wearing
eyeshadow. I think, I think just being goth is what I like about it. Hashtag not gay.
I think they, I think that was the appeal on further reflection. Okay, fair enough. Just for
me to quickly mention something. I just want to be the front man of an emo band. I disavowed
everything I said about Droom Eternal last week. Droom Eternal is great. I love it now.
Oh, yeah. I wanted to mention that because I saw you change your mind about that or say something
online about how much you like DOOM Eternal. What sounds like, I mean, you got to the end. I'm
right before the last area. You had some issues with the last boss and stuff or whatever. I still
think boss fights aren't that great. Sure. Because I have a whole video coming out in like two days.
Do you like waiting for the Marauders eyes to flash before you can shoot the fucking axe, man?
The Marauders didn't kill me once. I don't know what everyone's bitching about. What? Oh my god,
I died so many fucking times to those guys. I'm playing, I'm playing on normal though. I know
everyone is playing on ultra violence. I'm not. I'm playing, I'm playing on not easy,
the one above it that looked hard enough. So that's probably the same as you. Yeah. Yeah.
I've killed, I killed all the Marauders without ever dying to them once and I felt like a god
because of it. Shocking, based. Well, yeah, you're good. You do video games, clearly.
He is video games, you fucking idiot. Courses through my veins. So what changed your opinion?
Game stops in essential service. I remember we talked about how I like to talk to my
Twitter and you didn't like it. What changed? I'm going to change my Twitter handle to Game
Stop is an essential service. Good idea. Great idea. So tell me, Tom, what was your thought
process? Well, you can, I'll have a link to the I Am Games video that goes over everything in the
description when it's up because at this time recording it's not. But it's just like coming
to grips with, OK, the first thing that I realized that I did not know for the first like three or
four levels is that unlike Doom 2016, the chainsaw is constantly recharging. So you almost always
have at least one charge. Oh, I didn't even know that. OK. And that changes the entire dynamic
of the game because in 2016 you hold on to your chainsaw charges unless you really need ammo or
if you want to take down big enemies. But in this game, like because your ammo capacity is so much
lower, you're supposed to be chainsawing constantly. So I noticed that the whole flow of the game
starts to click because you're like, oh, that's why there's ads in every encounter because
they're ammo boxes with legs. I get it now. Yeah, that's true. I noticed in one of the loading
screens, it specifically said there's like a four, it's like a list that's like, OK, like,
well, I forget what it's called. But what's it called? When they glow yellow and you do a kill,
get health. Brutal. Yeah, like it's like a brutal kill for for HP, you know, like flamethrower
for armor, chainsaw for ammo, and then like bloody punch or whatever to build up whatever the I
don't know whatever the fuck it is. Actually, you you do brutal kills to build up your bloody punch.
So like they're they're clearly they're trying to get you into a flow of using these like in
rotation to keep all your stats up and keep your health up. You need to use everything. I really
enjoyed that. And once you do, OK, the best fucking thing, like the game basically becomes
first person Devil May Cry once you have everything unlocked, because like you can like
double jump and then double dash and then meat hook all the way across and like,
then like super shock on someone in the face, turn him into Gibbs, then you land and turn
around and you can blood punch and they turn into Gibbs. It just you can make an encounter just a
nonstop sequence of increasingly cathartic violence. And it's 10 out of 10. It's great.
Except for the parts that are awesome. What's your favorite weapon? Just a curiosity.
Dude, the meat hook and the super shock and so good. Yeah, it's good shit.
Like I I feel I feel a little bad. I feel like I'm missing out not playing Animal Crossing during
the the quarantine. I also want to play it, but I haven't been Doom yet. My my roommate has it and
like I could play it if I wanted to. But like, I don't know, on the one hand, like it's such a
time sink. Yeah, on the other hand, but like everyone on Twitter is doing it. And it's like
it's someone said that like us play like it's the opposite energy from that one summer where
everyone was out playing Pokemon Go. It's very now is everyone is at home playing Animal Crossing.
Hey, I heard though, this may be of interest to you if you're considering playing on on someone
else's switch specifically, because I heard that like there's only one island per switch. So even
if you made an account, you'd have to like share the land with that person. What? That's why I heard
a different account that doesn't that's that was like an annoying thing that like Nintendo,
I don't know. They I don't even know what the point of it is. That would be very weird if true.
I haven't explored it, but that's what I had heard and it made me dubious because me and
Michelle were thinking of getting it and splitting it. I was planning on getting Animal Crossing
now that I'm done with Doom. But then I watched Jim Sterling video on it and he said that there's
item degradation and items break out the time. And that made me not want to play it anymore.
Like what? Like your chairs and your furniture and shit? Just like, I don't know. They're just
like, he's just said like, yeah, there's like your, your like, your tools, your tools all break
and shit. I'm like, I'm not fucking with that shit. Maybe I'll play. That's not, that's not so
bad, though, because those can be replenished. And none of those are, you don't get like legendary,
like golden shovel or something. His like, his, his, his video basically broke it down to saying
that like Animal Crossing has always been like a grindy game, which I'm already not a huge
fan of, but he's like, Nintendo just makes everything more grindy in this one. And I'm just
like, I'm out. The point of Animal Crossing is the grind. Right. Which is why I've never played
an Animal Crossing game and why apparently now I definitely never will. Sure. Sure. What's a shame?
The guys are, what, what if you shipped Isabelle and Doom guy? Cause what if game was in same game?
Oh God. Yes. I'm coming. What if Gabe and Tycho found themselves trapped inside their favorite
video games? I don't even want to think about that. All right. Let's, let's do voicemails. We got
voicemails over here. Yeah. Let's do it. Gamer news covered. All right. As we said, speak pipe,
link in the description, leave us voicemails. If they're good, we'll play them. That's what you
get. Okay. First up, we've got Girona question as a corona question, I assume. Let's hear what he
has to say. Okay. On the count of three, hit play. One, two, three, go. Ayo, shots out to all my
needs out there hooping on this living in pod, eating bud, wave for a minute before this corona
quarantine should happen. My question to the PC people is, what's the most unexpected difference
or like alteration that you've noticed in your life as a result of like this quarantine or like
just Girona panic in general? Make sure y'all stay safe out there and keep sipping on that pure
out piece. Just sit back in a nice bubble bath and a tall flute full of a hand sanitizer.
I think we've, I think we touched on this already. The biggest difference for me is not that I'm
doing anything differently, just that I feel worse about it. Yeah, I pretty much agree.
Cool. I love to feel bad and it's been a great excuse. Oh, well, actually,
my roommates are all home more now. They're all like working from home more or just not able
to work because of it. And the result is that there's more, they're playing board games all the
time. And I've been playing some more of those occasionally, not that often, but once in a
while. So yeah, I guess that is a little different. Playing a game called Gloomhaven.
I've wanted that one. I want to try that. I haven't played it, but I've heard good things.
It is, Gloomhaven is weird. It's like, it's, it's like continuous. Like you buy Gloomhaven and you
don't like play discrete games of it. Like every time you play it, you like change the, like the
game itself, like it comes with this big map. And when you like do missions in the game, you might
unlock like a new area and then you'll take a sticker and like put it on them. Like you'll
uncover a new area and you unlock classes by like fulfilling quests with your current classes.
I, the character, the only character I have played thus far is a, he is a little psychic ratman.
Actually, this is funny. Sounds like you, man. Yeah, he's a little psychic ratman from the sewers.
And he basically, he basically, he kind of like just kind of skulks around and he like tries to,
he like in limited ways, like mind controls enemies, like makes them attack each other or
makes them move or makes them do stuff. I'm pretty bad at it, to be honest. But his,
his, his quests that I drew randomly is to, he wants gold. He just wants to accrue 200 gold.
And that's, once he does that, he'll have unlocked a new class by
finally afford that operation.
And, but so, so in encounters, like everyone else, like everyone else would be like, oh,
okay, I'm going to heal the party. Oh, okay, I'm going to like stun everyone. So they can,
okay, oh, I'm going to like get, hey, guys, move everyone into arrangement. Guys, be sure to like
move, don't go here, don't go here. I'm going to do a big AoE attack. I'm going to like, I'm going to,
you know, like, like do crowd control. And I'm like, I'm just going to let you guys do that.
And I'm going to like hang in the back room and like loot everything. Like fuck, fuck that,
like fuck the enemies. I just want money. I'm just here to get money. I will help you if it's
convenient for me. And you know what, it's fine. It's fine because if I unlock that quest, everyone
benefits, right? Good. Yeah, sure, sure. Makes sense. Yeah, that's my goal. Also, I named, I have a
backstory for my rat. I named him target practice because the idea is that he was like a little,
like freak, like in like a city or something, like in the sewer drains or whatever. And like the
local kids, whenever they'd see him, they would throw shit at him because he's gross. But he didn't
like speak English well. So he would hear them say, they would yell target practice as they threw
things at him. And he thought it was his name. That's charming. Thank you. I like that. It never
comes up in game, but I thought it was cute. In answer to the guy's question, not much is changed.
But soon he'll have 200 gold and he'll be able to buy and sell all those kids on the black market.
That'll be great. We're all looking forward to that. Not much. I've done a little more socializing
in the sense that my sister came to visit and she was here for two days and that was very nice.
Grace is a cool girl. Fun to hang out with. You're a dog. You're a dog and I'm sick of it.
And that was her claim to fame. Other than that, nothing's changed.
Yep. That's it. Based. Tom, any changes for you? Notable. No. Unexpected. Just
doing the same old, same old, but it's more annoying because things I can't, I got to worry
about wiping my ass apparently. I'll tell you, I'm running a little low on toilet paper. I'm
hoping there's going to be some in the store. That's the worst part is now I got to wipe my ass.
Never had to do that before. All of a sudden it became a big deal.
Everyone's shaming me on Twitter for not wiping my ass now that there's a pandemic going on.
Everyone's bitching about toilet paper. I'm just like Amazon.com, get a bidet.
Where in the constitution does it say I have to wipe my ass?
Negative rights or positive rights? Fucking big government.
All right. Let's go on to our next question here. This is from the unironic gang weed guy,
KK Corona with another K. How fun. All right. Let's check it out on the count of three. One,
two, three, go. Hey, PCP. It's everyone's favorite original voicemail character,
the unironic gang weed guy here to talk to you sheep out there. You normies think you have it
so bad because of social distancing. You celebrities having mental breakdowns in your
multi-million dollar mansions while we suffer. Bitch, please. This is what we introverted
enlightened version gang weed gamers deal with every single day, bitch. Gang weeders rise up.
The joke's on you. There you have it. I mean, just hard agree.
That's all there's to say. I saw a comic posted on Twitter by Ethan Cool. You know Ethan Cool?
Don't think so. Ethan with an EA at the beginning for some reason. Don't know.
He's cool. He's an animator. But he posted a comic that's like it's like a little neighborhood
being attacked by face eating reptile mantis people. And the news is like stay indoors,
stay indoors, world in peril. And his mom's got a shotgun and she's like I'm going out for groceries
now and the gamer kid is like stay inside. Don't mind if I do, right? Gamer heads, level up.
Someone's getting devoured out of the window. I laughed. I lulled. Oh, I'm lulling. All right,
let's move on to our next voicemail. Here we go. We've got a three-parter. This is from the Scooby-Doo
Mystery Murder Files presented by Rhythm I Asked Back. I'm a bit of a murder file myself,
if you know what I mean. Indeed, indeed. All right, let's listen to our intro track here
on the count of three. Here we go. One, two, three, go. Hello, it's me, your host. Holy,
not gone, Trump. You may call me the interviewer. You're probably asking yourself right now,
what the fuck have I gotten myself into? Well, let me tell you,
Bucco, you are about to listen to the best voicemail series ever. It's the best because it's hosted
by me. Holy, not Donald Trump. I have the best voicemails. Okay, let me lay it down for you.
Every week, I'll interview one of Scooby-Doo's victims, then Scooby-Doo himself, a fairness
or something. Okay. Also, viewers, aka the PTP, they're free to ask any questions on the
podcast. I'll answer them the following week. Don't come yet, the show is about to start.
Right the fuck now. All right, totally not Donald Trump. What's that? I have one question
right off the bat, which is how do you interview, if this is a murder mystery, how do you interview
Scooby-Doo's victims? Aren't they murdered? Presumably, not every victim is specifically
murder. Unless they're ghosts. Unless they're ghosts because it's Scooby-Doo and they like ghosts.
Well, that's true. That's true. That's gotta be it. There's your answer. All right, well,
let's listen up because we've got the creeper, not the Minecraft one, as they understand it,
but the Scooby-Doo one, who is a distinct guy, although he's also green. All right,
let's hear what he has to say. Here we go. One, two, three, go.
Welcome to the Scooby-Doo Mystery Biles. Our interviewee today is the creeper,
or do you prefer Mr. Creep? Creeper. Creeper, it is then. Now, could you tell us a little bit about
Scooby-Doo? Creeper, creeper, creeper, creeper, creeper, creeper. I see. You're saying Scooby-Doo
gave you the TSD so badly that that's why you have to talk in this way.
Creeper, creeper, creeper. What exactly did he do to traumatize you so much?
Creeper, creeper, creeper, creeper. He raped you in the butt. He must have been
paid for considering his massive doggy dump. Creeper, creeper, creeper, creeper, creeper, creeper,
creeper, creeper, creeper, creeper. He used his tail to rape your mouth simultaneously. You say
where it makes sense to die until you're coming and enjoying in the raping. It seems
to make the same circus. Creeper, creeper, creeper. I understand. It's hard. Some things are too
difficult to talk about. Creeper, creeper. Thank you for your time, creeper. Okay, there you go.
Thanks. Well, Trump. Now we know. It's totally not Trump though. It's not Trump. It's definitely
totally not. No, you're right. You're right. All right, let's check in with the rapist. Let's see
what Scooby has to say. All right, here we go. We gotta get both sides. We need to hear both sides
of this story. That's right. This is balanced, fair and balanced news always. Okay, here we go.
One, two, three, go. So, Scooby-Doo, we just got done talking to that creeper. Can you tell me
anything about what you did to that creeper? I raped him in the butt. He was real nice. Yeah?
Why did you rape him in the butt? We weren't just going to rob him, but then we found out he had no
money. Me and Donnie raped him in the butt to punish him. His wrath was real nice and tight.
Must have been a origin. It's hard to listen to. It's the first time you met Donnie,
wretch, but I'm sure it won't be the rest. It might be the times when you pick up on these days,
but he would enjoy your ass, waste or interviewer. I don't think you or Donnie will be getting any of
my booty anytime soon. I see you like to play horrible wretch or don't kid care of you. Enough
of that. Why did you leave the creeper alive? Too little time. Not enough fucking. Be shocked.
The cops showed up. And with that, that was just one of the other poll shows who lost its innocence
to the pause of Scooby-Doo. Next time, we meet another poll show on the Scooby-Doo mystery
modifiers. Same PCP time. Same PCP channel. There you have it. Episode one. Thank you,
interviewer. Good luck not getting raped. What an unfortunate state of affairs.
Yeah. This is not good that this is happening, but it is. Maybe big government can save us from
this as it can with all our problems. I can't think of any other mechanism that stands a
chance, frankly, about dealing with this travesty. More to come next week. Thoughts and prayers
for creeper. Yeah. He didn't ask for this, but we did spook those kids, so maybe he deserves it.
A popular opinion? He deserved it? Funny, funny. You know, we said we had to hear both sides of
the story, but they were pretty much the same. I committed a rape. I was raped. Yeah. I mean,
this is locking key right there. It checks out. Yeah, it does. It's credible. It's credible.
In a word, credible. Yeah. All right. Let's go to our final voicemail of the day, and we really
got to set this one up. All right. This is the one we've been waiting for. This is important.
This is a humble, Ugandan interviewer who has a series of pointed questions for the PCP,
and you guys need to pay attention, listen up, and get serious, because this is important.
Okay. So you're ready? All right. Here we go. Count three. Here we go. You got an interviewer,
take it away. One, two, three, go. Why are you gay? Thanks for this, everybody. That's the end
of the PCP episode for this week. Wait, I have an essay. I have a thesis written on this topic.
That's it. How did you read my Google Docs? I read the script of this episode. They're all
pre-prepared. This is a fake. We're tricking you. This is a friendship simulator in every sense.
It's all been carefully formulated. It's a focus group. Indeed. These are the optimal choices made
on every episode to optimize enjoyment and monetary returns. We're surging. Jesus Christ,
we need to get a sponsor immediately. We're surging. Yeah, yeah. We just had a rapist on our
show. Can't wait. The sponsorships are going to start rolling in. The viewers love it. It's hard
hitting journalism, goddammit. We neither confirm nor deny our support of rape. Please sponsor us.
Ray-Band headphones or whatever. It's Ray-Khan. You got to use the right names. Ray-Band sunglasses.
Also them. That's cool. I'm down for that. Anyway, leave your voicemails, everybody,
on the Speak Pipe link down below. There was a mere pittance this time, and that's perfectly fine.
If you want to leave them, go ahead. We'll check them out. This is decent. Yeah, this is fine.
This is a good number. I got no problem with that. That's it, everybody. That's it for this episode
of the Procrastinators podcast. We'll be back next week with another episode. In the meantime,
support the show and get bonus episodes. Oh, there will be a bonus episode out by the time you hear
this. Most likely. We have not recorded it yet. Whoops. I forgot about those. I forgot about those.
Shit. Patreon.com slash The Procrastinators. I'm sure it'll be great. You can count on that.
There will be like 36 fucking ones by the time you hear this. There's good. There's gold in them
hills. Indeed, indeed. So even if we can't think of anything good to do for this one,
even if we just slap this one together and shit it out, you know, it's fine. There's other gold
in there. No doubt. It'll average out to be good because of all the other good ones. Indeed, indeed.
Maybe we'll play Animal Crossing. Watch, go back. I laugh every time I remember the time when we
played poker and I c***. That bonus episode. Oh, shit. Spoilers. I spoiled it. Oh, you ruined it
for everybody. Bleep that out, Eleazar. Bleep it out. Bleep it out. It was funny. It was funny.
It was funny. That's my favorite. Of course, follow the news, updates, any Twitter posts.
Look, there's lots of rad content still coming out from Radcon 4 on the Twitter. So follow
at TPCrastinators. It all gets retweeted there and more news and updates. I've been seeing on the
Twitter like PCP, like highlight moments. Is that new? Oh, that's right. Of course. I'm so glad
you mentioned that. I forgot. Eleazar, at his suggestion, was like, hey, Nate, we should bring
back the PCB highlights. And I was like, yeah, so we all talked, we agreed. And so Eleazar has
been making little highlight bits on the PCP highlights channel, which there will be a link
to and you should go subscribe to because we're going to now, at least monthly, release more
PCB highlights of some of the best moments of the PCP historically. We've already got Nate's
legendary roller coaster story and his, I don't want to be a cog in the machine. We've got Ben's
Molly doing story. There's a bunch of other ones on there. There's the elephant masturbation
discussion. I'm actually going to give that one a retweet. Please do. That's relevant to my content.
And we're going to try to get more from everybody and have a good spread. Eleazar is the man in
charge. So if you're in the PCP patron discord, there is like a highlights channel in there.
Go post in there moments. You want to see highlighted and Eleazar will be looking there.
That would be great because I don't fucking remember. There's a lot of episodes. This is a show
to you guys, but this is just our life and it all blends together. Yeah, please. If there's like
moments like, oh, that was really funny. That is a thing that sticks out in my memory. Just tell
Eleazar, go in the patron lounge, be like, we need a highlight of this. Eleazar, this is good shit.
I think his name's at Facundo on Twitter, but put your link in the description Eleazar for
Twitter. If you want people, maybe you don't want people to. But for people to give you suggestions
for highlights, he's the man in charge. So that would be a good thing to do. But yeah,
more coming. We just released like four new ones. And yeah, we're going to try to get some.
I don't think he's Facundo. That might take his name on like discord or whatever it is. He's got
a name on discord or on Twitter. I'm sure he'll post it for your viewing pleasure. It'll be in
the show notes, I'm sure. Okay, there you go. So more highlights are coming and we're going to make
more. Give us suggestions. We love them and they're a great idea. And we want to get that
channel to 1000 subs already so we can make money off of them already. Jesus Christ.
BASED. Absolutely, absolutely fucking based. We've got to merchandise, man. With a podcast,
you've got to have highlights. You've got to have, I don't know, fucking merch and stuff. Jesus Christ,
let's make some money here. It's time to go. Let's do this thing. All right, there you go.
So more stuff coming. Add to your crossings on Twitter. Updates and whatnot. My lecture will
be out by the time you hear this. I have no doubt at this point, it's very close to done already.
We'll see if that comes true. And more stuff coming. We've got a lot more. More lectures,
more content, the big stuff working on, a certain diss track. We'll be getting together pretty soon
and you'll see that in your sub box when it stays. So there you go. I'm excited for all of us.
All right, that's it. See you next week, everybody. More PCP.
Eventually. There you go. All right, see you then. Bye.