Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever. Let's see who we've got in the menagerie today. We've got Gibbontake.
A-yup, lad.
We've got Tom Oliver.
Yeah, me too.
Ah, she has some fucking enthusiasm. You pathetic, cum-addled brain losers.
You fucking coomer.
Yeah, Ben's saying it. There he goes. Tell you tell him, Ben. Who tell him?
Coomer extraordinaire.
You're no better though, you are.
Audience, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry the show is not good anymore. It's my fault. Please.
Coomer on the streets. Coomer in the sheets.
I want to be that big army guy who's shielding that little kid in the bed from all the attacks and death attacks.
You know that political cartoon? This is a little baby boy sitting lying in the bed.
I can think of a way better example. There's this incredible image.
My soul is just like, hmm, as flames and knives blast him from behind to protect him.
That's the gay millennial version of the actual good one.
The soldier is me. The PCP is the baby.
Okay, I appreciate that. But the better one is there's a glorious knight in shining armor shielding a beautiful princess as they're walking through a thing.
As the crowd is throwing shit and he's protecting her. God, I love that fucking image.
Anyway, we've got Digibro. There he is.
This is the first time I've been awake at the time this show is recorded since the last episode that I was on.
I think that was at least a month ago.
I don't even remember who are you again?
No one knows.
I'm that guy who isn't in the endless war.
What? In 2019?
I know.
And Lethal Aurora Mage. There she is.
You exist as I always do.
You do exist, Mage. And how? And let me just start off by saying let's get this out of the way, everybody.
Ladies and gentlemen, you will have seen on the PCB channel by now the release trailer.
Right now at this very moment, the PCP Minecraft server is live.
It is live. It is active. It is a thriving community already. No doubt.
And you can be a part of it for a monthly. It's got a separate Patreon, $5 and you're in the Discord and you can play the game every month.
That's how it is. It's got to be incredible.
Get excited.
Come join us. Play with us. We want to play with you. It's fun. It's going to be fun.
Okay, that's out of the way. We can move on with our lives.
But that is the most important thing we'll say today.
I just have to ask, how long do you think you're going to play Minecraft for?
Who can say?
Let's say it lasts two months.
I mean, I think Mage will be playing it until the day she dies in 2020 by my hand.
That's for me. I don't know.
Wow. Wow, Ben. Wow.
I expect to check in regularly.
Besides, like if we use it for streams and stuff, we like, I don't know, do stuff there.
It could be a gold mine. And you know, why not try it?
I just, I read the bones and that's what they told me. Don't hate me. Hate the bones, okay?
Hey, what's up guys? Nate from the future here.
Hey, one clarification point about the Minecraft server, just to make sure everybody understands exactly how this is working,
is we are going to be grandfathering in everybody with a PCP pledge of the $10 or up,
of which there's a handful of people.
Those people are going to be given access to the server now without having to go pledge any additional money to the new Patreon.
But for everybody else who isn't currently at 10 or higher, everybody else has to go pledge to the new patreon.com.
So don't bother raising your pledge up to $10 that isn't going to work for you.
We're trying to make a clear distinction here.
So if you want to get in the server, you got to go to the new Patreon and pledge the $5 there.
If not, that's totally cool. Don't worry about it. Have a great day.
And again, that's patreon.com slash PCB Minecraft. See you there.
What were we talking about?
Well, I mean, let's get into it, whatever else is going on.
Hey, you guys, I suddenly remembered that drawing can be fun again, right?
Because I'm drawing fucking Endless War comics. I'm drawing fucking Nightstar comics.
I'm drawing fucking Phantom Horn comics.
I just read all of that like two days ago.
I can't believe how fast you're fucking putting it out.
It is incredible.
Fucking blast. I've made like 110 images, 120 images, something like that.
It's really fun.
In the span of like a couple of weeks, right?
Well, a couple of them I made a while back, like the first like 15 or so.
But other than that, yeah.
I think initially it was more born out of the excitement over meeting Chris Chan, right?
It was because the genesis of this, the genesis of the love hogs, if you will,
is that I was reading through Sonichu issue 12.9, and in one of her backstory lines,
Nightstar says that her eye is green because she got some slime in it during a science experiment.
And suddenly my mind expanded to encompass all of not only dimension 12.18, but also C197.
And I realized that it was all connected in a great circle of life, and it was a story that I had to tell.
It very quickly becomes like, it seems like you're trying to make it a tutorial for Endless War as well.
Like a user book almost, like to lure in new people.
Like hey, because your biggest video is your Chris Chan video, so it's like, hey, Chris Chan people,
come look at this comic that is secretly trying to teach you how to play my underground discord video game.
I mean, Chris Chan is in Endless War right now. Like they entered.
That's true.
That's fucking crazy.
Yeah, the world, this is one of those moments where it's like, oh, our lives have gotten too fucking weird now.
It's so cool.
She's in there, she's got the special role of visiting mayor of Quickville, although technically, she is dead.
She is a corpse in the sewers.
And has her scalp.
No, no, Dupati Shmoopal has been messaging me.
Dupati Shmoopal has acquired the scalp through various trade deals and barter swapping,
and I guess he wants to barter with me for various objects.
That's the kind of thing Dup would do.
So it's not exactly a tutorial, it talks about, like I do bring, I do mention game mechanics every here and there,
just because I think it's funny, and you know, I drop links in there and stuff.
It is kind of, Matthew told me that people are joining because they're finding the game in the comic,
which is really funny, and kind of what I wanted, but also it's just sort of like a loving tribute.
It's just sort of a fucking...
Alright, I have the whole first chapter, ready to go.
It might be done, but I think I said this last week.
I'm getting close to there.
I just have all these key points, I have these key images in my head that I must hit,
and in between those, I'm just scribbling out, I have to fucking power my way through to that image that I see.
The next page is one.
I see it, I have to make it, because there's tons of artwork from Endless War, right?
And these locations, do they, within the context of the game, do they have accepted visuals?
Do people have a joined sense of what the minds look like, or have you just now defined that through this comic?
Is that official canon, or should people continue to interpret it differently?
It's both.
It's sort of loose, there's a loose canon.
If somebody draws a really cool version of, like, all of the locations have flavor text describing them,
but they're vague enough that you could interpret it in many ways.
So anything goes, but the coolest stuff is the thing people stick with.
Every district is a big place, so the fact that two people draw the minds differently,
you can just be like, oh well, okay, I mean it's a big place, you know.
There's two different spots, and like, this is, like, the agreed, if you draw it is canon.
Like, this is the understanding, this is the community, this is a collective understanding,
is that it's all canon, and like, you just gotta find a way to understand that it's all canon.
And I mean, did you, I mean, I just want to, I said this last time, but not only, yes,
everything that's happening here is canon, Endless War, that's how it works,
but the involvement of Christian, and by Christian's explicit word, has made all of this stuff,
all of this canon to real life.
It's canon to real life explicitly, and that's just right, so far as I'm concerned.
Just right.
So wait, what you mean by canon to real life is that it's canon to the Christian universe,
which is real life.
Well, yes.
I mean, Christian is canon.
Sonichu is canon, okay, well, first of all, all this is explicitly canon to Sonichu,
because Chris said so.
But on top of that, so now, this, everything adjacent to this, and Sonichu itself,
and Endless War, and T-Bat, and even Radcon, if you can believe it,
all these things are now canon to real life, in that they literally physically exist somewhere in the universe,
because all fiction, this included, takes place in C197.
So, it's all real.
We will go there soon, as the dimensions collide.
Magichan is already here.
Magichan has been appearing, he's been making appearances in YouTube videos lately.
Chris has been making tweets about, like, oh, look who showed up in one frame of such and such video,
too fast for the human eye to see.
It's Magichan.
Right.
Excellent.
I just want to know what it feels like to have gone from somebody who, like, a decade ago,
was, like, researching Chris Chan, and, like, following her output with Sonichu,
made a lecture that was, like, the biggest thing you've ever made,
and now Chris considers everything you've ever made canon to her universe.
It's not enough.
I want more.
What I want, I will not be happy until...
I will not be happy until Chris draws...
Chris starts drawing comics with your characters in you?
Until Chris starts drawing.
And not in, like, a weird idea, guys, way.
Just in a...
I just want to see...
I want, like, a genuine back and forth.
Like, a genuine artistic back and forth between me and Chris.
And once...
Do you think that Chris would be bothered by any of the content in your comic?
I think that she was bothered by the 9-11.
But not...
Okay, Chris was not...
That was the funniest fucking thing in that comic, by the way.
That was the same thing.
And the gigantic explosion of blood.
That was awesome.
Chris was not bothered by the blood at all.
Chris was not bothered by Red Man's murder.
Well, I thought that you was pretty violent, right?
Well, okay. It was and it has been.
But I think that Chris has, like, really walked back on that
because the reception to the end of...
Whichever one with the Alec Benson Leary trial...
That one has these, like, gruesome executions.
But all those were made non-canonical and, like, retcon
so that they didn't technically happen.
Chris, like, fully walked back from that, right?
Because the negative reaction was huge.
So, like, Chris has learned through, like,
the application of one's hand to a hot stove
that you don't touch that anymore, right?
So, Chris knows on some level that, like, violence is bad.
And that's why I think she was like,
whoa, okay.
This 9-11 was no fun, you guys.
Because, like, people reacted negatively to her
over that one video where she makes fun of Clyde Cash
by saying that he is like the Twin Towers.
Weak.
Ah!
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Weak like water.
And he could...
He, at the time, could blow Clyde Cash out,
like, birthday candles, just like the Twin Towers.
Right.
So, I think that was why Chris was like...
She said something about the Twin Towers about 9-11.
It's like, oh, good thing this didn't happen in real life.
This isn't the real 9-11.
This is a different thing.
This is fictional. Those buildings were empty.
It's got her bases covered, totally.
Good job.
But she didn't care about the fucking gruesome death of Red Man.
So, I don't really...
Red Man's fine.
Well, Chris doesn't know that Red Man's fine.
Yet.
This is a big reveal.
This is a big reveal that's coming.
The revive system is a big reveal
that's coming in the comic later.
Okay, that's fair.
So, I don't know what's going on in that head of Chris's.
I don't know what upsets her and what doesn't.
It's hard to say.
We'll just have to wait and see, I guess.
And wait for those sweet lures to be added to his comic.
Like, at the point when Phantom and Strawberry
are standing around just dripping blood,
just like coated in it,
for pages and pages and pages as they discuss
their situation,
like, at that point,
I thought I was over the line.
And, like, I was like, Chris is gonna see this
and be like, what the fuck is this?
Fuck off. But she didn't.
So, who knows.
What would you do if she got upset over something you drew
and wanted to sue you over the use of the carry?
Wanted to sue me?
Oh, well, I mean, she can't.
So, whatever.
Okay, drama.
Chris was talking to this person,
and this is something I didn't know about,
but, like, I've heard about it lately.
Chris was talking to someone named Sockness.
And this Sockness person was going to go
and see Chris.
And this person was really weird online.
And apparently, there were, like,
dating question marks, and, like,
Sockness got a ticket
and was gonna go see her.
And then, like, Chris called up.
But she called it off in, like,
the most lukewarm, stupid way possible,
where she's like, hey,
I still love you
and I want to see you,
but it's too soon, you know,
to send too many red flags,
at which point, message over,
you know, this relationship's off red flags,
but then it continued.
Actually, in reality, it continues, like,
oh, no, we'll do it later,
when there are fewer red flags, right?
It's like, okay, whatever you fucking need.
Chris has never been good at, like,
what's the word, cutting off when you realize
it's not gonna work out and making a hard decision?
This is, like, what's going on
in the Chris Chan life right now.
This is the drama.
They're not gonna fuck or whatever.
But, right before this happened,
Sockness messaged me on Twitter
being, like, hey, stop using
Sonichu shit, stop, like, doing this,
or we'll sue.
This is copyright infringement.
Who's we? Who are you, individual?
And Chris responded to Sockness, like,
chill out. It's fine.
Ah!
Chris is into it.
When you are more autistic than Chris.
No offense, Chris.
I think she's less interested in it
now that, um, Nightstar isn't
now that, like, it's not, like,
she's not liking every tweet anymore,
but, like, I'm assuming she's still seeing it.
You are tagging her
every single one.
I gotta bring Nightstar back,
like, just for, like, a little visual call.
I just gotta, like, test the waters,
make sure Chris is still paying attention,
trot the little image of Nightstar out
in front of her, like, hey, you just see,
you see us, it's still canon.
Yep. Yeah.
That's the easy fix. Get that.
Also, Chris has been,
those two panels of
Nightstar going, hmm,
I get it, you're lying.
Um, Chris has been using those
as, like, reaction images on Twitter.
Like, when someone says something
that Chris doesn't agree with,
Chris will respond with those two images.
Cropped very badly
in such a way that you literally
cannot see Nightstar's face in either
panel, but whatever.
The intent is there, I guess.
I love it.
Yeah, so that's, so that's,
that's what's up with that, I suppose.
Pretty fucking fun.
Pretty fucking fun. It's really fun.
Tom, what's the state of a Zoomie game right now?
Um, well,
I'm getting ready to
start Devtober again.
It's been one year since
the production of the game has started.
Yo, Tom, are you far from the mic?
You sound kind of quiet.
I didn't think you sounded that quiet.
Okay, that sounds better, I think.
Sounded okay to me.
Okay, well, Devtober
starts in two days, and that'll be a year
since I started working on the game.
So I'm gonna try and get the final public demo,
like, complete, feature complete.
Nice. Like, a level and stuff.
I have a couple people who are helping me now.
The game's come pretty far.
I've been updating it every couple weeks
for Patreon. What are people helping you with?
Just if you don't mind, Sharon.
Um, well, I have three people...
I have, uh,
Sixten and my friend, Adar, who've been doing
the soundtrack, and we've been going back far.
They've been making some new tracks. It's pretty fucking sick.
They got the authentic OPM
emulator things.
So it sounds authentic to Sega Genesis,
which is dope.
And then this other dude messaged me on Twitter,
out of the blue, was like, hey, I do 3D,
uh, let me help.
And I'm like, what can you do?
And then I just took one of my concept arts,
that I just showed him randomly,
and he's like, here's a fully complete model
in like three days. I'm like, okay,
sure, let's do it.
So, he's like,
super stoked about that. So I got a couple people
to kind of help lighten the load,
because there's a lot of shit that needs to get done.
It's, yeah, that's the way.
When was the last, like,
uh, well, no, I guess I should ask, like,
um,
when...
when can we,
the rest of us see,
when can the general public see,
like, the new build or something?
You got one plan?
I'm hoping by the, the plan right now
is to get the final demo,
that's like, basically an entire level
with a boss fight, by the end of December.
Nice. A boss fight. Okay, cool.
Cool, cool, cool.
Yeah, so I have like a boss that I've modeled,
I gotta figure out, like, how to...
Did you end up, like, finding somebody to consult with
not yet, that is my next thing.
I gotta find somebody who's, like,
Tom, Tom, if you want to win every indie game
award, here's what you do.
You, okay, there was, like, a thread on,
on Vee about this the other day, it's like, you, you,
you know, you know what, like, the jumping capabilities
of your character are, you just make
tunnels of spikes, and just make it
so that you can barely make the jumps,
and everything except a perfect jump is surrounded
with spikes, and you will win
every indie game award that there is
if you just do that, because that's what
the game design looks like, right?
No, you should base it, I think if you,
the more you base it on, like,
going back and playing,
like, Genesis Shinobi,
and just, like, try to copy the level designs
to some extent, because, like, if you're,
you know, I mean, obviously your mechanics
are more advanced, I think, than Shinobis are,
but, like, you know, if you want it
to feel, like, more authentic to Genesis,
like, you know, try to do Genesis
level design.
Yeah, I mean, that's the idea.
Examine that stuff. The biggest,
I don't want to say issue, but the
challenge right now is going to be that, like,
Izumi's movement is insane, like, you can
traverse, like, huge distances
with, like, a double jump plus a double dash,
so you can, like, go crazy
ape shit, so I might have toned that down,
even though it's super fucking fun, and it's the best part
of the entire game. I mean, you can also look
at stuff, like, like, Mega Man X
has more, like, agile movement
than, say, like, you know,
Shinobi, like, there's, like,
dashing and stuff like that, and
there's definitely some
games from that era that, you know,
that, like, you just use
they just, like, make the levels bigger.
They're just taller and more vertical, you know?
Yeah. There's just going to be a lot more
space. I mean, the funny thing is, like, I was
playing it, I was working on the mechanics,
I'm, like, getting really, like, into, like,
the hit stop and, like, the cathartic, like,
game feel. I'm like, why didn't I just make a beat
him up? Then I wouldn't have to worry about levels.
All those levels are literally just a straight line
approach things. That's true.
I would have solved, like, 90% of my power right there.
It's always been crazy to me, though, that beat-ups are, like,
we're such a big genre, because, like,
they aren't, like, really straightforward.
Yeah. I mean, they literally are
go left the game. I mean, those are
go right the game, depending on the level.
I think the appeal of those is just the sound effects
of the punching, and it's just really cathartic.
Exactly. And that's, like,
that's the thing that I'm, like, being
really autistic over, like, the last, like,
month has just been, like, I gotta make
maybe if I put the hit stop, like,
a little bit more to feel even better.
Maybe if I make this part not part of the hit stop,
so it keeps animating, even though everything else is frozen,
it'll feel even better. And I'm, like,
Great sound effects will
enhance, like, anything.
Like, if the animation is so-so,
if you get a perfect sound effect,
nobody will ever notice.
If it's not, like, the animation's a bit
roof. There was a game someone recommended
to me. I was watching a playthrough of it,
and I muted it, and instantly
the game didn't feel nearly as good,
because the sound was doing all the heavy lifting.
I'm like, huh, that's interesting.
So when I did that, I muted my game and made sure
it still felt good. I'm like, hey, hey, I'm better than you.
Oh, that's a good idea. Yeah, so...
It's cool.
I'm hype. It's gonna be, it's gonna be good.
Yeah, this reminds me of, back in the day,
me and my buddy John, I mean, in college,
I made a couple of games. There was a game design club,
study and that stuff, etc. But,
after college, me and my buddy John were working on
a game. I forget
and I think we gave it a name. It was something
musical related.
And the conceit of it was,
I was doing level design, and most of
the programming, I mean, whatever,
I was a more experienced programmer and stuff,
and I had done level design for a game.
Me and my buddy Rich had done in college,
so I was doing it again. That was
primarily a platformer, and I'll just tell everybody
the gimmick, because that's the most interesting
thing about it. And it's when you establish
your mechanics, then you build the levels around it.
That's the way to make it the game
that I would want to most play, because I love
platformers and stuff. And so,
here was the conceit of the game. It was
that every level
had its own music,
or maybe every world would have its own song
that plays in the background. And here was the thing.
On the beat, and sometimes irregularly
on the beat, there would be an
indicator that would flash. And so, on
beat, again, this is like a musically
themed game, you would get abilities
that you could only do basically on the
beat. It was kind of like a
R-Hero meets, I don't know, Super Meat Boy
or something. And so, like, just for one
example, you would, like, your jump
would go like twice as high if you jumped
on the beat as opposed to not on the beat.
It's a little bit necromancer, right?
Yeah, yeah, this is before necromancer.
But yeah, it was like that. It was like that.
But you would, yeah, I mean,
we thought it was cool. We made a couple of levels.
We actually made quite a few levels. But I mean,
this was, I made a little
character designs. It was cute. It was a good stuff.
But actually, this was the time when,
right at the beginning, I was spending my free time.
I was, you know, going to work. I was spending my free time
working on this game with John. But then I
decided to do YouTube. So I'm like, hey, John,
I'm going to spend my time doing YouTube instead
of working on this game. So, you know,
I won't have as much time. Maybe it just doesn't
work out. I'll come back. So
maybe one day, me and John will pick up that idea
and run with it again.
But I thought it was a good
idea. I love doing it. I kind of miss making
games because it's pretty fun. It's also
really, really hard. So the big problem
that I'm reading about now with games,
and that scares me immensely is
everyone's like indie games are over. It's
impossible to get noticed or make
any money off of them. Oh, that's fucking bullshit.
I don't believe that. It's crazy.
The entire fucking like
industry, not industry, but like community seems
like so fucking down on everything.
And I'm just constantly reading things about that.
I mean, maybe, maybe it's a pragmatic thing.
Like we can point to things like Hollow Knight and
even like Blasphemous that just came out.
But those, those are like, okay, how many
indie games were made for like two or three
or four or five to stand out at the peak?
Maybe just realistically. The big gay panic
in the indie scene right now
is that everybody is
doing, they're adopting
a Netflix subscription service now.
So like you only, you get,
you're going to get paid on this. Like Humble Bundle kind of stuff?
Well, the platforms
like, like a lot of people who do
indies right now are doing mobile. And
both Apple and Android
both just announced a $5 a month
spot, not streaming service,
but subscription service for games.
And so you're only under that model
you only get paid for how many minutes
people are playing your games. Oh my goodness.
So you're incentivizing like pointless endless
bullshit that just wasted your time.
Because you're just, just like
you know, fucking Netflix
fucked over like movies and, and Spotify
is like bankrupting the indie musicians.
Everyone's like, well, the subscription service
is coming for games now too.
So everyone's butt hurt about that. Feels like
more every day, like we're coming
closer to just have your own
website, forget stuff,
just be, be cool and have your own
shit. Tom, yeah.
Tom, you're planning to sell the game, right?
Uh, initially I wasn't,
but now that it's becoming such a
big fucking to do and it's becoming
a brain blast of like cool ideas that
have no idea how I'm going to pull off, I'm probably going to have to just
to justify all the effort.
How much do you think you charge for it?
I don't know, more than
$10. It's only going to be four levels.
Probably be like an hour to play through.
I think, I think if the game is only
like, you know, 10 bucks or less
and like we have a platform
to promote it, so like at the
very least it's going to get some sales. I mean
you could talk about it on I Am Games,
you could talk about it on here, we could
talk about it, everybody's probably going to want to
promote that shit because it's going to be a fucking
just like we did with Davoo's game, at least a little bit.
And uh, if you, if
the game was successful enough, do you
think you would try to like figure out if you
could like reproduce it onto
a Genesis cartridge?
I mean, I don't know if it's even like
technically possible, because like I don't know what the exact
specifications of the Genesis are.
I mean, I would love to have that, it would be
like the biggest come of all time.
How many people actually have a physical Genesis anyway?
You know, these days?
Well, lots of people. Everybody?
Yeah, maybe. There's currently like
it's kind of like a boutique market right now
to make like limited run
like repro cartridges of games.
But usually the games are
designed like literally around the systems
capabilities if they're going to do that, you know.
In Tom's case, it's more of just an aesthetic.
You know, what would be interesting, there's
there's a, there's a video
on um, on YouTube
of some guy that
it was just, it was called Doom running on an NES.
And I guess
what he did is you just have a, you have
you open up a NES cartridge,
you put a Raspberry Pi in there, and then
you can have it output through
the NES, but it just runs the game off the
Raspberry Pi.
Yeah, Raspberry Pi is like a mini computer.
Why would you put a Pi in your fucking Nintendo?
That sounds pretty messy.
What were they thinking?
Oh, it was a parody video, no one told me
shit. I thought this was...
But like, I'm just thinking like maybe you could do that for a Sega,
like you get like a Raspberry Pi, it runs
the game off that, but it like interfaces
through the Genesis's video out.
For a Genesis, you would use a chili dough.
Apparently it is possible.
What's up? I, I, I don't know
anything about this. I've only heard that like indie
people say that like getting your
uh, game on Nintendo is pretty, is pretty good.
Uh, would it that... Yeah, the switch
is pretty fucking hot right now for
indies, but even, even now it's like starting
to get super saturated, just because everyone's
targeting that. Cause there's way too much fucking bullshit.
Like they are not quality controlling it.
So you go on there and just like switch the
new Steam.
It's, it kinda is, yeah.
Steam's kind of, I guess, I was reading
today in a thread that I guess Steam's reduced
like profits for indies by 50%
or something, like some update to the policy
and everyone's fucking butt heard about it
and I'm just like, I don't even know what's going on.
I'm just over here in my corner, coloring.
So,
I have no fucking clue. It's very strange.
I can't, I can't believe, I really can't believe
that like indies are getting released on the switch.
That seems like, that's like the
opposite of like Nintendo's old
Goose game. Oh, someone was telling me
about Goose game just yesterday.
My friend, yeah, my friend
Toby was telling me that I got
to check out Goose game. My friend Toby
Fox. My friend, yes, yeah.
He was like, hey, Ben, love the
Nightstar comic. Just back the
Vapors 2 Kickstarter
at kickstarter.com
slash project slash
Ben St. Slash Vapors 2.
Love your, love your stuff. However,
have you played Goose
game? And I said, I'm titled
and I said, Toby Fox, you're a fucking
hack. Deltarune wasn't that good.
Come back
when you've fucking grown a brain, a dick
and a heart and
um
Has anyone actually, I mean
I've seen a little bit of the footage of Goose
game. It's just Goat Simulator 2, right?
I mean, who cares? That's what I said.
I don't know about it. I know
people love it. I mean
it's at least visually appealing
and Goat Simulator was not. I love it so much.
I agree. It's true.
Have you seen the Goose Waddle? That's all I need.
Oh my god. See, that's what people are paying
for. Lol, cute Goose Waddle.
Wow, that's worth my $1,000.
I'm here for this Goose.
I stan Goose.
I mean, that's all you need, I guess.
I'm thinking this whole video game thing.
Did you watch
Dunke's video about Goose game?
I did not. I did not.
You'll see that like, there's a lot of
it's like the AI scripting
of the people that makes the game
interesting. You can like really fuck with the NPCs
and like do weird things.
You can lock the little boy into a like
what's it called? The phone booth.
You can no clip through the little boy
and
QPU over a couple dimensions.
Oh, can you backwards long jump as the Goose?
You gotta keep your Goose QPU
aligned at all times.
That's the meta.
I want to see, I want to hear
like the Mario wahoo, but like a Goose
like honk.
Uh oh, it's secret Waluigi propaganda.
Imagine if Goose makes it into Smash
and Waluigi still isn't.
This game looks like
this game looks like a
like a Kurzgesagt video or something.
This game looks like
a like mass appeal
YouTube video.
It reminded me a bit of Ooblets
that you guys know about Ooblets.
I know the name, but I've never met the man.
I've heard of Ooblets. I've seen a bit of it.
They're the ones who got in trouble
for being on Epic Game Store, right?
Yeah, yeah. I've actually
knew about them way before.
I was looking forward to their game
on Steam.
So what's the deal? Did they get fucked?
They signed an
deal with the Epic Game Store
that they were like really...
That wasn't a big mistake.
They were up their own ass about it.
They made a whole thing just like,
you guys are gay. This is fucking great.
We're better than you because we made a game
and everyone was like, go fuck yourself.
Yeah, they were kind of rude about it.
If they had just been like, hey guys,
we're going to Epic Exclusive because
we really need the funding, whatever.
If they were honest about it
and just nice people.
When I see people arguing about the Epic Store,
like the argument
that I see online
is like, people are like, guys,
indie devs have to go
on the Epic Store because it makes them money
because they need money.
Duh, you idiots. And the response is
like, well,
fine, yeah, business is going to make
money, of course.
The thing people say is like,
yeah, but a lot of people
kickstarted their project, crowdfunded their project
or something for a public release
and then turned around
and released on an exclusive platform.
You bought, you backed the project
to get a Steam key and then like, oh, there's no Steam keys now.
Double-dipping, as it were.
Right, right.
I believe that Bloodstain, for example,
was originally supposed to be on Wii U,
but now, it's been so many years or whatever,
like, no one's, like, what's the point?
No one's gonna buy it. So they just ditched,
and I mean, it's fair to have a grievance
if you want it on the Wii U, but...
I mean, if you had a Wii U,
you probably have a Switch by now.
I feel like it would probably not be
here. You don't want to be changing your ways.
I mean, I was the oldest codger of them all
and I don't even have a Switch by now.
That's true. If you finally moved,
whatever, people are entitled to their grievances.
If people break their word, fair enough.
Patreon.com
slash PolyStation2 to play my game.
Play the new build. You can play
all the new moves I've added. It's pretty sick.
The hit stop is now
perfect, feels like the best
shit of all time.
Yeah, I'm really happy with it so far.
Hey, let me give you guys an update from the
Nate Overse, which is this thing.
So, me and Gib talked about this yesterday
when we recorded the Pawnee cast.
Was that yesterday? Yeah, okay, I think it was.
And there's a couple things going on,
but I've noticed a few things.
It's the subject of hype culture and hype stuff
that I talk about sometimes, but I just wanted
to bring up this one, particularly,
I don't know, a perfect example of what's going on.
And there was even a new one a little bit after
I saw that from yesterday that's even more
interesting. And so, the
new chapter of One Piece, I won't get into the specifics,
but among other things,
the new chapter had a big
flashback to some of Roger's
history, like Roger's greatest
rival of the past, and we learned about
a lot of deep lore about him and Garp
and things like this, and
the relationship of the Yonkos back in
the day, like the big, important people in One Piece, blah, blah, blah.
I know a lot of people don't know, that's fine.
And then the second
half of the chapter, what it did was it just dumped
all the Yonkos
bounties, which are like the
they're like the One Piece equivalent of like the power level
rating, it's different. People decide that it's not exactly
the same as like Rayatsu from Bleach or whatever,
but you know, there's a similar kind of hype
surrounding them, and we got them for
all the Yonko, Whitebeard,
and Goldfucking Roger. We got
like all their historical bounties that are
like said to be the highest of all time.
So like this, this is a chapter that gave
us numbers that don't really
indicate anything other than like
how much value like the Marines put on these guys,
and then we learned like some back
story that like, I mean
just thinking about it rationally, like Oda
could have just made this up like yesterday
and read it into the story as like something
he's planning for the future. It's not like this
was something that was really planned out for a long time
necessarily.
And I think given my experience with this series,
I think this would have been hinted if he was going to do it before.
Okay, but the point is
everything in this last chapter was like
pure hype bait.
It's like, okay, there will be future developments
about like Roger's past. Okay, cool.
And like his old
adversary, this guy rocks, etc. etc.
his old crew. And then also we just learned
a bunch of bounty stuff, and that stuff really
doesn't actually matter very much
to the narrative of One Piece. It's just
like satisfying for like us
like lore fags. People who are like
we want to know these numbers. It just
satisfies the autism.
And some people were saying this
was the best chapter of One Piece.
And I went on, I mean
some people who are like respected members of the
quote unquote One Piece community.
And I just found that so strange
that like as opposed to like
I hope you're not gonna go on, yeah, don't do the entire
rent again, it was really wrong. No, I'm not.
I'm just saying as opposed to like
a big end of arc moment where like
all this artistic stuff
that's been set up for like months and possibly years
all is like satisfyingly
concluded in an artistic
climax. Instead
this like hype chapter is called
like the best moment in One Piece. And I
find that like the wrong way
to read One Piece basically.
So it's hype culture at work. And then
just yesterday after I saw that
somebody tweeted me on Twitter
and they said, hey Nate, have you seen this?
This is what they led
with like Nate, did you hear about
the Sekiro DLC rumors?
Have you heard about the hints about Sekiro
DLC? Okay, so first of all
there's no one on the planet who's more
interested in Sekiro DLC than me.
I am the number one most
strongest Japanese boy
who wants my strongest Japanese DLC
for my samurai game.
This is what I want more than anything. So
when I actually, I'm like, okay, don't lie to me now.
Don't tease me boy. What is this?
He links me a
post from here. I'll fuck, I've got it right here.
It's a post on Sekiro's
Twitter that it just looks like
this and it says
the one armed wolf awakens
and it's just a picture of Sekiro
of Wolf, like from the
opening area of the game.
So people are taking this like statement
of the one armed wolf awakens
as like, ooh, could this be like a reawakening?
Could this be like more DLC?
Well, okay lads, let's use a little
critical thinking here. First of all
if you scroll down beyond like
two fucking posts, you can
see that this Twitter feed
regularly, it is the official Sekiro Twitter feed
it regularly posts
like still images of the game
with quotes exactly like this.
There's one from a couple days ago that's Kuro
the little boy that you work for, your lord
or whatever and it's just him and it says
I heard stories of your death, yet here you are
and there's more just like
the point being, like this
image is such a
poor indicator that there is actually
any intention of DLC, there has
been no other like
clues that any DLC is coming
and yet when you just look at the numbers
this image has been retweeted
4,000 times and all these other
ones have been retweeted like
100, maybe 200, like
150 and like there's like 10
times the amount of likes because people
have been like tricked into
thinking that this is like a hint of DLC
when there's like nothing implied
here and this is my point
this is the vicious hype machine
at work. I don't want to be
led to believe there's actually hints
of DLC coming when the actual
evidence when you do and you look at it
critically there's just no reason to believe
that and it just sets people up
like me in this case for
disappointment. So it's just
endlessly frustrating to me
that all these people involved, like I feel like
people say to me on the episode yesterday
they said like Nate we just want to get hyped
and excited about things, why you poo poo
in our hype and it's like well like
because it's disappointing
and people like if I bought Securo
now under the expectation that
DLC was coming that could be a waste of money
if like that's what I'm buying it for
customers and consumers can be
falsely led down paths. What if I read
all of One Piece because I believe
something that was wrong and then I get to it
and I'm like oh well shit that isn't what I expected
my time was wasted. I mean I
love One Piece but you get my point
I'm endlessly frustrated
by how people view this subject
and they just don't want to believe
that there could be any negative consequences
of any kind by like believing
things that have no substantiating
evidence by overhyping
things and possibly poisoning the well for
other people. You know
what I'm saying Lads, does this make sense
are you with me?
It could be fun like you know it's
actually coming and like and you
and your friends are like yeah it's
going to release this day let's get hyped
it's going to be fun and it's sort of fun
in the moment just to share the information
excitement with someone but also
like the hype itself if
you don't know if it's confirmed or not
or just like if you get like
toxic about it or violent about it
it's just or aggressive
I guess. Yeah that's true
or even just set up for disappointment
that's the great bugbear here
I don't want people to be disappointed by
things because I feel and it can
mislead consumers and money could be
spent places where it doesn't deserve or
time or energy I just want to save
people from that and myself
so I don't know. I feel this
reminds me of a situation like it pops up
every few years I keep seeing it
it used to be on Tumblr but I don't use Tumblr anymore
so I haven't seen it in a while
every few years season 2
of Oran High School House Club
is going to be announced soon
and everyone gets so hyped
and just like guys no
that will not happen
they keep promising the reboot
of reboot you know that old CG show
reboot
every now and then they'll announce it
as a way to like generate fake hype
but they never do it
if you look down at the evidence behind
any of these claims I would bet almost 100%
the actual evidence for it is like terrible
you know what this your stance reminds me of
is when the new generation
of consoles started
Super Bunny Hop had a series of videos
that were kind of what like first
drew attention to his channel
where he was pointing out that he just
was not hyped for the upcoming consoles
and he had first it was like
the Xbox one why I'm not
hyped which nobody was
so like it was just kind of seen as part for the course
but then he put out a video where he was
why he was not hyped for the PS4
and his argument was basically the same
as yours it's like a lot of the claims
they're making they have no evidence for
and in the PS3's case
what they tried to bill it as was not what we got
you know so like
we look like villains when we are just
when we poo poo and people want to be hyped
he got overwhelming dislikes on that
like even though it got enough views
that people paid attention to his channel from then on
like it's like 40%
dislike bar maybe even more maybe it's
more than 50 I have no idea how it evolved
over time but like people were just really
upset that like just the
PS4 literally on that
E3 just because it was presented
so much better than Xbox one is
considered to be why it is so
successful and it's like one of the most successful
consoles of all time after the
PS3 had been didn't even
sell half as much you know with a long
lifespan and weigh the fuck more games
I just found the video
5 reasons to not get hyped for the PS4
13,000 upvotes
17,000 downvotes the
the case is clear
and like he's not being unreasonable and like
shitting on it he's just like hey man
don't take the claim seriously until they've been
proven and like some of this
shit is they're talking out of their
ass you know like yeah it ended up
being a good console anyways it's just like
don't buy into the marketing just
wait till it comes out and if it's good
then great you know like modern day
triple A games a lot you know they promise
a lot you pre-order
and then like it's shit
you know I'm
working on
here and there I'm working on a concept that I'm
going to reveal at some point
in the future it's like a think piece
I've been wanting to talk about for many years
like my whole gaming career has been leading up
to it it's like it's like I think I've
mentioned a little bit it's something like
the intellectual limit on like
what a game or any kind of product
can be it like when I like for example
with someone like Final Fantasy 15
when I see people being like this game looks
so incredible like look at all the things
look how like complicated the animations
are I already know
that the developers first of all
technical limitations on how much you can do with
a controller and how much brain power
the average player can be expected
to commit to any given game 100%
tell me you are not controlling
the precise movements of these characters
it's mostly AI stuff happening
and then also I know for a fact
there's only so much work a dev team
can pour into any given game
to make it like feasible to release
I just know for a fact
that like Kojima levels of detail
are like an incredible rarity
we like never get that much detail
as like a Metal Gear Solid 3 environment or whatever
so like it's it's silly
to just allow the hype machine to be like
it's going to be like No Man's Sky
generation stuff almost every single time
and people just allow their imaginations
to run wild and they inevitably
set up for disappointment
I think that the culture has
somewhat shifted after like
Watch Dogs because so many people
that and the one you just said
and also like No Man's Sky
the non-release of like Star Citizen
over the course of all these years
you know or Spore
it's just like all these games that over promise
and then like but particularly
like Watch Dogs where it like didn't even resemble
the original thing it's like
it's just a generic shitty game
and everybody was like buying fucking
special editions of it because what they
showed in the trailers
looked awesome but like
it was like a technical benchmark
but they didn't achieve that in the game
this has been going on forever
I mean the Killzone 2 trailer
from fucking all the way back
the Dark Souls 2 trailer
fuck
the entire Anthem reveal
haha yeah exactly
like did you guys hear about
Anthem how like
they had this huge big reveal and it looked
gorgeous and everything and then later it came out
it's like yeah the entire dev team
working on Anthem found out the game was called
Anthem on that reveal trailer
that's how like far behind in development they were
and it's just like
oh dear
I mean one facet of this
this isn't I mean this isn't directly
into the subject but like your video recently on
Digi or Digi's video about
the new remake of Link's Awakening
or whatever like that
you know this is a little bit different but it's like
it's like what's the selling point
of that game yes apparently
some things have been improved in like the gameplay
but like why
a lot of it matters just what are you looking
for out of the game if you just want
a game that looks like that and you want to experience
then I have nothing critical
to say basically that's that it is
what it is there's no doubt no point
doubting it it's weird we've entered
a period now where like
we people have gotten used
to buying the same game multiple times
on different consoles like whichever
console you have hooked up to your TV because
of the fact that we use our consoles for fucking
everything like my brother
Victor he does all of his
YouTube viewing everything
internet browsing usually just because he's too lazy
to open a laptop all through the
ps4 so it's like
just you know
Jesse is somebody Jesse and
Tom I know are both people who bought the same game
multiple times
like you bought doom on the switch even though
you already had it on PC
like to be fair I bought doom on the switch
I thought I was going to be living in a car and I wouldn't
be able to fare on a ps4 anymore
okay fair enough but like
you know still buy it
will buy it on the on the sake of like oh
I want to have it on the switch
and like a lot of people had links
I did that with Hollow Knight I straight up just
bought it on the switch I wanted on it
I bought guilty gear double X like at least seven times
I also did them with forager so yeah
yeah there you go
I'm not going to get ruined factory 4 on the switch
even though I have it on the 3DS
I had bought links Awakening DX
on the 3DS and played it for the first time
there in the virtual console
and like because switch doesn't have virtual
console yet I think they were just like
alright well we've been remaking Zelda games
which one hasn't had a remake and it's like
Link's Awakening had a remake but it was still on the
Game Boy we could a lot of people
like it let's just update it
with better graphics and sell it for
60 fucking dollars and people will pay for
it because it's got the Legend of Zelda in the name and like
to me it's like it's obscene
but I almost bought it anyway you know
I was just kind of like well I'll play it
I know I was really tempted
I'm still kind of tempted to buy it
but I think I really do want to just play
the original more and it was absolutely your
if you haven't played the original I would encourage
you to because it's fun it's a fun
game like it holds up
it's you could pick up and play it
the only thing that's frustrating about it
is that you can only hold two items at a
time and the sword is one of the items so you
almost always want your sword equipped so
every time you want to switch items you have to open up the menu
and you will do it a lot
the number one only thing that's really not
good about the game everything else is good
so that game
Link's Awakening an Oracle of Ages
and Seasons I couldn't get into them because
all of the micromanaging of your inventory
I beat all of those though that was annoying
it was definitely annoying
they did somewhat
like they mostly fixed it because they gave
you an assigned sword button
and an assigned shield button and I think
the gauntlets are just permanently on so it's
like you don't have to do it as much
but there still were ways they could have
made it even better like they could have
given you like a weapon wheel or something that you
could just instantly switch between because
it's not that there's a ton of them but there are a
few that you need to use a lot
so it's just like why make it so I have to go
into the menu at all
but you know this is the thing this was funny
I was like trying to get answers about this
I tweeted out I mean I don't know I've been doing this a bunch lately
I'll just say it like I was thinking about doing
this with Code Vein
Code Vein has been discussed on V for a million years
like the waifu creation people are going
hog wild about it but like
I'm just like okay I could maybe enjoy
the waifu playing as and the creation
and jacking off to IO like your waifu
in the game whatever I could do that for like
I don't know maybe even up to an hour
but once I'm done with that
I'm gonna want to actually play the game
it's apparently Dark Souls-esque so like
I didn't do this yet but I've been doing it with other games
I want to tweet like so guys is this game actually good
I think it is
I believe it is but I'm not
100% sure I know it was just a development for a million years
I mean people fucking love Monster Hunter so
I never got into it I still need to
it's the one from the
big difference it's the one from the God
Eater people yes okay it is
like just like that one yeah
but they're copying they're trying to know it's
it's from the God Eater people but I think it's like
more of a Monster Hunter type of game
because I read an article about it in like a game informer
or something before it came out
well I mean the way that ties into this the Zelda thing
is like so I actually did do this with Zelda
I just tweeted like guys like you know
me I mean this was like mostly
I'm a nostalgia blinded old fuck boy
and I hate everything that's new
but like just tell me like
I want to play a game for the gameplay the aesthetic
will only last for like a little bit then I'll get
tired of it because that's how I play games I want
good gameplay will I enjoy
the new Zelda remake it's considering
that I've like loved every classic Zelda I played
when I was young and I'm okay with that
kind of game remake which game
Link's Awakening was
that was on the original on the Game Boy
that's correct
did I ask the same question last week
no but we did just
cover this right now sorry I was
trading I was completing the trade the trade
is done I've given Master Slimal into Dupati
Smuple and I am Schmuple and I am now
in possession of visiting mayor
Christine Weston Chandler's scalp
in Endless War congratulations in my
pocket just had to announce it
I'm very excited anyway
mm-hmm what the fuck
were we talking about
Zelda will I actually like the Zelda gameplay
I think that you would definitely
prefer to just emulate
the old game like
if you I mean I don't it's free first of
all that's a big plus right there
the fucking game is $60
it's only five hours
long if you play it fast like
it's not a they didn't
change anything about it it's the same
fucking game they just change your
controls so it's like this is a Game Boy
game I can like I bought
it on the 3ds it was like eight
bucks maybe ten you know
like I was willing to pay that for the
ease of playing it on my 3ds
because I wanted to play it there I had been playing
a lot of 3ds but like
yeah I play a lot of switch but fucking
$60 I can literally just
download this game and play it on
any computer in the fucking house and it's not that
long that's how I played all the other classic
Zelda games it's not like there's a fucking
collection pack where I can just buy all
of these in one thing like you can do with
Mega Man or Sonic or the entire
fucking Sega Genesis library
like how fucking hard
is it for them to just put together
a pack of all the classic Zelda games
Nintendo knows they don't have to
because they can tell us $60
reskills they're the apple of gaming
they can go against before
before we go even further down
and like I wanted to talk about hype
for a bit if we're still on that
okay the
the whole thing with like hype I mean in video
games specifically I don't feel it because
I'm extremely cynical like the last
time I was hyped good for
any video game was
Dark Souls 3 and since then
I haven't really cared about anything that's
come out
do you feel any hype
at all for the promise of the next
Hida Takamiya Zaki game
the one that's being
written by the Game of Thrones guy
I mean yes and no
when's the next fucking book when's
wins of winter George
I don't know give it a couple years
it's been like a fucking decade
George is gonna drop dead and we're all gonna
die along with it
Elden Ring is
wait that's it
George George
he's known for killing characters
his final act is tragically killing
the ultimate character himself
before the books are done
the ultimate twist he's gonna die
at the ledger
anyway he's gonna die at the ledge of a fucking
cliff
usually with games
I'm not like I don't get hype
for media in general I don't get hype
but I do effect
I do get the hype thing
in other areas and I have
I've experienced
the unbelievable
anger that comes from somebody quashing
my hype
which is why I understand
the people who get upset about it
is because
I forget exactly what the situation was
but I was like trying to figure out
some things with learning to draw
art
stuff
just techniques
or approaches that are good or bad
or whatever
I was thinking I had something pretty good
and I was like talking about it
and then somebody comes in
actually I don't think I was talking about it
but I was reading people's things
I was like yeah this sounds really good
and then the people come in and say
by the way all of that stuff was
really stupid and
here's some examples of better artists
who are explaining why that isn't true
and it was like it destroyed me
and I got really mad but I didn't say anything
because I was just like
they're right they have the proof
and
the anger was like
this thing is provably stupid
in whatever way I forget exactly
but the thing that
the feeling was is that I had hope
you know I had hope for this thing
I was invested in this
approach and I realized
that oh yeah this doesn't make sense
and it's stupid and this guy came
you know he's destroyed
my hope and I feel like
a lot of the reason people get hype for things
is that they really want to be hopeful about something
and any negativity
that gets in their way is just like
how fucking dare you I have enough to deal with
without you making video games
upsetting for me god damn
people think that video games aren't
serious enough business to like
worry about this stuff with which I understand
to a degree it's 2019
the planet is dying
I just want to get hype for fucking
what's that condemned
what was the one with the cone head man
a blasphemous
I just want to be hyped for blasphemous and then you
come in and tell me that the art is good
but the gameplay is mediocre get the fuck
out of here what am I supposed to live for
yeah it's that
it's literally that feeling and it's like
how do you fix that
well you know what
let me just give one other counter example
you know what I'll tell you how you fix it
you do it eventually
I've been enjoying video games which is
you go and
watch videos of people
reviewing old games
and then find out
what ones are interesting and then go play
interesting old games and fuck
all that shit
how was that more work
I don't get it
I'm not specifically asking about like video game hype
because obviously the thing is just wait for it
to come out and then look at reviews
so that you don't get disappointed but like
I'm trying to figure out why people are so
set on being hyped that it makes them so angry
when people
quash their hype or tell them not to get too excited
because they're
it feels bad though
I don't know whether people were this hopeful years ago
is it because the world sucks more and we're so
we're so
we're too
we're too linked in with the brain nodes
to all of the bad things that are happening
we just want something
probably
I totally agree
that is a real thing that sucks
I've had people tell me that I ruined anime
for them because they started
looking at it too critically and now
maybe anime was never good guys
and I'm just like well I don't know how you could
reach like I don't know how I could bring you
to that conclusion because I'm thinking about it more critically
than you are and I still find shit to like
all the time dude that's that's how I feel about
I shit on one pieces little imperfections all the time
but I always end with one piece is my
favorite thing ever and people still
take away that I'm like taken away their joy
which I find perplexing
but I uh yeah I mean it's the same
same phenomenon I love
Dragon Age but I also love all the
videos at Bastion Dragon Age because so
interesting to see like
what sort of issues people have
with Dragon Age and I can go
hmm oh okay that's an interesting view
I'm about to go very pretentious
you know what it is it's that their love
is shallow and not founded
on critical thinking it's founded on shallow
hype and so when we criticize
from a deeper level perspective they
have lost their argument they have nothing
to fall back on because they haven't really thought about it
until this point I think there's also a lot
of identity tied up in it because nobody
wants to have bad taste
and like there's a lot of reasons to like
something um you don't
have to like every part of it like you
should not expect to like absolutely
everything about anything like maybe
you like 99% of it there's only
one thing that bothers you but it's still like
worth addressing but there's some people
who are like if you point out that it's
flawed at all that it's like oh shit are you
trying to tell me that my favorite thing isn't the
best possible thing like I can't
be wrong about this but it's like
you have enough experience to know
that there are other things other stories
that are more complete
that don't have these issues that this
thing has and it's like look one piece
is my favorite thing it has
more good in it more things I care about
in it than anything else but
I have seen things that didn't fuck up
the way this thing has you know let me tell you
there was one perfect example of this I was
talking to Pa Diaz Gord boys yesterday about
this issue do like this is this is the
perfect example okay so early on in one
piece there's a thing called the log pose
this is just how they got through the grand line
okay cool it's a compass
that guides you along towards the end
okay but but but here's the thing
here's the thing it when they get to the
new world after like the halfway point of
the time skip or whatever like Nami gets
a new log pose that has
like three nodes it's like it's like a it's an
upgrade it's I believe it's
only used one time to
get them to punk hazard after
they leave Fishman Island it's like the first
place they go after the time skip basically
okay the log pose like
automate a big deal out of this log pose
and like establishing this was he even goes
on like a little spiel about in the narrative
like this is how you will find your way further
you know towards the end of the grand line
in one piece but but though
that log pose has not been
used for the last like five
arcs and they've been traveling through
totally other means and basically
it basically seems like the log pose
yes it could come back to relevance later
it basically seems like it's been totally
abandoned because after that plot point
Oda introduced a totally different
like end point that doesn't involve
the log pose basically at all with these
road poneglas and now those
are the true way to get to like
Raftel or Laugh's tail and to like
actually beat like he he
pretty clearly he introduces this element
at the beginning of like after the time skip as
this is the new thing we're doing but then
he totally has scrapped it later which to
me just clearly reveals he did not
actually have this plan all the way thought
through and he just changed tax I don't
see how any of this is
necessarily a bad thing like you're
saying that like the fact that he didn't
plan certain things make sure like
does it make you dislike one piece
I mean I guess you could argue that this is the problem
time wasted in the narrative
emotional emotional investment
you see the thing is the thing is
I like this for the log pose
the thing I like one of the things I love
about one piece is that
you know there's so many curveballs
despite the fact that it's been going on so long
and so many arcs are like
on surface level seems similar
but a lot of things happen in them that are just
so like unexpected even though
you know I mean you know
what this reminds me of is the equivalent
there's an equivalent to this there was a time
when before the time skip the
strats meet this guy Papagu he's a starfish
he says I'm best friends
with the mermaid princess after the
time skip like because because
Oda did not plan this after the time
skip when they meet Papagu
they're like hey didn't you say you were friends
with the mermaid princess and the character says
because now like the way that
Oda writes the story it wouldn't make sense for him
to have met the mermaid princess Papagu
says oops I was lying
before that is clear indication
of Oda thinking
on his feet having to change
like what did this character canonically lie for
no other reason other than
to appear a little bit shady later
no that's because that's not the guy's character
in the context of his first
appearance surely like he was
always a bit of a showboating like
like
I'm not defending it
but I'm like I'm criticizing
your criticism you're saying it's absolutely
like certified proof
that Oda no I'm not saying that I'm saying
it's very strong
saying that there's room for it to not like
Papagu is like
he was kind of like that I mean it's kind of stupid
but I don't think that in any way
like lessens my
appreciation of the thing it's just sort of
look it just means it's a flaw
it doesn't ruin one piece it's just
clearly it's not a hundred percent confirmed
but it's very likely just proof
I mean to get the
reason for the log pose thing
the point of this all is that when you introduce
a plot element that you expect to be capitalized
on and the narrative sets you up like
the log pose served great purpose through
the beginning of one piece and absolutely
fulfilled its function and I have no criticisms
but when he goes all out of his way
to introduce that it's going to be used in this way
and then totally changes tech
that's where it's like oh like I thought
we were getting like maybe the new thing is
even better but it's not crazy
to be like oh you kind of dropped this
other thing I guess that's too bad maybe
it's for the best but like I just wish you
hadn't bothered doing that before
since you know it wasn't going to do
anything what this reminds me of in
another manga that I know all three of us have read
is Bakuman
so like
in Bakuman which is like it's
my favorite manga you know like so much
good shit happens it's so
interesting as a look into the industry
especially into the magazine of Shonen
Jump and like the mentality
which with these stories
of being written which you can also apply to
the manga itself which is really interesting
in a meta sense because like
in Bakuman they're writing
a story that is clearly
based on death note which they had
before real the same guys had written
and like in the
in Bakuman they're saying
that they want to end the series
when the rivalry ends
like when one of the characters dies
and like there's nothing more to the rivalry
that's where the manga should end
but they're already making
an anime adaptation
so the animators are like
can you keep the manga running
and in Bakuman
they do not they cancel the manga
so that it can have a real ending
and
and it ends up working out
but that's not what happened with death note
death note had
continued on and everybody hates the later section
so obviously they're trying to make
like they're trying to explain
why that happened
and kind of make good on it in the next manga
like you know we get to live the fantasy
leave out the fantasy of what if we could have ended
the story when we wanted to end it
but the funny thing about it is that
Bakuman also teaches us
basically L did nothing wrong
sorry I mean light did nothing wrong
that Shonen Jump manga are designed to go on
for as long as possible
like they might have an ending
in mind and certain ones
are designed to be shorter
but like one piece was designed
for instance with the capacity
to go for as long as Oda
had continued to have ideas
and inevitably
if he keeps adding in new things
like I'm sure he does have the ending planned
and like the basic structure of the story planned
but like you know he wants to add
in new stuff and sometimes he adds in something
and then going along just like
oh this isn't as good of an idea
and or like oh I had a better idea later
of what this could have been
let's just fucking let's just go
with that instead you know
you're totally right Digi and like
such things are 100% inevitable
I simply will not ignore
no and the funny thing about it is that
Akumon shows you how that's the case
but it also has that flaw itself
because they introduce this character
relatively like
later into the series because like
most of the stuff that the main characters
have had to deal with is like their personal growth
in the early part of the manga
then once they've like started to become successful
they deal with the problem of having a shitty editor
and that's like a whole arc
it's like volumes of them dealing with this editor
and then they reach the stage
where they have to be competitive with other people
who are other manga authors in the magazine
everybody starting new series
they all have to keep their stuff interesting
they struggle with you know different kinds of things
and then there's the part
where they discover the serious comedy
which is like their personal style that they're going to use
to get popular which you can see in Death Note
you know so it all ties in
it's a good metatapestry
but then like 14 volumes in
they introduce a character
who's like a weird
mastermind character
he's like this evil guy
who's like hiring
old manga authors to
is this the guy who writes by committee?
the guy who like
yeah he
it was the guy who was like trying to overthrow
he was like trying to make it to number one by coming up
with really crazy concepts and giving them to like
old retired manga authors
this is the guy who made up Panty Flash Fight
right? yes
he creates Panty Flash Fight
and like because of
Panty Flash Fight being so great
and his introduction like
his first arc is okay but it's kind of weird
because he's a very different like he's not a realistic
character you know
like up to this point this is felt like a real story
about what happens when you create manga for jump
now we've got like a super villain
and then they kind of
beat him and the story
continues along but then really
weirdly like three or four volumes
before the end of the manga because it's 20
volumes long they reintroduce
him and they start setting up for a
second even more complicated
arc where he has a really weird
scheme that didn't really make sense
the second arc
he has like a team he hires like a whole team
they write by committee
basically but it was kind
of unclear like what his goals were
and like ultimately
this arc just kind of
it starts it's like setting up
but then it's taking too long
and it's clear at this point that like we're close enough
to the end of bakuman's story
that we do not need another arc
like this manga could end
it could wrap up soon and it would be satisfying
um you know we're already well
into the characters careers
all that's really left is to finish off the like
central romance and all that stuff
like and get them the number one manga you know
wrap up reverse side but like we've introduced
this new villain arc and then it
just kind of wraps
and it's obviously because
people saw this and went
this isn't really that interesting you know
and the authors kind of went uh yeah
fuck it and like it ends really abruptly
this arc like it's
it still seems like it's in the setup phase
and then all of a sudden they like wrap everything up
and boot him from the story and then there's just like
a volume and a half left before the story
ends and I really think it was like
you know they thought they could just keep it going
but then they started this arc and it was kind of
retarded so they just said uh
fuck it let's move on I remember that character
pretty well because he embodied
like a um it was basically
like this when he comes back from
he's got this team that he hired to sort of like
all like get together and make a think tank
about what would be the perfect manga
and like they kind of do it and it's kind of
working but then that one older guy
comes in and he like and he just
like tells this like story he's had in his head
for years and it's like his passion project
and it beats them in the polls or something
so I mean I'm sure they could have done more
with that arc but like I mean that arc
that character that arc is there
for a reason and like it does explore
a theme I just remember like yeah
I just remember it feeling weird
that he came back that like they
had thoroughly bested this guy
and then like in the like such a late stage
of the game when like we really are
you know we're more focused on the main characters
and like them wrapping up their arcs
and then all of a sudden this shit comes out of nowhere
and there's a ton of exposition like
tons of explaining what this plan is
and uh it was just
kind of like this is like a diversion
you know this is this is
not as interesting as the main story
and then it just kind of wraps up and then the story ends
it's true that it's true that
it's like a slight black mark on the series
it's true those guys aren't as interesting
that villain is not as interesting as like
the main characters like personal
struggle and whatever I think I think that's like
okay I guess it's like
the manga's attempt to sort of comment
on like a trend in manga that maybe
the the the authors
don't really approve of like the like
outsourcing your writing
or writing by committee
I think I think they're good ideas
my like as time has gone
I've become a little more annoyed
by how much of how much
Apologia Bakumon engages in
for like the like
you know just like the worst
tendencies of the manga and like
Japanese cultural markets in general
like the way that it's it's sort of
criticizes the whole idle
thing and like oh isn't it
wacky that they're not allowed to have boyfriends
so people can imagine that they could
date them one day it's it doesn't
go hard enough into like weird shit like that
I don't know it's a little too
it's a little too willing to forgive the manga
Anderson be like oh that's just the way
it really also comment on
like it doesn't really criticize the like
absurd crunch that is the
job you know like it's
as it is
but it's just well it's just like
the people who work for jump it's like I mean you gotta
be this kind of person like yeah I mean
just consider like the people writing the story
are people who chose this lifestyle it seems
reasonable they would you know be pretty
into it unless they like hate it but
they're choosing to do it so I assume
they find some value and definitely seen a bunch
of criticisms of bakumon online from people
who like work in the manga industry
and just felt that like it didn't present
it realistically enough like
in terms of the the troubles
of it and like even though
the manga does go out of its
way to have the characters encounter
like lots of common problems that happen
to people like through this just
the necessity of the fact that they are
it's a story about them becoming the number
one you know so like
ultimately things are gonna go
yeah under like better than they normally
would because most manga
authors don't make it to know I have
these characters are major critically
create like they are the perfect mangaka
I love bakumon
I've long had a criticism is that the one
greatest of the main character disgusts me
it utterly repulsed me
his obsession with the one girl
like who even cares I'm not even interested
in the
it serves as a good motivation beyond that
I never cared about the girl at all
it would have been better if they just made her more of a character
like she's just kind of a trophy
yeah absolutely I wanted
she had like an arc that'd be great
her arc is non-existent
I mean I guess it's her becoming a voice actor
she's pretty much just a macguffin for like
95% of it
she does become a successful voice actress
but like we barely focus on that at all
she has a story just not like
a character arc
maybe that story is covered in girl jump
I mean I don't read girl jump
I would show it in jump because I'm a boy
yeah her character doesn't really do that much
but like I guess they used her
as sort of a vehicle
you know they comment on the whole idol thing
which is like yeah okay that's I guess you wanted to
talk about that
it reminds me that I need to watch
what's that anime you love so much didgy
with the guys becoming animators
and becoming a share of friends
share of friends
even I've seen share of friends
I've been fucking around Ben
I know
I'm a little mad still about like the
the one piece
the thing with the Papaku
I went a little hard there
I have like a thing because it's like
the ending of death note whether it continued
the point where it should have ended
that's like a flaw that I feel is a notable flaw
and I could understand people getting upset
about it and I could also understand people
ignoring it but you know
it's more understandable that people would be upset
something like
the whole like Papagu lied thing
it's so insignificant
Papagu lied people died
it's like why would anyone devote
memory to something like I've read the
thing I remember him saying that when you
say it but like it doesn't
mean so much to like devote
any memory to it
it's Nate's autism is the problem
it's like you can't
some of us cannot erase
this thing from our minds it's like
just the knowledge that
knowing Nate and
knowing Ben because you guys are both really into
stories being as robust as possible that
like every question has an answer
everything like makes
sense in context and it's like
it's not that you expect one piece
to be perfect it's not that
you would
you would most like it to have been
perfect but it's no big deal
because in the end there's just so much
in one piece that it's like it's not comparable
to anything else it's like
if that takes it down from like a
100 to a
1000 to a 999
the next show is at like a
yes
right like that's again
like let's say that you're
you're thinking of it as like a
and this takes it down to a
943 you know again the next show
is at like
it's like you make a pie you make a pie
and maybe you burn a little bit
of the crime maybe like maybe that's got a lump
in it or something but like you know it doesn't
make it doesn't make it a bad pie
it doesn't really even make it a worse pie it makes
it a rustic pie
you can see the author that's the author's finger
that's the author's finger you run into a little
you run into a little gristle in your steak
you just pull that shit out of your mouth
and put it on the side of the plate and you go
man I wish I didn't have to look at this on the side of my plate
but whatever you go remember that time
that Oda introduced that one guy
and he said this one thing and then like the next time
he was like oh I was just lying about that haha
what what a gas
it was just it was just such a small
moment I think it's just that I can't
imagine defaulting like
part of like I've only got so much
memory I've only got so many gigabytes
in my brain like I'd rather
fill it with like joy
than like anything like stupid
well I mean sure surely
you realize your memory shaming me right now
surely you understand that this is unacceptable behavior
I know I mean if anything I'm memory
shaming me because I have less maybe
and then you have so much
you have like a big brain or something
and you got all the one key
flaws like take up like a thousand
terabytes
you know it's just it when I point out stuff like
this I get your perspective give and we've long
approached one piece at the very beginning
of our show we approach it even from more
kind of different perspectives you said that
I think you said something like you didn't understand
one piece had flaws or I'm not
trying to say no I think I said it like
I never like I just loved it so much
that like I criticizing
it was never even in my brain
how much
how many times have you read through one piece
all the way
I haven't read through it all the way
I've I've watched the anime
all the way to like episode like
500 couple times
good lord even I haven't read
every single chapter going back I just go back
and regularly read excerpts from there
it seems like
it seems like you are like always going back
through shit so like
discussion I pulled from like
we went back yesterday arguing about
like exactly what Raftel was arguing about
Ponyglyphs I went and re-read like several
chapters to do research for this
ongoing live discussion that benefited
me 0% just because
I wanted to make sure I had the correct information
like that's the way I can say I did go back
set of kind of recently
to reread Dressrosa which is like
one of the longest and
controversialist arcs
because of the amount of stuff that gets
shoved into it and it sort of makes it
at the second half of it sort of ruins
it gets ruined by the amount of
like character climaxes
that are supposed to be going on and nothing
you know I wanted to make sure
that like
like hindsight we weren't like shitting on it too hard
or anything do you do you stand by
your general feelings before
is it oh yeah I mean it's all stuff
the first half of Dressrosa
is really good though which is why
I think I understand why people still
like is they think of the first half of it
and then there's plenty
it's just sort of like there's three
characters that have a back
story that have a
climax with the
you know the final fight with everyone
yeah and if you
had only one of those it would be a perfect
really good arc but because
there's two or three then it's just like too much
you know here's one
of the problems is that we're selling with Skypia
like everything perfectly in a
writing sense swirled into the ringing
of the bell like every character had attachment
to the ringing of the bell
and the defeat of Enru with Dressrosa
for example it's like totally separate
plots that vaguely tie into
Doflamingo but like they're kind of just
independent like Rebecca and Kyros
their mom getting killed by
Diamante like sure that
technically ties into Doflamingo but really
that was a Diamante thing and so they fight
him and get revenge on him wasn't
really like Doflamingo personally
like if it was like
like you know
if Doflamingo ruined this kingdom
the story then it would be great
if it was Doflamingo ruined Law's backstory
without Dressrosa
then it would be great but because it's both
they neither character has
a satisfying end at the end of that
anyway
let me just say my one final point
on the one piece subject is just that like
a lot of people you know I love one piece
but you know people here we talk about it critically a lot
because those are the main things that I focus on
because I don't know maybe that's just how my brain is wired
and interesting but
it's just true that none of this
moves the needle particularly far
and when I bring up these little examples
like Papagu that being a mistake
like these are just examples that
I mean I have a pretty good memory of one piece stuff
generally speaking I don't remember everything
it's just that I remember them but I don't
it doesn't keep me like people
disproportionately think they bother me or disproportionately
make me think that one piece is way
worse than I actually think it is
I think that you hate one piece
because of Papagu but it's like
I guess
I question the motivation to
devote memory to this
like I don't think I have a choice
if it builds up to such a level
will you hate one piece more
like if it's death by a thousand cuts
if the flaws of one piece
if the flaws of one piece piled up then absolutely
yeah absolutely nothing is sacred
small flaws like Papagu like happening
like a lot
would be not that bad
but like a big flaw would be
like if it ended badly
then it would be bad but if there was
a bunch of Papagu's
there's fears that one piece will end badly
and the things like the Papagu mistake
what they really do is they reveal like
oh that Papagu thing really reveals
he did not 100% plan that arc
that doesn't really matter to me
I would still argue that it does not
necessarily reveal that
I mean okay
I think it does
I imagine the reason is because
him knowing the princess
got you hyped for meeting the princess
thanks to Papagu or something
I just didn't think- I didn't even really care about that
well that's the thing if it didn't matter when it was set up
then when it gets like
the setup that you didn't care about
didn't have a payoff
or had a payoff that you didn't care about
then what is the problem
because what is the issue there
is that it reveals Oda did not
have a plan and it caused him to make a mistake
in his narrative
I can't
whatever
you can just say the good outweighs the bad
so it doesn't matter to you
I'm arguing that the bad that you're explaining is not bad
it's not even a thing
well then I guess we just disagree
I've made my case
die
let me just go way back to the beginning of this
because I've got one final point we can move on
talking about anything else
way back when we were talking about Zelda
I just went like because I tweeted
like hey guys tell me if Zelda is good or bad
it was interesting to me for what most people said
when I said guys is this game good
most people said that like
Nate you will like it
without giving a lot of detail
the people who gave more detail would say like
it still plays fun if you like the old Zelda you like that
but there was a very large contingent of people
who were just saying like it looks great
play it like it's fun
these are very general non-specific terms
and I don't blame anybody
for not giving me the exact details
that I would find most interesting
I'm just asking random people on Twitter
there's nothing wrong with that
but it was Digi's video
that gave me the kind of detail I wanted
I mean Digi hadn't played a ton
but just that one observation
that like in the original
everything's broken into square units
and like as a result of that
the village feels bigger
that's how it was intended to be played
and by radically changing how the game plays
it totally changes how the game feels
and these illusions we create
for ourselves
Digi's point I thought this was a brilliant point
like it's way easier in the original
to feel that this is an abstraction
of a village that like in quote-unquote
real life would be you know
bigger have more to do etc etc
but by making it like a playhouse
that's the design sense they're going for
like now it feels real
but like oh this really is like an insubstantial
village it really is that this isn't
like a real village and that I
I'm not as into that
there's one thing that I had not
observed when I made the video
because I haven't actually played the game
and it's an argument
that I think can work to make the game
interesting it's still very different from the original
it still changes it fundamentally
but the thing about Link's Awakening
and I guess this is a spoiler
but I don't care
the whole game is a dream
because Link
it's the same Link from a Link to the Past
he is knocked out
during a storm
and in both versions of the game
the opening cutscene is an anime cinematic
it's like
in the original game you see him
as like a full-bodied
you know Link
he looks like the Link from a Link to the Past
if he was drawn as an anime character
but like you know
when you see the Game Boy graphics
it's a very abstract representation of that character
when you see it in
Link's Awakening they still have the cutscene
where he is drawn as like a fully formed
man
so like it's only in the dream world
that he looks like a play set
and you know there's the tinges
on the edge of the screen where everything has that
like blur effect
so you could argue that even though it is
literally meant to look like a play set
it is a dream world
and like
in the real world Link is
the Link from a Link to the Past
he is still drawn as an adult man
this is just what the world looks like
inside his dream
and so that's kind of good
but it still changes everything
yeah it's kind of good but it's like that wasn't the intention
of the world in the Game Boy
original
no it was not portrayed that way
it was more meant to just feel like a fever dream version
of a Link to the Past
it's meant to be a direct sequel
I mean in the original
I think it's more of a twist to realize
that it's all a dream
and you could argue that that's more valuable
I think like generally you should
err on the side of the original
especially if it's a short game
you play that first
and then the new game will just be like
oh quality of life improvements
oh it looks nicer
and then the original experiences is maintained
because I'm in the position of
I beat Link's Awakening
years ago
I'm in the perfect moment
where
I would rather play the new version
with the new art style and the new controls
just to
if I'm going to play it again why not play this one
but like if I was right now
today in a situation where
I had never played either one
I would 100% recommend DX
over the new game because the new game is $60
and DX you can play for free
and like it's great
fucking game you will not be let down
like we live streamed it
for my last live stream in May
was having the time of her fucking life playing that game
which is like two hours of just like
not even paying attention to what
I was talking about in the chat
just being like completely enthralled
in this fucking Game Boy game because like
it takes you back man
those classic top-down Zeldas are great
I played them all I fucking love them back in the day
I love Zelda 1
I love Link to the past
it would probably be a fun game
if it wasn't such a fucking pain in the ass
but that one plays totally different
Oracle of Seasons and Ages were like
my favorite games growing up
they were so fucking sick
the Minish Cap is like one of my top
yeah that too
I fucking loved the shit out of
I never had a Gamecube so I never played Wind Waker
but I loved Phantom Hourglass
I thought Phantom Hourglass was the shit
oh yeah I had that as well
I did not play that because of the fact that
with the touch screen and it was just like
let me tell you this lads
you have a journal in that game and one of the things you have to do
is in a certain dungeon
it uses the two dual screen
the DS was the best console ever made
fuck every other console and one of the things you have to do
is you have to stamp your thing
you have to physically fucking close
and open the fucking DS
to stamp your journal
I went Gadzooks for that shit
you have to blow in the microphone
to blow away sand
you can't get that kind of quality
with a fucking switch
with a piece of shit PC
what about the Wii U
you can probably do it on the Wii U
that's a decent comment
you have to snap
I'm gonna snap my switch in half
as I'm emulating the fucking Phantom Hourglass
on that fucking game
you just have to buy a switch to light and tape them together
that's their long game
console gimmicks are great
I know I've basically given up
and become a switch man
but it still makes me sad to think about the fact that I think the Wii U is better
as an idea
having the
two screens
two screens was a great idea
on the DS and the 3DS
and translating it to a console was a great idea
I still really want to play zombie U
it made Zelda the best it could possibly be
is zombie U good?
I have no idea
it's such a fucking good cool idea
of the Wii U
the way zombie U works
is that the game
it's like a first person zombie apocalypse kind of game
and you walk around
you kill zombies and shit
but the controller is your backpack
and that's how you do all your item management stuff
and there's no pause
so every time you do your items
you have to look down and not look at the zombies that are around you
and fiddle with shit
and you can get fucking impacted anytime
bro fatal fucking frame
in fatal frame 3
gamepad as the camera
so you hold it up to the screen
and like take pictures of shit
that's fascinating
they should have made pokemon snap with it
oh my god what were they thinking
I've been screaming about that
ever since the fucking Wii U came out
how was there no fucking
pokemon snap it was bullshit
that's a big oof for me lads
that's a big gomen aside from Nintendo
if there ever was one
I don't know if we'll ever get another pokemon snap
the switch could still do it
turn the switch around
do they have a camera?
I don't know
you just hold it up and spin around
oh yeah
kinda works
I have a video that will probably come up before this podcast
it's about how they need to bring back pokemon puzzle challenge as well
fuck yeah
shit
alright well that's enough about all this shit
I forgot to mention
something that happened to me this week
was me getting trolled
oh no
is that that video
oh yeah I saw that shit
it's on twitch
I clipped it
the video is called
ben saint gets epically trolled by ween CWC
defenders
and it was just a bizarre interaction I had
I was on twitch doing my stream
doing a draw stream for the nightstar comic
and these kids
start messaging me on discord
and they assume they're kids
and they're saying like
hey I got some interesting stuff to tell you
and I say in the stream
like what are these guys doing
these creepy messages
and they give me a call and I decide to talk to them on stream
and it turns out
these are like three guys
and this one autistic girl
who later turns out is being blackmailed
to go along with them
she joins the rfck and she says
these guys aren't my friends
they're really blackmailing me
threatening to dox me and stuff
and these guys they get in
they get in my call and I'm like
hey guys what's up and they tell me
you better stop talking to Chris
she's our fucking mark
they keep pretending
they're her real friends
and I'm muscling in on it
but they're talking like they're mafiosos
they have this weird affective importance
they threaten me
they say we'll be keeping an eye on you
now that you're interacting with Chris
they say don't touch the poop
don't touch the poop
they say chris is their friend
but they're like don't touch the poop
because like
they keep misgendering chris
and I'm like hey you guys should use
the pronoun she asked for
and they're like no me and him have an understanding
these are like some
nonsense
they're obviously not chris's friends
they're obviously some shitty trolls
they fucking and then after the call
they keep messaging me they're like threatening me
to dox me
they went into rfck
and like literally doxed me
but like nobody cared and
that's like the weirdest place to dox me in
who would do anything
so they do that
and I don't know
it was fucking bizarre
I don't know what's going on with these dudes
you're tapping into some primal forces
some realms
I don't understand I suppose
I mean this is a big league
lol cow chris
yeah I guess so
it was so strange listening to them
cause there was parts where
they were implying like
don't hurt our friend
but also like if you do
you may as well make it entertaining for us
they were not on
one person was like hey don't be mean to chris
the other was straight up like make it entertaining
you need to make this entertaining for us
they were not
you better
like deliver
with that comic cause there's a lot of more people
watching it now
things like that it was just really funny
it was funny
yeah we'll be in touch
we'll all be watching you
I believe this is anonymous and they do not forgive
and they do not forgive
they claim to be from kiwi farms
I saw a couple people talking about
the incident on kiwi farms
the overwhelming response was
yeah these guys are embarrassing
it was just bemusement
it doesn't strike me there's a lot of solidarity
among the kiwi farms
like any one of these
troll people who extends above
who raises their head above the crowd
just knowing the kiwi farms a little bit
I expect them to be struck down
what makes you so special sir
if you actually cared about kiwi farms
for whatever reason
yeah I know but if you were a troll
and you're like I'm on behalf of kiwi farms
I will strike a blow against the enemy
you wouldn't show up and be like
hey so I'm here on behalf of kiwi farms
to say fuck you
yeah
did you have a kiwi farms thread about you
no
probably will soon at this point
I'm lately because of the nightstar comic
I've been brought up a bit
in the Chris Chan thread
and there is like an old super thread
there are tons who talk about Chris online
which I am like my video is mentioned in
but I don't have like a
a thread about me
I think like a lot of the PCP
shit talk it's just rolled into my thread
I think so
probably because I have a big ass thread
think of the PCP as Digi Bro's podcast
about anime exclusively
if you're on the outside looking in
that's probably how it looks
I don't think anybody is under the illusion
that this is a podcast about anime at this point
maybe people who have like never
or just heard about it for the first time
and are like oh a podcast
that Digi Bro's on
the less information you know
the more likely you are to think it's Digi Bro's podcast about anime
I mean the thing is I don't really promote
the PCP anymore so like whatever
growth it has is from people
if new people are coming
from me they would have to really
like get into like the discord
and like find out
about you guys before they were gonna know
the podcast and like I do have people in there
who are like oh yeah I've listened to PCP
but I've never even like watched any of
certain people's videos
usually there's one or two people they have though
it'll be like oh I'm a huge fan
of you and give and take and I don't watch
nobody else in that motherfucking thing
and I'm tired of hearing Ben's fucking ass
and talking about politics
and then
classic line
and like I think that there's
I think like there's two general camps
like I do think that
still to this day a bulk of PCP
fans
were at the very least have been
my fans at some point
like you know like
whether they necessarily came from me or not
like I think there's not
a ton of people who are like huge PCP fans
who don't like Digi Bro shit at all
I mean there is a contingent of people who have been around
since the pony days
but I also think that like
there's certain like there's a lot
of people who are much more into
endless war than they are into
you know my shit or anybody else
the endless war subgroup
is like a weird it's
they squeeze took the PCP
fan base squeezed it and a little
like tumor protrusion like squeezed
out to the side and that's
the endless war people
it's a double edged sword in a way because
the double edged of the the endless war
people are probably like the most engaged
with the PCP because of the fact that
several of us are in it
and they come to the meetups and stuff like that
and like often times again a lot
of them are also fans of all of our content
anyways because they found endless war through
the PCP so it's like
they're endless war fans and PCP fans
cool those people are very supportive
and they give us a lot of money and stuff like that
but like I mean it also
does make the podcast harder to penetrate
for if we did want new people
so it's like it's
like the favorite thing of people who are
deep lore but if you were to
go listen like I've often said
if you were to just like put on a random
PCP episode from recent times
it really depends on what the topics happen
to be like this episode probably fairly
accessible but like if you
didn't know who any of us are you've never heard of
endless war you literally have no idea what we're talking
about right now you know that's right and
like there's definitely episodes that start off
with like the one where you guys talked
about the meetup in
London I think yeah
there was one about that
it would have been totally incomprehensible
to anybody who didn't have like at least a modicum
of knowledge how hardcore you have to be
make like a playlist of like
the basic bitch ones
like a scoville rating
I've got good news
for everyone because what could be more
accessible than a simple five dollar pledge
to join the PCP
Minecraft heads and our new
faction that will absolutely dethrone the
RFCK fuck boys
if that happens because I'm also
definitely not going to play Minecraft
so like
that would just be another sphere where I would
just be like oh Nate and Maj are talking
about Minecraft shit now
Munchie and Ben are talking about ready fuckers cop
killers Nate and Maj are talking about
Minecraft
Tom Gibber talking about their comics
you guys are talking about potty cast
and I'm just talking about my
latest research into the world of autism
and that's all I've got
seems pretty good
it's kind of a cool mix I kind of like it
it's like you guys want to hear my latest research
into the world of autism yeah man
lay it on I've come up okay
I've come up with an autism rating scale
right
there are seven
seven different levels of autism
present on the internet
and I can categorize them by the kind
of stuff that they like
I'm planning to make a video where I'm going to do
just anime like like an anime
autism chart like how autistic is
this anime
and like grade everything
so there's basically
how autistic you are comes down to how obsessed
you are with things on like
a systemic level
like how
how much like detail and complication
you either
require there to be for you to enjoy something
or that you yourself read into
the things you enjoy
and there's different sliding scales
like different shows of different intelligence
levels which contributes to people's
ability to enjoy them and generally
you can enjoy
like if you're a level one autistic you can
probably enjoy things going down to level
three autism but any more
autistic than that and it becomes harder for you to
enjoy I see
but there are some people who are like autistic
authors who can project like they can
make stories that are less autistic than
themselves so for instance
Quentin Tarantino probably a level
three or four autistic but he makes
level two autism works
so Quentin Tarantino movies level
two autism generally
even the general public can appreciate
something as low as level two autism
that's like not so autistic
as to be for voting
to the average general population
is everything on the autistic spectrum
or is there non-autistic
work
there is non-autistic work all
anime is at least level one autism
there is no way to watch anime
with no autism
to get a sense of scale is somebody like
Ulillia like a seven
he is a six
on this scale
the new story teller
is a seven
so the way the scale goes
is basically like this level one autism
is basically where
the reason that you're
into anime
Dragon Ball Z is a level one autism show
because the autistic elements
of it are like the power levels
and the fact that it's like a super long
form narrative with a large cast
so like there's things to keep
track of but
if you are like really into keeping track
of things you'll quickly realize that
there's tons of plot holes and ass
poles and retcons and just
the story doesn't seem to care enough about itself
so if you're like autistic enough to
really care about that shit or intelligent
enough because those are also like
elements of the intelligence and construction
I'm planning to make a chart for like
basically each show will have an autism
level and intelligence level
um
whether it appeals to masculine or feminine
where do these charts
where do these charts appear on the scale
the good question the charts themselves they gotta
be pretty high on it
the charts themselves are like level three
to borderline on level four autism
which is where I sit
I'm like a little bit more than level three
but like going down
to level four which is the Evangelion tier
is level three autism
and so basically depending on what tier you're on
it is most likely that
the things that are on that tier
will be your absolute favorite things
like even if you find flaws
in them because they are like perfectly
on your autism wavelength
it's like this is my favorite thing
you know so for instance
something that I would put in between level one
and level two autism is
one piece
one piece gets more into level two
because of the sheer amount of shit that there is
to keep track of if you're keeping track of all of it
you don't have to keep track of all of it to enjoy
the show so it can appeal to more normie
taste as well but
people like Nate who I would consider to be
a level two autism
are into it for the level two autism
reasons I as a level three autism
am into stuff like Eva
that has more of a meta
more into the meta outside of the work itself
like the involvement
of it's place in history
the people who created it
comment on itself as a work
you know stuff like
Homestuck level three autism
and like even if you are
level two you could
a level three autism thing might be your favorite thing
if it's just so good
and like you're like yeah I might not be
quite autistic enough to love everything about this
but it's so fucking good
I have a question then
cause like I'm super
into Homestuck in every aspect
like I'm a big Homestuck autism
but like I can also
look over the things that Nate can't
look over in one piece which is less
how's that work
I think that
the different people have different
priorities in what they think makes
the story good or bad I think that
like the level two autism
I consider to be okay so here's
there's interesting things that happen as we go down
the autistic spectrum because
on the one hand the lower you go
the more like broad and ridiculous
the systems of the story
become but also
you care less and less about it being
good like in air quotes
like people at like
level one and two
probably care the most about everything
like being functional
like they want
to be believable in the end
like you know like JoJo's
Bizarre Adventure is a perfect example of a show
that like people enjoy because
it seems logical
even if everything happening is bad
no it's not at all and it's totally
riddled with mistakes
so I would put that at like level
1.5 autism
like it's got tons of shit for you
to sink your teeth into if you like the deeper stuff
but it doesn't do quite
a good enough job to satisfy
a level two autism who wants everything to be
like dotted every i, cross every t
but when you get to level 3
it's where you kind of enjoy the chaos
more than the order
it's like you don't even care as much
about it answering all of its questions
if it has just as much to say as possible
like Evan Gellion
certainly doesn't answer every single
question it raises
but like it just has so much
shit in it you know there's so much to take in
and there's so much meta
layering to it there's so much to like
enjoy after the fact that it adds to it
for you know the level 3
autism but when you get to level 4
that's when you get to like mega franchises
and where there's like just huge
databases like Gundam perhaps
like fate
like the fate franchise
like where you have to consume all this
any like deep lore of a major
franchise like Star Wars lore
Star Trek lore like if you're reading
the tie-in novels and shit that is level
4 autism
if you're playing like more
mainstream visual novels
that's around here
but then you get to level 5 autism
and this is where you get to like the more
obscure visual novels the people
who are just consuming like
everything because they categorically need
to have seen everything
sounds like you with anime
well there's I also
want to clarify that there's a difference
if you do things as a stunt or in order
to talk about it because like
I will watch shows that I
not necessarily going to enjoy because it has
a like career benefit to me
so like there's some kind of
there's some kind of pride tangled up
in that but like there are
shows that are
just like too dense for me to fucking
wrap my head around have you ever heard of horizon on the middle of nowhere
don't think so
horizon on the middle of nowhere is the most
like over the top with like
having just dozens and dozens of
characters who all belong to different factions
who all have different races and powers
and like different fucking magic
systems and like it's so
fucking dense and complex that there's like
it's a light novel that's like
600 pages in the first
book it has a huge index
just to keep track of what the fuck is going on
I tried to watch the anime couldn't comprehend it
so that's what I consider level 5 autism
level 6 autism something
happens we cross the
warning
we're losing functionality
so
when we get to level 6
then
there's two different directions that level 6
autism will take things either
they're very strident
about staying within the canon
and therefore they have
found an unimaginable depth
in every element of the canon
this is where we get the people who are upset about them
putting like taking sonic's gloves away
like because
they've put they've ascribed a ton of meaning to sonic's gloves
because they're obsessed with sonic and like
every part of the canon matters
sonic
by the way sonic meta is level 6 autism
tifa's tips are
3 centimeters too small in the remake
and I will not stand for this this is unacceptable
her bra should not be
exposed okay alright got it
but then there's the other route
that they might take which is
if they don't care about the existing canon
they're going to pump as much
of their own shit into the canon
as humanly possible
so this is where we get like the extreme fanfic writing
and like I would say fanfics in general
start at level 4 autism
like if you're even
writing a fanfic at all
that's pretty autistic
some people who are maybe
a little bit less autistic are doing it
just as a way to like test their writing skills
you know respectable but like
if you're taking it seriously as like something that has
like its own involved canon
level 4
if you're at level 6 it means
that you are somebody who is
maintaining like a wiki of my little pony
youtubers like
that's level 6 autism it's like
an obsession of level
a level of obsession with the meta of everything
that goes beyond it being good at all
like it doesn't have to be good you just have to be
obsessed with it
and you'll find depth and complexity
in it
like Chris Chan and
Ululila and
I wish I had a sound board right now so I could play
and this is what it means to go even further
beyond
and then level 7
is where we get to
like just functional
enough to use the internet and that's where I put
like the new storyteller where he like
clearly he's not participating
in social media he's not like
he might like read his own comments on youtube
but he posts like 7 videos a day
clearly lives in his parents basement
and he plays with Thomas the Tank Engine toys
like that is the that's as autistic
as you can get before you're not really
consuming media anymore you are not
functioning highly enough for that so like
it could be that autism continues past
level 7 I don't know how far it goes but
like any further than that and I can't
ascribe a show to it you know
sure okay so that's my 7
layers of autism and then the other scales
that you have to grade on it's like so each show
will have an autism rating and then
an intelligence level rating
and so like people who are intelligent
across the board might
enjoy things from different categories
and I'll also make side
notes about things like Astro Boy or like the
works of Osama Tezuka I think Tezuka
was himself a level 5
autistic but all of his work is like level
2 or 3 autism you know
although he has some obscure works that go
truly into the depths he has some stuff
that's more autistic than I think even he is
just because he was curious about it you know
because he wrote like a thousand
manga he wrote lots of shit
on the side
but yeah so that's the intelligence
category you might like
the reason that normies who are really
smart can enjoy Tarantino movies
is like they're not as attracted
to just the meta element like level
2 autists they just like the movies because
they're out of order and it gives you a lot of shit to keep track
of you know yeah like
normies who are smart are just like oh
intelligent writing good characterization
you know but like they're not as
interested in it as like fetishistically
as like a autist
is you know so then we've got
the masculine versus feminine
rating because this makes a difference as well like
just how masculine
or feminine you you conceive yourself to be
like what you enjoy out of works
you know if you
are more of a dude bro you're gonna like
more dude bro kind of shows and I did not expect
a Z axis to be added to this
oh there's another axis because there's gonna be
two different charts
one is the autism versus intelligence
so like there'll be
one chart of like the autism level and intelligence level
and then another chart of the
male versus female
as well as
masculine feminine
to be politically correct
I fall
you know like barely into the masculine
side I would say like lots of really feminine stuff
you know but there's also
the
the emotional
thinker versus
what was the word I wanted to use
pragmatic
that's a good word yeah pragmatic
thinker because there are
a lot of shows are beloved because
of the fact that they just have lots of information
in them and like I think
of Ben as maybe somebody
who likes a lot of the pragmatism
and shows a lot of like oh they set up this
really interesting rule system you know and
like and it says it
it's built out of like realistic
concepts and stuff like that like
um I think of something
like that no game no life scene
where he removes columns force from the universe
appeals to like the pragmatic
thinker who's like oh wow science
used in storytelling cool you know
whereas like emotional
good idea even though the execution doesn't make
any fucking right
yeah and uh and maybe you're too pragmatic
for it maybe it's like a little too emotional
or something but like
emotional thinkers are people who more
like don't really care about the logic of it
as much as you know whatever it makes them
feel so like that would be the other axis
I'm gonna I think I could apply
this to every anime I know of I think
I could make a reasonable deduction
of how autistic is it if anybody wants
if you have any questions any anime
you want me to put through the test I could
give you my quadrants
of what I think it falls into does anybody have
a suggestion
well I'm just on that last
I haven't seen double-decker
I'm comparing two series that are I think pretty smart
but like Technolize is probably
extremely emotionally based and then
versus like Ghost in the Shell extremely
like intellectual brain based
yeah you know I would say that
Technolize is definitely
more emotional but like
it does have a lot of interesting
it has a lot of like weird sci-fi
concepts that come out later in the show
so like you'd have to have some interest in
sci-fi to like get the most out of it and like
but yeah I would definitely
say it's more of like a feeling
kind of show it's more of
driven by that for sure
you know what's a good example of this
fucking Space Patrol Luluko
that's like pure emotion like no logic
Luluko I would put on like level 3
autism because it's so
so much of it is obsessed with the meta of itself
of its own existence you know that like
incorporates elements from all the other trigger shows
and it's like none of that shit even means anything
to you unless you've seen all these fucking shows
so you know it's
it's fairly autistic but
it's also like definitely way
more emotional thinker than logical thinker
because none of it really makes any sense or tries to answer
its own questions it's just pure over the top
you know teen
angst and emotions are what
controls the story you know
so like emotional thinking
probably right in the like
on the line between masculine and feminine I think
it tries to appeal to both
yeah I agree in equal measure
and intelligence level
I would say is like
just above average not like
high but you know like
yeah it plays around with some
concepts and it moves really fast
so it doesn't try to like hold your hand
and walk you through everything but like
yeah so that's my rating level 3
autism slightly above
average intelligence
right in the middle between masculine and feminine
and
what was the other paradigm I had
emotionally like yeah much more emotional
than rational
or what the fuck was that
pragmatic yes
psychopaths I would say is like
psychopaths isn't very
autistic at all actually it's
pretty straightforward you know
like well another
thing I put at like level like 1.5
to 2 is like shows that
play around with
like real world theming stuff like
Star Trek where like it has application
to real life because that's meta in a
sense like if that's what you care about
about it which I think people who like
psychopaths would appreciate that
you know like there's not a ton
to keep track of the complications in the story
but it does make a lot of like literary references
it does like
you know reference other movies
and you know sort of
expound on the
conversation through media about the future
so like in that sense I would say it's like level 2 autism
a series that has
tons of references should definitely
like that should inch up the autism
like significantly and like maybe the
intelligence a bit but like it's just a
reference that doesn't do anything that smart
can you give me an example of a level 0
autistic work
um ooh
a marvel movie
any marvel any like
disney marvel movie those are
crunchy lore and those have like lots
of references to an extended canon though
they okay maybe iron man one
I would say that those movies
they can appeal to both
like they're made to market to both
oh uh yeah
I was just reminded by May writing it down
sports is a
depending on your level of engagement
I mean if you're into
like a fucking saver metrics and stuff
if you get into like
fantasy football that's like
at least level 2 or 3 autism
yeah I feel like this this
chart is not like where would you put
the thing but like
for the people who are in these brackets
what could you recommend to them
level 0 autism is
the article in the mag the article
in the magazine that you see in the grocery
store saying that you know
brad and fucking angelina
are back together again
well if I present
this whole thing something I want to
clarify is like people
anywhere on the spectrum can enjoy stuff
that I would categorize as anywhere on the
spectrum depending on how they engage with
it so like for instance may was
telling like telling me about warrior
cats right and like the warrior cats
books are meant to just be
like children's books they're
kind of autistic you know like
they have a lot of factions and like
relationships and stuff to keep track of
a lot of characters but like generally
they're kids books you know
but there was a heavy online
community for warrior cats and like
a lot of them like it because they're
furries or just into like animal
project projecting themselves on the animal
characters or they're like
really intent on keeping track of all
the factions and like creating
you know diagrams creating their own
fan content and animations and fan
fictions making up their own OCs and like
the more of that you get into the more
autistic it becomes the more it's like
you're trying to take this
story and make it more complex
make it have more to offer
because you like the aesthetic
elements of it or maybe you just haven't
seen stuff that would appeal to your level
of autism like maybe there's something
that if you knew about it
you wouldn't have to you know
obsess over warrior cats but you're 13
and it's you know it's
put in front of you so that's just what
you apply your autism to. So there's a
distinction to be made obviously between any
individual consumer and the work itself
to be on totally different pages. Exactly
but I do think that there's
a like I think there's a limit to
how far out of somebody's autism
range they'll generally tend towards
and like what
made me think about this whole chart
like my placement of everything had to do
with the fact that I think
I'm in a position
where I'm like in the middle ground on almost
all of these statistics like by
being like level three autism
I can appreciate level one shit
I can appreciate level five shit
it has to get to level six
it has to get to the level of like appreciating
bad sonic games because you
can't tell the difference that's where it's like
too autistic for me you know
that's pretty far gone most
people aren't that autistic so like
I'm in a good acceptable range to talk about a lot
of different shit and appreciate it you know
and being like
the hardest thing for me to
appreciate is just really dumb shit you know
regardless of its autism level if it's not
intelligently constructed that's the hardest
thing for me to pass you know
but like anything else I'm like right in the middle
of pragmatic and emotional I'm right in the middle
of masculine feminine I can appreciate
stuff all over the spectrum
and you know I
from that vantage
point it's like I can look at absolutely everything
and I can say okay
I've seen all this type of show and like
only these types like the same guys who
like JoJo also like
all this other shit that's like the same amount
of autistic you know
except for guys who like it for
really autistic reasons you know
so
that's kind of how I base my ranking
anyway
this will all have possibly
already been explained in a video I have no idea
but now I just wanted you guys to be
in on it because I thought you'd all be interested
I think you'll all you would all be
like looking at stuff
and asking yourself like how autistic is this
I've been doing it constantly like
watching YouTube channels and be like
how autistic is this creator
because like some of them
like there's this guy I don't do not mean
for this to sound like a call out but
I've been watching shit loads
of like gaming reviews and documentaries
and like retrospectives
just tons of game shit
and I stumbled upon this guy called
Ant Dude and
he's like he's
fairly well spoken he does like
in-depth breakdowns of games
that are pretty
you know he addresses most of the stuff
in the game it's fairly in-depth
and enjoyable
his sense of humor is like
pretty much borrowed from like Egoraptor
and John Tron but not like
nearly as impactful as them
he's not like super funny
but like his super in-depth
reviews are of like Kirby and Yoshi
games
and I'm like that's kind of hella autistic
you know
almost everything on his channel is covering
some kind of mascot platformer
and it's like he's really positive
about these games for the most part
he can recognize their flaws
but he doesn't hold them against the games that much
he's like really positive about these games
and I look at it and I think like this is what happens
if you're like really intelligent
but like level 4 autism
you know not to like try to
diagnose this guy or anything I don't even know
if he's autistic I just find his taste
to be like what I would consider to be
in that realm you know
where it's like yeah I just want to look at like
cutesy fun stuff
and like I get enough depth out of analyzing it
that it doesn't have to
actually be that deep
you know
whereas something that's like absurdly deep is like
a dwarf fortress or something
that's like the appeal is that it's
super deep
and you don't have to read anything
into it because it's completely
all there
that would definitely be like
level 3 bordering level 4
autism level is like the games like that
yeah
oh my god do any of you watch the channel called
Seth to Zenrec
I know that guy I've seen some of his stuff
people like him a lot I've been getting into him
he's very demolition de-esque
but even more of like an edgy meme lord
but he plays like Ben
you gotta watch this channel just because
he plays every fucking
one of these like super robust games
like what's his name
Seth to Zenrec
Seth with two S's
if you just type Seth with two S's you'll probably get the channel
oh Seth scene
yeah something like that
yeah
he has like an African warlord as his avatar
like he always like shows that on screen
if it's like him talking
it's very weird aesthetically
but he plays like all the super robust games
and he goes into all the systems and like
why they are so deep
and what kind of crazy shit can you do
in these games
is it like video essays?
I think this is the guy who made
the Heroes of Might Magic 3
review that people kept comparing me to
because it came out at the same time
he's done all of the Heroes of Might Magic games
I think
but he's covered all kinds of stuff
like a lot of classic RPGs
and a lot of like sandbox games
and like usually the main focus of the video
is just showing you how crazy of things
can happen with the systems in this game
you know or like
how broken the game could be
like sometimes he'll play games that he's like
this game's not even good but because of the weirdness
of the mechanics and how broken it is
you can play it in like really entertaining ways
or mod it to be entertaining in ways
you know so
I'm just impressed by the level of depth he plays
the games to before he talks about them
which no other critic fucking does
nobody even touches stuff like Dwarf Fortress
so it's really cool that he's doing it
with fucking need
alright he's a good man
preemptively so
you know what I'm not subscribed to
no I think I am I don't know whatever
for some reason like there is like a wall
I'm like intimidated to get really into his videos
I mean I fucking binge them all the day
pretty much he doesn't have
like even though his channel
goes back farther than like the type
of videos he does now
like initially he was doing more like meme videos
it wasn't quite like serious reviews
over time he'd like somehow
became a reviewer but sometimes
the memers can grow
into the best serious people
because they get those memes in there too
and they just hit the sweet spot
I don't know what this guy does because I haven't watched him but
that's what it seems to be the case
do you want to move on to voicemails?
I think we should
before we go on to voicemails
I wanted to say one thing quickly
I solved a minor inconvenience
of mine that has been plaguing me for years
and I wanted to share it with everyone
on the off chance that you might have had
the exact same problem
and have been subconsciously looking for a solution
one of the veins of my existence
of just using computers
is having tabs
open of
sites I frequently use
and living in constant fear of my browser crashing
or my computer
updating or turning it off and losing all those tabs
that drives me
insane
so my
system before this is that you can pin
tabs and chrome and shit
so you can right click on a tab and pin it
and it'll stay nested in the corner
so you can have an army of all your frequently
used sites
so that's the old
system I had but the problem with that
is that that was originally something from
Max and the max version works great
every time you open the browser it automatically loads
all your tabs that you have pinned
and if you are in a pinned tab
and you go to another site it actually automatically opens
a new tab and keeps your pinned tab there
which is great no other
fucking browser works like that
so the features basically use this on anything that's not a
Mac but
earlier this week I discovered
a feature of chrome
that has solved this problem
completely and has no longer made me
worried about my browser tabs
or losing like or having access to sites that I use all the time
and it's if you're on a website
any website as far as I can tell
and you click the menu
you go to more tools and do create
shortcut it'll pop up and it's like
oh create a shortcut
then you can check off open as window
and when you hit create
it takes that tab and just makes it a web app
like it's in its own container
it's pulled out of the
out of the browser
and it's just you can pin it to your
taskbar and open it just like a regular application
and so you no longer have to
worry about your tabs anymore
they just work just like regular apps
like I have patreon
youtube and twitter all in my
taskbar along with like all my graphic design
apps and blender and game dev engines
and every time I want to use them you just click it
and it just opens up its own dedicated window
it doesn't open it up in your browser it just
runs its own self
contained version of itself
like a native application
and it's the best fucking shit
of all time
okay let me just let me play devil's advocate for a moment
here I see the one downside of this being
that like now that you're you've got this open
is dedicated like I've got the I just did this with
youtube just now but like
now I've lost the ability to like
on the top menu go to another website
while I have this open because it's dedicated to
like just youtube is this is this
correct am I missing anything
no that's it's it's it's it's designed
to run like a application
okay it just runs it in a container
that works like an application
sick the the the benefit
is that again like
you don't have to worry about your browser crashing
your computer updating all these things going away
because they're always in your taskbar like anything else
and it's changed my life
and I'm gonna try it
if you're level 3
computer autistic like I am this is a godsend
so
check check it out
let's try it out and let us know
in the comments if this is making a positive
difference in your life I'm curious how many people
want to use this
I have
I have something I want to say before we go
into voicemails I just want to do a quick update
on the Vapors to Kickstarter
which is that we have smashed all the
stretch goals
and at this moment of recording we're just shy
of eight thousand dollars
and the next stretch goal is ten thousand at which point
pins for
all everybody who is credible
if we hit ten thousand dollars everyone
who has already pledged at fifteen
or higher will just get a free pin
a new pin a third pin it's my heart
st logo black on silver gonna make those
just give them to everybody
fuck it how much time is left in the campaign
when you're listening to this there will be one
week left to donate
there's usually that bump at the very end as people
realize they gotta get it in so this seems
achievable this seems pretty doable I think
so I'm optimistic anyway
kickstarter.com slash project slash
bensane slash papers to link in the description
is the stretch goal that everybody gets
a free pin yes everybody
who has wanted to donate
so I can get a free pin everybody
was for a physical reward at least
if you donated fifteen dollars
say for just the book
and then the
well already you will receive one dollar
in your package because
we hit the stretch goal that everybody gets a dollar
because communism
and then if we hit ten thousand dollars then
you poor
who merely ordered a book before
will then receive the book
the dollar and the
pin just for having contributed
to the cause what is the pin gonna be
it's the my heart logo
Ben shouldn't you demand
I want the infinite chest pin
well you gotta pay you gotta get that one on
its own level that's like 45 bucks
for that one I think no for infinite chest pin
that's the first pin twenty five twenty
twenty five would get you the book and
the infinite chest pin
I paid the amount where I got both comics
just both comics
I got both comics
and the infinite chest pin
45 was the lowest I could do
to get the books and the pins
if you just got the book okay well let me
hold on let me look at the rewards
twenty five would get you
either both books or a book and a pin
if you wanted to get both books
and the pin you'd have to do thirty five
that's how it is
I didn't want to pay an extra ten dollars
because I don't put pins on anything
I just wanted because of the meme of infinite chest
I had a row of pins here
that bring me such joy every day
including my poobah pin and my rad come three
I still have my poobah pin
it's on my laptop bag
this Kickstarter is at least a level
two and a half autism based on
the amount of highly
specific reward tiers and combinations
of things one might
pay very specific amounts of money to achieve
I would generally categorize
both you and Nate into
level two autism
but I definitely think that
that's probably a bit higher than me I guess
I think you both like a lot of stuff
that's outside of your category
just based on how good it is
like I said
really good stuff can transcend
its categorization more easily amongst
intelligent people just because you're like wow
this thing might be really autistic
but it's really interesting
and you might even enjoy ironically some things
like Ulila's book obviously that's like
a level six autism book
but it's fun to read
it's fun
conceptually
I feel like my autism
must spike when I read
something like that because that is not a good
book it is not fun to read
and yet somehow
I can maintain
I can keep myself erect through the entire
process of reading it somehow I can
maintain enough interest that I could get
through it like multiple times
it's even though it's not even there
we move on to voicemail yes
yes indeed let's do that
okay I've got them pulled up right here
okay let me see here we go
okay so everybody of course leave us voicemails
we love them people speakpipe.com
there's a link in the description just go click on that
give us voicemails their quality
perhaps you'll be as as as
lucky enough has skilled enough to get into
the PCP voice grail
or perhaps you'll be degenerate lowly
to be locked away forever in the PCP
jail the voice jail
so it's a real gamble be careful
before you submit how many
how many voicemails we got
I think 10 I think an even 10
okay there's one
just preview thing before
we get to the real voicemails here's the
the proto voicemail what could this one be
about this is called crypto punk
alright let's hear what it has to say go
the dawn
of the PCP minecraft
server yes bring a new
age for those who choose
to mine at night
yay
this is the rise of the crypto
punk
patreon.com
slash PCP minecraft
people five dollars and get in
the server it's gonna be a blast
I'm hyped that crypto punk
is starting to get some roots
and becoming part of the PCP can
indeed I can't believe
I can't believe you actually made a separate
patreon I'm we did
and believe it really happened
okay alright
now on to the actual voicemails okay here
we go calling in is mickey
mouse in real life has
some things to say let's hear
let's hear them go
oh hey there
procrastinators it's a me
mickey mouse Mario
minis asleep so I can't be too loud
I'm here to discuss possibilities
for an exclusive PCP deal
with disney plus
we love your stuff but we gotta work on that
Ben sainte fella cause he
could be a little dangerous you know
we really can't have him saying
those things he says
and you know Nate I can't guarantee
anything but joining the disney
family could get you in on
well you know
something you're really
you know whoop that's all for now
I gotta go take Pluto for a walk in the
dead of night
getting touched once you've you know
done something about Ben sainte
um yeah I knew he'd have it
out for me
disney money and no more Ben sainte
this sounds like a win-win to me
yeah I gotta agree where's the downside I ask
where's the downside
well it's been fun
alright as Charlie mickey mouse
and his cohorts live as opposed to communist hell
in capitalist heaven and that's where I
aspire to be eventually
absolutely
they have a direct line to capitalist god
and they're definitely under the
under the
under the purview of you know emperor matthew
is from final fantasy 2 with his administrative
powers operating this whole thing
you know like clockwork
um okay let's go to the next one
uh this is uh
grailers and jailers
okay uh get to it
I gotta say I'm really
tired of this jail
grail shenanigans
I gotta say
it's cool people have been
submitting more quality
voicemails but this shit is
insane it doesn't matter
it's up to the PCP man
it doesn't
matter if you send in
six quality voicemails
in a row and they all get played and everyone
laughs it doesn't matter
you guys need to do something epic
you can't
pander and make all these
retarded ironic
memes like you got
put in the grail and then
you immediately dropped your spot
retarded
stupid
gay
okay I think we're all thinking we
I'm sure we're all thinking the same thing
voice grail I think voice jail
voice jail
well okay we'll obviously
we'll have to cut them in half and put half of them in one
and half in the other
we're opening voice limbo
for people who are just like
yeah it's just a big shrug room
where people shrug
does everybody get in voice limbo then is that
yes or just
voice limbo doesn't have a good rhyming scheme
to it like grail, mail
and jail we gotta come up with a better name
I mean I agreed with him he was just very boring to listen to
I'd call that a big voice fail
if you ask me
100% agree
he doesn't even deserve to be on paper
how dare you speak
against our system okay next up
you were speaking against
the system like the people calling
in try to
like joke their way into the voice
grail but they're not doing it right
that's true those are the real criminals
those are the real criminals and I won't have
any of it
next up we've got
from or says dictator Nate
presumably it's two dictator Nate that being me
okay let's let's hear it
go
calling out
Nate Massman
Ben Heads
it is time to rise up
Nate has suppressed
is he under the bed?
he has not played them
I tried to make them funny
I tried to have a good meme
make it so maybe they would laugh
is he just speaking through a toilet roll
it's suppressed
it's not helping your odds
it is time to rise
low quality low energy
that was low energy
see this guy is like
oh all my yang voicemails were so quality
were they equally as quality as this voicemail
and you wonder why they weren't playing
sounds like it's playing from the other
side of the wall
I think he's literally just like cupping his hands
cupping his hands over his mouth
sounds like it
as a sort of makeshift voice filter
listen I'm an equal opportunity
there are people who are like yeah fuck
Ben man I'm on Nate's side
and I don't play them either cause they're not funny
cause they're lame just make it good
and it'll get played I don't care what it is
except when Nate wants to talk about how the voicemail
suck and then he will play anything
like he just did
cause it's really funny
okay fair fair
okay got the next one right here
and this is from how
tf you pronounce
how the f you pronounce
presumably okay go
how the fuck you pronounce
gur and logan some of you say
gur and logan some of you say gur and logan
gur and logan
some of you say tetsuya nomura
nomura manga
manga devu davu
what is Nate's last name
Obama's last name
mojang moyang sahara
sahara even gay leon
code gay ass
what
what?
that was all about the delivery
tengen topa gur and logan
gur and logan
it's japanese what are you gonna do
our lips aren't advanced enough to speak
sheen seiki ebangerion
ebangerion
I don't know why but tengen topan
just makes me think of legos
tengen topan
tengen topan legos
tengen topan gur and logan
gur and logan
it is me
elu gay samurai
After my disgrace by the digital blow, I have been training for my comeback.
When I finally returned, I am very shocked to see you are playing very racist stereotype on your show.
The Chinese dog, Mao Zedong, is using very racist accent to sound like Japanese.
Chinese don't sound like Xato, it is very rude to me as a Japanese.
I have dedicated myself to finding the way to hell, so I can kill all the communists and restorers to Japan.
Nanking 2 coming soon to communist hell, it's only a matter of time.
Who is the Chinese character that has had a fake Japanese accent?
Chairman Mao has been calling in from communist hell to make nice with the PCP, which we appreciate.
Maybe Eroge Samurai just thinks Japanese sound like shit, maybe that's what he thinks.
I think it's contention.
He thinks Mao Zedong's stupid accent just reminds him it hits too close to home.
Perhaps the demon one is in his own eye all along and needs to do some self-reflection.
Think about Eroge Samurai, leave those good communist boys alone.
They just want justice.
Speaking of communists, we've got Carl Liebknecht at communist hell.
Do you know this guy? I don't know who he is exactly.
I assume he's a communist.
Is that like his email? Carlliebknechtatcommunisthell.edu?
Probably something like that.
Dot gov, of course.
I don't know, he'll tell us about it.
Carl, go.
Hello, this is Carl Liebknecht, the good boy of communist hell.
I'm really just here to spend some time with my comrades.
Anyways, I want to remark that you placing only certain denizens of communist hell in the voice grill
is the best pointless and adverse to counter-revolutionary act.
The ascension of our comrades is the ascension of all the peasants and the proletariat of the world
beyond your artificial stratification.
This, oh god, what was that?
Again, how is this happening here?
Oh man, another classic communist faux pas.
Another comrade falls.
That's alright Carl, just exclamation revive, you'll be fine.
I thought they had gun laws in hell.
They have so many gun laws, it's like, you know, Chicago, you know, politics, et cetera, et cetera.
It's like they say, the only solution to a bad guy with a gun is a good guy with a gun,
but there are no good guys with guns.
There are no good guys in communist hell, so it's just bad guys with guns.
By touching a gun, you become a bad guy.
Yeah, and that's how you wind up in communist hell.
Alright, let's move on.
We've got one from Zulfur.
Zulfur, okay, go.
Last week, upon hearing that the virgins are banned from making voicemails,
unless we fuck the PCP, I paused, reflected, and decided I want to sleep with a band.
The only question left is, who do I fuck?
Who do I marry?
And who do I kill?
I think about for a minute, Ben, Munchy, and Nate.
Fuck Nate, because he has 100k subscribers that could blackmail him later.
Did she has more?
Very Munchy, because I can introduce him to my parents without dying of embarrassment.
And kill Ben, because there's problematic egalitarian hate speech.
That's being disguised as far left talking points.
Oh, you can't force Ben.
My body, my body is ready.
This is hate crime.
We gotta cancel this guy right fucking now.
I appreciate him at least respecting our updated system, where no virgins allowed to leave voicemails.
So that's, you know, big appreciation for that.
Yes, yes.
Oh, you know, okay, I knew this day would come.
Everyone's out for me today.
Well, yeah, all the online scrolls, the de-packers.
They know I'm a danger to their precious system.
Indeed.
Okay, we've got another one.
Nate, this one's from, okay.
Nate, you uncultured fuck.
It's de-enverred.
De-enverred.
And again, this is another classified voice.
De-enverred?
He's German.
De-enverred called in last time, but this is de-enverred.
He's calling in.
Have you made a mistake last time?
I don't know.
Okay, anyway, go.
Somewhere in the deepest, darkest reaches of phlogmological space-time.
Go!
There he is.
I made it.
Sensei, thank you.
Ah, Agent 1488.
I see you've returned from your undercover mission.
You certainly know how to make an entrance.
I trust you have the intel.
What's happening?
My furor.
Apologies for teleporting directly to your inner chamber.
But the information I have obtained is of the utmost importance.
The pinkos have established contact with the other side.
Somehow they are able to punch through the veil between our phlogmos and physical space-time.
What?
How is this possible?
No signal can reach the other side?
The phlogm just don't create too much background noise.
It gupples the signal.
I want our top scientists working on these until their message is uncovered.
Yes, my furor.
There's just one more thing I have to report.
I managed to trace their signal back through physical space-time,
and have confirmed who is receiving the signal from Communist Hell.
Excellent work, Agent 1488.
Who is the person listening at the other side?
My furor.
It's not a person.
It's an entire organization.
There's nothing in our records about them.
But they've somehow amassed enough power to break through the barrier between their world and Communist Hell.
They call themselves the PCP.
Oh my God.
This is the dawn of a new alarm.
I didn't know Batman was a Nazi.
I didn't know Batman was a German man.
I guess he was all along.
Maybe this is like...
There's something about phlogmatogical space going on in there.
The phlogs, the phlogmos, is very intriguing to me.
Now I gotta look at phlogiston theory right now.
Figure out what it's all mean.
It seems like we're developing an alliance with the fine folks down in Communist Hell
against these clearly fascist motherfuckers,
Agent 1488 and this evil boss there.
Are they operating out of PC limbo?
Maybe they are.
They're somewhere in the in-between spaces.
This is level 3 autistic, level 4 autistic.
This whole arc.
I can't keep track of it.
Somebody do a lecture, please.
Okay, we've got one final voicemail,
and this is a continuation of another beloved saga.
This is not even Clusterpunk can save the PCP from me.
Okay, here we go.
Luckily I escaped from PC prison, but you guys were about to let me rot there.
So for retribution, I hacked some of your search histories.
Prepare to be exposed.
Okay, so Nate, we have Naked Girl.
Naked Girl abs.
Hillary Clinton leaked nudes.
Why was slavery abolished?
Why can't I own slaves?
Slave Black Market.
Good question.
Slave Black Market price.
Slave Black Market price USD.
Overnight live guarantee US shipping rates.
Okay, we can see where this is going.
Ben.
Ben energy.
Keto Pizza Crust.
Sonichu.
TeeSpring.com.
This is all true.
Is it gay to be around by burning Sanders neck fat?
What the fuck?
How to remove a cucumber stuck in my...
Okay, never mind.
This family is fucking loony.
How did he know?
Don't seem to have any search histories.
No doubt covering up many heinous crimes.
No doubt.
He's only searched one thing the last few months.
How to convince my friends I'm in college so I don't have to talk to them anymore.
Classic.
That's the easiest ways to kill someone.
Tips on where to bury a body.
Best alibis.
Rhonda Rousey home address.
Okay.
It's just hippopotamus porn.
I've never seen so many pictures of Gloria from Madagascar in one place before.
Okay, well I'm having a good time with this guys.
No wonder the police are arrested, PCP listeners.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
They're doing fine work, the PCP police.
We're the reason people are dying in jail.
All right, that's it everybody.
Speakpipe.com.
Send us your voicemails.
You know, we asked and you guys are delivered.
The PCP voicemails are seeing marked improvements and I'm appreciating it.
The ratings are skyrocketing.
It's just insane.
The climbs.
The financial benefit we're reaping from these voicemails.
You wouldn't believe it if I told you.
The corporate sponsorships such as with Disney Plus are flooding in.
So let's just keep it going.
Speakpipe, link down below.
Leave yours.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
$1.
Discord.
$5.
All the bonus episodes.
It's gonna be like 29 or 30 by the time you hear this fucking episode.
Incredible benefits.
Incredible deal.
And anymore we appreciate.
And now at a $10 pledge, guess what you get into?
The fucking PCP Minecraft server which also has a separate Patreon for just $5.
Oh my God, come play with us.
Video games, streams, build a home.
Wait, so we ended up making a separate Patreon and incorporating it into ours?
We thought it was a reasonable thing to just make an additional bonus for those people who are already pledging like $10 or more.
We're just giving them a free entry if they want to.
But we expect most people to do the separate Patreon.
Wow, wacky and crazy.
I know it's absolutely bonkers, folks.
So kooky and ridiculous.
Maybe it's crazy enough to work.
We will find out.
If it doesn't work, we'll change tags.
We'll keep you posted.
So go give us money at all these fronts.
Leave more voicemails and follow us at TPcrastinators on Twitter for all kinds of fun things.
And we will see you next week for another but blasting episode of the Procrastinators podcast.
See you there.
Bye.
Yeah.
Ding.