Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast, and it's me, Ben Saint.
And unfortunately I cannot share every precious moment of my life.
With you, the audience, and you, Gibbontake.site.
Ah, what?
That plug.
Thank you.
Just saying .site after my name.
You're welcome for saying .site after your name.
What happened this week?
What happened?
Well, I have a sort of topic of convo.
I've been, I've needed to, because I've been drawing the Clarissa thing, and it's been going sort of alright.
You know, a page or so every day of like blocking out panels and figuring out how to translate a script for an outline of a scene into a, yeah, it's pretty good.
But I have been beating myself up about it, and I've took to my therapist.
You gotta like let yourself, you gotta be nicer to yourself.
What do you like doing?
What makes you feel happy?
And that was like, you know, do you ever feel like you have no emotions?
Like nothing will make you sad or happy?
And it's just sort of like, oh, well I genuinely don't have an answer to what would make me happy right now.
Are you asking me or is that what your therapist said?
No, well, I mean, it's what got me thinking about it, and I am asking you if you've ever felt that sort of, wow, I just realized I don't have emotions at this point in time.
Sure.
I don't know what would make me happier or whether I'm sad or not.
I'm just, I don't know.
Yeah, sure.
It's a big, I don't know moment.
Mm-hmm.
That's, that's my thoughts.
What?
That's my thoughts.
That's it?
Well, I was just wondering because like, it's so weird.
I thought I had interests and passions, and sometimes I just feel like I don't.
I feel like.
Oh, sure, I feel like that all the time.
But that's bad.
Is that bad?
Okay, is that where you're going with that?
That's bad.
It's bad.
It's not a good state of being.
Oh, okay.
You should be able to, to at least know what would make you happy to do it and to like treat yourself.
Oh.
It's like, what do you call it?
Self-care.
It's self-care because when you, when you have no emotions one way or the other, you're
just sort of dead inside.
Yeah.
And so every day is like, I don't know, I guess I'm awake.
So this is what your therapist said.
She said, she said, you ever feel like you have no emotions one way or the other?
And, and you were like, yes.
And she was like, oh, well, that's bad.
Oh, you shouldn't feel like that.
Don't the extent.
Okay.
Anyway, that's out of time.
We're out of time.
We'll see you next week.
It's exactly how it goes.
Yeah.
No, no, it's just sort of, sort of, I don't know.
I've like with, with gender stuff, gender dysphoria and euphoria.
I've just sort of fallen off feeling good or bad.
I'm like, I need, sometimes I need reminding what it feels like.
I need more, I need more gender.
You know, ever since you got, I got on gender.
Like I need more and more of it, like to, like to just feel that same high.
But it's funny is like a feeling of gender euphoria is like being told I look really cute or something.
And I'm like, a sort of wave of something flushes over me.
And I'm like, I feel giddy.
And I'm like, oh, that's an emotion.
I get it now.
I haven't been feeling that for some reason.
Was I sad before?
I don't think so.
I was just nothing.
I think being more, being more emotional is a good thing.
And I should try and do it more.
I don't really know how.
Yeah.
But that's, that's just been on my mind lately.
Like, like crying at a film.
Yeah.
Or, or, or just, you know.
That's, you're saying that's something you should strive to do more?
I want to.
I don't know whether it's like, oh, objectively, it is good for the human to do this.
I mean, I don't know.
I just know that it feels great when I feel happy about something.
And I don't feel happy about much.
Generally.
I feel like.
I feel.
I feel you.
Yeah.
It feels sort of numb to like, maybe as a defense mechanism for like all of the shitty things
that are going on, just that I constantly read about.
And I'm like, yeah, well, we're all going to die.
And then very soon.
And it's like, as a defense mechanism, instead of freaking out about it, I just sort of block
emotional receptors and I don't feel anything.
And then it becomes harder to, I don't know, look into the future and be like, I want to
do this.
I'm going to strive for that.
I'm just sort of like making sure I eat.
And continuing to do a project or something.
And I'm like, that sucks.
Because I know what it feels like I can get reminded of what it feels like to be truly
happy and like, doesn't happen enough.
Doesn't happen often enough.
Yeah.
But what's the solution?
What's the solution here?
Drugs.
Yeah.
You know what makes me truly happy?
Doc.
I'll tell you what makes me happy is shooting up heroin.
I see eight balls, speedball, highball.
Put it in my bloodstream.
I think legitimately drugs are, the reason people take drugs is to get a feeling of something
when they're feeling like nothing.
So you know, they're all like, a lot of them are very dangerous and you shouldn't shoot
up heroin.
Probably not.
I mean, I've heard it's bad.
Yeah.
But like, that's the underlying cause of the wanting.
But how would I know unless I do it all the time?
I don't know.
How would I know?
I can't give it a go, said the therapist.
How will I know it's bad unless I try it again and again and again and again?
As that one guy from that one, from that one history podcast, again and again and again.
What's that guy's name?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
There's just a guy who does World War I and World War II.
It's like a one man podcast where he just talks about military history and he just says it like that.
Okay, anyway.
Sorry to derail that.
Well, yeah.
I mean, if you're looking for a solution, I think the answer lies in-
Dan Carlin's hardcore history.
I found it.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Dan Carlin's hardcore history.
The answer lies in self-care and whatever that entails.
That could be anything.
I know.
But the fact that historically self-care is sounded like, ugh, whatever.
That's dumb.
Self-care?
Well, to me, it has.
It sounds like meditation.
I can't meditate.
I don't know.
I don't get it.
I don't get the benefits.
It's just sort of like it's too abstract for me to grasp the utility of it for me to take it seriously enough for it to actually be useful.
And so self-care seems like a similar thing.
I don't understand.
Meditation seems like, oh, it's so specific.
It's like, oh, it's just some fancy mumbo jumbo.
Whereas self-care just sounds like, I mean, you could call anything self-care.
Well, you could, but it's the outcome.
I mean, I don't know much about it either.
It's just sort of like, I mean, you've seen like, oh, this is a social media post.
People talking about self-care day where it's, I don't know.
I don't know.
This is where I am right now is that I am confused.
Well, self-care is just, isn't it just anything that makes you anything you do to keep yourself feeling good?
I guess, right?
Keep yourself feeling positive.
Yeah.
Keep yourself from succumbing to whatever problems you got.
Like what I feel a self-care thing would be based on what I've read is that you say, for example, you have like your shower and you keep clean, you know, a normal amount.
But you don't really do it because you want it.
You just do it because I got a shower.
And if you, like instead of taking your regular old shower to get clean, you get like super clean.
You like get like super relaxing bubble bath and feel really good physically rather than just doing your regular old like utilitarian shower, having an extra little bit of spice, an extra little something to your normal routine that you wouldn't usually put in there because I don't have time for that.
Self-care is indulging in things that take time but are physically and mentally stimulating in a way that you would usually just ignore because, I don't know, I'm in a rat race right now.
I can't, I can't have fun.
I can't do things that are good.
Yeah, I think that's what I assume self-care is about is adding like you moments.
Like the point of moment and action is to benefit you in a way that is different from, I don't know, other ones that are just sort of like, oh, I got to get money because I got to eat.
But getting a really nice thing to eat.
Can getting money be self-care?
Can hustling be self-care?
Well, that's the thing.
To me, it's when I wake up, when I wake up at the crack of dawn and I start that hustling grind, for me, that's self-care.
It keeps me going.
Well, it's like...
I'm sorry.
But it could be though.
No.
No?
It can be in conjunction with hustling because hustling is sort of like...
What about grinding?
You're grinding your body against the grindstone of the commerce and labor and you're creating something of value that you can then get the money from.
But your body is being used up, your energy, whatever.
You are using your energy to create wealth that you can use spend on things that give you energy.
If you only care about the grind, you sort of leave your personal well-being to the side a little.
And you just sort of focus more of that wealth onto making more wealth quicker instead of fat stacks.
And so, I don't know.
I feel like there's more room in my life to care about myself.
And it's not even just like taking a bath, it's just sort of...
It's a mental practice.
To feel good about a good day's work, even if I could easily criticize myself for not having a very good week,
I should instead praise myself for having a week as good as I did, etc.
Mental stuff.
I had that physics professor in college who told us when you are doing physics, when you're solving problems,
it's important to let yourself feel good when you solve a problem, when you find the answer to a question.
Make sure to let yourself feel good about it as a way to reward yourself and keep yourself motivated to keep going and keep doing them.
It is all too easy to allow negative thoughts directed at yourself into your life and to ignore positive ones.
And I don't know why that is, but it just so happens.
And it's better to have a balance or more positive than negative, or I don't know.
I definitely beat myself up.
I mean, I know this is pretty obvious to anyone listening, and it's obvious to me too.
I beat myself up far more often than I am deserving of it, and I don't praise myself.
Make sure that doesn't sound good.
No, it's not.
It sounds like you've identified a key problem right there.
Yep.
The steps, like the literal steps are a little strange.
I don't know exactly yet.
I've been advised to buy clothes that make me feel more gender, make me feel like if I have like an androgynous sort of pair of jeans or whatever that I continually wear,
because I'm too scared of looking too girly.
I obviously, I like it when it works, when I can put something on that is girly and it looks good, and people compliment me.
That's like a big source of enjoyment for me.
I really like it.
But I just sort of, I'm scared.
I'm scared of looking not quite right, certainly in public.
And so I just sort of default to not wearing girlier clothing, wearing more gender affirming clothes.
And that's something I should steer away from, I think.
I should do things that make me happier, even though there's a higher risk of whatever.
Oh, I don't know, somebody looking at me and saying, da, da, you're a trans, you're not a woman.
Do you get comments on your appearance in public?
I don't.
No, not in public, but like among people.
When I'm out with people, among us, when I'm out or even just in the house,
if I'm wearing something that is feminine and it looks good,
I will sometimes get compliments from my mom or my brother.
And it's like, wow, all right.
That's how I like that.
You don't usually get compliments in public from strangers,
people you know.
I see.
But what about me, though?
What am I supposed to do?
Well, you've got to dress.
Let's get serious about what matters.
You should go full goth, I think.
I think you would look like a cool goth, because you've always been into that.
A cool goth, you know, that's very, you know what?
You've identified something there.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Being goth is cool.
What if you just made it a point to start wearing black lipstick or something?
It's like.
I don't know about that.
I don't know.
I mean, I don't know what you're into.
But something that would be like, oh, I look cool like this.
I should wear this more often, even if it's more of a hassle,
even if it's expensive to get into that.
And it's more difficult than just throwing on a t-shirt.
It's worth it because it's self-care.
You're spending that energy to make yourself happier.
You know, it's worth it.
Actually, I have been meaning to buy new clothes.
I haven't bought clothes in a while.
I've been meaning to go and like, well, let's just think.
I know that I need a new wardrobe.
I know that all my clothes suck and I've had them all for like 10 years and I like need some new ones.
But I don't know where I want to go to get any and I don't exactly know what I want.
I have some idea of some things I could get.
I don't know where to go to get them and it's hard and it's just so hard and it's such a hassle.
It's hard and it's a hassle.
I think that's the key.
It literally feels like a job.
It literally feels like it's like a job that I have to work in order to one,
determine where clothes are to be obtained and then to go and obtain them.
It is hard work making yourself feel happy.
That is true.
I think that's the key is that getting self-care doesn't just mean doing whatever you feel like in the moment,
which is usually just going to be, I just want to laze around today instead of working.
Like that's not self-care.
That's just sort of not caring.
Self-care is an active participatory thing.
You do something deliberately to make yourself feel better or to improve your whatever,
how you will feel in the future.
Yeah.
Because for me, another thing is like wearing makeup is something I've been afraid of trying
because makeups, one can easily be looking bad,
but I can get the hang of that, I'm sure.
But then there's the cost and the time investment for putting on makeup every morning.
And it's like, I don't even want to get into that, but I know that it would make me look nicer.
And so I should spend that mental energy to just get into it, figure it out.
It's going to take hard work, but it's a good thing to get about doing.
I wore that.
Actually, it's the jacket that I wore in the Radcon for lectures, the Tuxedo jacket.
I wore that the other day and I was like, this thing rules.
I wish I had like three more similar ones, but that's such like a specific piece of clothing.
That's such like a weird item.
You can't just find those, certainly not like ones that fit and ones that look good,
just worn as like a jacket.
Usually they're part of a set or something.
Yeah.
That's like the kind of item that I wish I just knew where to go to get one.
I would go and I would find somebody don't.
I mean, you could just blindly search for a little while and like thrift stores might have something.
Yeah.
Every time I've gone to the garment district, I've been disappointed.
I always go there thinking I'll like find some like weird stuff and I never do.
Or I never find any weird stuff that's like that I like or that I want.
I always go and I'm always like, I'm going to do it.
I'm going to get some, I'm going to expand my wardrobe.
I'm going to find some stuff.
I'm going to find some cool stuff and then I always leave like, well, I got a shirt.
What was the point?
Shopping is terrifying.
I hate shopping even though it's just sort of like, I feel like I need to stay there and mull over these things
for like way longer than the store is going to be open for.
Yeah.
And I'm like, oh God, I got a hurry.
I only have like six hours before the shop closes.
I got to choose something.
Oh, but what if I don't like it?
Then I spend like some money on one thing and I'm like, well, it's all right.
And I sometimes wear it and it's like, what a waste.
But I feel like, I feel like the alternative of just having whatever you have and just wearing that and not feeling anything
because you don't feel like cool or cute or sexy wearing it.
That's worse, I think.
Well, I guess what I'm saying is that the result in the past is often that I will go out in an attempt to fix that problem
of I don't have anything that I want to wear.
I don't have anything that I like how I look in and then I go out and I don't solve the problem.
I've just wasted my time and I end up no better off for it.
It's very discouraging.
It is.
But there's only so many times it can fail because clearly...
Are there though?
Well, yeah.
I mean, it's like getting a date.
You're going to go out and it's going to suck most of the time and then it's going to work.
Yeah, it says you.
Not if I have anything to say about it.
Hard work in the face of...
Sort of meaning to get back on Tinder or something.
I think I've been talking about this for months.
I should go on dates again.
But the same exact thing.
It sounds so hard.
It sounds like so much work.
It is.
Jesus.
But hard work in the face of adversity is...
I don't understand.
It makes it why it's hard.
I don't understand how anyone does anything.
They have emotions.
That's dumb.
I have it so easy.
In the grand scheme of things, I have it so easy.
I don't have a job.
I have nothing but free time.
And yet I feel like it's all consumed all the time by the projects that I have in the works.
I feel like I have so much more time than the average person and yet it's like...
I feel like I have no time for anything.
Most people have a 9-5.
Not me.
And yet I feel like I do less than most people.
Most people go on dates.
Go clothes shopping.
Me, I'm just like...
Damn.
Gotta keep messaging Alibaba.
Gotta get that book printed one of these days.
You know, some people, they could do the sort of thing that I do.
The average person, I feel like they have to squeeze that sort of thing out in their spare time.
Yeah.
And I just don't know how anyone does it.
I think it's hard.
Well, it's entirely because they're more mentally capable to do it for various reasons.
I think the structure of a job and the fact that you have to go, if you go physically somewhere,
you meet people, it's like slightly, you know, it's a social experience.
It's like there's aspects of regular work that give you more energy to do things.
I mean, obviously people come home exhausted all the time.
But when you hit like with us, we don't have like a traditional job.
We make our own hours.
Yeah.
And going out is not necessary for a lot of it.
There's not like a group of people that we are, the work people that we go to see when we're at work.
So it just sort of feels a little isolating maybe.
It's just, it's a series of things that make it harder to feel like anything is worth it.
And I think it's because we're not doing the hard work that makes everything seem so much harder.
The hard work of self-care, the hard work of...
Like if you're in a bad mental space, it's harder to do anything.
You know, depression does that.
Yeah.
And I think it's a similar sort of thing if you're in a bad, I don't know where I'm going.
I feel like I had a good point.
You're saying, you're saying, you're saying if we, are you saying we're caught in some sort of death spiral?
No, no, no.
I'm saying that it seems so difficult to do all these things.
And I think the fact that you feel like you have so much free time is another...
Well, I simultaneously feel like I have so much free time, but it's all just gets...
But it's all eaten up by things so quickly.
Sure, but the fact that you feel like you should be able to make more of your time is like a guilt trip thing.
You're saying that despite not having a nine to five, you're doing less work.
And so that weighs on you.
That's how it feels.
It makes you feel worse about life.
I think I mentioned last week I said like, I'm just like, where does the day go?
I spent the day like, I had meant to edit that day, but instead, what was it?
I had done a little bit of reorganizing.
I had messaged some printers.
I had checked my emails or whatever.
And then the day was gone.
I didn't even get to do the thing.
I think that the point I'm generally getting at is that it's harder for you than you're giving yourself credit
and you're beating yourself up by comparing yourself to people who just somehow magically seem to be able to do so much stuff.
I think it's not that you're in an advantageous position actually.
And it's a mental problem that is blocking you and making you feel like nothing matters
and that you don't have passion for anything, which makes it harder to do stuff,
which is why you look at the amount of stuff you do and you're like, well, that's not a lot of stuff.
And I don't even have a nine to five job.
I must suck.
Something is terribly wrong and it just sort of spirals like that.
And that's why the self-care is important.
It's sort of a fight against that sort of negative spiral.
Even though it's like on the grand scheme of things, you could objectively say, well, I do less work than some other people.
The point is not to then shit on yourself for that is to congratulate yourself for when you do get stuff done
to build up a more positive outlook on life, which makes you happier generally,
which makes it easier to do things, which improves the amount of stuff you can do anyway.
Yeah, I think I get what you're saying.
I've mostly been fine and been passing days and getting stuff done.
There's just some days when it feels like, oh, geez, my day was eaten up.
There's just some days when I feel like, where did the day go and like, wow, how much worse would it be
if I was like the typical person who has no choice but to give over eight to 12 of the 16 hours a day
that they have to themselves to a boss man.
It's not to say that having a nine to five means you're more capable,
because I know definitely people struggle the same way you do, but also have a job.
So it's just sort of doubly depressing.
There's something to be said for not comparing yourself to others
and just considering that whatever path your life is on, you're the only person on that path.
You just got to work at it yourself, bit by bit.
You got to be the best me I can be.
Yeah.
Sure.
I got you.
I don't know.
No, I get you.
No, I hear you.
But speaking of beating myself up for not working hard enough.
Last week when I said that I thought maybe that video would be done by the time the episode came out,
that was foolish and I should have known at the time that it was foolish.
But I said it anyway and I can never take it back.
Yeah.
Sure you can.
I was thinking about like what if I did the least work on it possible?
Like yeah, the laziest possible version of it could have been done last week,
but of course in hindsight I realized no,
that doesn't allow time to do such and such and so and so,
adding little visual touches that I was thinking of and I wanted to do.
So I've been going through it and I've been doing that.
And I am through.
I hope the pace will pick up.
At this point I have gone through and I have finished about an hour and a half out of like seven hours of it.
So it's slow going but I hope it will speed up.
I had to spend, this is another thing, another thing that it's like how does this take so long?
How am I so incompetent that I spent the whole day?
I spent an entire day, like more than an entire day just right click saving images
that I knew I was going to want to like put in as visual aids.
That took me an entire day just doing that.
But this is exactly the thing, you did all that work and you're shitting on yourself for it.
But it doesn't feel like work because every individual action, every right click save is like infinitesimally small.
It's nothing, it's not work.
It should take zero time.
The work involved in it rounds down to zero and then I did it like 400 times or whatever
and then it's like well that's 400 times zero should be zero.
Moving your mouse is, you're just moving a mouse and clicking.
You're also thinking about what images and then finding them, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Like it's not just zero brain energy work you had to consider like the best version of the image for the thing.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's the kind of thing that's like it is work and I'm doing work and I'm getting it done.
But then when I look back on it, I'm like I have done nothing.
You're being a shitty boss to yourself.
Yeah, I hear you.
Boy.
But the fact that I spent that time hopefully means that it will not take me another week to get the other six hours of content made.
I hope that it will now be like okay maybe you can, ugh.
I mean for me, things that shouldn't, like when I just think of it without looking too deep, I'm like oh that shouldn't take too long.
It always takes the longest because it's like right now the Clarissa stuff, I do feel kind of stupid at how slow I'm doing it and how easily I'm getting distracted.
And I'm beating myself up about how I'm not able to condense these pages into smaller enough, like efficient enough pages such that it's on par with like one piece which I'm reading every week.
And various other like comics that just sort of I see them and I'm like oh yeah panel layout.
Oh that's a diagonal.
I haven't put a diagonal panel for like 20 pages.
What am I doing with my life?
I'm just sort of like I'm just I'm freaking out a little about how long it's taking to do all that.
But it is like kind of the most like brain intensive part because I'm trying to translate an idea into a visual image and also trying to like set out a page so that it reads well and then I'm beating myself up for doing that but maybe not being as efficient as one piece.
And I'm like that's like in hindsight that criticism doesn't make any sense.
I can just go over the pages later and adjust them but it's like during in the moment I'm like I'm doing all this work and I'm like this isn't good enough.
I'm just sketching.
I'm not even I'm not even sketching.
I'm just blocking out like here's where the character would be.
This is they're going to have their arm coming out from this side of the panel and I'm not I'm not sketching it.
I'm going to go over it and search it and then do the line art.
It's like if it's not a sketch if it's not line art, it should take much less time.
The fact is the line art is the thing that takes the least time because the sketch lines are already there and I can turn my brain off and just draw lines.
And I don't even need to think the thinking part is the stuff that actually takes the you know the considering the pondering and the considering is the hard part.
That's true.
That's that's my experience.
Yes, it's the thing.
It's the thinking that is hard.
I've said that I've said that before about about comics, but I mean about anything really.
Yeah.
I forget what I was said last time about how many pages more it would probably take.
It's going to be way more.
It's probably just going to be way more.
It's going to be more than you said.
It's going to be more than I said just because I have in that moment, I had a very, very strict or conservative like estimate of how many pages each scene would take.
And as I draw things, I'm like, well, it needs another panel to show this and it needs more actually and just the page numbers go up.
And I'm like, oh no, I'm making so much work for myself down the line.
There's so many pages.
Surely I could condense this down lower and potentially I could if I go over it later.
But it's I don't know.
I think I was being too optimistic with how little pages I would have to draw to get the story to the end.
I see.
Yeah.
Because it's little things like you write the script and you're like, oh, this character says this.
But like screen real estate is taken up by the speech bubbles and you still need to show like establishing shots and characters reacting to things.
You could theoretically cram more onto a page, but like you would still have to draw the same amount.
Yeah.
I mean, sure.
There's ways because like one piece is so efficient.
The amount of stuff, the amount of plot points that can be going on in one chapter of one piece, even with multiple different fights going on in like 20 pages is incredible.
If you actually like think about how much stuff, how many lines of dialogue and action are going on in a single chapter.
It's like a definitely they've they've narrowed it down to like a like a fine science of how to do that.
Yeah.
Because one piece would be so much longer if it had the pacing of Bleach, for example.
Bleach was very much a more like artful, large panels, panels that take up entire pages.
The amount of pages that show a certain amount of stuff happening is much longer in Bleach, but it's so artful that nobody cares.
It's really lovely to look at.
But one piece manages to look cool and extremely efficient with its storytelling.
It's like it's unfathomable.
I shouldn't be comparing myself to it.
It's a little too high of a bar.
I mean, that is, yeah, that is like the most popular manga in like the history of the world.
Yep.
Right, sure.
So I understand your point there.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, you can only you can only condense it.
I mean, I'm sure it's it's good to be efficient when possible, but you can only you can only do so much.
You can only cram as much as you can cram onto a page.
Yeah, I can always improve.
I'll make Clarissa.
And then the next thing I do, I will I will be better at it because I'm constantly thinking about like every panel being necessary for the for the for the story.
I'm telling, which is something I've always liked because the more important the more the the if every panel is important, if every frame of animation is important.
Then you can save time by not wasting time drawing frames that don't do anything.
I mean, sure.
You can have as as least frames as possible as least work as possible for the same effect.
That's what I like.
Yeah, definitely.
That's what I that's what I go for.
Man, I remember thinking like I think I feel like I became a lot more efficient.
Like I showed myself that I could be faster and more efficient at drawing comics than I had ever been before when I was doing Phantoms Revenge.
And I remember thinking like, oh, I'll be really I'll be I think I'll be faster on the next thing.
But there has been there has been no next thing.
I have not drawn anything since then.
I assume at some point in the future, I will.
That could that could always be like I've had this thing as well where I know that I can on occasion draw super quick and get a lot done.
But during that time, I don't realize that I'm burning myself out and putting more energy in that I'm giving myself to like rest up.
And so I burn out.
And that's why I managed to do so much is because I was doing too much and I couldn't keep up and then I had to stop for a long time.
And so trying to reach that pace again could be foolish because I'm just setting myself up to burn out because the the burnout is like for anything is the the the harder you push yourself the like exponentially longer the recovery processes.
If you work just like a little less hard, your rest time that you need will be a lot less.
And so overtime will work will get get done keeping up a super high pace for like a number of years.
It's not not advisable.
I would think.
Well, I don't know maybe I'm saying like I was getting more done with less effort than I thought previously.
Okay.
There were times where that was the case.
Yeah.
I mean that that could just be like a more comfortable like drawing hands like you've built up muscle memory and certain things are easier.
So that could also be the case.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's, it's, you know, it's just like, geez.
Once again, it just feels like that's another thing like, oh, I'm not.
I don't have like a real job and I'm not even really working on like a comic right now.
I'm sort of in just in between things and yet just trying to sort just trying to sort things out in between things.
Feels like it takes up.
Oh my, I guess I'm not just sort of, I'm working on that video.
I'm working on that video right now, but at the same time I've got all these other like unfinished things that I have.
I realized, I realized the other day that like, oh shit, I never even finished drawing the cover.
I never finished drawing the cover for slime and punishment.
Like of course I've got to do that, but I like got so, I got so disgusted with the state of the book with the whole like the lady not messaging me that I just, I just put it through it all down.
It's a mid, mid cover drawing.
I was like, I'm not doing this anymore.
See, see to me, that seems like justifiable.
Like, all right, I need to break, I need a break from this bullshit because of this back and forth that isn't happening with the printer.
Yeah.
But the, you shouldn't be shitting on yourself for having needed that break.
Well, what I, yeah, what I need to do, I realized that what I actually need to do before I do anything else is I need to finish that cover and I need to finish.
I need to actually finish the layout because I, because I had, I did not actually finish everything.
I was simultaneously trying to get the book printing sorted out and then at the same time I was trying to, you know, get the PDF files and get the layout all done.
And so I can't actually print until I have that done.
And so I think what I need to do after the video is done, the first thing I'm going to do is I'm just going to like, fuck, I'm not going to message anyone.
I'm not going to do anything with that.
I'm just going to sit down and actually finish it.
And then I can get back to doing what I talked about last week, which is making a new Alibaba account and trying to catfish the old printer into, because that's how it's, that's what it's going to take.
I'm going to have to approach her with like, hey, I do not need to discuss anything with you.
I don't need to ask you questions about anything.
Just I have a, I have a project.
Please just print it for me.
And that's going to be giving you the highest chance of like, she'll actually do it and just make it as, make it as, as painless and as possible.
So that's the order in which I'm approaching things.
I've continued to order bags of green rock to eventually serve as things to serve as like a bonus podrans to put in packages when I eventually, whenever this Kickstarter actually gets around to happening.
I have many bags of many different kinds of green crystals.
They have a drawer full of them.
Many bags.
Some of them, yeah, they're all different though.
Some of them are smaller.
Some of them are bigger.
Some of them are greener.
Some of them are less green.
Some of them are lighter.
Some of them are darker and they all have different consistencies and it's very much like, it's so hard to choose.
It's so hard to choose which one I should go with.
If you should have them in like a raffle page and then twist them around.
I think tumble them.
Yeah, I think there were some.
Okay, obviously like prices is important.
Like I would rather get, I would rather buy more of the kinds of rocks that are relatively cheaper.
So looking at that, like, like I think I picked out a couple that were like, there was one that was fairly cheap, but it only came with like five of them.
The color was good.
The color was like kind of like, it was like a light pale green.
I was like, that's pretty good.
The consistency is good, but there was another one where like the rocks were smaller and they were darker, but they were greener and there were lots of them in the package.
So like they were smaller overall, but not that much smaller, but like I would got like 20 of them in a package for like $15 instead of getting like five in a package for like $12.
So I was like, they're not quite as big as I would like, but everything else about them is superior.
So I think that's the rock I'm going with is that one company.
I ordered like a dozen different ones to just compare and contrast like which guys should I go with for buying rocks?
Which is the best green?
And I think I found them.
I don't compromise on some things, but I think I've found the best compromise that maximizes all the different factors that are important to me in podron selection.
That was another thing.
I spent a day like I laid out all my different rocks and I compared different green rocks and that took like half my day and then I'm like, where did my day go?
That wasn't work.
I didn't do anything.
I just picked one rock out of a list of rocks.
That's not...
You considered them.
Yeah, it took me a while and I had to...
It was a project gathering them all to the point that I was like, I think I've exhausted all my options.
I have all the options before me now.
Now it's time to lay them out, make lists of pros and cons, choose the ultimate rock.
The ultimate rock.
The ultimate crystal.
This is where in the platformer game, that a wind would blow them all over the world and then you have to go collect them.
Then, Saint, you have to collect all of the green rocks for your plugeurs, your Kickstarter people.
I hope to see people pluge in one of these days.
Yeah, just like in real life, I hate when a sudden gust of wind blows all my rocks away.
You know what I mean?
It's like such a bummer every time.
I go out for a picnic and I lay out my rocks and my picnic basket and then a gust of wind just scatters them all to the four corners of the earth.
Yeah, I hear you.
And then there's the secret pages you can also collect, which make up Phantom's Revenge.
Oh, sure, obviously, obviously.
Well, not Phantom's Revenge, Slime and Punishment.
Right.
Phantom's Revenge is just merely a chapter.
Merely a chapter in the saga.
Oh, I have, I got new glasses.
I had to go through a whole fucking rigmarole to get new glasses from this company.
They were technically like a Christmas present or a birthday present or something.
Like my, no, it was a birthday present.
My mom wanted to get me new glasses and I was like, yes, I need new glasses, but she wanted me to pick the frames.
And so there was this whole rigmarole of like, I had to make an account on this website and then I had to pick a bunch of frames and then they sent me like several frames and I had to try them on.
And then I had to go and like, I had to submit a bunch of paperwork like to let them know my prescription and something and I had to get an appointment to the optometrist to update my prescription.
And so I finally got them and I think they were a little off.
I think they feel, they look fine, but they, I feel a little weird wearing them like just they make me ever so slightly dizzy.
And I think the prescription or like the pupillary distance is off and it's a little,
like I can read in them fine, but when I'm like walking around and like I turn my head and like looking at distant things, I feel like my,
something feels a little weird. I think I'm going to have to send them back and that's, that's frustrating.
Is it because they're too in focus or just some other thing?
I don't know. It's not like the clarity, like everything's clear through them.
It's just when I move, there's something about distant objects when I move my head, it feels a little bit disorienting or like something is a little bit off.
I can't really explain it any better than that.
Are they like circles? Are they Harry Potter glasses?
No, they're rectangles much like my old ones, except they're like sort of a different, they're sort of like half, they're sort of like brown on top and it's kind of greenish on the bottom.
They're called, they're called like emerald garnet was the color of the description.
I don't know. They have sort of like a brown, they have sort of like a tortoise shell to greenish fade coloring to them.
I like them. I think they look cool. They're not, they're not a huge, a huge change for my old frames.
But my old frames were just kind of like dark brown and these ones have a little subtle coloring to them.
But the fucking, but the old ones were like crack, they were falling apart. I had to glue them back shut several times.
I haven't had new glasses in a while.
Once I'm wearing, I've been wearing these ones.
My old ones I got in Poland, like almost 10 years ago, I think.
Holy shit. How can you have glasses for 10 years? Doesn't your prescription change?
Actually, no, I went, I went to my optometrist and got my first appointment in, well, it was a new optometrist, but I went to an optometrist and got my prescription checked.
And they said that like my prescription had barely changed since the last time.
Wow.
So that's good. My eyesight seems to be holding strong, you know, put that on the pros list, I guess. Things to be happy about.
Um...
Anyways, I'll probably have to make a fucking phone call and then I'll probably have to put them back in the box and address it to them and send it back and then wait like two weeks and receive a new...
A new prescription or a new set of lenses with a pupillary distance adjusted or something like that.
Oh, God, speaking of rigmarole. Hey, let me gripe.
Okay. I was talking on Twitter about how my new thing is Treasury Bonds. Do you want to hear about Treasury Bonds?
Uh, sure.
Sure you do. Sure you do. Everybody wants to hear about it.
All right, listen. Here's the deal with Treasury Bonds. There is, um, my, my, my parents turned me onto this. There is a thing you can do.
I think you might have to be a U.S. citizen, but you can buy, but you can buy these things called Treasury Bonds.
There's specifically a kind of bond called an I bond because they, they're, they're lettered. They have different letter types of bonds.
Well, this is the I bond and the I stands for interest that is pegged to the interest rate.
And so, um, right now the interest rate is really high or it was as of like a few months ago because the interest rate on the I bond is set every six months.
Every six months it updates to like what is the current rate of, sorry, inflation.
And it said interest. I meant to say inflation. It's pegged to inflation.
And so it's like four or five months ago, the interest was, the inflation rate was at like 9.86%.
So the I bond earns an interest rate of 9.86%.
And so what I read, what they were telling me, and what I realized, yes, this is what I need to do is at any point within that six month period between whatever, like June and October or whatever it is.
If I buy an I bond then, then for the next six months after I buy it, it will accrue interest at a rate of 9.86%. And 9.86% is insane.
So I really needed to like put as much money into that as I possibly could, like right now.
So I'm like, okay, I have until the end of October.
So like a week or two ago, I a couple or a couple weeks ago, I get online, I get go to the website and I make an account.
And they're like, we have we're having trouble verifying your information, you need to do some paperwork for us, fill this out, get this notarized, and then send and then send it to us and we will verify it.
And I'm like, okay, so I waited around for a while for a couple weeks until I had reason to go into town to go to a bank to find a notary public to get my frickin form notarized.
It means I have to find a guy who's professionally qualified to give it like a certain stamp.
So I did that finally, and then I sent it maybe a week and a half ago.
I sent it in the mail.
And so the other day I check my account or I check it and I'm like, okay, it's I hopefully that's been processed by now.
Time for me to buy some of these sweet eyeballs maybe trying time for me to lock in that sweet sweet 9.86% interest rate.
Are you are you joking?
Are you kidding me?
That's like a dream.
That's like that you can't fucking get that my bank account is earning like 0.015% some dog shit.
So it's a miracle.
So I go and I check the account and I and I and I check the email or whatever that I got in response and it tells me that it might be up to 13 weeks before they verify my documents.
Wow.
Yeah, it might be up to 13 weeks with so of course the window will have passed by then the window will have passed and the the the interest rate will have updated again and it will probably go down a bit.
I don't know what I'll go down to but I was I was I was it was gonna it was gonna be so perfect.
I was gonna lock it in right before the I was gonna lock it in right before the interest rate updated.
So I was gonna get six months at 9.86% then it was gonna update and in the next six month window I was gonna it would probably be a little bit lower but it would but only a little bit it would maybe be something like 8%.
So I was gonna get six months at 9% six month at 8% and I assume it will probably go down after that which you know whatever but that would be that would be a whole year at this great interest rate.
And I've I don't know I'm sure I've lost out on I'm sure I've lost out on at least hundreds of dollars at least hundreds of dollars by not fucking hitting this this window and you know what that's the kind of thing.
That's the kind of thing that bums me out and just makes me think what's it all what's it even worth getting up in the in the morning.
You know what I mean this for this fucking nonsense this for this complete this complete completely out of my control completely like arbitrary system to just fuck me over this way.
I couldn't have even I couldn't have even done it even if I'd acted immediately even if I hadn't waited to make the account and I hadn't waited to get it no to rise even if I'd sprung into action as soon as possible 13 weeks is still too long I still wouldn't have made it.
It was doomed from the from the from the beginning.
I mean, you could have started when you were born you could have started putting in bonds.
Well I could have heard millions of days ago.
I could well there's well that's I mean it was out of my control when this information was brought to my attention so I'm assuming that I would have found out I'm assuming that in every possible universe I would have found out about it at the same moment.
Okay so it's not even like so it's not.
I understand that it sucks.
So close.
I was so close to hundreds of dollars of free money give.
True.
Hundreds.
But if if every universe you would have been notified the same time you would have always missed it.
I mean yeah.
Truly it is your parents or your fault who did not tell you just like with everything else there is it is my parents it's my parents fault for not knowing about this ahead of time that's true they should have known sooner and told me they should have anticipated that interest would be this high in 2022.
So okay what what is this the thing like you put money in a bond.
Yes.
And over an entire year the interest rate that you put it in at is accrued.
Well it's every every it compounds every six months.
Every six months so half a year.
So yeah for six months let's say the interest was 10% just to be just to be for ease of math like you would you would buy the bond at a rate of 10% and then over the next six months it would accrue you know 5% of its value because half the annual rate.
It would accrue 5% of its value in interest and then it would add that to the total and then it would compound and then the interest rate would be updated to reflect the new inflation rate and then the cycle would repeat again.
Okay.
And what are the what is a bond made by who benefits from you putting the money in.
It's it's literally it's literally the United States government like taking out a loan from you.
You're literally just loaning the United States government money and they're paying you back with interest.
Seems like a no brainer.
Can it go negative percent can you lose money by putting it in.
No.
Wow.
It is it is.
Yeah it is basically guaranteed to not.
They guarantee that even if the interest even if the inflation rate were to go negative they will not like reduce money from you it can't go below zero.
No.
Right.
The thing about bonds the thing about bonds is that they are like they are basically the standard for like as safe as an asset can be like anything that you invest your money in.
Has the potential to lose money for a for a U.S. bond to fail or to lose value somehow like the United States government would have to collapse.
So yeah this is actually literally this is what do you remember that thing about like the Biden wanting to mince like a trillion dollar coin.
Oh yeah I forgot what that was about.
It's yeah it was it was an economic thing because the Republicans weren't like approving the budget and until the budget was approved the government it was literally this it was literally because the government needed to pay back its bonds.
And if it couldn't do that it had to default on them and if the U.S. government defaults on its.
Loans a.k.a its bonds that is like a fight that is like the tipping over the fucking World Trade Center sized domino in like a in like a catastrophic economic.
Cataclysm.
Well so because like everyone who has a bond will be like oh shit my bonds because because I'm going to take my money out yes because suddenly because suddenly the U.S.
U.S. debt which is like the safest asset that exists suddenly like confidence is shaken and it's like oh the United States dollars.
Suddenly doesn't look like such a sound investment anymore right.
It seems so I mean I know this is very unlikely to happen but it is sort of weird how if something happens everything collapses.
Well like if if confidence is shaken by whatever means then the entire economy would explode.
Well I mean it's because because it is such a because it is such a secure asset.
That's why the United that's why the U.S. dollar is like the fundamental currency that like so much of not just the U.S. economy but like the global economy is based on.
So yeah and suddenly if you shake confidence in the currency that like so much of the economy is built on then yeah like everything else suddenly is shaken.
Yes it's just like that's Rick and Morty episode.
Yeah which where Rick change Rick changes the value of an alien currency to be from one in to zero and then all of their money is worth nothing and so they all kill themselves.
I don't remember that one.
It's like at the beginning of season three or something where like at the end of season two is put in prison and then in the beginning of season three breaks out real quick.
And he has a scene like that.
How did he change the value to zero.
You hacked the computer.
You just did a big you just did a computer thing.
But but money is worth whatever people think it's worth.
Yeah but these guys these bugs they don't know.
They just like oh shit bug people.
Yeah the bug people like.
No that sounds like that sounds how who sees him.
But if you're paying me then our money means nothing and then I'm not going to do what you say and it's like a very like.
Yeah no no I do remember that I do actually it's coming it's coming back to me.
Yes it's exact it's exactly like that.
Anyway I'm just I'm just fucking I'm just shaking I'm just shaking and crying over here and I'm seething and I'm hoping and I'm like.
Oh god I'm gonna 12 weeks from now I'm going to look at the at the US Treasury page and it's going to be like oh the interest rate has updated it has gone from it is now like a pathetic 7.6 percent and I'm like it's not even worth it.
I'll just stick with a Bank of America 0.15 percent like it's this it might as well be the same for get it.
I wonder if there's like a there's definitely some British equivalent or.
Oh yeah every government has like bonds.
Yeah but like I'm wondering if there's like a royal bond like you can invest in whatever royal family is there's there's a little bit of a catch but it's actually not as bad as I thought you can't withdraw it for a year.
So if you invest it like you can't you can't have it back for at least a year but.
Okay so you have to leave it for a year but after a year you can withdraw it but whenever you withdraw it you lose the last three months of interest.
So if you left it for a year and then you withdrew it immediately you would only get nine months worth of the interest and that continues to be the case until five years.
And then after five years you can withdraw it with no with no penalty no loss of interest at all.
And then you and then after five years you can you can leave it to continue to accrue interest for up to 30 years after 30 years it stops accruing interest.
But I mean even so even so.
Could you the rate is the rate is the rate is so much better than it's earning in the in my Bank of America savings account that like even even if I took that three months interest hit it's like it's still you know vastly superior.
So.
You'd have it be like special money that you can afford to not have in your bank.
Yeah you have and it would be like a nice bonus every year or so.
Basically it's like whatever whatever.
Yeah.
If I had like all all the money that I know I won't need for a year.
Or more it's like if I just if I if it were just all in I bonds it would be it would just be like accruing itself it would be like I would be so much better off.
If I had it in that form especially because like you know maybe you buy you buy a bunch like every year right like you buy a little more every year and then every year that goes by it's like OK well some of my old bonds have matured.
And now I can take them out now I can take them out if I need them.
And then mean but meanwhile I've saved up some more money well OK so this year I'll put some more into bonds.
And then you know five years from now those will mature but then also next year the ones that I invested in four years ago those will mature so I'll be set for next year too.
That's that's how you that's how you do it.
Oh you know I'm just looking I typed in UK bonds and I am reminded of the thing that happened very recently with quasi-quarting.
What the new it's an it's a new guy in the he made up a little budget.
Saying there's a cost of living crisis and my solution as the money guy of the new government is to say taxes are going down across the board which means the rich benefit the most.
Yeah.
And it's a terrible terrible idea and apparently bonds UK bonds are plummeting.
Oh because of this.
So probably not a good time for me to get into it.
Unless that means it's more money.
I don't understand exactly but it says plunge plunge probably means down.
Probably means less money.
I mean like I say there's many different like there's these are I bonds so there's also I assume there's A and B and C and D and E and F and G bonds and those all those all work a different way they have some different like mechanism of calculating.
The interest rate just the I bonds just happened to be a really a really juicy one right now just because you know the last time the interest rate or the.
The last time the interest rate updated it was pegged to inflation and the inflation was like at a record high like nine point eight six percent.
So.
The pound sterling is at a thirty seven year low because of the announcement he made about tax cuts.
It's very annoying.
That's been that sucks.
Damn.
Yeah it's funny.
Yeah tax cuts tax cuts that benefit the rich people but then also like okay but then in doing so you've you've tanked the value of the pound sterling which rich people have the most of so they actually lost the most by it also so great great job.
They want to generate economic growth.
Sure.
Being a fucking Tory menace.
Right.
Get him out of there.
What's his name.
Quasi Quartang.
Chancellor of the Exchequer.
That's the new guy.
And this is a really offensive this is a really offensive thing to say but that sounds like a name that J.K. Rowling would make for.
I don't know.
Some goblin banker.
What.
I don't know where he's from.
He's of African heritage.
I don't know what country.
I see.
Goblin banker or something.
I don't know.
He has a fun name to say.
I like saying it but I hate everything.
Is it spelled Q.U.A.
No no it's a K.W. like Kwanza.
Quasi.
Quasi Quartang.
Maybe I'm saying it wrong.
I've not heard it said.
Yeah.
You never know.
Well that's my gripes about treasury bonds.
I should say anyone listening.
Anyone listening who.
This all happened because when I made the treasury direct account they said like we can't verify some of your information.
We need this form.
And then like approving the form is what will theoretically take up to 13 weeks.
So anyone.
Who is listening.
Who maybe manages to make an account and doesn't have to submit like additional verification in the form of a notarized.
Piece of paper.
You know take take my lesson.
Take my lesson.
That I've learned.
Get those eyeballs.
Do what I can't you know.
Enjoy.
Enjoy that 9.86 interest rate.
Until the end of October until the end of October you can lock in a nine point six nine point eight six percent interest rate on up to ten thousand dollars in in bonds.
If you have ten thousand dollars lying around that you won't need for a year.
Why not get why not get that nine nine percent.
Why not.
Think about.
So what would be the the results nine percent of almost a thousand dollars.
Well it would be almost almost five hundred dollars accrued in six months.
Five hundred dollars in six months and then.
If you put if you put it in five hundred and more.
Yeah.
If the interest rate doesn't drop.
It will probably drop a little bit so then maybe be like four hundred for the next.
You might end up with like eight eight eight to nine hundred dollars in free money just for basically putting aside putting ten thousand aside and leaving it for a year.
Which is.
If if if if the fuck if the stock market had like a guaranteed return of ten percent if any asset had like a guaranteed return of ten percent that would be insane.
That would be unheard of.
And guess what.
This is a guaranteed.
This is an asset with a guaranteed return of ten percent at least for the next six months.
So like.
Yeah.
It's fucking.
Just with the one just without one caveat that you have to leave it for a year.
It could be that because it's such a good interest rate at the moment that they're getting a lot of submissions which is why yours will take 13 weeks.
Yeah.
Possibly.
Possibly maybe.
You know I have a little bit of hope because they said up to 13 weeks.
So maybe that means it could take less than 13 weeks.
So maybe they'll get around to it in the next month.
That would be nice.
But I feel like I shouldn't hold my breath.
Hmm.
Oh I almost wish I almost wish I didn't have I almost wish I knew for sure that it wouldn't happen so that I could just forget about it.
But now it's like I should keep checking my email.
I should keep checking that email for the rest of October just to see just to see if it happens.
Oh well.
Money.
I like money.
Patreon.com.
Yeah.
I said I was wrong before the most secure asset class is not actually the United States treasury bonds but actually it's stock in patreon.com.
Because for the low low price of $5 a month you get access to up to what is it like 59 or 58 bonus episodes.
A lot of bonus episodes.
And that's just that's value.
That's value.
Yeah.
You can't withdraw the money but you can withdraw it in the entertainment value you get from the show.
Right.
Unlike an unlike a try unlike the treasury bond you don't have to leave it for a year.
You can get that sweet entertainment right now at the moment as soon as you pledge and it will keep you entertained for that whole year.
While you're waiting while you're waiting for your bonds to mature there's more than 50 episodes so you can every single week go to the US Treasury buy a bond and then every week listen listen to a bonus PCP episode every week for the next year.
And by the time you've listened to them all you can get that you can withdraw you can get that interest.
So that's that's my advice.
I started making coffee made coffee making coffee.
Yeah I usually take caffeine pills you just take my caffeine and pill form.
Oh I thought you meant are you I thought you was going to say you're starting to like handmade like grind your own beans.
Oh God did you did you see the flare up recently of like barista discourse on Twitter.
There's no I didn't.
It's a thing.
Okay it's a thing that happens every now and then.
Every now and then some reactionary psychopath in like nominally leftist Twitter like they claim to be a socialist that you know what one of these fucking like one of these fucking like a patriotic socialist or whatever quote unquote right.
They'll always be like.
Or just every once in a while one of them has a take that's like.
A barista is not a worker a barista is not a part of the working class right because they have blue hair and pronouns because they have tattoos and because they and because being a barista is like.
An easy job that like people with people with you know humanities degrees get in major cities right.
Wow.
Yeah very left very very yes very material analysis.
Hmm yes much much a relation to to to the means of production hmm very very good.
There was a flare up of it like a couple weeks ago so it's like and and you know some idiot is like baristas aren't baristas don't actually make anything.
They don't produce anything they're just they're they're they're PMC you know they're they're they're basically they're basically a bougie or close enough.
And they make the coffee though.
Yeah that's the response it's like that no someone said like they don't actually make the coffee man like like the growers in like Columbia make it right like the people that package it in South America make it the barista doesn't actually make anything.
You just like it's like oh here's your here's your cup of beans sir.
It's like yeah I thought you you were it's like yeah what I what I yes what I meant by I made coffee is that I have become a Colombian farm hand that is like producing the beans because baristas don't actually produce any value actually.
Yeah no I brew I've been brewing coffee because I ran out of pills and I don't want to I don't I don't get more I don't want to walk to CBS.
So I see so I'm doing it the old fashioned way and you know what extracting the caffeine from the coffee and then evaporating the coffee just eating the caffeine.
Snorting the snorting the powder that remains yeah.
It was it was funny I was having I was like oh god.
No that was my last caffeine pill and I'm out of energy drinks.
I'm like oh no where am I where am I going to get more caffeine.
Oh no whatever.
And then I remember like oh like normal focus normal coffee.
Yeah normal normal people drink it in coffee form and there's coffee in my house and there's a coffee maker so I can just use that actually.
I was having a crisis.
That's not like a good coffee.
I'm not really a huge coffee fan.
I'm not a huge coffee drinker but like it's fine.
And so and it's yeah yeah.
It's it's electric dirt.
Yeah I've got a small mason jar of it right here.
I'm going to take another.
Actually I have this jar is just the right size that.
If I fill this jar it's about three or four cups worth which means that that's about as much caffeine as I would get from a caffeine pill.
So that's convenient.
Same amount.
It all it all works out.
Did you ever I've never taken caffeine pills.
Do you get like desensitized to caffeine quicker through pills or is it easier to just take too many of them.
Honestly the worst like caffeine jitters I've ever had were from coffee for from like drinking an entire pot really fast and then I would be like jittery and like feel weird for the rest of the day.
I never got that with pills but it's just because I space space them out.
I think I probably am pretty like desensitized to cat to caffeine.
I think I probably am like probably have a pretty high tolerance to it if there is such a thing.
I think it's definitely a thing.
Yeah.
Like the first time I drank coffee is like what.
And now sometimes you drink a cup of coffee and you just feel okay feel normal.
Something has changed.
Yeah.
I'm probably pretty deep into like caffeine you know dependency addiction whatever you want to call it but like whatever.
That's fine.
Yeah.
It's readily available.
It's readily available and at this point is not much I can do about it.
Like you can't you can you can go like caffeine free and like swear it off.
But it takes a long time and apparently you will never be able to be awake again.
You'll never be fully alert in the same way if you don't have the caffeine again.
I think I've heard but I could be making that up.
There's no way that's true.
What does that mean?
You'll never be awake again.
I mean I said it in a silly way but like the the if you never take caffeine you wake up and you go to bed
and your energy levels are like normal unblemished or whatever.
But if you have caffeine in tea or coffee or energy drinks and you gain a sort of dependence on it.
You can quit and you will crash like you would with lots of other like substances.
But I don't know you'll never uncrash.
You'll you'll get OK.
But you'll never like waking up will be hard forever.
I mean I I think it's I don't know whether that's like a hard because that doesn't sound right.
It seems like it could be a myth because it could just be like people getting older.
Make having it that's finding it more difficult to wake up in the morning.
Yeah that's like that.
Ever seen that is what I heard.
So I don't know.
There's that that scene from Dexter's lab where when Dexter and Dee Dee drink all the coffee in the house
and then their dad wakes up and he's like you drank all the coffee.
We adults need coffee in the mornings.
You kids don't need it.
No you've got you.
So not my youth is gone so I need the coffee now.
So but fortunately I have it so it's fine.
I would not recommend coffee to a youngster.
I feel I've seen people like think it cool and and like epic to have their kids drinking coffee at a young age.
I think it's cool.
Hmm.
Like that is a that is a NASA child abuse right there.
They should be we should be having really like the parents parents that think it's cool to give their kids coffee
because they like coffee.
I don't know.
It's just sort of like you should not really think children should be having.
I mean they have energy.
They don't need it.
I mean it's probably fine.
Like I don't think I'm of the I'm of the my my I'm of the opinion that caffeine is not like particularly bad.
Like yeah kids can have it and it's OK.
But like yeah.
Why it's it's there's no reason but it's also like if you get like a dependence on caffeine
and you'll need it and then without it like you get tired more easily and children usually don't have those problems
but you can introduce those problems at an early age for no reason if they drink coffee early.
It's just like a strange silly thing that I've seen somewhere.
Didn't like it didn't like.
I'm pretty sure that if you just don't drink caffeine for a while you will just return to baseline eventually.
I'm pretty confident that that's that that's the case.
But yeah if you don't need it why why bother with it.
But I'm I'm deep.
I'm deep in the cycle.
I'm I'm I've become one of those.
I've become one of everyone that is to say somebody who starts their day with caffeine and that's OK.
It's normal.
It's not in our society.
It's normalized.
That just makes me normal.
Yep.
Taking a big swig.
All right.
Well that's my that's my coffee spiel.
Man.
Oh yeah.
Go on.
I've been playing Outer Wilds recently.
You heard of that game.
Outer Wilds.
Yeah I've definitely heard of it but I don't know what it is.
It's really good.
It's a game where you are a little alien on a little planet and you are you have this new technology.
They've just invented that can translate ancient alien language.
Go off on your little spaceship.
No man's sky ish.
Very surface level.
OK.
But nothing's randomly generated.
Oh OK.
It's a solar system with mysteries to uncover of an ancient alien race that used to live there.
And you go out with your little space shuttle and land on these planets and the scale of
the planets is more similar to like Mario Galaxy than it is No Man's Sky where you see
a planet and you zoom in and then you're in the atmosphere and you land and it's as
if you're on just any old video game.
But in this in this game if you jump and you use your jet pack most of the time you can
get out of the atmosphere.
You can see the curvature of the Earth.
Yeah.
It's really trippy and cool.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
You you go around.
The thing I really like about it two things one the space traversal is like really intuitive.
You have like the the joystick forward like up and down is using your jet pack or your
ships thrusters forward and backwards left and right is left and right and then to go
up and down is to the the two trigger buttons.
And using that it's it's very easy to get a grip of like how to move in a specific direction
no matter what orientation you're looking at because you're always looking straightforward.
It's a first person game.
So it always makes sense and one like you can lock onto a planet when you're in your
spaceship and it'll tell you like how much further you need to be using the thrusters
to the left or the right or up and down to like be in the right like traveling velocity
is matched.
There's like a button you can hold to match the velocity of the thing you're locked onto
and then you're traveling through space with that thing and then you can sort of like park
your ship in a place where if there's no like large bodies like pulling you around with
gravity you can sort of park your ship next to something such that the velocity is perfectly
matched and you can get out of your ship and fly around with your little jet pack and you
just go back to your ship perfectly perfectly match your velocity to to what to whatever
you've locked onto.
So if you point your crosshairs at a planet you lock onto it you get close to it you
match your velocity.
The sun in the center is always going to be pulling on you a little bit but if you're
far away enough from things.
Wait to land on a planet you have to like match its orbital velocity.
Yeah.
So like you're spinning around you're spinning around the sun with this planet at the same
rate that it is and then you start you you can you know thruster down land on the planet
and then obviously once you're touching the planet you're moving through space because
it's like it's a very compacted area you can zoom from one side of the entire solar system
very quickly and it's very exaggerated like I say you can jump on off some planets.
As any good video game solar system should be.
Yeah and it's you can like jump if you jump at the right time from one planet you can land
on another one with your jet pack.
Oh my god.
That sounds awesome.
That sounds so cool.
It is really good.
It's it's probably my favorite like space traversal like like system and then beyond
that the the mysteries that you can uncover are a really fun and not too cryptic.
They require you to think about like what you're learning and where you can like use
the information you gain from like logs of information from one area and then bring it
to another to solve a mystery so you can get into a specific location.
So is it just one sorry it's just in one solar system that the game takes place.
Yeah it's one solar system.
Okay.
And like if you know where to go it doesn't take long at all but sure figuring out where
to go gathering clues it's sort of like a point and click adventure game I would say.
Yeah.
Where like like an old school one where you're not given a goal other than explore.
We are a race of exploring aliens and we just want to see what's out there and then you
find what's out there and you just keep going.
It's like really cool.
That sounds really cool.
I would highly recommend Outer Wilds.
Oh that's that's that's a little that's enticed me a little bit.
Yeah I might check that out.
Please do.
I'm very close to the end of the game actually.
I didn't want to I don't not spoiling anything with my with my intro here.
Cool.
So so I should be finished.
There's only one mystery left I have to figure out is the place I haven't been able to get
to.
So in the comments don't spoil.
No spoil.
Yeah.
Stupid commenters.
Stupid commenters always spoiling spoiling spoiling spoiling my milk spoiling the my milk
what else can spoil.
That's it.
Bread just just milk.
Bread goes moldy.
Meat meat can spoil.
Oh yeah.
Cheese I wouldn't say cheese cheese doesn't spoil but it gets moldy.
It does.
Meat meat spoils.
Milk spoils I think that's pretty much it.
That's like the only two things I would use the word spoils for.
Yeah.
I have not been playing.
I've not been playing anything.
I've just been there's been pretty much just nose to the grindstone just like editing
editing editing until I can't fucking stand it anymore.
I can't for fucking stand it for fucking.
It's funny when I hear myself stutter in my in my vocals I'm like what an idiot.
It happens sometimes I think it I think it happens the normal amount of times everybody
stutters now and then.
Yes.
There was a man I owned a guy on Twitter yesterday.
Oh fuck yeah bro.
It was this guy who he is is not important except it kind of is but the gist of it is
that he had the most he just unironically in the year of our Lord 2022 unironically
just like if I were Shinji I would have just gotten the Ava and like thought it was really
cool to fight aliens.
Oh yeah I saw that I saw that guy.
That's a stupid bitch.
It's like what was it I rewatched Ava and I don't relate to Shinji.
What a pussy and words to that effect.
Just sort of missing the point.
Why is he so why is he so all I can't relate to the fact that like he's handed the chance
to save the world and all he can do is wallow in self pity.
Like oh my daddy doesn't like me boohoo.
It's almost like it's more it's like metaphorical of stuff and it has themes that are more human
than literal like let's kill the bad guy.
Even if you take it literally he's still the character is like being asked to fucking put
himself in mortal danger and like every time he does it he experiences like horrendous pain
and suffering.
It's like he shouldn't know this wouldn't feel good you moron but imbecile.
Yeah it is it is kind of baffling like that he would come to such stupid conclusions like
if I were Shinji then I would be better and I would win.
I mean it's it's it's baffling and yet it's like it's like a cliche like the like I would
have just I would just get in the robot and fight the aliens and fuck the girls like why
didn't Shinji just do all those things like that's what I would do like oh cool cool bro
happy for you.
He was getting out was like aren't these like I remember one of them.
That's like Mark Wahlberg saying that if he was on the plane he would have prevented 9-11.
Yeah if I was on that plane the terrorists wouldn't have won.
It was like he said like I get that it's like I understand the show but and then he says
he doesn't understand the show.
Yeah it was a tweet that was just sort of like I get it but but he doesn't get it.
He definitely does not get it.
I'm gonna find that.
It's a take that you we've all seen it before it's just surprising to see it I don't know
people are saying like damn this is this is like a it's like I'm back on Tumblr in 2008
like in someone's post and like I would just get in the robot if I was Shinji I would I would be like
hell yeah hell yeah I'll get in that cool robot like damn this guy's behind the discourse.
I think I've seen this I've seen this guy before by the way this is not the first time
I've seen a tweet of his this guy has had bad takes before but this one might take the cake
honestly could yeah I guess if he's done it before I was gonna say it could be like oh
a new generation of idiots are coming up and we've all seen these stupid things before
but they haven't and now they're doing it again the history is repeating itself and we were all
here to witness it for a second time.
Oh did oh did I ratio him almost I've almost I've almost achieved ratio parity with his
original tweet with my reply here I'll post the link for Eleazar I guess the this guy yeah
I've seen this guy before this guy is like no joke this guy is like a French like Christo
fascist who like works for a DC based like lobbying group that's like wants to implement the
Christian equivalent of Sharia law in like American government like this guy's like yeah
haha this guy had a funny Evangelion take and he's stupid but like he's a he's a literal
demon and he doesn't deserve to continue to draw breath is is is I mean I could have
told you that by the fact that he's got the little check mark oh yes and even worse and
worse than all that he's verified on Twitter yeah so you know I hate I hate this guy and
he's just here's just one more excellent reason I'm sorry if I'm treating you because you
watched it at an age where you were like he's just like me for real for real but it's just
not a great piece of filmmaking oh yeah and then like I mean filmmaking it's a character
like he's criticizing the character and now he's saying the film he's saying that he's
saying it's a bad it's a bad show he did a he did a thread about it and then he made
like an eight or nine post-thread and then when he saw that like he was getting ratioed
he added like 20 more posts to the thread yeah his takes on it are like it's just objectively
bad filmmaking though like like you're supposed you're supposed to relate to the
protagonist and the fact that I didn't relate to the protagonist because he has a problem
right because he feels negative emotions in a in a scary situation like that made it
unrelatable to me and therefore it's just objectively bad filmmaking right like and and
all and all and all the she her pronoun people are telling me otherwise are just triggered
he immediately went to like oops looks like I've triggered I've triggered the libs with
my with my shitty Evangelion tape oh yeah this is parody he says I get I get that it's
about being an angsty teenager right it isn't though it's not about being an angsty teenager
that's not what the show is about I mean I don't I don't see why I mean even if it is
about that I mean Shinji is that but like I don't I don't see it's more about abuse than
it is about angst like lots of characters can have angst but Shinji is fucked because of
his horrible bad and various other things right yeah it's about a lot more than just
remember being a teenager remember when you want your teacher said you had to do your
homework and you didn't want to shit Shinji Shinji is not like a normal kid there are
there are other normal kids that you can compare him to in the show and like you can see you
can very clearly see like no this is a kid with some with some specific shit that he's
trying to work through you can bet that if I had been plucked from obscurity at age 13
by a secret government organization to become a badass alien fighting pilot I wouldn't
have been like whoa is me just unironically I would have just I would have been like hell
yeah I would have been a much better child soldier than Shinji why I wouldn't have been
a pussy like Shinji I would have fought those aliens man I don't know I would have been
like fuck yes I'm finally being recognized like he's just that's a little sad that's
just sad like he I think he's he's like maybe he's seen anime where the main character is
a nerdy loser who gets transported isekai and then he's the coolest bad guy badass ever
and that's a you know an obvious power fantasy thing neon Genesis Evangelion is not a power
fantasy it's just such a stupid like expectation that he has he in one of these he says like
yeah yeah I would yeah I would have been like fuck yes I'm finally being recognized isn't
that isn't that the whole point of these types of fantasies like like there's only one thing
that an anime can be and it's a self-insert fantasy for like the fact the fact that Evangelion
is not a straightforward power fantasy self-insert thing is like well well it didn't work you
know it was it was trying to be this thing and it and it didn't do it so it wasn't good
and and like I just I just don't know how to as I say as I say this person is this person
is not only a moron this this person is evil this person is objectively evil in a terrible
human being so it's not surprising that a terrible take flowed forth from them but they
are also they are they are also stupid because their reasoning behind it is like just fucking
like child child level child level media literacy going on here anyway I hate it yeah yeah fortunately
like ton is fortunately he's French so most of his tweets I can't read is he French he
is or he lives in France yeah he's French he seems to speak a lot of history and yeah
he speaks in I mean you can tell in the original tweet he gets like the the tense wrong on a
couple of adjectives or whatever he they don't decline correctly and like that's fine yeah
he's French you see on his on his timeline most of more than a you know a significant
amount of his tweets are in French so that's whatever and yet he works for a DC based a
like a Christian lobbying collective or whatever which is weird well I thought DC like the
comics no no like Washington DC yes yeah Washington DC comics yes my favorite that's all my
that's all my hastily written notes about things that happened this week yeah you know what I
have one last thing that is it's a very stupid thing it's it will only take a second I don't
know where Philadelphia is in what state it is I know Philadelphia is a place where will
smish will smish will smish will smish will smish was born and raised on the playground is where
you spend most of his days but in West Virginia but like Philadelphia but where is it I think
it's in Pennsylvania Pennsylvania you probably don't know where Pennsylvania is either I mean
it's east coast not coast but close east area it's like it's like not okay I mean yeah there's
the there's America and then there's the east coast and like the northern part the northern
most part of the east coast is New England that's like Maine and New Hampshire and Vermont
and Massachusetts and Rhode Island and Connecticut and I think that's it and then if you go sort
of west from there you eventually hit the Great Lakes and sort of the area like on south of
the Great Lakes and just to the east of the Great Lakes that's what's called the Rust Belt
and Pennsylvania is kind of in that in the region between like New England and the Rust Belt
because because I hear I hear like Las Vegas, Nevada, Chicago, Illinois like but nobody ever
says nobody ever says Philadelphia Pennsylvania because it's got too many syllables I guess it
does have a lot of syllables yeah no you're right I think I think I feel you on that one
I think I didn't know what state it was in for a while
all right thank god that I'm not stupid
no I even like passed through it like when I my commute or not my commute my trip to and from college
back in the day I used to go through Philadelphia and I still was like I didn't you know how do you
know you're in Pennsylvania you don't honestly honestly yeah the whole like Rust Belt New
England like area it's like all these states just kind of go together and it's like am I in New
Jersey am I in New York am I in Pennsylvania am I in Connecticut at Rhode Island at whatever
it's all just fucking it's all just fucking there man it's all just mashed together who gives a
shit it's all just woods all just landmass soon to be destroyed by hurricanes no borders
abolish abolish ice from going to from from New Hampshire to to Maine what do they have up there
Maine is yeah yeah Maine is the the top the top or most the top or most one where all the
lobsters live and the moose the rain in Maine falls mostly on the Spain the that's how you know
that's how you know you're in Maine as you go and you see moose well I guess I guess they have moose
in like Vermont too they have maple syrup in Vermont they have lobsters in Maine they have beans
in Massachusetts they have Dells lemonade in Rhode Island they have cookies in Maryland cookies
because the Maryland brand cookies are popular over here so I know Maryland cookies I don't
even know I don't even know if you have I'm not even familiar with that no let me type that
that's an export oh from exotic from exotic I mean the the British probably hear that
like oh like Queen Mary I love the Queen yeah remember her remember remember Queen Mary no
image of the original Maryland cookies what the fucker what the fuck are these the hell is this
they're fucking Maryland cookies I don't even know their chocolate chip cookies they're from
Maryland they're probably made in in Beijing no it can't be I don't know no no not not all right
well now we got to find out because if they're not even an American thing that would be very funny
and they're they're probably there might be more than one place called Maryland might be
other yeah may well Maryland cookies are a brand name of cookie produced by Burton's biscuit
company in the United Kingdom that's so funny Burton's biscuit company is a British biscuit
manufacturer but why but yeah why are they called that why are they called that they started
making chocolate chip cookies cold Maryland cookies in 1956 but why but why it's literally
just like this is this is cultural appropriation this is like when that white lady made a cookbook
about dumplings and noodles and it was really racist of her this is this is like your that's
what you're doing to me there's only one sentence of background information I was under the impression
that the reason we call like cookies we consider the word cookie to be chocolate chip cookies
is because the popularity of Maryland cookies being specifically chocolate chip and then the fact
that you call all biscuits cookies was confusing to us but they were always done this to yourself
we've done it to us and we've gaslit ourselves into being stupid this is this is a massive
revelation and why is there no information about it I think you've mentioned this before
and I think I have you know what you I think you I didn't know what you were talking about
I guess we just didn't get into it at the time I just maybe you just assumed it was a brand you
weren't aware of yeah if you search Maryland cookies some of the suggested result is our
Maryland cookies American answer no right our story I'm on there I'm on Burton's biscuit company
since the very beginning our story has been about baking really great biscuits that people love
here I found a CBS news article called there's a UK cookie named after oh my god what I thought it
was gonna make me not I thought it was gonna add block me so I couldn't read the article but no
yeah there's a popular cookie in the UK and it's named after Maryland
there's there's no explain no there's no explanation as to why it's just like hey did you know this
exists okay bye I guess it could in Mexico in Mexico there's a great flavored soda called
Delaware punch what the fuck exotic Delaware our brands tell me about your brands tell me
about Maryland cookies find out more you're not gonna tell me anything are you now it's
just all the things you can sell well it's not it's not carbonated so it's not why do they call
it soda Delaware okay the brand is currently owned by Coca-Cola company but it has been
discontinued the Wikipedia article Delaware punch doesn't show like the branding or anything
it just shows it like a cup of it I want to see like what the bottle looks like bro weak I'm
so I it's not just that it's like oh it's English it's that there's no reason I thought there
would be like a like oh the I got the recipe from there I'm a resident like it's hot there
there must be a story behind it or like the if there's no story behind it then like the
only explanation must be like there must have been something that made them think that calling
them Maryland cookies would make them appealing and like I mean Maryland is a cute word I suppose
I suppose but like I have no idea what that it was an American place okay okay check this out
Delaware punch is named for the Delaware grape so it's like sort of named after the fruit that
it's flavored from so like okay there is there is a reason for that it's not named after
Delaware the state it's named after the Delaware grape a cultivar derived from the grape species
whatever blah blah blah blah blah yeah I found the same yeah but okay I'm gonna I'm gonna
directly ask Google why are they called Maryland cookies you've found that like a lot of news
articles are barely more than a tweet these days they're just nothing in them there's no journalism
going on they're just mentioning something I found out with the BBC recently just sometimes the BBC
mentions that there's things happening and that's it there's no like why is it happening at all
it's like okay why why you what there was this thing that was going on where like there was
disturbance there were people being disturbing and Lester and police were making many arrests
and I couldn't get any information from the BBC as to what was being fought over who was fighting
why were they fighting and I had to go elsewhere and it was like oh there's like a war there's kind
of a complicated ethnic like like fight between Hindus and Muslims in the area and it sort of
got sparked from a cricket game that went that turned into a riot of some kind or like a punch
up and it's like it's a lot more complicated but the BBC had no information about any of that
they didn't even seem to care to to look into it they just said the police have made many arrests
the police say the disturbance will be contained the end excellent how reassuring it's just like okay
where's the journalism I kind of like journalism when it's interesting like like I want to find
out stuff I want to know I found another article that's about Marilyn cookies but it's not about
it mentions they were made in the UK but it's not like it doesn't explain it it just it goes on to be like
here's how we handled a like you like the the marketing the launch of like a new flavor or something
so nothing no help there's a new mystery there's a new mystery that needs solving
oh well some some things man mankind is just not meant to know some things I was gonna go to
Maryland and I was gonna say where's the cookie factory and they say what's a cookie we don't know
that they're like official website I did I'm gonna go to oh you did okay that there was nothing
there it's just sort of like here's the different we got the Maryland cookie hazelnut the the mini
cookies isn't it cool wouldn't you like to buy them oh they make jammy Dodgers as well oh they do
didn't realize they have it on there have it on their brand those dammy Dodgers I made wagon wheels
yeah dude you have dammy Dodgers and wagon wheels oh I saw a post I saw a post maybe it was this week
it was from Java Giga and it was about like I don't know it basically just posted like a like a wall
of like different hostess products and was like can't believe none of these tastes good now that I'm a grown
up and like I actually hadn't tried a lot of them like I've never had donut sticks I've never had
there's there's a lot of them that I don't know it's dicks yeah donuts donuts dicks I think some I think
some of them though I think some hostess stuff would probably still taste good but a lot of them yeah
I probably think would taste like shit now cosmic brownies or shit there were there were a lot of cosmic
brownie defenders in the comments and those people are stupid cosmic brownies have always been shit
they've never they were never even good even when you were good actually that's just an objective fact
I don't really because I just don't I just don't relate to cosmic brownies like why are they why are they such
hostesses why do they have to why do they have little little stars on them like I would just I would
just I would just pilot the the cookies I would just I would just jump in your mouth stars or no
I'm looking more at the Burton's biscuit apparently they own the rights to Marmite or they make Marmite
biscuits gross like like a savory mark I can't imagine what that tastes like but they have a funny did you
know section I said Marmite is the number one most confiscated food product at London City Airport
why I don't know they they're just isn't that interesting people bring in Marmite and it gets confiscated
they can't get enough they can't get enough of it they want to get confiscated it says that on their website
yeah what I mean is that yeah I see it Marmite is the number but like I mean is that good maybe it's like
people really want to bring Marmite on the plane but it's in a container of liquid that is too large
and you can't have liquids that are that large in a container I've never had Marmite but I've had
Vegemite and I feel like it's kind of the same thing it's it's similar ish I think I've had Vegemite once
and it was just sort of like yeah that's that's that's the sort of like weird tangy sticky flavor yeah Marmite is
probably stronger I think I see well yeah I had Vegemite once and I was like you know they told me like only
use a little bit of it so I only used a little bit and I was like hmm yeah kind of like salty tangy fermented flavor
wasn't wasn't super into it you gotta have Marmite but maybe I could get but I thought maybe I could get used to it
on a crumpet yeah crumpet a butted crumpet with Marmite on top that's the best place for Marmite for me
I did have a crumpet once and I liked it I thought it was very funnily enough I thought the crumpet was very similar to
an English muffin which I guess they don't have in England um oh yeah you've got Maryland cookies we've got English muffins
yeah I was gonna say that but I think we did I had an English muffin for like for breakfast so I guess they do sell them here
I don't know where they're from though it would be funny if they are from America
well we got to find out now we got to find out this is a huge network
I think oh it's not a brand it's just a thing so where is it from yeah um
origin is there is there a Wikipedia article yes there is
oh it's a very old thing
the bell ringing of muffin men became so common that by 1839 the British parliament passed a bill to prohibit bell ringing by muffin men
but it was not a deal to my sellers in 1861 good quote unquote good sized muffins from street sellers were commonly sold for a half penny each
crumpets were about a penny okay so a crumpet costs twice as much as an English muffin
what the fuck which part did you oh bell ringing
yeah they're orange muffin men were bell ringing is prohibited for muffin men
you know it makes sense the muffin man like an old timey and then okay and it wasn't it wouldn't have been like they're extremely sugary muffins that we know of
that I think of because that's sugar is quite expensive so
yeah I guess I never I never thought about it okay so I didn't even know this that yeah a muffin man was just something you call just like a guy who sold like cakes little little confections
little little muffins street a street vendor yeah okay
English muffins are sometimes referred to simply as muffins in the UK well that's not true American style muffins are occasionally referred to as American muffins
no not for me when I think of muffin I think of the American style sugary like like sploado out the little cupcake thing
from the from the Seinfeld episode with top of the muffin two year top of yeah
you've seen that you've seen that one I haven't I haven't seen Seinfeld
I think it's I think it's a late you've never seen Seinfeld like at all
no I've never gotten around to it was never like on TV when I was young we had friends on all the time and like
and I guess I never really watched much friends I'm pretty sure Seinfeld is better than friends I think I'm confident friends is is boring
I didn't I never was into friends that much I just when I was young it was just so like I love that theme song and then people talk and there's a love track and I assume it's funny
God Fresh Prince was actually good I love Fresh Prince the increasing popularity of flatbread muffins is attested by the existence of muffin men a type of
hawker who would travel door to door selling English muffins as a snack bread before most homes have their own man before most homes of their own ovens
I imagine someone today like going door to door like would they come up and knock on your door imagine getting a knock on your door and it's someone like hey you want to buy some muffins
I mean I guess like Girl Scouts still do that kind of thing yeah that would annoy the shit out of me
um I mean you're not you're not a muffin boy you don't like muffins I guess I it's not that I don't it's just it's one of those like people coming to your door
is just a thing that doesn't happen unless you've ordered something and to be delivered yeah yeah I guess back in the day maybe it was just more
it's more communal especially if it's like in a city and everyone's like in like tiny apartments really close together
yeah it's just like it's me the muffin man down the old cobble street get your muffins
a well-known reference to English muffins is an Oscar Wilde 1895 play the importance of being earnest
um I'm still not seeing like why why these muffins in particular are called English muffins
well hang on something the man
I guess they're just called it to distinguish them from the American style I guess
Samuel Bath Thomas I guess that's the same reason that everyone else calls it American football
using his mother's recipe began making English muffins in 1880 in New York selling them to hotels
they were soft and spongy before baking like traditional muffins appears to be fork split prior to toasting blah blah blah
they became popular as an alternative to toast something something muffin house
all I'm saying is just that when I think of a crumpet I think of like oh it's just an it's an inside out English muffin
English muffin with no crust that's what I think of a crumpet is
the answer to the question then is it was from an Englishman who emigrated to the US that the term for the current understood English muffin product
he branded them as English muffins because muffins were already a thing
yes and apparently that today the company is owned by Bimbo Bakery's USA
no way
Bimbo Bakery's USA let me see
that's like is that like fanboy Hooters Bimbo Bakery
yeah I don't know
is the American corporate north of the border armor of the Mexican multinational Bakery
Grupo Bimbo
I want to go to Bimbo Bakery that sounds awesome
so there's a Mexican multinational Bakery product manufacturing company called Grupo Bimbo
and they now own the English muffin north of the border
you're jerking me around here
Grupo Bimbo
you're telling me that Maryland cookies are British and English muffins are Mexican
English muffins are owned currently by a Mexican company
oh look at this Bimbo Bakery's Spanish pronunciation Bimbo
so it's the same
yeah Grupo Bimbo
Grupo Bimbo
hell yeah
well what can I say other than fantastic
how do we get on this subject from crumpets
I have no idea
you said you mentioned a crumpet
oh it's called Maryland cookies and I forget why I brought those up
oh well
well we sure have learned
we sure have learned a lot
the Bimbo Bakery's is probably my favorite
what do they make anything else besides
soccer sponsorship
Sarah Lee acquisition
wait it agreed to acquire the North American fresh bakery business
okay so it acquired part of the Sarah Lee corporation
in 2010 okay
uh
oh they make Bimbo Bakery makes Arnold stuff
they make Entenmans
no shit
I love Entenmans
well they own Entenmans
right yeah that's a brand of
under the Bimbo umbrella
oh wow okay
I have not heard of a lot of these other
oh JJ Nissen I know that one
pretty a producer of bread commonly found in New England okay
um
fucking
Bimbo slang
oh they make Thomas's
oh my god yeah
when I think English muffin the brand I think of is Thomas's
and yeah it turns out Bimbo owns Thomas's
so yeah there you go
wow
Bimbo Supremacy
Bimbo Supremacy yeah absolutely
honestly honestly I love English muffins
they're a favorite
they're a favorite of mine
yeah so I mean good good for them
just one more reason to love Bimbo's I guess
damn
wait a minute wait a minute
stop hold on
it says that the company was founded in 1998
which company
Bimbo Bakery's
or maybe that's the
well it's the north of the border
arm of the Grupo Bimbo so
oh okay okay
so Grupo Bimbo if you go to that page
Grupo Bimbo was back from like 1945
and they did a lot
wow they've received accolades
oh wow look at all there's the accolades section
of the Grupo Bimbo Wikipedia page
they've received accolades
every year since 2011
that's very impressive of them
oh for the fourth time in 2020
for the fourth time in a row
Ethosphere Institute recognized Grupo Bimbo
as one of the world's most ethical companies
how about that
wow that's
doesn't that make you think
man I'm getting hungry damn it
shit I'm getting really hungry now
um
you wanna go to voicemails
sure
okay
well I've downloaded
them all but we can just listen to them
oh my god are there a lot more
there's
there's honestly less than there used to be
there used to be all like
wait a minute I have it set to 100 per
there's
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20 21
you do 3 to 4
5 to 6 to 7 to 8 to 9
there's 30 but like a lot of them are just spam
okay
alright so I think the first one is called
cell are you ready
uh yes
alright 3 2 1 go
uh
pro-grastinatus
it is I
perfectly continent cell
I have been engineered by Dr.Gerot
using the fecal matter of the most elite warriors
in this universe to be the next
step in evolution
the perfect life form
you foolish podcasters
have a long and stubborn
history of refusing to shit
this holy
icon
freely from my lower abdomen
is not a sign of shame
but the indicator of my complete
and not a superiority of
your entire species
hmm okay
very impressive
no
you know
I've never seen the cell saga
I've seen early
DBZ and I've seen like the boo
saga ending of it
I've never seen the gohan
cell stuff
I quite liked cell
I liked him less when he was perfect cell
and they did the tournament
and then they fight and they win
the whole android stuff
with the
and the red ribbon army
things
it's quite good
and then trunks coming back
and using a sword
I didn't have cable
as a kid so when we finally got cable
that was the first time I could watch
DBZ and it was
it was all the way in the boo
era so that was when I started
watching it
and like I heard about the older stuff
but I went back and I
rewatched just the very beginning of it
the Frieza bits
next one is called hey Ben
new fan here who is
Trixie and why is it funny they
sorry
didn't finish your question so
I can't answer
next one is called
hashtag bring
Trixie back I assume it's from the same person
who doesn't know who she is
but nevertheless wants her back
next one is
sim card no sim card
no service okay
next one is called hypothetical NFTs
here's a real one
3 2 1 go
an artist I followed was approached and asked to make an NFT of one of their works
the artist explained to the perspective
by that it was a dumb idea
wouldn't really provide value wasn't a good investment
and would be bad for the environment
the perspective by acknowledges this and still offered
tens of thousands of dollars so the artist
accepted the money created the NFT
and spent a good chunk of the proceeds over
correcting for the carbon emitted through carbon offsets
this isn't an offer but as a hypothetical
would you be comfortable creating and selling an NFT
in a situation like that
I'm sorry tens of thousands of dollars
for
for one NFT
I guess
I mean I know that they have
if
hypothetically
if hypothetically you could offset
the
the negative
the carbon emission stuff
I think the difficulty
is just that it
existing
legitimizes NFTs further
which does generally more damage
than you can just pay for
this is not
a scenario that I've ever heard of
I've never heard of like
an NFT guy comes to an artist
and says hey artist I will give you
tens of thousands of dollars right now
if you will let me
mint your
piece
one piece of yours
I've never heard I don't believe it
I just don't think that happens
if anything they would steal the art
and just make the NFT anyway
the money in NFTs
is from doing the big
drops of like the big sets
of you know the
algorithmically generated
the character sets
yeah
but they say it's a hypothetical
so in the hypothetical scenario
I would still feel a little iffy about it
because the
the overall effect is not merely
the one transaction
the transactions will continue
if the thing gets traded a lot
for its lifetime an NFT
will rack up
gas costs
it's just like I'd rather it not exist
I mean
okay
but like I don't think one
NFT
is like
tens of thousands of dollars in damage
to the environment
I think honestly yeah I think
if someone gave me tens of thousands
of dollars to make one NFT
yeah I think I could live with myself
yeah
it would be their problem
I don't think they meant that the environment cost would be 10,000
but like you would get money
and some of that could be used to offset the
carbon
damage
I wouldn't feel bad about minting one NFT
like I wouldn't think that that was like
a terrible crime that I had committed
or anything yeah I would accept
I would accept thousands of dollars
for someone to mint one NFT
because like it's not because it's not going to keep selling
like
I know it's a waste of resources
but like
these things are not
going to continue to circulate
nobody's going to give a shit
yeah
I guess you'd have to balance like
I would just think that that buyer was wasting their money
I would think they were a sucker
and a sap and I would let them
pay me for essentially nothing
sure why not
I
that's just not how it works
that's just not how it works in practice
no it's not how it works
I think there's more damage
I don't know whether it's like worth
like the damage to your reputation
is it worth thousands of dollars
if people think you're an NFT shill
would you lose thousands of dollars worth
of new potential work
I don't know how to like gauge that
well in the described scenario
I wouldn't go on Twitter and advertise
NFT because I'd already have the money
and I wouldn't need to do that
but like the thing would be an NFT
would they not like
say from Ben St
Ben St original
NFT official
I would just say
okay
maybe this guy
he goes to his
social media and he proclaims
guys I have minted
an artwork made by Ben St
that Ben St piece that everybody
loves so much it's on the blockchain
you can buy the NFT of it
I would I mean
I would just say like yeah
I let him do that because he gave me
tens of thousands of dollars and like
I don't
I like for for nothing
I don't know
that's that's it
I mean I don't think it would sell
but even if it did
like okay whatever
I don't know I don't
I wouldn't I would not I would not become
an NFT shill because I don't believe
in the NFT business model
but if someone
but if someone big gave me a bunch of money
to make to make an NFT
like what one and done
thing that I never have to
think about again sure
I mean I think
the root of this is like this guy's
asking could
NFTs be good if
hypothetical like scenario
is favorable to you
I'm like well yeah
if there were no problem
with like the
carbon emissions
and all of the other things that make NFTs
stupid I wouldn't mind honestly
you've described a very specific
scenario
where the where the deck is stacked
such that like this NFT transaction
is very favorable
and it's just it's just doesn't
really buy
and large it doesn't go like that
I think that answers the question
yes okay
next one is an
Imgur album
every squad got
and it's a bunch of it's the PCP
the
the dyke the racist
the Italian
this motherfucker
the funny one American serial killer
every squad got American serial killer
endless jest
the fat bitch I look cool here
the Sasuke
the motherfucking
a roach
what the fuck
this must be based on something else
something else
oh no it's it's definitely a meme I've seen
not with these specific terms
but just sort of like every squad
every squad has the list of completely
insane things that
not every squad actually has
I've seen the every squad got
the I've seen that format before
but like these choices are so specific
they must be
based on a specific like iteration
of that
other like why would they why would they put
why would they put Jeff
well I mean
if I were to vote
nine PCP members I would go with
this must be because it matches
some whatever
was here in the original version
yeah maybe
I like how I look in this
that's a good eye
I like how I look as well I think that looks awesome
look at that slime
delicious
like Nate's
shiny forehead
yeah you've kind of got like
one of those big
like reggae
beanies
is that what that is?
it just sort of like it bloops backwards and then
there's a whole other lump underneath
like a big big big
I don't wear a hat like that
in real life but I mean
I could
next one is called hey Ben new fan here
are you getting the new call of duty
I can't wait
yeah
yeah bro
your recording was too short
we couldn't hear the end of it
next Ben's weekly reminder
play delta ring chapter two okay
Ben's weekly reminder catch up to one piece
okay
next one is I love that Trixie
blammed youtube for her channel
failing
let's do one go
is that called corona
mmm
I mean we all know cold corona
was transformed by the trans beam
in the events of
road to radcon
and became corona Chan
aka the corona virus so
yes who knows what could have happened
since then
um
did Trixie blame youtube for her channel
failing I didn't watch that video
uh she did she did
meant
I wouldn't say that she like exclusively
blamed it but she did say that like
yeah youtube doesn't promote
my videos anymore and that's why I can't
uh she did she did mention
it as a reason yeah
it's just really like
man a
do you know who jack saint is
uh twitter man I don't know
what he does well he is a twitter man
I mean he was a youtube man I mean he
still is a youtube man he was away for a while
but he's back to making videos yeah I saw
I saw him um saying
like youtube is suppressing my new video
I
thought it was cringe I thought it was a little cringe
I like I like that guy and I
have liked his videos before but
uh yeah it is it is
kind of a video yeah his new video
was first of all he said so like
literally like one hour after the video
went live he was like I'm looking at the
metrics and I'm sure that the youtube is suppressing
it and it's like
I mean it might
be it might be not pushing it as
hard as usual because it doesn't like
the the title or the keyword or something
like that sure that kind of thing does happen
I mean a lot of the time it could be because
of lack of frequency of uploads
and doesn't push the new
one quite so much I mean I know
that it's funny because these things
are true to a certain extent
but it's so weird to blame
them when you don't actually know why
you can you can you can make inferred
guesses but it seems
kind of like pointless
to blame the algorithm for a video
not working when it could just
be that people aren't interested
I yeah I look
in looking at that
I
kind of thought that like there were probably
other explanations for why that video
wasn't doing well then why
then that like some sort of
yeah he's he seemed to say
that like youtube was deliberately
suppressing it because it was about
youtube creator burnout and like
I kind of think that what's more
likely there is just maybe
maybe youtube
maybe youtube doesn't like it when you call
a video something about
youtube burnout like it might not like that
title the algorithm might think that
that's like bad I could
believe that that I could also just believe
that like people aren't that interested
in watching a video about a youtuber
explaining like how they got
burned out because like who cares
it yeah
yeah so a lot of people
do it a lot of people fall into
that trap and it's
kind of dumb and like there's a little
truth to it but there's a little
truth it's just not enough truth to like
I think it's true
so much less
like it's true so much less often than
it's claimed
yeah I would
I would assume
I would assume that is
complained about more
and well the thing is that
even if it's justified
I'm not interested in people
complaining about it
it just annoys me a little
yeah
the thing about it does not make the youtube
algorithm like you more
it is not a solution to this problem
whining to youtube will never do anything
we know this
just continually make videos
I mean youtube is harsh
the algorithm is harsh
it's a little bit but people can still
I mean honestly yeah people can still
find your videos and honestly
whenever I see that it's like
this is definitely the case
for when Trixie did it it's like
hey I'm being suppressed by the algorithm
like my videos are not
being shown to people like what that actually
means is just the algorithm
is not boosting me anymore the algorithm
is not helping me and pushing me the way it used
to right the algorithm can
push you and boost you and put your video
in front of other people but it can't
it can't stop people from
finding your video if they want to
watch it right
so like
it just it's not
like youtube is hiding your video
it's that youtube isn't
promoting it which is not
the same thing
I think it's wrong
to see it like
oh youtube is artificially suppressing me
it's more like youtube is no longer
artificially boosting me
that's the difference
and that's what I hear when I see people complain about that
I mean I have heard reports
of like certain
keywords being said in a video
will cause it to be like
blacklisted or certain creators
to be blacklisted like
Alex Jones or something for things he
says and then they target them and I'm like
okay I can see that it's probably
what do you mean by blacklisted?
blacklisted meaning that it's hard to find
even if you type in their name
there'll be videos that come up
that are not of them but are about
them by other people
and I'm like okay well that's
potentially a thing I think
it's usually annoying to me because
it's an individual complaining about their
specific situation rather than
a video talking about
all of the available evidence and what we
actually do know for sure
and what is most likely
and least likely on a larger
scale I think I would be interested in a video
about the algorithm
with that but
largely we just can't know
cause it's this
insane black box
and that's deliberate
like the algorithm is deliberately
mysterious they don't want us to know how it
works I think you can
in hindsight find out
what the algorithm was doing
you can't really figure it out currently
you need a lot of
reference points
a lot of data
to come up to a conclusion and individuals
saying that they think their thing
is being suppressed I'm like I just don't know
whether you know what you're talking about
what's more likely
that that's
really happening
or just that the algorithm
has de-favored you
in a way that makes you think it's happening
and the latter is just more likely
most of the time
it requires extraordinary evidence
to really demonstrate like yes
this is a deliberate conspiracy by YouTube
to
suppress my content
yep
okay
next one is called happy birthday Ben
okay thank you
the next one after that is called an innocent request
for the host Ben Sains
from give i love you at givemail.love
3, 2, 1, go
hi Ben Sains
why don't you suck my butt
hmm
why don't I
yeah why don't you Ben
I have no answer I can't think of an answer
so
I mean
I guess I should
I should be sucking your butt
thanks for the voicemail
uh
next one is called
trad yig mayfuckers
from beat my ass at like
drum
3, 2, 1, go
yo
Winnie the Pooh
is growing up
do you think it's like
going through
poo
poo bear
pee
yeah
do I think that Winnie the Pooh is going up
through poo bear
pee
oh poo
but poo bear
oh he's growing up through poo bear tea
ohhhh
okay
okay he did something
yeah very good
I didn't catch it but you got it
hey man good job
good voicemail
don't talk with your mouth full
yeah
one criticism would be don't talk with your mouth full
other than that you know solid
voicemail
pain
3, 2, 1, go
pain, misery
and more pain
pain
it's the year 2021
then saint imperial calendar
month 3, pain
day 13, pain
after his kidney stolen
he yielded many clones
pain
they proceeded to rape and pillage our lands
governments fell apart
the world collapsed
pain
world order is in chaos
we all live in shacks
me my neighbors, pain
misery
everyone lives in shacks
he sends his clones out twice a week to piss test everyone
everyone
everyone lives in shacks
everyone everyone everyone lives in pain
if you find someone not on keto
pain
i think to myself you know water's keto friendly
he's on his throne drinking bang energy
and we just get monster zero
pain
after everything collapses
he takes your enterprises, becomes best guy ever
locks you in a cell and you only get pain
and he laughs every time
he loves pain
pcp
pain
destroy his kidney stones
kill ben saint
yeah
i was waiting for it to go
pa pa pa pa pa pa
he didn't do it
i mean what can i say
other than i agree
yes
next one is called
mikey tyke
one go all right so my the math book and I wasn't sure if the message quality
was great so I'm gonna record this one again this is a thread this is not a
voicemail well if you don't not let my if you don't let my fucky bastard
don't have the weed out fucking minion message just constantly man that's
just not about it
I mean these are these are you know there's artistry to these but like they
don't say anything no they're like well the YouTube poop like audio logs that
you would find in a in fallout something like that I think there's another one
here cuz the next one is called duh oi duh three two one go hello it is I
don't Jesus again and I think I might have messed up a little bit ever since I
released the mate messman this track which is completely destroyed best guy
ever he will never recover in shambles it seems that the PCP voice fail and also
the Kiwi farms have gone down and that's not very good also my son the baby
he died Jesus and that's also not good so I was wondering I would say those are
equally bad
god the audio quality on that was horrible did you hear it like ringing yeah
he was inside a cave he was inside it like a long tube it was like that whatever
he was speaking there was like a just barely audible like like like like like
dog whistle like high-pitched sound accompanying it sounded like horrible but
anyway how do I deal with not having a child very carefully oh yeah it can happen
at any moment good sorry about your loss did you the Kiwi farms is down I we
not mention that when that happened I don't know if we did mention it I admit
I admit I do miss it a little bit because I would occasionally check up of the
Trixie thread and just see what I know I didn't post in it but I did check it
occasionally I acknowledge that it's probably you know a good thing on the
whole that it's gone but yeah I have I have I did now I have one less thing
that I read now so it's it's never good to like fester I would say
yeah it's probably better this way for me even for just for me personally it's
probably better a clean a clean break yes not that there was going to be any news
about that ever again I mean well now they've got wee wee farms the new site
is that true no I don't know I mean they're doing something
last I checked there was still no it was still gone but I heard some people saying
that it was just moving somewhere so they definitely would want to because what else
Joshua moon seemed confident that it was gonna come back actually wait I mean let me let me
just check no
yeah it doesn't seem to be working so I guess it's still down that's good no it's good it's
good it's definitely good let there be no doubt that I think kiwi farms is bad and it's good that
it's gone uh I just I'll just need to find something else to something else to do with
you know whatever whatever amount of time I might have spent I might have spent reading it
uh he's got to wean myself off that so that's fine um next one is where was I am
son of Marowak son of Marowak yes three two one go
hey Ben congratulations on shaving your head this may be the first time but I hope that
it won't be the last time oh yeah may every week bring you bliss with every hair removed
congratulations welcome to the bald club oh yeah I've met son of Marowak he's bald as well
so you're in the bald club now you know it's been it's been like maybe three or four days since
I reshaved my head and it's it's so it's it's actually it's actually quite a bit it actually
requires maintenance to maintain the like smooth bald and instead of just having like yeah you got
you really got to keep on it it grows back quite fast um all you got to do is uh add like tons of
stress into your life to get all those hairs to fall out for good now now we're talking now we're
concentrated stress pills um the um yeah self self the thing you want to avoid is self care
actually yeah you want to avoid self care you want to get cancer that'll that'll speed oh yeah that's
the I mean if you can get that then like yeah probably you can probably just take chemo without
having cancer and just get the effects of the hair falling out anyway I think so I don't I don't
see why not it would just be like very expensive and for no reason sure sure and like but you know
whatever doctors doctors have to do it if you tell them you want it they have to give it to you
they they took an oath so uh there you go easy it's problem solved next one is Son of Marowak
the second one three two one go oh well you can tell I didn't finish listening to the episode
congratulations on shaving your head at least the second time at least you got the first time
whatever uh either way again oh right I did it once before again may you keep shaving your head
for many days to come uh I will continue I'll do it for you know what I'm gonna I'm gonna do um
I'm gonna do I think I'll wait maybe like two more months or something of um minoxidil and
just see what happens and I mean if nothing if nothing happens there then like I'll probably
just keep shaving my head um and that's fine next one is Piano Guy I'm chillin chocolate
three two oh god it's a minute thirty three two one go okay three things one uh piano guy
said you wanted to join the dpsp join rfck and dm me piano guy second of all um message
for my favorite uh pcp member probably uh Ben St you punk bitch motherfucker listen I had to deal
with 18 years of being a piano guy so when you a fake piano guy say I'm already seething in my seat
okay then you say you baptize a piano guy what the fuck you fake fan you can't baptize piano guys
you baptize eight guys get out of here I um and finally uh
I did it I asked the girl out and you know she said even though no one has investment in this
piano guy uh the answer will only be given on piano guy cp episode everyone go now except it's
probably not out but go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go
I I can't believe you baptize that piano guy I have um alias I put the sound of the piano
that when I said that uh it was um
I have yet to have one of these that is like oh I remember that voicemail these are all just like
I don't remember when any of these came from no yeah there's there's just been so many
next one is okay well there's a bunch of youtube links and then whoever posted them says glad I
can finally send youtube links again I missed it hey man appreciate it thanks for that uh
you're just making you're just making this list you faster to go through I guess is one way to look
at it next one is called more mega man stuff three two one go hey Ben so we already know
mega man legends is pretty base pretty base play command mission it's not like the most amazing
rpg but it's mega man I've heard so yeah I've heard negative things about command mission
although I I thought it looked interesting but uh I haven't played it I have heard that it's not great
but I I would I would give it a chance except except it just seems like it's really long and I
don't know if I'm really feeling starting up like a long rpg at this point in my life I don't know
I don't know uh I've seen some of the cutscenes
they look fine like cutscenes more like cutscenes also it's it's weirdly positioned in like the lore
it's like it looks like it's part of x but it's actually a like alternate timeline of x
because as we all know x the x timeline eventually leads into the zero games but
command mission supposedly takes place at the same time that the zero games would be taking
place in 21 xx no in 22 xx rather uh but like just in a different continuity for some reason
even though things don't seem that different it's weird that seems dumb but anyway I no I haven't
played it although I'm a little curious about it honestly next one is hi ben how does Nate feel
that you shaved your head well I mean honestly he's probably not aware of it so there you go
next one is called good good good three two one go so I was recently talking about
my friend oh come on there's too many too many in one week yeah and just from like talking
this is something that I know that I felt in the past he really stressed this inherent value
of having like a movie or a tv show based and all the thing you like and at being good and it seems
to like almost undervalued the actual work of the original manga uh mark girl I just think that
that's a really common one attitude and like normie culture kind of and I was just kind
of curious if you guys have noticed this too and if they're actually any good
limitations or something or superior adaptations that you've experienced because you know I really
I really can't think of him.
Yeah, it's...
That one just wasn't very funny.
Well, I think it's overexposure.
Like you said, none of them have a point.
They are just like weird sounds.
But too much of weird sounds, it just sort of stops being surprising.
I think the piano man was the best one.
Yeah, the sentence mixing that, the comedy of the piano coming back,
the do unrealistic...
The piano man one made me chuckle, but that one did not.
The next one is called Dean Dan Dodon,
and I think it's probably going to be another one,
3, 2, 1, go.
Hello PC, PC, PC, PC, PC...
Yeah, Muudan.
Okay, yeah, the next one is called Joel's Goals,
three, two, one, go.
Hello, Pissapia, it's your boy Polin.
No, okay, no, no, good try it.
Next one is an Imgur album.
It's called Funny Ben, Then Long Discretions.
Don't hurt your throat reading
if you can help it at ben.com.
I'll just post the link here,
even though you can see it and you don't need me to,
but I'll do it anyway.
Nice.
Okay.
Good calling, Ben Stinky reminded me
I found a green piece of paper.
Ben Stinky, so stinky, he turned to the page green.
There you are.
There, I did, I'm like, I guess I did.
Too weird to live, too rare to die,
Ben St. Athanlaka Khan.
Panic at the Disco is too weird to live,
too rare to die, album cover, except with Ben St.
I couldn't think of a more clever,
a more cleaver rename for it.
I was blanking on endless war memes.
And then there's me playing basketball.
Ha ha ha, he will, he will never be ballin'.
And then you see this.
I like my chest hair, it's copious, that's true.
This was at a request for Ben bowling.
If you squint, you can see the water is sparkling water.
Oh, I do see, a request from who?
Where's this guy getting requests?
Where is this guy getting requests?
I mean, they're in my discord, they joined.
So maybe it's in there.
He's in my discord too, actually, so maybe there.
Bald Ben St, twinkle twinkle, yep, that's,
that is how it be, except I shaved my beard
and I shouldn't have cut my beard, I should have cut,
I'm an idiot.
I'm already in the process of growing it back.
And then-
You grow your eyebrows out, curl them around
to make a new beard.
Easy.
Crazy Ben's evil, evil illegal weed.
No, I only sell good illegal weed.
More really good, only please.
And thank you.
Chaotic good weed.
Chaotic good weed, yeah, thanks.
Yeah, that's what I want, that's my weed goals.
I don't want my weed to be chaotically good aligned.
Weed gummy worms, oh, it's me riding the bike around
like you said.
A cop is hitting in the bush over there.
Hitting cop.
Ben St, Ben St slime weed gummies for sale here
on my person and at my home address of Ben St
at 69, 69, Ben St Boulevard, Maine, USA, Hong Kong.
What a serendipitous street you ended up living on,
Ben St Boulevard.
Just worked out that way.
Imagine, yeah, this vacancy opened up just the right time.
Big bald St, big bald head, they're right there,
there's me.
And then model Frank Ocean,
it's Cheezy's fave musical boy.
Oh.
Oh, I thought I had-
Is that who's that was?
Remember the making a comment?
Yeah, I thought I had put in the description
of the one week's episode,
but I didn't.
Frank Ocean is the guy Cheezy's stand is based on.
It's a thing in JoJo that you stand to manifest
with a gimmick or theme,
but then hero Hiko Araki would sometimes throw a reference
to whatever pulp culture Frank Ocean
sings Cheezy's favorite song.
Cat face.
A little more of the comic I'm doing.
It's a bit of a read.
Oh my God, it's so long.
I don't know if we can read the whole of this.
I like the image though,
that the fire, the wolf's breathing is very nice.
Let's, you know what?
Let's post, I'll post a screenshot.
In addition to the image,
I'll post a screenshot of the description
and you can pause it and read it if you're interested.
TLDR guy becomes werewolf to fight pumpkin-headed zombies.
Okay.
I sure hope Pumpk isn't there.
She'll be killed.
I like the teal and pink fire is kind of a neat looking.
Yeah.
The blue teeth, the blue eyes.
Blue eyes, white dragon.
Think about it.
Pumpkins that grow across the land.
Use the bodies of the dead to walk upright
and cross rivers up in mountains
and plant their seeds everywhere.
Neat.
So it's like the last of us had pumpkins.
So like a head crab.
Like a pumpkin takes over a dead,
an already dead person though, okay.
Oh, well that pumpkin isn't one of those.
Pumpkins all pumpkin.
Werewolf is, oh God, tearing this guy.
Taring his skeleton out of his body.
Ew.
The werewolf thinks he thoroughly destroyed the pumpkin king.
He does, but a really dead boy.
Maybe, maybe not.
Who knows?
We'll have to wait and find out.
Very nice, very nice.
Looks good.
I like the different colored ballpoint pens.
It reminds me of, you ever see what the fucking,
oh that stupid thing about the girl with the big boobs
and Nate thought it was like, oh so bold of an anime
to be about like girls with big boobs
shouldn't be discriminated against.
Galcochan?
Yes, Galcochan.
You ever see the manga that it's?
I've seen a bit of the manga, yes.
It's got that different colored ballpoint pen.
Different colored line art.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Next.
Girl with the big boobs.
I mean, it is true.
I mean, it's true though.
There's just so many things that I can refer to.
Yeah, but Galcochan is like sort of specifically
about it though.
Is it?
I thought it was about like, well,
it's about femininity or like being like the real,
like what is really like being a girl.
Yeah, it is.
All these things.
It is that, it is that.
But also, I mean, Galco being a big booby lady
is kind of, it's like an important to her character.
It is part of the character and the story, yes.
Yeah.
Okay, the next one is another Imgirlink.
And then.
It's Ben Sainz's final form.
It's just Walter White.
Okay, well.
I mean, you wear glasses.
Oh, I'm.
I shave my head.
I cook, I cook math, yeah.
You were a teacher.
You're literally.
Oh, that's true.
That is true.
Well, he taught chemistry.
I taught physics, but I mean, close enough.
What would be the physics equivalent of Breaking Bad?
Like a physics teacher gets into drugs
and uses physics to make a good drug.
Making illegal.
Not even a drug, actually.
Just a crime that involves physics.
Black holes, manufacturing illegal neutrinos.
Manufacturing illegal electricity.
With a copper wire and a magnet.
Gee, I don't know.
I mean, okay, I guess that's the last one.
We're done.
We're fucking done here.
Okay.
Oh, actually there's a, did you listen to the,
Vinny's Imgirlink album actually has
a little one second voicemail attached.
It's just a noise.
It's going, or something.
I think it's deliberate.
So I'm gonna call that a real voicemail, actually.
Well, that's the end of the voicemails.
And we're almost at the three hours.
Wow, three hours just fly by every single week.
You know, I got messaged by an old head PCP fan
who had not listened.
I mean, this guy claimed,
I had my suspicions about this guy,
but he claimed to be an old head PCP fan
who had not listened to the show in years.
And he messaged me on Twitter.
He just wanted to like ask me a bunch of questions
about stuff.
And it was really fun.
He was using, he was casually using the N word
despite not being black.
And I was like, okay, man, that's a little gauche,
but all right.
And he wanted to know,
he did not seem to know about people's genders,
which is like, okay, all right, all right.
But like the guy had not listened,
so like I couldn't blame him, I guess.
And then he was just asking me about like
stuff about mumkey drama and stuff about like,
what do you think of Jeff Thu?
I was like, wow, what a revelation.
This guy's like an open to time capsule,
and this guy stepped out.
Well, I mean, what was he at?
What did he want to know?
It sounds like it's just like all of the things
that would show that he's a person from before.
But like, is it sincere?
Well, I'm mentioning those because they were example.
But I mean, he was just asking me like,
how are you doing?
Like how's munchy doing?
Like how's so-and-so?
He was asking me like, how everybody's doing?
Or like, what's going on with these people?
Do you ever talk to Mage anymore?
What's Mage doing?
Da, da, da, da.
It was interesting, it was weird, it was kind of neat.
It was all right, just odd, just funny.
Why did I?
Yeah, oh, he said, he did say to say hi to you.
He did say to say hello to you and also to munchy.
So I'll tell you now and I'll tell munchy later
that this guy said hi.
Where the hell?
Yes.
He said, DeVoo is better than me.
At what?
In general.
DeVoo's a general.
And I thought, this guy must be a fake.
This must be a catfish.
I thought this must be a DeVoo.
This must be DeVoo on an alt account doing an op.
Catfishing me because nobody is a DeVoo fan.
That's no way.
Okay, well, anyway, I just thought I wanted to mention that.
It was a funny thing that happened just yesterday, actually.
Anyway, if you're a new head PCP fan,
patreon.com slash the procrastinators
for a million bonus episodes
while you wait for your treasury bonds to mature.
And that's the straight dope.
That's yes.
And that's what's happening.
That's the song of the south.
The way the news goes.
You got anything else to say before we wrap it?
Nope.
Me either.
All right.
Bye.
Goodbye, that's the end of the show.
It is.