Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
Hello, and welcome to another episode, a very special episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's been Saint with me. I've got Gibbontake.
Hello everybody. Before we get to the special guests, LordaGhost Kickstarter is a day or three days away from being finished. Go check that out. It's important.
If you haven't heard about it, you should go check it out. LordaGhost Kickstarter is good. It is a matter of urgent importance that you go and check out the LordaGhost Kickstarter link in the description.
We've got special guests. We've got a special guest. This is a guest that I've been wanting on for years. For years, I've been asking for this individual to come on and talk about their work, which we all know and love. It's Laserbot, the man himself behind Tales Get Strolled. Say hello, Laserbot.
Hello, I'm Laserbot.
Hey, I'm so chuffed. I'm so glad you're here. And with us, we've also got CeCe, who you remember from a previous episode, is the Tales Get Strolled. I like to call him the brand manager.
CeCe.
Hello.
Okay, and we've also got Cyber Shell, who is a funny guy.
I'm basically just here to witness the episode live. I couldn't miss this. It's Laserbot, guys. I don't think people even understand. This is a big get. How many other podcasts has Laserbot been on? Name one. You can't.
Yeah, actually, that's Laserbot. What other appearances have you done? I know you did the interview with Know Your Meme, which I read, and you were on the Newgrounds panel. Have you done any other podcasts or appearances anywhere on the internet lately?
No, I was kind of weird about doing recordings or anything like that. I just now started doing that.
Yeah. I asked you, I think it was after you left, like I put out the lecture, the Tales Get Strolled lecture, and you left a comment. And I think it was after that I asked you if you wanted to come on and you said you didn't have a microphone or you didn't have the setup to do it.
And I said, damn it. I said, three years from now, I'll get them. And it was true. So let's see. I thought we could talk.
It's really been that long.
Yeah, the lecture was three years ago.
Maybe not. It's been more than two. I don't know. It's maybe less than three.
Maybe less than three.
I checked. I actually checked because I just, I was, I checked on YouTube and me and you, Ben, we have the highest two Tales Get Strolled videos. We're the number one and two fans.
Is that, is that true? Is that true?
Yeah.
Wait, who's got more?
You.
Yeah, fuck you. Okay, sorry.
Excuse me.
Remember, I told you yours had like 400,000 views.
That's a lot of based and it's 300,000.
Oh, it's newer though. It's catching up. Yeah.
It's got a higher rate of acceleration.
It's all worth it just to bring in new viewers and new fans of this epic saga.
Yeah.
Uh, you, do you, um, uh, I mean, okay, we talked to CC the other week about running the website and stuff and, and he, well, you, you mean you're right here.
You said you were looking to like do physical prints of books and you talked about like an Alex plushie and stuff.
How is, how is that going?
The Alex more of a joke. I would like to do it, but I have no idea how I am working, you know, physical edition right now.
Actually me and laser bottle working.
Oh, we're working on it together.
He drew.
I was going to ask late.
Go on, go on.
He drew the cover for it, which turned out pretty good.
Oh, really? Like recently you did?
Yes.
Oh, wow.
Yeah. What do you, I mean, what do you think about?
What are you thinking about for the physical release laser bond?
I'm pretty excited.
I've kind of always wanted to see it released in physical form.
Yeah.
I've done that.
I've done, I've printed some, some books myself and done kick starters and stuff.
It's fun.
It's fun and exciting.
It's a lot of work, but it's great.
People love, people love that physical media.
People are suckers for it, including myself.
I will absolutely buy a, I will absolutely buy a book version of it if it gets made.
Yeah.
I would love to see it for sure.
How big is it going to be?
I mean, it's like a pretty, there's a lot of pages.
Well, we're doing it volume by volume.
Yeah.
I was figuring, I was like, that would be insane if you try to fit it on one thing.
That kind of doesn't make any sense because it's still ongoing anyways.
So yeah.
That's such a funny like image in my head of like tails gets trolled.
All of the volumes stack next to each other on your shelf.
I know it would look so great.
Yeah.
The current plan is, I'll go ahead.
No, no, I have nothing to say, please.
The current plan is for the first volume to have the first six chapters, but we might
need to change that because I'm having some technical difficulties, which I kind of posted
about on Twitter yesterday or the day before.
Are you talking about the shipping?
Are you talking about international shipping?
No, I figured that out.
You can get it a lot cheaper if you print it on Amazon, but the problem is they only
give you like a limit of how much, how like the file size you can upload.
And I wanted the pages to be in the highest quality possible.
And it ended up being like, um, like 800 gigabyte.
So right now I'm trying to downsize it so it can fit without a sacrificing quality.
The other services.
I have a question.
I'll go ahead.
I have a, this is a little off topic, but I have a question for, I was looking at my notes
here and I've got a question for laser bot in, in, in the, it's a tails gets trolled question
in the interview with the know your meme.
You talked about the, the initial incident, how a friend of yours was getting trolled
and that incited you to, uh, to make the first bit of tails gets rolled up till the part
where, uh, where shadow kills the trolls.
I was wondering, uh, who it, who was it?
If you could tell us who was the friend who was getting trolls.
I would, but I don't know if the person wouldn't want me to.
If that makes sense.
Yeah.
Damn.
But it would be an interesting bit of trivia to know.
That's the kind of factoid that I would love to know, but I guess that makes sense.
Okay.
Um, my other thing I was curious.
I was reading through that interview and I was like, hmm, I wonder.
So you said you, you drew it up till the part where shadow kills the trolls and then a friend
of yours suggested sonic going dark and killing the, and killing the trolls.
Um, so the, the first bit you drew ended with they bury the trolls and then knuckles
and shadow do the high shovel.
Right.
Was that the end of it at first?
Cause right now the chapter ends with sort of like a shadowy figure being like, um,
what does he say?
He's like, there, it's a, it's that, that double agent.
Oh no, the troll double agent, the guy with the headband.
Yeah.
Pory.
It's Pory.
And he's like, uh, we'll, we'll have to take care of this or something.
That wasn't there initially though.
Right.
That was added later.
Oh, it was there, but I, I still wasn't sure if I was going to.
So, oh, so even at the beginning, you included the, like the hook.
I kind of left the door open, but I wasn't sure if I was going to continue it.
So, oh wow.
So you had poor Pory is one of the most fascinating characters.
Pory is the one that I find the most mysterious and who I'm like always reading through the
comic, I'm always seeing Pory and I'm always like, he's, he seems really important, but
I don't know what he's doing.
We still don't have a lot of like, uh, we don't have a lot of background info on him
or, or like true motivations, you know what I mean?
I think that would mean he's like the first non troll original character that appears
in the whole thing.
Uh, yeah.
He's right here at the end of a chapter one saying, yes, sir.
The guy who says, find out who's doing the stick.
I assume he's talking to the troll king.
Yeah.
Maybe.
Um, can you.
Tell me about Pory.
What's, what's Pory's deal?
That's neckos and spoiler territory, sir.
Damn it.
Okay.
There's a lot, there's a lot with Pory, uh, later on.
And he's got a lot of plot as, as in stuff that's coming up.
Yeah.
What kind of animal is that?
But yeah, it's, it's, it's like the next arc and on.
It's throughout a lot of the story.
He's got a lot going on with his character.
All right.
I'll have to, I'll just have to, uh, be content with, with that for now.
Ben was trying to get spoilers out of him.
I'm trying to get advanced plot details so we could leak them to the press.
If, if I could, if I could.
Yeah.
Oil stuff, but I can't spoil Pory.
Nice.
Okay.
That's fair.
Yeah.
Fair.
If I could, if I could trick you, if I could trick you into some juicy spoilers,
then it would, then this episode would be, uh, it would be a must watch, but, uh,
all right, they couldn't do it.
Um, wait, if you plead anything you'd like to spoil, I would love to have it spoiled
right now.
Um, after the attack on troll city, the next arc is, uh, about shadows plan.
Oh my God.
That's, uh, that's, that's good news.
Another plan.
That's great news for us shadow fans out here.
He's been so long spent time making these plans.
It'll be great to see something finally come to fruition.
I will mention that, um, I will mention that, uh, shadow gets a lot more brutal as it goes
on.
Oh, that makes sense.
I mean, that's sort of his character arc, you know, it's just been like, you know,
that's the way to deal with trolls is you just kill them.
You just be violent and he just, he keeps doing more violent crazy shit, but it's
like, you know, it's against trolls.
So it's okay.
In, I thought, I thought it was interesting that you said it again in that interview,
you said that the, the, the cartoon or the, the, the non original characters are basically
original characters that just have the skin of a, of a, of a copyright character.
And you all, and you said that the initial idea for the story, it was the three possible
responses to trolling tales is just cry about and be a little bitch.
No, Sonic is try and make peace and resolve it.
And, and, and, uh, shadow is, you know, go ham and, and fuck him up and kill him.
Right.
And like, you know, fight, fight back.
So I guess that's like, I guess shadow is kind of the, I mean, right from the beginning
he sort of embodies the like the brutal response to any situation.
So I mean, sounds good.
Sounds good to me.
Uh, I think, uh, those are about actually wrote, but he actually drew an upcoming, like a preview
of an upcoming page with Mario and shadow.
Oh my God.
And I think that's part of a shadows plan.
It'd be nice to see him again.
It's been a while since we've seen Mario.
We got that like special, uh, star or whatever.
It's like, I do love the holy star.
Yeah, exactly.
It's been a while.
That was a while ago and it's, you know, I have no problem with it.
It's just the comic has a lot of plot threads.
So sometimes you just have to put someone on Mario for the back burner for the, you know,
next 10 chapters.
You know what I mean?
I forgot about the holy star and that we haven't seen Mario since then until you just mentioned it.
It's been a while.
It's been a little while since I read.
I'm, I'm, I'm very excited for Pory.
I've, I've had my eye on him the whole time.
Ever since, since doing, I think my reread before I did the lecture a couple of years ago,
I, I read through it again and I kept noticing Pory and I was like, this guy, he's definitely,
he's definitely important.
Uh, uh, he doesn't, he doesn't get as much screen time as like Alex.
He's not as, uh, he's not as, as iconic.
I think as Alex, uh, uh, but, uh, he's, he's, I like him.
I like, he's very mysterious.
I totally get so, he's so mysterious.
He's so weird looking.
He's so weird looking, but like he kind of just acts.
He does have a very striking visual design.
It's like, yeah.
Honestly, he's kind of, he has a striking vision.
Sorry.
No, I was just, I was just agreeing with you.
I agree.
Like Pory is a very interesting character.
And if you like analyze the plot, he doesn't really do that much.
I mean, he, he sort of like, I mean, any character that's sort of like a double agent type character is always very interesting to me.
So I don't know.
He's just like, I like Pory too.
I agree with you.
Um, do you, okay.
I, I have a question.
I wanted to ask about, uh, some like production stuff, but I think maybe if anyone else wants to ask like, plot stuff about
Tales of Disrolled, maybe now would be the time before I move into that.
Since we've got laser brought here, you know, for the, for the, now's the time.
I already, I already know more story details than I want to know.
I've already.
That's one thing I've been is like, I, I kind of like enjoy like experiencing it as a fan.
You know what I mean?
Like I appreciate everything you're doing CC.
Obviously, you know, I already said this a bunch of times for like, you know, it wouldn't have even come back without you.
So it's not like you have a choice and, you know, getting to know these things.
Cause you have to know them as the, you know, site admin and, you know, art team guy.
So I appreciate that.
All the work you've been putting in.
So it's nice to be able to just appreciate the series as a fan.
Yeah.
Well, I actually go out of my way to avoid spoilers.
Like I don't, I don't want to know.
Like I don't, I tell them not to show me the page they're working on until it's actually done.
Right.
Here's the thing.
I know some spoilers too, but like, I don't know.
I guess this is a question laser body.
Cause do you remember when the comic originally ended?
You did a big sort of, I don't know if it was an interview, but you just posted a bunch of plot details on DeviantArt.
Like, oh, here's what I was going to do with the, you know, the man, the man in the ice and all this stuff.
I don't know if any of that's still canon.
That's mainly what I'm referring to when I said, I know too much spoilers.
It's like from that.
Right.
Some of the plots the same, but a lot of it's changed.
See, that's the vibe I was getting was that like a lot of the stuff you talked about there wasn't
necessarily set in stone.
It was more just like, this is what I was planning on doing at the time I wrote this.
You know what I mean?
It was drafts.
Right.
Uh, yeah, I wanted to ask you like how far ahead in the, how far ahead of the comic did you generally have like written before, like as you were drawing it?
Uh, was that consistent or did you?
Yeah, yeah.
We had most of it either rodent or at least planned in our heads.
If that answers your question.
By, by most of it, do you mean like all the way to?
Well, what's how far do you mean all the way to the end and like how close to the end are we?
Oh, right now in the plot.
Yeah.
We had a lot of like most of it planned out even to end.
We know how it's going to end.
If you're wondering that, um, yeah, there are areas where it's kind of, it's a draft and it kind of needs to be like polished a bit and, you know, upgraded.
I would say flushed out.
Okay.
Here.
So, so here's my, here's my question.
Uh, so you know how it's going to end.
How close are we?
How close in the comic are we to the end?
Hmm.
Well, we're again in it to the end of the first arc with the attack and, um, okay.
So I can't really say for sure how long the rest of it is because, you know, writings kind of it differs because you can have a writing that's really quick, but it'll take like several pages to actually.
You know, capture that in comic form.
That's why, uh, that's why a lot of the covers have the earlier chapter covers have things from the next chapter on it because we thought we would get there sooner than we ended up.
Oh, that's funny, but it makes sense.
That makes sense.
Right.
Yeah.
Because you have a very strict page limit that you're sticking to for a long time.
Oh, that's right.
Yes.
Uh, okay.
For example, I remember.
So we're close.
Oh, sorry.
Mm hmm.
One example.
No, go on.
It shows the tales and wearing his defenders uniform in chapter four, but the defenders don't appear till chapter five.
That is interesting.
I actually never noticed that.
Show the show the cover of chapter four on screen, please.
Thank you.
You can just chalk it up to foreshadowing though.
I mean, it is kind of funny though that the specific chapters though, like it shows things that aren't in the chapter, but you know, as long as they eventually appear, it's okay.
Yeah.
I think that's actually really cool.
And another example, a more recent example is it shows, uh, like a Hindo's demonic form was in like a page, was in the chapter cover from like five years ago, but he only just appeared in the chapter just now or in this.
Right.
There is a lot of foreshadowing in the comic, honestly, like there's a lot of little details that you might, you probably wouldn't notice your first time around.
I, the one I always remember is the sky changing colors just because like in the background of, uh, it's like, it's like randomly happens the background of characters talking, but then like later you see that helps you keep track of like the timeline.
Because there's a bunch of concurrent events happening all at the same time.
So then you see that from like Coyote's perspective and he makes the sky green for just a few panels.
I don't know why I just thought that was really interesting.
I love the sky thing because the, the, like Tails gets trolled is kind of, it's famous for its, it's famous for its visual style.
Of blue sky green grass.
Right.
So like by change, like a character that changes the skull, the, the, the sculler of the guy, the color of the sky.
It's like color coding the whole chapter.
And I was thinking about if you had it in book form, you could like almost look at the side of the book and you could see the edges.
You could see, oh, these are the red pages.
These are when, um, you know, that, that beast is out.
Right.
And oh, these are the green pages.
These are when the tree is out.
Those are the white pages.
This is when, uh, Damaro's guardian, whose name I forget is out.
Mila Docs.
Uh, Mila Docs.
Actually, that's one thing I wanted to ask.
Uh, laser bot.
How is that actually pronounced?
It's a Mila Docs.
Okay.
Mila, Mila Docs.
Yeah.
I remember for a very long time, people online just called it Satan because that's what like Damaro was calling it.
But it was interesting to like get the Canon name and everything.
It was really interesting to see that fight.
Uh, finally be illustrated by the art team.
After like, I'd seen it in the script form many years ago because I just, you know, I assumed we were never going to get any more pages.
So I just read the 23 script.
I was like, interesting, interesting.
It was really cool to see that.
I realized I was, I was going to ask, uh, laser bot, how do you feel seeing, uh, the, the comic now being drawn by guest artists when you were the one that was drawing it?
Um, you know, before, for years and years.
I love drawing, but it's been really awesome seeing all the, uh, awesome fan art that people have been creating and the art team has been creating.
I really enjoy, enjoy it.
Do you, do you ever not, not to like, I don't mean this to like throw any shade, but has there been any like pages where you've seen it and you've been like, I would have drawn that differently.
Like I would, I would have made it look different.
I feel like I would have done that differently in all the pages, but I'm not complaining.
I did it.
I think they did a very good job.
Sure.
Makes.
Yeah.
I totally, I totally get it.
Um, it is really cool to see the art style of these like, you know, artists and just like seeing all the characters in just these different art styles.
I don't know why I just get a kick out of seeing the like the original characters drawn in these like more like hyper detail styles, but I do, I agree with you.
Like, it's like, you know, a big part of the charm.
I really love laser bots art and seeing it change over time.
So it's like, I love that he also, you know, he contributes to pages every now and then.
So it's not like it's gone completely or whatever.
And obviously doing stuff like that cover.
I appreciate the guest artists who can do a pretty faithful recreation of laser bot style.
But I also appreciate, you know, like that one, you know, really like rendered painterly coyote chapter.
Yeah.
Again, I'm the same way where I agree.
It's like the, like the, the, the hyper detailed style is really cool.
But I also do appreciate the people who can capture the essence of the original style without it being like the same exactly.
But, you know, at least going for like just capturing the style, you know what I mean?
Like the rougher style.
That one, that one coyote bit, it's not only good art, like it's well painted, but it's also just funny to see it.
Like to have it suddenly switched to this like, kind of Jojo-esque, like, like painted, like oil.
There is something just inherently amusing about like a fight scene starts and the art just gets like insane all of a sudden.
It's like, whoa, like if you didn't know anything, our tails get strolled.
Like you didn't know any of the behind the scene stuff.
You just like got to that part in the comic.
You'd be like, what the fuck is going on?
You'd be like, what the fuck?
Yeah, yeah, for real.
Yeah, that was kind of sort of the intention with that.
Like, yeah, it's perfect.
And I mean, laser bot experimented with his own art styles in the past to like, he would draw different pages differently.
And stuff.
So it wasn't like that too out of the ordinary.
I remember it was the first time Melodox appears.
I was like, I think I like kind of put my hands down and I was like, okay.
I started out thinking this comic was like, you know, haha, stupid tails got trolled.
How ridiculous.
Oh, it's bad.
But then I was like, okay, you know what?
We've come, we've gone places.
This this the person making this has really has really has grown and it shows.
And I was like, you know what?
I appreciate it.
Gotta appreciate that.
But I wanted to say, okay, so you say that we're getting close to the end of the first arc out of how many arcs.
Do you know how many arcs there will be?
We got the next one, which is the era of shadow.
That's the next arc.
The era of shadow.
Okay.
Yeah.
And then the next one's more getting more into the war.
And then the war arc, which is like, I think that and then I think there's the last arc, which is where it concludes.
Where's all the.
So I think it's four arcs.
I'm not 100% sure you said you said there's this this one and then the era of shadow and then the war and then the conclusion.
So that's four.
Yeah, I think so.
Okay.
Can you can you elaborate?
Can you elaborate on the era of shadow or the war?
Well, the era of shadows.
Focusing a lot on the shit with shadow and Mario.
And the lot and the trolls kind of whatever ones that are left after the attack kind of trying struggling and trying to recover from the wreckage.
Okay.
And the war will be between the trolls and the everyone else, I guess.
Right.
I don't want to go too much in spoilers, but.
Okay.
Fair enough.
But I will mention that troll city isn't the only troll place like, you know, there's.
That makes sense.
The world building has been like it's an interesting to see these locations like like one time we got a nice zoom out of like the map area and had like a nice shot of the jungle and the troll city and everything in relation to each other.
It's kind of nice.
So the other arcs.
Well, will the other three arcs be as long as the first arc has been.
I'm not really 100% sure on that.
They might be shorter.
I don't know, because it really depends on the thing and all that.
Yeah, that makes sense.
It is still kind of hard just to like wrap my mind around the fact that every single thing that's happened so far has been part of the first arc and then there's going to be multiple other arcs.
It's like some one piece level shit and just going to keep going.
Yeah, true.
I'm not complaining.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not saying that's a bad thing.
A thousand years.
Tails gets trolled a thousand years.
Hopefully not.
I wanted to see it complete at some point and you know.
Yeah.
My last question about that is you said you've you said you've know the arcs and you know how it's going to end.
At what point did you I assume it was you and Ember Graham came up with it at what point in the comic did you know.
Okay, we know how it's going to end.
Like when did you come up with that and like get it all figured out like okay I know the whole arc of the comic.
We a lot of times we would just kind of when we were prettier.
It's kind of hard to say when we started but after we started planning ahead which I would say it was.
I don't actually don't know how to answer that question honestly we just started planning ahead and we started brainstorming on these different plots and as time went on we just kept coming up with stuff.
For the story and I just kept building building on to it.
Do you I mean was there ever a moment where you were like oh I know how it's going to end like oh that would be a really perfect way for it to end.
Was there a moment where you like figured it out or had the idea or or no.
Yeah we have me and Ember Graham.
It was a when we were pretty far back actually in the comic when we were we came up with the end for it.
Like yeah I think you know you don't you know about what chapter.
No it's been like so many years when we were working on it.
I can't I can't remember when I first originally came up when we first you know came up with the plot.
Okay but it's but it's been you've known it for a long time though.
Oh yeah we've known it for a long time.
Fascinating fascinating I love that.
That's that's that was my biggest question actually is like how how like how much of the how much of it was made with the ending in mind.
It's interesting like the first few chapters clearly are like just sort of riffing on like one singular idea and like it's clearly coming like being made up on the spot basically like it's like the very first few pages is clear they didn't have all this like stuff
that stands out with all this lore but pretty early on you can start to see them plant seeds of stuff that would take a long time to get like developed out you know.
The I had I had one other question from going over the interview you mentioned that those initial trolls that were trolling your friend on DeviantArt you made like accounts you made like shadow the hedgehog and tails accounts to
troll them back do you still have those accounts or like do those still exist.
No they don't exist anymore.
Damn.
I would love to find them and read like the comments they left or something.
If they still existed I would.
Yeah it's been such a long time I don't.
I don't even know where you know the comments it would be or anything like that.
Yeah.
It was 10 years ago.
Oh there was there was another part you said that I thought this was really funny you said you and Ember Graham you use the conflict with the troll.
This is when you're talking about like after you've been making the comic but some people were basically trolling you for making the comic.
You know the haters basically you said you would use the conflict with the trolls for research purposes to try to make the trolling in the comic as accurate as possible.
It was a dark experiment we conducted for a long time.
The experience was a roller coaster.
I was wondering if you could remember any any particular moments from those those dark experiments that stick out in your memory.
I was really curious about that.
Well it was probably when it was happening was probably during the early stages of the comic all the way up to probably the Gary and the moral fires when all that kind of was taking place.
But we were trolled all the time or well a lot of people trying to a lot of people didn't really want us to continue the comic they were trying to.
This break us down kind of thing and we kind of got into a little troll war with them a bit and we would make posts to provoke them and then.
Oh no.
He cut out for everyone else too right.
Yes.
I cut out.
Oh you're back.
You're back.
Okay.
Where was I.
You said you would make posts to provoke them.
Yeah and we would have debates with them and really if we just kind of wanted to get as much information about the subject as you know because we were we want to know as much about trolling as we could so we can make the trolls in the comic pretty accurate.
I love that.
Did you were there are there any like bits of troll dialogue in the comic that you remember were like maybe directly taken from trolls that you were like quote unquote debating with.
I'm sure there's dialogue in there but I can't remember at this point.
It's been a long time.
There's not.
Okay there's not maybe like any particular troll in the comic that you're like oh yeah that guy was based on a real person who I had to deal with or something.
Or maybe they all were.
The guy with the the my little pony that dude was he asked to be put in there.
Any we kind of made like a little deal with him is I put me in the comic and I'll promote I'll help promote your your comics so we're sorry we'll put this on this pony guy in there.
Wasn't that the guy who hacked the the deviant art.
No.
No that wasn't a different guy.
Okay.
I see who was that guy.
The pony guy.
I can't remember his name.
Scat.
That's kind of embarrassing.
It's scat.
Wasn't scat.
It was scat.
Thank you.
What why did he.
I don't like what was the the deal that you worked out where he was like yeah I can promote your comic if you put me in tails good stroll.
I wonder if we knew that guy.
I wonder if we met that guy at brony con.
I don't know.
I interacted with him on Facebook.
And I think one of the people Aubrey who's in the tails gets trolled.
Community who I think cyber shell knows he interacted with him to your action might be information about this on the wiki let me look.
I don't actually think he ever got around to promoting it.
I don't.
I don't think we actually left on like positive terms.
So I kind of we I think we just kind of made fun of them a little bit.
Yeah.
Oh here we go.
Tails gets trolled org slash wiki scat and Fluttershy.
It's just a guy.
Oh it's just a wait this.
Oh it's it's one of those it's one of those like cell phone like avatar creator things.
It's just a guy.
I don't remember this troll.
I don't.
I don't remember this because I remember being like really confused.
I was like what the hell is up with this brony guy.
I don't remember.
I don't want to say it.
This is Nazi brony guy.
I know some guys like that.
Cat is a slender human wearing a black shirt and pants.
Fluttershy is a yellow horse with a pink mane and tail.
Look at that.
She is usually seen drooling.
Look at the bottom under trivia.
It explains the whole thing.
Scats design is based off a user on laser bots Facebook page who asked to be in the comic laser bot and his brother Ember Graham had made a deal with him to promote tails gets trolled on their social medias in exchange to be in the comic he had irritated the two and as a result was put in the comic in a more mocking tone.
Note that his laser bots old Facebook has been deleted the actual conversations have been lost time.
That's so funny.
Amazing.
Now I know.
Man.
Shit.
I think I'm out of questions.
I think I'm out of TGT questions.
Anyone else got me.
Oh, go ahead.
No, no, you go ahead.
Okay.
It's not a question.
I was just going to say I think troll face was also based off of real trolls that he encountered.
Yeah, yeah, he was.
I like the troll dialogue.
There's a lot of shit in there that it does seem like it's sort of, you know, it's very true to life and just them saying random shit like stop feeding like what the fuck that's just like a hilarious like Boba thing to say for no reason.
Stop feed just just.
Yeah, they just they just kind of.
Yeah.
That was more based off of how the trolls I've seen on video games aren't, you know, uninstall, stop feeding.
Exactly.
Yep.
That's a pretty good summary of what they're like, honestly.
I do appreciate the trolls of like they're not all they don't sound the same, you know, like different trolls have different weird styles of trolling in the comic, which I think is amusing.
There's quite a variety of trolls out there.
We wanted to make sure we showcase that.
Also, there's, um, yeah, the Ark without under under bite troll in in troll city, a very, a very out of left field chapter.
That one.
I really like that one.
Yeah, getting to see seeing the trolls as they see themselves.
You know, they're just trying to.
Society is just very amusing.
Just just to imagine an entire city of trolls is just a funny premise in the first place.
And then just yes, the idea of having like a troll often stuff is good stuff.
They have a they have a they have a kind of troll hierarchy based on these like contests of who can troll harder.
It's like, yeah, that makes sense.
I was actually.
Yeah, I buy it.
That was actually one thing I was going to mention.
The troll off dialogue was like a laser bot asked like people for suggestions on like what troll dialogue would be.
And he put it in the troll off between silver and under.
Oh, which is where like the app, the Adolf Hitler thing comes from.
You literally made Adolf Hitler get off his stick phones in the flames of hell.
He grew up the bottle cheap with right swapped quietly in the corner of the shower no longer secure in his position as the world's least likeable human being.
I guess I guess my last thing that I wanted to ask is, you know, recently, it was announced that you were not going to be actively working on the comic anymore.
You were going to be leaving it to Ember Graham and the the guest artists to to to finish it or really to finish like working on the main body of the comic.
I was wondering if you wanted to talk about that and say, I don't know what led to that decision.
Well, there was multiple things that kind of led to that.
One of them is just like, yeah, I don't know, I didn't really have the same motivation as I did before.
And I kind of just wanted to kind of have a new start and do something new, you know, fresh kind of change things up, you know.
Did you did you just I mean, is it just that you've been working on TGT for too long and you just retired of it?
I think that's a part of it because it's been working on it for a very long time and it's just kind of.
Yeah, sure. I mean, yeah, about a decade now, right?
Yeah, when it started.
Okay, I mean, that makes sense.
Was there anything else? Anything else about it?
I'm curious because I just heard about it.
I think it was from CC just heard one day like, oh, laser bots out.
And I said, oh, and you know, I assume that meant the comic was canceled, but I was glad to hear that.
No, no, the other guys are going to continue it because the story is kind of written already.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Anything else that contributed to that? I'm curious.
Well, the main thing is I already mentioned, but there was some other stuff going on that I just kind of with my brother, I just kind of wanted to do my own thing.
And, you know, a lot was going on in my life and I kind of wanted to.
I just was done with creating Taylor's Troll.
You don't want to go in any more detail than that?
No, not really.
Okay, fair enough.
So, I mean, do you...
Well, I was surprised just a minute ago when CC said that you had drawn the cover for the book, which I guess means you're not 100 percent out, right?
I am, but he's making hard copies.
It's like, okay, I do want to help with that. That's awesome, you know, because I really wanted to see it in the hard copy form.
I completely understand that.
Yeah. All right.
I mean, do you think you'll be doing any more things like that, just like any more like contributions like that, or was that it?
I mean, I guess if they're doing multiple chapters for the books, are you going to do a cover for each one, probably?
I'm not sure. I don't know, to be honest.
I guess we'll see.
Well, if there's no more TGT discussion, then I did want to ask you about...
You said you wanted to move on to do other things.
I've seen some of your older stuff that's your non-TGT stuff, and I've heard from CC about some of the others.
Like, I watched through all of Micorat on one summer a few years ago, I think.
So I've seen Micorat, and I think at one point you talked about maybe redoing that, although I'm not sure if you have said that recently.
And then the other day, CC mentioned God's Chosen.
God's Heroes.
I messed up. Right, God's Heroes, not God's Chosen.
So yeah, tell me about what your plans are post-TGT.
We actually, when I stopped TGT before I stopped the last time, in between time before the art team,
I was working on trying to make more Micorat and animation for it.
But it was taking too long, and I didn't get around to finishing it.
But we were writing a lot of new stuff with Micorat,
and we plan on actually eventually making maybe less detailed, very simple art comic strips of that,
so we can release what we have wrote.
Less detailed Micorat?
Yeah, basically kind of how Micorat looks already, you know, the original.
We're going to probably release it in that kind of format, but in a comic strip.
So I don't plan on going back to Micorat, so I kind of want to release what we have of it.
Yeah, you made Micorat a long time ago, like that was before Tails gets trolled, right?
Yeah.
Can you briefly tell me what was the inspiration behind Micorat?
What was the idea there that you were like, I know, I'm going to make Micorat, like how did you come up with it?
That's a hard one to answer. It kind of just happened.
It was based off of our imagination, but also a lot of things that actually happened.
We just kind of put it in a fictional manner that was pretty hilarious because I've seen a lot of, like, what?
It's you and your brothers, right? It's you and your brothers.
Yeah, back kind of when...
Go ahead.
No, that's it. I thought that the characters were you and your brothers, but I wasn't 100% sure.
Yeah, it was back in the time where everybody was calling everything gay and so on and so forth.
You know how that was back in the olden days.
I know. I know how it was. Not that long ago.
True.
God's Heroes.
I can talk about that a little bit, too.
Yeah, if that's what you're focusing on, I'd love to hear more about it.
God's Heroes is me and my brother Shim Shimo.
We've been working on that.
How many brothers do you have?
I'm trying to remember.
I thought Shim Shimo was Micah.
Yeah, that's him.
Okay, yeah. I thought Micah was the other one and I was like, wait, there's Laserbot and there's Zagar and there's Micah and now there's Shim Shimo.
Okay, they're multiplying.
I have more stippling than that, but those are the ones that I'm doing projects with.
I see. I see. Okay, cool.
Right, so God's Heroes.
God's Heroes is like after the TGT, like the whole story, probably in a distant future kind of thing.
Okay, distant future.
I mean, are there cartoon characters?
You know, in TGT, you have Sonic characters and Mario. No, there's not video game characters and stuff.
There's not any franchise characters in this series.
Okay.
They all died out or something.
I can mention the plot to it.
Anything you want to tell me about God's Heroes, I'm here for it.
Anything you want to tell me, I'm excited.
So the planet is the planet that they're on, which is a different planet. It's similar to Earth, but it's not Earth.
It's taken over by Satan.
Actually, is there anything different?
So they're not Earth. It's like an Earth-like planet in our different solar system or something.
Yeah, something like that.
Okay.
It still has Canada.
I was just curious.
That's the universal constant.
Wait, who's from Canada?
Cheedleman got his weed from Canada.
Oh, that's the trouble though.
I forgot.
Okay, yeah.
It's not Earth. It's just a similar planet that also happens to have a place called Canada.
That's fine.
Well, Telskis Troll is like a different planet than this planet.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. You're saying that Tails gets trolled and God's Heroes don't take place on the same planet?
No, they don't, but they're very connected.
And some of the characters that were on Telskis Troll show up in God's Heroes.
Okay, I have to clarify.
So Telskis Troll does take place on Earth.
It's on the version universe of it, I guess.
I don't know.
I guess it's on Earth, but then again, it's so fucking weird compared to all the other Earths that I don't know, to be honest.
You know what? Yeah, that tracks.
That makes sense to me.
Sure, it's Earth, but it's a different Earth.
Okay, God's Heroes' different planet, same universe.
Got it.
Yeah, yeah.
And they're connected.
Anyways, the plot to God's Heroes, which kind of starts it is, Satan kind of rules over this planet.
And all of the God's servants are hiding in the sewers away from them because they can turn people who have a weak will into sheep servants.
And the sheep servants are all the...
Sheep servants.
Yeah, they're actual sheep, and they're on their phones all the time.
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
And that's just kind of where the story...
Who are they?
What are they looking at on their phones?
I don't really... It doesn't really go into the...
Just whatever.
Okay, okay, yeah, they're on their phones.
They're phone drones, basically, and they serve their...
Phone drones.
Yeah, okay.
I'm for it.
Yeah, and their people on the sewers are basically hoping that God comes down and saves them from the Satan ruling the planet.
And that's kind of where it starts.
The war starts.
Yeah, they're trying... They're basically hiding because the planet's already taken over.
Is it... Okay, so like regular people live down in the sewers because on the surface is Satan and the sheep phone drones.
And a bunch of demons. There's a lot of demons everywhere.
And a bunch of demons.
Yeah.
Sure.
And then so there's a war.
It gets eventually to the war, but eventually God sends down a bunch of heroes, which is why the project's called God's Heroes.
And that's the gist of the plot.
Yeah, that sounds like a setup for an arc.
I see. Do you... I mean, can you tell us who the heroes are?
Well, I showed some of the pictures on... Well, I posted some of the pictures.
Yes.
I saw some of them on your DeviantArt, I think.
The dramatic one with the guy with the moon and with the big grin and he's smoking a joint, that guy.
That's oil guy and the leader of the people that are sent down to help the people in the sewers.
CeCe, CeCe, do you have the link to the DeviantArt somewhere? I lost it.
Yeah, I also didn't hear...
Did you post that?
I didn't hear what his name was.
Oil Guy?
Oil Guy. Oh yeah, now I remember.
I want to look at these.
It's Marin... Not Marin, not Marin Pan.
Eleazar, throw these up on the screen as we name them, I suppose.
Okay, here.
Oil... Oh yeah, Oil Guy.
Oil Guy. Can you continue?
You're trying to... Oh, sorry.
Yeah, I'm trying to post the pictures of the heroes.
Well, some of them are the heroes, some of them are the people in the sewers.
It's the Raptor. The Raptors won the heroes.
The guy with...
The Raptor.
Yeah.
The one who's just a dinosaur?
Yeah, the dinosaur.
Yeah, I see him.
The guy that has a hat and he's got a big nose and he...
That's Skateboard Guy, he's one of the other heroes.
He has messed up teeth.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Skateboard Guy, okay.
The guy that's got bumps all over his head, he's Bumpy Head.
Bumpy Head?
Oh, yep, now there he is.
Yeah.
Those are the heroes.
And the other one is Bomb King, the guy that looks like a...
He's a bomb.
That's the heroes.
The guy who looks like he's a bomb.
I don't see that guy.
You don't see it? I thought I had...
I don't think I see that.
I don't see a bomb guy.
I don't know where he is then.
I thought I uploaded that too.
Oh, wait, no.
I do see him.
No, I found him.
Bomb King.
Oh, here it is.
Yeah.
I didn't see him.
I didn't see him on the page, but I saw him in the Seamore by Ultimate Laserbot.
Like, recommended pictures for some reason.
Yeah, the link I just posted has all of them.
Oh, okay.
And the other people...
Got it.
The other people are basically the people that are in the Sewers.
The other...
Got it.
Yeah, there's a big O...
Just the normal people.
There's big O...
Yeah.
Big O.T. isn't the one in his avatar.
Big O.T.?
It's on the link I posted.
Yeah, that's the...
My avatar is based off of...
He's the one that's later on...
He's the leader of the fan club that's obsessed with the heroes.
Oh, God.
This is making me...
This is reminding me that I really need to get to the dentist soon.
I think I got a cavity.
Um...
Ah, shit.
Amazing.
I mean, since I haven't read God's Heroes yet,
I can't really...
I don't know what to ask,
but if there's anything else you'd like to share about it
or anything else you're working on,
I mean, go for it.
Me and my brother, Micah Shimshamo,
we've been writing it long.
Micah, aka Shimshamo.
You guys have so many...
You're a laserbot,
and then Zagar is also Embergram,
and then Micah is also Shimshamo.
Okay, I just...
I got it.
I got it figured out.
Micah's his real name, though, I think.
Yeah.
I see.
Yeah, it makes sense.
We've been writing it for a while,
and we've actually been kind of off and on
drawing the first book.
Oh, does Micah draw, or does Shimshamo draw, too?
Yeah, we've both been drawing it,
and it's got 10 chapters on there in the first book.
And we got...
We're like five chapters in drawing it.
We're doing the sketching to it,
and we'll eventually do the line work and stuff.
But we're actually planning on releasing it all at once.
It's like, this is season one, book one.
That was gonna be my next question,
is are you gonna release it all in one big batch?
Yeah.
That's why I'm taking so long for it to be made,
because we haven't actually...
We're still working on it.
That's gonna be the one that takes a while to make.
And then we can take break whenever we want,
and then get back to it, and, you know...
If you guys can...
If you got anything to say, you can go ahead.
I was just gonna say, I believe Shimshamo also
drew some guest panels for Kail's sketch tools.
Neat.
Do you know which ones?
Laserbot probably knows.
During Nick and Odie and Demarify,
he had Roadrunner was fucking with Demaro.
He drew one of the panels to that.
A few of the panels.
Demaro had a grin, too.
I don't know which page that was, though.
Let's see.
Might be hard to find.
There's so many different pages.
Yeah, it's a little hard to find.
I'm not gonna dig for it right now.
I might link it to you later or something like that.
I actually have...
Sure, if you post it here, we can put it in later.
I actually have the panels on hand here.
Oh, really?
Oh, my God.
Very good.
The first three were Shimshamo,
and the last one was Ember Graham.
Amazing.
I wouldn't have known.
Well...
Hey...
Fuck.
I think I'm all out of questions.
Okay.
Cybershell, Gibbon,
what do you guys want to...
We should just shoot the shit for a while.
Okay, no, no.
I just...
I've read Tails gets trolled,
not all of it,
so I was sort of...
And it was a while ago as well,
so I wasn't really prepared to have questions for this.
I do want to say
that as an artist,
trying to draw things,
Tails gets trolled is...
It's like...
Strangely inspirational.
It's just the sort of thing everybody wants to do,
is to have a huge, sprawling adventure
with all these characters and doing all these fun things.
It just feels fun.
I can imagine it being really fun
to come up with all this stuff and draw it.
So...
Thanks.
It's a great comic.
You should feel good about it.
True.
Thank you.
I agree.
It is a very fun comic.
That's a good way to put it.
It's just lots of interesting things happening,
and it definitely does seem like
they had fun coming up with all this crazy shit.
Oh yeah, it was really
coming up on plots.
Just coming up with anything you felt like
and just putting it in.
It's like...
For some of my stuff,
I always think it's got to be good.
It's got to be incredible.
I always think my stuff's got to be good,
but you're shit.
You're not bad.
I didn't mean it like that.
I always throw away too many ideas
because I'm like, that's stupid.
That's not going to work.
It has to be like a masterpiece,
like a fucking Leonardo da Vinci.
Like an over-critical kind of thing.
Yeah, yeah.
But it looks like...
I mean, maybe I am being rude here.
It seems like you have these ideas,
and you're just like, yeah, I'll just do it.
I'll just do it, and it just feels great.
It feels great reading it.
That is one thing I love about Tales of your Soul,
is you really never know what's going to happen.
It really feels like anything could happen.
Any normal comic wouldn't just stop
to have multiple chapters of a weed party,
but that's why I love Tales of your Soul,
because it does do that.
Yeah, we wanted to make sure there was no limitations
when we were creating it.
We just wanted to do whatever the fuck we want and add...
That's a great thing about internet creations and stuff like that,
is you really have no limits.
Your only limit is your own imagination.
Is it fine that I curse,
or is that just checking?
Sorry?
Huh?
Oh, yeah, you can say curse words.
Oh, yeah, okay.
It's fine.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no problem.
We're a PG...
We're a hard PG-13 podcast, I think.
It's safe to say.
Imagine you're working for Cartoon Network,
and you're pitching your...
You're like, okay, I got this idea for a cartoon.
It's about Tales, and he gets trolled,
and they're like, no, we can't do Tales.
He's copyrighted.
He's like, okay, we'll replace him with some other guy.
It's like, okay, go on.
All right, all right.
So in my Cartoon idea, this kid gets trolled,
and then his friend says, let's go kill the trolls.
And they're like, okay, we'll do it,
but you can't have any blood, and he's like, okay, deal.
And then Mr. Suit, Mr. Executive Man,
the entire second season is just a big party
where they all smoke weed, and they're like, no,
no, your show's canceled.
No, you can't do it.
You can't put that on the air.
There's like a gradient of artistic expression.
On the one hand, you've got Tales gets trolled,
and on the other hand, you have Bus Baby.
You have to choose one.
Bus Baby.
Which way?
Western, man.
Exactly.
You know, if it was...
I'd imagine...
I'm sorry.
I'd imagine Tales gets trolled.
No, go on, ladies.
Sorry.
I'd imagine Tales gets trolled as a adult swim kind of cartoon.
I don't imagine it like...
Yes.
Yeah.
Like adult swim.
Like a cartoon.
Yeah.
Like south kids on their channel, or shit like that.
I can see it.
I can see it now.
Yeah, apart from the rampant copyright infringement type dealio,
I could totally see this being like an adult swim type of like show,
you know what I mean?
What if...
I mean, what if someone just...
What if they just like...
50 Shades of Graded, by which...
You know what I mean when I say that?
I feel like in a perfect world,
he should just be allowed to make Tales get trolled,
and it's like...
Why is this not covered under like fair use and shit?
It doesn't make any sense that you should...
It's just so stupid.
It gets me heated to even think about it, but yeah, it is like...
I get what you're saying.
I mean, we should literally just abolish copyright.
But in the absence of that,
what if somebody...
What if some big corporation just 50 Shades did?
50 Shades of Graded.
We're like...
Well...
No, like...
50 Shades of Graded was like a fan fiction of Twilight or something.
It became its own thing.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, 50 Shades...
They just...
Yeah, and someone just took it and they're like...
We're trying to explain this all at the same time.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, and then...
Yeah, so I mean, just like...
Okay, we got this story.
It's all full of these copyrighted characters.
Well, let's just...
We'll republish it, but we'll just...
We'll just change the names.
We'll just change the characters.
I feel like...
I hear what you're saying.
I just feel like that would be so hard to do with Tales get trolled,
because there's like all these copyrighted characters.
They're always like doing these things that would be just like...
How do you properly...
I mean, like, okay, you translate Sonic going Super Saiyan, whatever.
You just have like a stand-in for that.
But then, like, a lot of the things, like, how do you have the scene where Bugs Bunny
explains that he only does the gay shit to, you know, trick them?
Like, that would make sense with a character that wasn't Bugs Bunny, you know what I mean?
It's okay.
That just makes it funnier.
Well, like, that it would be not Bugs Bunny?
Well, because you'd read that and you'd be like,
like, what the fuck?
This is so weird.
And then your friend who is, like, in the know and a bigger nerd,
then you would be like, oh, yeah, that part.
You know that character actually was based on Bugs Bunny?
So that's why it used to make sense.
But now it doesn't make sense in the remake anymore.
So to get the full experience of this, you need somebody...
You need somebody at your side to say,
ah, this character.
This character is based on...
You should just make each character...
I mean, isn't...
Like, get a hue in Photoshop.
Isn't that what part is, though?
Get a hue in, like, shift the hue so there's different color
and then, like, change the name, like, put the last letter
at the front of the name.
Yeah, just barely do palette swaps since, like, sales gets trolled.
Yeah, like, why not?
Like, that should be close enough.
I mean, that should be enough to get you not sued.
Isn't that what art is, though?
Just an excuse to connect to people and talk to people.
And if it gets to people, be like, oh, that character used to be Elmer Fudd
in the original version.
But they had to change it because of copyright.
I think it's good.
Wait, you're saying that's the purpose of art,
is to have conversations like that?
Yeah, copyright's good, actually.
Yeah, just...
No, not about copyright, but a thing for people to connect over.
Oh, yeah.
And having that conversation where you're like, oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, this is the...
Oh, yeah, I'm reading the...
What's it called?
I'm reading the One Punch Man remake of Tales Gets Trolled,
which has had all the copyrighted characters scrubbed out of it.
And you're like, haha, this part's so funny,
but it doesn't make any sense, and it's weird.
And then someone has to explain to you, oh, yeah,
this was actually Kermit the Frog, and that was Mario.
And then you go, oh, and that's a conversation.
I was gonna say, it's kind of bold to just make a piece of art that,
on its own, Flat Out doesn't make sense, and you can't understand it,
unless you know all this shit from, like, the previous version.
I agree.
No, I'm not even saying it's bad.
I would buy that version.
I understand.
Well, okay, the funny thing is, this sort of left the original,
but I would also buy that version.
There was gonna be Tales Realm, right?
Like, there was gonna be a version of Tales Gets Trolled
with non-copyrighted characters at some point.
Yeah, we were gonna make that,
but we never got around to actually making that,
which it wasn't a bad idea,
but it was just a concept, really.
Right.
Yeah, like I was saying, it seems like it would be more work
than you would initially think,
just to uncopyrightify everything,
but somehow make it all make sense still, you know what I mean?
Like, it's, I don't know.
I mean, it's like, is it really worth it to do that?
No.
I mean, in point of fact, the only good reason to do that
would be if, like, a network wanted to pick it up,
and they had to do it.
If you're just a guy making it, then, like, no, fuck it.
You know what?
Like, obviously, you don't have to worry about that.
You know what the weird thing is, though?
Like, there's shows, like, like, robot chicken,
but I don't know what, like, copyright thing
they were able to use.
I feel like it's one of the hardest parts of this.
It's the parody thing.
I feel like a lot of it could get covered under parody,
but, like, the title tale gets trolled.
Well, it's a bit much.
Well, that's making the physical version just called TGT.
See, that's a good workaround.
A lot of, like, bands will do that when they have a name
that's, you know, they're not allowed to use it anymore.
They'll just go, oh, I'll just go by the acronym,
so our fans still know it's us,
but then we don't have to have the copyrighted character's name
in the title of our thing, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
If you ask me, if you're just someone printing books on your own
and distributing them on your own,
I don't think you have to worry about Sega cracking down on you
because your book had...
Luckily, yeah, Sega is not so bad about this in particular.
There are like a ton of characters in there, but...
Tails is not a copyrightable name.
That's just an English word.
Yeah, I know.
It's just that it also happens to be referring to Tails,
the character from Sega.
If it was like Miles Tails Pro gets trolled,
then it would be different.
I hear what you're saying.
You're right.
The name, like, just Tails.
You can't just copyright Tails, period,
and, like, have that under all circumstances.
It's just, I mean, like I already said,
I completely think you should just be allowed to do it
and not have any problems ever at any sort of degree, but...
You could switch it around.
You could call it Troll Tails,
because that would be a pun as well, and it would work.
Yeah.
It was Tails about trolling.
Right.
There's a lot of little things you can do.
It's just, like we already said, it's like,
it's a lot of work.
Is there even really a point?
Like, unless you're going to get picked up
for like a network, yeah.
Right.
At the end of the day,
unless we're talking about, like, something like that,
I don't think it matters at all.
I'm just speculating on, like,
if it ever were to get a remake like that,
I honestly think it would be hilarious,
and I would treasure it.
I don't...
It looked like Tails gets trolled the legal version.
It really depends on how they would do it.
Yeah.
The execution.
I'm curious about Tails...
What was it, Tails Realms?
I don't think I'd heard of that.
Tails Realms.
What was that?
Can you tell me more about Tails Realms?
Well, we didn't really have anything on it other than we were...
We were in the process of drawing on paper
some of the characters,
what they might look like if they were original characters,
but I don't have any of that on the computer or anything.
I was going to ask,
if you have those pictures, I'd love to see them.
I would be interested in seeing those designs
if you ever, like, found them or wanted to recreate them,
but it's not necessary.
That's just an interesting piece of trivia, though,
because I knew that it was an idea.
I didn't even know you got that far,
like, drawing the character designs.
I thought I didn't even get that far.
That was really all it at was, is some sketches,
and I don't know exactly where they are right now.
Right.
I remember that was during the period
when it was, like, polished, was going on,
and you were trying about a bunch of different stuff.
Like, there was also a censored was briefly a thing,
but then that was just dropped pretty early on.
Yeah, we dropped it,
because we realized there was no way we could censor it.
You just can't, right? Exactly.
Like, you can do the first few pages
just by changing the words and stuff,
but at a certain point,
you just can't censor it without changing way too much stuff.
Yeah.
I tried, like, continuing it myself,
because I thought it was an interesting idea,
but once you get to chapter four with, like,
blood everywhere and stuff, like, you can't really...
You can't really...
Right.
Like, you could do a version that just censored the dialogue,
but, like, what's the point
if there's still all this horrific violence
and there's, like, drug use and sex stuff later on?
It's like, I mean,
what's the point in trying to censor it really?
Yeah.
You, like, four kids dub of one piece, like...
It was funny, like, I just Photoshopped the legs back together
and just, like, ooh, I got a bruise.
Exactly.
It would be funny.
Well, that's sort of what happened,
like, there's a little bit of violence in the pages they did,
but it was just, like, bloodless,
and it was just, like, the stuffers was, like,
stuff was supposed to get broken in half,
like, just nothing happened.
You could use the round with the Dragon Ball Z round,
have changed the color of the blood.
What if Knuckles invites,
Knuckles invites all the prostitutes
to all Cheeto Man's prostitutes together?
The hangman.
And they all hug and give each other a cold.
I'm just trying to imagine how a censored version
of the Corpse pipe page would look,
like, how could that even possibly be conveyed
in the other one?
Do you know what I mean?
I would think just to just show Tails' reaction
without actually showing the pipe.
Right.
Wait, the Corpse?
Corpse pipe?
Well, it would be very vague if it wasn't done, right?
Yeah.
Right.
Yeah, I was gonna say, that's the only problem.
Remind me.
After the Cheeto Man, the party, you know,
the plan goes off to give him all STDs,
so he has to kill all his hoes,
and then there's just that one brutal page.
Oh, like, the big, the big masquerade.
Yeah, the masquerade.
It's in a weird, like, pipe thing.
That's why I call it the Corpse pipe,
but it's like, yeah, it is basically a masquerade,
if you're right, that's a better,
that was a more apt description of it.
Death Pit.
I didn't even notice that it was in a pipe.
The Death Pit.
My favorite page.
That was the last time we saw Tails for so long.
Only recently, we sort of, like, got that page of him,
and he's like, oh, shit, back to Tails.
That was the other thing people used to get really upset
about back in the day.
I remember on something awful.
Anytime, like, Tails wasn't on,
it wasn't in a page for too long,
people were like, where's Tails?
I don't want to see these original characters,
I only want to see Tails.
Okay, pitch for the next chapter.
Anytime Tails isn't on screen,
all the other characters should be asking,
where's Tails?
Where's Tails?
That's basically how it was for a while
on something awful.
Like, it was a very interesting period
because people were very, like,
just dismissive of it at first,
and then there were people who were like,
went out of their way just to troll,
you know, laser-bond me, like, oh, this is bad.
But then, after, he just kept going.
Like, he didn't quit, he just kept going.
Eventually, people were just, like,
posting the new page and just, like, excited to read it.
This is bad.
Hey, why'd you stop updating?
I want more.
Give me more.
That's basically what happened.
So I can call it bad.
But I want it.
Basically, that's so weird,
that's like, that's really what happened.
The funny thing was, it was like,
they didn't want to admit that they liked it.
Right.
Yeah, people were in denial about it.
They're like, I just, I'm ironically reading it.
And people kept being like, guys,
like, I'm just, this chapter,
like, I really ironically liked this page, guys.
I really, yeah.
It's like, I mean, I used to look at the
something awful thread about control all delete.
And like, every time, I mean,
control all delete is a legitimately bad comic.
Right.
But every time he would post a new comic,
I've never heard of it.
Everyone there would jump on it.
That's the danger of a hate, like, watching.
This is like, this is literally how,
like, Darkseid feel like, sustains himself.
He doesn't even have fans.
He only has people who hate him,
but they, like, love to hate him.
So they give him money,
so they can control him into keeping on doing what he's,
it doesn't make any sense,
but this is literally how part of the internet works now.
Every time a new control all delete came on,
all of the something awful goons would jump on it.
They would all post it.
They would all be like, oh, it's so bad, guys.
This is so bad.
Here, they would do extensive rewrites of it.
They would make edits of it.
Yeah, the edits.
I remember every comic, there'd be some fancy fucking edit.
And people were spending so much time on it.
Pages and pages.
There were guys who had like, okay,
let's do our thing.
We're like, we'll take, we'll try to take out dialogue
and rewrite it to make the dialogue more snappy.
And, you know, people would post like,
guys, we are the CAD fans.
We are the fan base.
This is what we've become.
They're the ones getting the most excited about the new pages
and stuff.
I can't believe CAD is still fucking going.
They are.
God, is it?
Yeah, it's still going.
It was like, I don't want to get an old CAD tangent,
but it ended and then it rebooted with a new universe.
It was some bullshit.
I knew that that happened, but that was a long time ago.
It must.
Yeah, it was a while ago, actually.
I will never get over the fact that the comic,
the original run literally ended with the universe resetting,
but it wasn't, he even had to press a button
to reset the universe.
The button wasn't control or delete.
It was just a red button and everyone was like,
why wasn't it control or delete?
He should have pressed control or delete
to like reset the universe.
He's like, it's the most obvious missed opportunity.
What a fucking hack.
It was like the most embarrassing thing ever.
Buckley, you fuck.
I'd be like, if you made a comic called,
Tails gets told and Tails never got trolls.
Right.
I love that Tails gets trolled.
Exactly like that.
The first page.
That is really a descriptor of what happens on the first page.
I guess he continues to get trolled in general,
but it's that really...
It's the inciting incident.
It is the inciting incident, definitely, for sure.
It's the call to action.
It's the call to action that incites the hero's journey.
Exactly.
You're right.
It works perfectly fine as that kind of title,
but it is just funny.
Later on, you're watching this crazy Coyote flashback
to this Satanist stuff and then it's like,
what was this about again?
Oh, yeah.
Tails getting trolled.
Tails miles per hour from Sonic the Hedgehog.
Yeah.
I love that.
What was it called in Berserk when the whole,
you know, when Griffith ascends?
Eclipse.
The eclipse.
That's the beginning.
The very first page of Tails gets trolled
is Tails is Eclipse from there.
It is amazing how he's just like,
he's walking along and then these trolls,
they just start insulting him
and it destroys him emotionally.
He's like sobbing, sprinting away.
Like, he can't handle it.
I looked at the first page and there's something
really compelling about how the fact that,
like, left to his own devices,
no one's bothering him,
Tails is just walking along going,
la, la, la, la, la, la.
Yeah, that's the first line of the comic.
I love it.
He's so happy.
I think Laserbot wanted to say something.
I forgot.
I forgot what I was going to say.
Oh, fuck.
I just got a little excited there.
I wanted to mention that I say,
I quote that Kermit line all the time.
Have you ever been bitch slapped for lack of listening?
Lack of doing what you're told?
Because I'm not far from slapping you.
But people often forget.
I say it to my wife, if you know what I mean.
People often forget that after he says that he says,
did you see what I just did wrong there?
Because he's showing Tails what a lack of patience is.
Does he?
Honestly.
I don't remember.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Fuck.
So you're saying that I missed the point of the scene?
Yeah.
Kermit does a lot of experimental things with his choice of words.
Well, yeah, I really love that page of Kermit with the giant,
just the biggest fucking wall of text.
And it's like a metatextual thing where you have to deal with
your own lack of patience and read the whole fucking thing.
And if you don't read it, if you just skip it, I mean,
you can do that, but you'll miss out on an important lore
and a flashback later on.
You'll fail the test.
I don't blame you, Ben, because that Kermit line became
like a meme.
And people, like, re-posted it, but they took out the last part
where he says, did you see what I just did wrong there?
I mean, it's just a really funny thing to say.
Yeah.
And I...
Yeah, a couple with the image.
Yeah, I mean, he's doing...
So Kermit, so Serene.
So Serene.
Hmm, have you ever been bitch slapped for lack of listening?
Lack of doing what you're told?
Because I'm not far from slapping you.
There it is.
Yeah, I was about to post that.
Oh, did you see what I...
Yeah, they do.
They edit out.
They edit out the other.
And I got it.
Yeah, I googled it.
I googled it and I found the edited version.
It's so crazy to me how far, like, TGT reaction images have gone.
Like, the big one, obviously, is that Tom reaction face.
I had no idea.
I had no idea how far that had spread and how many, like, normies have seen that
and they had no idea what it's from, you know what I mean?
The Bugs Bunny panel has gone pretty far, too.
But the Tom face reaction, I was surprised how...
Like, you can see that.
You can find that anywhere.
I don't really...
I don't really think about the Tom reaction face.
I was surprised to see that that's kind of, like, the biggest meme.
Yeah, that's what I agree.
Like, that was just a random...
Like, it's a funny panel.
Don't get me wrong.
But I agree.
I don't think it's going to my, like, top panel or, like, what I first think of when I think of it.
That's why I was surprised that it got spread so far.
It is a very nice expression, but, like...
I think there's a lot of great expressions like that in the comic.
Oh, is it...
I can't remember.
Is it, like, a good expression, like, devoid of context?
Do the other ones require context?
Is that probably why it's spread, if it was, like, just a funny face?
It has a very, like, shocked...
It has a more...
It's definitely more applicable, you know what I mean?
Like, you can see what that one would've...
Simple, like, I can't believe you posted this sort of face.
Yeah.
Unsettled Tom.
But, yeah, you'll see a lot of people say that they didn't know this was from TGT.
They'll be like, I thought it was from the show or, like, something, and I'm like...
It's just so obvious to me.
Like, you just look at the art side.
It's like, that clearly tells you it's true.
It doesn't...
It definitely doesn't look like a classic.
I know.
It doesn't look like any other type of commentary media.
I agree with you, but I still see people say that.
Yeah, it's weird.
And I saw the other day someone drew porn of it, and that's pretty...
Oh, that face?
This reaction page of this one panel.
Jesus Christ.
I've posted, but it's not safe for work, so I don't know if you'd want to see that.
Oh, we probably can't show it on the show.
Yeah, I was going to say, I want to see it.
You don't have to put it in general or anything right now.
Like, obviously, I know you can't show it in the episode, but that's interesting.
People should know that exists either way.
Hey, Marin, put it up and blur it.
Pixelate it.
I'll try to find it.
Someone posted it in the server the other day.
Oh, here it is.
Here's the link.
You can click on it if you want, but...
Oh, my God.
I have to admit, I love...
Oh, it showed the thumbnail.
Okay, that is ridiculous.
Oh, yeah.
Yep.
There it is.
I was going to say earlier, one of my favorite parts about Tales of Troll is just all the fan art and stuff.
And yeah, it doesn't disappoint.
There's so much crazy fan art out there.
Yeah, but the thing is, the guy who did that probably didn't even know it was from Tales of Troll.
Yeah, it probably just was like, this will be a great meme.
This will get me lots of clicks because people know what this meme is.
Yeah.
What do you think about that laser bot?
Oh, the memes are the fan art.
Oh, the memes.
Some of them are pretty good.
Some of them I'm like, meh.
But the main ones are actually pretty well.
What's a dumb one that you think is dumb?
I actually haven't looked at that meme in a while, so I would have to look through them and be like, man, that one's kind of dumb.
But right the second I don't have one in mind.
I'm trying to think if I can think of any TGT memes that I don't think are that funny.
Yeah, they're...
Are there any lame ones?
There are some, but I can't think of them from the top of my head.
I mean, if they're lame, then I didn't laugh, so I probably wouldn't remember them.
I just remember the good ones.
Yeah, I'm looking at the comments on this porn image.
A couple people know that it's a meme.
One comment does say he says Tom gets trolled, so he knows.
The other ones don't seem to know.
This one guy is like, look at this fucking square.
Alright, look at this fucking square.
He sees a picture of a cat getting fucked with a weird face, and they freak out.
This is the most disturbing thing they've seen in the entire life.
There's really nothing you can say to a comment like that besides, like, what is this, your first day on the fucking internet?
Like, what's going on here?
I've got some...
This is vanilla.
If you don't even get the meme reference, then this is, yeah, beyond vanilla.
It's just like regular fur.
It's like, how could you not know this exists?
It's just regular old cartoon sex with a kind of weird facial expression.
Man, you're gonna be subject to worse horrors in this life.
Yeah, and the Tom gets trolled comment was posted today, so it was probably someone from the Discord.
It was probably me. Yeah, it was me.
Yeah, it was me, too.
Sorry, sorry.
It was me, too, okay.
Fuck, man, what a good comment. Am I right, dudes?
Yes, yes you are.
Hell yeah, hell yeah.
Oh, yeah, man.
Yeah, man, yeah.
Well, now what?
How's everyone's day gone?
How's everyone's life?
Are you relaxed?
Is the weather okay where you're doing?
Hope it's not too hot.
It's the height of summer.
It's the dog days of summer.
You know why they call it the dog days?
It's because the sun is passing by the dog star.
That's why they call it that.
I have never heard any of those expressions before.
You never heard the dog days of summer?
No.
It's not a common expression.
Okay, well, whatever.
You learned something today.
Anyway, how's life?
I'm doing pretty good.
Laserbot, tell me how you're feeling.
Just what's going on?
What's going on?
Tell us about your life.
I'm pretty chill right now.
Like I said, I'm sick right now, but I'm getting passed out.
Oh, no.
You don't have the coronavirus, do you?
I'm pretty sure I don't.
I had, I paid an artist to do some PCP related work.
And the moment that I paid them, they contracted the novel
coronavirus.
Well, that's suck.
I hope they're doing all right.
I hope so too.
Your brother said he was sick too, which is why he hasn't written
any more tales gets trolls.
Yeah, everybody's sick in our night.
Everybody around is sick.
We all got each other sick.
Sad, sad.
I don't know anything else.
Anything else going on?
Any hot gossip to share?
Nothing hard.
I mean, the only thing that's been on my mind is the Lord of
Ghost Kickstarter, which if I check, this would come out
on the 16th.
So there's like one, two, three, four, five days until it would
be over by the time this goes live.
If everything goes, if everything goes well, it might not
even be necessary by the time this episode comes out to say
it, but I do want to say to anyone listening, Lord of Ghost
Kickstarter, if you want the plush because I want the plush,
I don't care that I'm going to have to pay for a shipping from
the UK.
I'll pay.
I'll pay anything.
Right.
I'm what we, I'm what you in the business call a whale.
If you want that, if you want that plush, a great a sucker.
If you want the plush, I went and I upped my pledge by the,
it was, it was 45 pounds was going to be the increase in
price for the shipping plus the plush.
I increased it by 50.
Just because if I assume that if I think that if everyone who
wants the plush ups their pledge, that will probably go a long
way towards actually hitting the goal.
It will, which the plush becomes possible.
It will.
I expressly said not to do that just, just for the moment,
because I didn't want to like to give.
Well, I did it.
It's fine.
Like if you, if you know you're willing to take the risk,
it might not get funded.
But well, if it, if it, if it's, if it's five, if it's five
minutes from hitting from, from completion and it's nowhere
near hitting the plush goal, then maybe all.
Yeah.
I mean, not everybody will be able to.
Wait.
What is the, what is this?
What are you guys talking about?
Oh, this is, it's one of my comics, the Lord of ghosts,
which is about a little blob ghost.
Let me get a link for it.
Oh yeah.
To me and I'll look at it later.
I've, I've, oh, you should definitely read.
You should read Lord of ghosts.
It's very funny.
And it's very, it's, it's, it's, it's cute.
Give is a, give makes, give has a website with comics on them.
I actually, it's, it's like some sort of a way.
It's like a really badly made website.
I don't know anything about HTML or any code, but.
You know what?
It works.
It displays images.
It does its job.
Yeah.
That's how, that's how the tails gets trolled.
So it used to be.
And kind of still is.
Yeah.
And here's the plush that's been working on.
The Lord of ghosts is like a little comic and it's,
I wanted to, to kickstart a physical version of it.
So I can have it on my shelf and people can be like, oh,
I own the thing.
And it's, it's been going well, the Kickstarter.
We've reached the goal.
We've reached stretch goals.
The last one is this plush.
And the, yeah, it'll be, I, I, I'm excited.
I've been excited.
Yeah.
Good luck to you on that.
I, I wish you the best of luck.
Thanks.
It will have, by the time this episode comes out,
there will be, I think it's three,
going to be three days left on that.
Three, four days.
Yeah.
I, I upped my pledge, even though technically we haven't hit the goal
for the, for the plush yet.
I think if more people do that, we will hit it.
I mean, I'm, I plan to just be there when, you know,
the timer runs down to zero.
And if it's still, you know, a thousand plus dollars away,
when it's like a minute out from ending, then I'll be like,
okay, nevermind.
I'll take the 45 bucks with the pounds back.
Yeah.
But like, I think it'll, I think it'll probably hit it.
And like, if it doesn't, I can take it back.
But for the moment, I'm like, no, I'll put,
I'll put the money there because I intend to spend it.
Right.
And I, and it's going to help us push it over the,
because we got to get it over the threshold.
Yeah.
So I hope others will consider doing the same.
I checked the, I made a Twitter poll to like gauge how many people
would like, like add that much money to their pledge in order to get the
plush.
And I think if I look at the results so far, I think it's close to being
enough.
If they all,
Like the proportion.
Yeah.
The proportion.
Like a lot of people said no is too expensive, which I expected.
Cause it's a, it's a shipping to America.
It's a premium item.
Yeah.
Shipping and just a plush in general is quite expensive.
Well, hey, we got a hundred votes at the moment.
35% say yes.
65 no.
So that's 35 people.
35 times.
So that's so about a third.
So if a third of the people that were pledged increase their pledge by
45 times like 45.
So that's 1,535 pounds.
That would, I think that would get us to the, to the point, but I don't
know how many of these yes votes are like in the UK or elsewhere.
So not sure yet, but still got nine days to go.
So it's probably, it's probably possible, probably very possible.
Listen audience, why don't you think about it this way?
This is going to be a limited edition plush.
It's only going to go up in value.
So if you don't buy it now, you're losing money in the long run.
It doesn't make sense to not buy it.
You should literally take out a loan right now to buy the plush.
You should buy it on credit because you will pay it.
You will be able to pay that back and more.
Listen, if we have any kids in the audience, first thing you're going to
want to go grab your parents credit card right now, enter all that
information in the Kickstarter and just give all that money.
Yeah.
And then get off the Internet right away and don't come back.
Everyone says, oh, Bitcoin, oh, perfect store of value.
Oh, it can only go up.
Fuck that.
The Lord of Ghost plush is the ideal store of value because there's
only going to be like 40 of them.
Bitcoin's not even real.
It's just a bunch of fucking numbers.
Like you can't even hold it.
You can hold the plush.
You can't even hug it.
You can't, you can't, you can't hug a Bitcoin.
So what, so what good does it, what does it serve a man?
We all know with the next 10 to 15 years, the whole Internet is just
going to go down permanently.
And we're all going to have, the only thing we're going to have left is
our plush collections.
So if you don't have this now, you're going to be fucked in the future.
Yeah.
What else are you going to build?
What else are you going to build the bomb shelter out of, huh?
When North Korea goes ape?
Damn.
Sorry.
One thing I was wondering is how you actually made it.
Oh, so this, this was a, it's a company, I think they had, they used
to be called Budsies, but then they branched off into two things.
One for like mass production called stuffed animal pros.
And I asked them, you know, I got like a quote for like how
much it would cost to make 50 of these.
I gave them like a design and they started off as like a company
that makes plushes for kids.
Like kids would draw their like crayon drawing and their parents would
send that in and get a plush made of their like kids drawing.
And the kids would be like, oh, Pog, Pog based.
Yeah.
It's a really, it's really cool.
It's a really cool little service, a little expensive for a one off,
but you can do like mass production.
Obviously the more you like order, the cheaper each item will be.
And since the audience I expect is quite small for this plush,
the minimum, the maximum I'm expecting to shift is like 50.
So this is based off of if I make 50 plushes, this is how much
they'll cost.
I feel like I will just be swimming in these little guys for a
little while after the Kickstarter if we reach that goal.
But that's fine because they're funny.
It'll be good to have some extras, you know what I mean?
Especially for like, you know, you can hand them out on the street corner.
Save them for later.
Table at a convention or something.
I literally could.
I could when I make like lot of ghosts like act three when there's
like the finale or whatever it is.
I have the second Kickstarter and then I have a bunch of plushes ready
to go and it's not even going to be difficult to get them providing
we hit this time.
I still want to say it's a lot of it's a lot of money.
It's a lot of like logistics and like figuring it out,
but it's finally getting close to being happening.
It's cool.
Yeah, I still want to make a real Alex plushes with like a real cigarette.
What do you mean a real cigarette?
I heard you say that you mean like a real tobacco cigarette that comes
with the doll.
Yeah.
Well, you don't even you don't.
Well, you have to supply your own right.
He just comes with a little hole in his mouth.
You're trying to sell a plushie online and you have to abide by all
like the tobacco regulations because it comes with a cigarette.
Like you can't sell it to kids.
Like it comes.
It comes with a with a pet like you partner with like new ports
or something and there's a brand deal.
Yeah.
You try to set light to it and then you burn the plushies like oh shit.
Got to buy another one.
Right.
It's like the plushies flammable.
Please don't use the cigarette that's included with the plushie dipped
in fucking gasoline.
It's called planned obsolescence.
This is sort of a million dollars.
This is sort of this is sort of related but not really.
I have a question for Laserbot.
How did you come up with the design for the Troll King?
I looked up actual trolls and I just kind of used them as a inspiration
and I just kind of drew them.
Did you?
I always loved the twist of the Troll King being like being an actual bridge
troll and you know an Alex plush would be nice but there's so many other
original TGT characters that would make nice plushies.
I like a Troll King.
Yeah.
That's that's why that's why I asked that.
I'm actually going to be leaving soon.
So I do got a question.
What what series would you like to see TGT crossover with?
Oh I oh okay.
I don't think you've read it but Homestuck would be ridiculous.
Oh my god.
Oh my god please please.
They have their own trolls in there.
It would be it would be perfect.
You're right appropriate crossover.
Yeah, it would be so perfect.
Yes.
Homestuck is also about trolls.
Oh my god.
That's way better than my answer.
I was going to say One Piece.
Has One Piece been in?
Yeah, I don't think so.
I don't think so no.
The only anime that has been in is Dragon Ball Z and there was like Naruto references too.
Well do do Homestuck first and then maybe do One Piece if you feel like it afterwards.
I can just imagine Karkhet and Shadow the Hedgehog.
I can see it in my mind's eye.
Damn.
That's way better than my answer.
I was going to say like Frazier.
No, you know what?
Frazier is good though.
That would work.
Frazier is pretty good.
Well I mean Frazier is technically part of the Cheers universe so really you should say Cheers.
Yeah you got me there.
No you should have the whole Cheers cast.
If I see a Homestuck troll and Tails gets trolled I will lose my shit.
I will flying Guillotine myself in celebration.
Alright, I think I'm going to say that.
I was going to say are you headed out laser bond?
Yeah, I'm headed out.
Well, it's been a real treat.
Thank you for doing an interview.
It was much appreciated.
I was pretty chill.
Yeah, thanks man.
It was a great having you on and you too.
Don't be a stranger.
Maybe we'd love to have you on again sometime if you've ever got like a new thing you want to help promote or something.
Yeah, okay.
Love to.
Yeah.
Cool.
Alright, well then have a good one and we're going to go to voicemails soon I guess.
Alright, have a nice day everybody.
Peace.
Bye bye.
Peace dude.
Awesome.
I can't believe it.
It finally happened.
It's only three years after that comment he left on the video.
I remember seeing that comment and I was like damn I wonder if he is going to be on the PCB.
That'd be awesome.
And then he just wasn't and I was like okay I guess it's not going to happen.
And then it happened and I was here in the call when it happened.
Crazy man.
My hero, watch him as he goes.
I said this in the beginning.
I'm just going to re-emphasize this to the puny peasant PCP listeners who don't even appreciate how good of a get that was.
That was getting laser bought on a podcast.
Well, first of all, it's an ordeal just to get any of the technical difficulties sorted out.
But then even getting him to agree to do it in the first place.
If you listen to the bonus footage that will be coming out on a bonus episode, yeah, you can hear us struggling with technical issues for like half an hour
before we actually got the call to work.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah, I asked him years ago and he said he couldn't do a thing.
And I think he has not done like any like podcast stuff because he's literally just not been in possession of a microphone.
Right, or internet or a computer or just something stopping him from doing it.
It's always been like just something.
And that's why it's been like, I've been a fan of, you know, Tails is full for a long time, but I just, you know, statements from laser bought are pretty rare.
I would mostly get my laser bought news from CC lately and but like over the historically, it's like whatever you could get would be like an occasional
DeviantArt post or whatever.
I never even heard his voice until the freaking Newgrounds panel, which I was surprised to even showed up to.
So yeah, it's pretty, it's pretty, it's a pretty big get.
I just want to emphasize that again for you folks in the audience.
Don't even understand.
Do you think any other podcast could get this?
No, only only this podcast with the biggest tails gets rolled heads out out there.
Yeah.
Literally the two biggest.
Dab dab.
Besides the Newgrounds one.
The only time I heard his voice was that one video he made of it was like a scene from chapter three with a shadow.
Right.
There's like one animated thing from Tails gets told easy to like skip over if you're just reading the comic.
It's just reading the comic like as is because you know, it is.
But like when it came out originally, there was like, oh, there's like an animated version of this page.
And it was like, whoa, that's crazy.
Yeah.
But there was like laser butted laser butted Alex's voice in that one.
I assume that his it was his voice in Micorat, but he's kind of doing like weird funny voices in that one.
So I assume it didn't.
It wasn't what he actually sounds like.
Right.
And it's not.
Yeah.
You know, it'll be really funny if even though Craig said he's recording, he wasn't recording the whole interview has just lost time again.
Well, okay.
CC, are you still doing OBS or did you stop?
Yes, I'm still doing OBS.
Okay.
Worst case scenario, we still got most of the interview.
Yeah.
That's true.
It's pro.
It's all signs point to that it went fine and is okay.
That was pretty great though that there were technical difficulties from him and also from Craig.
I was there have been there have been days when Craig simply does not work at all.
I was like, when he left the call before, I thought maybe like, Oh God, it's one of those times.
It's happening.
But no.
Something about discord bots, I don't trust them.
I feel like they're prone to fail because they're like a billion different servers.
I have a billion different people asking them to do shit.
Yeah.
No, discord bots always work perfectly.
Are they like never any game game breaking glitches that give people trillions of slime or break the game or the economy.
The stock market never crashes and then skyrockets again.
It sounds like a feature.
You know, that's right.
They never fail.
They only add features.
That's the kind of dynamic like storytelling you can't get from a bot that works properly.
Yeah.
True.
Are you saying good?
No, I was just wondering about how bots work.
Like if they're, because they're discord, like the developer puts them on like a server and it's hosted somewhere.
And then every server that has it is like taking bandwidth from the thing.
I don't think that's how it works.
That would be weird.
You should, you should ask Crack.
You should ask Crack.
He's the only person that I know.
Or maybe Dwoob.
Maybe Dwoob might know.
One of those two might have an idea.
I'm not sure anyone else I know could even begin to explain it.
I tried to make like a, like a, like a ripoff of Endless War, Endless Mud in fact.
The very same that's in The Lord of Ghosts.
I tried to make a discord bot.
And also big booby mommy milkers.
I didn't make that.
That was a copy that Doon Koon made.
Oh.
But yeah, it's the same sort of like, it's really confusing trying to set up a discord bot that responds to any commands in any way.
I thought, I just spend like a couple days like tinkering around and like coming up with like, I type in a command and the bot will read it and then say something.
It's like impossible.
How hard could it be?
It doesn't sound like it would be that hard, but I believe that it is that hard, trust me.
I don't know.
I completely forgot all these things I learned.
There is, they look really simple.
If you go, you go into a server and it's like, oh, you can go and you can tag your little self and you can say like, oh, click this emote to give yourself a he, him pronoun or whatever.
Simple.
But yeah, when I tried, actually, like I couldn't actually do it.
Crack had to do it for me.
And that's the only reason Endless War exists.
Yeah, it's like, it's one of those things that like under the hood is like, actually, there's a lot of like.
There's a lot of communication going on between because he, because it's it's communicating between, you know, like the server, like you're typing and then it's going to discord and then discord is telling the bot and then bot is communicating with discord and then it's sending the the roll back to you right to your account.
Right.
So there's a lot going on there.
Um, but anyway, um, I mean, I guess back to just a what's up.
What's up with me?
Yeah, is that I'm moving.
I'm looking for a house.
You're moving.
I'm moving.
It's horrible.
Apparently this.
It's kind of horrible.
Uh, you know, it's, it's really not that bad, but I don't deal well with this kind of thing.
And I'm very stressed out about it.
And I'm searching for like an apartment and stuff is the worst thing in the world.
So I believe that's shitty.
I have, um, yeah, I've, I basically have not.
I was on such a roll with working on my game last month and then this month rolled around
and then suddenly I was like, wait a minute, I have to take care of some like financial
tax stuff.
And it took me like three days.
I basically did like a full audit of my like income, like by month for the last like two
years or two and a half years.
And that took me three days and I was like, okay, that's done.
Now I can't go back to doing the game.
It's really getting late and I have to look for a house.
So I've just been like house hunting and stuff.
And I, and it's a lot of waiting.
It's really frustrating because there's a lot of sending emails and waiting, which
technically you would think means, oh, I have downtime.
I can work on the game, but I am not capable of it.
It's too stressful and I can't focus because I'm too much like, you don't have any good,
like you can't just 100% hunker down and focus on.
I had a huge momentum going and then I had to be like, scree to a halt and do the tax
stuff.
And then I'm like, I got it.
It's other thing.
I got to take care of this other thing.
Cause if I'm homeless, I can't make a video game.
Yeah.
Same.
At least about just moved to and I moved a few months ago as well.
So everyone's moving out.
Did you have fun?
Was it my first?
Do you have fun moving?
Did you like your new place?
At least that's like a real question.
Yeah.
My new place is a lot better.
I've moved closer to the office, but we haven't actually gone back to work yet.
So I'm still working from home.
My, my best, my best case scenario, what I hope to see is like a, I'll look at like the
video retention rate for this video and there will be a huge drop off after laser bot leaves
and what that'll tell them.
And that'll be good because what that'll tell me is that new people heard that there was
a laser about any of you and came to see it and didn't care about the rest of the episode.
If you're one of my stupid little fucking fans, you better not have clicked off after the laser
bot segment or you're not going to hear me yelling at you right now.
If you're a cyber shell fan and you're not still listening and you're not still listening
to me, then I want you to hear me say that I think you're stupid.
You really showed them.
Yeah.
Good.
We did it.
Fuck.
Well, laser bot is gone.
It's one of the worst things like that.
I could imagine if you tried, you'd be like, you know, oh, I've got to wait for an email
from fucking real estate, whatever.
And you're like, I'll work on the game.
You get like an hour into like setting up preparation.
Like, okay, I just got to get into the zone and then you get an email back.
You get some notification.
Oh, shit.
I got to stop.
I got to stop everything and it just ruins your whole mood.
Even if it wasn't the email from the company or from the housing, like any email, you're
going to be like, if you're expecting it, you're not going to be fully focused.
You know what I mean?
At least that's how I am.
It's really hard to focus on something when you're waiting for like this real life shit
that's just brewing in the back of your head.
It's like that John Cleese lecture.
You know the one I'm talking about, Gib, right?
The one about creativity.
Yeah.
Um, cyber shell CC.
Do you know he ever seen, there's a lecture by John Cleese, the money python guy, and
he talks about like the science of creativity.
And he talks about like, yeah, it sounds vaguely familiar.
I can't remember if I've seen it though.
I think I saw maybe it's a, it's a good lecture.
He talks about and close.
I mean, yes, the open and close mode.
And he says that like to get into like to do creative work, you have to like be in a
mind, you have to let yourself enter a mindset that lets yourself just kind of like play
and not be, you know, not be worried about, you know, logic, not be worried about like
judging any like mistakes you make, right?
So it takes time.
So you need to set yourself out like a block of time to be creative.
To allow yourself to like sink into that mode because it does, you can't just snap
your fingers and be creative or playful.
Yeah.
I was gonna say that earlier when it's like, if you have like an hour to work on something,
you can't just like immediately get into the zone, you know what I mean?
Especially if you're like acutely aware that you only have a little bit of time to work on something.
It's gonna be a lot harder to get into that full, if it's not just like, there's like modes
where you can just be like zoning out and like doing like, I don't know, sprite work or something
like something where you already know what you're going to be doing is just like mechanical
execution, but then there's also, you have to be in the mode to like come up with creative
ideas in the first place, which can be really tough.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's funny.
It's funny because like I was like drawing sprites, doing the pixels on the sprites to
me is much more mechanical than like writing the code.
Because when I'm writing, like I was putting in like particle effects and stuff and I kind
of have to think sort of creatively and be like, what would be kind of like a good sort
of like equation to put in for like a parabolic arc for this like particle to fly at?
And I'm like, hmm, and I'll try this.
Oh, it doesn't work.
I'll try this.
No, that doesn't work.
Oh, that kind of works.
Yeah, that looks good.
Okay.
And then I'll have it, if I, if I have it destroy itself and then create this sprite and have
that sprite fade, it'll create a nice little like splatter effect, right?
And I'm like kind of playing with it like that.
Whereas a sprite, I'm just like, okay, I got my template.
I'll put the template in, change the colors, change some details here.
Okay, done.
Next one.
Assembly line.
Yeah.
Drawing is for hacks.
Art is criminal.
The advantage of pre-production phases.
Cause like you spend that big block of time not drawing anything, not making anything,
but like planning everything, sketching as well.
But like the creative process of deciding what goes where and why and how and, you know,
writing.
That's so much harder.
Yeah.
You do all of that in one go.
And then once the pre-production is done, you have instructions for your like, like
mindless, like automaton brain to just read the instructions, just do the thing.
You know, draw over the sketches.
Yeah.
Like edit the, the draft of the, the screenplay or whatever it is.
You got to have us, you got to have a pre-production in anything.
Yeah.
There is something nice about like zoning out and just like doing like, you know, you
don't, you don't have to like be problem solving.
Like when you're like programming the game or whatever, you can just like do, you know,
you just want to draw a thing.
You know what you want it to be.
And you just do it.
You know what I mean?
Like when I'm editing a video, it's like most of the time I sort of already know what
I want it to be.
Like I just have to actually manually do the whole thing.
Yeah.
It's like, it's sometimes it depends if I can be like zoned out.
Like if I'm making good progress at a good rate, it can feel like kind of therapeutic
and nice, but sometimes it can feel a little tedious depending on how long the project
goes for.
When, when you've already made all the decisions.
Right.
There's something comforting about executing on.
Yeah.
Like once I've written the script and voice the script and then I just have to slowly
piece together the fucking video, which can be a pain.
But like, you know, once you've drawn the outline, like you basically know what you have
to do.
You just have to do it, which is a different kind of mode.
When the, when it's time to be like, how am I going to do this?
Make decisions.
Then I got to like YouTube, close YouTube, no music on, no distractions.
I have to sit and I have to focus when that's done.
It's time to just actually like, you know, like this though the sketches are done.
Now I just have to ink or whatever, or, or I have to do the final version.
Then I can be like, oh, guilty pleasure.
That's when you throw in some bullshit.
Best of the worst playlist on the second monitor and you just.
Yes.
Literally do that all the time.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
It's really hard to like get into that mindset when you're like really like, I have to shut
out all distractions.
I have to actually do the creative part of my job now being creative so hard.
I have to do my job.
Decisions.
Thinking.
Fuck.
I mean, it's weird.
It is weird.
Like it never know when it's going to come, right?
The inspiration.
I mean, like you never like, you can just be like sitting there like trying so hard to
think of a good idea and you'll never do it.
And then you just be like watching a video or playing a game and then a good idea comes
and you're like, I have to like stop what I'm doing and like write this down.
Well, that's what that's what John Cleese says.
He's like, you know, you don't, you can't like make yourself think of like a great creative
idea.
You have to end, you have to sort of let yourself enter this mode of thinking in which you are
open to sort of playing with ideas until you happen upon a good one.
And you have to be in this mindset where you're not judging yourself for like, oh no, that
was wrong.
That you had an idea and you had a thought, but it was a stupid thought.
And it was dumb.
I mean, if you have good ideas, like if you have good ideas, like that statistically
you have like way more like bad ideas and you have to filter those out.
I mean, you shouldn't beat yourself up just for having a bad idea.
You know what I mean?
It's, it's, it's right.
It's like the creative mode is you're just, you're playing, you're playing with, with
ideas.
You're not, you're not thinking like this is what I'm going to do.
You're thinking, what if I did this?
Oh, what if it was like this?
Oh, who knows?
It could be anything.
How, how droll.
A trap I sometimes fall into is, is trying to set aside time for like, for that creative
mode stuff.
I'm like, okay, I got to figure out something to write today.
But then I think of it in terms of like, like a checklist, like zero out of one, like creative
ideas, and obviously, or like good creative ideas.
And like, you can't guarantee that.
And if you're thinking by the end of the day, I need to have come up with a good idea,
you're not going to be in the right mode.
You're going to be thinking too much about like making it good, making it proper.
You can't beat yourself up too much about like not having a 10 out of 10 idea every day
or whatever.
You know what I mean?
Like it's so hard to come up with good shit like that on the fly.
I mean, it's more like you just make a good thing as good as you can make it.
And you hope like some divine inspiration will hit you.
And you have like some really good ideas you can work in there.
That's why I like having this exact problem.
Just feels like it feels like it's really open mode the entire time.
Yes.
He's so organic.
Like it really does feel like he didn't do any real pre-planning.
Like he just started drawing page one.
He just, okay, then now I'm done with page one.
What happens next?
Well, let's figure it out on page two.
And this was like, you know what I mean?
It's like just sort of, and then from that organic sort of structure, a more like intricate
plot arose.
Like, you know, even in like a great manga, like sometimes it'll come up with plot threads
and then the author will be like, oh, that didn't make any sense.
I didn't go anywhere.
And they'll just drop it.
You know what I mean?
You can't like beat yourself up every time that happens.
I've been having this problem with, I've been having this problem with the road to
Radcom, the last chapter of road to Radcom, which I've been meaning to write for weeks
now.
And I, you know, I've had all this fucking shit on my plate, which has been, but it's
not helped by the fact that when I think about it, I think about, okay, I don't know
exactly how I'm going to write it.
I know it has to be like goofy.
I know it has to be silly and I got to make it weird and wacky and stuff.
But I'm like, but I don't have any weird and wacky ideas.
I don't know what I'm going to write.
I don't know what it's going to be.
I don't know how I'm going to do it.
When, right?
When, when, when, you know, obviously what I actually have to do is not think about the
fact that I don't know what I'm going to write.
I have to just sit down and, and focus and think about it and just let myself be like,
what if, what if I, what if I wrote this?
I mean, what if that happened?
Oh, that would be funny.
Maybe I can then this.
No.
But what about this?
Sometimes.
Oh yeah.
Go on.
The sad thing is I feel like I used to be a lot more creative when I was younger than
I am now.
Like when I was when you're a kid, you don't have the inhibitions.
Like when you come up with like that, like you just have way more ideas and you're not
like filtering them out as thoroughly.
You know what I mean?
You don't have like it.
That's like, you get really in like a bad mindset where you're just like telling yourself
constantly, like, I need to come up with this specific kind of thing.
And like the more you like obsess over not being able to do it, like the less in a mind
space you are going to be in to do it properly.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, exactly.
Kids are always in the open.
Which is right.
Kids are always in that open mode.
Kids are just playing constantly.
They don't like understand that the world is a horrific nightmare yet.
They're like, oh, this is fun.
Yeah.
That's one thing I kind of liked about tails gets showed like you were saying earlier.
Like he just made the comics and, you know, he didn't care about like what, like how
people like, you know, whatever.
That's which is sort of how I made comics when I was a kid too.
I wish I still had some of them, but I don't sadly.
I like it.
Just another thing I like about tails gets trolls.
It doesn't, it doesn't feel like he's making it for some audience.
It really feels like he's making the comic just so he can have it and read it.
You know what I mean?
It doesn't, it doesn't feel at all.
Like it's pandering to anyone except his own sensibilities.
It doesn't feel like it's pandering.
But I mean, it does sort of take a notable turn.
Some of it is a response.
Some of it is a direct response.
Like you're right.
Like sometimes stuff is a response in just like, like noticing the tone of people.
And then there are parts of tail control, which are literally a direct response to the audience.
You're right.
Like completely.
But even that is just, he's doing that because it's something he wants to say.
Exactly.
He wants to say like, ha, ha, fuck you trolls.
I'll clown.
I'll clown on you.
If Tails is gay, I'll show you what Tails looks like when he's really gay.
It was funny when he, yeah, he like, I always like that.
Honestly, I love when an artist has like a sort of hostile relationship to the audience.
You know what I mean?
In, in Tails gets trolled case.
Yeah.
He, he, it made magic happen.
I think the tails gets a thing actually came from people complaining that he used homophobic
slurs.
So he kind of made, so he kind of made that to like troll them.
He was a, one of the first people I remember making some really long like posts on DeviantArt
about how like, he's like, he's like, I call things gay, but I'm not homophobic.
I have nothing against people.
It's like, that's just what you call things that are gay.
You know what I mean?
Like this was back in like 2011.
This is when people talked.
I was just like, I remember reading his post.
He's right.
I know.
I was like, it's like, you know, I can tell this guy, he's not like, he's not using slurs
as like, as like out of a hateful place.
He's just like, that's just like how he was raised.
Honestly.
That's how he talks.
It's like people like look at like, oh, they say like retard and stuff.
And it's like, you know, who's the people saying like slurs entails a choice from the
trolls?
It's from like the people that are not like endorsed by the author.
You know what I mean?
It's not like, you know, it's not like this is, they're saying this is good behavior.
Yeah.
And when it's like a character like Knuckles, it's, it's, it's shown that he's kind
of not a perfect angel boy.
Yeah.
Knuckles is dumb as hell.
Like, you know what, you're not supposed to read the comic and be like, yeah, Knuckles
clearly knows what's going on.
It's not like Knuckles from actual Sonic.
Right.
That's one of the weirdest things.
He's like an anti-hero.
He's literally, he's like a, he's a big dumb ass.
He's constantly a dumb ass.
Someone said this earlier, this call.
I can't remember, but like, yeah, like there are like copyrighted characters in Tails
He has told, but they're not like the copyrighted characters are basically original characters
like wearing the skin of copyrighted characters.
Did you, yeah.
Did you read the interview with, with?
Yeah.
That was an interesting interview.
I was paraphrasing him.
He said, it's not exactly those words, but he basically says that.
Well, I mean, it's clearly like, even when they start off a little, I mean, clearly all
the characters are inspired and derive like, you know, some from their actual copyrighted
counterparts, but there's so many like unique things to each character that especially
as it goes on, like, you know, Silver from Tails gets trolled as completely different
character from Silver from Sonic the Hedgehog.
There are some things like, you know, Elmer Fudd still wants to get that Wabbit.
Right, right.
Bugs Bunny still kisses dudes.
Exactly.
Plenty of elements from the original work, but not like the characterization is definitely
a bit different.
I don't know.
It's interesting.
It's interesting, but it's still using copyrighted characters.
So it's this weird gray area.
Honestly, I would love, I would love a 50 shades of gray grade version of two.
I would think it was the funniest thing in the world.
It would be really funny.
Even the censored version, which I didn't think was like a good idea, but it was still funny
to read.
You know, I kind of, I haven't seen that.
I kind of wonder how a version of Tails gets trolled would be like, would it be like, would
they still be like animals or would they just be like people?
Like, I always wondered about that.
It's really hard to like truly match because there's so many specific elements that like
you would just like, there's so many individual aspects you'd have to workshop.
You know, fucking, how could we possibly translate this into like a generic version?
You know what I mean?
I'm, I'm, I'm picturing them as just people, but like it would be, I feel like with so
many characters, it would become very hard to tell them apart.
That one fight with like Mario in laser bot style, specifically that the Mario Luigi
fight where they're cycling through the power ups from Mario would be like really confusing.
Like, why is he in like the Fox outfit that can turn into a statue?
And then, you know, it's like, what's going on over here with the frog suit?
It'd be a little hard to genericize that.
I mean, you could do it.
I'm not saying it's impossible, but it would be, there's a lot of little elements that
are like, it would be very tricky to do properly to the point where it'd be like, that's just,
I don't know, it would be funny.
You're right.
That would just add to the funniness.
You're completely right from that aspect.
I know it would, it would make parts of the comic like totally incomprehensible, but
like, I like that.
I don't know.
That's literally just funny to me.
And I mean, there are parts, when there are parts of a thing that don't make sense, and
you're like, why is it like this?
And there's like a deep lore answer.
There's like a production level answer that you would never know as a reader.
A little bit of that to me is like engaging.
And I like it.
Oh, wow.
I know a secret about this media that like, not the casual reader might not know.
It's legitimately compelling.
I would love to see that version of the comic, but I just can't justify like, why would they,
there would be no reason to make it unless there was a reason.
I mean, you know, they want to get picked up by someone.
I mean, why would Laserbot?
Yeah, like, no.
Laserbot, Laserbot should not make that.
No.
Maybe if it made a ton of money and he wanted to pay someone else to make that version,
then I'd be like, help, please, please.
I want to see that.
It's definitely one of my top comics that I would pick to get like redone one punchman style.
You know what I mean?
Even though like, I will always say I love the original.
The original art is classic.
It's perfect for what it is.
Also, I like the original.
Yeah, I like the original.
And yet, inevitably, the remake had to be the one that got popular because I know that
that crisp art is just going to be so much of a draw for a lot of people.
I say this in my video, too.
There's a huge amount of people who will take one look at this comic and will not read it.
It does not matter what you say to them.
Like, no, no, it really gets good.
No, no, like, they just can't.
The art is just too much of a hurdle for them.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Like, there's people who won't even watch black and white movies.
You know what I mean?
Let alone read a web comic that looks like it was made in MS Paint.
Black and white movies are better than regular movies.
Yeah.
They're not wasting all your visual information on useless color.
All those cones.
Fuck the cones.
All I need is the rods.
Thank you very much.
My favorite, like, lore about black and white movies is that, like, if you were, like, there
on location, like, when they were filming, like, a western, like, all the cowboys are
dressed in, like, hot pink and, like, turquoise because those are just, like, the colors that
show up best in black and white.
You know what I mean?
Like, they weren't dressed in regular colors because they would just be too muted and
bled together.
I've never heard that.
It's true.
It's really interesting.
Like, behind-the-scenes photos of old westerns and stuff.
I only know that in Psycho.
They used, like, chocolate syrup and some of the blood.
Right.
Yeah.
They'll all sort of little tricks like that.
Right.
Yeah.
Because in black and white, it doesn't matter.
Makes perfect sense.
But those were the days.
Those were the days when we weren't bound by the shackles of having to use things in
the right color.
I actually knew kids at my school who wouldn't, like, want to play, like, old games.
They're, like, all those graphics.
Right.
That's, like, how it's going to happen with new kids.
Like, they're going to see the pixel art and be like, uh, this is old.
It's shitty.
It's, like, that always gets me.
Like, I mean, I know most kids aren't like that or whatever.
I'm sure, like, pixel art is still popular in a lot of ways.
But, like, there are people who just see old games.
Especially, like, the PS1, like, blocky graphics are like, uh, it looks bad.
It looks shitty.
I mean, I love that look.
Maybe it's because I grew up with that, you know, generation of gaming.
So I'm nostalgic.
But there's something to it, you know?
It's definitely, like, an art direction thing.
Like, every technology, like, limitation creates, you know, breeze innovation.
And then that just becomes a different way.
Like, a different way you can paint with, like, code.
Right.
In a 3D or whatever.
You know, it's, like, just a different way you can do things.
And I always, I get a little mad.
I get a little seedy about, like, how modern games kind of, like,
Pixarify the rendering.
Like, three-dimensional games all have the same sort of lighting.
No matter what art style they have.
And it didn't used to be like that.
You didn't always have to have, like, dynamic shadows on a cartoon.
They still do that in every game.
Dynamic shadows and, like, bloom and, like, lens flares and shit.
It's just, it doesn't work.
It doesn't always work.
The only thing I could do...
Yeah, sometimes they make stuff just too, like, shiny, too, like, plasky and too, like, I don't know, too...
They just wanted to look like, yeah, I guess Pixar.
Everyone wants their, like, game to look like Pixar and stuff, you know, I don't know.
When I saw that new pony, the new pony designs, I'm like, oh, it's just Pixar.
They just look like Pixar made them.
Goddamn.
At least, you know, you can turn your nose up at Flash Animation, like, the old Gen 4 Milo pony.
At least they looked, like, unique.
The new 3D ones just look like Pixar.
It makes me mad. I hate it.
Yeah, that's another thing.
Like, Pixar and Disney movies, I can't even tell the difference between them anymore, because they just look the same.
And they all, I mean, have you seen the redesign of the Veggie Tales?
No.
They gave them the Pixar eyes.
The Veggie Tales have Pixar eyes now.
That's brutal.
I know.
Even Veggie Tales.
It's not like some Christian shit, I don't know.
I don't know what Veggie Tales is.
Oh, no.
It's true.
Yes, it is.
What?
Wait, let me find the...
Let me find the new Veggie Tales designs.
It's called Veggie Tales in the House.
No, it's not. You're lying.
Jesus.
Oh, and Netflix originally.
Oh, God, you're right.
No!
I don't like it.
I had no idea.
That's so...
Oh, that looks so bad.
The tomato.
It looks like inside out.
They just look like inside out.
It's so hard to articulate why this is so off-putting, but it looks wrong.
That's not how they're supposed to look.
The pickle looks a little better than the tomato, but the tomato just looks like the fuck.
Excuse me, he's a cucumber?
Whatever, I don't fucking care.
That's Larry the Cucumber.
Thank you very much.
I think it's literally just the eyes.
It's a pickle Rick.
People are so different.
It's people Rick.
The mouths are a little different.
Don't dare compare Larry.
Wait, I saw a fucking image.
Hold on, I got to Google.
Chad Larry Cucumber Virgin Pickle Rick.
Some guy at the NSA is looking at your search.
He's like, what the fuck is wrong with this guy?
Found it.
I'm posting.
You can't stop me.
I'm posting it.
Wait.
I haven't stopped you.
I haven't stopped you, but your shitty internet didn't stop you from posting it.
Yeah, it can.
I definitely agree with you that Larry the Cucumber is better than Pickle Rick.
Well, I'm glad we can agree on something.
There we go.
Look at it.
The list is extensive.
Hates it.
Virgin Pickle Rick.
Lips?
Oh, his friends as well.
Virgin Pickle Rick hates the God he doesn't even believe in.
Chad Larry the Cucumber.
God made you special and he loves you very much.
Who do you?
Loves God.
Loves Jesus.
Loves his friends.
Loves his lip.
I don't know what that means.
Yeah, no, the eyes.
The eyes in the new one.
I get it in that sense.
Why wouldn't you want to rip off Pixar, like the most profitable fucking animation studio?
Like it makes sense to rip them off.
It's just like when everyone does it, it sucks.
It's horrible.
Maybe it's not.
Okay.
That green lady in the back is the one that really looks like a picture.
Yeah, she does not look like she belongs with the VeggieTales cast at all.
What even is that?
She looks like a fucking vegetable.
What vegetable is that?
Is that a spoon?
Yeah.
Honestly, I don't know.
I don't think there's any plastic like vegetable beauty standards going on here.
It doesn't make any sense how thin she is.
It really doesn't.
It's just, I know they had to give them the irises.
They gave them the more detailed eyes, I guess, because it's cute.
It's not.
But is it cute?
I don't think it's that cute.
I don't know if cute is really what you want to go for with a vegetable.
I kind of think like silly and simple is better.
Maybe I'm biased.
I don't know who the character is with the pigtails, but that one looks like the least ruined,
because that's sort of what the character is.
The least.
Well, that one.
It's supposed to be like a cute girl or something with a bow.
Okay.
I guess in the old one, there was a, yeah, there was, I think she's a squash.
I don't even remember her from the old ones.
I remember the little asparagus kid with the hat was like the little sidekick or whatever.
I guess maybe given squash girl his role.
Is this image implying like all of the other ones that we don't see have been cooked.
They've been used in cooking.
They've been gone.
They don't exist in this reboot.
What is that blue lady?
Is she a grape?
Is she a plant?
Maybe a turnip.
A plant.
She's too small for an eggplant.
I don't know.
He's making me fucking.
It doesn't make any sense that the squash is smaller than the cucumber.
It's all a bunch of nonsense.
They ruined it.
My childhood.
Ah, they're raping my childhood.
Ah.
I didn't watch what you tell us as a child.
Or my childhood would be ruined.
I don't even like.
I never watched much of it, but I was always like super like aware of it.
You know what I mean?
I was like, yeah, this thing exists.
And I like, I don't even like, I don't have any attachment to it, but they still ruined
it so much that I like reviled by it.
I'm like, what did they do to you?
I genuinely do have a, have a little bit of an attachment to it because I went to church.
As a kid and they had VHS tapes that we could borrow and they had some veggie tales tapes
and I would borrow them and I would watch them and I liked them.
Like I didn't, I was pretty indifferent to the fact that they were like God stuff.
I was just like, yeah, whatever.
They're, they're funny.
And I think they're, I'm entertained, but they are God stuff.
They, they tell like, they tell like Bible stories.
They tell like stuff about like the, the Jews.
Like the Israelites like.
You could have ended that.
I didn't, that's good.
Well, yeah.
I mean, the Israel, depending on your.
The Israelites do in like the march around the walls.
They, they, they perform the miracle where they march around the walls of Jericho and
they make the city collapse or whatever.
Yeah.
Veggie tales really.
Hold me on the Israelites.
It's literally like Old Testament wrath of God stuff at once in a while.
I mean, you know, they do it in a silly way, but they do it.
And you know, God bless them.
Tomatoes or fruits.
I think I read, I think I've said this on the podcast before, but somewhere there's
like an interview.
I think it's like, I think it's like the Twitter account, the veggie tales,
Twitter account or something said that yeah, technically the vegetables and
veggie tales don't have souls.
So they won't not actually be saved by God.
They will not actually inherit the kingdom and be raised up into the bosom.
That's so weird, but it does like, it specifically says in the Bible, like humans
get into heaven, not fucking vegetables.
I mean, like specifically says not.
Specifically says that if any sentient fucking vegetables start growing around,
they ain't, they ain't getting in.
I don't know.
I love the idea that it can be completely sentient and like fully conscious,
but not have a soul.
Like what is it then?
It would be, it would be, it would be heresy for them to imply that Larry the
cucumber would be saved by Christ's sacrifice on the cross.
So they don't go to heaven.
Do they go to hell or do they just not exist?
Do they not have any sort of apparel?
Well, as we've learned, as we've learned the fate of the damned according to the
book of Revelation is not everlasting torment.
It is destruction in the fires of Gehenna.
Duh.
Isn't that like a, isn't that like a real place?
Is that the one like Bible lore verse you memorized to dunk the Christian,
dunk on the Christians and be like, yeah,
I know more about the Bible than you do.
I know, I know lots of Bible shit.
I know lots of.
Name one other thing about the Bible.
Name one other.
Oh, that's what that's why your name is wrong.
That's what there's a part.
There's a part in the Old Testament where a guy is like, hmm,
I want to breed some striped cows.
So he is like, I know what I'll do.
So he cuts stripes into a stick and he puts a stick in a,
in the pond and the cows drink from the pond with a stripe stick in it.
And then they give birth to striped calves.
Dude, whoever wrote the Bible is fucking retarded.
That doesn't make any sense.
What the fuck?
What are you talking about?
There's an, there's an,
there's another part in the Bible where it says that pie is three.
Oh, right.
I remember hearing that in a bunch of like, yeah,
like really sorry.
There was just like back in the day, pie was three.
It was close enough.
God damn it.
It was.
Yeah.
It was three universal drift.
Universal drift has changed like the fundamental like geometric
constants of our reality.
Yeah.
There's a part that describe,
it describes a circular, I think it's a well or something.
And it says it's this many cubits across and this many cubits around.
And if you divide the numbers, they're exactly divisible by three.
The pie is equal to three.
Lamal.
So as you can see, I'm a, I'm a fucking genius and I know all about God.
And it's true.
The vegetables are going.
Is.
rhubarb.
Petunia rhubarb.
Look at the fucking voice.
Voice by 2B.
Kira Buckland.
First.
This is a scene girl.
First of all.
Wow.
She's cute.
First of all, I like that rhubarb is being represented.
Rhubarb is an underappreciated vegetable, but she doesn't look like rhubarb because
rhubarb has like big leaves.
She doesn't.
Why does she like a bowl?
She's.
Dear.
Vegetables writers.
You have anthropomorphized these vegetables to a point where they're no longer recognizable.
And I would like a refund, please.
It's.
I mean, you say that, but I'm serious.
Unironically.
Why, why didn't they make the body like pink, like rhubarb and then have her hair be green,
like the leaves?
Like that.
There would be a way to do it.
Well, it wouldn't be.
They, when they designed Petunia rhubarb, they're like, we need to get at least like,
at least 300 entries of rule 34.
So she can't be too busted and having green hair and shit.
This is so annoying.
They have her wearing like a pink sweater, but like.
None of the other vegetables were clothes.
Her body should just be red.
Yeah.
And her hair should be green leaves.
They are too anthropomorphized.
What is this orange hair?
This is insane.
I'm losing my mind.
Some of the vegetables are fruit.
Petunia rhubarb is cracking my mind in half.
I don't understand what I'm looking at.
I'm staring into the abyss.
What were they, what were they thinking?
Dear VeggieTales creators, first of all, God isn't even real.
Second of all, what is going on with Petunia rhubarb's design?
In order of importance, these are my two complaints about the new VeggieTales.
The old VeggieTales, I was okay with the God stuff.
God used to be real, but now he's not.
The new one is just, is just a lot.
All that God shit was great in the 90s.
So cool.
Yeah.
I had no idea she did VeggieTales voice.
That's like quite, she's got quite the resume.
Wait, does she do, was she to be?
She does anime and video games and like some anime films.
She got her start on like new grounds and shit, I think.
Oh yeah.
She, she, oh yeah.
She was near automatic.
She was like in some really like shitty flash movies in like 2004 or some shit.
I thought I recognized the name.
Oh, okay.
She's, she's not, she's not as hot in other pictures as her headshots, but I mean, what
do you expect?
That's headshots for you.
Well, yeah, rhubarb though.
Yeah, let's focus on the rhubarb.
Let's focus on what's important.
I'm sorry.
I don't have enough information on VeggieTales board to contribute much to this conversation.
Have you ever, have you ever had rhubarb?
No.
Oh, it's good.
Oh, it's sweet.
It is good.
Did I make you try it or did you already know?
Do you have you already had it?
They don't grow, they don't grow that in England.
It's a, I don't know.
I've had it before.
I had it in a pie.
I must have made you-
Rhubarb crumble, rhubarb crumble.
No, I've had it way before you ever uttered the-
No, I invented, I invented rhubarb crumble.
I invented rhubarb pie.
No.
It's my thing.
Stop copying Ben's love of rhubarb.
Who's Ben loves rhubarb?
He talks about it all the fucking time.
Everyone, it's a defining characteristic.
It's the thing, it's the thing about me and you're stealing it?
I called it.
Pick another vegetable.
VeggieTales superfan Ben Saint, widely known for his love of Petunia rhubarb and has drawn
all sorts of-
No.
Part of her and made weird Twitter-Countess role-plays her.
She, she is a disgrace to rhubarb everywhere.
She's not, we don't, the rhubarb community, roundly rejects her.
She's like the Candace Owens of rhubarb.
Rhubarb is what I'm saying.
Yeah.
I'm not much into VeggieTales, but I'm a member of the rhubarb community, so I can't help
but stan Petunia.
Cringe, cringe.
This is a, she's split, she's split the rhubarb fanbase a Sunday.
I might have to watch some VeggieTales after this, because I'm mostly familiar with like,
just like you see random clips on Twitter of just like some crazy like religious moments
being like, whoa, this is so wacky.
But I'm sure there's like some like 10 hour YouTube essay like, this is the lore and why
VeggieTales is the greatest show of all time.
I haven't seen anything like that, but it wouldn't surprise me.
I don't know if you saw when, when the, when things were really heating up between Israel
and Palestine, I posted that video of the little asparagus, little asparagus asking Bob
the tomato, the Israelites, weren't they God's chosen people?
I bet they always follow God's directions and Bob the tomato.
Oh, you'd think so.
Wouldn't you?
I remember that clip.
That was good.
Cried, I cried.
I feel like VeggieTales is popular because like all Christian media that was trying to
be educational was just like horrible.
Like it was all terrible except for VeggieTales.
And it's like, it's like the king of that niche.
As a kid who was pretty indifferent to God stuff.
I just liked VeggieTales because it was funny.
Right.
I thought, and I liked it.
So it was great.
I can absolutely see it appealing to any kid.
It's just like a, seems like a regular ass cartoon at first.
It seems like VeggieTales seems like a show like that should teach you about vegetables
and like healthy eating habits, you know, not like the Bible.
I think, I think I remember being kind of like thinking it was cool that they actually
just tell these like Old Testament stories.
It's kind of, it's like history.
It's kind of like a history thing.
Yeah.
A lot of those stories are pretty interesting, honestly.
Like where, like I had never heard about, oh, the Israelites fucking collapsed the wall.
They like, they performed a miracle and God collapsed the walls of Jericho when they blew
their trumpets.
It was like, that's weird.
Neat.
Cool.
Thanks for telling me Larry for the one.
There's, there's one where they, there's a, there's a, they do a version of the one
where the guy, I think it's, is it Daniel or that they throw into the den of lions and
God appears as an angel and like protects him from the lions.
I might be conflating some, some stuff there.
I think I've talked about this exact thing on the PCP book.
I think, in fact, I think I remember someone in the comments correcting me and saying,
no, Ben, that story was not about Daniel being thrown into the lion's den.
That was Steve or something.
It was another guy.
I really hope someone in the comments is like, oh God, they're talking about fucking
veggie tails again.
Skip this episode.
They will.
They will be.
I, I promise.
We are at two and a half hours.
Do we want to go to voicemails?
No, let's skip it all together.
This will be the episode where did you stop doing voicemails?
We should, we should just split this episode into like the laser bot segment and the post
laser bot segment or we've been going for a while without them now.
But no, not that long.
I don't know.
We should go.
We should do voicemails, right?
We have to.
Okay.
I have one, I have one particular question that only you two people can answer.
So is everything that happens in Lord of Ghosts canon to endless war or how does that work?
That is such a great question.
And the answer is yes.
Yeah.
The way in endless war, because it's like a, a, like a big community, like people come
up with law all the time for fun.
They come up with their own OCs in the, in the discord and they were doing all that stuff.
We came up with collectively as long as you make it and it's cool and people like it,
then it's canon.
It doesn't matter.
There's no like authority that says yes or no.
So people like everything is canon.
So, so it is canon.
Yes.
Excellent.
It's, that's, I think, I think, I think that makes me, um, I think I, I mean, I think
I would have liked Lord of Ghosts anyway, but, but the fact that it is, it is technically
like a, it starts in, in Lakakam.
The fact that it has the endless war tie-in just makes me like makes me very, um, I feel
very, I feel very connected to it.
I feel, I feel very, uh, invested in it.
Like you technically could read it immediately following like S nega slime descent.
Cause it's exactly that moment where it starts.
Right.
Yeah.
I remember reading it for the first time.
Like, yeah.
Okay.
So there's clearly like some shit just happened and it's like immediately following after
this.
Cause I remember reading it and me like, am I missing something?
And I was looking on the wiki and I was like, oh, okay.
So this like really happened on the server and all this crazy ghost shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, it did.
That I unveiled it.
S.
It was so fucking cool.
It was a, Lord of Ghosts takes place directly after S nega slime descent, which was a, an
animation that Gib did that coincided with and heralded the end of season one of endless
war.
There was like a big in-game event that included the, this, this animation that Gib did in which
the, the nega slime descended and, and de-slime the city basically.
Uh, yeah.
And Lord of Ghosts is the immediate.
Yeah.
Other stuff happened in the game after that, but Lord of Ghosts is like the immediate aftermath
and side story to that.
I guess.
Yeah.
There it is.
So we're reading it.
I mean, like this is like weirdly like specific like of lore that happened right before the
comic started.
Like what's going on with this?
And then I was like, oh, this like actually like happened.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah.
It's not required reading or like you don't need to be.
Right.
Oh yeah.
The intro of the comic like explains the whole premise.
It's just like, it was like, huh, that's kind of an interesting premise.
Yeah.
It is.
It was pretty wacky.
Um, people ask me.
The Lord of Ghosts had a whole.
If Lord of Ghosts is difficult to get into if you don't know endless war and trust me,
you don't need to.
No.
All the concepts, like the sewer stuff, I feel like it's explained in the comic.
You know what I mean?
Like it definitely helps to know about it.
Like you would immediately know what was going on.
But I mean, it's not like, it was actually pretty easy to understand without even fully.
I mean, I'm not in endless war.
I'm only like aware of it, but it seems interesting.
If you like the character of Lord of Ghosts, it might, I mean, it would probably be interesting
to, for you to know that he did kind of have a whole sort of life and story as an endless
war account.
Right.
Yeah.
That's what I mean.
I was like, he was, he was all the mayor stuff.
I was like, what the fuck is going on with this?
Yeah.
Cause I was like, that was like so much backstory that I was like, we'll be like, why would you
not just put that in the comic if this was happening?
Like, you know what I mean?
But I was like, oh, cause you know, it wouldn't make sense.
I mean, it would not make sense to put it in the comic, but like, you know, it was continuing
from these events.
It wasn't necessary.
He ran, he ran on a, he ran on a platform of a beat.
He was pro porn.
And he also, he had, he had, he had the pity vote.
He had the, he had the pity.
I love winning an election.
The pity vote, which is hilarious.
These two factors made a huge landslide.
And it was, it was a legitimate win.
It wasn't like, like a, like a, like people actually voted for it.
Right.
Yeah.
It was just a plot point.
It was like a real election, which is really funny.
We had an actual poll in the server of people to vote for who was, who was going to be mayor.
Yeah.
And as soon as Lord of ghosts became mayor, there, a whole thing happened where like,
you know, the ghosts used to live in the sewers, but then because Lord of ghosts was mayor,
he declared ghosts legal.
So suddenly ghosts could roam the streets.
It was literally that scene from Ghost Busters two or Ghost Busters one, I think, where all
the ghosts like shoot up out of the ground and are like terrorizing the scene.
It was literally just the one getting in the taxi.
It was just that, but green.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
Dude, Slimer is such a endless war character.
He's like a slime green ghost.
I think that I think they ripped off.
I think they ripped off endless war when they made Ghost Busters.
We don't, we don't acknowledge Slimer.
We don't want to give him the attention.
He's too much.
He stole our shit.
He stole your shit.
He stole our IP.
He stole your vibe.
Your aesthetic.
He did.
He really did.
It's not fair.
I don't know.
It's what do we think?
Voice voicemails?
Oh yeah.
Sure.
If you want that episode to be less than eight hours long, probably need to get to voicemails
eventually.
Or you just skip voicemails.
Just drop it.
Just completely drop the segment and everyone who left their voicemail is going to be like,
what the fuck?
This is the first time they ever didn't do voicemails.
No.
I can't do it.
I have too much.
Damn my integrity.
I just have so damn much of it.
It's such a curse.
I do respect the consistency.
I mean, have you guys ever missed a week that wasn't like related to being at Radcon?
I don't think we even then, we managed to do live PCP episodes.
Oh right.
Yeah.
If you count the live stuff, then I mean, obviously didn't miss anything.
I just meant like as far as the actual just weekly schedule, it's been pretty adhered to
as far as I can tell.
Thanks.
Yeah, it has.
We didn't have the same voicemail format back then, but since then I have, at some point
I decided all voicemails are fair game and we have run every single one since then.
That pig guy shows up.
I fucking hate that pig guy.
I'm still like the more we talk about it more likely is to show up again.
Maybe there'll be pink copycats or like copy pigs.
The pig.
I don't want to talk about that.
I don't want it.
Okay, we can just get right into the voicemails if you want.
The first voicemail is called the pig.
I don't know.
I'm not talking with a pig.
We're not talking with a pig.
We're moving on.
No, you won't guarantee.
Maybe next week someone will call in some pig males.
The first voicemail is called big chicken's egg of a fan perspective on Ben's work ethic.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, Ben, I can't help but think that your popularity and subsequently your own money
would improve if you would choose to focus all of your effort on one of your series as opposed to the scattershot approach you take nowadays.
I know you said in a previous episode that the way you work creatively is that you get this idea and you cannot move forward until you get that idea out of your head.
As a fan of, for example, the Vapors, like I am, it's very hard to want to keep up with the Vapors when the chapters are so bespratic.
Especially since now you're working on the Simon Punishment game, which in and of itself is a very esoteric piece of media that requires vague knowledge of Chris Chan lore and RFCK lore.
Antibad lore.
Or for somebody to really be invested in a series when everything is so scattershot.
However, if you finish the Simon Punishment game, then you can go on to do the 102 lecture, which could be a boon for your popularity if it's anything like the first lecture.
So yeah, I don't know, just thoughts.
Hope the house hunt is going well.
If not, you can come and stay on my couch.
Kisses.
Love you.
Bye-bye.
I mean, yeah, but like, tell me something I don't know.
What was his advice?
Do one thing at a time?
I mean, isn't that already what you're doing?
I mean, he just meant only the Vapors.
Is that what he wanted?
Yeah.
He wants more Vapors.
I mean, he said he thinks Vapors hard to keep up with.
I mean, it is hard to keep up with Vapors since there is no Vapors coming out because I'm working on something else right now.
That means it's easy to keep up with because there's no new Vapors coming out.
You know, I remembered.
I was horrified to realize that it's been almost two years since the Vapors to Kickstarter and those Vaporettes.
I mean, I released the Vaporettes for the first Vapors book after like one year.
So I think I might want to just really, maybe when I fucking put the comic up, I will also put the Vaporettes up because I did mean to at some point publish those on the internet.
They weren't going to stay book exclusive forever.
So I don't know.
I guess I'll do that at some point.
Anyway, this guy, I mean, yeah, it is weird and scattershot and probably hurts my follow ability, but I just really want to make this fucking video game.
The reason Slime and Punishment is not even God can stop me.
I was going to say the reason Slime and Punishment is like esoteric and hard to get into.
It's like, it's also like part of the reason why it's like good and special in the first place.
You know what I mean?
Like it's such a unique piece of media.
I mean, it's not even that hard to get into and understand as long as you have like a little bit of understanding of Endless War because I mean, and I guess it helps to know a little bit of song issue.
But other than that, it's not like incomprehensible.
In my opinion, even if you don't know what Endless War is, if you started reading Slime and Punishment, you could get the gist and be like, oh, OK, they're in the city and Slime is the currency.
And that's it.
That's all you need to know.
And there's a tower and I guess it's like in charge of everything, but like whatever.
It's not important.
Don't worry about it.
The thing that I like about that and that I also kind of like about Lord of Ghost a little bit is that like, like just the fact that Endless War as its own separate entity, just this existing thing and like events that happen in that like will affect the comic.
But like, you know, you didn't choose to have, you know, acid rain.
That was something that happened and then you worked around it.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Like it could.
It could only it could only be what it is.
It could not have been less esoteric than it is my kind of my hope and this might be overly ambitious.
This might be foolhardy, but I'll admit to it anyway.
A bit of my hope with the game is that the game will be something that is accessible enough, enjoyable enough in a in a sort of broadly appealing way that it will maybe a wider audience.
Might see it and like it, then would have read the comic otherwise.
And it might bring more attention to the whole to the comic and by proxy also to my other stuff, Endless War and etc, etc.
Isn't the only problem with that that you're hoping people will discover and get invested in Slime and Punishment via the finale game, which will have the ending spoiled and also be almost impossible to understand without having read the comic.
Lore wise, they won't understand it, but I mean the game seeks to provide a mechanical challenge that can be enjoyed even if you don't fully know the lore.
Yeah, that's fair.
What's going on.
Yeah.
If it just has good art and stuff.
If the if the game is fun and it looks good and people play it and like that was a fun game, but I sure didn't understand any of that.
I guess you're right.
That's a good incentive.
You know what I mean?
The game enjoyed and be like, I wish I knew what that meant.
Like, oh, here's all comic you can read to know about what that meant.
Alternatively, that's exactly what I'm hoping for.
You could make a build of the game that is specifically for like newcomers and put that on like itch.io or something.
We have some sort of like intro cinematic.
You're a pony or something.
You got to kill these guys with a sword.
Isn't that interesting?
It sure is.
And people just enjoy playing it.
I think I want to rub people's faces in it.
I think I want people who haven't read the comic to have no choice but to grapple with.
What is he talking about?
If there are enough just like interesting things happening in a game.
It's such an unusual thing.
It's such an unusual thing to happen in a game that is like so hard to understand.
Like so much preliminary media needs to be consumed.
Like no game does that.
Right.
It would be really funny to see people's reactions.
You can play the game.
You can play the game without reading the comic, but you won't understand the story of the game.
You won't understand the motivation behind it or why it's happening unless you've read the comic is my intention with it.
And you know what?
That's all part of my vision.
It's all part of my vision and it's all completely non-negotiable.
But it is what it is.
Next voicemail is called A Poem for Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
This next poem goes out to Ben St. of Patreon fame.
As I wake in the morning I go for my phone.
I just can't let go.
Can't leave them alone.
They've mentioned my name.
Time to make them pay.
I'll work on my game, but not today.
I just can't stop yigging.
Could there be something wrong with me?
Tweet after tweet.
Will I ever be free?
I just can't stop yigging.
Last word must always be mine to say.
I'll work on my comics.
Someday.
Cruel.
Overly cruel.
Savage.
My feedback is you kind of sound like a robot.
You should get better at enunciating.
Oh my god.
I've made like five or six tweets about yig in as many months.
It's slowed down considerably.
So I don't know why they're still getting mad at me about it.
This is like a month late.
Even I, eventually I did realize if I keep banging this drum,
I'm going to start looking like the asshole.
So I should stop.
And I did.
So yeah, very funny.
Very funny.
I can't stop yigging.
It's true.
I'm guilty.
She's a yigger, Jerry.
She's a yigger.
Next voicemail is called, uh, what is it?
Uh, fuck, I lost track.
How to explain trans to cis people by a cis person.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
So here's how to explain being trans to cis people.
I mean, I guess Gib can back up whether this is actually an accurate description or not,
but I don't know, seems to be to me based on listening to trans people.
As a cis person.
So as a cis guy, whether as an adult or at least as a teenager,
there's almost certainly going to be a point in your life where you wish you were more
masculine than you are currently and you want other people to see you as masculine.
So you do stuff to your body to make yourself more masculine and like the way that you talk
and the way that your body language is and all this other shit.
So then just imagine instead you wanted the reverse of that.
If you wanted to be less masculine and more feminine and be perceived as such and do all
the stuff to your body and like the way that you behave in order to produce the opposite effect.
You see, it's really not hard to understand.
It's not some difficult thing that we have to solve.
It's easy.
You know what?
That seemed pretty reasonable.
It's a pretty simplistic explanation, but it works.
It is kind of like that because I was obviously raised male.
I had these ideas that I should be more masculine, but I never wanted to.
All of these things that were put forth as like the path towards being an adult male
was like, okay, I guess I do all this.
Never having considered that I could maybe not do that and do the opposite instead.
And once I realized that and I was like, oh wait, this is way better.
I actually like doing this.
That's it.
Sounds based.
I think I get when you put it like that.
I think I get entirely what he's trying to say.
I also never had the desire to become more masculine at any point in my life, to be honest.
Yeah, I mean, that's why I said it was simplistic.
Yeah, yeah.
I think it generally is right.
It's just like, it's not going to apply to everyone, but like, yeah, like, you know,
I feel most people will grapple with that at some point.
Like, you know, like, oh, this is what society expects of me.
I need to either, you know, accept that or disagree with it.
There are certain masculine traits that I do admire and seek to enhance in myself,
most notably being ripped.
Actually, pretty much that's the only one.
Yeah, it's just that one, actually.
It's like, that is the thing.
It's just like, it's so hard for me not to just be like, yeah,
but there's no reason women can't be ripped.
I mean, that's like a completely fabricated society,
societal expectation.
I mean, that's what it all is.
It all comes down to that too.
And so it's like, I don't know.
You come down to like, society dictates all of these things.
And it's, it's, you're only trans as much as your society tells you
that you are the other thing you want to switch.
Right.
You know what?
If we lived in a radical gender anarchy where like,
no one expected anything of anyone,
people wouldn't like need to be trans because like gender,
it would be a different concept.
You know what I mean?
Because there would be no, because you wouldn't,
you wouldn't be assigned anything.
Right.
So you wouldn't end up being the opposite of that.
Yeah.
And just strive towards whatever you felt like.
Another thing I think is a good way to make people think about it a little
more is just to ask them why, as a cis person,
why are you like a man?
What makes you like that?
Like,
Going up to my neighbors, why are you a man?
Like, why are you male?
How does that work?
Why are you white, friend?
Because it's the question they ask, like,
so why are you trans?
I don't really get it.
Like, why are you not trans?
Just say the same thing.
That's like one of the weirdest things.
Oh, that's just, that's just like when Donnie Darko asks,
why are you in that bunny suit?
And Frank asks, why are you in that human suit?
That's exactly what being trans is like.
It's like that one scene from Donnie Darko.
I was going to say, like, I totally, like,
I pretty much agree that it's not,
it's like basically it all just comes down to like,
what society expects of you.
So I'm not entirely sure.
I basically agree with the general message of that voicemail,
but I don't know, like, to me, like, I never,
it's so obvious that trans people are real,
because like, I am a guy and I have no desire to be a girl,
so like, I can't empathize with that at all,
but it's like, no one would just like,
pretend like that, like, it doesn't make any sense to me.
Like, white people are so like, vigorously denying it,
and it's like, what, why?
It's because of the pity vote.
It's because of the pity vote,
and I've become Lord Mayor of Endless War.
Next voicemail?
Next voicemail is called Audacity Rant,
not directed at you.
This is from Oblivionfall.
Shout outs to Oblivionfall.
Is this about how Audacity is banned now?
Oh yeah.
It's probably going to be about how Audacity is banned.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
You all need to get the fuck off Twitter.
Audacity is not spyware.
Everyone's saying that it is, is lying to you for attention,
because they love the dopamine they get,
when they get 30,000 likes for spreading false misinformation.
I sure love that.
It's so fucking annoying.
If you must know what is happening with Audacity,
it is this.
They collect diagnostic data.
That is your country of origin, your CPU,
your OS version, error codes, and crash reports.
That's fucking it.
That is the only information they get.
They do receive your IP address,
which, oh god, someone at this IP address used Audacity
within the last 24 hours, because in case you didn't know,
that information is scrambled after 24 hours,
so your data is completely anonymous from that point.
That is the only data being collected.
They are not collecting your audio or sending it to the cloud.
I've seen people say that.
They're full of shit and they're lying.
Oh, but they said that law enforcement might ask for information.
Yeah.
And what information do they have?
Oh god, the reverb effect crashed for this IP address six hours ago.
Shut the fuck up.
Look, if you really don't like this stuff,
let me give you a little life hack.
Audacity does not need an internet connection to run.
You can just disable it in your firewall.
Not that it fucking matters, but if you care, you can try that.
But don't fucking uninstall and don't tell other people to uninstall.
You absolute fucking moron.
Please stop it.
Good, because I was going to be, I was going to say,
I'm too lazy to uninstall it.
I'll just let them steal my data.
I don't care.
I had a feeling that it was, it was sort of blown out of the bush.
Yeah.
I had a feeling too.
It's like, I was like, there's no way they're just like, it's not like,
it can't be as bad as everyone thinks it is.
You guys were all on board.
You guys were all into the meme.
You totally bought in, but now all I want to say,
listen back to the beginning episode.
I specifically said, I don't know what is going on with Audacity.
I just want to explicitly say,
I didn't pretend like I knew what was going on.
I just heard people say it was bad.
Let the record show.
You can listen back to whatever shows.
There was a clip of me saying that I thought it was real.
No clip.
Was that before or after we started talking laser,
but I'm trying to figure out if that's in the episode or if that's going
to be in like the pre bonus.
You'll have to, you'll have to subscribe to the, to the, to the
Patreon to get the bonus episode to see if I was lying just then.
I think, I think we were talking about it in the pre,
before laser bots audio was working.
Yeah.
So yeah, that would be,
Well, whatever.
Point is I was going to just use Audacity no matter what,
because I'm lazy.
I'm fucking lazy.
I've been using it since like 2007.
I'm not going to stop now.
I hope they're stealing my data so I can,
I can sue them and get mad about it and make Twitter posts.
My data is great.
I want, I want them to see how great my data is.
Cyber shell, you make,
how do you get so many likes on Twitter?
I don't know.
You're so popular on Twitter.
Only you fucking kill it.
You kill it on Twitter.
I'll tell you why it's because you use Twitter to like get into
arguments and dunk on people.
I only use Twitter to make funny jokes.
That is the only reason I use it.
I don't post anything that isn't like,
is this funny?
I think this is kind of funny.
This might get some likes.
Like I'm not, I mean,
I self promote my stupid videos,
but those tweets don't get a lot of like,
they're just normal.
I can't disagree.
It's, it's why my Twitter was good for a while there.
Cause I only posted funny comics and just like puns and stuff.
But I don't like anything else.
Except maybe trying this.
You need it.
You need to follow it in the first place.
Otherwise it won't work.
Well, it's the hard way.
When I got the zero like tweet.
Yeah.
Then you just delete it.
If you get zero likes on a tweet,
you delete that shit.
That's embarrassing.
Not that ever happens to me, of course.
Actually, it doesn't.
There's never happened to Ben St.
Ever.
And don't even think about going and searching through his
Twitter replies.
Cause he's already deleted the ones that had zero replies.
Don't count replies.
Don't count.
Okay.
Fair enough.
Next.
Next voicemail is called, uh,
what's it called?
It's called fast talking super listener.
Tarbuck transom.
Three, two, one, go.
When there's a misunderstanding or a miscommunication,
do you think the speaker or the listener has more responsibility?
Obviously it's both.
And also obviously it's not exactly equal.
At least I don't think so.
I think it's like three to two listener to speaker.
What about you guys?
Uh,
I hate to do this, but it depends entirely on the situation.
Like I can't just.
Yeah.
That's what I was going to say.
Credit to the speaker as per person.
Cause you can say something vague and ambiguous and then it's
on you or you can just not understand something incredibly
obvious.
It's completely on the listener.
Like there's no, I can't divide it up based on
some majority of the time.
Maybe I don't know.
Here's an example.
Like a first impression.
The pressure is on the speaker to make sure they don't
miscommunicate because that's an important thing to get
right.
And if somebody hears something wrong, you can just
clarify and that's fine.
I guess it's more on the situation.
Yeah.
I guess if I have to go to my head, it's more on the speaker to
say something that can be understood.
I mean, I don't know.
It's your job to say the thing.
I would say, I mean, in the same way that I think that like,
if an artist makes a piece of art and someone reads it and
they take the wrong message away or the message that the
artist didn't intend, it's not the list.
It's not that the listener failed or did something wrong.
Yeah.
The onus is on the artist to convey what they want to convey.
So yeah, I guess, I guess actually I would generally say the
listener is probably the one who should be catered to.
And it's, the speaker is the one acting.
Yeah.
If you're saying something, you're the one trying to
communicate something.
You're the one like, who has a goal.
Like I want to say something that is understood.
I mean, the listener, their only job is to listen to it.
You know what I mean?
Although there are plenty of cases where a listener can just
not, can just decide that they want to misunderstand you or
pretend you said something different.
I'm assuming this is like a one-on-one conversation.
It's easier to like, if you say something to your audience
and like most of your audience doesn't understand what you
meant, then like, yeah, that's clearly on you.
You know what I mean?
Like it helps if it's that kind of situation.
Yes.
Okay.
Uh, next one is called Tarby Transum.
Three, two, one, go.
Fast talk in Craftsman and Cloud Chaser Eternal,
Tarbuck Transum here.
I work exclusively with hand tools, with surprising speed
and surprisingly little expense.
I think you and the other caller would be surprised at
exactly how easy it is to make complicated furniture
like chairs.
But what I mostly had in mind was bookcases.
Even you can make a seven-foot culvert case in two to three
hours.
It would last for decades starting from basic wood.
The most basic tools that I recommend is $35 for the entire kit
and that is an entire shop's work.
I think I understand the basic premise behind the bookcases.
What is important is the bookcases.
Hundreds of bookcases.
I want to be surrounded by shelves.
I want them to coat every wall.
My goal is to live my life in a honeycomb of shelves and drawers
and bookcases.
So there is more to ceiling storage fucking everywhere.
Do you have a weird dream like that that no one would take
seriously like having a private ball pit or something?
Like the honeycomb is mine.
You can't have it.
If I had more floor space, I would like more shelves
because I do have a bunch of junk kind of just sitting on stuff.
I'm going to take the hard opposite stance and say,
I'm anti-shelf.
I don't want any shelves in my life.
I want books piled high straight from the ground to the ceiling.
No shelves involved.
How did you get them?
I don't read books.
I just look at them and admire my collection.
I, well, I'm the same.
I would have like a big like old fancy like stuffy like like a library
for old British royal something or other.
You have to pay to get in.
Only white people allowed, you know, all that stupid shit.
Hell yeah.
Classic British library.
The classic like evil like British library with the dark leather bound books
with no text on the side.
I like the aesthetic of that.
Made of human flesh.
Yeah.
The Necronomicon is the sort of thing you would see in Harry Potter.
But I would never read any of them.
I just like the fact that they could fill a wall with leather and paper.
You know?
I would love to have a room like yeah.
Just full like a library like Beauty and the Beast style library
where all the books are completely just every single book is just tales gets
trolled but like a slightly different size.
Well, well, I mean by the time that all four arcs are done,
it's going to be enough to fill up an entire an entire wall of bookshelves.
I still can't believe you said four arcs and we're only almost done with arc one.
I mean, he said we've gotten similar estimates in the past.
Like, oh, I would do 100 chapters.
But it's like to hear that it's just like, what the fuck?
How much shit can possibly you said?
Sisi, you said when you were on the other day, you said four arcs.
And honestly, I didn't believe you.
I thought like there's no way.
There's no way.
I always knew that was the case.
But I like just specifically to hear it from laser boss mouth.
Like they're literally playing to that much out in advance.
Like what the fuck?
Like it's cool.
It's good.
I'm glad.
I would rather people to plan out their comics like that.
But fuck.
Was that was that was that Sisi?
Yeah, to be fair.
He said the end of the first arc is the attack on troll forces.
But that only really started like a chapter, like chapter 11 or 12 or 13.
Right.
Yeah.
The assault has been going on for ages.
You're right.
But I mean, there is a bunch of stuff before that.
So maybe this is like the second.
I think I think Ben might be right in that, like maybe there really are four arcs,
but arcs two, three and four are just going to be shorter.
They're just going to buy virtue of the comic existing in its current format.
It will be shorter.
Yeah, the war.
I mean, he said the war.
It sort of feels like we're in the war now.
Right.
I guess it's just technically one battle.
This whole thing has been one battle basically, which is ridiculous.
Like it's been going on for that long, longer than the fucking.
That's true.
Oh dark and berserk.
It's just been going and going.
He said he said there are other troll civilizations.
So I mean, I guess maybe, you know, yeah, this is just one battle with one troll city.
And I made it becomes a worldwide conflict.
I guess.
Yeah.
Makes sense.
There's a guy named Mr. Claire, who's the mayor of fuck poor people, which is what
the city is called the troll city of fuck poor people.
I think you mentioned that before.
That's like a different city.
Yeah.
It will be interesting.
I was trying.
I said this a little bit.
I was like, I want to hear more, see more world building from laser bought.
You know what I mean?
Because like, yeah, we haven't gotten too much of that.
I would love to see another troll civilization.
I would love to hear him go like here.
There's another troll city out there.
It's called Nalaka Conom.
We've got to send it all in a collective universe.
Oh, we should have said endless war.
We should have said T-Bap.
We should have said that's what you put in the fucking comic.
Mr. Homestuck.
Fuck Homestuck.
Just another spoke on the wheel of slime and punishment, just like more lores and universes
to connect to.
My goal is for endless war to be the saint elsewhere of web comics.
You know what I'm talking about, right?
Yeah.
The smash bros of web comics, except not really.
Like the autistic boy with the thing.
Yeah.
Everything is technically because of all the crossovers.
All of these shows technically exist in the same universe.
And therefore all of them are the dream of an autistic boy staring into a globe.
I use that scene of the boy with the globe.
I use that entire scene in one of my videos.
And I got completely copyright-striked and demonetized.
But it was worth it because I just thought it was so funny.
I was going to say it.
Blast it.
Well, I mean, technically in...
Oh, fuck.
There is an alternate dimension.
There is an alternate universe where Alt Timeline, Ben St.
is staring into a snow globe imagining all of the other goings on.
I don't know how that fits in.
That's in The Forgotten Chapter of the Slime and Punishment Saga,
which is called Nuts.
Which I guess...
I'll put a link in the description.
I never talk about nuts because I just did it on a whim like one day.
But it's like a whole framing device thing.
I won't even look for it now.
I don't remember where I put it.
Next voicemail.
Fuck, I lost track.
I gotta go back to Speakpipe.
The next voicemail is 419.
When Ben talks about Noita...
Wait, did I post it?
No, sorry.
The next one is Audacity Follow-Up and Corrections by Oblivionfall.
So, I hope he says...
No, actually it is spying on me.
No, actually...
Okay, 3, 2, 1, go.
Just a follow-up to the Audacity thing because I realized my previous voicemail was recorded on the 5th
and people aren't gonna hear this until the 16th or later.
So, just to cover my ass, let me say this...
Audacity do not need to collect your IP.
Even though it's just for 24 hours and then it's irretrievably lost and can't be leaked anymore.
The simple fact is they don't need it for diagnostics.
It's unnecessary.
And so, yeah, I think we should ask them not to do that.
And if a fork comes along, using the fork obviously would probably be a fine idea.
I don't particularly want to have to use my firewall or use a VPN to use Audacity.
Even though, again, they're only holding it for 24 hours and nothing's gonna really happen with it.
But the misinformation of, oh, they're tapping your microphone and sending it to the Russian government
and that shit is completely fucking incorrect.
There's no evidence of that at all.
And I wish we were sure.
People are getting a lot of attention for saying that and it made me mad,
which is why my previous voicemail had a lot of fucks and shit sent in.
Yeah, you get the idea.
Okay.
Oh, here it is.
No, I found it.
I found nuts.
There's a link to one of the pages of nuts.
Nuts the beginning.
It is dimension A12F22X75 parentheses C, just in case anyone...
Wait, that's not the first page.
No, I gotta go back to the first page.
You gotta put this on your site.
I should...
You know what?
I should put it on your site.
Yeah, I was gonna say like...
I don't know why I put it only on MSPFA.
I was surprised that this isn't on...
Yeah, this site.
Not.
Oh, so that's what MSPFA is.
Yeah, this is fully...
This is fully RFCK Canada and it is completely essential lore
and I just like never made a big deal out of it or told anyone about it.
Man, I love that even if you try to follow Slime and Punishment,
Ben will still fucking cuck you and not show you important lore for no reason.
I'll just make some chapters in secret and forget to mention them.
Yeah, that's true.
Okay, next voicemail for real this time.
This is...
Yeah, when Ben talks about Noida, 3, 2, 1, go.
Yeah, that sounds kind of cool.
That is how I feel.
Honestly, I've seen people play Noida.
It does look really cool, but I just keep being like,
oh, I'll get into that later.
I'll play it later and I will play it later.
Simsy was playing Noida and he was showing me some of his deaths the other day in the mines.
He hasn't gotten his first win yet, so I watched him desperately try and get the Fire Mage wet with a water potion,
but he was standing on a hill and I said, no, no, you fool.
You got to lure him down into a hole so you can get him in a puddle.
You got to get him in a puddle.
Gravity, fucker.
He's not going to get wet standing on a hill.
I had not...
Oh, I think I mentioned this.
I'll say it again because I'm proud of myself.
I finally did the 33 Orb, get everything run, God run, got the permanent cosmetic item, the Golden Amulet.
My character has a Gold Amulet now forever.
I didn't play Noida for like a week or more, like two weeks after that.
Just yesterday, just because I was kind of stressed out and I wanted to relax,
I opened up a game and I played it for maybe like an hour or two and I died really bad because I was out of practice.
I love Noida.
I fucking love Noida.
I thought you abandoned Noida.
Yeah, it is interesting.
I thought you were like, no, I'm only into modded Minecraft now.
That's the only thing I care about, modded Minecraft.
Well, you play as a dark wizard in both things.
You're just playing Noida in Minecraft.
No.
I didn't do every quest, the Sunseed quest.
I didn't complete the Sunseed quest, so I have to create the Sun.
Wow.
Look at this fucking casual.
Didn't even complete the Sunseed quest.
Everyone laughing at me at the moment.
Didn't even create the Sun.
Yeah, I got a...
There's a whole bunch of like bosses.
There's like new bosses and like the recent updates that I just never went and found.
I should just go...
I hate when games add new bosses for me to fight.
So much work.
I hate new content too.
I hate it when like, they add a bunch of new cool stuff.
I have had it happen where like, I'll 100% a game and then they add new content.
I'm just like, ugh.
Now I didn't 100% that game and I can't go back and do much new shit.
Like I've moved on from the game at this point.
If I moved on from the game, then yeah.
It's like, what do you mean I don't have all the trophies anymore?
I don't want to get more.
I had them all.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Next voicemail is called when Vinesauce Joel plays Noida.
Three, two, one, go.
Holy shit, that's so fucking cool.
I have to buy that immediately.
Did Vinesauce Joel play Noida and...
I don't know.
I feel like it's like sort of an attempt to dunk on you a little bit in a loving way,
but like, he's comparing you talking about a game on a podcast or watching someone play it on stream,
which is of course that's going to be more entertaining and interesting
and be a better job of getting you interested in the game.
You know what I mean?
Oh, I see.
That's his reaction to watching someone play.
Yeah, whatever.
I see that Vinesauce Joel did play some Noida.
Good for him.
I mean, I've watched, I really like Fury Forge's Noida videos,
although he doesn't really do like gameplay.
He does sort of explanation videos.
The one I've watched play at the most is McQueen.
He's pretty good.
I don't think he's really doing it anymore though.
I mean, yeah, probably watching Noida is more fun than just hearing me be like,
oh, and then you can squirt water on fire and the fire goes out and it makes steam.
Oh, Pog.
It is funny because that sounds so stupid,
but I love that watching these chemicals interact with each other.
There was this browser game where you just make powders and watch them interact
and that's what Noida reminds me of.
Noida is literally made by people who made that power game.
That makes perfect sense
because I used to have so much fun just like making a big flammable thing
and sitting on a fire and going, oh, it's odd to fire.
I did that.
Yeah.
It's the people that made the powder game.
They basically made the powder game and teamed up with some other guys.
Real video game, which is a good idea, honestly.
And they were like, let's make a rogue-like action game out of our powder shit.
And they're like, okay.
And then they did.
Good for them.
And I'm glad.
Noida seems pretty popular, not like AAA mainstream popular,
but pretty popular for like an indie game.
People have heard of it.
Yeah.
I'm thinking I might want to stream it again soon
because I'm sort of having played it in a while
and I've kind of got the itch again.
That one stream where I beat it was very hype.
It took me a bunch of tries.
Oh man, that was so exciting.
That was a great stream.
That was like two months ago or more now.
It was a while ago.
Ben, that was eight years ago.
It could be.
You could tell me that.
No.
It had to be.
God, it was this year, right?
Yeah.
It had to be this year.
Oh my God.
I don't even know.
All right.
We're dilly-dallying.
Next voicemail is called...
It's Janess.
Three, two, one, go.
I would like to know your thoughts on the general reaction to
Biden withdrawing the troops from Afghanistan.
My thoughts on the general reaction to it.
I don't really see much of a reaction to it.
But they kind of did it without making a big deal of it.
That was on purpose.
Most of the reaction I saw to it.
I didn't see that much.
I just saw a couple people being sort of making fun of the fact
that they kind of just quietly did it and didn't say they were doing it.
Mission accomplished.
We did it.
We beat the war on terror.
Mission.
We kicked their ass.
Just like Vietnam.
Victory for America.
Undefeated.
Zero deaths.
USA.
What's the KD ratio?
I was literally about to say...
America, we may not win every war, but we got a pretty good KDR.
I mean, if you consider the nukes we dropped on Japan
versus the amount of soldiers that died in Japan,
it's pretty high.
Oh.
Oh, we got...
We could throw thousands to the fucking meat grinder
and we would still be killing it on KDR.
And that's exactly what we should do.
I wonder, like, of all time, the UK versus US,
who has the highest death count.
Well, honestly, everything the US ever does
should contribute to the UK's count,
because we're just a, you know, we're a spin-off show.
Subsidiary.
Exactly.
Every piece of colonialism the UK ever did.
And that includes America.
Yeah, I think UK might win.
Well, I mean, the United States has a bigger population,
but the UK was around a lot longer, so...
The British Empire at its peak was just enormous,
like the global reach and influence.
Okay, but would the British...
But citizens of the British Empire
were not necessarily, like, British people.
It might have been, like, people from the colonies.
Yeah, okay, if you're talking about, like,
the state has directly killed.
I think America might win, honestly, if you're going on that much.
Are we talking about, has killed other people,
or have had their own casualties in war?
No, no, no, I mean, like, kill other people.
Like, they're enemies in war, or, like,
actually control wars.
America definitely wins if you include all the CIA covert ops
in, like, South America and shit.
I'm gonna say that just because the UK was, like,
around more during, like, colonialism
in, like, the spice trade era,
I feel like it, like, laid its roots down
and probably had a much longer lasting effect
on a lot of the world.
So I kind of want to go with the UK.
Someone in the comments will be sure to correct us,
but, yeah, I feel like they're both, they're both up there.
Honestly, if you've got an opinion on this,
please weigh in in the comments, because I don't know.
I'm sh... I'm... fuck.
Who's the most...
I don't know enough about British colonialism,
like, I don't know all the intricate stories.
I don't know more about, like, the bad shit America has done.
So I guess I should just say America.
We win everything, even the being bad competitions.
No.
No, we're not.
We're not.
That's the only thing America wins anymore.
No, we're good.
Uh, next voicemail is called
tar... tar-badative trans-a-dendum.
Three, two, one, go.
Correction to my voicemail about speakers' listener responsibility.
The obvious best answer is that the person
who has the majority responsibility is the one that's me.
If I'm speaking, then it's the speaker,
and if I'm listening, then it's the listener,
because I'm the one that I can control.
It's only that ratio I said if neither party is me
or if the other person has also adopted this opinion of mine,
because they know true wisdom when they hear it.
It's equal parts trust in myself to be good
and a way to hold myself accountable,
should I falter, within reason,
at collaborating with others in the field of communication.
Just another reason they call your guy tar-badative trans-a-dendum here.
The left is Jordan Peterson.
That was already an incredibly confusing question,
and now he's answered it in an even more confusing way to me, honestly.
I just answered it in a way that is like,
but you didn't see this come in.
But it wasn't even like, here's the voicemail,
here's the answer voicemail.
There's a follow-up voicemail that was submitted days later.
Like, yeah, of course,
when you consider the fact that you can only control your own actions
and not that of others, and therefore,
like, yeah, obviously that changes the consideration.
Whatever you learned here.
Nothing.
No more voicemail.
No, okay.
Next voicemail.
Next voicemail is...
Did I post it yet?
No, I fucking didn't.
You did.
No, obviously I did.
It's called Sonic Shroom.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey there, PCP.
I heard you guys talking about holo nights.
It's on the podcast,
and so I just wondered, like,
if there's any other Metroidvania kind of games that you guys like.
I've been playing a really good one called
Ender Lilies.
It's kind of like a holo night,
but it's got more of a gothic theme to it.
More?
More of a gothic?
I was going to say what.
But yeah, I know I've seen some...
I saw this.
I saw this on Steam.
I saw this on Steam the other day.
You know, I just thought,
yeah, what are you guys into in that kind of genre?
Am I wrong?
Do you have a car alarm going off in the background of that?
What the fuck was that sound?
I thought it was a bird at first,
but I think it was a car alarm.
It was too modulating too frequently.
No, it was an alarm.
Whatever, it's fine.
Metroidvanias.
Honestly, I can't think of anyone that I've played even remotely recently.
The only, like, Metroid likes I enjoy
are Metroid Zero Mission and Metroid Fusion.
What kind of Castlevania has ever entertained me?
I've never really been a big Castlevania bloke.
I'm only...
My biggest Metroid game that I'm a fan of is Super Metroid.
It's just classic, but I do love the Zero Mission and Fusion.
They're great too.
Yeah, I love all the Metroid games.
I've played all the Castlevania games.
I prefer the classic Castlevania games.
Yeah, actually, I'm a little familiar with the 2D ones,
but not like the Castle...
Not like Simply the Night, you know what I mean?
Not the Vayneas.
Yeah.
When you say the classic ones, you mean like the pre-Symphony ones.
Yes.
Yeah.
I never played the old ones.
The first one I ever played was Symphony of the Night.
And then my favorite Castlevania that I played the most
was definitely Aria of Sorrow and the Direct Sequel too.
It had a Direct Sequel, I forget what it was called.
Aria of Sorrow, Dawn of Sorrow.
Yes, Aria of Sorrow and Dawn of Sorrow.
I played the shit out of those.
The other ones on the handheld were like, okay,
but that one was the best one.
Or the one I played the most anyway.
Yeah, those were good.
It was Fusion.
Oh, what's that one?
It's that series that's like...
It's that indie series by the Japanese guy who...
It's all about cute girls and it's a Metroidvania.
Momodora.
She's got the...
Yeah, I've played the...
I've played most of the Momodora games,
and those are good.
They're not like huge.
They're not as big as a Castlevania,
but they're good.
They're good Metroidvania action.
Although like...
I think it was made by a Brazilian guy, actually,
or something like that.
Wait, really?
Yeah.
You know what?
That might be true.
Or a Venetian guy or some shit like that.
They get...
There's like five of them and they get...
Like the first one is really basic
and they get more complicated as they go on.
The second to last one is like a pretty good, solid,
like kind of platformer action sort of game in that vein.
The last one is very good.
It is definitely a Metroidvania,
although it's smaller than like a Symphony of the Night.
It's not as big as like a mainstream Nintendo game like that,
but it's really good.
Those are good games.
Hollow Knight's good.
I mean, Noida is...
Noida has a bit of that in that it's a side scroller shooter
about exploration.
I wouldn't really call it a Metroidvania,
but it's a metroglainite.
Something like that.
Add powder in there.
Add powder in there somewhere.
Yeah.
I should say I have played Hollow Knight a lot more.
I've been streaming it, actually.
Everyone twitch.tv slash give and take.
And I'm really enjoying it.
So that's a good one.
That's a good ass video game.
Have you fought the boss that's like...
I think it's like a bunch of Beatles that like drop down from the ceiling?
No.
I don't know.
The moment I'm at the boss that's like four or five big circle guys,
and they're all in a room and you got to get them.
It's like in the nobles quarter or whatever.
I feel like maybe that's the one.
I remember there was one where there was a bunch of...
There's one...
Yeah, I remember these ones drop from the ceiling.
And I remember you could kill one before the battle started.
There was a trick you could do that could kill one of them.
So there would only be three instead of four.
And it made it a lot easier.
But that was the hardest boss for me in all of Hollow Knight.
I think it was because my nail wasn't well upgraded at the time.
Yeah, I think the most recent big boss I defeated was the Hornet Fight
outside the outskirts of the city and the dust.
Have you fought the Mantis Lords?
Yeah, yeah, that was ages ago.
I don't know how far in I am, but I've got the super dash.
I've got the double jump.
I've got all the three nail techniques.
And then the secret other one.
I know people say that when you upgrade your nail, the game gets kind of too easy.
And that's probably true, but I just fucking upgraded my nail all the way
because I just want to have fun.
I just want to have fun playing the game.
The last upgrade is there.
If they didn't mean for you to be able to have it and use it
and balance the game around that, then why would they put it there?
So I didn't listen to the haters.
I got all the nail upgrades.
I got super powerful and I won.
Anything else or next voicemail?
No.
Anything more on that bullshit?
Okay, good, good.
I don't want to hear it.
Next one is called Ben's Been Talking Shit.
Now he'll taste comeuppance.
That's a gross joke, by the way,
because Chris Chan would call her semen her comeuppance.
So I don't want to taste that.
Why did you say that?
Why did I say that?
It doesn't matter.
Just do it.
It's funny because I like it.
That information is just kicking around Ben's head
and he has to inflict it on all of us.
Didn't even mention the Fanta.
She had all these weird, I mean the Fanta is a whole different thing.
They had all these weird things.
What would she call it?
She would call it...
Oh no, she would call it her comeuppance,
but she would also call it navy.
This popped into my head the other day.
She called it navy because it was like semen.
Oh, god.
Like semen.
So the navy, yeah, yeah, really.
Brilliant.
Okay, next one is called Ben's Been Talking Shit.
Now he'll taste comeuppance.
Three, two, one, go.
So Ben, you've been talking shit.
I actually think I only send in voicemails
because I want to piss on the podcast.
How dare you, honestly.
How the fuck dare you say something so fucking accurate.
Piss has not comeuppance.
It's a different fluid.
You just gonna go?
39 seconds of this.
I have stopped.
No, I can take it.
No, go on.
Just piss.
Just keep pissing.
The piss sound isn't nearly as bad as the shitting sound,
in my opinion.
What the fuck are you doing?
Last, last week there was, I don't,
I still believe that guy was really shitting.
Oh, wait, no, the next one is called Me Taking a Shit Week 2.
I'm not even clicking on this one.
I'm going to do it.
I don't know.
Viewer, viewer beware.
You're in for a scare.
Skip ahead if you're some kind of weirdo
who doesn't like to hear sounds of shitting.
Three, wait, there it goes.
Three, two, one, go.
No, come on.
This is too dramatic.
Sorry, I'm going to have to agree with you,
but I think it's more likely that this is real
than it is someone downloaded a bunch of fake shit sounds.
Yeah, what do we think?
Should we not play this?
Is this a little too much?
Are you really going to let shit guy, like,
browbeat you into finally screening the fucking messages
when, you know, pig guy and all these other heroes
couldn't do anything?
He's going to take, you're going to send the message
that you will cow-tow and capitulate
to these shitters on microphone.
Shit, you're absolutely right.
We can't let the shitters win.
No, let them win.
I don't care.
No, they're faking it.
They don't actually shit.
Well, I will continue to not listen to them.
It's not true.
It's just a joke.
It's just a meme.
This is just going to be like the boy who cried shit sounds
and whenever they actually want to talk,
whenever they actually want to leave a voicemail,
I won't listen to it.
Isn't this why you guys have the voice jail
so people who have commit crimes
can't submit in multiple more new horrible crimes?
Like, wasn't that the whole point of it?
The shit is voice jail material.
I vote voice jail.
You know what?
You're absolutely right.
We do have voice jail for a reason.
I think I agree.
Yeah.
You know what?
Yes, voice jail.
Voice jail for the shitters.
It's the only...
How can I...
It's so simple.
How can I not have seen it before?
You just want to...
Although there is...
Ben just wanted a perfect utopian society
where everyone can have freedom of speech
and then some guy had to come up in the middle of the town square
and just take a huge shit
and now he was like,
okay, I guess we have to make some bridges
to this freedom of speech thing.
It's the tragedy of the commons.
The...
Oh, I was going to say...
Yeah, the thing about the voice jail
is that there is no actual mechanical disincentive
from someone in voice jail
just sending voice mails anyway.
You can't tell them that.
What the fuck?
They have to think it's real.
Well, they should be...
They should be ashamed of themselves
if they don't honor the social contract
that the voice jail represents.
So, no sir or madam.
No more shit voice mails.
Shame.
Next voice mail is called
smacking a dog with a newspaper.
Next voice mail is called Frost Drive.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, I gotta agree,
the nightmare of having your head crushed is pretty bad,
but I got a worse one for you.
I thought of this the other day
and I can't stop thinking about it,
which is when AI gains self-awareness
and becomes conscious.
People think the scary part is the AI going evil,
and it isn't.
The scary part is what happens
after we kill the AI consciousness?
Where does it go?
What happens?
What if it gets sent
to some type of purgatory type dimension
and because it's completely unnatural
and never meant to be there?
It glitches purgatory and gains control of it.
And then every human that dies after
will never get sent to hell
or heaven or reincarnation.
But instead,
we get trapped in that purgatory hellscape
controlled by the AI we killed
and it wants revenge.
How do you kill an AI
that wants revenge?
We're already living in that reality.
It already happened
and we're living in it.
This is purgatory.
I can't feel scared about this
because you need to believe in purgatory
and the afterlife.
This presupposes a lot of things.
And also that you can kill a robot.
Yeah.
Okay.
Robots will have souls.
Robots can't even exist
that will be AI consciousness.
I mean, eventually.
Yeah.
It'll happen to in our lifetimes, maybe.
And then this is so beyond metaphysical nonsense.
It's like a cool premise
for an anime or something.
If that's what he was saying,
if he's saying like,
this is something that actually is scary,
then I don't really agree with him.
That's fine,
but it doesn't scare me in the same way
that thinking about having my head crushed
scares me because it's not immediate.
Like, in the same way that like...
It's a lot easier to imagine
your head getting crushed.
I mean, that's like a real thing.
The thing about the head getting crushed
is that it is a thing
that I could physically experience myself
that could happen to me.
This thing about,
oh, an AI takes over purgatory
and human souls get trapped.
Like, that's...
What is that?
I'm scared of physical things,
not metaphysical things.
I have a question.
By your head getting crushed,
do you mean like it getting crushed slowly?
Because I think that would be worth it
being crushed like fast.
I mean, both,
but yeah, probably slower would be worse.
Yeah.
But I'm scared of both.
I've been the example that I keep talking about
is having being run over by a train.
It's not even just my head,
any part of me.
I mean, I know this is weird.
It's not even if this is crazy,
but I'm pretty scared of having any part of me
run over by a train,
but in particular my head.
The thing I think of is,
you know the end of the Terminator
when the Terminator gets crushed
in like one of those presses?
Yes, yes.
That's the thing I think of.
Like, imagine if you were crushed by that thing.
That'd be so fucked up.
Yeah, that's exactly the kind of thing
that I am afraid of
and it keeps me up at night
and I think about it.
This is why Ben wears that hat.
He's trying to protect his head at all times.
You know, it's like,
I don't know, just the thought
that there are train tracks
somewhere in the world
and at some point in the future,
I could end up on them
at the wrong time.
Who knows why,
but it's possible I could end up
in the wrong place at the wrong time
on a train track somewhere
and be crushed by a train.
It could be that that's my future
and I just have no way of knowing.
I don't think you would get run over by the train
though.
I think you'd get hit by the train
and fly in like,
fly in the air.
You know, that's a good point.
Unless you put your head right on the tracks.
Imagine, here's a really scary scenario.
I'm going to try not to think about it
too hard as I describe it,
but imagine you're on a train track,
you're hit by a train,
you doesn't kill you,
but you're sort of like,
stuck to the front of the train,
the air is rushing against you,
you're kind of smacked against the train,
you're sort of splatted against it,
and you're sort of being held in place
by the wind,
but the train is still going
and you're slipping,
and you're slipping down
and you can't stop yourself
and you're slipping further and further
and at a certain point you know
that you will slip under the train
and be crushed.
And you can't stop that from happening,
but it's not immediate
it's a slow slide before you finally
go more and more underneath
and then you fall.
Man, I can promise you
if you get hit by a train
and then you're pinned to the train
as it's moving forward,
you're going to be dead or unconscious
before you're feeling
slowly getting crushed under the thing,
like the concussive force
of getting hit by a train
will kill you
or instantly render you unconscious.
You know what?
I think your body would get ripped in half.
That's a good point.
I'm talking about really like you
smack on the front.
The thing Ben is afraid of
is being awake and aware
of these things happening to his body.
I'm telling you
any of these things happen
you're going to instantly be blacked out
and then dead
and you're not going to like
consciously be aware of what's happening to you.
Yeah.
Then again,
I know this is not a rational fear.
I'm not trying to like be like
you're dumb for thinking this.
I'm just like, you know,
it's even less likely than that.
You're right.
You just need to like
work out your like head muscles.
You just need to lift.
You need to lift, bro.
Really big head muscles.
When you get your head chopped off,
you still stay alive for like 10 seconds.
Oh God.
I was...
Think about what that must feel like.
Think about...
You would probably roll around
and then you die.
Think about how it feels
when you pull a muscle, right?
When you have the feeling
of having a pulled muscle
anywhere in your body.
Now think about that
taken to the absolute extreme.
The muscle is completely severed.
Now think about that
experiencing that in every one of the muscles
that every one of the delicate, complex muscles
that connects your head to your body.
As well as the fact that you're having
separate from your body.
You gotta think...
You're gonna think about it right now.
This is what adults do.
This is what grown-ups do.
They spend every day thinking about dying horribly.
We're like fucking
10 hours into this podcast
and I just want to go to bed.
I don't want to think about being fucking...
The adults think about their heads being severed
from their necks, you fucking coward.
I get worried about like
slipping and falling
in a totally avoidable way.
I can't imagine getting onto a train track
accidentally putting my head so close to the track.
How would you get there?
But if I'm just slipping and falling
and I just happen to fall into a road
where the car comes by.
Yeah, that's the thing.
You're just walking on the side of the road.
Cars are going by so fast.
They could just instantly delete you
and you would have like nothing to do.
You have no...
You couldn't react.
Honestly?
It's the feeling of like
I was looking at my Pokemon Go
and I just realized
oh, if something came
I probably wouldn't have been able to react.
Shit.
I could have died in that moment.
I don't find cars that scary
even though they're like a million times
more likely to kill me
than any of the things that I am.
Then here's the thing about trains.
Is they're pretty easy to avoid.
Just don't go on the track.
Cars can go anywhere.
I know.
It's not rational.
But they're so big.
They're so big.
You should become a train.
Yeah, Thomas the Tank Engine style.
You're right.
I was just saying,
somebody's all like stubbed my toe.
Shining time state.
Shining time state in America.
Exactly.
The lore.
All the lore with the Ringo
and the George Carlin
and all the stuff.
I remember I was a big Thomas head growing up.
I love Thomas the Tank Engine.
That was like one of my first things
that I obsessed about.
Thomas head.
I don't...
I don't think I...
I wouldn't call myself a Thomas head,
but I did watch the show and I like...
I had little toys.
I didn't have any like...
I love the toys.
I didn't have any toys or anything.
Did you see that movie with that,
the purple train?
I vaguely...
Most of my Thomas memories are like
blurred together.
There's an awful,
terrible Thomas the Tank Engine movie
with like a new character
that is like
extremely...
I can't remember.
It's been such a long time.
What's it called?
Thomas the Tank Engine
and the movie.
I don't know what it was called.
Thomas the Magic Braille Road.
That was it.
It had the girl from Matilda in it?
Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
I never see it.
I ain't never seen that.
It's probably too old for it.
I haven't seen it,
but I know what you're talking about.
It's...
I mean, I remember seeing
a nostalgia critic review of it
and I was like,
oh, I know that film.
I didn't...
And then he showed me.
He showed me the ways
that it was not good.
And I was like,
oh yeah.
Yeah, that was terrible.
I'm so glad he remembered it
so I didn't have to.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Yeah, he did it.
He fucking did it.
I mean, that's why I watched it.
The Madman.
I wanted to see...
I wanted to see and talk about
my films.
I can't fall to there.
Next voicemail,
or I don't even remember
what that voicemail was.
What was the question I forgot?
Something about...
Do you want to...
AI...
Oh, right, right, right.
I was like,
how did we get on talking about
the fucking trains crushing
into death?
Because we're talking about scary things.
So, of course,
we're talking about
Thomas the Tank Engine.
Next voicemail is called
How to Save the PCP.
3, 2, 1, go.
PCP
Featuring
Tommy J.
Notorious Revolutionary.
Make it happen.
He already had a better guest.
A better guest called Laserbot.
He already had Laserbot.
It's all downhill from here.
This is the peak of the PCP.
This is episode, what,
271 or whatever the fuck we're on.
It's just like,
yes, Laserbot, finally.
The show paid off.
Finally.
I'm listening to every episode of the PCP.
Finally a good episode.
All 270 episodes
we're leading up to this one.
Next voicemail is called
Aiden Welch.
Welch, 3, 2, 1, go.
Hey, I want to respond to that,
a vegan you had on my show.
Because
We had a vegan on.
The way I see it,
chickens need to take the steak
in their own future.
They need to
They hoist themselves up by their Bruce straps.
Okay, because as it stands,
I feel these chickens are complicit in big farms
all across America, okay?
Yeah.
If they want to do something, if they want to...
It was the same with slavery, actually.
They should do something about it,
like in Chicken Ride, okay?
Like in Chicken Ride.
Why don't they just do it like in Chicken Ride?
Like the U.S. arming these chickens,
like we do with a lot of militias.
But as it stands, I don't think they even care.
I think they can't pull themselves up by their bootstraps
because chickens have webbed feet.
Also, because in pulling yourself up
by your bootstraps is impossible.
That's the point.
Well, they have wings.
There's multiple...
They could flap a little bit.
They could just...
Why pull yourself up by your bootstraps
when you can literally just fly?
Yeah.
Wait, I mean, they can sort of fly.
They can sort of fly.
I mean, Chicken Run was all about chicken fly.
That was the climax.
Because they couldn't fly, they tried to fly.
There's chickens.
They got...
No more voicemails.
Okay, next voicemail.
How many left?
There's a dump.
There's not that many.
There's like...
Oh, like 20.
10 more.
Oh my god.
There's like 10 more.
Ooh-Woo-Lillia is a dump slut with a fake microphone.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, hi, guys.
So it turns out that I did a little loopsy.
My audacity was picking up my laptop microphone
and not my Blue Yeti.
Okay, so we're gonna turn on my good microphone now.
Oh, god.
And we're gonna hear it.
You ready?
Yeah, the pig is.
I called it.
I did the pig power down, is it dead?
I hope.
That was Robo Pig.
You know what?
Yeah, that was a different pig.
Satisfying?
No, that was the pig.
That was the, what, like death metal pig.
Yeah, but he turned off.
I think he ran out of batteries.
I think he turned off.
I think that's the end.
I think that's the end of the pig arc.
It's the mechanical pig shark
from James and the Giant Peach.
Remember that guy?
You remember the mechanical shark
with the grappling hook out of its mouth
and James and the Giant Peach?
I remember.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But it's a pig instead.
And it grabs you when you listen to a voicemail.
Oh, that's much better.
That's much better.
Next voicemail is, sorry, it's loading here.
It is called Mr. Larumas.
Larumas.
It's not done loading yet.
Quick fill time.
No, I don't refuse.
Okay, sorry.
I'm sorry.
That was a lot.
That was a lot to ask.
I shouldn't have put you on the spot.
Okay, here it is.
Mr. Larumas.
Three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa.
What?
This is Samurai Samoa.
Oh, not really.
I am an idealized memory of Samurai.
I see.
Fascinating.
It's just like the old days.
You are now enemy number two.
Samurai Samoa have no more teru enemy.
Bezerkeru chipo.
What the fuck?
You break brocode.
Samurai waifu not to give brojobu in a week.
Fuck you.
Okay, until you next time.
Sayonara.
Yeah, I haven't been able to think of a new character,
so just give me a couple of weeks.
I'm sorry.
Enjoy Samurai for the week.
Okay, we will.
This is an idealized memory.
Directors' Commentary.
More voicemails should apologize.
Sorry, I haven't made a voicemail in a while.
Sorry, I haven't come up with an iconic character in a while.
Take all the time you need, it's fine.
Nice to hear the Samurai is doing bad
and is upset with his marital problems.
Next voicemail.
Did I load it?
No, I didn't.
Whoops, here we go.
It is called...
Ben, I reply on Twitter Saint.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, I sent you a Twitter DM in March.
Just checked March 27th.
And you have not opened it.
March 27th.
We did talk about how the way to reach us is easy.
Did you lie to this poor man
and not answer his Twitter DM from months ago
and then erroneously claim that you answered Twitter DMs?
Because I have opened DMs on Twitter
and I emphatically do not reply to any of them, basically.
I generally do reply to Twitter DMs
as long as they're just like asking me...
Okay, if you're who I think you are,
someone did send me a message on March 27th.
All you sent me was the link to the Anamorphine Time podcast discord.
And I don't want to join the Anamorphine Time podcast discord.
That's why I didn't respond.
Craig.
Please.
Craig, are you joking me right now?
Craig is the dog of the fit.
Are you effin...
Craig's tired.
It's like your teeth are like,
God damn, why are you taking it so long on this episode?
It's four hours in.
Are we gonna beat the record?
For longest episode?
A lot of that's getting cut
because we have to cut out all the parts where Laserbot wasn't working
is the mic and shit.
That's true.
I'll be three and a half acts.
Anyway, I don't want to join the Anamorphine Time podcast discord.
So, wait, no.
I shouldn't answer the voicemails.
I gotta get Craig.
How do I do it?
Is it Colin Craig Leave PCP?
Is that the command?
Okay, I'm not recording that channel.
Okay.
Then Craig join PCP.
Please wait.
I will attempt to join in five seconds.
Three, two.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
Looks good.
Thank you, Craig.
Anyway, I don't want to join the Anamorphine Time discord.
I'm in too many discords.
Maybe I should join, but I don't.
I don't want to.
That's why I didn't answer you because it was no point.
If you expect a reply, ask a question.
Don't just like send a link.
And that's like, you shouldn't expect a reply to that one.
I mean, come on.
Yeah.
I think so.
I feel like I'm in the right here.
Next.
You are.
Yes.
Thank you.
Next voicemail is called Ben.
I care about things, Saint.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, in regards to maybe on Anamorphine Time,
you asked who I am.
But if you pay attention and listen to my voice
and my offers to change your diapers,
you would know who I am.
But you don't.
You don't care, Ben.
And it hurts.
Why won't you care about me?
I don't.
I don't understand.
I mean, I recognize your Twitter handle.
Who's that name?
What do you want from me?
No.
It's Bob Disgaea.
I don't know what the connection is here.
Who's Disgaea?
Bob Disgaea.
I'm sorry.
You're going to have to pay me a clearer picture.
I don't know what you're getting at.
Next.
Next one is called Bad Comment Show Update.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm moving this week, so I don't have time to do one.
There will be two next week.
Sorry, I haven't got a voicemail in a while.
That episode, this should have been in this week.
And one for the normal episode.
Just do it, then.
Just do that.
Ben seems to like this show,
so I think I'm going to actually supplement
by going back and doing bonus episodes
of really old episodes starting from the beginning.
We're starting someone's opinion.
Finding shitty comments on like PCP number one
and stuff like that.
That's fine.
But yeah.
At least two next week, but none this week.
Okay, listen, that's fine and all.
You didn't have to leave a voicemail.
Take to write an episode of the worst comment.
I mean, don't just read the comments, pick the worst one,
and then like, in the time it took you to send this voicemail,
you could have made that thing and sent it in.
You could have, yes, you could have picked a comment,
read it out loud, and said why you think it was bad.
Right?
I mean, it's not like there's that much that goes into it.
Don't apologize for not having a voicemail this week.
That's literally...
I feel like that must be a bit.
It's an intentional bit.
Apologize for not having a voicemail in the voicemail that you're sending.
I hope that's a fucking bit.
Okay.
All right.
Love your work.
Love your work on the voicemails.
Next one is called...
Oh, I didn't...
Sorry.
Fuck, I didn't post it.
It is called LGBTarbuckLegbaTransom.
Sorry, it's loading.
All fill time.
L-E-S-R, sync that up.
Bird, bird, bird.
Bird is the word.
Okay.
Here it goes.
Three, two, one, go.
Gender nihilist TarbuckTransom here and a weird conspiracy of circumstance
led to me casting this most recent episode of the PCP onto a television
instead of listening at my computer.
And naturally, the TV doesn't have ad block.
So I got a bunch of ads for AIDS medication before I got sick of it
and dug up my Bluetooth speaker so that I can stream at my usual to win
one-quarter speed ad-free.
But before I did, I checked the ads on a few other episodes,
and only the last one has ads for AIDS medication.
The only thing that I can see being different is that you had a rainbow
tested thumbnail and LGBT keywords everywhere.
So YouTube thinks that I must be one of them tumblers and have AIDS,
several kinds of bigoted.
Awesome.
Also, I'm related, but LGBT should be pronounced Legbat.
Legbat.
The, you know, we got a lot of, we got a lot of down votes on the last,
like not a huge amount, but I mean, our recent episodes have gotten like
single digit down votes.
The last episode, as soon as it went up, it got like a dozen or more down votes.
I saw there was someone in the comments saying monkey or riot.
So I think it may have been a raid or something.
I don't think so because that person has been, that person's been in the comments
for a while and I'm pretty sure they're just having a goof.
Well, maybe.
I don't think that person's been around for a while.
I mean, it was like 16 dislikes or something, wasn't it?
I know, but it's a lot more.
Well, now it's more.
I think it's probably got like 30 or no.
Well, okay.
It's more than usual.
The ratio was bad at first.
I actually noticed that.
Like, yeah, like you said, they all came in right at the beginning, all the dislikes.
And then it sort of, you know, it's more than usual, but it evened out.
It like became more normal.
So it's like not even really that noticeable, but it was definitely noticeable right at
the start.
Again, what's the point of a dislike, mom?
You guys know that doesn't do anything right.
I just thought, I just thought it was interesting and I don't know what it had.
So I think some people thought, oh, is it because there's a gay flag in the thumbnail?
The huge contention of like anti-LGBT PCP fans just saw the thumbnail.
Like, what the fuck is this going on in this episode?
Or maybe, I mean, maybe just ex fans.
Why would they be?
Ex fans who don't listen anymore, but who have never unsubscribed, but who see the flag
in their feed and they're like, I don't know.
It seems unlikely, but I mean, maybe, I don't know what other explanation there is.
But the other thing, I got a pop-up on YouTube.
I was on in my own account and I saw one of these pop-ups for the episode.
And it was like rank this episode out of five stars and like click, what did you think of
this episode?
And then it gave me a bunch of options.
It was like, did you find it, you know, entertaining, informative, life-changing, inspirational?
Life-changing was one of the options.
Yeah, I've seen that.
Have you ever seen that pop-up on YouTube?
I don't think I've ever seen it on one of my own videos, but I mean, I know it's for
like, it was for a different account or whatever when you were signed into your main channel.
But that's still like kind of funny.
It is funny.
Obviously, you click every single adjective and then send it five stars.
I gave it five stars.
I know I only gave it entertaining.
You didn't even say that latest episode of the PCV was life-changing?
I didn't say it was life-changing.
Damn.
I mean, because I was a little concerned.
It seemed like maybe we had triggered something in the algorithm that made it seem sus.
And I was like, do they think that we're spreading like vaccine misinformation because we talked
about Vax millions?
Is it the rainbow flag in the thumbnail?
Something, I don't know.
I mean, nothing happened.
It didn't get taken down.
It didn't get any strikes or anything.
So nothing ended up happening.
I was a little concerned that maybe the algorithm was like, the eye of Sauron was kind of like
leering at it for a second, like, hmm, what should we do with this?
I don't know.
I'd never seen one of those questions before.
It was very weird.
Prayed.
Well, like, prayed off of the floor after being flattened.
By the way, I missed a voicemail, but it's not actually a voicemail.
It was just this image.
Oh, yeah, I get it.
I got it.
You get it.
This is the Sarazee.
The Sarazee.
But it's far more realistic now.
Far more true to life.
So far more believable.
Crunchy and bidcrushed in this image.
I, yeah, I actually can't even tell if that's me.
I think that's you.
I mean, it would make sense, right?
I mean, it's patreon.com.
It could only be.
It could only be me.
I don't know who else would be.
My little bro.
Yeah, I just noticed that this is from my little bro.
It's pretty good.
It's pretty good meme.
Pretty good meme.
Scrolling through that.
Those were the days.
My little bro.
Yeah.
Wait, is it like a real website?
It was like on meme base with rage comics and all that.
Yeah.
I was going to say the little,
the little banner at the bottom gives me like nine gag vibes or something.
Yeah.
I've never seen that before.
I never, I never hit up my little pump.
My little brony.com.
What is that?
What does that have to do with Sarazee?
I was only like paying attention.
Nothing.
I think it's just.
No, no, no, no, the original.
Yeah.
The original image that this is an edit of is of Sarazee blowing up the wet pumpkin
headquarters after the Homestuck drama.
Okay.
Yeah.
What is the implication here that Munchie is blowing up your Patreon?
Munchie is blowing up.
Yeah.
And you are turning around.
Blowing it up.
I can't even tell.
Like, are you supposed to look upset about this?
Like you can't, there's like no.
Blowing it up to the moon.
You can't distinguish any features.
Yeah.
I was going to say.
No.
I'm completely smooth and JPEG artifacted.
I'm shitty like the sword.
You can't even touch me.
I just want to do this.
Munchie, why would you betray me?
I do.
I look like I'm made of mud.
I look like a fucking muck monster.
This ooze.
I'm being vaporized by the nuclear blast by the fallout.
I like it.
Munchie, is he crying out in like pain?
Is it like, I'm sorry.
I had to do this.
Sensei.
That's the expression.
Nice.
That's what I get.
He's just like incoherent.
He's pressing the button.
I don't think he, I think he's clearly happy about this in this.
He's singing.
He looks.
No, I choose to believe that he is pained.
He's, he's, he's shedding a single tear after defeating his sensei in a duel.
He never said.
Turning you into a JPEG artifact.
Purple.
Yeah.
Last.
I think the purple's lighting can be explosion.
But yeah, go on.
But I'm so smooth.
I'm so smooth.
Um, last voicemail.
We're finally made it.
This one is called soy boys, uh, based three, two, one go.
God, I've been rewatching.
Shadow Visor fell boys.
Get your soy pugs out.
Soy, soy, soy, soy, soy, soy, soy, soy.
Right.
Cause I, someone point, I think, I think this is Sean, um, pointed out.
Yeah.
The, the abbreviation for shadow of Israel is SOI.
So, so if you're, so if you're doing, if you're participating in the shadow of Israel
rewatch, uh, you are a soy boy.
That's a great nickname for that.
Uh, yeah.
Um, spork town heroin in my discord was saying that she tried to watch it again,
or she started it again and thought that the first episodes were boring.
And I think she's probably right because the weird stuff doesn't start happening
for a while.
Cause at first it's just like a completely normal.
Let's fuck around in Minecraft.
And it's only after a while that like the shenanigans start.
So yeah, it's, it probably takes a while to get done.
I was like, I was trying to figure out like, what the hell is this again?
This is so much is the, um, that the Yogscast thing.
Yeah.
It's the, it's the Yogscast one that like kind of evolves into like a narrative.
Right.
So I actually do kind of respect that.
It's kind of a cute little take on like a let's play.
You know what I mean?
Even though it is like, I don't know.
I feel like nowadays that's not even that epic.
Like, like plenty of Minecraft YouTubers have done stuff like that.
But at the time it was like, wow.
Epic.
I was never a huge Yogscast watcher, but like I did, I was aware of that.
I was like, interesting, interesting.
I, someone, someone linked me the Yogscast just as a, I'd listen to it just cause someone was like, hey, give this listen.
I was like, okay.
And I listened to some of it and I was like, yeah, this is fine.
And then I just found the let's play the shadow of Israel fell.
I think maybe on the subreddit or something.
And I listened and I, I didn't know what I was in for.
And then when like the Israel fell stuff starts happening, I was like, oh my God, what is this?
Probably other people have done similar things since then.
Maybe they weren't even the first to do it.
But still, yeah, any attempt to weave some sort of narrative into like a let's play.
I think that's such an interesting concept, honestly.
It's like, you can do it.
I mean, obviously you could do it cringe and bad, but like, you can definitely have a good, cool story.
You can only tell in that kind of medium.
You know what I mean?
What, what I think makes it better is the fact that in general, I'm pretty sure that Simon and Lewis, they don't know what is going to happen.
They're not just like playing characters.
They're just being themselves and just reacting to like stuff that the other players are like sort of acting out in front of them that they like have not told them about ahead of time.
It's kind of D&D-esque in that regard, which is, you know, it's kind of like you have a bit of a dungeon master situation going on.
Yeah, I was mostly aware of these guys just because like, do people, do you people even remember what Yogg's stands for?
Does anyone even know what that means?
Because Yogg's stands for Ye Olde Goon Squad.
It was, they spun off of the something awful like wow guys or something.
It was like, so I was like, oh.
I didn't, I didn't know that.
I didn't know they used to be wow.
Yeah.
So they were a spin off of Goon Squad or whatever.
Like it was like, so I was like vaguely aware of them from that.
And then the weirdest thing, I don't know if you know this, one of the Yogg's cast people is a playable DLC character in Sonic and All Stars Racing transformed.
It was like for charity.
Yes.
The last podcast guy, whatever, is a playable video game character in a Sonic game.
Which one?
It's Sonic All Stars Racing.
It's such a weird mashup.
It is.
It has, okay, like Smash Bros is weird.
Sonic and All Stars Racing transformed has Danica Patrick, the TF2 characters, Wreck-It Ralph.
It's an insane roster.
Danica Patrick?
Danica, I don't know who that is.
A real life NASCAR racer, which is just here.
Hold on.
Which is just a weird cross-promotional thing.
It's like Unlucky Tiger Woods and Mario Gold.
Right.
Again, this was for charity and it was completely optional.
So, you know, if you don't want to download, have the Yogg's cast guy in your game, you don't have to.
But you could do it.
Which, oh, it's not even his, it's just him.
Yeah, it's just Simon.
It is a YouTuber in a video game, you know what I mean?
If I had known, if I had tried harder on my YouTube channel, I could get to be in a game with Sonic.
I would have tried a lot harder.
I'll tell you that much.
It's not even his avatar with the Viking helmet.
Oh, yeah.
Well, it's not like they can't use Minecraft related things.
I mean, that's like a, well, I guess Viking helmet is generic enough.
They could have gone away with it.
But yeah, I don't know.
It's literally like just a guy.
It's not even like, yeah, his character.
It's just him, you know what I mean?
His character in Minecraft is he role-plays as like a dwarf with a Viking helmet.
So like, you could just make him a dwarf, right?
Right.
But no, they just made him look like he does in real life.
Yeah, it's like, here's your podcast or character.
Blank stare on his character.
The actual model looks really not that good.
He's just staring.
Yeah.
Oh, that's funny.
His hair.
His hair looks like shit.
I love it.
Um, aptly characters in the game aren't even sacred characters.
There are a lot of funny and getting cast characters.
It sounds like a mess.
It is a good game.
I'll say that much just for the record.
Yeah, it is.
It is good.
Oh, what's his, what's his name?
Simon Yogg's cast dwarf character.
What is, what's the fucking character's name?
Simon.
His name is Simon Lane.
Honeydew.
This is dwarf name.
Right.
They should have made fucking Honeydew in the game.
Don't put the actual guy.
Yogg's cast like still a thing.
I mean, it has to be right.
It's too big of a brand to just to dissipate into nothingness.
Even after they had a big controversy.
I believe, I believe that the Yogg's cast, not really.
It's sort of splintered and a lot of the people who were involved with the Yogg's cast sort
of made their own channels and continue sort of on their own.
They got big enough that they can make their solo careers for sure.
Like Louis, I'm pretty sure that Louis from Yogg's cast is the guy who like founded the
Polaris like content network or something.
He's doing like management.
He's doing like content network management stuff.
Right.
I think I think I have the feeling that they sort of retreated from the public eye after
the very public like failure and quasi scam of the Kickstarter.
That was one of the worst Kickstarter stories I've ever heard.
Like just an unfortunate.
That's the one when people talk about when people talk about like embarrassing terrible
starters, there was like that one.
That event alone seriously probably impacted the public like faith in Kickstarter.
You know what I mean?
Just like the fact that a big profile like that big a profile, you just didn't expect
them to completely like it's not they delivered a disappointing product.
They did not deliver anything.
They just failed.
Which is a thing that can happen on fucking Kickstarter.
I backed Barkley too and they never delivered anything and it was just a big sad story and
I'm still sad about it.
They did, you know, it's still technically in development and they did put out a kind
of broken pseudo demo.
Barkley too, they put out the jank demo just like a month or two ago.
The last programmer remaining on the game like he said publicly, I give up this ain't
happening.
Here's the source code.
I'm leaking it.
That's so sad.
But you know what?
It's sad, but it's like at least I can give up hope that it would ever happen.
That one hurts me a lot.
I was really hyped for that game.
You know, they have they have.
Yeah, they have terms on Kickstarter that are like, keep in mind, we Kickstarter are not
responsible for whether or not the people you're backing.
It's weird because there is some legal liability.
You like Lord of Ghost Kickstarter right now this weekend.
It ends on Monday.
Do you want to contribute to a Kickstarter that's actually available?
Do you want to contribute to a Kickstarter that's actually going to fucking deliver?
Then I got a Kickstarter views called Lord of Ghost.
Yeah.
Wednesday, Wednesday, July 21st, 2021 at 154 p.m.
EdT.
So translate that to your own time.
6 p.m.
I think in the UK time.
This is the last PCP stream on the last PCP you're going to hear before it's over.
So this is your last chance.
I just want to stay for the record.
If you don't contribute to this Kickstarter, you are a fake fan.
And I don't know.
Stop listening to the PCP.
Fake fan.
I agree.
Stop listening to Cybershell too.
Unsubscribe from Cybershell if you're not going to listen to the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter.
What the hell are you doing?
You don't deserve to know things about Sonic.
Exactly.
I agree.
Well, we got to the end.
We did it.
Oh, that was the last one.
Oh, thank fuck.
Yeah, we did it.
What are we at like five hours now?
I was getting like to the point where I'm like, okay, if there's more voicemails, I think I might just drop out.
I think I might just go to bed.
I just have to dip.
Well, we did it.
It's over.
I mean, is the podcast over?
Have we said goodbye yet?
Well, we'll say goodbye now.
Say goodbye now.
Become a patron.
Lord of Ghost Kickstarter.
Minecraft server.
Speakpipe for the voicemiles.
Goodbye.
Bye.
It's really badly done.
Goodbye.
See you later.
Read Tails gets trolled as well if you haven't.
That's a good one.
Yeah.
Read Tails gets trolled or I'm banning you from the Tails gets trolled as well.
You're going to preemptively ban.
Do that too.
True.
You're banned until you read it.
Everyone is banned.
Yeah.
You have to submit.
You have to submit proof.
There's like a quiz that you have to take and if you fail, you're just never allowed on the server.
You know, I actually thought of doing that.
That's awesome.
You know what?
Okay.
I guess this is actually the end.
Goodbye.
Bye.