Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream.
I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
Hello everyone. Welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm Ben
Saint and Gibbontake is here as well. I'm here. I'm also here. It's the two casts. We haven't had
one of these in a while. For some reason. It feels like we have had two casts. It hasn't been,
actually. There's been a guest or there's been Tom. There's been three for a while.
I think you're right. I think you're right, but I don't know why you would be right. Why would
you do this? I have to make up for last episode for being slightly wrong.
Too much benefit of doubt. I'm still not convinced Riley is like an evil mastermind.
I definitely gave him too much credence. I was too on the fence on that one, so that is my bad
a little bit. I think it's maybe giving him too much credit to think that he is like some kind
of mastermind or whatever. On the one hand, I am completely right and therefore the best thing
to do is agree with me unconditionally. On the other hand, I can't. I mean, agreeing with Ben
saying, could you imagine? On the other hand, every single comment,
every hundreds of comments in the last episode saying, God, I hate Ben, but he's so right.
Every single one. Yeah, those are funny. I have issue though. Here's an issue I got.
Wait, let me let me send it. I was going to say, on the other hand, I kind of understand if you
feel like you don't have all the sides, then don't not coming to any conclusions. I feel like you
should have had all the information. It was all there, but if you didn't have it, you didn't read
it, you never got around to it, then okay, fair enough. If you're like, well, I'll withhold judgment
until I'm satisfied. I don't think I was totally wrong, but I can see how people are like, oh,
that's cringe game. I'm like, yeah, sure, sure. Yeah, I can see both sides of that issue.
But yeah, the issue I have was with the group of commenters who were being like
outwardly, openly transphobic towards Trixie wanting to even towards me.
There were a handful. There were a handful of those and they were all bad.
I don't like that they're mixed in there. They're embarrassing. They're embarrassing when I see
that. It was really quite, you know, because they hear like, oh, a trans person doesn't like
people who are being transphobic or saying things and like, haha, whatever.
But like, there's two things to it, right? There's one, it's despicable, die, but also,
it sort of ruins their own argument against Trixie. Like, if you have problems with her,
like the trans stuff, it sort of like to include transphobia in there is like,
antithesis, it goes against your own argument because you're sort of muddying the waters with
stuff that actually doesn't have anything to do with it. Because they don't know what
people are, right? Did you even listen to the episode? Do you even know what's going on? Do you
even know what the actual problem is? Were you even paying attention? Yeah. Well, I think they
all know, right? It's just that they ascribe like being trans equals bad to that whole thing as well.
Like, oh, did you know Trixie? They kept saying did you? So I'm thinking about it. But like Trixie's
trans, therefore, she's stupid and would do all these things. Oh, that's why. Oh, that's why.
That's why she did all these stupid things and is a bad person.
It's like, it's, it betrays a misunderstanding, a misunderstanding of Trixie and also of,
you know, they don't know like the transfer perspective of trans people is just that they
don't understand what it is. Like, it's, they don't care to know what it is. And so they make
big assumptions, usually very negative ones about the, you know, trans people in general.
And it's like, if you know your shit, you realize that it has nothing to do with
the arguments against Trixie. And so it allows people who do know their shit about trans people
to dismiss arguments that include transphobia in them. So you're doing yourself a disservice.
Also, fuck you, because that's horrible. You shouldn't be your bigots. It's kind of a bad
thing to do. It's not great. It frustrates me because Trixie is legitimately delusional.
But when I say that, those people think I mean something else. They think I'm agreeing with
them about something that I do not agree with them about. It's just, it just comes from a
place of ignorance. And that's cringe, like on its own, aside from all the political stuff
around, you know, surrounding it. It's just stupid. It's just cringe on its own. Imagine,
imagine being like, they just don't know what words mean. They just haven't thought it through
and are like angry that like the world is more complicated than their sixth grade understanding
of things. That's, I feel, I would feel pity. I would feel pity if I didn't find them so
despicable and want them destroyed. Yeah. Yeah. And it's been like annoying because I like, I want
to like say yes, I agree with Ben. Yes, Trixie is bad. And then that's right. It's all the
things that people associate with that are assumed because a lot of this drama around Trixie,
if you didn't watch the last episode, go watch the last episode of the Progress News podcast
where we talk all about it. But like a lot of that stuff is on Kiwi Farms, which is like, you
know, like literal like scum fuck place website. Like you don't want to be there.
Those guys, it's, I've said, I've said this before, but those guys are so embarrassing because
like they pretend they have this very, very thin pretense of like, we do not take a side.
We do not, we are above petty concerns of like whether you call this person a he or a she.
It's totally fine to call them a he, even if they're a trans woman, because it doesn't matter.
Like call them whatever you want. But if you do that, if you don't do that, if you call them a
she, people in the thread will lambast you and make fun of you and demand that you stop. They get
upset, which is pretty cringe, pretty cringe, pretty cringe to be triggered by pronouns bro,
in my opinion. Yeah, that was basically it. It's just sort of like, I don't like that there's that
element of it. And I would encourage everyone who has a problem with Trixie to, you know,
not hold back just because you're afraid of being called a transphobe, just leave the transphobia
out if it's in any point part of your reason why Trixie is bad, because it's stupid. You don't know
what you're talking about with regards to that. It's, it's, yeah, it's, it's, it's, you're, I don't
know, if you think that's the problem, then you're just, you're just confused. You're just,
you're just confused because two things like happened at the same time. I don't know.
I mean, it's not like being trans is, is like, like, it's not like being trans is like,
like not indicative of anything like this completely the same. Like obviously,
she's changed a lot through going through this transition. She's changed her mind about certain
things. She's changed her perspective. But that's not like a blanket thing that is like, oh, trans
people, they change always for the bad. And that's why trans people are stupid and insane.
And it's like, no, that doesn't, it doesn't track in any way. Lots of people transition
in different ways. It's a very personal thing. It really has nothing to do with anything other
than the specific person that you're talking about. You know, anyone could be trans and they
will all transition in the way that they would, you know, because that's who they are.
I'm glad you brought this up. Most, most people commenting seem to be on board, but definitely,
definitely a handful were confused. They were confused. And, you know, it's good,
it's good to set them straight, set them on the right path, the far right path again.
No, that was so fucking funny. I listened back to most of the episode and that joke is like,
I don't know. So right. So right. So I'm so right. I'm alt right now. Dab, dab, dab.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know. Yeah, that's about it. That's all I had to say on that topic. I didn't really want to
talk about drama all over again because it's like, no, not really. What else is there? What
else is there to really say about it? voicemails? No, Ben. Yes. Yes. What have you been doing the
past week? What's been going on in the same past week in the cathedral? Well, I mean,
I haven't really been. Oh, wait, Ben, happy birthday. Oh, yes. You had one of those. It was my
birthday four days ago as of this recording on the seventh. Yes. That was pretty, pretty good,
I guess. That was, yeah, they confined me now. I got a lot of, I got a couple of nice pieces of
birthday fan art on Twitter. Thank you to the people who made me those. I really liked all those.
I don't know. That was fine. I didn't really, I didn't really do anything. I did go and see
Munchy and Kazzy as a sort of late birthday hangout yesterday, and that was fine.
I don't know. I'm 33 and I'm dust and bones. I'm 33 and I'm drinking pee.
Yes, please. Ben, you look, you don't look a day over, you don't look a day over 32.
What's your secret? Well, zip, zip down and grab a, grab a bucket and a bucket.
Well, yeah, because you got to store it. You got to store it over long periods.
It, you know, you got to age it. I see. Yeah, yeah, yeah, it gets more powerful the longer it's,
it's steep. Terrible. Oh God, I'm gonna throw up. I'm gonna throw up just thinking about it.
Fuck, I don't even, what did I do? What did I do on my birth? Did I do anything? No. Did you wake up?
I did. I, unfortunately, I did. I feel like I'm forgetting something.
Oh, whatever. I got, I got that. Oh, Nate and Michelle called me. That was, that was cool.
I don't know. Whatever. It's fucking, I didn't do anything.
I found some new, there are some new energy drinks, though, that are, that exist now and
being out yesterday. We found some and I tried some and I didn't, I didn't love any of them. I was
really disappointed. Some of them had really cool flavor names, but they weren't that good.
Rain has a new flavor called white gummy bear, which is like a great idea and was very exciting.
But it was just okay. It wasn't like my favorite or anything. It was just fine.
There's a, there's a new, there's new monster ultra. There's ultra gold and ultra watermelon.
What does the ultra do? Is it just the ultra? No, the ultra is the, it's the different flavors,
but they're all like zero sugar, like zero calorie. What is there? There's white, there's
ultra white, ultra, ultra black, ultra violet, ultra blue, ultra sunrise, ultra, there's ultra red.
Ultra brown. Now there's ultra, now there's ultra gold and ultra watermelon. Oh, there's ultra rose.
No, Rosa, Rose, whatever. Oh, ultra paradise. Ultra paradise is the one that looks like slime
because it's like super bright green. And I, this blew my fucking mind. I was so sure that
ultra paradise was green apple watermelon flavor. And I remember thinking to myself,
ooh, green apple watermelon, that sounds really good. I can't wait to try that. And then trying it
and thinking, hmm, that's really good. And tastes just like green apple and watermelon.
Everything's, everything's coming up millhouse. And, but I was looking up what the new flavors are.
And apparently ultra, ultra paradise is not green apple watermelon. It is kiwi cucumber
lime flavor. And this is, this has changed everything for me. Nothing will ever be the same.
Maybe, maybe it's all in your head and it's actually just a bunch of sugar and you just think it's
a fruit when it's just sugar. It's just, it's just, it's just the color of the can that tricks me
into thinking they taste different. Yeah. I could believe it. I could believe it.
I don't know. None of the, none of the new flavors blew me away. I was a little disappointed.
There were opportunities there. Wasted opportunities.
It's just, how, they didn't fill the void. The, the, the new, the new monster ultra
colors didn't fill the void inside me. What, what should I do?
From being one year older, you have an extra year's worth of voice to fill. You've been collecting them.
I've been, I've been void gazing. I've been chasing it. Yeah.
I just, I just gotta find something else. Gotta find, gotta find meaning. I can't,
I think, I think I, I've said this before, but I think I've finally hit the point where I have no
more joy. I have no more joy to extract from Noida anymore. I, I'm just, I've got a game going
right now. My wand is amazing. I'm at the last boss and I'm like, well, I could go and collect orbs,
but what's the point? You know, what's the point? I know that feeling right now. It's,
it's in Minesweeper. Even though Minesweeper is like endlessly fun, I'm like, I can just complete
like an evil sized board in no guessing mode. Evil sized. Yeah. And it'd be like clickity,
clickity, clickity, clickity, clickity, clickity, clickity, clickity, clickity, clickity, clickity,
down the track, down the Minesweeper track. And I completed it and I was like, ah, yeah.
Well, I can do that now. It's no longer that much of a challenge. Yeah. Just the times I lose is
usually just when, oh, it's very difficult and, like, I can't do it, and then I lose. Or I just
slip my finger, but if I can, you know, if the, if there's no, like, big guess work,
I'll just go all the way through and I'm like, okay, I've spent so long listening to
YouTube videos and playing this game. I don't care about what I'm doing, but I guess I'll
do another one. Oh, yeah, I guess I'll just do another, I guess I'll just start up a new
Noida because I beat the last one. Okay. I've been playing Dark Souls as well, that sort
of thing where I got the Black Knight Greatsword early on. I was like, oh, I guess I should
do a strength build. And I just played the game with a strength build, one-shotting most
things. It's like, this is so boring. I've played the game like this at least two times
all the way through. And it's not fun. Dark Souls 1 is very slow. The Black Knight Greatsword
is extremely slow. But I know all the enemies, I know all the places, I know everything. I
can just run through it, kill everything, grab everything, kill the bosses. I'm like,
I spent like three, four hours to last, you know, that day just doing that. And I didn't
enjoy myself. I was just on autopilot. I was playing the thing.
Yeah. Yeah.
Why go to be like that?
Where am I going to get? The dopamine well has dried up. We got to find more. We got to
migrate somewhere. We got to be nomads and roam somewhere to find new supplies.
I think it's just because it was so easy to click on. I've been, we wanted to get into more
into Subnautica. And that was pretty cool. Subnautica seems scary.
It is. That's why I liked it. I played it and it's big and scary and wet and it's an ocean,
you know, like a big scary wet ocean. And the day-night cycle causes it. Because it's
you know, an alien planet. There's no artificial light anywhere. As soon as the sun sets,
underwater is like almost completely pitch black. And if your torch or your flashlight, I
should say, that can run out of battery and you have to like collect materials to craft
batteries. So you could be out in the middle of the ocean. The sun could set. Your torch would
be out of juice. And then you'd be right at the deep down and scary. There's big scary monsters
making noises. And it could be anywhere 360 around you because it's, you know, water. It's great.
The idea of a giant like beast looming up out of you, at you out of the depths of the sea is like
one of the scariest things I can even imagine. Oh, dude. There was this one bit
where I, you can only go so far down with your regular like mask, what do you call it? O2?
The thing you breathe, canister, you need like to upgrade it so you can dive deeper and stuff.
So I can go down a certain way. And then I got that upgrade and then I found a cave. And I was
like, oh, let's go down into this cave now that I can. I went really far down and then it opened up
into this gargantuan like underground cavern with very strange, completely new foliage and
flora and fauna and like different fish I'd never seen before. And it was all just this
out of reach. And then there was big scary screaming noises. I was like, ah, no.
Like it was very, very, very dark because the sun can reach down there. So I was like,
I had to throw a flare down and it just kept going down. I was like, no, no, no, no, no.
If this is the next part of the game, I don't want to play anymore. I don't want to go down here.
Yeah. Yeah. Wait, you have a VR?
It's not VR. Maybe it is VR, but I don't have one. You can just play it with a controller.
Oh, I thought Subnautica was a freaking VR game. There's a non-VR version?
I don't know. It definitely is in VR. You can play it that way, which would make it so much
scary. Oh, yeah. Yeah. You have a VR, so you could play that version if it exists. I haven't
seen it. But I won't. But I fucking won't do it. I mean, it's very satisfying overcoming these fears
because when you're first plunked into the ocean, you don't know anything. So anything could be
like, you're thinking, okay, sharks, are they going to come? How am I going to respond to that?
Oh god, I don't know how to play. I don't know how to move. Left, right, up, down. Oh my god,
what the fuck is that? And then you're constantly running out of food and water. You have to find
materials to cook things so that you can live, so that you can disinfect seawater, so you can drink
it. So there's a time thing. You can't just relax. You have to keep going out into the ocean to get
things. It forces you to face the scariness of the unknown until you're comfortable in a certain
area and then you branch out a bit and then you get more materials. You find secret materials,
special materials. You get gold and you can make super computer chips and you can craft vehicles
that can go even further. You make beacons and you can build underwater bases.
Can you build a chainsaw wand, though? I didn't think so.
Noida 1, Subnautica 0.
I don't know about a chainsaw, but you can definitely get a drill at some point to drill
through big veins of iron or it was not iron. I think it's not iron. That's pretty good.
Yeah. Very nice. Impressive.
So are you saying, so is it terrifying or no?
It is terrifying, definitely at first.
I feel like it's not supposed to be like a scary game and yet I feel like just the feeling of being
in that in the sea with the possibility of monsters is just, it's too scary even though it's not
trying to be. I think it is trying to be pretty scary. Because it's the unknown and you can't
see you very far because it's murky and there's these big huge kelp. I don't know. They're not
called kelp because this is an alien planet. Everything has a funny name. There's these
huge forests of kelp and you can swim through them, but obviously they block your vision and then
you hear a weird snarl from some predator and it could be attacking you, but it also could very
easily be attacking some other fish. So you don't know whether a prompt from an audio cue is
something that you should be wary of or something that you could get used to just happening because
some creatures, they just make noises. So you have to get used to all of these things. It is
supposed to be like venture into the unknown and figure it out because you crash landed and
nobody is there to help. You have to get your scanning thing and you craft a scanning thing and
then you can scan items like creatures, but you have to hold the scanner on them. So if I needed
to scan a predator to see what its weaknesses are or whatever, I would have to get in range of one
to scan it for long enough and hold the scan beam on it while it chases me and I was like, no, no,
no thank you. But yeah, you can build up your knowledge database of all the things you've
scanned and things you understand. It's such a satisfying progression of that kind of survival
game. I think you really would enjoy it. Yeah, I could see there's aspects of it that I do think
seem pretty cool. And I think I watched Joseph Anderson review of it. Do you know him? I think
I saw that as well. Yes, I know him. He's the project methematosus lol. He pretty much is,
who actually makes videos, Lamal. But yeah, it seemed cool and I considered playing it for a
little while, but I never got around to it. I think maybe the reason is because my current set
up in my room is like, it's not quite big enough to make VR work. I can use the headset. I can just
barely sort of make it work, but it's a little smaller than is optimal. And I have a problem
with, I set up the sensors and they work and they have enough space, but I can move in ways where
the table will clip between me and the sensor and it'll stop sensing me because the line of
sight is interrupted and stuff. It's just a little bit inconvenient. It doesn't quite work as well as
it should, which is a bummer. I think I watched a video at the Xammon Life of Gaming, talked about
Subnautica in a best of 2018. I think that's why I was so interested in it because he really
sold me on how it works. Xammon Life of Gaming was that channel that Jesse liked or he knew the guy
who made it, right? Jesse knew the guy, yeah, and friends, I assume, they're like forum friends.
I met up before, but yeah. Xammon Life of Gaming was that guy. He was very nerdy looking and
sounding, but he seemed to really like guns and most of his videos were about FPSers.
Yeah, he's a good boy. He would always take special mention of how the guns work in the
game and whether they're accurate and so on, which I thought was pretty funny.
He's got really good content. I have subscribed and it's been good.
I liked his old stuff. Does he still make videos?
Yeah, I have so often. I haven't checked his channel in a long time, but I would.
He went through Marathon, which is a franchise I hadn't heard about.
Yeah, he makes videos about things and I'm like, I never have heard of many of these things,
but I like that he's so into them and he cares about these types of games so much that he can
really praise something done right in a certain way for shooter games and stuff.
His last video was five months ago.
So he makes them occasionally. Oh yeah, I haven't seen any of these.
These are all new since the last time I checked. Awesome.
This is my bread and butter. It's just a YouTube video where a guy talks about a video game.
I have endless appetite for this. I cannot stop watching this genre.
It's just there's an infinite amount of it and I can just put it on
and I can pay attention or not pay attention and that's what I do all day every day.
It's fucked up, honestly.
Truth? I've talked about this. We've talked about this.
Put on a video to ignore, but then sometimes I get distracted by it and I do pay attention
and it does distract me from what I should be doing, even though I didn't want it to.
Did you see the red letter media best of the worst supercut of really memorable moments from
almost a hundred episodes? The hundredth episode is coming out soon, apparently,
of best of the worst. Oh no, I didn't see this. This montage, I guess it came out yesterday?
Yeah. No, I haven't seen it. It was just so... I don't know.
I had seen all of those videos multiple times and to see so many of those moments,
I'm like, oh, that was a great episode. Oh, that was a great episode. Oh,
that was in a great episode. All of these were in so many great episodes of best of the worst.
How many fucking hours of content have I watched of that?
There's a hundred episodes of best of the worst. Soon to be 100 episodes, yes.
That's insane. It doesn't seem like there's a hundred. I would have guessed there were maybe
like 20 or 30. Oh no, wow. Way more than 20. What? What? I just... I don't... I can't believe it.
Also, I can't believe this best of the best of the worst. It's only two minutes long, like...
It's a very short... Only two minutes. They definitely would have cut out the things.
They can't have like... I just feel like there's more than two minutes worth of memorable highlights
from that. It's not like highlights from the show. It's like highlights of movies they've
watched on best of the worst, like little clips, like exploding environments, like a
environment explodes, like that part. And then there's things like that. Remlazar is on there
for like a frame. So it's like... One frame. Yeah, just little bits of all of these things. Like,
how do I remember this? Oh my god, I do. I can get of them. The guy blows up at the end.
I don't even... I don't remember some of these. Like, I don't remember the movies themselves.
This one, it's like really at the beginning, it's like a guy with a beard and a mohawk
getting his head chopped off. I don't remember that at all. I have no clue what movie that was from.
I guess I like don't remember the movies as well as I remember the discussions, because I mean,
a lot of the time I'm not even looking at the screen, right? I'm not like watching it. I'm
listening to it passively. Wait a minute, it says... I guess I forget the Raiders of Atlantis. I forget
that one, yeah. Is that the one with... The mohawk guy's head chopped off? Yeah, Raiders of
Atlantis. No recollection of that whatsoever. Red Letter Media. What a franchise. What an
unlikely story. A bunch of fucking weirdos from Milwaukee. They said they'd never amount to
anything, but they made a couple of shitty movies and then they made a YouTube channel and now look
at them. Have you seen any of their movies, because I actually have not seen Space Copper?
I haven't, no. I've heard they're bad, so I'm like, I'm not that interested. It's a movie,
it's different. What's the one about a gorilla? They had an old movie they made that's something
about a gorilla. I don't know. They made a lot of old movies, like little fun film,
student projects stuff. Space Cop. Hold on. No, Revenge...
Low budget features produced by and starring Stoklasa and the Red Letter Media affiliates
have been largely horror and comedy, such as Feeding Frenzy, The Recovered,
Orange's, Revenge of the Eggplant, and Space Cop. I swear to God, they have one about a gorilla
and there was a... if you like a patron or something, you could get a behind-the-scenes
documentary. Am I having a stroke? I was 100% sure of this, but maybe I'm confused. I don't know.
And I think I wanted to watch it, but it cost money and I said, no. Oh well.
Yeah, I haven't seen Space Cop or any of that. It looks like... I'm sure it's fine.
I'm sure it's fine. I think these guys are funny, but I don't necessarily trust
that they have immaculate filmmaking sense. I've seen a bunch of their old sketch comedies on the
channel. You left? I left to pee. Oh, lol. I didn't hear what you said. Have you ever gone back and
watched their oldest videos in chronological order? No, not all of them. I think I've watched the
making of some of their old films, which were interesting. If you... If you go back and...
I mean, I'll look right now. If you go to their channel and just sort their videos oldest to
newest, you get their fucking fruit pal puppet shorts. Oh, Gorilla Interrupted. Gorilla Interrupted
is the monkey movie. And there's a trailer for it posted nine years ago.
I remember Dale Jackson reporting. I see. I've seen that one.
Like their movie reviews don't even start until... Well, I guess it's the Plinkett reviews. Yeah.
Or like the oldest stuff, the oldest like review content that they have on here. You know? But
yeah, it's all these fucking puppet shorts with fruits. What was up with the fruit? I've never
actually looked at these. They just are like... It's like a satirical sitcom about a sassy black
apple married to a cowardly bitch of an orange man. I think I've seen one of these, the bitch orange,
I remember. Oh, dear. Oh, I'm still... I can't look for a job, sweetheart. I need to spend that
time finishing my ice sculpture. Yeah, that... Wait a minute. All right. I just think it's pretty
funny. So the star was Phantom Menace Plinkett review. Seems to have come out after a Star Trek
review. I never saw that. Is it a Plinkett review? Well, I'm going to click on it. I don't know. I
think these are... I think a lot of these are reposts because like the channel has existed
for 16 years and the oldest videos are only nine years old. So I don't know if these are
necessarily chronological. Yeah. Like I know Mr. Plinkett, I think he existed before the Plinkett
reviews. Yeah, 2012. No, it definitely came out before 2012. Nine years ago. This thing about
the Olsen twins movie, this little skit of him like getting a phone call from the Olsen twins,
Plinkett's in that. And even back then, Rich was playing him in the live action bits.
Yeah, I think there was older stuff on here that has been removed and I don't know what it could
have been. I wonder. Maybe some like internet historians. No, maybe it's a cataloged somewhere.
The shameful history. Oh, yeah. Orange's revenge of the eggplant. So many of their old
projects were about like puppets with fruit. Oh, wait, wait. Stoklasa created his first
video review for Star Trek Generations after watching the film in 2008. Stoklasa believed
his own voice sounded too boring for the review. I remember seeing this in an interview actually.
Are you reading this on Wikipedia? Adopted the persona of Harry S. Plinkett, yeah, Wikipedia.
Thought his voice was too boring. Man. Imagine if every fucking YouTube video essayist.
Because that's basically what it, imagine if every one of them was like, my voice is boring.
I'm gonna like adopt a wacky character. Yeah, it was great. It could be great. It could be great,
but it could be, it could probably get pretty annoying too. Well, sure. But like, I think
it was his like creativity to even think that, oh, I don't want to just be a guy,
a shleby guy talking about a movie because that's a stupid crazy thing to do. That's the worst thing
you can be. So I'll just like play into like the crazy old, shleby, insane nerd thing and be like,
oh, oh, this movie sucks. So I like to fuck my cat, you know, like that's, it was the stereotype
that's playing into. That's the natural progression of ideas. Yeah. Yeah. It's the only, it's the only
way. Everyone knows. It's the only way. Everyone knows red letter media is good. I don't know why
even bothered saying anything. Sure. I just went one time on a lark. I was like,
let me look at their oldest shit. And I was like, what is all this fruit doing here?
Some of us funny though, the orange Apple bits are like funny enough, I suppose. Holy shit.
Space cop trailer nine years ago. When did they make space? What?
I'm looking at nine years. I mean, maybe they were making it nine, but it probably didn't come out for
a while after that because like, I'm sure they made the trailer like well before the movie was done.
What is the 2012 same as all the other things early on in the channel? So it could be a reupload
in fact, you know, I think I was six years ago. I'm so raisey for space cop. That's an old
I think I was thinking of guerrilla interrupted, but I think it's space cop that has like the
making of documentary that you can like buy, I think somehow on their fucking, I don't know,
gum road or some shit on a gum road, please, please and thank you.
Um, yeah, red letter media. Good channel. What more can I say?
God, this is so weird. I'm scrolling. I'm like, haha. Yeah, I remember that. That wasn't that long ago.
Eight years ago, eight years ago, seven years ago. Yeah. Yeah. Best of the worst episode one,
eight years ago, almost 10 years old. No, not almost, but eight years is a long time.
It's so January 2013. It's so unsettling. I mean, you can see in the old old videos,
like they look so much younger, but like even even just over the course of best of the worst,
they look a lot different. Like Mike's hair is going like has recently started to go gray at a
rapidly accelerating rate. Mike looks Mike looks the same as ever, but better. He just like learned
to comb his hair and trim his beard. And now he looks perfect. And he used to look like a fucking
chipmunk. But other than that, he hasn't changed. What did I say? Did I say Mike? Yeah, I meant Jay.
You said you said yeah, yeah. Josh has just gotten Balder. Mike has just gotten fatter and grayer.
Rich, I guess, looks rich, looks pretty much the same. Like when he was when he was like young,
young, like in his twenties, he looked he looked different. But at some point,
he just got kind of like fat and stupid looking. And he has just kind of stayed the same.
Classic, good old reliable, not to be cruel or anything, not to be mean.
Josh looks the same because he has no hair to change. So he's just like a smooth egg
unaffected by the passage of time. Wait, no, I meant Jack. I meant Jack. I'm so. And also
Jack did used to have hair like really early on. He yeah, he had but he looks really funny with
the hair because he's like a ginger. And he but he's like bald, but his hair is like fluffy
on the side. So he looks like a clown.
He had clown hair. I can totally understand why he would why he would trim it. He looks much.
You know, he kind of the old clown look, it has a certain appeal. If he was if he was some sort of
like if he was playing some kind of character, like some kind of wacky scientist for children
or something, I think that would be a perfect look. But if he's not going for that, then probably
shaving it is the right thing to do. Lamal, you know, it's a little bit of bold. Yeah, in general,
I think so. Yeah. God, you know, who looks Josh without his beard? That's a mistake.
He should. Yeah, it's good. He should keep the beard. It's it's much better.
I did wonder about like whether it's like a like more of an objective thing or like a
perceptual thing. If you see someone with a beard more than you see them without a beard,
then obviously it's going to be different when they are without the beard. But can you get used
to it? And is it better? Like, is there a clear judgment able to be made with regards to beer
and hair and stuff? I mean, everyone might have their own opinion. In my opinion, it's not it's
not merely that like I was used to him with the beard, seeing him without it makes me go makes
me feel weird. It's that like beardless, you can just see his face and his his jawline is just is
so like pudgy. And and he's got like a very pronounced shadow anyway, even when he's
shaved the beard. So like just have the fucking beard. And it looks like it looks like deliberate.
I don't know. The with the beard he looks. I don't know. I guess it makes you look
like I guess a little more badass, I guess a little more hardcore in a way, whereas like
beardless his jawline and his chubby cheeks just make him look like a soft
a soft fucking. What's the word? Potato man, puke. Oh, potato man. Did you say potato man?
Yes, I think something like that. The roundness. Yeah, something like that. Yeah,
you get what I'm saying. You got you got to you got to play to your strengths. You got to you
got to do you got to do an assessment, a frank assessment of like, all right, what do I look
like? What are my problem areas? How can I how can I how can I mitigate? How can I mitigate these?
In Josh's case, a beard is is necessary in Jack's case, shave in the head. That's what you got to do.
In Jay's case, it's to, I don't know, change everything, grow the beard a little bit, but
sort of not the way all Jay needed to do was just have his beard be normal. Like the reason
he looked bizarre before was because he did his beard like weird, like he would have like,
he would have like weird like sort of semi mutton chops, or he would have like just like
just the the mustache and it was like, what are you doing? And his hair would be all messy,
but now he's got the nice like comb to the side. He's just got like the nice normal beard on his
like pretty normal face and it just looks good. And he's improved his dress sense to I think he
wears like he wears like, I don't know, like leather jackets now and it just works. It just
works for him. He's still a manlet, but he looks like a manlet who knows what he's doing.
Good for him. Good for him. I'm looking I'm looking through Jay footage.
Well, so this is the the the boy judging corner of the procrastinators
podcast. The boy judge, maybe the past judgment on boys.
Then I don't know about this boy right here.
Which yeah, wait, which you got a particular one? No, no, I was just saying that like this
the boy in general just in general. Yeah, this this boy is this boy is not is not living up to
his boy potential. Is there a way to boy potential and potential like boy potential? No, that doesn't
really work. No, I'm sorry. You fucked up. Fuck. I didn't fuck up. I was experimenting and it
blew up in my face. But you know what? At least I tried. No, no, you shouldn't have.
You shouldn't have done that. No, he's right. He's right. I should have. If you hadn't tried,
you wouldn't have failed. So but let this be a lesson to you.
Yeah, red letter media, movies, boys. It's all it's all good. It's all good. Have we forgotten?
Have we forgotten any boys that need judgment? There Oh, there's that. Well, there's that one
guy who wears like the flannel shirts and he has the mustache and he's bald. And he's like
Tim Tim. He's he's new regular, I think he was there before. But I think lately he's been
around a little bit more often. Yeah. Yeah. He's fine. I don't know, whatever. He looks like how
he looks. I mean, obviously, like a bold, bolding is like difficult to make look good. So it's,
it's like, you know, whatever. His mustache thing is a bit was distinctive, at least. I don't know
where I hate it. It's distinctive at least. And I don't have any strong opinion about it. And I
like him being like a really weak drunk, like he can't take his liquor and he goes like really
slurry really quickly and everyone laughs at him. That's really funny. I guess, was he just
doing that that one time as like a bit? No, I think he really can't hold his liquor very well.
Maybe. I think they all drink about the same amount and he starts going, well, a lot quicker.
I mean, they all drink about the same amount, except, I mean, Mike, Mike seemed to get like
kind of hammered sometimes. Like Mike seemed to be drinking like the heart stuff and like
actually confused. Mike is a real alcoholic. I don't, I think. No, literally, I guess. I
shouldn't say real, like I know anything. I think, I don't, I mean, I don't know. They make fun of him.
They poke fun at his drinking a lot. They make fun of him for getting drunk, which,
which he definitely does. I feel like, and maybe I'm jumping into conclusions here,
I feel like Rich might be like an actual alcoholic. And that's why like a lot of the time,
like the other guys will have a beer, but he will have like something else. I feel like at some
point they were like, Rich, you are actually an, he's like, you know what, I'm actually an alcoholic
and I probably just shouldn't drink. That's, I don't know that for sure. I just, I've noticed,
I've noticed that I never see him with it with a drink. And I think like, there's got to be a
reason for that. They do like mention it at some point. Yeah. Why Rich is having energy drinks or
like water instead of beer. I think. Yeah. And it's because he doesn't want to have alcohol,
which is like, so there must be a, there must be an issue there, which like, if so,
I thought it was a medical thing, but maybe it's just like basic alcohol. I guess it could be like
a medicine interaction. You know what? It could totally be that too. I didn't even think about
that. I just jumped to conclusions. That's a real boy judged right there by Benson.
That guy's probably alcoholic. I mean, it's one explanation, but I guess it's not the only one.
So yeah, shows what I know. Thank you. Thank you for broadening my, my, my mind. Thank you for
expanding me into new ter, unexplored territories of the human condition. Speaking of medicine,
so I'm on the, I'm on the vaccine waiting list now. I think I should, I think I need to go and
redo my application to let them know that I'm a former smoker, because apparently
that is considered a co-morbidity and can get you moved up to the priority list, lol.
Very funny. Well, it is a long thing. So. It is a long thing. I gotta admit, I'm embarrassed to
admit this. This is going to be very cringe, but I am scared to get it.
Where do they stab it? Do they stab it in your shoulder? Cause that's fine. There's plenty of
flesh there. My, my roommate got it in the, yeah, in like the upper arm. Yeah, that's easy.
Cause it's, no, it's, I mean, I don't, I don't even see it. No, no, no, no, that's not what I mean.
I mean, I don't like the shot. I am scared of, of needles and such and like, that's bad, but
it's okay. I can take that. No, I'm, I'm scared of like, I'm scared that it's going to do something.
Oh, it will. It'll, it'll probably make you sick for a bit. That's cause it's like a small,
it's a baby coronavirus in there. Essentially. Something like that. I mean, I've heard people
say that like, I don't know, apparently it's very rare and like there's only, only one brand has
done this and it's not even the kind you can get in a marriage. There was one brand in other
countries that gave some people blood clots and like, I guess. That was bullshit. That was
bullshit. It was like, well, I guess nobody knows for certain, but the tests were done.
The amount of people who got blood clots after getting the vaccine is so low that it could
easily have just been normal instances of having blood clots. Like people were getting very scared
about it. I think it was in Europe, right? It's the AstraZeneca, a vaccine. That's right. That's
the one. It was sort of fear mongered like that because in Europe, a lot of people,
a lot of people in Europe don't trust vaccines for some reason, or at least in France, I've heard.
So it's sort of a political thing to like, not seem like you're trying to push vaccines too
hard because the public won't like that. They won't vote for you or some bullshit. So there's
lots of, oh, we got to ask as many questions as possible. Is this causing blood clots? Like,
if somebody brings that up, a politician in one of these countries can't just dismiss it,
it's kind of like, oh, they have to address these concerns because even though the concerns are
probably bogus, they would look bad if they don't follow it up. And so in the UK, nobody cared
that scientists said, no, there's probably another thing. And we got the vaccine. We kept
getting the vaccine for our people. Then everyone in Europe was like, oh, we're all busy with
bureaucracy and paperwork because we're trying to discern whether this blood clots are actually
like a real threat. And it turns out, really, no, it's so little evidence to suggest that that's
true. And then so many people just waited too long to get their vaccine, lol.
It's not, it's not, it's not rational. It's, it's genuinely just that like, I know that there are
other people that are like, scared and don't want the vaccine. And even though like, it's not,
those aren't even like people who I agree with. But I know that they exist. And my animal instinct
is like, if they're afraid, I should be afraid. You know what I mean? Understandable, yes.
I'm not so, I haven't been, because like, I've been told, they'll call you when you're ready.
So everyone's somewhere on the list. It's not like you have to sign up to get one. They'll just
I had to, I had to sign up. I had to sign up somewhere.
So like, they say they'll call me when it's my turn. And I haven't really thought about it.
And I never really like considered anything potentially going wrong.
I just be like, yeah, now I've got the thing. Eventually I'll have the thing.
It's just, you know, I've heard, I've heard, even though I've heard that like, oh, it makes your
arm hurt. It's like, oh, it makes you feel like it gives you like a mild head cold or something.
And I'm like, even though those don't seem like a big deal, it's still like
scary because it's like, wait, I'm putting something in my body that's
that's fucking with me even a little bit like Jesus. And it's stupid because like,
obviously coronavirus would fuck with me more. But still, but still it's like to
voluntarily like fuck with my body is like, yeah.
But I'm, but I'm kind of like, I think I'm kind of just like scared of like doctors and medicine
in general. This is a thing that I have been like in the last few years. And I never used
to be like this. I think I've become, I've become paranoid, terrified.
It is. It is. I told you it was going to be cringe and then here it is that I'm right again.
Far right. Yeah. Scary. It's scary. I'm so scared. I'm so fucking scared. I'm so fucking scared.
You're going to go to the doctors, the hospital, whatever they're going to say. All right, Ben,
Saint, sit down here. We're going to, we're going to, we're going to throw this needle at you.
You're going to take it. You're going to, we're going to, we're going to, we're going to
tie you to this wheel and spin it. And then we're going to throw syringes at you like a dartboard.
And, and you know, one in five of these syringes has syphilis on them. So you better watch out.
No. Not, not syphilis. I'm so scared to even exist in a human body.
You know what really? Such a terrifying state of affairs. Yeah.
What really does scare me is like medical trash cans, like the bins that they throw,
used needles, things that have been in other people, things that are like not, not disinfected.
They just throw them in like a medical waste bin. I've seen those bins sometimes like just
open top and I'm like, God, if I just put my hand in there, I could have every disease on earth
and I would die instantly. I don't, I don't like the idea that I could potentially fall into that.
And then, oh, the needle with the aids on it got onto my face. And now I have face aids.
That sucks. I really, really unnerve me when I see like a medical waste disposal thing.
Sure. Sure. I mean, true. But I mean, there's so many things that could kill you in so many
different ways. They're all over the place. I mean, you could just walk out your window
and you fall. If you're on the second floor of your house, you have enough fucking potential
energy to kill yourself instantly. You just walk out the window and that's it. You did it.
Oh, there's an electrical socket. Oh, there's enough voltage there. There's enough voltage
there that like, you know, if you fucking stuck two tongs in there, the amps going through your
body would fucking kill you. There's like, there's a potential drop there that's lethal.
Yeah, you just take the toaster and the bus. Dude, have you ever thought about like how in like
thrillers or whatever, there's like the torture scene or like there's a bad guy and he's got a
weapon and he's in your house like, oh, shit, what am I going to do? He's got a weapon in my house.
Nobody needs a weapon. You just like, you just get like, you go to the house like the cupboard
under the sink, you get like, some sort of like, you know, cleaning thing, and then you force it
down someone's throat, you get bleach and you put them like household objects are so dangerous.
Well, I mean, yeah, but you would have to I mean, to do that, you would have to,
he would have to like wrestle me first, he would have to like dis, what's the word, he would have
to like, disable me some or hold me down in a way to kill me with that. Yeah, I mean,
there's kitchen knives and stuff as well. It's just sort of the idea that like a weapon,
like somebody brings a gun, I mean, a gun is long distances, very loud and dangerous and obviously,
but like so many things in your house could kill you right now. So easily if you just fell into
like a strange mindset where you're like, what if I just did this and you idiot die?
Sure. I mean,
that there's a there's a word for that, like the idea that you can see that a train is coming and
you're thinking, hmm, you know, if I did walk off, I would die right then. God, I sure hope I don't
do that. I better sit down, I better clinch my my legs together so that nothing moves.
I think about that all the time. And I think about being hit by a train. I think about having
my head crushed. I think about having my head crushed every day and what it would feel like.
And it's a horrifying thought that I keep having and can't stop myself from having and sometimes
I'm just sitting or I'm lying down alone and I think about it and it's so unpleasant to even
cross my mind the possibility that I like bad and sometimes I like involuntarily like scream a
little bit because I thought about it too hard. This is true. This is true about me. No, I understand.
I feel I feel similar. It's like when you something has like fucked with me that I've seen,
maybe just in a video even. I'm thinking about it now and and and then it like beyond that point,
it's like, it pops into my head randomly and I'm like, oh shit, I should not think of that. And
now I'm thinking of not thinking about it, which causes me to think about it.
I'm having like an anxiety attack. I'm thinking about what it would feel like to have my head
crushed and it's so bad. I hate that I exist in a universe where not only can this happen,
it has happened. It has happened to other people before. How fucked is that?
I wonder what like therapeutic methods there are because I've because
like to like guarantee getting over something like that because I've heard, you know,
you've all heard of like, oh, if you expose yourself to the things you don't like,
you'll realize it's so bad. But it's like getting your head crushed is a little different. How do
you expose yourself? Do you watch like horror movies? Would that make it worse or better? I don't know.
I don't. It would probably just make me think about it more. Yeah. I don't know.
I don't know. What can be done? I don't know if there's any solution to this problem.
Dude, what if COVID cures your ability to get your head crushed?
I read, okay, I read that apparently a large number of people who had COVID develop
like neurological or mental issues afterwards. Wait, large amount? How many?
I think it was something like, oh, God, I'd have to find the article, but I think it was like 40%.
Which, yeah, they develop like- That seems impossible. How could a vaccine do that?
And it does 40% of that. No, no, no, not the vaccine. Not the vaccine that having COVID,
having full-blown COVID, and you develop these. And by neurological or mental,
includes stuff like depression or chronic anxiety or something, right?
Not like brain damage, but some. I mean, some people's brains are damaged by COVID,
but it's other things too. Depression is- But it's like a large percentage more than
other things. More of a percentage, significantly more people who were treated for COVID
would go on to develop issues like that than people who were treated for, say, the flu
or something by a percentage. And this is very bizarre. This is a very bizarre piece of information,
but I had to wonder what if the vaccine does the same thing? What if the vaccine does it too?
What if the vaccine will give me depression or anxiety or something?
That sounds crazy, I know. It seems like if it's something that happens with COVID,
it could happen with the vaccine, because the vaccine would be like a small dose of
the disease to get your body immune system able to recognize it so that you can fight it in the
real world. So it might make you depressed for a bit. I don't think anything would be long-lasting,
from a vaccine. It doesn't seem like it has the power to do anything.
Okay, I don't know. I might embarrass myself by not knowing what I'm talking about, but I don't
think that the vaccine is just a small dose of the virus, because the virus itself does not
create immunity to itself, because you could get COVID and then recontract it and get it again.
It's something else. It's some piece of the genetic material that causes you to create a
certain spike protein. I don't even know what that means. I don't know either, because I haven't
read up on it, but I just understand vaccines to be the purpose of them is to get your body's
immune system. Give it the data. It's like a data download. Here's the cheat codes for when this
enemy you're supposed to roll. This Dark Souls boss enters the body. You roll here. This is the
eye frames, and it's like, okay, thanks. It's basically a little tutorial for your body's
immune system. That's what I think of it as. Now that I've thinking about it like that, it's kind
of cute. It's your body's immune system. It's a little Dark Souls guy, and he's rolling around.
He's like, oh, I died. All right, let me try again. That's you feeling a little bad after
taking the vaccine, but then he gets it, and then the real thing comes, and he can roll.
He can do all the rolls. He can do a soul level one, fists only, attack, and win.
I know that some people who got COVID got what was called long COVID, which was when
you don't actually have COVID anymore, but your immune system over responds to the virus,
and it continues to do its thing even after the virus is gone, and it gives you symptoms
that last for months or a year, where your immune system is just making you sick continually,
which is fucking cringe. I heard some people speculating that could the vaccine,
since it's just about your immune response, could the vaccine trigger a similar thing?
To the best of my knowledge, it seems like the answer is no. I haven't seen any reports of
long COVID being brought on by the vaccine, which is good.
I mean, I don't know. Nevertheless, it's scary because I don't understand.
Sure, sure. I think the important thing to understand is that all of those
potentials are very, very minor. Otherwise, it would be a very big story.
In the grand scheme of things, COVID itself is a much more...
Vaccine, yeah. You want to take the vaccine over getting COVID, so it doesn't really matter
what the potential bad things are. You'll probably take the vaccine on the off chance
that it will save you from COVID, and the side effects of the vaccine are largely lesser and
rarer than the side effects from COVID, which can lead to death, and it's worse.
COVID is the more dangerous danger, it seems. I mean, not that I would even expect to die if
I got COVID. No, yeah, that's even the thing. I guess neither of us know exactly how these
side effects would manifest in a person like us. We don't know whether we have the exact wrong
set of characteristics that would lead to the most rare, terrible of circumstances from the
vaccine, but I don't know. Whatever. Whatever, yeah. I guess I must have been a little,
little kid when I got my other vaccinations, and I wonder if like, did I get mildly sick
from those vaccinations, too? And I just don't remember. Did they cause my autism? Is that where
it came from? Makes you think, makes you wonder, hmm, two things happened. Yeah, I was just a
perfectly normal kid. One must have caused me. Socializing. I walked into the playground,
and I did the finger bang like, I was talking to everyone. I was the king of the castle, got my
flu jab, and I became a social introvert. I was star quarterback. I was star quarterback
before I got vaccinated. Yeah, I took that. I took that and I became a social intro, and
I lost all of my memory of my Chad's days, and everyone also lost their memories because they
also took the vaccine. Nobody remembers when I was a Chad. That was the big, that's big pharma
doing that. Big pharma wants everyone to forget that they can be Chad's. They want them to be
cringe, cringe, autistic consumers. I used to be a Chad, but now I'm a queen. I guess it's better
lol. It's, it's more, I don't know. I'm sure, I'm sure George Soros is happy about that for some reason.
The, I don't know. I don't know, man. I just, everyone I know is getting it. Like, one of my
roommates is, is vaxxed. I think, like, I know a couple of people who are getting vaxxed. They're
all, they're all, they're probably, they're all gonna be fine. It's all gonna be fine. The worst
thing, the worst thing about people getting vaxxed is that we're gonna run out of the ability to
sell, I have COVID shirts. No, our markets. Have we even sold one of those? I am really curious.
We sold a couple. No, we did. We did a few people.
Oh my God. Incredible.
I know. Imagine someone out there, maybe you listener, own that shirt. It's gonna, it's only
gonna, it's gonna age like fine white. It's gonna get funnier and funnier as the years go by.
It's an investment in the future. Honestly, now is the time. If you haven't done it already,
click the link in the, the T-Spring link in the description. Get your own I Have COVID shirt
before it's too late, before your vaxx and you can never again claim to have COVID. You should go
out right now and get COVID just so you can wear that shirt because you'll, this is a chance that
will, that will pass you by and never come back. This is, this is a moment in time and you don't
want to miss it. That's, that's all I'm saying. That's all I'm saying. Oh, fucking boy. Um,
well fuck. Yeah. You want to go to voicemails? I, well, I got one really for voicemail. Oh,
sure. Go on. No, it's not too early, but I got one little thing to say. Um, so, all right, you
might not have anything to say about this, but I was watching Buffy, um, season, season five.
Classic Gib. Yeah. Classic Gib, watching Buffy, enjoying it, but I had noticed something. Um,
in Buffy, it's like, not a kid's show. It's sort of teenage young adults. So there's blood,
there's gore, not extreme gore, but like, you know, 90s gore. Um, the, you know, vampire's blood,
there's quite a few sex scenes. There's a known like explicit nudity, but there is like suggestive,
like, you know, back of, you know, you know, back nudity and stuff like that. So it's like,
gotcha, gotcha, gotcha, gotcha. There's been, there's been love interest stuff in the show.
And there is a new couple that have is two, two women, two ladies. No fucking way. And they are
together. They are, they are canonically going out with each other. They're girlfriends. What the
fuck? And it's like, ah, cool. You know, television show in the 90s, they had a lesbian couple that
wasn't like a joke and it's cool and it's cute and it's wonderful. And I love it and it's great,
but my mind, my mind is blown. But here's the, my head has been crushed by this information.
But the thing that fucking pisses me off so much is that they will not let these lesbians kiss
on camera or at all. They just really, they will not let them kiss. There is so, it was this one
particular episode where this couple, there was a thing with one of the parents and they were like,
I don't like you doing stuff. Your new friends are a bad influence, you know, stuff like that.
And she's like, the episode was about her. And then her friends, you know, the main cast were
like supportive of her as against her family who are shitty. And it was like, this is when she came
out as a lesbian, you mean? It was more that she came out as like a witch because, you know, allegory.
Oh, sure. But that, yeah, they didn't really talk to the parents about the gayness, but
lesbian is, it's known by everyone else. And there have been like a few like funny jokes
about like people's reactions to like, oh, oh, you've, oh, like girlfriend, oh, like it's,
it's surprising. But nobody like makes fun of it. So that's nice. It's a good show in that regard.
But they just won't let them kiss. They won't let them kiss. Despite the fact, despite the fact
that in this episode, it was the perfect romantic moment. They were dancing together. It was a
slow dance. And it was like, I'm so happy and you're stood up for me and you, my girlfriend are so
wonderful. And they'd hug. They hug on the dance floor. They hug on the dance floor. And it's
so. They hug zone each other. It's so actually cringe inducingly like unsatisfying. Everything
was leading up to a kiss. We hadn't seen a kiss up to that point. And other characters kiss
constantly. Buffy. I was going to ask, do other characters kiss? Yeah. Buffy kisses her boyfriend
so much. She has so much kissing. Nice. And it's like, oh, okay, I see what it this is.
Now, I'm pretty sure, I'm pretty sure it's the show runner, not the show, like creators, but like the
like TV, like saying, no, no, you can't have them kiss. Sorry, you just can't do that.
Like, I'm pretty sure the show runners would have wanted them to be able to. But no, TV says no.
So that's fucking a lot. I mean, I mean, if if they're if they're just dating, like if they're
just straight up fucking dating each other, like I don't why, why not? What's the problem? It was
so confusing. It's because they they've even had like scenes in that. Unless they're trying to keep
if they're trying to keep plausible deniability, I would at least get it. But if they're not doing
that, then why would it be an issue? It's so strange. Like there's innuendo, you know, because
it's like ha ha witches. Like what are the witchy things they're doing together? It's like, ah,
that sex like implied sex, but they haven't confirmed sex. But they did. Okay. In that very
episode I'm talking about, they had a scene where they were snuggling together in bed together,
talking about stuff. Yeah, like really cute and romantic and like, you know,
they're overtly going out. Everyone knows they just lips on lips. I don't know why. Imagine
you're you're you're a Christian soccer mom, and you're flipping through channels on daytime TV,
looking for something that you don't want your kids to see. And you flip, which are you going
to be more upset by? You see the two girls kiss or you see the two girls snuggling in bed together?
I feel like they're equivalent at the very least. I don't know. It's bizarre. It was so it was so
like bizarre is the right word because I felt so like it was one of those like moments that I
don't doesn't happen often with me. But I was it was like, oh, come on, like throw popcorn at the
screen. We like, what the fuck? They couldn't do it. I just had a thought. I just had a thought.
But I don't think it's true. My thought was what if the actresses just didn't want to do it. But
like, no, that's no horseshit actors are fuck actors are perfect actors will kiss whoever you
fucking tell them to kiss. These are pros. There's no way there's no way I doubt it. No, I doubt that.
I guess I could look into it. But they're quite young. They're not I would be shot. I would be
shocked if that was the reason like young hip 90s kid actors doing like, which is which is more
likely which is more likely to not to be against it, though the actresses or the fucking or the
cigar chomping execs at the yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Easy, easy choice. The worst thing ever cringe.
Let them kiss. Let lesbians live.
Let them live. Maybe they I don't know maybe they maybe they will later. I don't know your
significant other than why live exactly. Maybe I mean maybe as they stay on the show for a while
and the audience and they it becomes clear that the audience accepts them maybe they will
be allowed to do that eventually. I don't know. I could I could see it. Well, the thing is they
have been they've been like girlfriends for a while. It like started off as like a weird thing
like the one character used to be used to have a boyfriend. They were like, I actually find that
I like this person more means more to me. It's like, okay, that's been set up. It's been building
up. It's gotten to a point where they had an extremely romantic moment and they didn't do it.
And it's like, if not, then when would the right person the time be? It's like,
there's an episode about one of them.
Yeah, I'm working record about it. But yeah, yeah, you're all torn up inside. Yeah, damn.
Why don't they fuck? Where's their vaginas? Where's the where's the where's the what's the
what was Plink Plinkett say in the in the Force Awakens like there's something missing. Where's
the sacks or whatever. Yeah, I don't think that fuck. I don't think they can't fuck a black guy.
What the fuck? Oh, yeah. Yeah, that is a thing. Like, like, why wouldn't they?
They just didn't. They just didn't they just didn't they just didn't think Finn was an
appropriate male romantic lead for no particular reason. All right, I haven't seen the fucking
Star Wars. I haven't seen any of the new ones. I saw like Force Awakens because it's like, oh,
like a new Star Wars. So I was like as an event. Sure. Sure. I haven't seen the other ones, but
like, yeah, it seems like there's just no romance in those. I'm like, I mean, that's what Plinkett says.
It definitely would have helped. Yeah, I wonder I wonder if there's like a, oh,
I can't have sex in a thing. We just can't have that. I think I don't know. I don't know if it's
a J.J. Abrams thing. Maybe it's like, wait, no, that kind of it can't be a J.J. Abrams thing.
It was like a weird thing with Spock and that black lady in the Star Trek movies.
Oh, I didn't see that, but maybe.
It's like Spock was like getting his bone on with some lady and Kirk is obviously a sex boy.
I don't know. I'm tempted to say that like culture, like I'm tempted to say that like
youth culture these days is like more squeaky clean, no sex, please. But I don't actually
know if that's true. Sometimes I feel like that's true and maybe they just thought it wouldn't play
well with an audience. I don't know. I would say it's definitely the group that are mostly online
of the new generation. I don't know what percentage of the new generation is like
too online like Twitter online. But those that crowd seems to be very squeaky clean,
puritan, weirdos. I don't like it. Yeah. You know, I say that, but I was honestly,
I was kind of like that as a kid. I had sexual thoughts, but I was very much like,
no, I'm not a person who has sex. I'm not like, I'm not like horny or anything like,
like publicly I was very much like, no, no, no, that's not for me. I'm not interested in that
kind of thing. Yeah. Yeah. I guess I can't judge. I guess I really can't judge.
Yeah. It's like, even though now I see it and I'm like, I don't know. I was definitely,
well, I definitely was fucking wanted to look at adult content when I was under the legal age to
do so. I remember this one time when I was very scared of being caught seeing boobies
where I think it was, I didn't want my parents to find, I found an image, right? It was just
like a very tame image. It just happened to be anime. I didn't know what anime was.
Because I typed in boobs into Google and I saw them and I was like,
you know, oh my God. Holy fucking shit. I could just, if I wanted to, I could just
see these things that I heard about. Oh my God. I got this really, really tame anime.
It's like really like covered up, but you know, it's kind of, it's obviously supposed to be sexual,
but it's very covered up anime image. I got the file, I put it on a USB, I took it to school,
and then I printed it out on the school computer so that my parents wouldn't find out.
That's so fucking funny, but I know I am completely, I would have done, no, I fucking print it out.
Not, I didn't take it on my school computer, but I secretly printed out images onto,
on my fucking inkjet printer. It was, it was only because the printer in my house was like,
you know, right next to mom's computer or the family computer at the time, and I knew in the
school, in the art department at school, there was a printer that was like easily accessible
in a computer area that nobody really went to, and I could easily get in there and be like,
yes, nobody will find out. I can do it during lunch, I can do it during, during, during break,
or whatever, and nobody will find me. And it was just such a bad, like not even good image.
I just like, it was just, it was boobs, I googled it and I have it now.
And you found it and you were like, oh my god, I have to save this, otherwise it could slip
through my fingers. I might never, I might never find these again.
It's true, I might never find it. If I type in boobs now, the whole, the whole games changed.
I'll never see those again. The meta game has shifted.
War, but war never changed. Oh wait, no, it wasn't that. It was, you, you would type boobies,
because, and then you would get the bird. Remember that? No. The blue-footed booby?
I mean, I know, I know what the bird is, but I never had that experience.
That was the first, that was the first word I typed in was boobies, which is adorable.
Very funny, funny, funny that you remember. I don't remember what I, what specific, what terms
I was searching for. Who knows, who even knows? It's fine. It's whatever. Late at night,
fucking one in the morning, parents asleep, dial up internet is
pbbang logging on and I'm like, I'm gonna, I'm on a fucking question.
Go to Google.com, type in girl. Sorry, no, go to fucking yahoo.com type in whatever,
because this was a female. Go to ask. Go to ask jeves.com, and ask, where
is the pornography sticker? He directs you, you like, he, he ushers you in his hands like,
Oh, this way, sir.
Follow me, follow me, my lord.
Right, right this way.
Right.
Better, simpler times, better times.
Ask Jeeves.
I can ask Jeeves.
What the fuck?
Before we reinvented racism, we'd solved racism back then,
but then we had to go and re-invent it.
And now, and now there's no more boobs on the internet.
Nah, well gone.
What did you say?
Where is the pornography?
Yes.
Sir.
I shouldn't call, why would I call my manservant sir?
We call him Jeeves.
Where is the pornography, sir?
On askjeeves.com.
Oh.
Oh, what happened?
Oh, it's news articles about people getting caught on child pornography.
Yeah, I don't think I want to be on askjeeves anymore.
I'm going to exit out of that.
Bummer, bummer.
Jeeves, why did you send me to this place?
Jeeves, that's not.
What were you thinking?
You're fired, Jeeves.
The first thing that comes to his mind.
You're fucking fired.
You think your pension?
Forget about it.
Nah, you're done.
You're out in your ass.
No more fucking, no benefits for you.
You're going to have to fucking, you're going to beg in the streets.
You're going to say, I was Jeeves once upon a time, but not anymore because you fucked up.
Ah, okay.
That's all well and good.
That's fine.
That's cool.
I'm out of shit.
I don't have anything to say.
You want to go to voicemails or no?
Well, I can, one last thing.
My pee is a strange lime green color.
I was a little worried, but then I looked up.
You know what I bet it is?
Okay, I think I know what it means, but go on.
No, no, no.
Tell me what you think.
I think it's vitamin B, right?
Yeah, you got it.
Yeah, I'm a genius.
I'm a penis.
It's a penis.
I've been having multivitamins for like, you know, food supplements, vitamins, voetamines.
Just get them in me.
But I drank one today and I'm like, pee in green.
I guess I have enough.
I don't really need to take that, actually.
Yes, if you.
Which is good.
This means my urinary tract is all functioning and it's doing its job of getting rid of the
excess bullshit.
If you have excess vitamin B, it makes you pee.
I mean, it's not like green green, but it's like neon yellow to almost like a highlighter
yellow, like.
It's like Sergeant Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club band, John Lennon, yellow, green.
Sergeant Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club band.
Oh, his suit.
Yeah.
Yeah, I see.
I see.
Yeah, I'm pretty much like a word, yellow, green.
Some people just see it as one or the other and I don't get it.
I mean, honestly, like, I mean, different, different photos of these, it looks different.
Like in some of the more, the more like saturated, like high contrast ones, it looks yellow, but
the less saturated, like group shots of him, it looks green.
I think it's like, I think it's green though.
It's green.
It looks more green when it when it's shot on the yellow background, but on a blue background,
it looks more yellow.
You know, because that's how colors work.
Oh, God, it's so confusing.
Wait, is this is this dress white and gold or black and blue?
This is your eye black and blue.
Yes.
Based.
I'm, I'm, I'm so proud of myself.
I'm so proud of myself for identifying the pee.
No, because I've had, I've had that.
I also was taking multivitamins and was like, why is my pee greenish?
And I looked it up and was like, oh, it's vitamin B.
Okay.
No problem.
Too much of that shit.
I took, oh God, that reminds me.
This is so embarrassing.
The other, it was for, for Christmas.
My parents, no, it wasn't for Christmas.
It was for, it was more recent than that, whatever.
I saw my parents not too long ago and they gave me a bottle of gummy vitamins and these
gummy vitamins were incredible.
They were so good.
They were the most delicious gummy vitamins I've ever had.
And in case you're curious, these are, the brand is Welby, W-E-L-B-Y.
Welby adult gummy multivit, they taste incredible.
They taste so good that I couldn't stop myself and I ate like half the jar all at once because
they were like too fucking delicious.
That's the stupidest thing you could have done.
I, you don't understand.
You don't understand how good they taste.
You fool.
Well, it's one, if you like the taste, you should have spread it out over less times
so you could enjoy the taste more.
And also, I don't think you're supposed to take so many vitamins at the same time.
You're not.
But as soon as I had done it, I was like, I was like, oh my God, what have I done?
And I started Googling like, how many,
can I overdose on multivitamins?
The general consensus seemed to be that no, the only thing that would be in any multivitamin
that can actually be toxic is iron.
And these don't have iron in them.
So the worst that was going to happen, I mean, they all said, okay, some vitamins are water soluble.
Those, no problem.
You will just pee them out easy.
Some of them are fat soluble.
And those, you might get kind of sick if you take too much of them.
Yeah, you can over-saturate yourself with them and it'll make you sick.
It's not so bad.
Iron, too much iron can actually be poisonous, so that might be a problem.
So I'm like, okay, some of these vitamins, there's no iron, but some of them are fat soluble.
And I was very scared.
And I went and I induced vomiting.
I spent like an hour making myself throw up so that I could get these gummy vitamins out of me.
And I'm like, oh, they were so good.
Why did I do this?
Why did I turn something so good and beautiful into something so horrible to such a nightmare?
Literally, why the fuck did they make them so tasty, though?
They only need to be a little bit sweet so that it doesn't, it isn't bad.
They don't need to be like delicious.
These are, I mean, I appreciate the deliciousness I do, but, you know, it backfired.
It backfired in spectacular fashion.
I'm so stupid.
I don't know.
I just love gummies so much.
And I'm not kidding.
I have had so many different gummies.
These were not just some of the best multivitamin gummies.
They were some of the tastiest gummies I've ever had.
They're shockingly good.
Do you still have the...
I have the bottle.
Yeah, I have the bottle.
Maybe you could reverse engineer why the gummies taste so good from the ingredients.
Dextrose, sucrose, pectin, citric acid, sodium citrate, natural peach flavor, natural orange flavor, natural strawberry flavor, vegetable oil, beta carotene, or purple carrot juice concentrate.
The carrot juice might have something to do with it.
I don't know.
The dextrose and sucrose pretty standard, pretty standard main ingredient for a gummy.
Maybe it's the natural fruit flavoring.
Maybe.
I mean, it was the flavor and also the texture.
They had a perfect gummy texture.
They weren't, they were juicy.
They weren't too chewy.
They weren't rubbery.
I don't know.
It's so hard to describe them.
They were just chewy enough.
There's...
I don't know.
The other...
It was also bad because like I'm trying to do keto and I can't eat half a...
I can't be keto and eat half a bottle of the...
Even if they weren't vitamin, I can't eat that many gummies.
Honestly, I feel bad even.
I'm sort of glad that they're gone because now I'm not eating them anymore.
Because now I'm eating like normal vitamins that are not gummy vitamins that don't have any carbs in them.
Because carbs bad for keto.
So, you know, problem solved.
But I think...
I keep thinking like, damn, I mean, if I'm ever...
If I'm ever wanting to have gummy vitamins in the future, I want these.
I want these well-bees.
These are just shockingly good.
Everyone, I cannot...
I cannot recommend well-bees gummy bites highly enough.
Really, just 10 out of 10 is my review.
Let me know in the comments.
The active vitamin I was having was like a dry pill that you put into a glass of water and then it fizzes up.
It turns a blood red, which is kind of cool.
Does it taste like...
Does it have like a flavor in it?
Yeah, it tastes like cranberry, raspberry a little bit.
Okay.
Quite nice.
I just take a pill.
I think I have like spectrovite when I got from a CVS.
I need a fucking effervescent beverage.
Okay, so that's my fucking story of why I had to puke.
It's so...
Puking is so bad.
And when I do it, when I do it, it like fucks up my face.
Like after puking for a while, I looked at my face and my eyes were bloodshot.
And there were like spots on my skin, like little tiny blood specks on like around my nose and eyes.
Like tiny capillaries had burst.
And I'm like...
Oh no.
Are you straining that hard?
You know, I didn't feel...
I mean, it was a bit strenuous, but I didn't feel like I was like pushing myself to the breaking point.
And yet I must have been because I was clearly like bursting capillaries in my fucking face.
And I'm looking at this and I'm like...
I look like a nightmare.
I look like...
I look like decrepit and like sickly and like a mutant.
Like I just aged like 30 years just by doing this.
God, no.
I should avoid doing this at all costs in the future.
It was very, very unpleasant to see that.
Yeah, I've been vomiting recently because of the sickness that I'm not quite over.
I'm still like this whole last week I've been like...
Oh, I feel fine today.
Wait, no, I don't know.
I don't.
I'm feeling terrible and fine and sort of bad and fine.
So I think I'm on the mend, so that's good.
Like the vomiting days are...
They're so annoying.
Like it's like a combination of...
I feel like the world is going to crumble around me because I feel so weak that it can't move.
And I know that I need like sustenance in order to live.
And I'm like, am I going to be able to make breakfast today?
I don't know.
Oh, God.
Because I don't know that I'm going to vomit until it's too late and then I'm vomiting.
Because I feel sick and I'm like, I hope it just goes away.
Sometimes it does.
Sometimes it doesn't.
I've never had my fucking eyes bloodshot from puking, though.
That sounds so scary.
This...
Yeah, no.
That is consistent.
Whenever I throw up my eyes get bloodshot.
The burst capillary spots on my face, that was new.
I'd never noticed that before.
Very creepy.
I don't know if that's normal, but I mean...
That's not normal.
Oh, God.
What do you want me to do about it?
I don't understand.
I don't know, Ben. I think you're fucking falling apart.
I think we should...
I don't see...
I don't see why it would put like enormous strain on my face to be doing that.
Like my fucking diaphragm maybe, you know?
Like why my face?
I don't know.
It wasn't...
It was oddly satisfying when I...
I mean, it hurt and it felt bad,
but it was in a way oddly satisfying to, you know,
attempt to throw up and finally get it.
Oh, yeah.
I finally got it.
I think there's definitely a part of the brain that's like,
oh, you successfully expelled the poison from your body.
Good job. Now you feel good, you know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which is sort of abstractly enjoyable,
even while the process is like nightmarish and suffering.
Oh, definitely the worst part about vomiting is the...
I'm not literally vomiting yet, but it's getting close.
It's getting closer and I can't do anything about it really.
I just have to sit by the toilet and wait and there it comes.
And then it's gone and then it's like,
oh, it's a great start to the day and I feel full of women vigor
and I can do everything.
I mean, what I did, because I needed to throw up,
what I did was I just drank tons of water, like too much water.
Oh, no.
Like make myself bloated by like drinking like half a gallon
or a gallon just like right there.
And then it's like my stomach's so full it needs to expel
and it like kind of like forces the issue and it made it like,
that was how I, if I was feeling like,
okay, I'm kind of feeling like I'm going to puke,
but I'm not quite there yet.
I would just like chug some water and then it would like get me closer.
This is disgusting.
No, this is the worst podcast ever.
Vomit, vomit talk with Ben and G.
Well, you know, everyone knows how it feels.
Everyone knows how this is a relatable gamer moment for everyone.
We've had shitcast.
We talked about pee.
We talked, in previous episodes, we've talked about shit.
This is the pee episode and the puke episode.
So you can double your money.
The vaccine and some other stuff.
The transphobia.
That was the first thing.
Oh, sure.
Right.
Yeah.
But mostly the gross shit.
All your favorite things.
Cool.
Okay.
Well, you want to go voicemail?
We actually have a lot.
So let's try and be fast.
Yeah, I know.
Let's try and be fast.
Yeah.
You have to go all the way back to page three.
The first one is called.
I know the first one is called who is Yig even for.
Do you see that one?
Yep.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys.
So while we're shitting on Yig studios and don't get me wrong,
we definitely should keep this up.
I just got to ask.
Who is it for?
Like what audience are they trying to court?
I legitimately don't understand it because they're always going
on about how much they hate parasocial relationships.
Fuck parasocial relationships.
I don't know you anything.
You don't know who I am, but it feels like their entire
business model is built around it.
Like having meetups and.
Constantly making videos of them just getting high and shit
like anyone cares.
I don't know if I agree with that.
Think that they're friends.
I just legitimately don't understand.
I mean, it's not like you have casual fans because you're not
making anything that's worth watching at all.
And it's not like you're making your old fans happy because
you're constantly shitting on them.
Calling them entitled and not giving them blue rays that they
paid for.
So I just really don't understand what Trixie is trying to do.
You guys can enlighten me.
Let me know.
But I don't think you don't either.
I think you are wrong.
Anyway, PCP forever.
Tom will never die.
Tom will outlast all of us.
I think you are wrong to say that Yig is about like courting
parasocial relationships.
I don't think it is.
The meetups they talk about doing are not with like fan.
They're not fan meetups.
They talk about meeting with like other, you know, people that
make creative.
So people like noise.
Raps.
Yeah.
It's like other other people who make who make raps.
They talk about like meeting up with those people on their bus
tour, which for the record is never happening.
There is no RV.
I think the stuff is that it's it's weird because it's like it's a
Trixie project with music and and I don't know how much of the
direction like obviously Trixie wants to do a lot of this weird
music stuff.
And that's fine.
That's cool.
I guess.
And the anime is fine.
It was fine.
It was fine when it was on when it was on the after dark channel.
Yeah.
The there was a comment or something that somebody was
complaining.
Nobody minded the idea that this this channel that she's had
with 300,000 subscribers who subscribed for a particular type
of content are like they're obviously not going to be happy
with like the majority of the things that is anime analysis
still being made.
But like they're obviously confused and like, oh, OK, what
what the fuck and they're leaving and and Riley was like,
yeah, well, if you don't like it, you can leave.
We're definitely trying to bleed subscribers who don't care
about what we're doing.
Yeah.
And I'm like, if that's the case, why did you want to then why
did you put it on this channel?
Yeah.
Then if you even what what was the point of starting here?
Like it seemed to be working fine.
Like you had the void gazes chases on the after dark thing
that could be the whatever did you know nobody minded nobody
minded when it was on that channel.
It wasn't like because people who were subscribed to that
channel already wanted to see like the side content the other
stuff besides the anime analysis.
That's what that channel was for.
You put it on the main channel and it's like, well, this isn't,
you know, most people are like, this is not what I signed up
for.
I don't know the who the who the intended audience is.
I mean, it's it's a little.
I don't I honestly don't know other than like they're making
stuff that like the stuff they make.
Well, sure.
But like, what does that mean?
I don't I think they're just making it for themselves because
they like it, which on the one hand is like, I guess that's admirable.
If you're not like catering it to anyone, but at the same time,
no, I also don't really know who it's supposed to appeal to other
than maybe if you if you knew these people and by people,
I mean Trixie because nobody knew these other people before.
If you knew them and you're invested in whatever they're doing,
then maybe you're interested in these videos that she's making
with these other people.
And if not, then you're probably not.
I guess that's mostly just like on the off chance that the people
Trixie has as followers also like her music.
That would be that's what they're looking for.
I just want to.
You know, hope they have enough people into interested to like
survive with the money they could get from that.
So yeah, sure.
I just I just.
OK, yeah, it's bizarre.
Next voicemail is called protagonist three, two, one, go.
Who do you think in your opinion is the protagonist
of the PCP me me?
I mean, what sort of question is that?
I don't see anyone else is like more important.
I'm the protagonist of my own story and the PCP is really a thing.
I feel like I feel like.
I mean, I don't know for sure, but I feel like everyone should
feel like they are the protagonist.
I would I would hope that everyone involved.
Sees it sees it sees it as their project sees it as their
project to an extent.
Yeah, yeah.
If it's not me, then it's nobody.
Like like from the outside looking in, maybe if it's a show,
you could you could just you could like ascribe a protagonist
onto the podcast from the outside.
But from the inside, I can't think of anyone other than myself
because that's it.
I don't I see my own perspective way more than anyone else's
because I'm me.
So yeah, I don't know.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Funny question, but I don't know if it really has a great
answer.
Sorry about that.
Next voicemail is called return of a hilarious gimmick.
Three, two, one, go Beatrice more like but yeah.
Yeah.
More like nice.
But I like it didn't it sounded like there was more more like
but.
Okay, cool.
Next one is called sad, but surprisingly sexy boy.
Three, two, one, go.
Holy fuck.
Movies.
People movies are videos where real people are the primary focus
sort of like reality.
I hurt myself.
You know, I do have a sizable chip on my shoulder and I always
have had a chip on my shoulder about the fact that I am not
more widely known on YouTube.
People movies are not more successful.
I'm not, you know, a member of the glorious 100k subscriber
clock.
I allowed myself to be fired from the show so that it could be
allowed.
I might never have 100k subscribers.
I've never even had 10,000 subscribers.
I was also until recently a member of a podcast called
The Procrastin Interest.
I deserve a lot more recognition than I can.
That's not me being arrogant.
I mean, it's just a fact.
I've been doing this for so long and I've been doing it for so
well.
I decided to formally leave the podcast because this would be
insane.
And it's just one of those, you know, random, deep and sad truths
of being an artist that I haven't, you know, hold on like wildfire
and playing other channels and other things have been lucky
enough to do it.
You heard some legal people move video logs.
I...
I don't really get the Jesse, like, a bit.
Okay.
What did it say at the end?
We were in a people movie all along.
Okay.
Sure.
It felt like what was supposed to be happening here is that we
were supposed to be contrasting what Jesse was saying with
what Trixie was saying.
But I don't really see them as like...
I don't see the connection.
Jesse's saying I should be more famous.
Trixie's saying...
I mean, she's saying I'm what, like...
That I was...
Describing what people movies are and saying that she quit
CanTent and the PCP.
Man, maybe I'm missing...
Yeah, I don't know.
Maybe the song is like, oh, like, you could have it all.
Like, oh, the all AK 100,000 subs.
Is it just saying subs go down?
I think we might be just saying that.
I mean, maybe.
I don't know if it's if it's if there's a message here.
I'm afraid it flew over my head.
I apologize.
People at movies.yig.
Next voicemail is called pure Shadden Freud pumping through my veins.
Three, two, one, go.
Here comes Trixie, worse teeth in the game, looking just as
unattractive on the outside as she is on the inside, burning
bridges left and right.
The PCP knows she's untrustworthy and ungrateful.
The dick show things.
Yeah, you're a bunch of drama whore and cowards, which is true.
Not to mention they still think she's a pedophile.
Nate Baseman laying down the ultimatums because he's not
blind and he knows a train wreck when he sees one.
Just to think that this man quit his job and moved to Virginia
just to make content with her.
Bad role, dude, bad role.
Also, what the fuck are movie movies?
Didn't she ditch the Digi branding to make herself more appealing
to advertisers?
If so, excellent job, honey.
You're really killing it.
I only got one last thing to say.
Brush your teeth, bitch.
I mean, I believe she's brushes her teeth now.
I believe that's canon.
Other than that, I agree.
Yeah.
Thanks for the voicemail.
Next one is called, next one is called
Gibbtfo love jelly beaner.
How much do you want to bet?
He will mention the Jews.
Odds on the odds on admission of the Jews.
100%.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
I don't like Jews.
Oh, you said it.
I said it.
It was you all along.
No, that can't be.
I kind of said that.
Maybe I blacked out for a minute there, but I'm pretty sure.
I'm pretty sure I didn't say that.
I, you know, I think you probably did say it.
Actually, I don't know, but I just think you would and did for sure.
Sorry, but it's true.
You got to look yourself in the mirror.
Take a long, hard look.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called Digi bro.
Three, two, one, go.
Tricksie has spoken.
Digi bro is dead.
Well, not anymore.
Fuckers.
Guess what?
She transitioned to Tricksie and I'm transitioning to Digi bro.
My pronouns are autistic and pedophile.
My gender is human content machine.
I'm going to make anime videos while wearing women's sunglasses
and nobody can stop me.
If you ever want your name back, Tricksie, you're going to have to
liquid Chris style rap battle me for it.
I don't think she wants it back.
More like a golden snitch.
Ha, got him.
I'm a fucking legendary PCP music intro creator.
I'm unstoppable.
Also, if you want a new co-host for content.
I can even pronounce it right.
Content.
Do you say content?
It's canton.
Canton.
You have to say it exactly like that.
I don't think you're going to get liquid Chris style challenge
to a karaoke battle.
I think she's happy to leave the name, but enjoy it, I guess.
Enjoy yourself with it.
The next one is called...
It's a link to a YouTube channel.
The link goes to a channel called DITRH, which appears to be a
Flat Earth Truth video or channel.
Alright, let's give this a listen.
Three, two, one, go.
David Weiss is the greatest Flat Earther of all time.
He's really cool and he goes on lots of podcasts.
He'll give you a Bitcoin if you can prove the Earth is round.
Dude, a whole bit.
But the Earth isn't round. It's flat.
Nobody can prove that it's round.
Because when they never went to space, it's all fake.
And the world is not spinning. It's stationary.
Whereas the Coriolis effect?
Well, you can't prove that it's real because it's bullshit.
I've never seen the Coriolis effect.
The Sun is spinning overhead.
It's spinning around the disk.
And the Moon is also doing that.
And the Sun goes in and out between the tropics and stuff.
I know that.
You can circumnavigate, but you can't go north to south.
Because if you go south, you end up beyond the Ice Wall.
Who knows who's there?
It could just be New Tartaria. Who knows?
All I know is that the Great Pyramid of Chihulu, Chathula,
or whatever you say, is covered in mud.
Why is it covered in mud?
It's covered in 20 feet of mud.
Because there's ruins everywhere.
Have you ever heard of the wow lines?
They're called wow lines because they make you go wow.
There's ruins everywhere, man.
There's an ancient civilization.
Rome was a worldwide phenomenon.
They don't want you to know this.
They don't want you to know your history.
The Civil War was a cover.
Like the bit of just being a big conspiracy weirdo
and not thinking Ireland and Scotland are different places.
No, that was a different guy.
That was the same guy.
Was it the same guy?
Maybe it was the same guy.
I wasn't convinced until you told me about the mud
on the Great Pyramid of Chihulu.
Why is it there?
Why is there mud on Chulula?
Maybe there is an ice wall.
Why else would there be mud?
Why can't they ask the question?
Why can't they say where the mud is from?
A simple question should have a simple answer.
Am I right?
And it does.
No curvature, baby.
Well, you know what?
I believe all saw it.
Oh, my God.
We got four more voicemails
while we've been listening to them.
No.
We got our first the page.
Rapid fire.
The next one is called
Hi Ben smiley face.
Did you see that one?
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben.
I heard you weren't
invited to Radcon 5.
So I'm thinking 4.5.
Maybe you can make the next one.
You know, Radcon 6.
We're going to have a
Golden Witch 101.
People have floated this.
Nice lecture.
I miss those.
Those are pretty cool.
People have floated the idea.
I think it has.
I think it's not.
I mean, I don't know.
There's enough there to talk about, I guess.
But do I actually want to do it?
I don't know.
The next one is called
Gaming 3, 2, 1, go.
Hey guys, it's me.
It's that Mario Kart guy again.
Oh, fuck yeah.
I'm actually playing Mario Kart right now.
I'm listening to the new episode.
I'm in the middle of it.
Incredibly through base.
It's real interesting so far.
It's a little bit of a bummer, but it's also really great.
There's a lot of back and forth.
A lot of different viewpoints.
Ben is right.
There's lots of different viewpoints.
There's Ben, right, and others wrong.
No.
But I found out something crazy about the switch.
And this one's going to be the end of me.
You can actually take it out of the dock.
And it still plays games.
No kidding.
It's like a Game Boy.
But it plays video games.
Dude, this is a game changer.
How did you do that?
Like, literally what the fuck?
What do you mean what the fuck?
What's so confusing about it?
This changes everything.
Bro!
The entire console is the thing.
And then the stand is just a stand.
Console out of the stand?
That's...
I'm sorry, but why aren't more people talking about this?
Why aren't more people talking about this is all I'm saying.
Why is there mud there?
Let me know.
Why is the mud?
Why is there mud on the chinchalula?
Okay, next voicemail is called
Hey Look It's a doigazers.
I gotta say, doigazers needs
to get some fresh material
because it's wearing a little thin.
Like, I get it. They do drugs.
Alright, let's give it a shot.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, welcome to doigazers.
This is your host, Dee.
And today we're going to be smoking some weed.
And then we're going to be
debunking Ben St.'s claims
that we don't have
an RV using facts and logic.
There's no RV.
Benjamin, I correct to inform you
that we do indeed have an RV.
It is almost...
It's almost done being complete.
We just have to make a few calls
to the Lego Corporation
about some missing pieces.
And then, you know, after that, we're ready to roll.
The numbers just don't add up.
There's simply no way they can afford one.
After that, we're going to release our diss track.
To say nothing of the fact that
living in an RV is difficult
and wouldn't work.
And she's been quite a thorn in the matter of fact.
They wouldn't be able to hack it.
But they can't even get that far.
They simply can't afford it.
So she really needs a diss track made about her.
And Riley will be in it.
My best friend.
And after that, we're going to smoke some more weed.
So stay tuned.
And give me some more money.
You know, I'm making $900 a month.
Right away.
But, you know, that's all getting smoked away.
So...
I need more.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Patreon thing also.
Side note is almost up to
$8.
Great.
Okay, next voicemail is called
Watch Out 3, 2, 1, Go.
I'm pretty sure Tommy J.
is at large.
I'm pretty sure he's sending in voicemails.
No.
I'm like 100%.
It's impossible.
I'm pretty sure some of these guys are Tommy J.
Putting on a funny voice.
It can't be true.
Oh, no.
You've reached our defenses.
Maybe it's coming up.
Tommy J's. But you know what?
You know what? If he is,
it hasn't been a problem.
Whatever.
Maybe you're right. Maybe this wild
conspiracy theory is true.
We can never truly know.
Okay, the next one.
Watch Out.
Watch Out, the voicemail is called
Tommy J is at large and on the loose.
He's on the lam.
Next voicemail is called
Sclerosis Man, 3, 2, 1, Go.
Damn.
Ernest for your brother.
Are you going to fuck him?
Yeah.
That's right.
Okay.
Good. It's fine.
It's not multiple sclerosis.
Just the one sclerosis.
Singular sclerosis.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called
Sclerosis Man, 3, 2, 1, Go.
Hey!
Give and take this track.
Let's get it.
Get it. Hey, give and take.
You're really a fake.
I don't like your hair or your glasses.
You're a snake.
I came to drop rhymes about all your
crimes and all of your projects.
You keep clandestine.
Here's Riley to take you to school.
Yeah.
Get him, Riley. You're my new best friend.
Yeah, golden bitch.
I'm going to get this guy
give and take.
I have a girlfriend.
I'm the fizzier.
Yeah.
Yeah, brother.
Okay.
Give and take. You're a real bad girl.
Every time you speak, it makes me hurl.
Every breath you take, I wish you was your last.
I drove your ass to school,
so pay attention in class.
Riley!
Oh, god, I feel so fucking owned right now.
Yeah, get it, Riley.
This was a Doidgazer's original.
Name Ben, you're still not cool.
Holy shit.
You're okay.
Shout out to everyone who gets me money.
I don't owe you anything, though.
Get me more money.
Okay, that was a winner.
That was a real climb.
That was a real high point in the Doidgazer's side.
I really got stabbed through the heart
a couple of times.
Honestly?
Those bars right there.
You know, I'd unsub, but I think I might go back.
If this is the kind of quality
that the channel is dropping, I might have to go and resub.
I'm interested now.
They pulled me back in.
Next...
Next phone.
That's really good.
It's genuinely funny.
Next voicemail is called
the plural word for mice.
Three, two, one, go.
Mouses. Hey, Gib, obviously
the plural to mouse is
meese, like, jaw.
Right, because Goose and Geese.
Right.
Call me back. It's Mouses.
Goose. Goose and Geese.
Moose and Mese.
Mox.
Mox and Mese.
What about an ox?
What about an oxen? Ox?
Eeks.
I believe you. What about a moose?
What about a cat?
No. No more questions.
No more questions. Only voicemails.
Next voicemail is called
Bees.
Bees in my eyes
and bees everywhere.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh!
Konnichiwa.
Konnichiwa to you as well.
This is Ninja-sama.
Peno-Sento-san.
Resist.
Tretel.
We asked once more
the ninja's just
higher register.
Ninja scroll.
This is the last time
we request
return of the scroll.
Ninja is not civil.
It calls me a racist.
We'll be declared next week
Peno-Sento-san.
Tushio,
the Tokyo Ninja
Chrono. Serious.
Se, Konnichiwa,
to you as well.
Peno-Sento-san.
Samurai-sama.
My god, no!
Oh god.
Unlikely allies.
Peno-Sento-san.
I never thought I'd miss the old best too.
No.
Sayonara.
That can't be true.
This is so bad. This is so fucked up.
I can't do it. I'm sorry.
I just don't have it in me.
It's going against my nature.
It's my nature to steal
and hoard scrolls.
I'd be living a lie.
I just want to say
it's not cultural appropriation
when I steal samurai
and or ninja scrolls.
It's cultural appreciation.
I love them so much.
It's cultural appreciation
and value when I sell them on.
I love the Japanese people
so much that I will
keep the scrolls
even though a Japanese man
will be killed over it.
That's just the level to which I
appreciate their culture.
I'm so right.
I'm so right. I'm far right.
Fuck the Japanese.
Next voicemail
is called Riley Killed Pizza Party
Man this is bullshit.
Pan pizza suddenly decided
I don't want to do pizza party anymore.
Is that true?
We finally got a man in.
It's all a lie.
Somehow this is Riley's fault.
I fucking know it.
He's got his fingers in every pie.
Just keep making the show.
He's got his fingers in every pizza pie.
Get it? It's a joke.
Huh? Yeah? Pretty good.
I've got my fingers in every one of your eye holes.
Ow. God.
No, don't crush my skull.
And then I use your head as a bowling ball.
How about that?
No.
I saw Cheezy saying that he had killed the Pizza Party podcast.
I thought it was just an off-handed like Cheezy just likes to say that.
I thought it was just a joke, but I mean, it would make sense if it were true.
They realized we had that they've been compromised by Cheezy.
That the PCP had an in and then they shut the whole thing down to get us off.
I want, it's time to dance in their grave.
It's time to dance in their grave.
We got you got to go to the last episode and comment and say the PCP one.
PCP beat the Pizza Party podcast.
We subverted it from the inside.
We took it down and we didn't survive.
Not a single drop of blood was shed.
We did it all through intrigue and subterfuge.
The gentlemen's right.
Gentlemenly war warfare, psychological warfare with our clown secret agent.
Our psychological guerrilla warfare.
Sewing discord.
Speaking of clowns, I'm behind on.
I'm behind on.
Cycloneos.
Cyclone.
I'm way behind.
I'm like three weeks behind.
Three weeks of shit.
You got to get on that.
I know.
The clown designs.
There's more of them and they look cool.
Really?
I got spoiled a little, but not too much.
I know that someone dies, but that's not much of a spoiler because it could be anyone.
So.
Yeah.
So it's fine, but I should catch up before I get genuinely spoiled.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called doid gazers finale.
I'll go going out of the high note.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello and welcome to another episode of doid gazers.
This is your host, the and today we're going to be, of course, smoking some more weed.
As we do.
And then we're going to be talking about the fire disc track that we released against
give and take who is the catalyst to everything genuinely fire in the world.
And then we're going to be talking about how my RV totally exists.
It's not a ban.
I found that out because Riley told me so and, you know, he knows everything.
And then I just wanted everyone to know that the baby's all right.
You know, baby's cool.
I was worried about the baby.
Baby don't want to say nothing, but you know, he's cool.
He's like halfway across the tub and he he's like so scared to get in.
Oh my God.
Sorry.
This is the last door.
Oh my God.
Sorry.
This is the last door.
But Ben, Tom, given like just continue what you're doing, please.
Or just switch to a different like podcast.
If you have to work brand do it because like you're the you're the best.
And I love y'all like you guys.
Thank you.
No.
That's nice.
Oh shit.
I didn't expect that because there was a baby involved.
There was a baby, which means I like I feel sympathy.
I'm ambivalent.
I'm ambivalent about the baby.
But I mean, you know, someone mentioned the idea of a rebrand.
And I don't think it's too stupid an idea.
I think it's so different now.
We may as well, but I just don't know how to do it exactly.
Like what?
Yeah, I agree.
Like, I mean, we did the rebrand with like the graveyard stuff as a bit of a like mini rebrand.
It's true.
The show is so much different than what it used to be.
I don't know.
It's not a crazy idea.
But I have at the same time, I have no clue what we would change it to or what.
We could change like the name of this podcast to not be called a podcast.
It'd be called The Procrestinated Show.
So it was the PCS.
But what?
I like procrastinators.
I don't want to get rid of that.
But I guess, you know, what would be like an appropriate name, do you think?
I mean, wait, why would we start calling it a podcast?
It's still a podcast.
Because the acronym PCP is like the thing people think of.
So if we change that, everything will change.
Even if it's still called a procrastinator something.
I mean, honestly, I would think that if we change the name but kept the abbreviation PCP,
that's probably what I would do because PCP is...
Well, no, because the point of a rebrand is to like, you know,
not associate with what people think of the previous thing, right?
Necessarily.
People have like negative opinions of...
Because I've heard some people think of that PCP show as, oh,
the show that hosted that person who was a pedophile.
And that's the only way they know the PCP through like Dick Masterson area of things.
I'm like, ah, that sucks.
I don't like the fact that some people know that acronym as that.
So rebranding would be to get rid of that association at least.
I mean, I'm not that worried about it.
I guess neither am I, but like, it's something.
Like, if there's a reason to rebrand, I would think that would be changing to something different.
I'm not...
I don't know.
I'm not worried about like, Trixie Stigma exactly.
Like, that doesn't make me worry at all.
But the idea that like the show is different and therefore call it something different,
if only to just distinguish one era from another is like, makes sense to me.
I don't know.
I would have to think more about it.
I would need a strong idea of like, this is what the new show should be called.
You know, I would need something that's like, ah, that's a good idea that would be cool,
but I don't have any ideas like that because I'm stupid.
Maybe we could just have like a formal rebranding.
Like, it's the new arc that keep the PCP like procrastination or whatever,
but it's now like just golden age or something.
Golden age.
We just call it PCP2.
An ironically could work.
Just from now on, it's called the PCP2.
It's just a little sillier.
Whatever that means.
It means whatever you think it means.
You do the homestuck thing, the homestuck symbol thing.
We should rebrand.
We should stop coming on the show.
We should just hire like, we should just hire like ghost podcasters.
We should hire two people to like be on the show instead of us.
I don't know.
Wouldn't that be wacky?
Okay, whatever.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called Pover D.
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, I'm a party cast patron.
I pay like a dollar a month for that show.
I'd like more.
Also would be cool if then you caught up on one piece.
Then maybe you could have some of those dollars.
Some of those cents per month.
Maybe like 10 of them.
I don't know what the split is like.
I have no idea.
That's all.
Just, you know, keep up the good work, boys.
At this point, it's such a meme that I need to kick.
No, I'm just saying we, I should get talking to Nate too.
Because we haven't done a party cast in a while.
Keep, we keep leaving it.
Well, I keep leaving catching up on one piece.
I need, I'm, I'm, I had almost caught up at Radcon four.
And then I like haven't read since then.
So I'm like, I'm a year behind again now.
Yeah, I have a lot to catch up on.
I don't know.
God, I'm always just like, yeah, I should catch up on it.
But like, I can always do it later.
Like it's not, it's not going anywhere.
I don't feel any urgent need to catch up on.
Unless I wanted to be on the, on the POTY cast.
Ultimately, like when one piece ends, you'll be like, oh, well now I should.
Cause, you know, if it, if it does like get to the point where you
haven't read it since that point, that point.
And then it ends.
It's like, well now I got to read all of it.
So it's really just in postponing the inevitable.
Yes.
That's, that's exactly how I feel about it.
But I do think it's cool.
So you just, just should read it.
Maybe after I, cause then, cause then you can like reread it.
You can reread it later.
I haven't even considered that possibility.
As it comes out slowly and then you can blast through it as well.
You can have both experiences.
It'll take a lot of time.
Maybe after I finish my secret project and I have some,
and I feel like I have some more time that I'm willing to spend on frivolous
activities, I will do that then.
Perhaps, perhaps.
Next voicemail is called Researching Flying Submarines voicemail movie.
Three, two, one, go.
We've saved the peg, so it's time to go.
I was at the beach, watching a sunrise.
The orange ocean glow brought a tear to my eye.
Until I saw a plane flying up so high.
There's more planes in the sea than ships in the sky.
We need a billion glad to make submarines fly.
These are so weird.
Yeah.
These are so odd.
I can't really grasp what the vibe is going for.
Like I felt like this one was supposed to be poetic.
I mean, I think they're all, they're all rhyme.
They all rhyme, but like some of them feel like more obviously comedic.
Yeah.
Some of them feel like I don't know whether it's supposed to be comedic or a rap or a poem.
I think they're all mostly supposed to be silly to one degree or another.
This is like, this is like an opera.
This should be, I feel like this should have, there should be like a band camp album that
is just each of these in order.
If you ever wanted to just listen to the whole saga from start to end.
Yeah.
It feels like a piece of a larger thing.
There are like elements that recur like pigs, but in this one, like the pig was only like
in the figure of speech about pigs flying, which I think that was a reference to the
last one.
I think a pig did fly.
I think.
Am I crazy?
Yeah, it did.
Okay.
So it's like obliquely referencing it, but like, I guess nothing really happened in this
one.
He just watched a sunset and contemplated flight, which is, uh, these are, these are,
these are, these are, these are like, these are like nothing I've ever heard before.
I can say that much about them.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called doid gazer's finale part two.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, these have all been people movies.
Um, Ben and Nate, you're still not cool.
Thank you.
Give me money.
Of course.
Uh, next one is called part three, I guess.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, that this track was a music movie.
Fuck you.
Yeah.
All right.
Got a hand.
What about a regular movie?
What, what, what about a regular movie?
I don't know.
What about a regular movie?
No.
I guess there are regular, I guess movie movies are movies about movies.
So movies are just movies.
Wow.
Makes sense.
It does.
Unless it's an animated movie and then it's a cartoon movie.
Wait, wouldn't, wouldn't a cartoon movie then be a, a movie about, about cartoons?
But no, a cartoon.
No, be a cartoon about movies.
Oh God.
Jesus.
Uh, next voicemail is called the real best guy ever.
Three, two, one, go.
Yo, it's the real best guy ever here.
Hey, good to hear from you.
You know, Riley best to me cause I'm five eight, but you stand no chance pal.
Bring it on.
I give you a little kiss.
I'm, I'm too scared.
Yeah, trust me, they're stupid.
I'm too scared.
I think you would crush my head and I don't want that.
So I'm going to have to, I'm going to have to cowardly refuse with my tail between my
legs.
I'm sorry.
Next voicemail is called for jelly beaner.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh my God, baby.
You want me to fry you up some fucking potato pancakes?
Some latkes?
No, just.
Cool.
It would be the anti-semitic remorse.
Delicious.
I couldn't even hear that.
Next voicemail is very quiet, but whatever.
It was quiet.
It was, he was frying, he was frying up latkes for jelly beaner, but it was offended by the
anti-Semitism.
I think that's, he won't do it because it, whatever.
Yeah.
Next voicemail is called Ben Pilled.
Three, two, one, go.
What is it with you people in the comments going on about bad Ben politics?
What are the bad Ben politics?
I know.
Socialist ideas don't like that.
You're real, not a fan of that.
Imagine.
Is it respecting people's identities?
Don't like that Ben takes the side of trans rights and doesn't, dead name, Trixie?
Honestly, it's us.
What was the bad Ben politics?
I'm out of a loop.
Honestly, it's us that there are a number of people like, I disagree with Ben on politics,
but he's right.
Like, what do you disagree on exactly?
There was a, it was similar.
It's a common sentiment.
It was like, oh, that Ben, he's being based right now by hating Trixie.
A shame about his dumb lefty positions though.
I wish he was stopped being a dumb lefty.
It's like, what?
Okay.
I guess I can see where you're coming from.
I guess.
Yeah.
Wait, wait, I want to read.
There was, there was a comment.
This is from the Kiwi Farms thread that I saw and I just wait.
I want to find it.
I just, I just, this one, this one really, it really struck me that this guy completely
gets me.
Eleazar.
Cut out this awkward sound.
Oh no, here it is.
Here it is.
Ben, Ben Saint is a literal Jew commie bottom feeder.
Yet he appears like a fucking chad to these people because at least he has a spine and
isn't afraid to tell someone to fuck off.
Literal Jew commie bottom feeder.
Ben Saint.
Absolutely true and, and valid and accurate.
And I thank you.
I feel seen.
LeMau.
Yeah.
Anyway, a fucking vote, vote Bernie fucking losers in the comments.
LeMau.
Bernie 2020, 2024.
2020, 2024.
That's very fun.
2020, 2020.
We want to run on a, we got to run on the fucking the Cor, the Corbin, the Corbin Sanders ticket
for president of the, of the United Nations.
Next voicemail is called ideas man.
Three, two, one, go.
All right, guys.
Hear me out on this one.
What if you made one more episode with a topic now hold on.
I know what you're thinking.
Unthinkable.
But this one's a good one.
Voicemailer rules.
Get it done.
Come on.
Just one topic episode.
You can do it.
I believe in you.
I feel like we have been over the voicemail rules.
We have talked, we have talked many times about what makes a good voicemail.
It's, it's only, it's only when it comes up that a voicemail sucks so bad and we say,
ah, this sucks.
And sometimes we give a reason why, but a lot of the time we just say stupid, lol.
And move on.
So I don't know.
Maybe there's a topic in there.
I don't know if there's a full episode.
I don't, I don't know if there's a whole episode.
Maybe part of an episode.
I mean, we've, it's, I don't want, I don't, I don't want to get into it now.
I, I, I guess.
Hmm.
I think a reason like a topic episode would be more difficult now is because there's only
two of us, maybe three of us.
Yes.
Like in the day when there's a single topic and six of us or seven of us were on an episode.
Sure.
Everybody would have one thing to say in a half long episode.
Yeah.
And it would fill out the episode if people just had their one thing to say about that
one topic.
One topic between you and me wouldn't last nearly as long.
No.
No, I don't think so.
No, I agree.
That's totally true.
Next voicemail is called inexplicable.
Three, two, one.
Go.
So do you guys know about the pool multiple and the stop to flow model?
So the pool multiple or P, U, E, L multiple.
It is a formula and the output of that formula, whenever it gets to a range of above like
four, Bitcoin tends to reach its peak.
Whenever the pool multiple reaches something like 0.5, that's when Bitcoin reaches its
lows.
So this pool multiple, it seems that it hasn't reached eight yet.
So that means that Bitcoin still has a lot more to go before it reaches its peak.
And the pool multiple has been pretty accurate so far.
There's also another thing called the stock to flow model.
It's just a price prediction for the, for Bitcoin until the end of time.
And it's been pretty accurate.
And Bitcoin also has a four year cycle, right?
Every four years it reaches a new peak.
And so if you add four years to the last peak, the next peak should be around like, I don't
know, February of 2022.
And I think the price is going to reach something like 100,000.
So that's my prediction.
$100,000 Bitcoin, February 2022.
Yeah.
Peace.
I have not heard of those things, but it's interesting.
I mean, I, huh, I have heard that there was an idea that you could out like guess where
it's going with an algorithm, but I have heard that maybe there's something to that.
I have heard that there are models like this.
I haven't really looked, I probably should have looked into them before I got into it.
I made me Bitcoin investments, but I didn't.
Maybe I will.
And then once I understand them better, I will maybe consider, if I were to read these
and it was like, okay, the math is rock solid.
Bitcoin is like very likely to continue to grow for the next year or so.
Then I think I would be like, well, I might as well trust the math.
I would, I would consider it a stock to flow model, well multiple.
And then you also mentioned a four year cycle.
Do they do all three of these things like agree with each other in terms of their predictions?
I mean, hopefully.
Interesting.
Good thinking.
Next voicemail is called a thing not shit on enough.
Three, two, one, go.
A thing not talked about enough with all this is why the hell did B decide to become a touring artist
during the pandemic?
Who the hell thought that was a good idea?
That is true.
Yeah.
I feel like she's been very lax on believing COVID is that big of a deal, but I don't know
exactly whether she's had a statement about that.
I just get a feeling she doesn't think that is that.
Well, she was scary.
Well, she was on.
She was on the Bill Gates did COVID thing for a while.
Yeah, that was strange.
Very bad.
Stupid.
It's one of those like, I can't tell if you're joking, but you see.
She wasn't, she wasn't joking.
Yeah.
And which, but I don't know how you could do that.
And also think she, I haven't heard her say like.
COVID is not a big deal, but she doesn't act as though she thinks it's a big deal.
Case in point that she's going on supposedly going on tour, which again.
I mean, she was doing road trips.
There is no.
Like with the Yig gang, she's been driving around.
It's like, I don't know.
I feel like before that, maybe she was a little more reserved.
Maybe they've sort of convinced her that it's fun.
You should really get out in the world.
And it's like, cool.
Maybe.
Cool.
Who knows?
I mean, I mean, get vexed first.
Get fucking vexed.
It's not going to.
I'm expecting to be vexed probably within like maybe a month or so.
I don't know.
I don't actually know, but you know, other people I know are getting it.
So it seems like it's, it's, it's basically, we're basically there.
Yeah.
No, I agree, voicemailer.
Next voicemailer is called Sorry If This Is Too Serious.
Three, two, one, go.
Yig Studio is comprised of violent and shady people.
Yes.
Riley is a compulsive, manipulative, sociopathic opportunist who abuses drugs.
Probably.
She is an emotionally vulnerable person that's slowly retracted from a friend group
after attachment issues with a romantic partner and after breaking up.
Yes.
Some distance from their former support group of friends in the middle of an identity crisis.
Riley has convinced Trixie to overtake her once popular channel with his group.
To leech what money Trixie had, convincing her to let the Yig crew attempt to invade every other content creator group Trixie was a part on.
To attract attention for financing their awful and sustainable lifestyle.
When Trixie splits with Yig Studio, because her online identity has crumbled into irreparable ruin,
financially useless, Trixie will have nobody.
I'm afraid if nobody can help her.
She's got, she's got well off parents.
People are too worried.
She'll, she's fine.
Yeah, I don't know.
She'll be fine.
Even if her, even if her, even if her internet income became zero, she wouldn't die.
Like, I, I, I see this a lot.
I don't know how much of like, if there's a, like a blame for this.
Is it, oh Riley's a super manipulator or is it Trixie making the gross decisions ever?
I think it's both.
I, I don't think you can say that Riley is completely like, like being, I don't know.
I don't know.
Swept up by Riley to a point where she's completely vulnerable.
Maybe she, I don't know.
I think that Riley, I don't know enough, but I feel like it's the same.
Yeah.
I think that Riley is an opportunist who is encouraging this because it is to his benefit.
But I also feel like Trixie is probably to some extent also encouraging him.
She's encouraging, she encouraged the whole thing of it.
Maybe like, she allowed him and them into her life in the first place.
Now, I mean, Trixie, she, I mean, she wants this.
Like she wants this all to be happening.
She is enthusiastically going along with it.
So, you know, I don't like, I feel bad like saying this stuff like I know anything about
what's going on in their heads.
So from an outside perspective, this, this voicemail is like, yeah, I can see that.
It's just about as, as valid as anything I could imagine.
It's, we cannot agree that it's not, doesn't look good.
Doesn't look good.
Yeah.
This is, this is similar, this voicemail is similar to my take on the situation.
Similar read to my own.
With a few, a few little nitpicks.
And next voicemail is called Razzmatazz Bean.
Bring back the PCP cock discussion arc.
Three, two, one, go.
Holy shit.
Oh boy.
I sure do wish the PCP would stop talking about foreskin for every episode.
Said the listeners.
And then a finger on the monkey's paw curl.
This is, this was it.
This was, this was when we entered the dark timeline.
We stopped talking.
I like that.
That's an arc.
That's an arc of the show where foreskin just kept coming up.
It was.
It kind of was an era.
Yeah.
It's, it's in the, it's in the, it's in the, the, the early late stage, whatever.
There should be a timeline made of all the stupid PCP arcs.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
With like over overlapping like, like lions that denote like when a thing was happening.
They all like kind of overlap with each other.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
There's like times when.
Along the timeline.
Yeah.
Like, like, oh, Final Fantasy 7 came out and then like seven episodes were about that.
Yeah, true.
Pokemon was a thing for years.
I guess it was, it wasn't like every episode though, but there was constant.
It just kept coming up.
Like every other episode.
It just kept coming up and kept coming up.
Next one is called Guerrilla Sausage.
Three, two, one, go.
Yix Studios is super fucking gay.
And so is Ben St.
But at least he's cool.
Also, isn't eating Guerrilla meat basically just the stones throw away from cannibalism
or am I just like.
That's what I, that's why I feel like it's gross.
When I learned that like, oh yeah, people hunt Guerrillas for bush meat.
I was like, God, imagine eating a Guerrilla.
I would feel really fucked up about it.
I mean, yikes.
It's like you get a hand and it's a human hand looking thing, but it's a Guerrilla.
I mean, if the only thing we should be hunting Guerrillas for is for monkeys paws for their
fingers to curl when we make ill advised wishes about foreskin.
Next voicemail is called Sad but surprisingly enticing boy.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey Ben, I was watching your old lectures again.
You know how it is needed some background noise when Jack hammering my cock to incest head high.
Absolutely.
And I noticed something.
I couldn't help but ask myself whoever allowed you to exist on this astral plane without a beard.
Don't get me wrong.
Today, you're a pretty boy.
Wouldn't say no to messing with that chocolate starfish, but back then you looked like one
of those dudes that import dirt poor Thai women to date on reality TV shows and bragged to
them about their 2009 Subaru.
Anyways, say I love her and stop talking about Drixie all the time.
Don't burn all the bridges.
Save up that spy for the eventual RV fallout.
Puts me kisses.
That's a fair point.
No, what I said about Josh and how he needs to have a beard is like true not to the same
extent, but it's also true of me.
I looked just much better with a beard, which I'm growing it out again now.
It's coming along.
Yeah.
Next voicemail is called Hi Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, so a couple quick questions about Nate.
So his content can't shit.
Is that why he left the podcast and is not coming on?
He's focusing on that.
But also aware of the league and their shenanigans.
He is aware of the league.
He knows of them.
Yes.
Oh, did he talk to him about it?
He meant he was sort of jokingly mentioned it.
Yeah.
He's aware.
But I, I can't, I can't comment any further.
I don't know.
We didn't like talk about it at length or anything.
He's just, he's just frozen with fear about the idea.
He's got a chastity like shorts, shorts.
There's no, there's no reason why Nate could, why can't tent would keep Nate from being
on the PCP.
I've said, he just doesn't want to come on for whatever reason.
He just doesn't feel like it.
And that's, that's literally it.
That's all there is to it.
Yep.
Next, next voicemail is called fuck Trixie three, two, one go.
Also, fuck Trixie.
Trixie's a shit.
Yeah, I agree.
Has never made good content.
Didn't involve other PCP members such as Nate and Tom because they're great.
They think that Ben may have done something with Trixie at some point and that may have
been good.
I don't know.
I have to disagree.
A few of her videos in the past were genuinely interesting and informative.
That one about main six's ages.
That one and that one retrospective on the career of the your name guy.
I really liked that one.
So I wouldn't go quite, I wouldn't go quite that far.
So there's a lot of good anime stuff that is now gone.
Yeah, all based.
Next voicemail is called slowly three, two, one go.
Hey, so about like Trixie and again and all that isn't like separating people from their
other relationships and being like, oh, it's us or them isn't that kind of isolation sort
of classic abuse tactic?
Should we be worried at all?
It is.
Yes, it is potentially worried.
I feel like I couldn't do anything from over here.
Some people have speculated that what's going on over there is like really dark and I don't
feel like there's any like strong evidence for that.
No, I've looked for it.
It can't really be ruled out as a possibility.
I haven't seen anything that's like isolating from like clips of like Riley shouting at
Digi on live stream.
So telling you shut the fuck up.
I don't know if that's like indicative of anything other than Riley just being a loud
mouth.
It's hard to say.
I would say it isolating from other social groups is an abuse tactic, but it's just it's
just hard to say like to what what is the intent here?
Like who is who is doing this to who?
I don't think it's that much of a stretch to think this Trixie just is self isolating
from other groups because she likes this new one better for whatever reason.
So yeah, who knows.
Next voicemail is called what a tragedy.
Three, two, one, go.
The real tragedy of this whole scenario is that the alias Digi bro was just so phonetically
satisfying to say and the only people who would really say it nowadays are those who
are out of the loop or intentionally trying to misgender her.
And as neither of those people, what am I supposed to do?
Just sit in the corner of my room with Digi bro to myself in repetition until I meet my
daily quota, hoping that someone else takes the name for themselves.
I'm well that other guy took the name.
So you can call him that now.
You problem solved easy.
It's kind of a little shame that it's like it is a shame.
It was a good name.
It sounded good.
Yeah, I agree.
Next voicemail is called Jebediah goes international three, two, one, go.
Hello, this is me, Jebediah Pritikson.
I don't really know what to ask today.
Because did you hear about this news about fucking pooping?
You know.
We're having up to 100,000 troops on the border of Ukraine.
I can't say that I did.
Sir.
Give me your education.
Shut up.
Bye.
Fuck you.
I like the sort of like aesthetic of Jebediah Pritikson just sort of slumber like slumbering
and lumbering into like a voice call.
He's like not prepared for it.
She's like, oh, hey guys, like he walked into a room and just saw us.
He knows what he's doing.
He knows exactly what he's doing.
Next voicemail is called Jebediah can't find the them three, two, one, go.
Oh, so I gotta say I don't know how to find the leak.
I guess.
What?
And I'm not as gay as them, so.
No, please.
How to find the leak?
What?
Do you know what he's saying?
Let me do it again.
We got a hurry, by the way.
We're at like, we've only got 10 minutes before we hit the three hour cap.
Oh, fuck.
That was our asses not to go over.
Oh, shit.
Is this the last page?
All right.
Keep going.
Yeah, we're on the last page.
Next one is called a shambling zombies.
Last coherent words to this world.
Three, two, one, go.
I've heard that one before.
Yeah.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
Okay, got it, got it.
Next one is called canned tent.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, everybody, and welcome to this week's episode of canned tent.
And that's going to do for this week's episode of canned tent.
Thanks for the voicemail.
Next one is called.
You didn't even on can it.
Next one is called give diss track emotional warning bad word piss.
Three, two, one, go.
So on the last episode, you said that give should have a diss track done against her
because it, it builds character.
That's right.
I thought I should build my flex my creative muscles and try my hands.
So here I go.
Okay.
All right.
One, two, one, two, three.
My name is me and I'm here to say I'm going to diss you give in a big way.
You are a girl on the internet.
There's nothing on void.
You talk about things on this podcast with your friends.
You make funny jokes and cool art.
I've got something to say to you.
You suck.
That's my diss.
How does it feel?
I'll bet it feels like this.
Oh, there's the bad word.
Okay.
That's it.
Thank you.
Thanks for the voicemail.
Next one is called Noi to good three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben, you know what Trixie's opinion on Noia is?
No.
Next one is called a good idea three, two, one, go.
All right.
This one's for free.
PCP DND.
Yeah.
We floated this idea.
I wanted to do one at Radcon.
We just didn't have time and it didn't happen.
What if we just did DND instead of a regular podcast for a few weeks?
Okay.
Or like alternating.
We could try that.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let's do that.
Let's just fucking do that.
Why not?
I'm down.
I'm fucking into it.
Yeah.
I always wanted to do like a DND with the PCP and it just has never materialized.
It takes so much, it takes work though is the thing.
And I hate work.
Yeah.
And I guess if we're just two of us, it would be like, well, I do this and then you do that.
You can't do it with just two people.
We would need Tom in there.
We would need regular attendance because you can't.
I mean, you can sometimes miss a sesh, but you shouldn't be missing seshes.
Next one is Margar.
Oh, there we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Margar here.
As it turns out, I play a lot of Dungeons and Dragons, both as a dungeon master and a player.
And I have a number of opinions about some of the stuff you guys have talked about in terms of DND.
Namely, Ben and your opinion on players asking to make roles.
I think that a core aspect of Dungeons and Dragons is using the mechanics and abilities that your characters have to solve problems.
And I don't think that it's inherently a bad thing to ask DM to, you know, use your abilities in that way.
But it might just be a case of you having a different expectation of the game than it is sort of capable of providing.
And there are a number of games that you might prefer that aren't as sort of mechanically focused that I could maybe recommend to you.
Because there's a lot of games out there and they're all pretty different.
I generally do like role-playing games that are less mechanical than DND.
So I do think if you like the mechanical part of it, then maybe there is just a difference in expectation.
I really do think, though, that like, I really do think it's, I mean, you can have your own opinion,
but it's not the way that I want to play is not to be being like, hmm,
my character has seven ranks in a climb.
Hmm, can I make a climb check to ascend to heights of dazzling intellect? Hmm, DM, please?
You know, that's stupid.
A terrible example, but hopefully you understand what I'm saying.
Next voicemail is called Based Ben Believer, 3, 2, 1, go.
You know, I never thought it would happen, but a lot of people have been saying it lately and it's really true.
Ben truly is the most based member of the PCP now.
Thank you. I know.
All it took was Nate the Voo, Mage, Munchy, and Nate leaving the podcast, Tom not being on half the episodes,
and Gib being milk toast and never having a stance on anything.
And so that leaves Ben as the only person with actual informed opinions on things.
And just by default, he is the most based person on the podcast and it's just incredible, you know?
I really think the transition from Old Ben to Communist Ben was really rough and there were some real lows there.
He was maybe only slightly better than Munchy, you know, in the PCP member rating.
But overall, I mean, on the other side of it, Ben is more based than ever,
and I couldn't be happier for it, keeping based.
I have stances on things.
Thanks? I don't, I don't, I don't feel complimented.
No, fuck you. Fuck this guy. No.
No, fuck you.
Next voicemail is called Based Joker 3 3 2 1 Go.
When I tell my friends that I listen to the PCP, they say, hey, that's pretty based.
But when I tell my friends that I listen to the PCP, well, suddenly I'm cringe.
But see, that's the thing you people don't understand. I'm, I'm not cringe.
I'm just ahead of the turd.
Wait, that's it. That's the rebrand, the PussyPoo.
No.
Yes, that's it.
The PussyP, the PCP.
He said PCPoo, but I say why not change both?
The P-
Twice?
The P-E-E-C-P-O-O.
Perhaps.
Also, I should, I will say, I keep forgetting that this guy exists, and then he makes a voicemail as really, really good.
Voice Grail, I think.
Voice Grail for Based Joker?
Yeah, Based Joker.
You know what? He's had too many hits. I'll give him.
A Based Joker ascends to the Voice Grail. Congratulations.
First in a while, first in a while, but I think he's earned it.
Yeah.
Next voicemail is from Cross, and there's a YouTube link, and the link is to a video of like a, of like a, a no, like a, like a synth music setup.
Playing some synth sounds.
Three, two, one, go.
My friend Jake Ellis made this sick-ass space shanty.
It's like a sea shanty, but it's a space shanty.
Listen to it, please. He deserves it.
Here's a clip of it.
Pretty based. Pretty based.
Pretty good.
I guess I'll put, um, I guess I'll put the link in the description.
Yeah, in the show notes.
In the show notes.
Jake Ellis space shanty number one.
Sounds pretty based.
Next voicemail is called Put, Put, Prince.
Three, two, one, go.
Uh, third week now, I've had some ideas, but I don't think they're funny enough, even though I know these things aren't the highest.
But instead of like leaving a three second voicemail, I'll put my phone in and I'll leave it in song.
So, uh, kick it, Bonnie.
One, and a two, and a three.
This is...
I mean, as a big Simpsons fan, I have to appreciate it.
I appreciate the reference. It's classic.
Cool, man.
Nice voicemail. You're ascending the ranks.
Uh, uh, adding music is the first step towards becoming a classic voicemailer.
Historically speaking, it's true.
Next voicemail is called Really Quick Question, three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP, it's me, Max Clutch.
I just wanted to get a quick...
This guy makes me nervous.
Is that Trixie?
See you next time, boys.
Okay.
What was the question?
I don't know.
Is that Trixie?
So Trixie, and he just gunned it.
The question is, is that Trixie?
The real question is, was he driving towards or away?
That's what I assumed a hit and run, but we just don't have enough information.
Next voicemail is called Fuck PCP Callers, three, two, one, go.
Alright, so I've started to catch back up with the PCP episodes as I rage at online Smash Bros.
And I just finished what I hope is the last of the Tommy J arc.
And this got me thinking about a rant that I've had brewing in my head for a while.
I fucking hate the PCP voicemail callers.
Why do they think that anyone gives a fuck who they are?
The sheer you on these people is insane.
I think it all started back with Riddle My Ass Batman.
Because when he became a recurring caller, everyone thought,
Ooh, her there, I'm gonna do that.
Except that they couldn't do that because they aren't creative or funny
and they don't have any sort of production value.
And then Samurai was the second wave of this.
And now all these obnoxious Kretans tried to rip him off.
You know why the Samurai works and you're a larping dozen, you fucks?
It's because the Samurai didn't make it about him.
It was always about Ben stealing the Skrull.
It's like if I felt the need to leave a voicemail every week going,
Hey guys, remember me? I'm fuck Dibuster.
I said that Dibuster is bad. Isn't that so cool how I said that Dibuster is bad?
By the way, I also write novels and draw.
That's so unique. You guys should follow me because I'm a one of a kind person.
And also please have me on the podcast.
No, no one gives a shit.
Anyway, I'm not actually that upset.
But hearing Ben rage at Tommy J was pretty funny.
Okay, then yeah, that should be the end of the Tommy J arc.
I think there is a lot of truth in what this guy is saying.
Yeah.
Yeah, like the whole league of Nate fuckers is kind of funny.
Nate isn't here to feel the brunt of the tidal wave of all of these funny things.
Yeah, but that's not that's not their fault.
No, but like some of the characters are just just explicitly made for that purpose.
And there's multiple of them.
Yeah, but each one is its own gimmick and it's it's just there for one call and then it's dropped.
Yeah, so I don't hate them or anything.
But like I feel like that that joke has sort of run its course.
I bet. Yeah, I mean, what more can you really do with it? I guess.
I guess we'll see.
The next voicemail. I think the last voicemail.
Thank Christ is called Mr. Suck and Fuck 3, 2, 1.
Speak and go.
Trixie, my golden princess.
I have such wonderful plans with her.
She still has her decadent vimosis.
No stop, please.
That excess for skin.
That hollow poop of blood.
This is like being in a fucking haunted house.
You feel it with strawberry ice cream.
Top it with sprinkles and chocolate syrup.
I'm getting hungry.
And then I'm going to...
Yeah, go, go, go, go, go.
Get it. Get it, Mr. Suck and Fuck 3.
Itadakimasu.
Gross. Terrible.
Oh God, why? Why does it end like this?
Decadent. Well, I think that's a great note to go out on when you say.
Yeah, I think we fucked up.
We went over the limit.
Eleazar, just maybe you can snip out a minute here or there or two to get it under the three hours.
Sorry, fucked up, fucked up. So sorry.
Okay, that's it. Patreon.com slash the procrastinators bonus episodes.
Speakup.com slash PCB voicemail.
I think that's it.
Get the I Have COVID shirt and goodbye.
Goodbye.