How are we gonna read the Super Chats at the end?
Hello everyone. Welcome to episode 100 of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
One zero zero, one zero zero, one zero zero, one zero zero, one zero zero, one zero zero,
one zero zero, one zero zero, one zero zero, one zero zero, one zero zero, one zero zero,
Okay, alright, I'm the best guy ever. Today we have with us Hippocrite. Hello!
Why don't you wear his tiny hat?
It's me! You better fucking believe this is the most exciting podcast you've ever seen in your fucking life!
Have your ass glow to that fucking scene!
I blew out my voice with this shit and you're gonna fill the full brute force of my fucking spiritual cock up your ass pretty soon, bitch!
We've got Digi, bro!
Hey, it's me! It's the one! You know the one! He's the Bippity Boppity with the Flippity Flappity!
And, uh, Tom's next to me.
Tom Oliver, everybody!
I don't even know what to say in response to that. What's a Flippity Flappity?
I'm getting bad images from that, too.
You know what's a Flippity Flappity?
Yeah, we've got some ideas. Mr. Ben Saint!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Woohoo!
Woo! What a rush!
And let's have a shout out to our cameraman, Victoire, behind the cameraman. Yeah!
There he is!
Yeah!
Woo!
The layers! The layers!
The layers.
Alright, today's episode, everybody, is a very special episode.
Ben is not in shot.
Hey, help! Help!
Today's episode of the Progressives Podcast.
Friendship!
Okay, Urban Dictionary.
No!
Who's got a working phone, because my phone is not working.
We're going to urbandictionary.com.
Give me everyone one of your phones.
We wrecked the internet before.
We have had, I apologize to everyone who's been waiting.
We've had some technical difficulties.
Oh, and by the way, that's a good chance to say,
if you're thinking of super chatting, feel free to do so,
and we encourage you to wait until the end,
because we're not reading, we're not distracting ourselves,
any of that pedantic fan bullshit.
I got it first.
Until the end of the episode,
when we get to the questions section,
we will be looking at all the super chats we've gotten,
and feel free to send them then,
and we will look at them, and we will evaluate them as we do normally,
because as we all know, your questions are usually trash,
and we don't want to waste everyone's time interrupting the podcast every second.
Don't expect us to reach out at all during this.
Yeah, we're not reading chat at all.
Enjoy that. We'll get back to you at the question time.
What do we got for friendship?
True friendship is not when you go to school,
and hang around with someone,
just because you have no one else to chill with.
It's not calling someone up when you're bored,
because they are fun to talk to.
It's not when you can't think of a birthday gift,
and end up buying your friend a Walmart gift card.
It's not when you have to talk to someone about something.
Oh my, this actually goes on for paragraphs.
True friendship is a group piss.
Yes, absolutely.
Group piss!
We just pulled out our cocks just a few moments ago,
and the yellow snow was as fucking vast as space itself.
And not one of us looked.
And I believe that,
because I wasn't looking or anything to see.
Trust me.
Give me the zoom, dawg.
They can just see the group piss right here.
Oh yeah, there it is.
Group piss!
Look how iconic.
Look how iconic that is.
That's like a fucking Adderwood cover right there.
No, is that not the new banner for the PCP?
Oh yeah!
We just go shot a boomage in there.
That's a good idea.
That actually would be an amazing banner for the PCP.
It would be.
Nate, what are we talking about?
We're just going to talk about friendship.
Have you ever even had a friend?
What are your experiences?
What friendship is.
And first of all, how it's not real.
It doesn't exist.
As most people use it.
Okay, all right. Here's the real thing.
Let's get started.
It's already something.
Please edit in the entirety of the weird
utilitarian podcast right now.
Cut the episode.
Good night, everybody.
We got ahead of five minutes. It's gone.
Okay, here's the thing.
Here's where I want to start with a concept of friendship.
I care about you all and I enjoy working with you.
But here's the thing. If you fucking betray me,
I will drop you with the drop of a hat.
At any moment, you could do it.
And I will drop you without a moment's
hesitation.
So the point I'm getting at here is how
this is kind of ties in with love.
Because love and friendship are pretty related.
Unconditional love, unconditional friendship
is highly immoral.
And I don't think anyone should ever do it.
And that's my foundational principle
when I'm approaching this.
I don't understand why it's immoral.
I understand why maybe it doesn't make
sense.
No, it is immoral because it encourages bad behavior.
And if you have the wisdom to recognize
that you can avoid doing that,
then you should do it. If you're just ignorant
and you don't realize you're doing something wrong,
then that's not immoral.
True Friends is putting up with this.
No.
Alright.
We'll get into all this.
If you keep applying friendship,
there's no connection.
But friendship isn't about that.
Friendship is that spicy look you get in your eyes
whenever you look at the male form
and you just know it's not getting sweaty
and starting to heat up.
And you know, whenever I look at your
eyes, hold on.
Whenever I look at guys,
shift away, I'm thinking about something else.
Yeah.
Nate, friendship is real.
You started off saying it wasn't real.
That was his real.
That was his look.
It's not real like tables and chairs are real,
but it's real like, I don't know,
the law is real.
That's true.
Sort of.
It's real in the way that like,
math is real.
We all pretend that we have our own benefit.
Yeah, friendship is real like math is real.
Because we all agree on it.
Friendship is real like magic is real.
I mean, all fucking know magic is real.
No one's debating that.
We were talking about this before.
I want to share everyone.
I decided
relevant to this story.
I think it's a story that you all will enjoy immensely.
I was telling everyone in the car.
It's kind of personal.
But I've chosen to share
because I think it's mostly making fun of me.
So hopefully you'll all appreciate it.
Shrap fucking in for this.
This is unreal.
This is no peak weird utilitarianism.
I apologize to everyone already.
Everyone involved.
So,
I have a girlfriend now.
And that's pretty cool.
Nate's always bringing up his girlfriend in the fucking car.
Sorry.
Here's the thing though.
So the issue of
love
eventually came up.
As it tends to do.
Love came up.
And what happened was
when the first thing I
looked at the table,
there was questions of like,
how come you haven't said I love you
and stuff.
I had to be honest and be truthful
and say, listen, here's the thing.
I don't believe love exists.
That's where I'm coming at.
This is so uncomfortable.
I know.
I apologize.
Chemicals in your brain.
Here's the thing.
We had to define the term love
before I was comfortable saying that I love you.
We had to define the word.
We had to define our terms.
Which I think is how you should have
conducted every relationship with everyone.
And your definition is what everyone would consider love to be.
I know.
But it was really important to me that we established that word.
Clearly had to happen as Nate had to sit down
with his girlfriend and be like, okay,
we need to establish her so let's go to
urbandictionary.com.
Look, look.
This is just the thing.
I had to establish what love was
and what I was willing to say because
like I said before,
I don't want people to think when I say that I love them
that I love them unconditionally.
That's really important because even if my fucking son one day
is gay,
he'll be out of it.
Music is a lot like love.
It's all a feeling.
And it fills the room from the floor of the ceiling.
That's what I think about.
We all understand this.
I took some magic clowns to tell us.
Friendship is real a lot like how magics are
a lot like how magnets are real
and mostly aren't.
Scientists tell us they are.
I haven't had a serious girlfriend in quite a while
and I wanted to be quite clear
because I believe it is the most
moral way to live.
You know that picture somebody tweeted of like
the robot body with the human head that said like
this is peak the utilitarian body.
Sorry ladies, this is what peak ethics looks like.
That's kind of how I feel about like my moral system.
I wanted to be clear
that when I say
what I mean is
what I mean is that
I enjoy your company immensely.
I want to share my life with you.
I want to live together.
That's just what it is.
No, but I wanted to be clear
that what I'm not saying is if you betray me
that I will stay by you.
If you betray me.
You're nate.
I say the word
I want to make sure that it's clear
that I'm talking about a bumblebee that is
yellow and black.
I think one of the major problems
of this day and age is that people
are using the same words but talking about
different things.
I agree with that.
That's a different subject, but I agree.
I honestly think it's, I believe
that what you did there was a good idea
and I think I would have done the same
if I had doubts about the like
you know if I had thought there was a possibility
nate confirmed to doubting that this is a very
stupid girlfriend.
If I wasn't sure that we thought
that it meant the same thing, you know
I didn't like
ask but I had the sense
before I was willing to
I had a sense that it was
the same understanding before I was
like you know, Michelle would just walk home
and she was like, yeah, yeah, I love
getting unnecessary work and getting
shit on by my boss and I love knocking the promotion
that I was promised. I sure love that
and you're like, oh, maybe she thinks love is something else.
Maybe she doesn't know that love is a good
feeling. Well, like
some of us have
really hardcore autism and we
need these things.
Some of us?
It's a hundredth episode.
It doesn't do to be talking with
words that like people disagree
on the definitions. So I'm giving you
shit.
In principle, I'm okay with like, okay, well
let's settle what we're talking about.
Love is honestly my least favorite word
in the world because love is the most
loaded word.
Aside from God, love
can mean literally anything.
And friendship
is similar. Friendship is similar. When some people
say they're friends, they mean one thing.
When other people say they're friends, it's totally different.
What are you saying, Gib? Nothing. Nothing about
what? About what? I just said
my little pony friendship is similar.
I didn't
absorb the lessons from my little pony friendship
was magic well enough. So I need to go to
UrbanDictionary.com
We've already extrapolated friendship
to love and gone to the
origin point of is love
real or not.
We've already been
an awkward fly on the wall.
But here's the thing though.
As
is defined by
our
explanation of the definition of the word
love, I love all of you guys.
But that's the thing.
There you go.
That's how it is. Love only means what it means
in my head that I have not explained to you.
Don't you fucking get it, Nate? That's the problem
with words inherently. Everyone has their own
definition of words that exist just in your head
and hopefully it's the same as everybody else's
but we can't guarantee that. She's on his fucking
phone. Just fucking read the chat
and Michelle is in there losing her shit.
Oh no!
Is she mad? Is she mad at me?
No, she's just incredulous and screaming
for the help.
Michelle, I'm sorry.
We're not reading chat.
I just wanted to make sure we're not fucking anything up.
I was actually going to ask you to check.
If things start dying, I want to know.
I also wanted to encourage people to like the camera setup
I'm sure they're loving it.
Let's pull this back. No one wants to hear about
your fucking gay awful bullshit anymore.
We've already done an entire episode on it.
We can tuck your ideas
into the shallow grave they deserve.
We can tuck our ideas into the
between our asshole and pussy.
And to our both asshole and pussy.
Yeah, that's right.
Alright, friends.
How would you say
friends?
Friendship is what we mean
when we say what anime
is about.
Let me just fucking give us an actual conversation time.
Please God. Everybody,
how important would you say that
friends are to your life?
Like, how much of your time
goes to friends? How much of your thoughts go to friends?
Well, how important
this is a distinction.
How important or how much do they take up?
Both of those facts.
The important level is like
8, but usage is like
6.
So friends don't take up as much
of your time as how much you've been thinking about them?
Well, no, that's not what I mean.
Thinking about them
I put that into the 6th category.
How important are they
because how much I like friends
and how much I like the concept of friends
and how much I want to be near friends
but I don't really think about
what's been doing.
I really feel like
human existence
is like you do things to survive
and then when you're surviving
there's not so much
we're social animals
so social
relationships with people
either a significant other
or people who you just want to spend
a time with, which could also be
a significant other, but sometimes it isn't.
Are you making a distinction there between the two?
Well, one of them you fuck and the others are just friends.
Yeah, yeah.
But you can be friends with a significant other as well.
And let's do this back.
We are social animals.
None of us are like Nate, we all feel love
and friendship.
You guys are just too cowardly
to understand that none of that shit's right.
Yeah, that's right.
That's what I'm saying.
Listen, I've watched
a lot of Rick and Morty.
I'm fully blacked out.
On the words though.
We agree with you, it's just we don't care
talking about it into such detail.
But detail is important.
I think what Hippo is sort of touching on
is that there are a lot of people who
like... Give me a frame!
Help!
There he is.
When you made a distinction between
a significant other.
Some people
feel...
A lot of people just want to fuck
and so they find a significant other
less based on whether they are good friends
and more based on whether they are good fuck.
You gotta put up with them
so you can get that.
And other people have people they like to fuck
who are also their friends.
I understand the distinction between
someone who you're not having sex with
that means it's much harder to put up with them.
I feel pretty passionately about the connection
you have.
This is where it comes
from the whole thing of
bros before a hose for example
is a pretty...
And bros is gender neutral
and bros is gender neutral.
That is true. I generally feel that
just out in the world
there's a feeling that love between
guys is sort of a... it's purer
than the love between a man and a woman.
Because men are more complete.
No, that's not what I'm saying.
When a man is interested in a woman
99.9
basically 100% of the time
he wants to fuck her.
I've told her all this in detail.
Imagine all the lectures I do on this
I give to her nightly as she tries to sleep
so she can.
She said in the chat that the conversation Nate was describing
was four hours long.
Oh my god.
That's right.
It was just a big circle.
It was a big circle.
Wait, if it was four hours long
your Kingdom Hearts discussion was five hours long.
Yeah.
No, it's true.
You're not wrong.
I was the only person who answered.
How much has been thinking about friends
and how much you give your life to friends?
How much do you have a bad romance?
Ooh.
Wait, you went woo
and I forgot the question.
Do you like your friends?
Yes.
When I was young, a teenager
I was like very socially awkward
and friendship was like scary.
And friendship was witchcraft.
Meeting new people and going from
primary school to secondary school
nobody came with me so I was like
a bunch of new people
and I'm a stupid idiot
so I didn't bother to try and make friendships
but later
it just
you come to a point where you realize
that you're much more important than
you would have otherwise thought
because you think in your head
oh, it's just
stupid high school politics
it's like
you have to be cool and you have to be this and that
and it's not about being popular
it's just about
having meaningful relationships
that fulfill you
and the reason I realized this
the moment this crystallized in my head
is when I was playing The Sims
I was dedicated to getting that guy
all the skills so that he could get the big jobs
and the career ups
but I couldn't be bothered to call people
on the phone and have parties and stuff
and he got so depressed he couldn't do anything
I was like oh god, oh it's too real
that's exactly the real life
So did you set it out in your life to make new friends
or something like that? I set it out in my life to be better than The Sims
Okay, excellent
By the way I just want to zoom out Victor
I just want to let everyone in the audience know
that all the people on this couch are doing episodes of the PCP
and everyone on that couch is looking at their phones
zoning out and also zoning out
even harder and doing nothing
You aren't supposed to be reading the chat!
If I don't read the chat
how will I know if the fucking stream is going okay?
Re-checking constantly
Re-checking is the reasonable thing to do
I resent the fact that you think I'm zoning out
I'm listening attentively
I heard that Lady Gaga reference
Get fucked
This is the age team
Yeah, yeah, yeah
You asked him a question
and we were giving him time
and also I set up this in a way that it would go around
all six of us one by one
to discuss these two
I'm not listening to any of this and you shouldn't either
Once again, Munchy James Johnson
is fake news
Okay, well, so Gib,
again, I guess what Munchy is asking
is how much do you depend on
and feel the need to work with your friends?
More than I used to
I feel like friendships are important
to continue to work on
as a thing you have to try and do
and hopefully they try and do it as well
and if they don't then it becomes
get better friends, I guess
Oh, go on
No, no, I was done
Relationships and of course friendship
because friendship and relationships are always work
and work is not a bad thing
that should be treated with any sort of
I have to check into my nine to five
work is just something that you put in time to
work in the sense like art work
more so than work work
I think it was in general
Productive work
I think there needs to be
invented another word
that means that, what you're saying
because work
is like production
there are people who will use it
to mean like my favorite thing to do
and people who use it to mean my least favorite
thing to do and those need to be two different words
because like creating art when I say
like oh I love working
I mean like I love working
on my art
but when I say fuck I hate working
I hate going to a job
You go the stuff you don't like work
and the stuff you do like funk
That's good
So anyway, friendship is
things that you need to work on continuously
to reap the rewards from them
if you leave them there then you will not reap rewards
and work can just be talking to them
or it can just be, this does not have to be
a daily thing but you have to put in work
to get benefit from any sort of relationship
whatsoever
That's generally true
and I guess to get to my answer to this question
Friendships
are important to me obviously
since I'm involved with the PCP so much
and stuff
You have to push your complex feelings and nebulous feelings
into a specific number from one to ten
Okay, I'll try to do that but I was just going to say that
on the other hand
I have noticed in myself
that every friend who is no longer useful to me
I have abandoned
That means you're not gaining reward back from your work
That's true
If I called up a friend from my hometown
they'd be willing to talk to me
and just chat them up
I don't talk to my old friends
from
previous places I've lived that much
and it's not because I don't like them
it's just because
we can talk once in a while and catch up
but we can't
we can't hang out anymore
That's true
The way I see it
Friends for the most part
are people who you want to do things with
and you can zoom in on me
I'm going to talk for a little bit
Oh, which is
like changing the universe over there
Try to increase the audio
I feel like
friends are people who you want to do stuff with
and who you would rather do things
with them than do it alone
I hate going
I hate like
Yeah, why not
It moves
Don't put that fucking cup there
It's gonna spill
You might fucking special stimulate tea
Yeah, don't shout out
That was so distracting
I forgot what I was like
Friends are people
I don't want to do this shit by myself
I'd rather do it with somebody
So let me call up my pals
and have them come over and shit
But then it has to be people who you want
to do the same things as them
and I think that inevitably if that falls apart
the friendship falls apart too
It's just like
I love all my friends from back home
They're all great people
They're all people who I respected
who I wanted to do things with
but eventually they all got into street fighter
and cars
The Disney property
Hell yeah, they were really into cars
Fucking Lightning McQueen beds
in every household
I had to hear so many fucking
truck impressors
What the hell is that guy's name? The Larry the Cable Guy truck?
The Major
Did they actually get into
Pixar's car?
Yeah, they fucking did
You should have seen it when Cars 3 came out dude
They were going fucking ballistic
You should have seen the line outside
Fucking planes promo night dude
Fucking boss in the first night
planes release bro
Anyway
So yeah because those guys
do those things
they would come over to my house every weekend
because everybody hung out in Victor's room for like
years and my friends would
all come over and they just sit there
and play street fighter all night and I would come down
and I'd be like hey what's up guys and I'm just like
oh yeah I don't like street fighter
and that much so I just go back
to my room and gradually that led to like
well once Victor moved away
like that wasn't the hangout spot
anymore and I literally have not seen most
of my friends since then except for
at a New Year's party
but like yeah it's like
it doesn't really matter that I like those people
if we're not going to do anything together
then there's just nothing
there's no like
I can still call them my friends
but I feel like friends has more of an active
role to me
Victor get over here with that fucking thing
this group itself
to me
what are you fucking doing
what's happening
you are the cameraman
zoom the fucking camera on me
alright tell you Victor
I appreciate your reference
love does not exist
love does not this group itself
would at least to some degree
definitely have drifted apart
if it were not for me saying guys
we need a podcast to hold us together
therefore the potty the purpose
of the procrastiners podcast
really unironically was to keep
this group together that is what it was
made for that was my original intention
because everyone's getting away from pony
no one was going to be doing the same thing
people were splitting up
people used to love MLP to keep us together
unironically
for sure
Ben stop joking around
I can't stop goofing
I can't stop screaming
but it's true I mean look at you right now
it's a stimulant T
stimulant T
look right now
this group itself is pretty
varied and red pilled of course
Ben is just a comic guy for the most part
he makes videos sometimes
but he's kind of doing something
he's a pokey tube
it was a big mistake to choose pokey tube
for MLP
you know I don't know whatever
like Digi's hardcore anime stuff
I dabble in that and other stuff
Tom does his specific type of videos with the 3D stuff
and the tech reviews he was doing
much is like a draw guy who didn't really have a defined role
recently
the point is we all do different stuff
and the PCP was a uniting thing
that kept us friends
and of course we're in the same group chat
but we've already seen some of this
when people have more shit going on in their life
they'll show up in the chat less
it's perfectly natural
so to have something
if there's someone
PSA to everybody out there
if you want to stay friends with someone
and you're afraid of drifting apart
evil way
you need to fucking put in work
evil can work
evil is pretty good
but if you're trying to get married
because you're afraid of someone leaving you
and for only that reason
for example I would consider that an immoral thing to do
if you're trying to keep someone with you
and they're like hey man you're not treating me good enough
you're like oh how about we just get married
a guy who does that to a woman
because he's afraid of her abandoning him
I think it's being kind of immoral
I gotta give credit
both to Nate and Munchy
for the fact that you guys are
I can tell
because I've kind of disappeared
I don't mind melded with someone
he's been mining at night a lot
I'm always mining at night
you need to stop
PSA do not mine at night
do not
mine at night
I'm fucking telling you
you have to stop that shit for your own fucking good
like all your fucking bones
we're currently working on legislation
to allow us to come to your house
to inspect your graphics card
if you're mining cryptocurrency at night
or anything else in Minecraft I don't care
it's gotta be stopped
I'm gonna have to get creeper
on your fucking $5,000 graphics card
and blow that shit to smithereens
back to digit
don't mine at night
because of the fact that I'm kind of
just like mind melded
some kind of
what's it called in Rick and Morty
the fucking bird person
he's like an intense spirit bond
or something like that
I'm in one of those things
I don't really show up in the chat that much
because of the fact that most of the stuff
I used to talk to you guys about
I just talk to the person I have in person
which I prefer
in person interaction is always better
and if I can meet you guys in person
that's the way I'd prefer to just
you don't need to know what's up with me on a day to day basis
we'll meet every three months
and just talk about all of it
and do a bunch of fun shit
you've not really done that though
we have
I've met you
literally the two of you every couple of months
for like the last year
we have not talked about
what you've been doing
like only recently have I ever even heard
of some of the ideas you've done
oh you mean like creatively
all new
all the shit I've told you here is like brand new
I guess Munchy's making a point that he feels
it's a little bit less
he feels that there's a lot here
what I'm trying to say is that you guys
have been the ones trying to make sure
that I don't fall completely away
because I routinely get messages from Nate and Munchy
like just making sure I know
what the fuck is going on
because I wasn't a part of any of the planning
for Radcon 3
so I barely knew what was happening
kickstart jail everyone
when we were going to go to Boston
when we visited back in
the double date times 2 plus 1
yeah the double date times 2 plus 1
when that was going on
like that morning
it was Christmas morning when I was supposed to drive out
and it was like a huge snow storm
and I wasn't sure if I was like comfortable
driving six hours in it
and I was like I was not sure how much fun
we were actually going to have because I don't really know what we're doing
those guys might just want to be with their families
they might not really want to hang out more than a couple hours
and we're going to have to be there a whole weekend
so like but then I thought
well maybe Munchy will hang out with me the whole time
I'm sure that'll that had happened
and I don't know but I didn't know anything about Boston
never been there never seen it
I thought it was like I didn't know it was like a huge
fucking metropolis
everyone I tell Boston
to thinks it's like some like weird bum
fuck nowhere place
where it's literally like an insanely important
part of like human history
in my mind Boston
is like I expect it to be like
a cobblestone like London looking
kind of town
we got haven yeah
because it was because Boston got ancient
it's old as fuck so I just assumed
that it's not like we stopped
building it
you have to understand where I am from
we've been making stuff
you've got to understand that where I'm from in Virginia
we literally have like preserved
the old colonies that were
built when we first came
and they're still like that
so I go places like that
like the place I went to college
is like a town that was like 200 years old
and like it just looks
old and cobblestone even though like
obviously people still live there
it's still like a functioning city
so I just kind of imagined Boston that way
but then I got a text
I guess he's the hardest selling title
like that morning before leaving
I got a text from Nate that was just like
Nate did you really looking forward to seeing you
in Boston and I was like well we got to go now
listen to this
listen to this baby boy
he wants to see me
yeah
I wanted to touch that face there you go
oh god
you have no idea where that tongue has been
I have no idea where that hand has been
he's tasting his own tongue
okay but anyway
the point of this is you have to
be able to talk to your friends
and just that smallest amount of encouragement
wasn't enough to fucking get him
up to Boston
and that's completely changed all of our fucking lives
you know right and the snow just happened
to stop right at that moment
so it was like oh the snow stopped
and Nate wants me to go
and it's only 12 so we still have time
or whatever we can make it
and then we did it
and it was great and now we all want to live there
you know a lot of this to me seems to come back
to a fundamental principle about how I live my life
that I talk about a lot
my content shit and it's that I take
complete responsibility for everything
that I have in my life and the things that I want
in my life so I don't
expect any of my friends
to remain my friends
I have no expectation they're gonna do that
unless I make myself
valuable to them and like helpful
and positive in some way
no matter how long you've been friends with someone
they don't owe you
nobody owes anyone anything
if you expect
people to want to be your friend
you need like not like
you need to give them shit but like
it needs to be worth their life
they need to get something out of it
not material stuff but like you know
like conversation someone to talk to
someone to feel like they understand what you're talking about
someone who's been with you for a long time
just comfort
like maybe it sounds kind of cynical
you know relationships are built on
like mutual
mutual benefit that people
are to each other that's exactly right
that's just what a relationship is
that cynical
you could read it like
I'm only gonna be your friend if I'm getting something out of it
here's what's important about that though
if you are willing to accept friends into your life
who you don't have expectations for
you don't say like listen
if you are being a real piece of shit
this is not continuing
if you are generous enough with yourself
you are actually doing a disservice to those people
because you're not
you're not giving them barriers to rise to
so they can improve themselves
so that for like I'm a big guy who thinks that
self-improven is the root of all happiness
I'm a big guy
like if we just allow people
like for example that's why I don't like
I don't like enabling people
to just I don't like the idea of like
giving a person a fish instead of teaching them to fish
like obviously I think
moral issue
like if you give them the fish
you are
you're choosing
not to give them the way that's better for them
long term you know you understand what I'm saying here
I'm talking about like
I'm getting really distracted about what's going on behind me here
but something about
something about fucking
I'm losing my goddamn training thought here
what's going on
nobody owes you shit
it is best for you
yourself so that you have more to offer the world
because then you are just you literally
have more value as a person
so if your friends are just pieces of shit
who just placate you and just over and over again
say like everything you do is fine all your fuck ups are fine
like don't worry about it will still be your friends no matter what
they are doing you a disservice
by not holding to a higher standard
which will force you to grow and improve as a person
and if they really care about you
if they're really your friends that's what they'll do
and that's how I approach life there you go
that's how I treat my subs that's how I treat everybody
that's my concept
that's a good twitter video yeah you're right
you know what you're right I should do that
did you touch on something that I want to talk about
because this ties into the age difference
grow lol concept
show the concept we've got going on
right in the background
where you talk about how you prefer
in person meetings
and obviously I agree this is quite nice
well
I feel like
no but
hey that I put the impression
how is that going to read
in the video form
you can't see my
it's also in my knee
that's what we'll tell you
yeah that's what I'm saying
but I get the impression that everyone is very
I mean
chatting online and going into internet calls
is not at all something that anyone
would desire to do
well it's not the ideal
it's not the ideal
but I've lived my entire life having mostly internet friends
because I was an introverted kid
when I was a little babby
just like you are right now
well it's like
here's the thing
with give for example this is really relevant
if we didn't have internet communication
we wouldn't have any communication
it wasn't fucking England so it's all we got
so I don't think it's either
we should always meet in person
or not at all
you take the best you can get
I'm just saying an interesting point
that I've had most internet friends
have any of you had
serious online friends
oh yeah I mean
up until I started having a relationship
that period
of me sort of burning off
my friends from back home
just because again
while I liked them all fine
we weren't doing any of the same shit
so for a while I was just talking to the PCP
pretty much
all the time and then
that was most of my
social interaction
and funnily enough being in the PCP chat
made me stop talking to everyone else on the internet
because I used to have other internet friends
outside the PCP
but it was just that it was so much easier
because there's a bunch of us
and if I told you guys about something
going on we could have a whole
conversation about it and then if I try to tell somebody else
it's like well now I gotta have a whole fucking
second conversation about it
so like to me it was just
kind of like the most convenient social interaction
is to just post in this chat
where all of the people most relevant to me
will see it and if you're not in that group
it's just like too much of a pain
in the ass for me to contact you
to tell you what's going on with me
you know
you can tell me what's going on with you maybe I'll be interested
probably not
but you know
it's a roll of the dice
but you've had mostly
in real life friends right
I mean for me growing up
I usually had one friend
any place I lived that was relatively
close and I did cherish
those friendships but I would move
all the time and lose those friends so like
I'm used to sort of transient
friendships and that's why
a lot of my online friendships
they were just as valid as my offline ones
but they were also just as likely to
just end out of nowhere
yeah
I stopped talking like if I don't
maintain contact with somebody
eventually after a couple of
like you know let's say
six months of not talking to somebody
it feels like do I even still know them
you know and then sometimes
people will come back and they'll try to establish
like Tom there was a while where we just totally
fucking didn't even hear from you
like after the
PCP got formed and I started talking to them
you sort of were hanging out
with like a different click
and really talk to each other until
BronyCon when you met
the rest of the PCP guys and were like oh these guys seem cool
I won't pay them on whatever this is
I don't matter it's fine
this is a conversation
so I'm out of the shot
well now they're together
once you were in there
Victor got the both of them
did you hear this lives
there you go
kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss
kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss
kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss haircut
Well, okay, there's two different things I'm talking about here
One is like actual social media falling like you make content whatever people are gravitate to you
I mean like I met my girlfriend through my videos ultimately, you know
She we connected through what I put like my snapchat info out and we eventually connected
I don't like you and may met the same way. Yeah, you know
It's just it sure is a pretty cool thing that we got all the social media going on. You know I'm saying
Are you going into like
Fans who become friends a little bit a little bit
Yeah, I think there's like a word that we might need for like people who are fans
Well, he said friends fans that you like but aren't technically friends. Yeah, I guess
Like if they rise to just be friends then then you're
This is great come back to this and just I'm saying but did you as an instrument
They say that you feel like after six months. You don't really feel like you know the person anymore
Yeah, you've been much better recently, but I felt that way about you recently
Well, the funny thing is just dropped off the map
The funny thing is about me that I will open my mouth every time something has changed
But nothing has changed like I moved into yeah, okay
I moved into a house
That is in the middle of like nowhere and it basically it's just like well
I'm here for the next year
So I'm just gonna make videos and smoke pot until this year is over
So like there's just nothing new to tell people about it's like I am in the same sort of I'm the same sort of person
I was however my mind state has shifted and that's harder to describe in my mind she's shifting right now
Your gender for you by the way it came up with your gender
Well, you're wondering when you're sober and you're wondering when you're hot
Okay, so would you say that like like now like are you coming out of of the the dark ages would you say
It's really changed I mean he's you know
It's just a it's like I'm here cuz rad cons happening
Yeah, and when rad cons over I'll go back home and I'll put my nose in my work
And that's where I'll be until I move
And then I'll put my nose in my moving and I won't be able to talk to anybody
So I'll be too busy moving and then I won't be able to talk to anybody because I'll be too busy setting setting
You know what my new place then I won't be able to talk to anybody
So I'll be too busy trying to get back to work because I missed all that work from when I was moving
And then I won't be able to talk to anybody for the next year because I'll still be catching up on work for the rest of that
Year, that's what happened the last year. That's why I lost contact
Well, here's a fact. Okay. Here's a here's a utilitarianism type fact
It's just that the financial structure of the PCP was facilitated to encourage friendship
Because it was financially structured by me as a genius to to incentivize people coming back regularly to participate
That was the main goal of it. It's all like percentage based
It's based on people who like come and do the most they are the ones who will acquire the most money, you know
All that it's however much you put in it's how much you get out. That's right. That's that's right
And so, you know basically like guys who show up a lot get you know a good chunk of guys who don't get less
But there's always an incentive to contribute more and because it's all percentage the better the PCP does the better everyone
Does and so basically what I'm getting to is I want to just take a moment to say everyone you're welcome for this friendship
You are welcome. Yeah, I accept your attitude
That's all I've got to say
It's my point
Talk to your friends when you get the chance not you just anyone
I'm so bad at maintaining friendships. I know we're talking about this extensively and talking to my friends
Frame
And look the camera just loves them
Just drink it in
Like it doesn't matter how lonely I am sitting there being the loneliest boy of all and I'll just be thinking and I'll be like
Oh, man, if only maybe I wish I talked to my friends more
But then I'll like think about all the friends that I have and be like no, I bet they don't want to talk to me
I don't really have anything to say to them, so I just won't even bother
Here's the problem then the problem is you are not being smart enough with your brain and here's
You're not being smart enough with your brain in the sense that okay, like
When I think I recognize I recognize that I'm a weak human flawed machine
And I know that this weak human shell
Sometimes will feel loneliness and I need to
Calculate in my plan for how I continue to operate this vessel that I need to account for friendship issues because I will get lonely
So with that which before you get lonely because if you feel lonely you might feel like guilty about reaching out to friends
Like oh, I'm just reaching out to him because he's my friend
But you can trick yourself into thinking that you're actually a good friend by just
Constantly doing little updates with your friends like I don't know checking in with them frequently that way you never
It's like if you eat a lot throughout the day if you want to stay fit
You should eat a lot of vegetables throughout the day
So you don't let yourself get hungry and then you binge and you fuck it up
But just like that you should you should manage you should schedule your friendship a little bit throughout the day
So that you don't let your loneliness build up and then you just feel like a piece of shit
Like the Sims yeah, just talk to your friends when you want to but yeah, but no one wants to do that. Nobody wants to do that
I can't small talk to save my life
Like here at radcon like we're just like constantly just like doing random shit. Yeah, that's how you know dance-off toilet seats comes around
That's right, but like in terms of like online like I can't just be like hey Nate. What's up?
I mean, I never do that. Hey, what's up? I'll never in my life
Okay, I'll post memes all the time all the time sure in the chat when like when there's when there's no like
Purpose that we're like that there's like when there's no like purpose that we're deliberately trying to do
I find it so hard to like maintain a conversation if they're if like it's not going leading towards something
Yeah, go into some end goal. I'm like, I'll just be like what's this? Oh, it's that okay done
Yeah, I agree that it feels like that and I agree that that that is not even a bad thing to feel because did you when me
Knew for started talking. I realized I was not going to get into the pants of this famous person just by asking
Hey, did you have how's it going? Yeah, right?
I scheduled my conversation with you specifically could emotionally manipulate you to being my friend, right?
That's the right way to do it. Yeah, that's how I got into the group. Yeah first place
Yeah, I think like I only talked to digi and Jesse at the time because when I had something to talk about
We all loved just the stuff, but I think I'll share a kind of like weird autism where we want our social
Interactions to all be like plotted and like a game and like everything is like like there's like a stat management
Or like we're trying to envision at least like Vincent in the vapors like everyone stats as we analyze them
Yeah, sort what combination of words will I say to make them like have this impression?
And I completely agree that that is definitely what we all do
But let me just pause it that maybe it shouldn't be that way
Maybe we should try and change it. I the point where we are just normal people. I don't think I don't actually think that way
But here's the thing in my life. I think that's how a lot of our friendships
It's just that in my life overall
I have certain goals
I wish to reach and all I care about is reaching those goals and friendship is a great thing
And that's one of my goals to have good friendships and have good friends
So but my goal is to not put more effort into things that I have to
There's no one has an obligation to talk to anyone
No, there's an obligation to have any friends whatsoever
I just think that it's a nice thing to have and it will help you emotionally physically spiritually and sexually to have friends
Absolutely, I want to know something that is I think a sort of pratfall of it. Why Nate? Why Nate?
I know what they want to say
Oh
What are the pratfalls of
Communicating through a chat room Chris pratfall. What does pratfall mean?
Pratfalls is like a stage fall. Oh, it is. I think so. Yeah, like a pitfall. Do you mean a pitfall?
Like what's the like what Stephen Colbert did?
He's right. A pretfall is a stage fall. That's right. I mean, if I could meet a hero John Oliver once again. Okay, one of the pitfalls
Yes, there you go. Did I get on camera when I was sharing that bit of that tidbit of wisdom?
No, you did not.
Wasted!
Do you know how hard it is to switch between six people?
He's right. Do you know how hard it is to keep my gun in my home studio?
There you go. We got it.
That's a mean. That's a mean.
That's a good one. That's a mean.
Oh no.
I just put it down.
Anyway, what are the pitfalls of communicating through a chat room?
Sometimes you have, you think that you're in there all the time and no one else does.
Because I read every message that gets posted in the PCP chat.
How?
I just always do. I just read the whole thing every time I enter it.
Sometimes there's just a ton.
I mean, if there's like 5,000 messages, I will just skim it and see if it's something I care about.
I'm not going to read all of it no matter what.
But generally, the way I use the internet is just constantly clicking between the same five or six websites over and over again.
That's how everybody uses the internet now.
Unfortunately, but Discord is one of those.
Although I actually had to remove it from my taskbar so I would check it less.
Because I would get so obsessed.
I would just get locked into it for a whole day and I'd be like, this is so bad for productivity.
That's an insanely interesting thing about how you will be able to receive messages
and visually know and understand the conversation that is currently happening or that it has happened.
But no one will know that because you have not typed something into the chat.
It's not like where I can just talk to you and you have to say yes, Munchy.
I know that you're seeing.
I've got a sort of sense of who...
I know Ben doesn't read all the chat because Ben will come in and ask a question about something that was discussed literally a minute ago.
I'm really bad at not reading the chat.
But generally...
Even when we at Ben extensively, he will not look at his messages and his ads or what not.
But generally because the PCP is the only...
There's only a couple Discord groups I'm even in.
It's like the PCP, my Patreon Discord, the PCP Patreon Discord, and a couple that I have muted.
So if I'm opening it, that's the only reason.
I check it so often that most of the time there is nothing new there.
But I do read it probably more than anybody.
But I just don't respond.
So it looks like I'm not there.
Tom, what is the importance of friendship?
How much time does it take up in your life?
How much mental energy?
How much do you care about your friends?
I mean, I care about my friends a lot.
There was a period for a while, like last year, or maybe 2016, where I felt like I fell off the bandwagon with everybody in the PCP.
Just because 2016 was a pretty shitty year for me.
And I remember going into Radcon too.
I was like, I want to actively try and participate more and get back into it and be...
Because it was bumming me out that I wasn't...
And you've taken a way more active role since then, in general.
Yeah, because I just, I don't know, I'm interested in it.
I like being a part of the group, I like helping out, I like doing things.
That's why I was like, I'll go do all the podcast part, because I know how to do it, and somebody has to get it done.
So, no, even my offline friends...
It's weird, because I have a couple offline friends that I've had forever.
And they're like two very different kinds of people, I guess, from our relationships with them.
Because we're saying how friends have to be like...
You have to get something out of it.
One of the friends I have, I kind of don't...
Do you even like hanging out with them or anything?
That depends on the day.
But I've known this guy forever.
Maybe you get a sense of comfort, a sense of regularity.
Something like that, a sense of stability in your life.
It's interesting though, because I have another friend that I've known for probably close to 15 years now.
And we don't have anything really in common anymore.
We're both kind of like nerds and play video games.
That's like a very service level thing, and he lives like four towns over.
But every time we hang out, it clicks.
And we just throw out and just talk shit, whatever, and it's like fucking great.
So, even though we don't have any really common interests anymore,
we still get along really well.
But in terms of friendships and relationships, my favorite is when they're into the same sort of shit I am.
Because I feel like that's so important to me.
This is something that I don't think people who don't create things really get.
That sometimes the friendship is the end goal.
Like, oh, we're just going to go out to the club and do whatever.
And that's the thing. And I'm just like, no.
Well, I mean, that can be fun and all.
Well, it can be. But for me, I don't know.
Because making art and doing things is so central to who I am.
If you can't, at the very least, comprehend that.
It's almost like a deal breaker.
And if you're into that in the trenches with me, it makes it so much more valuable.
Because the biggest part of who I am, you understand.
And we can discuss that on a deeper level.
Friendships are cool and all.
But having friends is not the end goal.
I have end goals of my own that I want to improve.
And you're blocking your own face.
Oh, I didn't even know. Oh, wow, is the camera on?
Yeah, but friendship for the sake of friendship.
That's fine. I'm not saying that's bad.
But a great friendship, I feel like, is something that helps you in your life
as you're pursuing the things that you want to pursue.
And hopefully you're doing the same for your friend.
I would describe my relationship balancing work, artwork, and friendship.
Due to the fact that I feel like you need to live your life in order to create good art.
You need to have moments that are not art.
So I would describe it as almost...
This is going to get really autistic.
And I shouldn't be thinking about like this.
I shouldn't be able to visualize it like this.
And it should just be a normal human thing.
But I'm autistic and it works like this.
I view not working as creating coal ore in Minecraft.
I know exactly what I'm talking about.
You're banking experience.
And then when I go to work, I'm mining that.
You're not mining that.
You're not!
No!
Go on the side!
Thank you!
Yeah, so I get my pickaxe and I mine that shit.
But eventually my reservoirs will deplete.
So I need to go out and live my life.
So I can have stuff to use my art.
And obviously, I just enjoy planting those coal blocks, those diamonds.
I just like it.
I've got the more extreme version of that.
Where I can have a difficulty justifying doing anything
unless I know I can make it into art.
Unless I know...
I'm only mining for diamond.
I'm not going for anything less.
I'm constantly...
The shows I watch are dependent on
do I think I'll be able to make an analysis video.
The people I...
I hang out with you guys because I know
we're going to make videos together.
And it's not going to be...
I usually go for iron and up.
Because it's not really like you can know
that like this specific...
I don't really think of it like, okay, we're going to a movie.
What can I do with this movie?
Because just hang out with your friends.
You might have a conversation and you might see something in your life.
I'm trying to be more like that.
I think it was a big problem in my life that I got that way.
And I do think...
I mean, a big part of what makes a Radcon fun,
like especially this house,
this house has so much random shit
that we've been able to take advantage of
to make art out of.
We know that it's going to be like that.
Shout out to Dan.
Shout out to our boy Dan.
We're coming for your ass.
We're shutting you down.
And the audience won't really know this
because they haven't seen that much of the content we've made.
We've filmed like countless fucking
weird random vlogs
based on the random shit in this house
and what it's inspired us to do.
Can I just remind everyone
what a great fucking idea was
to get the arena?
So, shout out to my boy Gib.
Rest in peace.
Just real quick,
for everyone in the audience,
Radcon 3 is not all live stream let's plays
and vlogs. It's not all that.
There's other stuff. We promise it will be here soon.
It's not all that.
I would hope that people fucking understand
that you have to edit the videos
before they can come out.
But on every fucking live stream,
they're like, wow, another live stream.
We paid $9,000 for this.
And even when the live streams are happening,
there's always like another thing happening.
The whole point of Radcon
is that two things are always happening at the same time
unless we're all in the same video.
Pretty much.
Well, if something happens to you right now,
there's Victor's mining on my fucking CPU
for that cycles.
He's buying PCPine right fucking now, dude.
That's right.
Who's talking?
Ben.
How important,
how much time does friendship take up in your life
and how important is it to you
and how much do you think about it in shit?
Uh.
It's like a dog.
What is wrong with Ben?
He's having a panic attack.
I get panic when I see myself on the screen
because I don't like what I see.
Then why do you ask for the camera to be on your office?
I don't know.
It's a real hedgehog's dilemma
of the camera.
Well, I mean, how much do I think
of friendship? Probably
Seven.
Like a bunch.
I think about my friends
and the people
that I care about
and that inspire me
and I aspire to be like
and everything.
I think about that a lot.
Seven or eight.
How much do I actually interact?
Two.
That's pretty low.
Ben has always been
as long as I've known
as long as Ben's been an independent person
it's been incredibly hard to get a hold of Ben.
Just across the board.
It's always tough.
It's true if you like call Ben with your phone
maybe 50% of the time he'll answer.
Less.
But everything below that
like trying to message him on Discord
and maybe it's just that Ben's lifestyle
has him less tuned into what's going on
than the other types of communication apps.
Well, but
I don't know, tweets, messages
like text messages you won't respond to
is this all part of the same thing?
Tweets, I will
it's like
I'll see them
most of the time I'll see them
and I'll think
okay and then I'll like
think about it for a while
and if I'm still thinking about it
like days later
what I want to say maybe then
if I'm still thinking about it
I'll be like I'll respond to that
and then I'll do it
You know, you were just telling us a story
about how our mother
our dear sweet departed mother
was trying to reach you like yesterday
rest in peace, the funeral was a great time
It was actually here, we had a funeral pyro
and everything
That's what the group piss was on
We had to put out the funeral pyro
somehow
Look forward to that in the behind the scenes
ACP vlog
Very Nate's
And I'm not joking
it will be in there
Anyway
our mother, our dear sweet mother
was trying to reach Ben and called him for days
and eventually
she stopped calling him eventually
Ben called her back days later
and said hey mom can I help you with that
and she says oh no I stopped
I just called Nate and they took care of it
Ben claimed that her little words were
oh I gave up
Yeah
They gave up
Mom's the same way, mom never answers a phone
Only I'm a thousand times worse
No, you just don't know the stats
Mom won't answer her cell phone at home
you have to call the home phone so she picks up at home
and when she's out she's hard to reach
You got to know the tips and tricks
Ben, multiple times
I have woken up
and there will be the little discord red notification
from Benz and I'll click on it
One
and there will be nothing there
so this has happened multiple times
where you've tried to get out of your shell
and talk to me
but then you're like no I can't say hi
I have to delete this
Really? Yeah
Yeah, sometimes
It's way too scary
We're literally every single time
you've been like Ben
you have my full attention for like three hours
How embarrassing
It's fully confirmed
Sometimes I'll spend a lot of time
thinking about a note that I want to send to somebody
or spending a lot of time debating
Do I actually want to commit to talking to this person
like this is going to open up a whole conversation
but once I've sent a message
you know sometimes I will delete it
Sometimes I will delete it
I've deleted these messages a few times
but not very often
I've done it once or twice in my entire life
Yeah, I've only if it's something
I'm fucking literally fucked up something
Yeah
I have this thing where
I won't respond unless
I think of something to respond with immediately
and otherwise I will never respond
I'm a little bit the same way
where I'll occasionally get messages
from certain problematic people
and I'll be like
I feel like to think about what I'm going to say to this person
I don't want to talk to this person for that long
I'll think about this for a while
I'll come back to it
I think there's one to it now
Sometimes it'll be something
that like it doesn't really
need a response
and other times it'll be something that merits a response
but I don't know what response to give
or that I want to give
and then I'll just be like
We're so fucked
My problem
The thing is for me is that I'm constantly inundated
with people trying to get my attention
and like it's on every different social media
it's in my emails
I can't tell the difference
I can't take a response immediately
You gotta put in the big toe
not clickbait
I'm going to
I'm going to a convention
next month
and they keep emailing me
about we need you to tell us
what are your panels going to be
and because I couldn't immediately
give them an answer
they had to send me 20 emails
before I finally got back to them
and this is how tons of people who
maybe set up a collab
with me or something
If you're someone who's tried to reach me
and I've never responded, I'm sorry
but there's a thousand of you
Here's back scenes footage
Did you approach me to try and give me to design
t-shirts for him?
I gave him designs like maybe
like three days afterward
have not heard back from him for like four months
into this day
There's a couple different
I was just going to say that
I feel like I'm having trouble
coming up with stuff to say
because I don't really have a grasp
on how good I am as a friend
like in terms of like
responding on things
You're good
You're one of the high tier respondents
I would say that you are probably
the
I think we're the best
Me, Munchy, Tom and Gib
are the ones you can rely on
like fast in the PCP
Everyone else will wait in eternity
I'm in the chat all the time
I like reading it and responding to things
I know the feeling of
I need acknowledgement
from this person whether or not they've seen it
so I will try to
at least type the letter K
K
And then I add KK after
I would consider you one of my most important friends
because of the fact that you are
one of the only people
who not only do I
love and respect your content
but you actually watch mine
because you're the only PCP member
who watches like
actually both of you
Well, I kind of stopped recently
I do watch your main channel
Yeah, but those two
will watch like my obscure podcast
Yeah, I will do that
and it's nice
that like
someone at least
who's friends with me
actually thinks my stuff is all worth
their time
It's not because
I don't think it's all not worth watching
The reason I don't keep up with all your shit is too full
Number one, you are way too
way more into anime than me
so lots of you talk about it
I don't even...
I'm sure if I clicked and watched it I'd be like
Oh, I can understand this
but like the title and thumbnail I'm just like
I don't fucking know what that is
It's just that because
I have my own stuff to do
like working on my own
Stopping and being like
I'm gonna marathon like 75 hours
I can't really...
I never demand anybody to watch my shit
unless I think it's like
specifically this video is the one that hey
you guys will actually
you guys are gonna care about this one so make sure you watch it
but like otherwise
I just kind of count on the people
who I know are gonna check it out
I know I put out way too much shit
to like ask people to watch all my stuff
but like I'll watch everything everybody else does
in the PCP, you know
I am always like completely on top of the content
I mean I watch...
I don't know, I basically watch everything
The comics I'm sometimes behind on
I'm usually pretty good about instant update
I'm usually pretty good about...
I'm subscribed to all of you and generally watch everything
I didn't think you watched subscriptions
I got into them in the last couple years
I mean I finally have
incorporated them into my lifestyle at long last
Alright, well update to the Nate lore
There you go, there you go
Hippo, back at Recon 2
we didn't really know each other but we kind of liked each other
but what brought me and Hippo to be
big bros that I can consider to be a bro now
Yeah
Nice to meet you
It's fucking arm retrieval
because arm retrieval, the arm retrieval cast
has literally fucking like
tripled friendship
points ever since that fucking podcast
that like started
because here's what would happen, we would record a podcast
and then just because we were so pumped up
from talking about home sex so much
that we would just stand the call for like
fucking hours
It's unfortunate because some of the funniest stuff
was post arm retrieval recordings
When we did like the...
well it doesn't matter to talk about it
I was in some of the arm retrievals as well
not all of them, but yeah I experienced some of that
except for the ones that went super duper long
You see it with the PCP as well
like it's kind of like
so you know the podcast
is a reason for us to stay together
at this point it's a monetary reason
at first there wasn't any money in it but at this point now there is
so now there's like a hard reason for all of us to
contribute and do it but like
the real shit is kind of after the podcast
ends and we just hang out in the call
or beforehand
That doesn't happen
I hang out there for a while most of the time
Well okay, there will be
like maybe 20 minutes
of like okay I'm giving my audio to you
That's the real shit
That's not the real shit
That's not as real as like
post arm retrieval recordings
We did
an entire like we found a site
where you can create like
generate a suburbs thing
We just laughed about it
for fucking two hours
That's great but I'm thinking of the whole existence of the PCP
early on in the days we used to do that more
We're doing it less now
but there's still some
records saying that we kind of prefer text chat to voice chat
like we never go to happen to a call
for anything other than
I much prefer voice chat and I want to do it more
but no one else
What do you mean by prefer
being a voice chat is more of a commitment
which I'm less willing to do
because it means I have to focus
If I had to voice chat
I can't jack off at the same time
without it being obvious
It's a great way to communicate obviously
via voice chat of course
I like to be doing stuff
Maybe cool PCP
let's plays of TF2
You know what it probably isn't
it's probably that I draw more than I like video edit
so I don't even listen to anything to draw
so it's extremely easy for me to
be at a call and draw at the same time
and here, munchy fact
some of the most potent and extreme
and vivid emotional
bonds I've ever had with my friends
by this day were forged over
video games
Video games are the perfect excuse
especially online
I'm thinking about TF2 specifically right now
where I met one of my friends
to this very day who I love dearly, Paul
I met him just over
fucking voice chat because he was like
ranting about some weird republican shit
at like 3 in the morning on an Australian
furry only servant
he's not a furry and neither was I
I didn't know he was a furry
the only two non furries
in the room
and so
it was great because video games
are the perfect like you're talking one of them
you have to communicate and there is an objective
goal to do
but it's not like you got to
we're not fucking Comcasters right now
we don't have to fucking continually
Comcasters?
Comcasts, Gestapo
Stomps doing shit on your internet
we need them to get here to fix our
yeah
you have that baseline objective
you need to work with each other to do
but on top of that it's all just sweet
fucking game to know you
fucking like lore, fucking world building
fucking character building shit and that's what's good
video games fucking expedite fringes a lot
because it is good and I like it
and there's a goal and fucking thank you for Victor
well guys
we've gone through a lot on friendship
no we're not done
it's time we have to stop being friends
we have to stop being friends
I mean we probably going
like an hour and a half, two hours I think
are we really
I haven't even started reading like this
this is episode 100
we're going all night
not really
we could start taking questions if we wanted to
no
what do you have to say
Ben has notes he asked
I'm embarrassed
I'll die
what kind of people do you look for
what kind of friends do you work for
I want to be friends with people
I admire
and people that I think are cool
what if you become friends with the people you admire
and you learn their faults
and then you can no longer admire them in the same way you used to
it's a learning experience
if they turn out to really suck
then see you later
sorry for the shame
I guess
I kind of like having idols that I'll never meet
personally
who just are gods in my mind
I have those
that's how I feel about parkourdude91
because parkourdude91
commented on my lecture
and it was great and he
tweeted me and it was fantastic and I love him
and then many months later when I sent him
just like a tweet
congratulating that he was back on youtube
he was like yeah I hope you're still rocking that pizza onesie
like he remembers who I was
and I get the impression that he's
doesn't have really a lot of his play right now
and I could message him if I want
but like first of all I don't want to disrupt him
because he's literal a fucking genius
and he needs to be like a given space
and not fucked with
and also I almost feel like I'm not worthy
to talk to him
he's just so above me in every way that I cannot
I don't want to soil his fucking reputation
by ever having sent a message to me
fascinating
here's one thing that I want in friends
and that I need in friends
I think you'll agree with me Ben
you can't be too nice
now there's a culture that
especially in here where we are fucking rude
and rowdy and we'll just say whatever the fuck
and start drama with anyone
I'm not really about that
I want friends to be genuinely nice
but you can't be just nice
there are a lot of people in my life who I've met
who are just a nice guy
we can be rude to each other because we know
that we like each other
but there'll be like milk toast
like yeah I'll hold the door open for you
you know like I got your back you know
whatever and like that's nice and I appreciate it
and I like those people
but you have to have some sort of interesting
quirk about you that makes me gravitate
towards you you have to have a personality
that I genuinely care about
you can't just be nice
you need to have some meat on your bones
there should be a base layer of like
you're a nice person you're not a murderer
I almost feel like
I have this feeling that I don't know
if anyone else feels this way
but I almost feel
niceness is like being hot
and when you're going to sleep
and you have your blanket on that's really hot
but sometimes you can get like too hot
you can get too comfortable
it'll be really cold outside and you'll walk into your bedroom
like oh I can't wait to cozy up
but like you'll get too hot
so yeah I gotta take these covers off
I'm too hot right now this is too nice
I'm too comfortable I need to get more
what I hate is friends who just are like
yes men like if there's shit
that you need to be called on and they don't do it
a lot of that I think is cause
you want your friends to be honest
I don't want to be surrounded by a bunch of yes men
who just suck my fucking dick all day
I want people to give me real feedback
don't get me wrong I want my dick sucked all day
I want other people to do that
I have some people I know
or used to know who just like
I would talk to them and I would be having a discussion
like I have this problem I'm going to go to my friend
and I try and like see if they can help me with this
but I don't have the answer myself
I need to bounce ideas off someone
and the discussion would always go
I would present a situation
I would state my case and they would just kind of agree
with whatever I would present
there was nothing I could say that they'd like
no I disagree or no try this instead
they're just like you're doing everything right
like good good yes good yes I agree
I hate that
it's just kind of useless
yeah because like I feel like either A
you're not actually paying attention
I don't know which one's worse
so it's just like oh god I can't stand that
so like one of the things I really like
was when Hippo called me on my shit because I asked him
I was like am I fucking gay
he's like yeah you're gay fix it
that's not exactly what was said
but that was how I interpreted it
and it was good
he's bi-sexual
I'm like almost not gay
do you want to comment on that kid
I can't exactly remember what
the conversation was about
like why
your place in the procrastinate
is why something
and I was just like am I just
not a part of this anymore
you're just like well you just haven't done anything interesting
I was like oh I gotta do some interesting shit
you weren't making videos
you weren't making anything
and yeah
it really I think I guess
where this group is concerned it's an active thing
so like yes
if you're in the PCP you're like a member of the PCP
but if you like just decided like
look I'm going away for like six months to do stuff
that's fine but your absence will be felt
it's not really
but you kind of become like less of a member
just in the sense of you're not in the consciousness
of people who think about the show and stuff
I gotta talk about the kind of people who I look to
for friendship
is people who are working on something
because I want to work on it with them
like I generally
cause they end up bringing value
when I have friends
who I'm not really sure
what they're trying to do right now
it's harder for me to work with them
like if my friends are telling me
that like they're just like
not really sure like what
like oh I don't really know what kind of videos
I'm trying to pursue or I don't know if I want to do
YouTube or I don't know if I want to do this or that
or whatever they're doing
yeah well not like that
but I'm just like you know
if I can't follow the narrative
then it's like it's hard for me to help them
to work towards anything
cause I'm like well what are we building here
like to me when I'm hanging out with people
it's like we're trying to
you know like when we went to Boston
part of it was like let's scope this is a place to move
we're doing rad con 3 and part of it's like
this is a test to see what it'll be like
to have a you know
I gave you the hardest sell I've ever sold
fucking anyone in my entire life but like
like in an hour and a half I just straight just talk
and most of it wasn't even necessary cause you had me
so irrelevant
yeah
but like
yeah so
so it's easier like for instance
like Tom you and I
you had also messaged me I think at the same time
that you messaged him
I told you something similar
like that I
I like your stuff but that I was
I just like had no clear idea of
what you were trying to do at the time
and it's like I don't know how to promote
your work if I don't know
if I don't get what the goal is cause like
right now I'm really big into the idea of
trying to like promote everybody I really want
to get into marketing figuring out how to
like
but like in order for me to do that
I need to know what are you trying to sell yourself
as like who are you trying to
be what is the thing I should be pushing
like do I mention
uh
for a long time you you had noticed
that your rebel pixels link was still
in the channel descriptions of the PCP
and that was cause just at the time
that we you know made the podcast
that was what I had seen as your
current flagship you know so that's
why I linked it but like I only linked
whatever I considered everyone's main thing
you know and then like
obviously if that shifts but
like at times when it's not clear
what your main thing is and once you had rebel pixels
it was a lot easier cause I started
like posting those videos on Twitter all the time
and stuff and being like hey
this one was interesting and
I can help him grow this channel but
like you know it didn't we didn't make it
that far we got 10k's
well you know it's a complicated thing
you know it's kind of weird we
are kind of merchants
of social influence is sort of what
we have and that kind of can be
passed on from one person to another
like if you just bring a person on a live stream
and you've got like 10,000 subscribers
or whatever and you bring someone on they can end up
you know 50 subscribers after that
and look at our special guest PewDiePie
come on in
it's just
what I'm saying is that like there's kind of a weird
gamification of friendship
that's happened or like a monetization
of friendship that is real I mean
this podcast is sort of like that
but really it's more of like I don't know
do you ever feel the pressure of like people wanting
to get close to you just because they know that
that's like a currency that you can offer them
yes a lot
yeah I'm sure you do more than any of us
yeah definitely I feel
I ever really get the like the idea that
they are trying to be my friends specifically because I'm famous
because I'm not really famous but I definitely do
ever every so often have the pressure of
like someone really likes me and they
want to be my friend but I don't like
well there's that a lot
yeah I get just when people friend me
on discord as happened during this
live stream buddy I'm not gonna friend you
why would I friend you who the fuck are you
I will not accept friends from anybody I don't
know the worst oh my god the worst is
when you get people to say hey can I be your friend
or yeah I'm like that's
I don't think that has ever been
listen guys stop being
arrogant just think for
one second with your pea brain have you
done anything that would make me want
to be your friend take responsibility
think to yourself do I offer anything right
now or even if you're the best person in the world
have I demonstrated that I have value
or that I bring anything to the table
if so then I might want to be your friend
that's like the Gary V method where you talk about
like Gary V he's like a social influencer guy
like you got to work for free like if you want to
like be noticed by somebody like just be like
what can I do for you I mean in a sense that's true
yeah in a sense did you
this is how I knew I was fucking in
way back in like out in like
2013 you had
a ton of Skype friends you're like alright I need to purge
all these people because of fucking Maslow's
or some fucking bullshit
oh because of Dunbar's number yeah yeah
that's hilarious yeah yeah
I definitely exceeded it by like three times
yeah so you're like alright I need to scrape all these people
off and so you did that and I was clenching
my my asshole was tucked
and my balls were fluffed
and I was waiting
and I was waiting and then like like it turned
past midnight I knew that I was fucking in
and I was singing something like weird fucked up
video like haha nice one munchie
I was like yeah I'm his friend
I'm his fucking friend
got him
manipulated
emotionally fucking manipulated
got him
that's hell yeah
that's the way to do it
the only difference
between those munchies stand right there
and what most people do is that most people just don't think
about it enough to realize they're emotionally manipulating
people yeah because everybody does that
shit whether you think about it or not it's just
you know how you choose to phrase it
I mean that's what communication is
like you always choose to
represent your best self to people you know
which is the same shit it's the same shit so
you know
what about those lists though you had a list or something
what's going on with that
it's been stupid
family or friends where do you value more
yeah yeah I was going to say
in high school I remember I was
okay because I really hated my parents
my damn parents in high school
was making me do it oh my
what
shut up
I was really angsty as a teen
you still are
I'm getting to that
and I was really angsty as a teen and I was like
man I hate my family I didn't choose
these people I chose my friends
friends
I don't care about my friends I like my friends better
than my family because I chose my friends but you know
I sure I was an angsty teen but I mean that's
true you know like the people
you're friends with are the people that you choose
to be friends with and I think that's
cool I think that makes
really important because you're like you know
you're kind of defining yourself by who you choose
to be friends with absolutely and that's important to people
especially for kids I think one of the
best things you can learn
to grow as a person is to know
that the best way to become friends
with somebody is to be better
at what they do than they are
so that they're impressed by you that's true that was your
philosophy when you met us basically back in the day
some degree
I totally agree with that philosophy
and that's a lot of the people
who I seek out online to this day
are generally people who do
usually
similar content to me but that I think
are really good at it either as
good or better than me and that like
as time goes on and I'm less
and less impressed with people who are doing like
not impressive work
like at this point I want you to act
like you have to be at least
even better than I am for me to even
like turn my head because
like you know I want to see stuff
that like I want to surround myself with
people who are going to push me to be even better
it's just the thing that
I hate the most in life is entitlement
and especially
I mean where it's relevant to this is friendship entitlement
and it's like people who message
you and like expect
you to message back okay I know I've said this before
in a way but it's like I literally
consider it a form of violence
that you're perpetuating on me
if you message me
if you message me and then get mad
if you just say hey
if you just give me the hey and then you're like
well what the fuck why didn't you message me back
motherfucker I've been waiting two weeks
I said hey
let me tell a story real quick
it's just I want to
shit talk this person in my life from years ago
make sure you mention Star Trek because I have to piss
and it's around 55 minute mark
you're right it's time to get to Star Trek
in high school back when I still used Facebook
after I left high school and I was in college
there was a girl who had
like a crush on me in high school who
she messaged me like once
I mean I never checked my Facebook even back then when I had
was she into the vampire hunter D aesthetic
yeah she was into like the long hair
like sexy choir boy thing that I was doing
was it that girl who would draw like comics
and put you on? no no that was that was Jillian
that's a different person it was not Jillian
Jillian was alright we were kind of friends
this is another girl
she was Carrie her name was Carrie
and just like I Carrie
my team in League of Legends
and listen
so she did this thing where she messaged me on
Facebook just sent me a private message
just being like hey how you been that was like a year
after I left and was in college I just ignored it
but oh I forgot
she could see that I had read the message
on Facebook they can do that
so that means you never read your message
but this is my first experience with that
and basically the point is just that
several months after
that initial message where I saw it
and I just didn't respond I get a huge
wall of text saying how mad
this person isn't me for
not responding to that and like I think
why you think you're so much better than me
you think you're like you're above talking
to these people they're you know talking to me and like the old
people who you grew up with like what the fuck
is that about dude um
and of course I just didn't respond
I mean she saw that I read it again
but I didn't respond and then I think another
six months later so I get another message
that's just like hey I want to let you know
I'm really sorry about that last message like you know
I'm just having you know I just didn't really want to
I really want to touch base like I wanted to connect
but like listen you're asking
for something from me I don't know
you shit I don't know anybody
shit I don't know anybody communication
other than like I don't know
like my parents or my friends were like waiting
for something like right now that I promised I would
give them like a message back or whatever
and if you expect that
there was a problem with
you and I think a lot of people have that kind of
entitlement um and it disgusts
me deeply that's how I feel let me let me
tell you creepypasta right now yeah
get on me you get
a message there's the creepypasta
no
no get away all right get back
up you're fucking up the camera
oh god
okay Jesus fucking
he's committed
it's not real
someone messages you
on discord
they're like hey how you doing
you don't want to respond
then then then you like leave it
and then three minutes later you get the message
hmm are you there
are you there
hey are you there
did you get my text
hey just want to make I haven't heard from you
are you there
did you did you get it
that yes I have
got it and fuck you
and die
I don't want to talk to you is the reason I haven't
responded to you uh yeah that's right people need
to recognize that sometimes people don't want to
fucking talk to you uh and you know most
people do but it's just it's just these edge
cases you know these edging cases that I deal
with a lot in my day to day life and it's just
these joking cases
um yeah I don't know
we got uh are we
done more lists should we should we do
uh oh yeah
read the last one
I just want to add to the things that I
look for in people yeah all of my
best friends throughout my entire
life have been short
white people with brownish hair who get
really mad when they suck shit at video
games which they suck shit at everybody
I don't get that mad when I suck shit at video games
you're not my best friend
but I do suck shit at all
so do you mean just Ethan or something
so did you mean just you're like number one
yeah number one
what's the trend here
like three I think
that's good enough
uh friends
I want my friends
to believe in me
that's important but friend doesn't believe in me
well we're all out that's it for us
goodbye everyone
but I don't want them to believe in me too much
you know well like to the point where
they're too nice okay and they don't fucking
call me when I do something hard
do you mean specifically believe in you
or believe you no I mean like believe
in me and like have faith in my abilities
and like you know like okay I want
them to think that I can accomplish my
goals but not so much that they think
that I'm infallible but but of course I'm sure you
recognize that it is basically it's due
they will determine
you know at runtime in real life
whether or not you are likely to determine
your goals based on your performance
I guess so it's really you I guess maybe it's more
on me but I don't know I don't think I'd want to be
friends with someone who was like this guy's
I think what you're saying I mean
why would this person choose to be friends with me
if he thinks I'm a fuck up and he thinks I suck
well the thing is I think it's more than like
um people I want I want people
to be supportive of my goals
because like if I'm like constantly
proving like I can't do them that's fine but like if I
say like oh so what do you want to do I'm like
oh I want to make comics like that's gay
like I don't I don't want that kind of person around me
I mean if you're like I want to make comics
you haven't done that you need to do better
you need to actually that's fine yeah that's good
that's that's called being real I mean
because it's about being a good friend
I think and I think a good friend would do would
hopefully do something like say
listen if your friend says like dude I've decided
I'm going to be
I'm going to be a fucking pottery
pottery maker
I'm gonna I'm gonna make a million dollars making the best
pottery in the world and then you could sit there
and be like well hey man that's great I encourage you
to be like I support you I'm your friend I support you
or you could be what I would consider
a superior friend and say I'm a fucking fag
I'm a fucking fag no you say uh okay
um so what's what's the economic
realities of being a famous pottery man
like how are you gonna pay off the loans you're gonna
have to take to go to school yeah what is your plan
walk me through this that's exactly
what everyone should do you shouldn't say listen
my end goal is to be a pottery maker
therefore I will
just aim for that and figure it out
as I go because that's a recipe for disaster folks
that's how we got the kind of
student debt that America is in right now
what you got to do is have the full plan
for and if you fuck up along the way
here's the thing if you don't want to be a dick
in the process of doing that just just do like
our boy Aristotle did and just ask questions
and let them dig their own grave or blow your mind
with this crazy plan it's like oh
you convinced me that's right that's right so
yeah
uh was that your last note there Ben
I think I have one more okay okay
um
Ben eats during the podcast
saying there it is everybody
would you have your vape can you vape into the mic
can you vape in the house you can't smoke in the house
oh I'll get it in a second
I'll get it in a second um
it's just vapors not smoke if you're friends
so
I think it's really important that friends should be able to tell
each other
no
stream you can't see it but Victor's expression
right now is
maniacal
all of the Collins
when they get that specific mood and look
like literal goblins
they look like literal
zoom in on this
zoom in on it why don't you just look at it
oh yeah there he is
the camera
yeah
thank you
okay back to the
action all right back to the food
I really think it's important that friends should be able
to criticize each other Ben stop eating
on the fucking dream
yeah
um and tell each other when they think you're
fucked up yeah okay right agreed
agreed and it shouldn't be a friendship ender
and if it is in your friendship
probably success
yeah though I mean oh to be fair it's not like
if friends just come at you
with constant negativity about your life
that's I mean if they don't have like
if they're if someone's like there's two ways to do it like dude
your shit sucks you're gay I fucking hate you get
die as opposed to like listen
dude
I mean that's a good friend right there but another approach you can take is
you know of course like hey listen dude
I respect your goals but listen
I'm seriously concerned about you because
I'm not sure the economic realities this thing work out
you know just as what I think about
so I mean
have you thought about this you know to probe in this shit
yeah there he is there's my boy
wake him his shades
can't be seen without his shades
and you know that's another way to do it
that's also good that's all I'm saying
munchie yes go
relationships are a two way street remember this always
you gotta put in work to get rewards
and you always be kind to your friends
but know that you need to push them to be better
just like how they should push you to be better yourself
they should push you down the stairs
yeah
there he goes
is that you pickle read
there he is
there were two tiny stairs
no one can hear you because the mic's over here
it's time to go to the questions everybody
let's go to the questions
super chats are open everybody
if you gave us a super chat we'll reveal it
we probably won't be able to see it
we fucking pee coming you live
right fucking now
from downtown sharing bars at Joe's
dog
from downtown exact address of this house
please comment
rate our shit
it's time everybody send super chats
we're all gonna be looking at our fucking phones
I fucking call page in lines
I call the page in lines
oh there it is
wait listen do it to the mic Ben do it into the fucking mic
it's just not an episode of the PCP without this
shit
one one one one one one
one one one one zero
one zero zero
okay who's got a question
they haven't even heard us say
oh yeah they haven't
okay I'm sure they'll come in
I'm gonna tweet the tweet for the pity question
you better fucking do that shit
who's on top of super chats
no one has asked any yet so I'm on top of it
oh wow almost just threw up
a large quantity of vomit just came up my esophagus
and then went back down
we got a five dollar super chat that just simply
from from fit emcee that says
Ben equals vape god
well fit emcee is
watching right fucking now
vape god was a guy
fucking shouted fit emcee my literal hero
vape god is a real person who commissioned me
to draw a girl
and I drew young Sophia
well I'm sorry to correct you fit emcee
but Ben is not technically fit
no but I know him and he's cool
he knows him he's a good man
we got 50 dicks
dkk's what the fuck are dkk's
oh there might be like Denmark currency or something
okay from smickelkoon
can someone please do a 100 pp episode
celebratory backflip
oh dear
can anybody do a backflip
I don't know my life but I'm willing to try
oh I don't know
this is not a good idea
you'll destroy the space
I could do a somersault
or a car
a single jump
focus on my feet
woo
pcp 100
I know I can't do a backflip
alright there he goes
this is the best we got
alright
I'm gonna hurt myself
you're good
careful you're good
yeah
alright well done
fuck yeah
okay well we got everybody
I hope that was worth 20 dicks
I hope that was worth 50 dutch
dutch kronen
we got champagne
our good graph
killing good games
our good graphics killing good games
I spelt so wrong
yeah cause budgets
spiraling budgets
okay but here's a question though
is there any way to avoid it
stop giving a shit about graphics
stop being a coward
stop being a coward and embrace
stylistic restrictions
the indie market has proved that there are buyers for those games
that's true
triple A is just in its own world though
well that's why triple A is gay
if people stopped
getting a constant stream
of photorealistic games
then people would stop
this is why I have no pity
for these companies
oh god games are so expensive now guys
you are the ones who developed the
let's make everything photorealistic
mentality that wasn't on the people
that was you saying we're just gonna keep releasing new hardware
every couple years we keep milking you mother fuckers
I mean it's a complex thing like you're saying
cause it's a reciprocal cyclical
cyclical process of people
you could kind of blame for a lot of it
it was the shift of emphasis
towards spectacle
well that was just like the console
I mean everyone was doing that the Sega Saturn
the Playstation 1
it's a lot of other super changes
it's been 100 episodes
how much more must we endure
you can stop watching it
as long as you have things to say
the PCB shall endure
King Cobra asks Munchie are you gonna do more vids
like the Jace one
do they mean
more lectures
you'll definitely be doing another lecture
more lectures in the future
if he means more lectures then yes
we'll be doing one this time
and if you mean more Jace videos
as in like performing a character
then that's all my content so yes
Tyler the Fancy says
you'll be releasing the D&D session
recorded at this year's Radcon soon
I brought that up just a minute ago
and no one could have possibly heard it
so this must
wait what sorry what was it
Ben was talking about potentially doing a Dungeons & Dragons
I thought you hate Dungeons & Dragons
I do but I do it anyway
we can do a D&D redemption stream
or something
I wouldn't do D&D but I might find like a rules light
like a game system
the whole stuff thing we did was way more fun
well it doesn't have to be that
we can look into it
I actually have looked into it before
but then I dropped it but now that we're here
Ben I've always wanted
to fucking have a homestuck D&D
I've always wanted to do that
I'm gonna do that now but I've always wanted to have that happen
listen to this comment MattLand
super chat thanks buddy
how did Ben get so thick if he is so poor
keep it real my dudes
don't let Tom forget my shirt
what do you think Ben? I eat all carbs
that's the trick everybody
I'm healthy I'm eating all carb diet
Saad Hassan wants you to pull off a sick
celebratory cloud of vape
here we go
J-HeartBs asks opinions on fans
i.e. me
obviously we need
yeah there she goes
it's like the Ben move today
it's pretty good
he screams to cover
his discomfort of being on camera
yeah and it's not really covering anything
because she's playing his day
Giffy from the patreon lounge
asks where's the best meme created
well so far we're not even like
it's too soon to say
yeah it's too soon to say
but so far it has to go to my vain
man Dan
Dan soft toilet seats
oh by the way I've been liking this
don't mind at night a lot though
is that a new thing
when did that happen
first time I heard it was in the car
as most memes start
for some reason just said don't mind
at night and then it just you know
might just be bringing out the horse
songs all the way
I'm sorry my voice
this guy's man is pure discord
howling at it
viewers I put my body
through such physical stress
and mental harm directly for you
you hear this you hear that
that's my voice going fucking up
except for screaming every single
fucking video non stop
this godforsaken hellhole
I do it for you
I do it for you viewers I'm full in
fuck yeah Rad God 3
I'll blow out my fucking purse
I'll blow out my hearse
I'll blow out my fucking grave for you
ever since we all hashtag entered the arena
we've all been spiraling downward and by the way
the final player has logged in
has a bit like you know
when you're on an MMO and you're waiting for my people to load in
to join your server
all the players have now assembled in our server
for Rad Country IRL
so the game will begin soon
all we need to do is press fucking F4
to ready up and we will be fucking in that way
my boy we will be in that way
also we should like hard sell Dan toilets
really quick by the way because as we
as we've stated before this is
literally like the perfect incarnation of
why we need PCPHQ
because that video could not
exist in any form
if it weren't for being here
go watch DanSop
open letter to DanSop toilet seat on this channel
if you haven't seen it
that was all improbable
why are you encroaching over giving so hard core
DanSop toilets
it could not happen
because we can't do that over voice
this was a pure in person thing
and this kind of stuff would happen all the time
would be even better if we were in PCPHQ
so please you'll get content like
DanSop toilets
but even better probably even written
meaning that you're doing skits now
I wanted to mention that like
doing this has made me very comfortable
with the
we're in the middle of that
damn pocket
he's having trouble logging into account so he can't do it
well anyway
I think that this has proved the
functionality of the idea of
like a
PCPHQ because for me the experience
has been what it would be because I've been
leaving every night and coming every day
you know like from a hotel
and yeah the idea of just being
able to like drive 10 minutes
up the road and like create
shit and then just go home is really
nice that is the dream ultimately
and uh yeah
you know I mean I just want I
look forward I really look forward to having the
content all out and having
the audience cast judgment on whether
or not we have fulfilled our job
and I think we absolutely will but I
want the people to confirm that they are
happy with what we have delivered
I have to read these chats before they disappear
if the PCP was a band
what instrument would each member play
trumpet I already have a trumpet I plan to learn
how to play the trumpet because I really like the trumpet that I plan to do that
soon it kind of fucking broke but
I'll fix it
I play guitar
I sing and I play the clarinet
I pick that back up
I play jazz clarinet that's right
oh
I'd be the guy just managing
the sound boards and like causing feedback
you'd be the DJ like an incubus
you know the designated DJ
I'm thinking a little bit more like
Brian Eno or something but
sure I can be the incubus fucking
they've got a designated DJ
in their band I mean Lincoln Park has one too
they were probably inspired by them
I do actually play the saxophone
but I think that playing the saxophone
is a good encapsulation of who I
am you are a good singer
because I would be there I'm there
I don't really need to be there
but it's quirky
and everyone likes it when you are
what about Tom you play anything
cowbell
and here's something I don't understand
but maybe you do William Baker for $5
that's what is the sexiest fundamental force
what's that new one
oh it's gotta be the color force
the color force?
is that like the speed force?
no that's the strong
the one between the one between
shout out your favorite content creator who isn't in the PCP
does that have to be from
Dr. Wolf
he didn't even say it had to be
YouTuber it's just content creator
Dr. Wolf
of all creators of all time
all of my favorite content creators
not in the PCP are either
inactive or
like most of my favorites
like Andrew Hussey and Yannar and Kallinsky
I would call them my favorites but
it's not like they update them
yeah so let's go through my
descriptions and see
what about you give
he's a good boy
I have a deep place in my heart
for Twin Perfect
I also love Demolition D
that's enough for now
Scooby 1961
Fitness Guy on YouTube is a hero
Gabe and Tycho from Penny Arcade
not cause I love the comic
but I love
their empire
I love the indie stuff
is it just the empire itself
I love their podcast and I love the empire
and I love their whole attitude
and what they do and I wish I was them
I love the freakish trollish bodies
yeah I love how
Tycho looks like a boiled egg
yeah he sure does
we're still going here
my answer would probably be Dick Masterson
just you know I'm
fucking obsessed with this show and I've learned
I feel like I've learned a lot about how
to think of
how to just think about the world from him
in terms of protecting yourself
and just not being fucked with
and having a very aggressive attitude
towards your surroundings
you know
I've looked through my descriptions
I don't like any of them as much as Andrew has
I was going to say M.D.E
but from my perspective
I found out of M.D.D.
through Yandering Katsuki
which just kind of feels like a subset of
it's a million dollar extreme
yeah a million dollar extreme
Charles Carroll and Nick Roachford
I mean I like them
I think they're good
but they're not Parkour Druid 91
they don't fucking sing Weed Eater
they don't sing Weed Eater
that's what I care about
Tom how about you
I'm gonna have to go with M.D.E.P.
by the way can I give one shout out to
Jan Productions
who made that public PSA do not mind at night
so many
asks do you have any Boston specific
plans aside from content
killing Gibbon take
going to a specific restaurant a museum
finding a burial spot
on home soil for Ben
well
I'm gonna go
house hunting and I think I'm gonna take
Munchy and Gaze
with me
okay cool
hang out in Boston
plans that will be fulfilled here at Radcom
because I want to stay here at Radcom for all of my
you know most of my stuff
but there are points that I want to take these guys
eventually I have a lot of ideas
I want to take them to fucking Newbury Street
I want to take them to fucking everywhere
on fucking Boston just the entire fucking road
the common obviously Faniel Hall
I want to do the walk that I did
just the other day walking Faniel Hall to the ICA
fucking ICA will blow
you two right there you two fucking schmucks
would love the
jipper air you would blow your fucking load
I've never been
Russell has emerged back
from the black
he's asking has my
royal rumble form been achieved yet
yes yes I have
I saw it with my own eyes
he has been materialized from the dark evil
Pokemon hell
you are really gonna fucking like it
I think
we did good
I was like yeah
why do you guys call things gay all the time
why?
we're gay
it's because we're all gay
we understand the nuance
because I can think of no greater insult than
saying you're just like me
you ever had one that you're like
afraid to read because you're gonna have
you might suffer the consequences
this is a
f100 and so far not a single bottle piss
bottle piss
I'm sorry guys
the group piss took it all out
there you go
that was my real purpose all along
finish saying the group piss
there's been piss capades
what more do you want
hey listen to this though Paris Pickle
says why is hippo so cute
please blow me a kiss
what?
they gave you 1.99 pounds
of your own currency
blow me a kiss
there you go
There he goes. No
Look into the fate system of role-playing it's more role-playing less rule-focused and character creation is pretty
I think it's not related. I don't think it's related to fate stay night. I don't think it is
Anyone of you have had any of you had a paranormal experience. Yes
On the ghost episode where where I was a little baby when I was a little feeling the sun was going down
I was just I was just like walking on my soul. So we're mining at night
And there was I just saw something like weird shadowy fucking like like shadow man figure and I ran downstairs crying
It was super scary, but it was cool. So was I on the ghost cast
I think I was and I might have told this story, so I'll tell it very quickly
But my college was like had a reputation freeing haunted as many do and we went on like early when I first enrolled
we went on like a ghost tour and
They they took us around to some haunted spots and we went up to some room and there was supposedly a ghost there and
There was like a flash. No someone flashed a camera and I saw in the camera flash in the window
I saw what looked like people I saw a
An old man in a poncho and a little boy and I was like, oh cool ghost
I was like, hey, I just saw a ghost in the window
It was an old man on a poncho little boy and the guy was like, no no no the ghost here is a woman
And then some goth girl was like, oh I felt something because I have spiritual powers and I was like
Yeah
She got touched on the butt by a ghost because she was sitting on a haunted radiator
And that was my paranormal experience Paris Pickle followed up on the kiss. Thanks for the kiss hippo. I am actually a woman crying
Hey, here's a thing Mars Lou Mars Louise Evans says name your favorite hentai Joe Jin Chi
I'm gonna go with shout-out to acid head just all their work with one piece of Naruto
They got big tits. They got big sluts. They got everything you could want everybody
They put they's the same one every single time. So if you don't like it, then you're not
Yeah, it's a dojin
My circle wait, no, no, they said just what's it? What's what's a dojin?
She and what's not a fan work if it's been released if it's not like published by a major publisher
I don't know. I don't know. It doesn't have to be hentai. Well, they asked for a hentai one. Okay. Well, my favorite is probably
Chinpoko sama, which is about this
Unfathomably hot girl who gets who summons a gigantic penis monster in the night to fuck her and eat her and it's cool
I went and read that one. Yeah, you talked about it. It works really fucking beautiful creep me out because she like dies in the end
Yeah
Doesn't make it
Metamorphosis
For metamorphosis, yeah, I would I would like a copy of metamorphosis. It's just it's a cultural touchstone
Well, what is it? Oh, it's a it's a dojin about like an okay
It's a portrait of the stupidest girl who ever lived basically. She's a she's a kind of nerdy girl
She gets a makeover and then all of a sudden everyone's super attracted to her and she ends up just like
Because she can't handle like the attention
She starts just like fucking everyone and then nobody wants to like hang out with her
She becomes like a bicycle everybody hates her and then her life just spiral like everybody hates her now because she's a slut
She like meets a guy who likes her. He like drugs her and fucks her and just gets wrapped up in this whole thing
Her father rapes her. It's this whole big
She got her mom is mad at her for the dad raping her and thinks she's a slut
She kicks her out of the house and she's she goes to that boyfriend who I'd like fucked her obviously doesn't care about her
That guy starts using her for like prostitution
He just keeps giving her drugs so she doesn't care and she just spirals down from there
She becomes homeless sure it's fucking a lot of homeless people
Just to like survive and eventually she gets she's pregnant
She has an abortion that happens again
and then she gets kicked to death by a bunch of urban youth in Tokyo and then she dies and the final thing we see is
Like a little flash to like what her life is like her with her daughter like 20 years later
But actually that's a dream and she died drugged and like fucking pregnant being stomped death by teenagers on a public bathroom floor
It is actually terrible and like
It's a good story for what it is
Oh my god
On the opposite of the spectrum
The hentai that made me that gave me the biggest laugh like which I think is worth a lot of points
Say say so say so to eat on shot. Hmm is really funny
It's not even like it's not even like my thing at all like it's like it's like femdom bullying stuff
It's like that's not really
But it's got this the premises that the kids dick
Magically can detach and then it can magically like reattach to other things including like girls can like put it on themselves
And so these like bully girls like pass this dick around and it's it's just really funny and it's the arts really good
Ending is hilarious
For me to record a Vic vlog so I did Victor if you would like to
They asked for shirtless Victor
Why Victor is shirtless you want to comment on that at all Victor
Digi bros fan black one blade asks how is Vic and hope doing?
Oh
Daynecks Jax's transform you to damn god damn it
We're pretty much out of super chance, do we just want to like end? Oh, well, let me get a Twitter
Let me get the Twitter
Let's put in the hashtag
The patreon lounge read some patreon lounge ones. They're all
Come on. Let's read a horrible one. Let's read a horrible
Exactly who would be dead now this was the Stone Age with cavemen
That's the worst question ever
I mean, we'd all be dead
With caveman embarrassing
Was that let's let's rag on them crafty crafty stop
I thought had to be intentionally bad. There's no way. Oh, no, these questions are good though
If the Hunger Games style competition starting the PCB house right now
Which PCP member would come out on top shout out to my boy a faku no Alvarez. Yeah, when we do the the arena
That's true. He's right about that. It's basically exactly the entire purpose
Okay, okay
I've got a good I got one. That's a missed super chat that was then sent by my fan into my discord
Okay, what do you guys if you end up checking discord this week, please ask them my question
Which was how much does Ben spend on vape stuff per month?
I had a bunch of mods that these are really cheap mods and I had like two of them that broke in rapid succession
So it was kind of an unusual time
But in general, I would probably say I might spend like that's not the same pipe that you had at my house
Is it it's a new version of it's a new model?
Yeah version 2.0
It's the same make. I probably buy like a bottle of juice probably like 30 much better than your previous
For maybe like $30 and that usually they'll probably
a month or
$30 none of this
We have a question. Yes from lethal rora mage
Where is mage? Well, I'll tell I'll tell you boys. She is right here. Oh fuck
Mage
Yeah
It's so great to see you I'm so 100 how fucking hype are you I
Without you fucking what do you have to say?
You guys you are getting rad content not even at the fucking house rad con is the fucking crucible of Christ
Can we get can we get mage for Radcon 4 can we
Had plans to get mage in for Radcon 3 that unfortunately didn't work out
But we will put our best effort in to make sure that mage can be around for the next one
So, yeah, I really want to I hope so
Yeah
Yeah, she'll just wear like a purple
Let's let's ask a question to mage. Yeah, here we go. You're from the Twitter our pity question
Maze why would I question so bad? Here's a question. That's relevant for you. No, I'm sorry. This is too embarrassing to read
I can't do it
This one
It's loading
Is because it doesn't know the whole thing is jealousy slash envy for a friend a good thing as in a
Motivator to become better or more successful or doesn't rather make you unmotivated instead. What's your take mage?
You mean in general or personally for me, I guess for you I guess for you
I
Don't get jealous necessarily have friends, but I guess it technically motivates me
I usually take whenever I if I ever get like jealous or any yes
I just motivate myself to get better so I wouldn't have to feel that way. Okay. I'm jealous of your ability to not be jealous
All right. Got one more question for you. Listen to this mage. Is there any exotic dish?
I know you're a food connoisseur that you've wanted to eat. Oh, this is from at XG upload by the way
Is there any exotic dish you want to eat but you're too much of a pussy to eat it
You know
That's more of wanting to be a lie
I would eat that shit
Yeah
I mean it's Twitter, so they're all bad
Here's what we can all win on this at monkey away as this is a very complicated questions thoughts on the wild success of the PCP itself
Yeah, it's um, I mean I never expected it to get as big as it did but it has not felt it hasn't been like an explosive growth
It's been no it's been like it's felt really gradual
But like stepping back and looking at it. I'm like wow really got a lot bigger than I ever expected
Oh, it was it was very strange because the period where like we
Like I was editing it in the early days and then I sort of for a while
There was like a long period where I was editing and then like when I stopped was when I
got really busy with my own shit and
Like it was interesting because in order to you know for the episodes to get edited
We had to come up with like a system and everything to figure out ways to do it
And then it kind of became a well-oiled machine and then like I came, you know like
Like I've been kind of not on every episode for a little while came back and was like, huh
I can't help but notice that we've like like this is this is not the same as it was six months ago when I was editing it
like everyone's taking it way more seriously and like in the time that it that like
Like everything else is the PCP what you put in what you get out like be the reason that the PCB has been way more successful
Is that we've all been working way harder on it. That's true. And especially now after the episode that shall not be named
monsters
Monsters to is coming by the way
Transition into a real fan
We've all made it concerted up. We've taken feedback and we've been listening to people's concerns and we've really been trying to make it better
I think we've done a lot
Made a Magna Carta of the reasons why the PCB is shit, which we are not gonna read
But we know the criticisms and we're actually trying to make them better and and we really care about this project
This is not just a fucking nothing show that we do for no reason at all
We genuinely care for the show. We want to make it better. It's like it's like the content that we can do together
But we've got lots of ideas for other stuff if things get to a place above it
I mean, yeah, we are we are you know, we're taking we're taking things into consideration and trying to evolve the PCP show itself
But also like PCP as a channel. I really
Appreciate and and I'm excited that like, you know, like like non-main stuff
I mean, this is a while ago, but when me and you did the D&D things. Yeah, that was fun
Yeah, like things like that
I think we should do more like side like collaborative like non-main PCP stuff. Like yeah, that kind of really nice cop killers, huh?
Yeah, yeah, we're out of focus. We might like get the fuck hype for that. Oh, yeah. Yeah, we've got some in the chamber
We got some a lot. We've got some in the chamber. That's the bullets in the chamber
Yeah, yeah, you might say
All right, well, I mean that's it for the Twitter. Thanks Twitter, everybody
Let me just see if there's anything
Let's see if there's this is your absolute fucking last
Let's see if we can get a dope-ass question like
Okay, this is not the last one Dane Dane says do you think there's anyone to get to do on a call this is not
We asked
And then the final question from Robert Floyd in the patron lounge are friends real
All right, maybe just an AI in this phone for example also you are all AI's in your flesh phone bodies
That's it. My body's finally achieved. Have we have we finished? Are we done? I think we've said all there is
the least effective phone ever
Hey, we got bonus episodes
Five dollars on the pcb patreon get access to the bonus episodes follow us on Twitter at tbcrastinators
Downloads of this show. I don't know this will be on the mp3. We'll see what we can do
We'll see you soon everybody