We're riding on the internet. Cyberspace set free. Hello virtual reality. Interactive appetite. Searching for a website. A window to the world. Got to get online.
Take a spin now you're in with a techno set. You're going surfing on the internet.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. How are you doing? How are you doing Munchy? How are you doing?
I cannot think of a single worse thing than having only one layer of flesh.
Tom, what's going on with you dude?
I like Chuck and Cheezus.
Yeah we do. Hippocrit, what's up?
For all my social media things, follow all those right now, bitch.
God damn. Please follow me at atchuckiecheez.com.
Yes, also my Chuckie Cheez account is to be announced.
Yeah, we're here to promote our new Chuckie Cheez social media platform that we're getting into. Endless Jess of course is here as well.
Guys, it's me. Five nights at Freddy's. Who let that faggot Chuckie Cheez in here? Where's that fucking, I hate Chuckie Cheez for anything.
You fucking bitch, I'm gonna crack your fucking skull in.
I'm the only mascot pizza parlor for kids, children place around here. This is only big enough for one.
You're a fucking poser. You're a fucking poser. I'm haunted. You're not even haunted. You're not even fucking haunted.
I'm haunted with the good times that all of us have.
You're wholesome and you suck.
You're a gay mouse. You're a gay little mouse faggot bitch.
You're a little bitch. All right, all right guys. I'm a sentimental bitch. What can I say?
Fuck your pizza and fuck you.
Guys, break it up. We gotta save this for the bonus episode which you can purchase on patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Yep, yep, Freddy Fazbear versus Chuckie Cheez. There it'll be. That's what this month is gonna be. Good job, good job.
Guys, everyone shake hands. It'll print money basically.
I'm not Freddy Fazbear. I'm five minutes at Freddy's. That's my legal name.
Well, it's great to have you here as always. So, he's gonna be a regular folks.
So, today we're talking about social media. Social media. So let's see what the old urban dictionaries say about that shit.
Social media. Online networks where both adolescents and young adults go to express one of two statements.
One, I'm complaining about my boring shitty life used as an alternative to actually making life interesting.
And two, look how superior my boring shitty life is to your boring shitty life.
Used to passively belittle the only 250 people the individual knows.
You know, Nate, one time I want you to go to Urban Dictionary to find that the definition is literally just the word gay and read that.
It just be so much funnier. So much more engaging to me personally.
So much more sentimental. One day. I hope we get there someday.
So, our world is controlled by social media, right? We're all slaves to it. There's no escaping it.
I've noticed at this point in the way the world works now, all the building stuff is mostly done.
The hard lifting and building and putting together stuff is done.
And now it's about optimizing strats, you know what I mean? It's about optimizing what you can squeeze out of the other people around you.
And that's kind of what social media is. It's about manipulating people to be into your shit for good or ill.
And it's pretty good. Big fan. I like it. I do it. I do it.
I mean, you mean that from the perspective of a content creator trying to spread things. It's not just that.
It's also a place for people to subscribe to youtube.com slash patreon.com slash Ben St.
And various other things. I like it. It's pretty good. It's the way of the future.
I hate Facebook. Facebook sucks.
It doesn't make any dollars that they give to me. And therefore, what's good are they?
But then again, if you were a mod, then you'd be doing it for free.
Mod VP guys, did you ever hear about that one social media platform called www.4chan.com?
It's really funny guys. It really makes me feel happy. I like to talk about games I've never played before and make fun of them.
Should we define exactly what we're going to talk about?
Are we talking about the platform or are we talking about our experiences with using it as a content creator to spread our message?
I don't even know. I don't talk about the worth of it and specific websites individually.
Who do you think wins in a fight, like a cancer fight between anime avatars on Twitter and religious relatives on Facebook?
Religious relatives all the time.
They own the power to be real people.
They're real people whereas the anime avatar people are whiny.
I'm going to say the anime avatar people because there's literally no end to them.
The religious family members, if you block enough of them, you'll run out of family members.
But the anime avatars, they just keep coming. You squash one and fifty more take their place.
Every second around the world fifty million anime avatars are born.
And you can stop this if you dial this 1-800 number for 1-800 anime avatar genocide to kill them all in their homes while their parents watch them with a gun and a sword.
588 ChuckieCheese.com
Please donate to ChuckieCheese.
ChuckieCheese will come into these people's houses and he'll show them who's the original scary.
Scariest than Five Nights at Freddy. He'll jump out at them with a sword and a knife.
They have to do that. What if we just, you know, bite the bullet and talk to our religious family members and tell them that all these anime avatars are like atheists and against God and then they'll take their guns and kill them themselves.
Oh my God. All the division from all of your friends and family on Facebook.
If only they knew about the anime avatars on Twitter that could band together and it would all be good again.
It'd be just like the ending of Watchmen where they, you know, we save the infighting between humanity by giving them a greater evil enemy.
Yes. In order to fix one social media platform you have to band them together against a different social media platform.
It's the perfect scheme and it'll never fail. There's no way it can backfire.
That actually got that. That actually is really good because that reminded me of something.
The other day I was thinking about how I'm going to remake Watchmen but I'm going to replace every character with like different sauces.
So you've got like Worcestershire sauce, you've got ketchup, you've got A1.
And so like the film starts out normal but then over the course of time each character has their like own like composite layer
and I just add more and more sauce to them each time and I just watch them go.
At the end of the film it's basically all just A1 sauce and you can't see anything.
Unfortunately Munchy, the greatest remake slash parody of Watchmen already exists.
Some website literally made a version of Watchmen that starred Hillary Clinton.
Oh my fucking god.
Trump the fuck? I'm not joking. This is something that exists.
But how much sauce is there?
There's a lot of sauce dude. It's Hillary Clinton.
Blue sauce.
Is she white or is she like Owlman or is she...
She's Doctor Manhattan my friend. She's the enlightened one.
Oh the blue penis. The blue penis pill.
The traps aren't gay guys.
How much sense?
To be on topic, I have a thing we could all talk about since we're...
No.
No, no, no, no. I know you hate me.
Enough!
But we are of a generation, maybe Munchy less so, but we grew...
No, no, I'm just...
Why don't you just listen to the person than any of us? Let's be real.
We grew up before social media and now it's fucking everywhere and we're a transitional generation.
We've seen it come into existence and now it's everywhere.
We're the last ones who will never know what we've lost as a species and can never get back.
We're the last living souls.
And I'm wondering how everyone got into social media, whether you resisted at first or what did you first make a social media account on?
How'd that all go?
The first social media account I ever made was on a Pokemon fan form and I used to role-play on it all the time.
Sick, dude.
It was so fucking... That's where I got my name, Bros.
I guess I would say the...
I love social media, so good.
I guess I would say the first thing I ever did was I remember back in the day signing up for AIM, you know, AOL Internet Messenger
and that's where I came up with my legendary name I've been using, Mega Man X-1331.
Yeah!
Oh, it's dope, right?
I mean, other than that, I never got into Facebook.
I remember the original social media in my day was simultaneously the best and worst place in the world, Gaia Online,
which was this big retarded anime, video game, everything forum for dumb little teenager nerds.
And you just... The whole... It ran on this really malicious, addicting coin system where all of your posts gave you a penny
and for a thousand dollars you could buy clothes for your little avatar and it hooked you, man.
This means, Jesse, you were the original anime avatar social media account.
Oh my god!
Holy shit!
It was inside of me all along!
Banned me! Somebody get me out of here!
Get me out of myself!
Did any of you guys ever use MySpace? Because I totally skipped over that.
I did, not really because I wanted to.
I just had friends who were like, I remember my friends sat me down and made me a MySpace account
and then two years later sat me down and made me a Facebook account, despite the fact that I didn't want any of it.
Probably the only social media account I signed up for back in the day because I wanted to was DeviantArt
because I drew shit and I was like, this is cool.
You got social media raped, dude. You got raped.
Yeah, multiple times and that's why I'm the fucked up person I am today.
I had a MySpace account, I'm pretty sure.
It was for a brief time because I only got into it shortly before Facebook came and completely steamrolled it.
But for a while I did have a MySpace account.
I'm sure it was really cringey and horrible because it was from when I was 17 or 18 or whatever.
Wasn't that archive? Didn't you have an archive of that? I think I've seen it.
Well, I wish I did because I was thinking back on, man, I like to see my old MySpace page.
I like to see some of the weird, cringey messages I sent back and forth to fucking girls and stuff.
So I was trying and I can't remember my login for shit.
I can't remember how to even get into it.
So it's just lost to the annals of history forever.
I was never really into social media.
It took a long time for me because I didn't have friends and I was like a gay.
So I didn't know MySpace, I skipped over that.
Facebook was becoming huge and it was actually my mom who pressured me to get it
because she saw that people could make friends on it and she's like,
you could talk to your friends on this thing.
I'm like, fine, I guess, I guess I'll get Facebook and now I have Facebook
and I have never used it really.
I just occasionally people upload photos of me and then I can see, oh, cool.
That's what I look like at that moment in time.
But I mean really the earliest online interaction account that I ever set up
was either Club Penguin or RuneScape and I think it might have been Club Penguin
which is sad because it's dead and everything ever of it is gone.
Download the app, bro, download the app.
I did download the app.
How was the app?
I undownloaded it because one, it's gay and two, it's like incredibly limiting
and you need to pay for anything to happen.
It doesn't feel right because it's not even that I care about having a penguin game to play.
It's just the memory of that being the first time I've ever talked to people on the internet.
RuneScape is still around though, so that's cool.
You said, hello, I'm a baby, please nurture me and someone said ASL.
RuneScape.
Yeah.
The first time you ever met.
Okay, so like I just logged into my old Gaia Online account.
Oh, yes.
And whoever's editing this, when you do the pictures of us in the corner,
I definitely want my Gaia Online profile pic, my avatar as my picture on this one
because it's the fucking sweetest avatar in the history of the world.
Everyone's gonna see how cool and edgy and cool I am.
I think I actually have seen, it wasn't your MySpace, I've seen your Gaia Online before.
That's fucking perfect.
We should all put our worst fucking avatars possible from our old.
I don't even know.
Mine's the best.
Mine is a masterpiece.
It's 100% good.
I'm not even being ironic, I think.
I think I'm being sincere.
I say that it's probably legitimately cool.
Hey, so let's talk about something about social media that you see a lot.
Let's talk about social media hipsters as in the people who just like reject it entirely
and say like, oh, it's useless.
Yeah, like I remember feeling that way about Twitter for a long time
and it only changed when like I started doing YouTube stuff
and it was like, okay, like I guess I'll figure it out
because it might be a useful way to talk to people.
I mean really, I was like a social hipster.
I thought social, I didn't have a phone until I was like right now,
I just bought a phone right now.
How old is Jesus?
Like I've never, I didn't have any sort of contact with human beings until I was 20.
Well like, yeah.
You see the results.
How old do you think, like, I've been thinking about this actually myself,
like at what age would I give like a kid of mine like their own smartphone
and like connect them to this giant network of fucking shit out here.
I would say 16, 16, 15.
I can't though, that's the problem.
12, 14.
The problem, because like it's interesting you mentioned this
because I have a younger sister who is only 15 right now
so I have seen this play out in real time as someone who is, you know,
10 years removed from her generation and can observe it.
Like my parents were super hesitant to like cave into all this like technology and shit
but like you need it now, you know, like she needed a laptop
at like 11 and like all her friends are on social media and using phones like now.
That's what they want, man.
That's what the corporate elites have made this world into.
Exactly.
That's what they want to make, turn our kids into degenerates as early as possible.
They'll be googling BBC before you know it dude.
It's all downhill.
It's all downhill from here.
That actually reminds me how my mom forced me to love Sonic the Hedgehog
even though I didn't want to.
Yeah?
Tell me the tale dude, tell me the tale.
So in kindergarten I would take like...
You poor fucking junkie.
I'm so sorry.
That's abuse.
Forget Daddy of Five.
This is like real abuse here.
Yeah, real shit.
So in kindergarten I would like take a bus and I had to like walk a little bit
so my mom was like here you need like a flip phone
and so she got me a flip phone and it was fucking sick
and I would whip it out during school and I would pretend it was my dick
and say hey I'm gonna call fucking Obama assholes
and then be like oh my god.
They'd be like oh my god that's some sauce bro.
That's some serious sauce.
Just too powerful dude, too powerful.
So anyway, it was just like a phone like before phones were everything
they were just phones.
Like imagine like just like the phone little square thing and that's what it was.
I don't understand.
The little square iPhone little thing you click on
and then it's like oh that's what you can only call things.
That's the only thing you can do is you can just talk to people.
It's disgusting.
I can't think of a single worse thing than talking to another human.
Anyway.
I agree.
So there was one thing that like my mom was like you know what?
You know what?
You need to do something here.
You should get a game on your phone and it'll be really fun dude.
And I'm like but I hate video games.
All I want to do is fucking hang around people who I don't know is house
and go through their fucking garbage.
God damn.
But then she downloaded fucking Sonic 1 on my mobile phone.
Now keep in mind this is not like a like this phone size is like the size of like half of a fucking iPhone.
Like like like really small like I can barely see anything.
And there's like like there was no like backlight so I'm playing like like like Game Boy Advance
no backlight like like Sonic 1 on a fucking tiny screen not even using like a game controller.
Just using like like the number pad and like arrows.
And that's how I played and beat Sonic 1 for the first time.
And because I was so fucking shit I literally like I toiled and fucking mined and like starved to death
on like on like Marble Zone Act 2 for fucking years and I couldn't get past it.
Until like two years later right before I'm about to like get like my first actual real good guy smartphone
I decided to like spin like 72 hours just finally beating Sonic 1.
And that's how I did it.
That's my story about how my mom is a mind break dosion and she forced me to like Sonic even though I didn't want to.
You forgot to mention that she also forced your ringtone to be the Sonic sound and made the background Sonic.
It made all your contact Sonic pictures.
Sweet fucking Gaia Boy.
Look at this hero this module stud.
Holy shit.
God damn.
I have never seen a man more powerful than this dude.
The fucking galaxy behind him.
Holy shit.
We need to play Gaia Online guys.
We need to all play Gaia Online.
Just how do you.
The crass consciousness was fucking insane.
The crass consciousness levels of that.
Is that a little happy potato in the bottom in the bottom.
It's a little it's a little chick.
It's a little chicken chick.
Okay.
I'm getting mad fucking war from this guy like like like this guy obviously fucked up.
He obviously fucked up making like a markable and now his like chakras are inverted and he and he's like a totally like male dominated brain.
So he like he just knows how to plunder puss.
That's all he's ever known.
He's just in a bitter puss famine and all he knows is bitter puss starvation and he's just trying to fucking sling it whenever and all possible.
He's like at a level like like seven seven crass consciousness.
He's fucking up there.
He's ready.
How do I get back to the man I once was?
He's his own beast now Jesse.
You can't control him.
You are.
He's his own person.
We split apart this fall from grace when I stopped using Gaia online.
I just noticed he has a cane too.
He's a sword and a cane and a fucking nebula behind him.
He's a fucking galactic pimp.
When we went back to my little pony it wasn't it wasn't far enough.
We have to go backer.
We have to go back to being in wombs.
He's like a combination of like a pimp and a celestial warrior and a school shooter and a god and and and a kingdom hearts and a kingdom.
He's so like oh my god.
He's just gonna rame some fucking dream with that.
You can fuck.
He slammed so much puss he like opened a rift in the universe behind him.
I don't know.
I don't know what that background is but it looks like he's like really tiny standing on the top of a table in some kitchen.
Yeah.
Oh it kind of does.
And he's got a tiny galaxy.
Yeah I don't know what the background is like why it's like a weird kitchen thing.
I don't know if you can change that but I definitely I made sure to put the fucking celestial warp hole behind me.
He's one inch but his density is like the same as our son.
Yeah.
Because that that celestial warp hole that you know that's where I was born from and where I will return to one day.
God willing.
If you all pledge enough to my patreon.com slash endless Jess.
I can become that man again.
Please this is my dream.
Please.
That like universe in the background is the endless.
Yes it's the source of my power.
God damn.
Oh my fucking god.
He's so he's his hat too.
Man I can't wait for Ben not to edit this picture in and everyone is like what the fuck are they talking about.
No.
Ben you son of a bitch.
God damn it.
Why do why do we even bother?
Why don't we just hire a big old monkey from the fucking zoo to do our taxes.
Our fucking what is wrong with you.
Why don't we just get that son of a bitch Donkey Kong and do it.
Yeah.
They can prove his worth for once.
Save the mic.
Pull his own weight.
The most the most useless member of the procrastinators fucking Donkey Kong.
I'm sick of his shit.
He never shows up and he only was interested when we started doing the Patreon.
Like that's the only reason he's fucking here.
He's only in for the fucking money.
We just need to fucking kick him.
Donkey Kong what the fuck.
Yeah that greedy.
You know it's all about the fucking banana horde with him.
That's all he talks about.
That's all I hear about.
His precious fucking banana horde.
He's just in it for those Patreon nanners.
And I'm you know and you know what the rest of us need money Donkey Kong okay.
He converted the Patreon to only pay us in bananas.
And that's not working for anyone but him.
Perfect banana.
And it's a fucking crime.
I cannot think of a single worst thing than talking about social media.
Yeah.
I cannot think of like the worst thing.
I really wish you were doing.
I've been trying to think of this.
I've been trying to think desperately of anything interesting to say about it.
Okay.
I have a point.
I can bring up about social media.
Please Tom.
Okay.
Do you see because everyone except for possibly Bunchy was around before social media.
Do you find right that it's incredibly frustrating that social media has completely transformed
our like perceptions of success and audience and like like our perceptions of talent and
skill and all that.
Oh yes.
Because I feel like because of social media like now I feel like pressured to like be famous
almost or like be successful back in the day like it was just like you did shit and
like you kind of put it out there for your community.
And like if your community that was like the length like the reach of your social kind
of like perceptions.
But now with social media like celebrities can be like anybody sitting on their couch
doing whatever.
So like it's like celebrity used to be like this kind of like separate thing where like
you weren't but now it's anybody.
So it's like well why am I not like have a million subscribers and like all this shit
because like there's no excuse now for me not to do it.
And like this is and we've like kind of changed our perception of like skill and ability because
I know online and all these exceptions to the rule like these great people kind of rise
to the top and that kind of changes what that kind of feels like the new norm because that's
all you see.
So it's just like why am I not that good.
Why am I not that famous.
Why am I not that successful.
And it's just like if you don't even have a hundred thousand subscribers it's like you're
not you're not anything.
Right.
Well I don't worry.
I don't worry so much about how it's changing our perception of like fame or success.
I worry about like how it's changing our perception of each other as human beings
and even of ourselves because we all have this like everyone in the world now has this
alter ego that they sell to the world via social media and like the people you see like
if there's anyone in your life who you know on social media and also off social media
it's like the social media person is not them.
It's not even like remotely them.
Nobody online is even close to their like you go on Facebook like you know.
You've got friends on Facebook and you see them posting like political shit all the time
just because that's all there is to talk about on Facebook.
So they're just posting this inane annoying political shit.
They're getting in arguments and like anyone they look like on Facebook they just look
like annoying assholes to you who you would never talk to and you look at this person
who you know as a human being like this is not you this is not this person.
The real version of this person doesn't give a fuck about this.
It's only on social media.
Let me tell you about that real quick because I've had a couple experiences that relate to this
and it's so I went skydiving a couple years ago just for fun and I went by myself purely
for the joy of doing it because I was really interested in trying it and I also want to die
but so I went and did it and but like the thing about it that was really interesting to me
was how like the big theme that dominated this whole place was like hey guys
you know buy the pictures that we're going to take of you while you're doing it.
Don't you want to upload this to your fucking Facebook?
Don't you want to like tweet about this to everybody?
Like that's what we know that's why you're here right?
You're here so you can put this on fucking Facebook and show everyone how cool you are
which you're actually not you're just doing this so that you can look cool online.
Like every so many people were just there for that reason and then just the other day
I was at the Creation Museum where it's just my favorite place because I love Jesus
and like I did the zipline thing.
My parents were in town we did this zipline thing and it was super fun
but again like there was just so much like there were all these pictures they automatically take
and they're just trying to shill you on like buying the pictures
obviously so that you can post to social media so that you can look cool
and like feel like a cool boy.
It's just God like I that's what I resent about social media.
Now it's got people so focused on like like perception of each other
as opposed to actually doing things that are actually fun and interesting.
It's always weird for me to think about stuff like that
because like I've never really used social media in the way that a lot of people just you know
they use it they take pictures of things where they've been
what food they're eating you know just retweeting,
re-blogging like things that they see or agree with.
Like I don't do that because I have been primarily a creative person on the Internet.
I've been making stuff I put stuff out there to be to be shown
and it's the same basic principle like I like attention.
I like people to say how good job but for people who don't create stuff for the Internet
they it's like it's like a totally different side of you know of existence
just being there I don't I can't really understand exactly what they're going through
like I get the basic like they just want to feel like the you know people like them
but I don't know what their their purpose is like what they they expect to get out of something like
like oh you got like a ton of followers now does that mean you're famous does that mean you're popular?
Social currency yeah it's a social it's yeah it's a currency.
People they want attention and love and stuff like everybody else
but they they're doing it in a very passive way they're not really trying
but they don't feel I don't know what whether they feel like it's like something they're doing actively
and failing at if they're not famous or whether they just do it because they don't realize that you don't need to.
Well I think a lot of people just enjoy any kind of feedback like for a lot of people
I'm sure like one like on whatever they post is yeah something to make some happy and I admit like
I totally do this as well so I'm not trying to like excuse myself like I think a lot of this just
appeals to like base human instincts to like feel happy when people give a shit about you in any capacity
and the fact that social media has changed the game so the entire world like can can focus on whatever you're trying to do
you know it's just it's going to change the way we we go about the shit but like you know I tweet pictures of funny things
I see mostly because I think they're funny but but like at the at the base level like yes I'm trying to like I guess
like get love you know like to feel like people give a shit about me which is why I post things from my day that I enjoy.
I do that stuff as well like I think of something to say I record it or I take a picture of it
but it always goes back to like making I don't know some sort of video so making it presentable
and I you know like compared to just throwing it out there with nothing and I'm not trying to say like
You make puns all the time that are related to videos or anything.
Well not that not that I mean like like say if I have like a vlog idea like I have a point I want to make
I wouldn't just make it I would put it in a vlog on give and take that would either have something else in it
or well actually I don't know maybe I'm gay maybe I don't know what I'm saying.
It sounds like you're making a distinction kind of between like I guess this kind of not important things that people put out there.
Yeah that's the thing I was about to say like I don't I don't I'm not saying I'm more important because I put more effort into the things I say
but I feel like I don't I don't understand the mindset exactly of people who who just you know throw stuff out there.
I don't know whether they enjoy it or whether they even consider it being anyone really enjoys it.
I think everyone like feels like obligated just like an empty zombie feeling but like they're just like addicted to like this.
This this this disturbing endorphin rush of like all day constantly selling yourself for it like we're just endorphin whores now we need that rush.
Would anyone in the world rather like make a tweet and get like I don't know let's say like a thousand likes you know and a bunch of comments.
Would anyone prefer that to like having a good friend that they go spend like a few hours with like which of those sounds more appealing.
It's just like it's just like this weird drug that people like nobody I think nobody's like in love with social media like at most people tolerated or accept it.
I think deep down inside we all feel the same way about it.
That's why like Black Mirror is such a successful show because deep inside we all know that this shit is fucked up.
We just can't do anything about it.
We can't pull ourselves away from it as a society like.
It seems harmless and it kind of is but it's just like it's like a cumulative like over time you just forget why you started doing it.
It's like it's supposed to be like a nice addition to life to be able to talk to your friends when they're not there.
And then it sort of becomes you know a replacement for it or or it takes over your real life or it just makes you forget what you're doing.
It's freaky and it's sad like I remember you know you know like I had this friend who was like really going through a hard time and like really depressed and like you know like we'd sit and talk
and like we'd like connect as humans and she's talk about like how sad she is and like you know like real stuff but then like I'd see her posting on social media constantly
and it's all these like happy like look at me selling yourself smiling fake fucking posts because that's what you have to do and it's just like this can't be healthy.
This is fucked up that we have to constantly sell ourselves as these people with good lives when all of our lives are secretly terrible.
Like you're not allowed to be sad on social media because then you become that guy and like nobody wants to be that guy.
Yeah I have been that guy but I feel like well like no no I have just been that guy there's nothing more to that I have been that guy.
I feel like occasionally occasionally it's okay but it's it's always like like dangerous like oh you feel bad but you don't want to talk to anybody because you've already talked to them recently about how you feel bad.
So then you're just stuck thinking like well I mean this is what happened to me like if I if I didn't have any like doubts I would be posting constantly about sad things but I don't.
I keep it all bottled up but then I don't have any wanting real life to go and talk to about it so I don't know what to do.
It's just it's just one of those things this is gay I don't like it.
Being sad in the modern age I it has gotten like worse than being sad used to be for all of human history because like social media has like worked against us to compound all these feelings of anxiousness and loneliness and like.
It's because you just I not to mention not to mention the worst and feeling lonely when it looks like everyone else is having like this fantastic wonderful life and like even though it may be a lie but it looks that way and it's just.
I think I know why that it is is that when you post something like oh man life sucks and it goes on Twitter.
It stays on there like you have to delete it you know have to actively delete it if you're out with a friend and you're like man I'm feeling sad and they're like oh what's up buddy and then you talk to them and then it's done and then.
You know they don't have to constantly know that it's there or see it occasionally again people aren't constantly you know learning of it of the first time like.
You know media has it's very fleeting but it's still sort of permanent this like entire new obstacle to human interaction like it took me this long in my life to master regular face to face human interaction but now there's like a whole new set of rules were like.
If I if I want to talk to somebody like especially about something serious like if I'm sad or like if I want to you know like you pull their fucking name up in the little box and you just like stare at it like.
Okay how in the fuck do I start this kind of like what do you even say in that little box I don't know how to start a box conversation on Facebook it's the most nerve wracking thing in the world like.
Hi what's up can I talk to you you can't do it and then you know there's that ever present fucking fear that you're just going to get that scene it's just going to say scene for like 48 hours.
And then you're just dangling from a fucking like a fish hook like what did I say wrong what did I do all I said was hi.
It's a nightmare it's a fucking nightmare.
It's interesting the way that like those kind of situation.
I just I've never had that but I've but I never use it so like my social media experiences I only talk to people that I don't interact with in like real life on a daily basis.
So like I don't have that weird perception of like trying to interact with like people I know in real life online and for me it's very separate like.
That fucking message box and that fucking like check scene has made it a thousand times harder to like reach out.
It's become worse than it's ever been in human history.
There's no more like calling someone on the phone and just talking there's no more just you know you just can't you just can't because it's going to say scene for 78 hours and you're going to feel bad for that long because they're busy doing something and you know you know in your in your rational mind.
That life is just hectic for everybody and everyone you know you like I can't respond to a message.
Nobody likes responding to a message and that's part of why you feel bad messaging in the first place.
So you know that like it's nothing personal probably but you don't care you lizard brain you're fucking fearful amygdala fucking animal part of you is sitting there curled up in a corner.
You know like they hate me they want me to die they're never going to talk to me again.
They just want me to do the wisest guy talking to me and I'm just going to fucking kill myself with a guy that's praying on you when you're already at a low point.
Did I did I ever tell you guys my it's an anxiety machine.
That's what these things do.
I think they do it on purpose.
I think it's they're trying to like they know they know what they're doing.
Yeah like they know that this system is in place.
They must have heard like you know this is a criticism like sure I guess there are advantages to but you know it's it's inherently creates this problem as well.
And let me tell you guys this the story ahead about this.
So when I was in high school I knew this girl and she was kind of weird but she was she was very I don't know interested in me and I don't know we eventually went our separate ways.
But like a couple years later I just get a message from her on Facebook and this is when I still use it in college sometime and it just like hey what's up or something along those lines.
And I you know I looked at it and I was like I do not want to talk to this person and so I you know went off to do other things.
And like a day later or something I get this fucking message from her again.
It's like this giant wall of text called me a fucking piece of shit.
Like I think I'm so much better than her like I can't be bothered to talk to this girl.
It's too much trouble for me to go out of my way to talk to this girl who cared about me so much in high school or some shit like that.
And so like and it's all because she saw the like she saw the scene message.
She knew that I had seen this and chose not to respond.
And as a result she felt all these horrible feelings and I didn't want to feel that way but I what could I do.
That was Facebook who did that and just to finish it off like I get a message like a year later.
Like I believe that was still mad and just like you know OK I'm still mad about you not responding but you know maybe we can get over this and then I believe like a year after that or so.
She's like OK you know what I forgive you so thank you young lady for that narrative arc.
Sorry I spaced out there for a second.
I was farming my turnips that I have in my house and I didn't want it.
I didn't want to.
I've told you a thousand times turnip time is not podcast time.
There's I can't put my turnips on wait then they'll they'll they'll see the box that says seen and they'll know that I'm ignoring them.
I have to tend to them immediately.
Yeah anyway the worst thing in the world even more than the check mark scene box is when is when you're just mind your own business and you get the.
And then you check your phone and then like your brain doesn't even process each words you just see like whoever the fuck huge piece of text.
Like you just see you just see like a paragraph and you know shits about to fucking hit the fan and that you are going to die.
No good person has ever written that much in a message in the history of the world.
The worst was like before the smartphones when like it would say like text message one slash seven.
Oh boy.
And you always like to think that you know you don't do it to other people that but it's impossible to not do it.
It's just it's everything you don't do affects people and everything you do do is is really terrible.
It's it's it's it's just constantly it's constantly like death.
I just don't.
I mean it's constantly death.
Yes.
I everything's bad.
There's there's a few moments that I can recall where like like reading a big thing like that like oh no no no this is the exact worst thing you could have said it made me literally sick.
I was just like no I just I threw my phone on the bed and I jumped out the window and I'm dead.
I fell into a pile of poop.
It's just horrible.
Every single time.
Sometimes even worse than long paragraphs are just messages that are just like oh or like hmm.
That just just just like one just like just like I just noise just noise messages just so you know I just wish like I just wish that there was a way to get better at it so that you could you could.
You could just like make people feel better in text but it's so difficult because you can't you can't like you could send them a little emoticon saying you know hug but it's not the same as a hug.
It's not the same as like it's not the same as like like like sometimes sometimes people just need to vent in front of you and you just you don't need to say anything you just need to be there and they need to know that you're listening and you can't do that in text.
If you ignore them they think you're ignoring them and if you say something then they think you you have something to say I don't it's just fucking.
I mean yeah we could talk about the weakness of like text as a medium in general because do you guys ever get this like there's some people I talked to in a very specific like cadence.
Like I'll always put just for whatever reason some people I talked to I always put like lol at the end of my sentences.
So if I ever don't put lol it looks like I'm fucking pissed and this is this is real this is terrible like this yeah like you box yourself into this this sort of thing or like you always put a smiley face if you don't they look you look mad as fuck.
It's just I can't fucking hate writing text and talking online that way so limited so bullshit thank God emoticons make things better at least a little bit.
You can't there's no you can't understand like the context and stuff with.
Yeah they won't know that my cadence that I'm using in my words like when I called you a big dick nigg like that was ironic don't you understand.
It's no it's it's super fucked up and there's a bunch there's like I mean everyone has this when you you said something in jest or you said something as a joke and they take it seriously like no no like fuck and they're like totally like changes the tone of the entire conversation.
Then you have to fucking backtrack and explain yeah and then you're just like fuck and then like any any kind of energy that was going is gone and then it's just like I guess I'll talk to you later.
You know what I'm glad I'm glad things like Snapchat and Twitter video and YouTube and all this around so that at least there's audio at least there's video and audio that people are communicating with more nowadays instead of just.
It's better and and emails and messages as if people are doing that more often if the Internet is getting better at handling video in large quantities than that would be better for everyone I think.
All that being said you guys are all whining social media spy is matter.
Well I mean there is the fact that he's a symptom of this fuck.
He was birthed from the fucking wireframe res dimension of the net.
First I was nothing then I was a tweet.
You're like the roadkill on the information super highway.
Oh oh that reminds me dude OK fucking going back to that one thing Nate said about how people want to take your picture and like use it to like profile like racially profile you.
Yeah that's what I said right.
So so one time I walked into a fucking Mexican restaurant and I was like I was I was looking like a used Band-Aid Sultan motherfuckers I was ready to expend no expenses.
I was ready to throw my green no matter where.
And up comes this fucking like like hunchback hunchback of carne asada.
She comes up and she's like you have to pay for it.
And I fucking I punted her in the next fucking week.
She's gone.
That's my media story.
Where did this happen.
Where was this.
This was this was my my Mexican zone.
Oh right.
OK OK.
The zone.
I like the Twilight Zone.
Yeah I don't like this.
Like the thing that bothers me the most of this shit is this like industry that sprung up around like supporting people's social media addictions in that way like that seems not good.
That's that's a bad thing to me in my in my humble opinion.
Yeah it's just no one's actions should be motivated primarily by wanting to look cool on social media.
You can do that as a consequence.
That's fine.
I just don't like that.
Too focused on that's that's the problem.
You guys are just you're just thinking about it too much.
Just don't use social media for anything other than just like hmm I'm thinking about this.
I guess I'll just say it's not like the goal should never be social media.
Just use it if you want to.
And if you don't want to it's not just like like the social bitch.
It's not just the social media like like websites like things like discord as well.
It's still the problem with with text is being is bad for for for communicating.
Well sure then yeah.
So like a lot of the time it's just it's just worse than being there in person.
But of course it's necessary because you can't be there in person because I don't live in the same country as any of you people.
I would have never known any of you if it not for the social media.
So like it's it's obviously good that it connects the world but it's it's terrible because we're connected in a weird robotic not real human way.
I would challenge that a little bit and I would say that yes like we absolutely you know like we came to know each other through YouTube which you know.
Well the thing about the YouTube is that it's video is that we could hear each other and we did podcasts.
It was it was more real than just text and comments and things like that.
Yeah I just like would our complaint mostly be about like the problematic nature of like just using text and not having context or something.
I would say it's more than that.
I mean the text is a huge fucking problem because like it doesn't matter what medium is if you're communicating through.
Delete language in bullish language.
I actually do kind of hate the spoken word and the written word for that matter they're both bullshit.
But like I was going to say that God I'm looking at this picture this big titted bitch and I forgot what I was going to say.
Social media putting social god damn social media distracted me from the shit I was trying to say.
Yeah I don't know.
It's it's it's gay but like I would say that the way that we talk to each other now like using discord the way we do now just to like you stay in contact with each other and you know like be friends.
That's not like the same as social media per se that's that's a difference.
It's it's it's not but it's just them.
Social media is like the way people relate to like the mass audience of the people out there you know like that's as opposed to like one on one.
Because you said like the first social network thing you sign up for was AIM and I don't think AIM was social media because that was more about connecting you with people that you already knew like social media is when you
Okay that's true.
Try and project yourself out into an audience.
Yeah that's true.
And try and.
That's not the issue.
Alright Tom.
There's something shit in my mouth a little more Tom.
I'm sorry.
All right.
I'm just I'm trying to make a distinction.
But you're right here.
You're right.
I don't know.
I just it's it's so I think the weirdest thing for me is just like how like there's these huge corporations now that like are subsisting on everyone's desire for for attention.
Yeah.
Like Facebook is like like I mean I always knew that Facebook was like fucked up.
But like when you realize how Facebook makes its money like you know it's just advertising like that's how they make their money.
And the reason they have all these fields you to put in is because you're being logged into an advertising database.
Like the scariest thing for me ever because like I'm doing all this research on like business and stuff is when I found out about Facebook ads.
And like if you use the Facebook ad manager it's the scariest fucking thing in the world because it like it just taps into everyone's profile.
So you just type in whatever you want.
It's like here are like seven million people that are exactly the specifications you're looking for.
And we're going to you can pay like 10 cents to shove ads in their face.
Like that's how they make all their money.
And it's like super fucking weird how they've taken your personal life and like are making money off of it.
It's super fucked up.
Yeah.
I mean it makes sense logically.
I get the business side of it.
I just don't like it.
Right.
Well that's the whole thing.
It totally makes sense.
I mean that's why like if I was ever going to like start selling a product I'd use Facebook ads because it totally makes sense.
But like it's still like fucking evil and like really creepy.
When are ads going to die?
I have never bought anything.
The only time will be ever completely changed like the nature of the economic system of the country.
That's the only way that advertisement.
The only things like I ever buy is when I type in Google for something that I need and I find it and then I research it a bit and then I buy it usually because it's an electronic something or other.
But like an ad for like I don't know maybe even something I'd like like oh look Mario Kart 3 like a new one.
Go play it on your Switch.
I'm like well I play video games but you know I'm the right demographic but I'm trying to watch a video right now.
I don't give a shit.
There's more to advertising than just like saying like here's the thing go buy it.
It's planting the seed that you might want in the future in your head.
So like now you're aware that you know Mario Kart 3 for Wii Switch exists or Nintendo Switch exists.
And so like in the future like when you're thinking about like oh what's a game that I might want to get.
I mean that one looked okay.
Maybe I'll do that.
It's about like the long term game I think.
It's about planting like brand recognition.
Like subconsciously like everybody knows about the Galaxy S8 because you've seen it everywhere.
So like it's just like in your brain.
And I didn't know what until just now I'm starting to think maybe you're an ad.
I'm starting to think I'm being shooted to.
Buy the Galaxy S8 from Samsung.com with my affiliate link.
Hey guys.
Welcome to the new Rebel Pixels.
Please please give me quarters.
Oh by the way that was an excellent time to debut.
What I've decided is your new nickname Tom.
And it's Tom Cintiq Alternative Oliver.
That's you.
That's totally fine.
That's a nice pre-packaged meme there you got there on a silver platter.
I don't even get it.
And I'm proud of not getting it because it means I'm one less into the internet thing.
I take it back.
Advertising is not stupid.
It makes sense.
It works whatever.
But I hate that everything is based on views and clicks and watch time and people having
and it's like just give me five bucks on Patreon.
But I like Patreon so much more because I don't know where I'm going with this.
It's nothing to do with social media.
I just I just I fucking hate everything about the world and the internet is pretty gay.
The internet is definitely like all the stuff I hate about the world but like more of it
all the time.
And right at my computer where I'm trying to play Dark Souls 4.
You know the Facebook is just getting worse.
I was pretty excited to do this topic and then coming here I realized that there's nothing to say.
Yeah.
No one cares about your turnips.
We've already talked about them.
God.
Why do you turn me into the A1 sauce?
Don't put me on your burger.
I can turn into solids.
Please just give me a chance.
What are you talking about?
Are turnips A1 sauce?
Is that real?
Yeah.
I made it.
Please have some.
Please drink it.
Mom.
No.
Are you are you fucking me right now?
Is A1 sauce made from turnips?
No.
You fucking fool.
I deceived you yet again.
You fucking Washington fat cat.
You don't deserve to know real things.
I'll only give you lies.
God damn.
Alright.
You gotta fucking play dude.
Social media is gay.
We all hate it and it's fine.
I want to talk instead because it's a terrible topic and we should never talk about this.
Instead instead.
We can go to questions at any time.
Well instead.
You're right.
Let's talk about Munchies turnips.
I don't know.
I want to talk about like fucking RuneScape.
RuneScape is cool.
I went on RuneScape.
RuneScape is social media dude.
You were chatting about cuties.
Yeah.
It's a multiplayer.
Let's talk about MMOs.
MMOs are huge and it's like you talk to people and they're nerds.
Sometimes you find out that they're like 30 years old and they're like, whoa, wait,
a 30 year old can play a game and it's like impossible.
How are you like talking to me as if anyone could be talking to me?
You're 30.
You're like, that's the size of one of my parents.
That doesn't make any sense and then I'm like, okay, cool.
Yeah, I can talk to people of any age.
Story sounds like it's going down some dark roads.
It's weird when you realize that you can talk to people of like multiple different big
ages and realize that they're just human.
I think playing World of Warcraft made me realize that adults are people and that I would become
one and I wouldn't change.
You know what?
People interact with teenagers and realize they're not human.
That's true, man.
That's one of the great things about a social media in general.
The tale of two kitties, rape me Eddie Murphy.
Case in point.
Case in point, Munchy.
He's not a man.
He's a beast.
Social media is really good for getting past any kind of like normal social obstacles
that would be in the way and I met some pretty cool people who definitely would not have
gotten to know because they live a million miles away thanks to social media.
This entire time that we've been doing this podcast, I have had non-stop in my ear Facebook
notification dings and dongs and beeps and boops going off.
It's gotten worse to like not let you off of it because even when you don't have it in
a tab, even when it's not open, you'll still hear the notification beats.
How is that possible?
I don't know how they do it.
And now I got to a thing where like not only like a thing will come up on my desktop now
of the notification.
You must have installed something.
You fucked up.
No, no, you fucked up.
There was notifications, right?
Yeah, there was a little thing.
Some sites do this now that say, oh, do you want to allow this site to enable desktop notifications
which just fucks up everything and you have to turn it, you have to turn it off.
Otherwise you'll die.
Maybe I'd like to ask the internet if they'd like to enable my dick in its ear.
How'd you like that?
My puppy dog dick in your ear.
Skeetin' on the internet all over here.
That's what I was saying to you.
Hey, hey, is this social media?
Kaiser Permanente, duly exanenite, 60 milligram capsules.
Is this social media?
Because I'm gonna drink it all.
Oh, there he goes, folks.
There he goes.
He's taking the red pills.
All right.
You know, I'll tell you the ultimate red pill.
I am Red Permanente.
I do not like social media.
Shut up, Sans.
I didn't like that character.
I did not like him at all.
I hate him.
You know, I'll tell you the ultimate red pill.
You know, isn't real life the original social media?
Oh, my God, no.
This is too black-pilled.
I can't look at that.
I only see darkness.
Wait, what does that even imply?
That real life is just as good as real life.
Real life is just as good or bad as Facebook.
Maybe it's that we spend all our lives trying to impress people.
Like, okay, yeah, here's a red pill like all men care about
is tricking women into having sex with them.
All women care about is tricking men into giving them resources
and our entire lives are based solely on those facts
and everything else is irrelevant bullshit.
Just beating around the fucking bush.
Are these the red pills?
Are my red pills?
I hate them.
Nowadays, I can put in a good old video game
and just go into a microphone for four hours
and people tell me that they enjoyed it
and I can feel so powerful.
That shouldn't happen, but it does.
And I thank social media for making people
emotionless as voids of human beings
that enjoy me just playing a video game.
How stupid is that?
You used to have to go out and make a friend
and now you can just load up a fucking let's play
and you've got an instant friend all pre-packaged
and ready to go.
So, so, so good.
So good for my ego.
Here is the official Munchie stance on social media.
Okay.
People are vapid, people are valid,
connects people, very cool, awful,
no value, very value, fun, being not dead is a lie.
That's the end of my notes.
It's like...
It's just like home stuck.
Everything Munchie says is typed into Google Translate
and translated back and forth from different languages
like 20 times.
It's translated into ancient Mesopotamian
and I'm just...
I'm not even talking right now,
I'm just transmitting these ideas
directly into audacity.
Some always figure out how to do that in real time too,
which is a really impressive part.
Yeah.
Very...
Well, I could certainly...
I could talk about this topic for a thousand years
because I hate social media with an intensity
that rivals that of a thousand vengeful gods
and I want to die just thinking about it.
I want to die every aspect of it,
every facet of it is bad.
I actually know how to fix social media.
What if...
You know how like there's like the text boxes?
What if we replaced all of those on every websites?
Instead of them being boxes,
they were cowboy hat shaped.
Hmm...
No, I'll tell you how to fix social media.
Social media.
You...
Control...
Out...
Delete...
This is what I would do.
I would implement a law.
My favorite webcomic.
Yes.
There needs to be a law for the entire land,
for all the world.
If anything you say,
anything,
if a hundred people have said it before,
you are executed.
That's a pretty good rule.
Because I'm sick and tired of hearing the same jokes.
I'm sick and tired of people just repeating each other
like thinking they're clever from saying the same shit,
regurgitating memes.
Press one, guys.
Press one in the fucking comments if you hate memes.
Oh, god.
You guys, god damn it.
You did it.
You know what?
That really bugs me.
Because sometimes I hear a joke somewhere,
and then by the time it gets to my normal friends,
it's gone through its phases of becoming boring and stupid,
and it's gone to various websites like 9Gag,
I don't fucking know,
and they catch onto it and then they say it,
and I'm like,
well, I know that it's a joke to you,
so I'm not going to make fun of you for saying it,
so it's fine,
but I still, I just feel a bit bad.
I just feel a bit bad about the fact that
we see the same things,
and nothing can be unique and fun anymore.
That's why every time I make a joke,
I make sure that it's,
I slave over it to make sure that it's not a meme.
If any of my jokes become memes,
I will kill myself.
Yeah, that's my curse.
Everything I say becomes a meme
because I'm too goddamn funny and cool, I guess.
I can't, I can't not create new memes,
and then people just repeat my own shit back at me,
and I want to strangle them.
I want to strangle everyone all the time
who repeats anything that I've ever said.
It's my jokes, you can't have them,
and if you can't put in the effort
to create your own original jokes,
then you shouldn't be allowed to say anything
that you even think is funny ever, you should be executed.
I agree, and similarly, but a different take on that
is when you have a group,
or you have a joke in a certain group,
there's a lot of 4chan jokes,
just say Pepe, for example.
Pepe was a big dank meme,
and then other people started picking him out
and using him for different stuff,
and Katy Perry tweets a picture of Pepe,
and it just gets out, and the joke becomes diluted.
This one has managed to survive
by just escalating how fucked up Pepe is
and just making people not want to use him anymore.
That was good stuff.
But Reddit constantly is stealing jokes from 4chan
and just reposting it there.
And it's not just me.
My secret club is being infiltrated by other people.
Get out, you fucking normies!
Get out of my secret club!
Nate was the real Pepe all along.
There's a bird! There's a bird on my window!
That wasn't a joke.
I can't tell if you're launching into a bit
or making a real observation.
No, that wasn't a fucking joke.
That wasn't a joke.
There was a bird and he looked at me
and he ran away because he was really scared.
Well, it's probably scared because you just yelled
that there was a bird.
It was the Twitter bird coming into touch.
Oh my god, no!
It was doctor foul play.
It was probably doctor foul, to be honest.
Okay, well, I think we're good.
Shall we go to questions?
Alright, fine, finish your point, god damn it.
Why don't we just put them in the oven
and cook them till you're cooked?
Let's take a fork in them, alright?
Go on, go on.
Just one last thing.
When I go to my friends and I really like them...
Hey guys, I'm Munchy.
Let me tell you all about my new ghetto supernova butt beams
coming out of the eighth chakra dimension
of the fucking Flipple Club.
Listen, someone said to me the other day,
funny Prozac clown makes me want to kill Christians
windmill style.
I thought it was really funny and I really liked it
and it made me laugh.
Thank you, Kyle, for saying that to me
and it was really funny.
Good job, Kyle.
Shout out to Kyle.
Thank you, fan.
Okay, alright.
Alright, let's go to questions.
Everybody remember at Twitter,
at TP Crassinators,
ask us questions there on Saturday when we record this shit.
Okay, let's see what we got here.
First question by at Wienermeister says,
what is a Chuck E. Cheese Fun Buck?
Munchy, tell us, please.
Why are friends...
How did you know that we were going to watch Chuck E. Cheese?
Why do they even watch the show
if they don't know our official currency?
The official PCP currency.
It's another example of social media being bad, you know?
We have these fans that are not even good.
These fans, they don't even watch the PCP
in Chuck E. Cheese.
Like, we keep telling them that they're supposed to.
You can only watch the PCP in a Chuck E. Cheese.
That's the only time you're supposed to.
And you know what?
If you're not doing it fucking right.
This question actually just reminded me
of a point I did want to make about social media.
And it's a grad to 4chan.
My social media stuff is totally fine,
but I spend way more of my time
just anonymously browsing and posting on 4chan threads
because I much prefer to be anonymous.
And it's much more enjoyable to be appreciated
on the value of your ideals, you know,
in whatever context, or not your ideals,
but your ideas that you put forward.
Like, it's way more enjoyable to succeed
in a pure meritocratic system like that.
Okay, that's it. That's the whole point.
But 4chan, wait a minute.
Are you telling me that you've been the 4chaner
this whole time?
I am.
The 4chaner 666.
That is me.
I am the legendary villain
who's been playing the PCP for generations.
It was me all along Jesse.
It was me all along.
You're that son of a bitch
who said all the wrong things on 4chan
about the stuff I like.
I'm saying of all of you, dude.
Oh my fucking god, Jesse.
Oh my god. Oh my god.
I hear you want to die real quick?
Hold on. Let me tell you how you should do it.
So I was on 4chan once.
I'm sorry.
Don't do it. Big mistake.
But also, I saw a fucking web him
of your video, of one of your videos.
It was the Super Mario Bros. 3 one
and it blew my gosh dang gasket out.
Whoa, what?
That's awesome.
You said, well, I knew that
a bunch of my shitty videos
are memes and viral things.
You're telling me
that my Super Mario Bros. 3
masturbating on the couch video
that people actually...
a web him?
Yeah, I saw it on 4chan.
I saw it on V1s.
Was it the whole thing?
I don't think it was the whole thing.
I think it was just like 30 seconds.
Well, that's pretty cool.
It's the whole thing I'm fucking pissed
because that's free-booting
and I'll kill everyone involved.
But if it's just a clip
with big fucking gigantic words on it that says
it's just property, go there.
Then it's okay.
You need to put giant watermarks
across all your videos.
We're not allowed to laugh at this
unless you laugh at it on YouTube,
on my channel, and subscribe,
and Patreon, me and Les Jess.
Speaking of that,
I actually, you know,
my Galco video has got a lot of views and shit.
It's like somebody posted a 30-second clip of it
on their Tumblr
and got 17,000 responses or something,
and I'm like, that's my 17,000.
Give him back.
Give him back, guys.
Weaponize thickness, bro!
No, no.
Guys, shut up.
He's weaponize thickness guy ever.
You know what?
That video going as viral as it did
makes me so angry,
not just because it sucks,
but because all of your other videos
are so good.
And like, that weaponize thickness meme,
everyone keeps repeating it.
That's what I said before.
People just repeat shit.
It's so fucking annoying.
No one has any creativity,
no spark of life to them.
And it's like, God,
there's so many things that you've said
that are funnier than that line.
I know.
It's funny if you're like an 80-year-old
who's never heard a joke before.
Guys, you know the show?
Here's what the show said.
Yeah, that's exactly what it is.
And you know, like, it's weird.
I'm getting the sense that I think
a lot of the reason the video was so popular
is because it was passed along to like,
I mean, I don't want to jump the gun and be too...
Social justice warrior fat chicks.
Kind of.
Like, a lot of people I see
responding to the thickness meme by being like,
yeah, because I also say like real women have curves.
Meanwhile, like in context,
we're talking about fucking Galco,
like the sexiest woman in the world,
talking to a literal child with like,
it's not that she's talking to like skinny bitches,
like, yeah, I'm, you know, big and beautiful.
No, you're not...
You're not...
If that's what you got out of that scene,
you do not understand what I was trying to say.
So please, people,
educate yourselves.
Those SJW fat chicks, you know,
I used to think that SJWs were a force for good,
but then the fat chicks started infiltrating their ranks.
And they just tainted it like a cancer from within,
a fat cancer.
Yeah.
Like, what is ethics in our journalism?
God damn it!
All I want is ethics!
Damn you fat people!
You ruined social justice!
You ruined the movement!
Now I have to go be a fucking all right F.A. Meemerman!
Guys, please drop in our music job of the hut.
I want one of those.
Yep, it's true.
Okay, I guess let's go to the next question.
Okay, here's one.
I don't know.
This might be self-injured in masturbation,
but after Kraft's dwarf here,
my buddy, you know, a friend of the show,
says, is there a PCB betting pool
on the likelihood of Nate succeeding in Mia Maffova?
Do you guys think I'm going to succeed?
Do you think I'm going to fail?
No.
What do you think?
You've already basically failed, haven't you?
No.
Like the second one was like after midnight, right?
It was not.
Look at the fucking date.
It was on time.
God damn it, they've all been on time so far.
All right, all right.
Yeah, I give that like two more days.
You think so?
We'll see.
Sorry, I cut out for the entirety of that question.
Is Mama Mia fuck a butcher?
This guy's like, is there a betting pool
that Nate's going to fail at Mia Maffova?
Nate, I watched the first one.
Yeah.
And I just saw, I was just like,
all right, Nate's finally just going to make some vlogs.
No, there's still a fuck ton of editing.
I'm just like, what is wrong with you?
I know, I can't stop.
Just fucking talk.
Like I'm trying to force myself to stop.
Like that, but it's very hard.
You know what, we need to,
the new challenge for Mia Maffova,
you should just make it all in Windows Movie Maker.
You have to make it in that.
That's not a bad idea.
Maybe I'll do something like that.
Yeah, you'll still make cuts.
I will make cuts.
And you'll do the thing where it goes all the different colors.
Yeah, half the video will just be in Spectrum View
and it'll just be like flashing colors.
Yeah.
By the way, teach me what Spectrum View is,
because that sounds awesome.
I don't actually understand what that is.
It's like, have you ever seen,
like all the old Windows Movie Maker,
like AMVs where it like goes from like,
it's like goes through the color spectrum,
like it's all red and it's orange
and it's, you know, yellow.
Oh my God, that's awesome.
Like phases through all the different colors.
I really want to do that for like actual videos,
but it's too difficult.
Yeah, in the way.
You want to click on Windows Movie Maker.
We need to all get Windows Movie Maker.
That's the end of it.
By the way, guys, by the way, guys,
if you want to know what Munchie sees the world as,
like, I don't know if you guys know this,
but I am, I'm like, I'm like reverse blood.
Like I see way too much.
I'm not supposed to be able to see.
And if you want to be able to see the way I see,
you have to do this.
Download, hit, hit, like, like, hit Film 4,
like, like record your day and then go in
and you do the following.
Maximize contrast.
Crush blacks and whites.
Then turn saturation all the way up.
And then go into audio and turn gain all the way up
and add reverb.
And that's what everyday life is like.
I thought crushing blacks and whites is what you did all day.
Oh my God, I 100% believe you.
Fuck yeah, that was awesome.
That was the best joke ever.
It's the only reason I fucking live, dude.
It's the only reason I fucking live.
That's the most like plausible, munchy theory.
Like I totally believe that's how you see and hear the world.
The only thing that makes sense.
I don't know if you mentioned, maybe I missed this,
but I expect some sort of like bug vision
where there's like a thousand of each image
appearing on your vision, on your eyes at all times.
Something like that.
Okay, here's bug vision, but it's all different images.
Yeah.
It's all the multiple realities that exist simultaneously
being perceived at once.
Of course, of course.
I'm gonna call, bro.
What can I say?
I'm gonna call.
Okay, here we go.
At Anna Allen, I guess.
At Anna Allen 4-4 says,
Have any of you guys ever thought
to go into stand-up comedy?
Well, none of us really have any experience
with stand-up comedy or anything.
None of us have any interest in that.
Whatever.
Wait, I'm a real comedian.
I'm not a YouTuber.
I don't want to be this.
This isn't me.
This isn't the real me.
I'm gonna get out of this one day.
It's gonna be a fucking distant memory.
I swear to God, I'll be a real boy.
I'm gonna be real.
This isn't me.
This isn't YouTube.
It's not real.
I hate social media.
I hate podcasts.
You know what?
I would love to...
This is what I was supposed to be.
You're right, dude.
We all need to escape.
I think...
I've thought about it.
I mean, you know, Jesse's actually done it,
so he's a real boy.
I've just thought about it a little bit,
and I like the idea of doing it,
because you're around actual human beings,
and that appeals to me.
But, Nate,
how are you gonna cut between clips?
Oh, no!
How are you gonna crush blacks and whites, Nate?
How are you gonna crush black and whites?
I'll bring my crowbar and see what I can do with that.
Crowbar is crowbar,
and you'll fucking destroy the timeline.
By killing so many white people and black people,
you'll fucking evaporate everything.
That's enough undertale references
for one-day munchie, okay?
Oh, no!
It's the only thing I care about!
Love is Sonic 1,
and I'm social media,
which I love,
and I'm just the biggest postage child for.
Remember when we finally beat Undertale,
and right at the end,
like, Asgore comes out and he goes,
okay, that's enough munchie references for one day.
That was pretty good.
And then Fly comes in and says,
get on the ground!
Life is really the biggest undertale of all.
Okay, here we go.
At ZombieNinjaCow says,
opinion on birds,
gay or okay, cool or drool.
Good question, dude.
Both cool and okay.
Birds are tight.
I think it's a combination of cool and drool.
You know what, okay.
Birds are tight, they're sweet,
they're hella good,
and hella nice, too.
I drool whenever I see one.
That wasn't a joke.
I drool because...
I saw a bird at my window.
I saw him, and he was fine.
I'm the hunger.
I drool at them because they are delicious
and also sexually arousing.
Right, right.
And also the, you know, the birds.
All right, I'm hearing a lot of positive bird,
you know, propaganda going on here.
I think you guys might be all Twitter sleeper agents
with your fucking social media.
Fuck you, okay.
Birds invented Twitter,
and they can destroy it.
I'm gonna crack your poop.
Here we go.
At MichaelCera4,
hey Michael,
I enjoy your content,
says Nate,
how do I become a strong boy?
And you guys can all feel free to comment on this.
You eat rocks and...
Yes!
Oh my god.
Okay, okay, okay.
Here's how you do it.
Nate, shut the fuck up and learn your place,
you goddamn bitch.
Yes, sir.
Get rocks.
You get rocks and sharpen your mouth with them.
You get the dirtiest rocks you can,
and just sharpen your teeth
until you can bite off more.
It's like webkins, you know?
You gotta crush some fucking heads
so you can crush even more heads.
It's like Cookie Clicker,
only with rocks and teeth
and grinding and destroying your enemies.
You just have to make your teeth so sharp
and crack bones just by licking them
with your fork-tooth tongue.
Uh, that's a good start.
After that,
just go to 4chan.org.
No, go to the gym.
Don't go to 4chan, you idiot.
You gotta get educated
or you'll go to the gym
and you'll just fuck around
and waste your time.
Okay, do a little bit of research
so you can come up with a plan.
Just do starting strength.
Just Google starting strength,
just do exactly that,
and just by doing it,
you'll be like,
okay, I need to learn other things
and you'll figure out other shit you can do.
There you go.
Here's your cheat sheet.
Rocks.
Dirty rocks.
Yeah, just powerful rocks.
Rock soup.
I play Wii Fit
and that's all I need.
I bought Wii Fit once
and I thought it was gonna be fun.
I spent like $200 on the Wii Fit
and all the accessories.
I don't know what the fuck I was thinking.
I was gonna be really fun.
God, such an idiot.
How we fit this fucking rocket
down your fucking throat?
What do you think about that?
You fucking government insider?
You fucking neo-Nazi skinhead?
I got my drones patrolling.
They're gonna defend me from that shit.
Okay, last question.
Here we go.
At Miguel Achoans 1,
I think that's right,
says,
do you guys ever feel like doing YouTube
isn't worth all the bullshit?
No, I've never had that thought
in my entire life.
I've never had any sentiment
even close to that.
I think not doing YouTube
is probably a bad idea.
Well, you know,
YouTube has given me hope
that I'll be able to do something more interesting
than just code all my life.
YouTube has given you all the hope
it's sapped away from me.
Yeah, that's definitely...
I'd say so.
Before I started doing any YouTube shit,
I was just doing my school shit.
It was really boring.
I was not really having a good time.
And doing YouTube is what I enjoy most in life
and just want to do it all the time.
I feel similarly.
If I hadn't tried at all,
then I wouldn't have any friends
and I would be really, really bad at talking still, probably.
That's good.
Be worse, I'm sure.
How many clothes do you think can fit on your body
and have it still be comfortable?
Oh, I've done this.
I've done this.
All of them.
Good, good job.
You won.
You passed the test.
I'm going to send you to Antarctica.
Cool.
That's right, that's what you'll find with my dad.
I did actually wear all of my underwear at once
just because I had a lot of it.
And it really hurt.
Dude, everything's giving.
Everything's giving as your tradition.
I wear my pants as a shirt and my shirt as pants.
That's not a joke.
I do that every year as tradition.
That's impressive.
Dude, I disagree.
I hate, I'm only comfortable.
The only clothes that is good is no clothes.
The only time I'm comfortable is when I'm like butt naked,
maybe socks, and like a big blanket,
and I can like spread it open like a moth man
and be like, like captured girls in my wingspan.
If you're a man walking on the streets tonight.
Yes.
Munchy, Munchy, I must know, do you have it
so that the bottom of the t-shirt goes up
and then your legs go through the arms
and then your penis is dangling from the ankle.
That's exactly how it is.
Oh, that's great.
Good job.
I love that.
Somebody draw that.
You crazy, you draw that shit.
I know you're on this.
Guys, if you just draw me, then you will see Pee Pee
out of the corner of your eye.
Oh, God.
You're gross.
That's a sin.
Okay, that's enough.
Thanks for asking all the questions, everybody.
Make sure you tweet us more at attpcrasinators
next time, next Saturday.
Support my watch, my watch sauce.
I'm going to remake Watchman with sauce.
That wasn't a joke.
That's an actual thing.
I'm going to be doing that.
I hope you look forward to it.
Every character will be sauce, report to me
which sauce you want to be who.
I'm going to put it A1.
I'm going to get all the sauce.
I'm going to get all it in real life
and actually get the film and put it on
an actual real millimeter film.
I'm going to put the sauce over it
and it'll be really good, guys.
Thank you for having me to support my book,
Watch Sauce.
Thank you.
Also send boobs to my Snapchat, the Hippocrite man.
That's the only social media I will be using
from now on.
Please, please.
Yes, also all sexy women.
Send me pictures of yourself.
Or, you know, alternatively, have sex with me.
But Snapchat me at, was it Nate Bestman?
Yeah, do that.
Do that.
That's what I want.
Also everything those guys said,
but for me and not them.
Don't say you're a woman.
And then I'll leave you.
Wait, Jesse, what did you say?
Everyone, not them, but me.
What they said, but with me.
All the women, all the money, all the girls,
all the good stuff.
I said it first like it first dibs.
First is the worst dibs.
First is the worst.
All the motorcycles, all the fancy sneakers.
It's all mine, baby.
I've got it.
It's all, I'm hoarding it.
I'm going to try out my new brand of shoes.
I refuse this reality.
No, guys, protect your fancy sneakers from Ben.
He's a known sneaker thief.
Watch out.
That was the best thing that ever happened
to any of us all the time.
Nate, Nate, please.
I don't know if you ever said this before.
Bring me to the masses, guys.
Make this a meme.
Explain the sneaker story.
Please, Nate.
Yeah, okay.
I think this is going to be covered in something before.
Okay, but I'll just tell it before we end.
So I had these fancy ass sneakers in college,
and they were fucking dope.
And I didn't bring them with me
when I moved out to fucking Ohio.
So they were still in Massachusetts
in the closet or whatever.
And so when RideCon 2 happens, I believe,
or maybe it was RideCon 1,
I get to Digi's house,
and I embrace Digi as a brother.
I turn the corner, and what do I see
adorning the feet of this Judas?
Of this Judas Ben St.
But my fucking immaculate sneakers,
my fucking pricey ass sneakers,
that when I say,
Ben, why have you done this to me?
Why have you taken what was rightfully mine?
My poor sneakers.
And he just looks at me,
he's like,
Mom said I could have them.
Mom said I could take them.
They were my sneakers.
She didn't have permission
to give away my fucking sneakers.
So Ben, to this day,
insists that no wrongdoing was ever committed
on anyone's behalf,
and he will not apologize
for the sin he has committed
against me and our family.
And until he does,
I will have his blood.
I will kill him.
Introducing a new brand of shoes
by Munchy Minstrel shoes.
I get Air Jordan's,
and I cover them in Minstrel sauce.
Is that what Robo Boop de Wares?
Is that his tactical dancing skills?
Yeah, it's tactical dancing
for ninja footing.
Fuck this, fuck this.
Yeah, we're done.
Bye.
See you later everybody.
Don't come back.
Don't.
That wasn't me,
like putting on the drums.
Oh Munchy,
I'm taking,
I'm crapping my pants
all over your turnips.
I'm crapping on your turnips.
I'm sorry,
I can't help myself.
Stop it.
I'm
crapping
my
pants.
I'm
supposed to
be
crapping
right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
Why did I'm jerking?
Myself, I'm sucking.