Hello and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast PCP, and we're here
once again to entertain you with wildly new stories about our lives and the things that we
like to talk about. I'm the host of this thing, I'm the best guy ever, besty boy, Nate Cool Guy,
we also got Digibro, we got Ben Saint, H-R.com, Endless Jess, Lightning Bolt, Lightning Bolt,
Sleep, Sleep, Sleep, and The Davoo. Bunch of Z's. Yeah, because our topic for today is indeed
snooze factor. Sleep, the restful thing you gotta do every night. Sleep is a boring topic,
a lot of people say sleep is a boring topic, and I'm one of them. Sleep is a fascinating topic.
No, sleep is the most interesting topic in the world, and it's because I've got a great anecdote
about my life and how it's been ruined by sleep. Here's the thing, this podcast, conceptually,
if you're doing a podcast about sleep, it's all just gonna be people talking about how little
sleep they get, what hours they sleep, what weird ass sleep schedules they've gotten onto,
and possibly, if we're particularly unlucky, dreams. Oh no, we're not getting into dreams.
Let's avoid the topic of dreams. Except for mine, because I had a really interesting one last night.
You won't believe this, it was trippy. I must have been high, I must have been on drugs or
something, I must have been taking PCP. Shut up, I had a dream this morning, when I woke up this
morning, and my dream was that I had slept for like 14 hours straight, and that dream came true.
It was real, my life was ruined today because I slept so long, it doesn't even make sense.
I hate it, it's the worst. Every day I wake up, and I don't get out of bed, and I feel like I
have slept the entire day, I feel like it's like eight in the afternoon, I feel like I just
keep putting off. Eight is nighttime, it's not afternoon. I know, I feel like I've slept until
eight in the afternoon, but then I... No, it's night. But then, shut up, then I get up, and it's still
early, and I don't know, I'm confused, I'm confused about my life. I do hate that, I do hate that.
My schedule. And Digi famously has a retardedly gay sleep schedule, as he describes it, right?
Yeah, I sleep at random times, it's pretty much been that way my whole life, I've never been able
to like... Was school a challenge for that purpose? Yeah, like, for me it was like, you know, because
we had a bedtime of like 10 o'clock, and me and Victor both had this problem, we just lay in bed
for hours, and just stare at the fucking ceiling. You know what I would do? You know what, I did
that exact same thing, I would stay up and I would play my Game Boy SP, such fond memories of playing,
no, not my, yeah, my SP, with the fucking backlight, the backlight ruined my sleep schedule. If it
wasn't for that backlight, I would have gotten a thousand more hours of sleep. Yo, the reason why
handheld consoles are totally worthless. You gotta download Flux onto your Game Boy SP. Yeah,
that's right, I'm going to hurt my eyes when I'm blasting fucking Super Mario, Mario Luigi
Superstar Saga playing thousands of hours into the night. Exactly, that exact game with the
exact situation. Yeah, dude, best game of all time. So anyone want to, anyone, anyone here
likes sleep? Does anyone have a positive view of sleep? Well, I guess there is a whole lot less
of it you have to do. I love getting into bed at an appropriate time. I enjoy that. Here's what I
feel about sleep is I hate getting, I hate starting it, and I hate stopping it. I hate
everything about it. That's fair. Like when I, resigning myself to go to bed for the evening is,
I'm just giving up, I feel like I'm just saying just it's over, I've failed, I've failed at whatever
it is I'm trying to do right now, time to just embrace it, embrace oblivion. That might be more
true than you know, because theoretically, if you subscribe to the, well I forgot the term for it,
but the term that every time you go to sleep, you die and woke as a new person with new memories,
you very well, might have failed. That's actually what I'm counting on when I go to bed.
To be reborn like a magnificent phoenix. I don't have a sleep schedule, like I don't go to bed when
I'm physically tired, I go to bed when I'm emotionally exhausted and drained, and I don't want to live
in this world anymore, and I just want this version of me to die, so that tomorrow some new man can
take my place, and maybe make some more leeway than I did, maybe chip away at the world a little bit
more than I accomplished. Which really, if you think about it, is what humanity does on a whole
as well. We're just sending out new foot soldiers to try to pave ways for the rest of us. I completely
relate to what Jesse was saying, though, and I brought that up at the end of Insomnia Analysis
too, where I was saying that whenever I have these days where it's like being awake is only
going to make me more miserable, and the only thing I can do is try to sleep. Oh yeah, right,
I remember that. It's like a reset button, it's like, okay, fuck yeah, this is all a failure,
it all has to burn, we'll try again. It doesn't work, it doesn't work, because the longer you
sleep, at least this is for me, the longer I sleep, the guiltier I feel when I wake up.
It only makes everything worse. Well, Ben, I have some luck in this regard. You can restart,
you can reset the SEGA as many times as you want, you're still playing the same shitty game. It's
still fucking Disney's Roar of the Beast. You're still playing fucking Sonic and Knuckles, and you
don't have the expansion. Oh, it's like... I have some luck in that situation, Ben, because I don't
have any way of keeping track how long of how long, like, I kind of think... What do you mean,
you don't have a clock? Well, I fall asleep, and I'm like, well, because you know, I usually have
to lay in bed for like an hour before I'll actually pass out, so I don't really know when I fell asleep,
I have like a kind of vague idea, and then I wake up and it's like, well, I guess I slept for eight
hours, maybe it was 10, I really am not entirely sure. I'm such a fuck, I need to, I can't allow
my, because it'll happen to me like it happened today, I'll sleep for fucking 12 hours straight
if I don't set my alarms for eight hours. I don't even know why, I'm a deformed individual,
I'm not a real human being, I've got some shit fucked up inside me, I have to, I have to set this,
like, I set literally like eight alarms to go off in five minute intervals every morning, that I,
it's a real fucking annoyance every night when I go to sleep, I have to calculate, okay, eight
hours from now, I'm gonna need like 10 billion alarms to go off, so I don't fucking waste the
entire day. You want me to talk about how I get myself awake and all that stuff, okay, so I'll
start with at the beginning of life when sleeping is miserable, because you're a kid, you can't
decide anything, and your parents are old people who don't understand, no white noise, white noise
wasn't invented yet, when they were people, and freaking ASMR wasn't invented at all yet, right?
White noise existed, just wasn't something you could load up on your computer. Well, it was all
black and white noise. If you couldn't load it on your computer, it effectively didn't exist,
you had to create your own white noise farm, like a wind farm. Yeah, like in the old days,
they had out, they would hibernate. Quite individual. You had to grow TVs out of the soil
with little rabbit ear antennae, that's how you pluck them out of the ground, like turn them.
Brief tangent. I discovered white noise, like, incidentally, because like there was an attic
fan, like right next to, right outside my bedroom door, and whenever there was something to happen
in the house that we had the attic fan out, you know, like some corpses that we had to burn,
something like that, I don't know, I don't know. We turned on the attic fan, you know,
to whisper away all of the sin, and I would just be laying there in other tranquility,
and I was like, what is this that's going on? How is all this noise making me sleep better?
Oh my gosh, too bad I'm a kid with no agency over my life and can't just turn on this attic
fan every night, all night. You know, so then when I get my room, have my own computer, I
discover like white noise, and immediately get into rain sounds, shout out to rainymood.com,
it's rain all the time. On that subject, I gotta say that the onset of summer has been the best
thing for my sleep life, because now I have an air conditioner unit in my window, it's super loud
and rattly, but it's perfect white noise, it's like the, it's like the thumb of a mother's heartbeat
as I rest in the womb. Yeah, man. Yeah, it's like a heartbeat. I keep it, I keep it at max,
my room is like an icy tomb, so I'm just like sitting there in a cold embrace. You gotta love
that, that healthy rhythmic sound of a heartbeat that sounds like, that's the sound of a healthy
heart right there, for sure. I gotta say, Duvou, relevant to the rainy mood, I do owe quite a bit
of sleep in my life to the website, or rather type rain fire jazz onto Google, and you'll get this,
it's like a mute this play, or a play these together thing, where it'll play a video of rainfall,
a video of like a burning fire in a fireplace, and then a video of the song, the smell of black coffee
from Phoenix Wright, like the jazz version. Oh yeah. I actually found a three hour video,
which was most relaxing jazz music, and it was just that on loop for three hours. Yeah,
that's lazy. And if you're on this, on this website, it just keeps looping those things forever,
so I've had like times where I've listened to like 48 hours of just that song over rain and fire
all day. The only time a YouTuber is allowed to cry is when it's all over, so one time,
so I found out about white noise, and maybe some of you guys, maybe some of you guys have
back we have, I don't know if DeVoo would, but from the oblongs, anybody remember the oblongs?
I remember, not that well. What was this? I don't know. It was an adult swim show.
No, I know the show, I don't know what you're talking about specifically. It's not one of the
adult swim shows that anyone cares about or remembers. It only had like, it only had 10 episodes,
but they would replay them like. Bob Oblong was an inspirational character, he was the coolest
dude with no limbs. But there's an episode where basically the concept of the episode is that
the Milo doesn't realize this, but the only way he's able to get to sleep is because of the sound
of his parents fucking in the room next to him. Oh, I remember that. Yeah. And so the two of them
start fighting and Milo can't get to sleep. So someone tells him that he needs to start using
white noise, so he just starts turning on like every appliance in the house, like running water
and turning on all this other shit. And then it ends up flooding the house. And then that ends up
being how they tie the plots together, because once he floods the house, then the parents,
you know, like have to work together to save their kids. And it makes them rekindles their
marriage and they start fucking again. I remember that I actually kind of, I didn't really, it was
one of those messages that was like supposed to be heartfelt, but rub me the wrong way because
the message was like, okay, we're married, we'll stay together, not because we really like each
other, but because we've got our kids. All right, all right. So well, fuck that. I don't care.
So like with rain, interestingly enough, one time I was like in a hotel with my brother and my dad,
and I put on some rain. I thought, yeah, I'm all into this rain stuff now. And my dad was like,
I can't sleep with this because it makes me want to get up and shut a window. I can't live with
this rain. But if you're not getting wet and you hear the rain, it's just okay. But sounds like
outside rain. Yeah. And like, I remember getting a whole app from my phone that has a huge collection
of white noise things, including the sound of a dripping faucet. Like who the heck is that gonna
keep us sleep? There's also typing, the sounds of typing. You know, until until recently, I never
got into any of this white noise shit, except in college, me and my buddies did love just
vegging out to Bob Ross for like hours on it. We would watch him. We would literally sit there
and do nothing, say nothing, just watch Bob Ross paint shit. We watched like seasons after season
after season of this game. It was awesome. Guys, were you were you were you fucking high bro?
You know it my dude. Who do you mean dog? Yo, Bob, go green dog. Go man. You know what,
since we're never I'm never gonna find another time to do this. An anecdote about when I was
watching Bob Ross when he was being streamed on Twitch, and there were dozens of people who were
acting like he was doing it live. And I don't know if they were joking or not. The people were
like, oh, you should paint this differently. And then someone said paint rainbow dash please.
And that's always stuck in my mind is the funniest thing ever. So hilarious. Let's see. I want to
Bob Ross, you Bob Ross, this landscape is real nice, but we're going to need some rainbow dash in
there. We're just gonna need to complete this this work. So I don't know if we want to bring up
ASM markers, but that's like a whole separate podcast we've been planning for a while. We can
touch on it a little bit. I would say that I find it really weird and bizarre. And when I see
everyone says that until they actually understand. Most people don't like it. Well, that's because
they're idiots. Why do these people have billions of views and I don't know whatever. The some of
us like ASMR, some of us don't. I like putting on something to listen to. Sometimes I like having
someone talking when I go to sleep. But like, I don't know this. I've maybe I just haven't been
in the right mindset. But when I've put on the ASMR and like listen to like a guy talking real
close to my ear about, I don't know, whatever object he's holding or whatever it is that they do,
it's, it's, I don't know. It's like, okay, you know, I'm not going to do too much. I'm not going
to go into too much, but I just want to say that it's a whole world of stuff out there. And not
everybody even likes to hear human voices. That's why there's a whole bunch of stuff that's just
like tapping or like, I will it's because because Ben clear is being ignorant and he thinks that
ASMR is just a bad voice. You literally are ignorant. And that's okay. Yeah, I'm just
clarifying about it. I mean, I don't know. I'm just saying there's there's stuff for everybody
theoretically. I mean, maybe people don't like any of it. But I know for a fact,
you haven't seen all that there is. So you guys say, oh yeah, I'm going to go watch every ASMR
video ever made and fucking browse back to talking about yeah, whatever. To be continued. I'll kill
you guys. Do you actually though, listen to ASMR to get to sleep? Has it helped you? Absolutely.
Absolutely. Yeah, I mostly listen to music and there's like, oh, I can't do that. That like,
like flood by Boris. And like these days, death consciousness by have a nice life. And I always
end up putting on death consciousness because of the fact that I've never stayed awake through
the whole thing if I listen to it when going to bed. So like, I think clearly it's it's
Victor. It's having victory over me. Now it is an 85 minute album. So that's probably part of it.
I was going to talk. I was going to explain like how I get myself up. So like nowadays,
what I do is I have two tracks going at once. I have an ASMR video just like one or maybe two
that are shorter. Two tracks at once. So they get like, so they get like 30 minutes of ASMR.
Then I have like music going on. And then after like an hour of relaxing music,
it's like six hours of rain. So I like put the song on a playlist. I could take like an hour
and a half rain in stuff like that before. Yeah, rain from inside a car for 90 minutes,
which is awesome. That's a great. I love that sound. Like put down like four of those. And then
the tent is the best. That's a good one. That's a good. I like that sound. Now it's raining in
the car is my favorite to sleep. I can't get to sleep when camping because of the sea. I don't
I don't actually like that either. I just don't. It doesn't work as well like on YouTube because
like you can tell it's coming from a speaker because it's coming from one direction. Right.
Well, did you ever be saying that like rain is not relaxing for you? It gives you a headache?
What? No, literal rain, like not the sound of it. So I just imagine that that artificial rain
makes you think of headaches, right? This was only a recent thing. Like in the last couple years,
I started getting low pressure headaches where anytime there's like a strong low pressure front
coming through, then I'll start getting headaches. Oh, man. Sometimes when I detect a small change
in air pressure, I imagine that like the media has hit and like just to smash the earth's atmosphere
off and that like this is it. Like the earth is over. And I look out the window expecting to see
like a huge mushroom cloud. Oh, man, how do you wait? More and the sky torn open by like some
cosmic catastrophe. And I'm like, okay, I'm with you. I'm with you. But how do you detect a change
in pressure? Exactly. Like you can feel it in your ears. You feel that? Oh, okay. All right. In regards
to dreams and like destruction of the world, I remember one time like I woke up. Oh, Jesus,
into the dreams we go. All right. No, just short one. I had a dream. I had a dream that I woke up
and my brother was with me and I looked up into the sky because for some reason there was a giant
window on my ceiling and I saw that the moon had just exploded and like a whole bunch of
fragments of it. You realize you were playing Sonic Adventure 2 and Shadow showed up and you
went on a Rolla Keeg adventure through Edgeland. No, like the whole moon. The whole moon just
got exploded and I pulled out my camera, my phone, which is right next to me and I recorded it and
I'm like, oh man. Like an assassination classroom. Yeah. And then I woke up and I was like, oh my
gosh, I'm so glad that was just a dream. But I got it on tape. Oh wait, no. That's my favorite part.
But I recorded my dream. That's my favorite part when you're still 50% dreaming afterwards. Like
one time I woke up but had a dream that my dad was yelling at me. But then that turned out to be fake.
No more dream descriptions. This is going to start a chain reaction. Yeah, I agree. I'm already thinking
of one. I just want to talk about what an idiot I am. That was it. All right. On a weirdly related
subject about recording dreams, I watched the movie Paprika the other day, which is all about this
machine that like lets you see people's dreams. And it really annoyed me that like, you know,
in the movie you watch someone's dream and like it's an anime. But then like the people that see
into the dreams with this machine, they see it on their screen and what they see is the exact same
anime footage that you, the viewer just watched. And it really annoyed me because like a dream
is not a fucking, a dream does not have like camera cuts and angles and like a dream is not,
is not composed in the way that an anime is. I understand that. I've been editing videos too long.
It just seems a reasonable, a reasonable way to handle portraying what you seem. Is it lazy maybe?
Is it like all stuff like that? Anytime that someone tries to represent something that would
not be experienced like a show as a dream. Dreams and fiction never seem like actual dreams except
for the one time that a dream in fiction was portrayed like an actual dream, like the dreams
that I have every night was when Chuckie says to Tommy, hey Tommy, what's going on here? And
Tommy turns around and he's got a clown face and he goes, I'm not Tommy! And then later in the episode,
Drew has the same dream. Or no, it's Chaz. Chaz has dream. Chaz is Drew. Drew is Angelica's dad.
What's he doing in the kitchen? And Stu turns around and he's a clown and he's like, I'm not Stu!
The theme here is that there's a lot of surprise clown faces in Jesse's dreams.
I have a lot of surprise clown face dreams and it all goes back to that fucking Rugrats episode.
That in ICP is responsible. Maybe the Rugrats grew up to be ICP because of that fucking dream.
That was a dark carnival visiting violent day in his dreams as an infant telling him to spread
the gospel of the Six Jokers cards and bring forth a new era of enlightenment. I'm not Stu!
So hey, let's just go back to freaking uh the playlists for to go to sleep to and how I like
to end them with a wake-up song. It's all about you, isn't it, DeVoo? It's all about DeVoo's plan.
He's got to get his shit out of his stupid playlist. I'm not DeVoo! Jesse, your interpretation of that
episode of the Rugrats is the plot of Homestuck, by the way. What? Is that true? Making me hate it more?
Only a little bit. Of course. Of course. Well, I like to go for, like, getting back to wake-up songs.
What the fuck, just wake it? DeVoo, you just gave me whiplash. You changed subjects so quickly.
DeVoo's good at that. All right, go on, DeVoo. Go. Wake, wake, wake, wake, wake-up song. Wake me up!
Wake me up! I can't wake up! Wake me up! Save me! Save me from the nothing I've become.
That should be our opening song. So yeah, like, you know, like ones that are just kind of chilled
out and start off, you know, just kind of kind of smoothly, you know, a lot of steely dance songs
are like that. I was going to say, like, immediately I thought of the what's, uh, do it again, just
Yeah.
Dude, there's too much happening in those songs to, I don't know, sleep to.
Although I like My Old School. That's a great song for that. I like ones that do get a little bit
more energetic, especially toward the end. There's also, there's also what's, oh, I don't understand this at all.
What does that do with sleep? This is totally unrelated. To our podcast, to our lives, to our friendship.
What happened? You know, it's a great, you know, it's a great video game about sleeping.
Roar of the Beast.
You mean, yeah, let's talk about Yume Nikki. That is a great video about sleeping.
Yume Nikki is this, is this RPG maker game. It's 2D Spray Graphic. It's about this girl,
this, this Hikikomori, this Japanese girl who won't leave a room under any circumstances and
all she does, all you can do as her is you go to your bed and go to sleep and like record
things in your dream diary. That's what the title means. Yume Nikki means dream diary.
What? Who's trying to interrupt me?
Sorry, I just got cut out for like 20 seconds there.
Oh, okay. Well, you're missing some gold here. Anyway, you go to sleep as this girl and you
wander around these crazy dream scapes and you find all these objects and these like
abilities and you can do stuff and you find a knife and you can stab things.
I remember that. That's right, because you know, actually won the competition the first time and
went back in time to make Yuki win the competition. I remember that.
That's Mirai Nikki and Yume Nikki is way better.
You know, you know, I really love Yume Nikki. I love the way that everything is super fucked up
and it's not at all like, like you were saying before, like the portrayal of like
dreams is just like a flat anime. That's really boring and I don't give a shit,
but Yume Nikki is like this big crazy world where shit, you don't know what the fuck is
going to happen and you can like interact with things in weird ways and you like collect items
and fuck with things. It's just, it's really out there and it's the best. Everyone's watching
this has probably already seen or played Yume Nikki. If you haven't do it, yeah, I would hope
so. It's one of those, it's one of those few like RPG maker games that has kind of reached
not mainstream success, but is like known by audience. It's definitely a cult, a very cult.
Yeah, yeah. I guess so. I mean the places I hang out, everybody knows about it. It's up there with
off and space funeral. I think it's not quite up to snuff with my RPG maker game, the classic
which is unreleased, which is one screen of me walking up to a tree and going, fuck that tree.
Alright, slow down. Please, please. Another great RPG maker game, Master of the Wind, if
anyone wants to play Master of the Wind. Why the fuck are we talking about video games? This is
a sleep cut game. Yume Nikki is a game about sleeping and it's fucking cool. The only real
point I wanted to make here has been ruined. No one's going to take it seriously anymore because
it's like, I was about to finish it and then I got cut out of the freaking chat.
Well, give it a try. Okay, so wake up songs. Here's the thing. Ever since I started using those,
waking up has been finally a good experience for the first time in my life because what I realized
is that no matter what you set to your phone to wake you up, it's coming out of your phone. It's
unpleasant. It has to be like all the way up on the volume in order to register and it sucks. But
you get a nice wake-up song and it's like, man, waking up. I can wake up inside, finally.
They really called my name and saved me from the dark. It was awesome.
Hot dog. I don't typically wake up to anything. I don't set alarms for myself. I just kind of
wake up when I do. I'm curious for you guys because I know everybody's a different kind of
quote unquote morning person or non-morning person. For me personally, I have, I struggle to actually
wake up, like I'll lay there and just be like in and out of awakeness until I finally make up my
mind and I'm like, okay, I'm getting out of bed. But then once I'm out of bed, it's just like zero
to a hundred. There's no like groggy, I need coffee. I have an extremely groggy morning
thing. I'm not a morning person at all. I can't say for sure, like recently whether or not I'm
a morning person because I'm not used to like having to be up anyway. So whenever I wake up,
even if it's the morning, I've probably slept enough because I just wake up naturally. Yeah,
same here. But back when I did have to fucking get up for stuff years ago, I remember that like my
girlfriend would try to get me out of bed. And according to her, because I have very blurry
recollection of these moments, I would turn into a fucking savage animal, the likes of which humanity
was not prepared for. And I would just turn into like Wolverine Berserker rage. The things that I
would do in my mind to just putting holes in her face, knocking her teeth out, slapping her around
a bit, slapping her tits around, throwing the bed upside down, throwing the bed on her, trapping
her under it, setting the house on fire. The willingness as I run into the night in my tidy
whitey. Yeah, the sheer ferocity with which my sleeping, my sleepy self attempts to defend not
getting up is covered in scat. That's that's how Victor is when I try to wake him up. Victor gets
really violent and angry with me if I wake him up for anything. I'm the same. Unless it's lunch,
in which case I can coax him into like, because this is when I walk into Victor's room in the
morning, he's usually like just in the process of waking up. And he looks at me with this scowl,
and he goes, what? And I'm like, I'm like, want to go to lunch. And he sits there and like processes
it for a bit, like trying to figure out if he has money. Well, I can sympathize with that because
from the way you describe your life and from some of the videos I've seen on your after dark channel,
it seems like your life is just you walking into your sibling's rooms randomly. Yeah, that's
pretty fucking their girlfriends. Like it seems like if you're not editing videos, all you do is
wander around your house in a fucking Applejack shirt and pajama pants cut off at the knee and go
someone take me to fucking take me to cook out. I can promise you Victor's listening to this right
now clapping his hands and standing up like giving you a standing ovation for the exact
miss of that. You know, it's been a bit like that historically when I've had to wake him up for
things. Oh, you know you have been you know you have you've been a kill you Nate. I mean,
it's just because your sleep schedule you always go to bed later than later than everybody else
when we were you know, picturing like this slimy amorphous, like fucking,
like, I was gonna say like Aldrich rising in the coffin, amorphous fat like losing
under Victor's door. You can't close the door. You can't keep him out. He's coming under the cracks.
This is exactly how Victor imagines Victor Victor is the Gwendolyn to Digi's Aldrich just
fucking seeping into the orifices, possessing him and using him for his pleasure. There's a reason
that whatever Victor does like an impression of me. It's always like
you know, my brother, I think is more of a morning person than me. But what's cool about
waking him up is that he lives in the basement, right? It's very dark.
Wake me up. Wake me up inside. Wake me up. Wake me up. I want to hear what I want my brother's
story to do. I don't care. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Every time I hear those words, I have to. Okay,
go on. Go on. So he's in the basement on the far end. And like, like if you go down to the steps,
he's on the other end of the basement, right? Don't go in the basement, man. Arl Stein, he told
you. Yeah, that's true. That's true. Yeah, the base under the directly under the light. And he
he lays on his back. And so he's just it's so dramatic because the basement's so dark with
the light descending upon him. And it just makes me want to like slowly walk up to him and like
grab a key or something. It's like, it's just so epic. Like one time I woke, I tried to get him up.
And I didn't even want to wake him up because he was so glorious, just like, like just laying
there with a very, very stoic face. I brought my whole family down like, Hey, guys, look at
I invited the neighbors over to check this shit out. It was awesome. We got the community involved.
Isn't that the plot of Totoro? Didn't she get us like, find him sleeping there in this meadow
and like go get her friends to go check out Totoro? Look at this majestic animal.
Fuck. Hey, let me tell you guys, here's something that I can't decide how I feel about
people who can just fall asleep by accident. I don't think I don't think I've yeah, like, like
just fall asleep watching a movie. I have, I don't think I've ever in my life fallen asleep
without meaning to. I've never like sat down and like fallen asleep in the middle of a movie.
You never like decide like, I'll try to watch a movie and then you just like
never. Never. I've only done that all the time. And I would make me jealous sometimes. We would
be up watching adult swim as youngins and you would like pass out. And I'd be like, Nate,
you're missing the anime. I remember that. I remember. I hated doing, I wanted to watch those
goddamn animes. I was robbed. I would have to be like exceedingly exhausted to pass out during a
show or like with adult swim, though, I would always pass out during the one show I didn't
really care about. And that's the one, like I couldn't make it to my favorite shows because
I'd pass out during the one that like I that was boring, like fucking pilot candy. You know,
I've always been a really heavy sleeper and it's always been pretty easy for me to fall asleep.
But yeah, I don't know. I'd fall asleep during anything when I got fucking late.
Fucking shade. I mean, shade. I once saw shade fall asleep on the top stair of the stairs.
He was like going up on his way down. He's like five or six years old. No, on the top. Like he
he walked up to the top of the stairs and then just passed out on the top of the stairs.
I could. I might have done. He also cannot stay awake in a car. Like if you're in the car for
more than five minutes, he will absolutely pass out to this day. 18 years old and still
passes out from like when you guys have that thing. Falling asleep is difficult for me. It
requires it requires focus and effort. It's weird. It's tough for me to do. Speaking of sleeping
in a car because it's like if I'm in like a long car ride and I'm getting really tired, but I can't
quite get comfortable enough to fall asleep. I have these times where I like go into sleep for
like five seconds and I realized there was this lapse of audio and I'm like, whoa, it's like
that's cool. In fact, there's only one time where I actually fell asleep at a very specific moment
that I could remember and it was like instant. Like I went to some sort of camp thing for like a
whole day and I don't remember being ultra tired, but I literally just lay down face first on my
own bed with my mom right behind me with all my clothes on. And then my mom started taking off
my pants and then I fell asleep halfway through getting my pants. I wasn't listening to any of
that, but now I'm listening to all of it. Very incredible. Yeah. So like I'm like, I'm probably
like six or seven years old. You know, I was going to say one of the best ways to stop yourself from
falling asleep is to get a boner and boner achieved to continue with this mom taking off your pants
story. Yeah, I fell asleep halfway through getting my pants taken off, you know, and like my mom was
like, I didn't even like quite think about it until my mom was like, you fell asleep like
immediately. I'm like, oh my gosh. Yeah. I literally remember the feeling of my pants getting taken
off and then it cuts to black. And I'll bet the judge went easy on it because she was a woman.
Shameful. Fucking classic double standard. There's only one way I can regularly remember
exactly like or approximately when I fall asleep. And it's a great way for me to figure out how long
it took me to fall asleep. Flood by Boris as Digi mentioned before, which he got me into. It's
this one hour thing, this one like this one song that's also an album and it's just over an hour
long and it's awesome for sleep. Uh, is it wake me up? Wake me up. Come on. I guarantee they're loving
this. Yeah. So I am. And so like it has all these different sections. And so what happens is it,
you know, it varies at which section I fall asleep. And so all I mean, all I have to do is just
remember which segment I last heard, you know, and then I'm like, oh, that's exactly how long it
took me to fall asleep. That's really cool. Although I can't, you know, I want to bring up Flood again.
Like what happened to me? The other tool for Mario Sunshine. I, yeah. No, you, Eddie, Eddie is
talking about the album from They Might Be Giants. Stay with it. Oh, shit. I don't know. God.
All right. So like, uh, but like, yeah, like albums like Flood that did you got me into, like, I
think that really helped me get more into music for sleep. Wait, is that really what you were
talking about? Because I was just making a joke. It's a different Flood. It's a Flood by the band
Boris. You know that if you listen to any fucking time that we've been Boris, that Hawaiian shirt,
that Hawaiian shirt wearing fuck from GoldenEye, I told you, I hate that guy. Yeah, man. What
where does he get off ripping off album titles from a, from an American institution like They
Might Be Giants? Yeah, good question. But like there was this other album that did you got me into
called Ocean Songs by Dirty Three. And I listened to that one for sleeping a lot too. But then what
happened at some point is that suddenly I developed this aversion to any music that makes me emotional
and I can't do it. I can't handle it anymore. Like when I play Flood or Ocean Songs, I just get too
like afraid of the world. So now like the reason I like those albums for sleep is because I find
them completely unemotional. Like any song that's going to make me feel anything is going to be an
obstacle to fall into sleep. I would assume what they have like, okay, what they have though is
this sort of, they have this really like, really full emotion. It's like if emotions are colors
and you combine them all to make white, that's what Flood is like, you know, it just feels like
all the emotions. And it's just too much for me. That if you like, if you listen to it loud, then
yes, that's what I would say I feel. But if you listen to it like at one, which is how I listen
to music, you know, like the minimum volume, then I mean for bed, then I don't think it really conveys
all that much. I guess. But yes, now all I can listen to is like stuff that just feels like
elevator lobby music type stuff. That kind of thing is just like, that's truly unemotional.
And that makes you feel, all right, that's all I have to say about that.
I want to move into what I wanted to talk about this podcast. I decided I'd save this
for later, because I want to talk about it. Wait, wait, wait, wait, you're going to save it?
God damn it!
I think he thinks he's funny. He's laughing. He's laughing as though he's funny.
I'm laughing. He's pretty funny. Come on, guys. That's a good joke.
It's a really good joke, guys. I want to talk about getting rid of sleep.
Yeah. Sleep needs to stop. Sleep. No, not even transhumanism, because, all right, first of all,
I'm going to tell some stories and anecdotes and some weird science facts, all right?
First of all, weird science fact. Nobody knows why we sleep. The only scientific reason that's
been discovered is because we get tired. Well, there's one very good reason. You've got to eat
big and you've got to sleep big if you want to get big. That's important for that. I mean,
if you don't sleep, you die. Right. Well, we know that getting too tired will make you die.
But we don't know how sleep fixes that. It's the weight of all your sins, weighing down your
eyelids. Yeah, you need Jesus to take the wheel every once in a while, so you've got to sleep,
so that can happen. I think it's basically just a stress reliever. It's like we take
in too much information. We can't handle it anymore and we need to just fucking lay down.
But nobody really knows why. I think when I was growing up, I had this impression that sleep was
like a healing process. It's kind of like in RPGs, right? I still think of it that way. You lose
all your health and then you go sleep and your health is restored. But it doesn't, it's not.
It doesn't do anything. It's just you not thinking for eight hours. It's got to be really useful,
though. I mean, from an evolutionary standpoint, having to sleep is a huge
weakness to predators. So it's got to be useful or something. Well, here's the thing. We've also
figured out there already are. They have already, like for years now, had pills that will make you
not sleep. Oh, bullshit. I don't believe this. They have had them. That was, they exist. Okay,
there's got to be an asterisk on that. And there's also, there are people out there who just don't
sleep. Yeah, if you take enough boner pills, you won't sleep as a side effect, but that's not the
main purpose of the drug. No, the main purpose is to make your winner 10 feet long to let you
get fucking elephant in the face all the way up fucking drunk. I'm going to tell you about the most
jealous I've ever been of any story I've ever read. It was a Roger Ebert article where he was
talking about how he met, he was like hanging out at like some like party or something in like
Italy or some shit. And he meets this guy and this guy is like showing him around his place.
And he's got like just this insane amount of projects he's done. He has like all these old
cars he built and shit and like all this other like artwork he'd made and stuff. And Ebert was
like, how the fuck do you have time for all this? And the guy said, well, I don't sleep. And he was
like, I didn't believe him. But then he didn't seem to be lying. And there was no reason not to believe
him. And everyone around him corroborated it. The guy just didn't sleep. And he got so much stuff
done by way he was just a fucking anomaly. I mean, it doesn't seem that weird, right? Like,
I believe that there's a human out there who's like, why we sleep, then how hard would it be
to believe that some biological anomaly of a person just doesn't do it? It's possible. It's
possible. There's a thing called the sleep diet that a lot of people do. And they say that it's
what Leonardo da Vinci and a bunch of weird people they were. And you don't take like an extended
sleep, but like you sleep in like six 20 minute naps. Yeah, there's a lot of there's the uberman
sleep schedule. The uberman is where you it's yeah, it's six 20 minute naps. There's you it takes
about 10 days to train yourself onto it. And it's gruelingly hard. I tried it. And I couldn't do
it. Look, I've been trying to fight sleep for years. I hate sleep. I want it gone. Biggest
problem in the universe. Every random idea that some internet fucking blogger has for how to sleep
less. I've tried it. And the problem is that there's nothing in my life that I can do to can
like to force myself to not sleep. Because like I have too much time to get everything done. So
like if I get tired, I'm just like fucking I'm just going to sleep. Like there's not like there's
nothing to I can say, oh, I'm going to get so productive. The only way to defeat sleep is to
just always be having the most fun you've ever had in your life. Because if I'm like really
having fun, I will not sleep for fucking ever. But the second I get bored, or even like a little
bit frustrated. I basically I sleep for an eternity. That's almost every like like you said earlier,
where it's like you only sleep when you feel defeated. Like that's yeah, that's my like,
I sleep. That's why it's so hard for me to reset my sleep schedule, because it'll happen naturally
if I find something to do all night. If I'm like, I'm going to make a list of my top 100 favorite
fucking asses in in Pokemon, then like is number one is number one. The Pokemon white
female trainer. He's got some thick ass thighs. But I if I get onto that, I can do that all night.
And like, it won't be until I can do the voodoo voice all night. Yeah, no, I can I can sit there
I can sit there and crack open a comic book and read all the character's voices in Guja voice
all night long. And and then I won't stop until I'm done. And then you won't stop out until you
are Guja. And that's when you start secreting underneath Victor's door. Oh, no, Conrad's
Guja again. He wants to hang out with me. What a fuck. I really hope that Guja becomes a meme,
Jesse. I've been doing that fucking voice all the time. It seems like everything that any of us
have said in the last 10 podcasts has become a meme. Yeah, we're kind of on a roll with the
self perpetuating memes. That's the best. We're a mean machine. We've always wanted to be.
Let me take the time to fucking complain and and bitch at all of our fans because they can't
read my mind sufficiently. And they're not they're not cool enough to understand what I say without
me explaining it or just or telling them honestly and forthrightly. I asked people to give me quotes.
Oh, yeah. Everyone gave me everyone gave me quotes that weren't the exact kind I was looking for.
Yes, I went on Twitter the other day and I was like, everyone tell me fucking memorable quotes
from all of the people. And like one, I only got quotes from like half of the PCP members. And
two, most of them were terrible because I had a specific thing in mind. Specifically, I was trying
to make an alignment chart and like chart everyone being chaotic evil. But you didn't tell anybody
that part. You just didn't tell anyone that. I thought it was obvious. I mean, what else would
I be looking for quotes for? What other possible reason could I have? I thought you were going to
make some kind of compilation. And then I was like, what the fuck is how can he possibly be
willing to go through all the episodes to find all these? Everyone was like, remember when when
Davoo is goo? And I'm like, you fucking idiot. That quote does not speak to any kind of moral
attitude whatsoever. I think Davoo Collective can be put on an alignment chart pretty easily.
He's got to be somewhere in the neutral. Yeah, something like that.
It didn't fit my artistic vision. I don't know. Are the Borg really neutral?
You know what? I want to actually go on a rant about alignments because I was thinking about this
last night. Okay. I was laying in bed and I was thinking about how nobody understands any superhero
but me. I'm the only one who gets these characters and everyone else should just not be allowed to
enjoy them. Okay. And I was thinking about how everybody always puts like Superman as lawful good
and Batman as chaotic good when really it should be reversed. Now Batman's like lawful. Batman is
lawful good because Batman has a code. Superman doesn't need a code. He's just a nice guy. They've
all got it backwards. Everybody, nobody understands. Superman is neutral good. Superman is neutral
good probably. Here's the thing. The alignments are way too simple and like I hate it when people
think that like you can actually box like a well-realized character into them. Like they're
meant as a simplification. Man, this sure is a great podcast about sleep. Get out of here.
So my favorite episode of American dad is the one where he gets the pills that make it so he
doesn't sleep anymore. Yeah. And he just becomes like his life becomes awesome and then his wife
starts doing all this shit and then the one guy at the end he smokes the cigarette and he goes
life. It's really funny. You know, that's not a real thing though. That was a work of fiction.
That was a science thing. I have read things that have said that there are actually anti-sleep
pills are not on the market yet, but they are. I have often heard that Vince McMahon is one of
these individuals that does not sleep. I've heard and it's been corroborated by numerous sources
that Vince McMahon sleeps like at most one hour a night for like the last 40 years and he's 70
years old and he's gonna live forever. He's doing fine. Yeah. And he's still chacked. And he's got,
well, okay, but he definitely did Roy's. I do enjoy the act of sleeping. Roy's come from Vince
McMahon. We just shaved them off of his skin. You know how the curse mark in Naruto came from
that one guy who was the origin of all the curse marks? He's that for Roy. Vince McMahon takes off
his skin mask and it's just a big giant steroid pill underneath. It was me, Austin. It was me,
Gudra. I was Gudra all along. I do like the act of sleeping, but not that much. I don't like
having to sleep that much. So like, I would like two to three hours every second to third day.
That would be perfect. Hey, you know what? You know what? I want to break this on a totally
different area of sleep. I hate sleeping with another human being in the bed. Typically a woman.
I find it disgusting. I can't sleep at all. It is in fear every time that I've done it,
which has been a lot. Let's keep it on level. We talked about this on Digibro. It's horrendous.
I was saying that I'm envious of the fact that Victor and his girlfriend will hang out late into
the night and then Victor would just go home to go to bed. That's what it's all about. There is
nothing wrong with, I just hate sleeping with other people. If they touch me, it's weird. I don't
like it. When you're married, it's an art form of figuring out how to never come in contact while
you're actually trying to sleep. 90% of the relationship is figuring out how you're actually
going to sleep in a bed with this person. It's horrible. People make fun of the Brady Bunch because
the parents had separate beds. I think they had to figure it out. They push those beds together
on the reg, my nigga. You know they do it, but then they go to sleep separately. Here's the
thing. I definitely, when I get married, want to have separate bedrooms because it's like,
when you think about it, the whole tradition is a social construct of having to share the same bed.
Social construct because they like this way. The Chinese don't do that shit. Back in the 1800s
or whenever, you know, didn't have any room. It was like one room for both the parents and then
another room for all seven of the kids. Then as houses got bigger, every single kid is going
to campaign for as much space as possible, but no married couples are going to want to be in
separate rooms because they'll look like they don't have as good of a bond as their friends do.
Yeah, I hear you on that too. It creates this artificial scarcity of rooms.
Expectation or something going on. You're really into that artificial scarcity phrase.
It's good phrase. It is a good phrase. I just can't get to sleep without jacking off at least once.
That doesn't help me at all. I'm just back where I started after I jacked off.
Well, it doesn't help me to get to sleep. It's more like I can't not jack off while on the
bed. And so even if I have firsthand experience that it doesn't matter if I have sex immediately
before bed, I will jack off 20 minutes later and trying to explain that to your girlfriend who's
sleeping next to you on the same bed. Why you're half of the, now mind you, I'm really good at
jacking off quietly and without moving too much. I know how to do it without having to shake the
bed and wake her up. You know, I'm pretty sure she was not even aware of half the times I was
jacking off sometimes in broad daylight right next to her. But you know, there's sometimes right
behind her face as she was cooking. Sometimes in the supermarket. How am I going to get behind
her face while she's cooking? You mean just like behind her? You gotta stand on a footsteller.
I mean, she said she was a giant anyway. But anyway, yeah, it's like,
like she would go to sleep and I'd be like, I can't, like I don't want to wake her up,
but I'm not, I can't get to sleep. And then like for me, I have this, like if I lay in bed for
like 40 minutes and it's not working, I get up and go do other stuff, you know. So I'd be like
laying in bed, like fucking awkwardly trying to be quiet. And of course she's not listening to music
or anything. She just fucking passed out. So I'm sitting there in silence, like, oh, fuck,
this is so weird. And then I get up, get on my computer, like a laptop, you know, watch anime
and shit, then jack off again, because I laid down again. So now I have to do that whole process
again stand over her and jack off on her and let you know, that's, you know, that's her responsibility
to accept that burden. Right. But yeah, it's just, you've got to jack off. She needs that
pitter-patter of raindrops to fall asleep. So you've got to jack off over her.
Actually, I do wonder if having a bunch of sound going on would fix a lot of that, because I feel
like if I had like, if I had to sleep with someone, I might just like, I might just like super
multi-layer it, like put on like the sound of rain, the sound of fire, like two ASMR videos,
a whole bunch of stuff, just to the point of-
One thing that relaxes me to sleep, like the sound of my boyfriend jacking it is like the
rhythmic thrumming of a mother's heartbeat in the womb.
That one's close. Hey, but you know, you know, I can't relate to needing to jack off before I go
to sleep, but I can relate in that I feel extreme anger at myself if I haven't jacked off during
the day when I go to sleep. It's like, I wasted my day. What was I doing this whole day if I
didn't jack off? So it's a wash, you know? Yeah. Nothing, nothing fills me with regret like that.
I actually, I surprisingly know what you mean, because like, I'll be going to bed and jacked
off. I lost, I lost a little bit of joy out of my life. Well, it's just because there's,
I feel like there's so much porn in the world that every day I don't jack off, it's like,
I've pushed back that like the tide has gotten away from me more. That's true. Like, you know,
like if I, if I jack off three times in the same day, and then it gets to a point where like,
I've seen everything on the couple, like everything new on the few sites I use, and I'm like, wow,
I'm like ahead of the curve for Jack. Like, I feel like this, to this current week of porn,
I've seen all of it, and I can check that off as like, in the historical context of porn,
there's a whole week where I know everything that came out that week. It's, it's such an
interesting, you know, it's such a telling insight into you, did you, that you think about porn in
the same way you think about like anime or like any of the media you're trying to consume. It's
just another art form to be consumed. Yeah. You're a beast. I have strong, I have strong regrets
that I can't do like porn analysis where I stand to date.
That you can't do porn analysis. You know, Cece's been talking about maybe doing some of that shit.
We need the, we need the, the pornographers do that.
Well, the problem with doing porn analysis is that it's all going to be the same. It's always
going to be like, and this, this picture is attractive because the line art curves in this
way. And that's what makes it odd, you know. Well, I mean, if you're, no, that's, that's dumb,
because I mean, if you look at just, just the one example is that, that Bane porn that, that
fucking like Pornhub did, that was like, I don't know. You don't know what I'm talking about?
God, it was this, it was this, like clearly the TV board on 4chan was responsible for making this
happen. It was like, there was just some porn where like this guy brings a chick home to his house.
His whole family is Bane, like his mom and dad.
How have they told you about this before? Wait, is the guy Bane too?
Yeah, they're all Bane. Everyone's Bane. Mom's Bane, dad's Bane, the kid's Bane.
Wait, is the girl Bane? The girl's Bane too. She puts on the mask and she becomes Bane.
Every line, every, every line of the script, like was a meme, was a TV meme. It was,
it was insane. And like, that's fucking fascinating. That was the coolest thing I've ever seen in my
life. So, uh, you know, go Google that. I don't, I don't know. Why is nobody doing episodic, uh,
vlogging of the sex factor? That's a great question. That's a really great question.
Literally all of my friends are watching it at this point. Yeah, that's, you know,
it's the new X-Hamster original series, which is literally a reality show about porn. It's,
it's like America's next top model, but for porn stars. Oh my, yeah. Do you have to make,
do you have to make porn? Yeah, they're all like upcoming, they're all like new people who are
trying to become porn stars. And there's like the male team and the women's team. And they're
trying to like, what's like the, what's like the challenge they have every week? It'll be like,
who can give the best advice or something. Yeah. No, they're trying to be actors. There's one,
in episode two, there was a part where they, it was just like a minor competition for the guy's
side where they all had to stand around this bathtub and they all had their dicks out. And
there's two women in the bathtub making out and whoever got an erection fastest would, uh, then
they would make his dick into a mold, like for a dildo. And it might do to a hero d protagonist
one, that shit. Clearly a one piece fan. Um, oh yeah, you're right. Hero d protagonist. I looked
into it. I looked into it. The d stands for danger. He's not actually one piece. You know,
you know, that's kind of thought in the way that it dehumanizes them. Oh yeah, it's great.
Something about dehumanization is very, is very attractive to me. I don't want to think about
the humans really like low budget, badly edited, uh, like reality show, but it feels just like
any other reality show aside from the fact that it's particularly badly edited. But, uh, like,
yeah, it's, uh, it is what it is. And we played a drinking game with it, me and my friends, just
like, uh, every time, like certain, like every time they show the logo or like show certain
characters, you have to drink or, uh, whatever. But yeah, it's, uh, by the way, Blair Williams,
Blair Williams is going the distance. Blair's going to win it. I'm calling her right now.
She's the champion. She's got the hunger. She's got the fire. She's got what it takes to win
this competition. So Blair sleep. Um, yeah, right. How many hours a day do you think Blair Williams
sleeps? Uh, man, I, uh, in eternity after each one of these sessions, she needs to recharge
because she brings such intensity to the competition. It's going to take months to recover. Yep.
Yep. I think we've all officially got our brains on porn now. Nobody's thinking about sleep anymore.
That's true. So I don't know. Should we wrap this up? Anybody got any more thoughts on sleep?
Let's want it to go away. They don't have sleep in Star Trek. I'm, uh, what? Of course they do.
No, they don't. They have those like, they have those pod things where they just like sit in it
and it'll like give them however much sleep they want. And then they have those in, um,
it's not true. They have those in, um, that, what's that anime with the, the Star Kingdom
and the Empire? Uh, Legend of the Galactic Heroes. They do have it in there. Yeah, don't they? Yeah.
Yeah. Good. Wait, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, what? I've never, I've watched The Tone of Star. I've
never seen these fucking pods. Everyone has quarters that they sleep in. Yeah, but they can also use
uh, the, the strings. Isn't there like a rest? I have never seen this shit. I remember there was
a part where like, like in between battles, right? Yeah, like when they're about to do something
that's going to take a long time, they'll like go into the pod and just like get the quick rest
or whatever. I'm pretty sure. Yeah, like they don't, they don't use them all the time. Yeah. But
they have them on, on the ships that crew members can jump into. What the fuck? Why did I not see
this shit? Star Trek about that. No, that's just some, that's a good thing. Uh, well, I'll have to
look into it, I guess. Here's the upside. I mean, I hate, I hate sleep. I wish I could stay awake
and work all the time. However, me too. I made a graph the other day about my motivation to work
and how it's, when I wake up, it's usually, it's like dirt at the bottom, but then like as the,
but the day gets closer and closer to being done, it like ramps up because I become desperate. I'm
like, oh my God, I haven't done anything today. That's fair. Uh, and so I guess, I do schedule
my whole day around, like I do like structure how I'm going to start the day very specifically,
like oftentimes if I'm working on a video, uh, I'll have my bed scooted right up next to my desk
and my, I don't have like a bed frame, so it goes underneath my desk nicely. Wake up, um,
I, I wake up and then I was just waiting for an interruption there. Um, and feel just fine
your face. Oh, and so then the first thing I do is like I make one edit, like, like the first thing
I do is I'll like, you know, there, I just did one edit, you know, and that way when I go to the
bathroom and get breakfast or talk to people, I am taking a break from editing rather than waiting
for the moment at which I start working on editing. So I do a lot of work. In fact, actually,
what I did yesterday or this morning was I was trying to finish this anime and so I put the next
episode of it as, um, my wake up song because it was Gonkotsuo, the Count of Monte Cristo in OP for
that is a really nice song to wake up to. I can't imagine waking up and immediately trying to process
it. Subtitle. Well, you were watching dubbed, but you're really onto something there though with
like the doing a little bit of work right away. I mean, like more artists than I can even count
say that like, you know, you just got to do like a war like when you wake up, you got to do like a
warm up sketch to get in the fucking zone. You got to like bang out like one or two real quick ones.
So you're in like a drawing mindset and like I'm sure that applies to others. You know, I've been
doing that a little bit too, Davoo, but you've reinvigorated my desire to do that to sort of
force yourself into it. Good advice. I just kind of wake up and immediately watch like all the YouTube
videos. That's like the first thing I do. I mean, I'm, I've been in the habit of like getting up
and then I go on Twitter and I checked to Pastic for any messages and I check my email and I
look at my Tumblr and I just, and like sometimes it really fucks me up because like before I'd know
it like six hours of gunfire. Yeah, fucking around on social media. Definitely always like the first
hour or two after I wake up are usually like just reading and responding to comments and like
watching every YouTube video that's come out. And sometimes if a lot of long ones have come out
and I just don't think about it, I will end up sitting there for like hours. And the only upside
to that kind of is that I won't eat like I won't think to eat for that time. So like I'm convinced
that the only way that I keep my weight in check is that I sleep so much and I forget to eat any
time I get into something like, you know, sleep for eight hours, wake up, sit on the internet for
two hours and then realize you're hungry and like, I don't know, seems like a good weight loss.
Whoa, hey, Ben's, I just happened to open Twitter because Ben suggested, I just saw that
Idol Yo-Kai did the draw cast, the first Pokemon draw cast, you just drew all the Pokemon.
Way to go, dude. Nice work. They look beautiful. Shout out to you, Idol Yo-Kai. Anyway, yeah,
they're awesome. Let's wrap this bad boy up, shall we? Anyone else got anything to say?
Yes, I got to say, go to the Procrastinator subreddit, r slash the Procrastinators,
because I don't know if everyone knows about it, because we were talking about-
Oh, I don't think we've ever mentioned it on-
Yeah, I think we got to get people on there, because you know, I'm sure some people have some
degree in which they're thinking, man, if only there was a place where I could follow everything
that the TPC people do. Well, you're-
No, I use it myself, like I log on there and I check the fucking r slash the Procrastinators.
Yeah, hello, Reddit. Did you know that Harry's Razors, they loved these Razors so much,
they bought the factory that makes the Razors. No, I'm serious. Like, I log on to the subreddit
to see if any of you guys have released any videos. Oh, yeah, that's cool.
Because I don't want to ask in the chat, because you guys aren't always online and like-
And this subreddit is not only for a way to exhaust it.
And let rival Steven take care of it for me.
All songs that these people make are posted on here. Because that's one thing, is that not
everyone is able to follow all of the sound clouds of Jesse and Digi and so on. But all of the songs
that are made are also posted here. And best of all, all of the fan art that people draw is posted
immediately to the subreddit. So you can- Not all of it? Do you not-
Well, hopefully all of mine. I mean, I get like two or three a day.
Hmm, I see. Just whatever rival Steven has to catch.
Well, we encourage anyone who follows him on Twitter, just feel free to post it there anyway.
All right, that's enough. And he also not nearly all of our videos,
because not all my after dark stuff gets posted there, I don't think.
Oh, man. Guys, you gotta help out. Because like, rival Steven is this guy who stood up to the
challenge and has been posting almost everything. But you guys can do it, too. Do our bitch work
for us, please. Thank you very much. Yeah, please and thank you. Okay, and with that,
we're done. Wrap it up for the day. Thank you for watching this week of the faux-po-cast,
this thing. Thanks again. We'll see you next week. Everybody say goodbye. Bye.