Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast, it's morning in America and it's afternoon in Japan
where Gibb is reporting live from Japan, he should send breakfast in America because that's an album by the, what's it called, Super Tramp, are they a British band?
Half British, half Australian, I believe, they're members. I really like Super Tramp. Yes. I love Super Tramp. Good reference, one time in my old house, like two houses ago, me and a guy just got really drunk and just were like, oh my god, you like Super Tramp, I like Super Tramp.
When I was young, life was so wonderful. The miracle was beautiful, magical. Yeah, I remember. I remember when things happen sometimes. How's your week been, Gibb?
My week, gee, I don't know, it's a blur. Oh, I beat Outer Wilds, that's the thing. I talked about it last time, but I beat it.
You beat what now?
Outer Wilds, remember the game, the space game?
Oh yeah, I downloaded it, but I haven't played it yet.
Give it a go, give it a good old try.
It's on my desktop, so yeah, I should. I just haven't gotten around to it.
I'm halfway through editing, finishing to edit my video, like the final cut.
I had to do the whole rough cut, and now I'm going through the fine tooth comb, like doing the final edit of it, and that is half done.
I have three and a half hours out of probably seven and a half hours, so that's what I've been doing this week.
Oh, you mean you've gone through three hours? I thought you'd cut it down from seven to three somehow?
No, no, I have edited three and a half hours of it, and there is about three and a half hours, probably four hours left to go.
Crazy.
Two weeks ago I said maybe I'd have it done by the time the episode dropped, lol, that was silly, that was too optimistic, but I said as much.
Progress is progress.
Yeah, hey yeah, it is.
Hell yeah.
I made a bit of progress on the Clarissa, I'm now in the final scene kind of, the showdown.
I'm at the showdown.
Of the sketches?
Of the blocking out of the pages.
They're sort of half sketches, I'm deciding where the characters are standing and what poses they have, and I might change that before I properly sketch them.
Like a storyboard almost.
Yeah.
Yeah, I gotcha, I gotcha.
Cool, how many pages is it at?
Oh, I knew this, I counted them, I think right now.
Yeah, the most obvious question, you gotta know this one's coming.
I think it's like 80 something pages that have been blocked out and need to be sketched, so 80 something pages currently and will include more by the end.
And there's 50 that are already out, you can read right now on gippentake.site.
Clarissa Gunsmoke and the Bandit King, I forget the exact URL.
Just go to gippentake.site and read my comic.
Yes, indeed, indeed.
But yeah, it's like I'm not technically getting that much done, but I am always getting something done, so it's coming along.
I don't know whether I'll be finishing things up by the end of October.
I hope to at least be in the sketching phase and then see how many pages I can get done.
And then at some point this will happen, the progress is slow but steady.
It'd be nice if it was first, but I can't have everything.
No indeed, no indeed.
True words were never spoken.
When's it gonna be done?
Huh?
Give me deadline right now.
No, no, no, no, no.
Before the end of the year, because I don't think I have anything coming up that will distract.
So as long as I keep the work in every day, every weekday, and I do a certain amount of stuff, couple hours a day at the very least, yeah, I can get it done.
Christmas is always a big busy time, but November isn't.
November's fine.
I'm feeling a little bit, I don't want to be a Grinch, I don't want to be a Halloween Grinch, but I'm feeling a little bit anti-Halloween this year.
I'm feeling a little bit fed up with all the spooky season pumpkin posting.
It's the second and I'm already a little bit sick of it, if I'm being completely honest.
The spooky posting is just sort of like whatever, but I like Halloween.
Every year, every year, the noise, noise, noise, noise, they just keep posting and posting.
You're gonna go around in a devil costume and steal all the candy so they can't trick or treat.
It'll only be tricks.
I'm gonna go around dressed as a Mormon saying, I don't let my kids celebrate Halloween and I won't let you seduce him.
I won't let you groom him into Halloween-ing with you.
I don't get it. I don't really like it very much.
The aesthetic is not that appealing. I guess it's fine because it's different.
I feel like it didn't used to be the whole month of October.
Back in my day, I don't remember.
I mean, the sheer Halloween decorations start going up.
I don't know.
I have a similar feeling in that-
I like spending Halloween with friends. It is a fun holiday, but that's about it.
That's as strong as I feel about it.
It's like the Halloween posts feel obligatory by a lot of people.
It's mostly just tweets where I'm like, oh, spooky.
Here's a gif. I'm like, yeah, I've seen that before.
Everybody's got their own little thing doing.
I think they're just sort of excited and that's fine.
The posts aren't what I'm interested in.
I like the stuff that happens on October because you're guaranteed your favorite content creator is gonna have a Halloween special.
They're all gonna do it.
That's quite fun.
Yeah, okay. That's fair. That's true.
I never used to. I never used to dress up.
I dressed up when I was younger and I was a little kid for Halloween and stuff,
but when I got into my teenage years, I was like,
what am I gonna do wearing a garbage bag as a cape and a little hat?
I don't need to do that.
So I didn't and I'm like, that's a garbage bag and a little hat.
That's your costume. That's your idea of a Halloween costume.
Yeah, I didn't give a fuck.
Hey, what are you this year, kid?
I was just wearing this garbage bag and a little hat.
You mean it's Halloween?
Yeah.
But I want to get back into that.
I want to actually make a Halloween costume this year.
I want to try and make something or half make it and half buy some stuff at thrift stores and put together an outfit
instead of just relying on store bought masks that we got 19 years ago that are in the Halloween box.
Because that's what I used to be.
If I don't put any effort in, all I've got is the Halloween box and the Halloween box is really old and sucks.
I used to always try and make it an opportunity to do what I guess I would later come to know as cosplay.
I always used to want to, for Halloween, I always used to be a video game character.
It's a little lame to cosplay on Halloween. It's not spooky.
I feel like it's worth something. If you're going to do it, you should be on brand with it.
I suppose so, yeah.
It's not an anime convention.
That's what I would tell my young self if I could go back and do it all over again.
Yeah, I mean little babies.
Little babies are allowed to be like a minion or something.
Well, if you're scared of scary stuff, you can be like a little Captain America or whatever.
Well, everyone, who did I see saying like, fuck, everyone is going to be the Queen's corpse this year?
Everyone is going to be zombie.
Shit, was the Queen named Victoria?
It's Elizabeth.
Elizabeth, sorry, everyone's going to be the zombie Queen Elizabeth.
You know, I hadn't even considered that, but that is kind of an obvious edgy joke costume.
Do you remember the year that the Dark Knight came out and everybody was fucking the Joker?
They were fucking the Joker?
They were fucking the Joker, Jerry.
Oh my god, yeah, he got so much sex.
They fucked him. He got so much puse.
No, everybody was Heath Ledger's Joker.
It's going to be that with the zombie Queen Elizabeth.
The new hit blockbuster was the Queen's funeral because there's nothing else in the cinema.
That's how it feels.
Basically, I want to make a thing. I just haven't decided.
I made a tweet just now, just today.
I'm like, what am I going to be? What do I do?
Because I don't know. I could be Friska, but she just wears a jacket.
She's not scary except when she's trying to kill people.
What am I going to do?
Yeah, blah, blah.
I feel like, I don't know, I think that'd be funny.
I know I just said Cosplaying on Halloween is wrong.
I don't actually think it's wrong. I just think it was lame when I did it.
I would tell myself not to do it, but I hold myself to a different standard.
Because I did it enough.
I did it enough.
Were you Mega Man X?
No, I was Link from Zelda one year.
I was Squall from Final Fantasy VIII in eighth grade.
I don't know. It's so stupid, pitiful, pathetic. Die.
Do you have pictures? Do you have pictures we can put on the screen of Ben St. as Squall?
No. I mean, maybe my parents have some pictures of it. I hope not.
I hope not.
I don't know. Looking back, it's sad because I used to think it would be cool.
I used to want to cosplay as Zero from Mega Man Zero.
I was like, damn, I want to dress like that. I want to have a costume like that.
Oh, with the long blond, like, spiky hair thing?
Yes, but specifically the one from the Zero series, which looks distinct from Zero in the rest of the series.
He had a different artist.
This is the case for Zero as well as for everyone else.
You can't just dress like that.
Or, in fact, basically anything that I wanted to dress like.
You can't just dress like that and look fine because you don't have that body type.
You don't actually look like that.
If I tried to dress like Mega Man Zero...
Sorry, his name's not Mega Man Zero. His name's just Zero.
I don't know. I would just look like a fat weirdo.
He has a very twinkish body type.
Despite how much I appreciate the character, I simply could not pull it off.
Same with Squall.
It's not really made much of in the game, but Squall is a very tall, handsome, lantern-jawed, slim-build sort of guy.
I was like a dumpy kid.
I'm sure it just looked miserable.
It's hard to look good when you're being a character that doesn't exist.
Isn't it fun, though?
To dress up?
I did have fun, but I shouldn't have. That was my mistake.
That was wrong of me and I apologize.
I didn't have the school bullies to laugh at you directly.
It's such an obvious way to make you aware that you didn't look perfect.
Nobody laughed at me.
In fact, even one of the kids who I wouldn't have called him a bully.
I didn't really have bullies in school, but there was a kid from a clique that I considered to be more diametrically opposed.
A kid I thought wouldn't like me, but I got a compliment.
I was like, oh, that's a good game. I liked that game Final Fantasy VIII.
I was like, oh, what? Oh, cool.
It sounds like it was a good idea and it was fine, Benz scene.
It sounds like it was not embarrassing at all.
But let me tell you, it was embarrassing for internal reasons.
I embarrassed myself to myself.
I'm not worried about anyone else's opinion.
I don't care what anyone else thinks. I only care what my extremely self-critical version of myself thinks.
Yeah, man, I'm a rebel. I don't care what anyone else thinks except the voice in my head that tells me what a loser I am, that one.
I'm very concerned about it. Let me shape my whole life around it.
Man, dad.
Yep, I'm a renegade.
I could do like a steampunk, goth, vampire, queen sort of thing.
Just trying to think of like the classic.
I was thinking of like being like a character, but I don't know.
I don't know whether I want to be a reference to something.
Because it's easy if you're a reference to something. You just reference the image or the character design.
And you can like, you know, steal their look and get all the things.
But that feels too easy.
But then again, I might not have the patience to do a lot of work on it.
So I might take the easy approach and just like get some like red boots and goes Marcelline or something.
I can play bass. It works.
True. Yeah.
Damn, I didn't even think about even think about costuming.
I just assumed I wouldn't do it.
Maybe I could do something.
Maybe you could be the Professor Brothers or whatever those guys are called.
No, would anybody, would anybody get that?
I mean, you've referenced it before. I don't even remember what they're about.
Yeah. I mean, would anyone outside of the podcast get it?
Even people who listen to the, first of all, people can't see me on the podcast.
Yeah. We're not going to dress up for, we might.
I mean, it depends on when we're recording the one near Halloween.
Bonus episode idea. Episode recorded in Halloween costume.
But you can't see us.
But every so often, if we're wearing a crinkly outfit, we'll crinkle.
We'll crinkle for you.
And you'll know. It'll change the whole vibe.
We'll change.
I am not sure if I will do a costume or if I did, like what would I wear it to?
I'm not sure. I haven't worked all that out yet.
But I'm not completely sure. I'm not, I'm not saying I definitely won't.
But I won't if I don't have any good reason to.
Sure. I mean, I'm not really going to go out to a party wearing it.
I don't have any parties planned.
Maybe I'll find something.
I just want to like do it to do it and then take some pictures.
And then I can wear it during Halloween.
And then I might just, if I make something cool that I can just wear normally.
That'd be cool.
And I can just wear forever.
Why only do Halloween on Halloween?
You know, you know, actually, oh man, I had a
realization on the subject of costumes.
I have started, okay, because I've lost, I've lost a bunch of weight.
I'm down to like 160 pounds, which for my height is,
which for my height actually puts me BMI wise,
it puts me just under the line of being overweight.
So I'm just barely no longer overweight according to BMI.
I guess so.
This is, I feel like, like it just, it feels hard for me to get to this weight.
It doesn't, like I'm usually, but I am now.
So anyway, what I'm saying is that I feel like BMI underestimates how much I should weigh.
But that's a different subject anyway.
I have lost a bunch of weight.
And so I now fit into a bunch of clothes that I have not been able to wear for a while again.
I fit into a bunch of shirts that I used to really like.
I wore one the other day, a button down.
It felt good.
I thought I looked good in it.
But I was wearing the jacket, the same jacket that I wore in the Radcon 4 lectures.
It's like a black tuxedo jacket, sort of.
It doesn't have tails in the back, but it's sort of like,
it's sort of a tuxedo jacket.
But it's like, I don't know what you'd call it.
It's like a short, sort of like half jacket.
It's like, doesn't reach all the way down to my waist.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's like a tuxedo crop jacket.
And I think it's so cool.
And I wish I had more of them.
I was looking for like similar things on like Amazon or eBay.
And I couldn't really find that many.
Almost all the things I did find were women's.
Which is like, well, I mean, I would wear a women's, I would wear a women's jacket if like,
as long as it didn't look like super girly or anything.
But most of the ones I found were, they either looked girly
or they were like really expensive.
So that was kind of a bummer.
There weren't that many.
But I was looking at the tag of it to see if I could find any information about the manufacturer.
And it was like, it's like a costume jacket.
It's made for by like a costume company.
Not like a regular clothing company.
I was like, huh, okay, sure, whatever.
I guess I'm not supposed to wear this in quote unquote real life.
Yeah, that's a bunch of hooey.
It is a bunch of hooey.
Thank you.
That's what I've been saying.
I think partly I just want to, I want to try doing something like a little ostentatious,
a little out there, a little extreme.
For me, in a way that I can like get used to, I don't know, wearing more wilder things in normal day to day.
Because I tend to like chicken out still and wear a t-shirt and whatever, like jeans.
I'm like, that's fine, I guess.
It's clothing.
But like, I can wear other things.
I can wear more or better things.
What if I did that more?
What if that was, I don't know, then I had to explain it.
I am not, you're saying you're saying you want to wear something outlandish and attention-grabbing.
On Halloween.
As an exercise.
As a practice.
Because you're allowed to and it just sort of would make it easier to like, I don't know.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm embarrassed about like, wearing things that are more feminine.
And I don't know.
I want to get better at it because I do like it when I try.
I mean, you can wear whatever you want on Halloween.
So you can truly go wild.
Nobody's going to say shit.
Yeah.
Okay.
So where are we going from here?
I don't know.
That was really my only thought.
So it's just like, I want to do a Halloween thing.
And that's my mind is set on that for the moment.
That's all I'm thinking about.
I'm going to obviously work on the Clarissa, but I don't know what October will bring.
And it will just probably be a month.
And that's, that's how it usually goes.
I feel pretty confident that my for this October, I will, I will finish editing my big video probably in the next week.
And I really mean it this time.
And then maybe I will get it posted in the same week.
Although you never know.
Sometimes things can happen.
Like if there's always the chance that I try to upload it, but like it gets flagged.
And then I have to like do some fuckery with it to get around copyright stuff or content flags or something.
Or there's the chance that like the rendering might prove problematic because it's such a big video.
And sometimes rendering really big videos can be a real fucky-wucky.
So I'll probably get that done in like the next week.
So my October will probably be, I'll probably, I guess I'll, once that's done, I'll be going back to finish up Slime and Punishment and getting that the book version of it done and hopefully produced.
I was thinking about, I was thinking about what I was going to do for the Kickstarter trailer for Slime and Punishment.
And I have a green screen.
And I was thinking, I wonder if I could do some kind of, I wonder if I could do some kind of like in character green screen like from New Los Angeles City as the cop killer sort of little message.
I think that would be cool.
I think that could look pretty cool.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Use a little filter.
How would you a green screen if you're, are you going to have your green like mask, the one that has your teeth on it?
Wait, what do you mean?
Don't you have like a mask, like a little fabric thing that you can pull up over your face that has like your gross slime teeth?
Oh, sure.
Well, I wouldn't wear that.
I mean, that would cover my, my real face.
No, we just use a fricking, just use fricking color shift video elements.
Just, just make myself purple, crunch up the contrast, add some filters.
Maybe I could get it so that my teeth look green.
Anyway, you know, that would be pretty cool.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I guess we'll see.
I just, I thought that would be a, I thought that would be a fun way to approach it.
It might, might be cool.
I don't know.
Oh, um, speaking of kick starters, um, the clown, the clown milk Kickstarter.
She, do you see that?
She's his clown milk.
Yeah.
Kickstarter.
He met, he mentioned it.
It is, it is, it is, it is sluggish.
It's going sluggishly.
It is not on track to hit its funding goal.
I hope it, I hope it comes from behind and hits it.
I pledge five bucks.
It does seem to be that it always ramps up near the end.
So I can, we can hope.
That does, that, that does.
It's got to, it's got to be like a big marketing push closer to the, the end of it.
I hope he, yeah, I hope he's able to like maybe do a podcast appearance or two or something
or something to, uh, yeah, get eyes on it.
I think it's at like a little under two K now of it's like 16 K goal.
You know, I wasn't, I had no idea like what's like what the market is like for clown porn.
Like for all I know, it could be like a very untapped market and there's a, and there would
be like a ground swell of like support for it.
It's, it's weird.
I feel like clown, like sexy clown women as an idea has become more popular more recently.
I don't know.
You know, I feel that way, but it might just be because I know cheesy.
It might be, but I don't know.
Like there's like Twitter users that dress up in clown makeup and they do like the Hong Kong sex.
Like it's a, it's a.
I have seen a couple of them, but I see them because cheesy follows them and cheesy retweets
them sometimes.
So that's why I'm like, is it, is it really becoming popular or am I just, have I just
been exposed to some more, more of it than none?
Well, I mean, I look at the, the likes and I'm like, these aren't like niche accounts.
They're quite big, like reasonably big.
I mean, I think, I think that they're more popular, but I don't know how popular in general.
Yeah.
I think, I think like 10 years ago, the idea would have been like, like people were talking
about how clowns are creepy, like that was the thing.
Nobody was talking about how clowns were sexy.
There's, yeah, there's one, um, there's one, I think she's a Twitch streamer or like an
Instagram girl.
She's called, I think she's called bouncy clown.
Uh, she's cute, but, but her bio is like, her bio says like cute clown, not scary clown.
Yeah.
No, I think, no, I think you're right.
I feel like there's been a little bit of like, hey, maybe clowns are all right sometimes.
I think it's just like a general sense of like people embracing like grossness.
I think the pendulum has swung a little bit the other way on clowns.
I feel similarly.
Yeah.
People in general, I think are like embracing grossness as like a comedy thing, like going
goblin mode and being like a horrible thing.
So like clowns used to be scary, but now they're sexy is like, could be a part of that.
Hmm.
Oh, monster girls, but girls will, they will just kill you like a stab you in the face.
Somebody do that so hot.
Somebody needs to write a video essay on, you know, the, the semiotics of the, the intersection
between clowns and got clowns and pop culture and goblin mode and what it means for society.
Um, man, oh man.
So anyway, uh, I've been, I've been, I've been keeping my eye on that, but reminder to
any viewers that haven't, they should check out the clown milk Kickstarter if they're,
if they want to see that succeed.
Yes.
Uh, what else?
What else?
I didn't, I don't have any notes.
I didn't write any notes for this, um, for this, this week.
Yeah.
It's sort of been a weird week.
And by weird, I mean normal.
I'm just like, I have a good day and I get some work done.
Then I have a bad day and it's sad.
Then I'm okay.
The week's over.
I got some work done.
Well, that's good.
Okay.
New, new month.
Oh, I've got to do my money spenders podcast.
I kind of forgot that.
I have, you know, I recorded a, I did record a, a patron, uh, thing a few weeks ago.
I said in that, that like, I don't think, I called the monthly Q and A's, but I haven't
been doing the monthly for a while.
And I think it's time to acknowledge that like, I'm not going to do them monthly.
They're probably going to be more like every couple of months.
And I think I'm, I think I'm okay with that because, you know, I have this podcast to
say everything that happens to me on a somewhat regular basis that the patron one is for, um,
I don't know, uh, opining about more things, more generally the direction my life is heading,
I guess.
So a more zoomed out view is, is okay.
I think.
Yeah.
That's the same with mine.
It's, it's more personal, more things I don't want to be said publicly, but I'm okay with
saying a little bit.
There isn't, there isn't, there isn't too much.
I guess there's some things that I would not say on the PCP.
There's not that many things though.
It's pretty, it's pretty uncommon for me to have like something that I don't want to
talk about on here.
For me, it's mostly just like trends thoughts.
And I'm like, well, I mean, if I'm talking on a podcast with you, you won't get it.
So it'll sort of be me talking by myself.
So I may as well just be talking by myself on my own podcast about that sort of stuff.
I mean, guilty.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Gip.
That's fine.
If only you could have just not been CIS, if only.
If only.
Then we could have, then we could have like a friendship, but you know, the moment is
just a purely business relationship.
We got going.
Yeah, it's, yeah, it's too, it's too bad.
You know, it's, it is a shame.
You know, I did always want to be a girl, but unfortunately I'm not, I'm not CIS.
So it just didn't work out that way.
You shook the magic and you asked and I said, yeah.
In another role of history's dice, perhaps.
Speaking of being a girl, another one more page, new turned in one more page.
Yes, I saw this week.
It's slowed down a little bit.
I haven't, I haven't heard from Simsie about his page in a while.
I think he, I think he might have like, I think he might have like taken a hiatus from drawing.
I might ask him again about it.
And if he like, I might just like finish up the sketch that he did for him rather than
like find someone to do that.
And then maybe I'll just do the rest.
I might just do the rest of that page myself, even though I had a hard line stance against.
I mean, it's worth reaching out for sure.
I did ask, I did ask him about it again, but that was several weeks ago at this point.
So yeah, maybe one more, maybe one more try.
And then I'm like, oh, well, oh, well, he seems, he seems like he's,
he seems like he's not feeling it on Twitter recently.
So I think maybe he's, maybe he's not wanting to do it at the moment, which is fine.
We love that boy.
We miss that boy.
Love that boy.
Miss that boy.
Precious.
Precious Simsie.
Come back to us.
No, it's fine.
The dojin though.
Yeah.
There's only what, like maybe five pages left or something like that.
And then it's, there's no cover.
Still don't have a cover.
There was a, there was, there was a guy, that guy who worked on Scott Pilgrim that I wanted to ask if he'd draw the cover.
And I have, he was a little bit, at first he was busy and then he was like, sorry, I've been busy.
Let me get back to you about it.
And I was like, okay.
And then he didn't get back to me.
So I might give up on that too.
Hmm.
I think, I think Kaiji might have wanted to draw the cover.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
And I didn't know anything to say.
What, huh?
Is there a lag?
Is there a lag that is like closing conversational difficulties?
No.
Is there?
Can you hear me?
Right now?
I can hear you.
Yeah.
I just don't know when you're hearing me.
I think we're fine.
No, I think, no, I think we're good.
Hmm.
Oh, this disease, I don't have, I don't have that much to talk about.
I can talk about.
Do you want to hear, do you want to, oh yeah, yeah.
Something.
The Last of Us part two.
You played that game?
No.
I remember hearing all sorts of bad things about it when it came out.
And my brother's been playing it and I've been watching him.
And it's good.
It's actually very good.
I like what they're doing.
I have seen video essays talking about it.
Because I didn't play the first one and I didn't plan to.
And I wasn't going to play the second one.
But I have heard people talk about it.
And a bunch of the video essay people that I follow have said that the game got a lot
of backlash when it came out.
But actually it's kind of good.
Yeah.
Although the story is maybe a little bit confused, maybe not confused, but like all over the
place.
And like thematically it's a little bit like, hmm, what exactly were they going for?
But like there is a, there are themes there.
Is my impression.
I would say it's a lot more cohesive and people are giving it credit.
I don't know why.
Like I've heard that as well.
They think it's disjointed.
It's very simple.
Well, it sounds like people are split on the ending.
And I guess it's like, I guess like half of the game you play as the person that kills
Joel.
Yeah.
And then you have to sort of play as them and sort of see like what their deal is.
Which is a, which is a, which is a, I think that's a fair and reasonable thing to do in
the, in the story, but I can definitely see how it's off-putting.
If you like Joel and then the game is like now understand why the person that murdered
Joel kind of was, was, was a justified or not justified, but like, you know, why they,
they had their reasons come to play as them and understand them as their own person.
See, that's the, the service is challenging.
It's a, it's a challenging decision.
That's surface level though.
I feel like having, having seen the game play out in real time with the cutscenes happening
when they do, it's not about just like the, the, the frustration of playing as Joel's killer.
It's like more of a, a broader theme about like the, the necessariness of revenge and
how it's like self-defeating.
Cause the whole Abbey, right?
She is the person who kills Joel.
Her dad was a guy who Joel killed at the end of the first game and he was a very important
guy.
He was going to save the world with a vaccine and Joel killed him because the vaccine would
have killed Ellie.
Well, that's like, that's the, I mean, I've heard, I've heard, I've heard some people
question whether that vaccine would have actually like worked.
Sure.
I mean, yeah.
But in theory, they were going to try it.
They were doing that.
Yeah.
But the thing is that was Abbey's dad.
Abbey obviously hates Joel and is dead set on finding Joel and killing him.
What the fuck?
And so why is it a Libyan?
Is that a Libyan fall?
A Libyan fall.
Yo.
We already started recording.
I'm recording.
Okay.
Hey, good to see you.
You have a surprise pop in.
Well, I was going to be recording a draw cast right now, but I couldn't find people.
So I said, fuck it.
I'll do something else.
I see.
Cool.
Okay.
Now this is what we're doing, I guess.
So last was part two spoilers, by the way.
Have you not seen the game?
I don't know.
You don't know.
It's not the kind of game I'm ever going to play in my life.
So I don't care.
Yeah.
That's me.
Like I've been spoiled on it because like I was never going to play it.
The last was part one.
So, okay.
So the thing with Abby is that her desire to kill Joel for revenge of her father and
the rest of the fireflies that he killed kind of fucks up her own life because the one,
the, her boyfriend that she was seeing ends up with some other woman who is one of the
women in the game that Ellie ends up killing.
Her life, her boyfriend is sort of like, he doesn't like that Abby is constantly all
about killing Joel and this revenge thing and they grow distant because of that.
Abby sort of grows distant from her friend group and sort of finds like her life has
less meaning.
And after, you know, she kills Joel, she comes back and her life is kind of sucked.
It's kind of sucked of like purpose and it's like not good.
It's a bad thing.
So it's framed as Abby's desire for revenge was not good for Abby.
And so in parallel, Ellie goes off to kill Abby because she killed Joel and Ellie has
a similar sort of like lust for revenge.
But then we see through Abby's like situation that it's, it's not a good thing to go for
revenge.
It's a bad thing to do for your own life.
And Ellie's friends and like potential love interest are put in harm's way because of
her lust for this, this, this catharsis of killing Abby to revenge Joel.
She puts her own life in danger.
She fucks herself up and her friends and her, you know, and it's like, that's what the game
is about.
It's about like how revenge is self-defeating.
And it doesn't really do much for like anyone else.
And I was, I was just, I just like it.
I just like it as a, as a theme.
I like how it's portrayed and how it's not, it's not as simple.
Yeah.
It's not as simple and like one note as people I've seen make comments about why like it's
a game where you shoot people and the game tells you that you're a bad person for shooting
people because Ryan, that is not at all what it says.
That's sort of a cliche at this point.
Yeah.
Cause like you obviously shoot people for survival because that's the world you live in.
But it's specifically the revengeful killings that are not necessary for survival or self-defense
that are, you know, sort of bloodlust.
That's the thing that they're having a go at.
Like why'd you feel like Joel doesn't deserve what he got?
And also why does Abby feel like she deserved to do that?
Why does Ellie feel like she deserves to do any of this?
It doesn't, you don't need to do that.
You're just fucking yourself up.
That's the sort of message.
And it's controversial, but like, I like it.
It's, it's well told.
It's a story that I am into.
It's interesting.
And I don't like when people like sum it up in such stupid ways.
Yeah.
They don't have a choice for, there's a woman in the game who isn't
conventionally attractive.
So, you know, it's all terrible.
We have to fucking hate everything.
There are a few people like that.
I don't know how many, but it definitely felt like the first wave of hate was like,
I can't believe that somebody killed Joel and she's an ugly woman.
I know.
I saw this a lot of it.
And it was just so silly.
Is that, Abby's not ugly, is she?
She's like, she's not like, she's kind of like muscular.
She's muscular.
She's like jacked.
That's the problem.
And she's got a normal person face.
It's like, she's not a beauty model.
And it's like, it's like, wow, what normal person, person in a post-apocalypse that
has big muscles for survival.
It makes sense.
It's just sort of like, you know, it's a silly thing to get mad about.
And I know some people got mad specifically about how she looked.
It's just not realistic, though.
You know, like a woman just wouldn't be muscular like that.
It just strains suspension of disbelief, I say, in my mushroom zombie apocalypse.
You know, unrealistic that women would exist at all in a post-apocalypse if you think about it.
Mm-mm.
True.
Yeah, they say the mushroom crowd would have killed them all and then it'd be Lisa instead.
Remember Lisa?
From The Simpsons?
No, from Lisa the Painful.
Oh, yes.
There's not enough women or something.
Wait, wait, Lisa's not even in Lisa the Painful.
She's dead.
She was dead the whole time.
Spoilers.
Why'd you say that?
That had nothing to do with anything.
Wait, I thought you meant...
I was talking about the game.
I was not talking about a character.
Oh, yes.
Right.
It would be Lisa, I understand.
Like it would be the, there's only men scenario.
Yes, you're right.
That's the only apocalypse that I think could ever happen.
It's the most realistic scenario, even though they never explain why that happened.
But that makes it so realistic.
It's the ovaries.
Or...
There was the flash, there was the big flash.
Or the balls that are protecting the flash.
It was the balls, it was the balls for sure.
You get right down to it.
How are you doing, Oblivion?
I'm doing okay.
I'm working on new animations for my Patreon.
I've leveled up my art quite a bit.
You think so?
I think so.
I can...
How so?
Pixar didn't happen.
I'll send pics.
Justify yourself.
Yeah, I'll just chuck a couple in your DMs.
Why not?
Sorry, audience.
I'm not ready to have these be public yet.
Okay, all right.
They're too saucy.
There's one for you, Ben.
Aside from that,
something's been going on.
Kai is completely recovered from his top speed right now.
That's some good news.
Looks good.
Nice.
That is good.
And...
Yeah.
This looks...
Is this Falia?
Yeah, this is Falia.
I don't know how to describe it,
but the style does look a little bit different.
Well, I learned to shade at all,
which I hadn't done before.
Or at least rendered sweat.
Yeah, the oily, the skin reflection.
Yeah, I can...
It's nice.
You know, maybe I can stand back.
I think it's the Betty Boop lips.
Oh, maybe, yeah.
I think that's what's...
She didn't have lipstick before, did she?
She did sometimes.
It was like every so often.
I think a cropped version that you can put on screen,
Ellie is our...
Also, don't mind the Anatomy being a little personal.
YouTube's mad at us.
YouTube got a little mad at us.
I know.
For that ballpoint pen sketch
of Give as Haruko.
That one time.
Oh, yeah.
You got stuff like that happen.
But, I don't know.
Okay, all right.
Life's going all right.
Are these for an animation?
No, those are just for an image set.
I am doing an animation as well.
Okay.
That is going pretty okay.
Again, maybe I'll need to make a cropped version
of what I'll send you for Ellie's already used.
I think I've seen a whip of this.
I don't know how far beyond, far along it is.
I took a couple weeks off to do some
drawing, basically.
So, it's probably not much further along
than what you saw before.
It is an animation involving my character
moving her funny boobies around.
Her fun bags, you might say.
That is funny.
Oh.
How do you feel about Halloween oblivion?
I think Halloween is a good time sometimes.
I like spooky skeletons.
Somebody has the 10-foot-tall Home Depot skeleton
down the street for me.
It's like leaning off of somebody's third-story balcony.
Oh, my God.
V Home Depot skeleton.
That sounds like there's some lore here.
Well, there's Home Depot cells
like 12-foot-tall skeleton for some reason.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
It's a well-known Halloween artifact
and someone got it.
I don't know, man.
I was saying, I'm not really in the Halloween spirit
at the moment.
I'm not really feeling it right now.
I'll be honest.
I've never done a Halloween.
I've never done a trick-or-treat.
Oh, okay.
That culture just sort of escapes you.
It wasn't really present in New Zealand too much.
Yeah.
Though we did have, the church would,
and churches all over the country would throw
what they called star parties on Halloween.
I've never heard of that.
It sounds like some witchcraft.
It sounds like some astrology.
Yeah, maybe you're correct.
You just come down to a church,
they just have candy out in the open
people can grab.
You can dress up with no scary costumes
and there's a sausage sizzle going on.
Wait, what's a sausage sizzle?
I mean, I think I can guess from the name.
You have a little barbecue and you throw some sausages
and you put them in buns with ketchup
and grilled onions.
You mean a barbecue?
Yeah, you mean a barbecue?
You call it a sausage sizzle.
That's so funny.
Ever go to a Bunnings warehouse?
There's always a person selling $1 sausages outside.
Bunnings?
I mean, I know about Costco $1.50 hot dogs.
And I know about Sheets $0.50 hot dogs.
Damn.
I think they're $0.50.
I've never been to a Sheets.
I just know that Michael from Repstugog
was a big Sheets hot dogs fan.
I think they were $0.50.
Like $2 for a dollar or something.
Anyway, that's beside the point.
Okay, sausage sizzle.
Very funny name for a very specific kind of barbecue.
Yeah.
Look, we didn't really...
You can't bring pork chops to a sausage sizzle.
Get that shit off the grill.
No, it's only sausages and nothing else.
Only sausages.
If it's not encasing...
I like the idea that somebody...
They have the covertly acquired pork chops or whatever,
and they throw them on the grill before anyone can see.
It's like, no!
No!
The pork is gonna ruin...
You don't have plates to eat it on.
You get the...
You have basically like a napkin,
and you get the bun with the sausage in it,
and you just carry the napkin around,
and then you dispose of the napkin when you're done,
or use it to wipe your face or whatever,
and there's no plates or anything.
It's very much like a portable thing
that you can just eat in public.
You don't have to sit down.
Yes, I know what a hot dog is.
I know.
But I see, the point is there's no plates.
We don't call it a barbecue because it's only sausages.
If you were gonna cook other stuff in the backyard,
you would call it a bobby.
In that instance, I guess.
Interesting.
I never heard of that.
But I mean, I get it.
I mean, I've been to a pig roast.
As a kid, as a child,
at my karate dojo,
they had a pig roast one time.
Wow.
Where they roast to the pig.
And the pig never forgave you.
I doubt it.
I doubt he would.
Yeah.
That would be.
I mean, I'm getting hungry.
I'm getting hungry thinking about that.
That's no good.
It's no good.
You know what I could do?
This month, I could explore
my vampire characters that I made.
Did you see this tweet?
Oh, I did see the two vampires.
Yes.
Oh, there they are.
Daki and Makalar.
What's going on with the mouse one?
The mouse one.
Okay.
So you know how a vampire
turns into a bat?
Yeah.
She turns into a mouse instead.
You know?
And so she wants cheese.
I feel like
prior to the
pop culture codification
of what a vampire is
by like Dracula
media,
it wasn't like, oh, vampires turn into bats.
It was like
vampires can do all kinds of crazy things,
including turn into animals.
Yeah.
But then they just had this one famous vampire
that turned into a bat and then suddenly it was like, oh yeah,
vampires turn into bats.
What I wanted when I was coming up with it
was like, I wanted a vampire character,
but I wanted them to be like
not derivative of popular vampires
because vampires exist
in almost every
culture ever
because it's
quite often
misogynistic.
The ones that I got these ones from
were like Indian
and sort of Indonesian myths
where a vampire
is a,
I forget the name
that it was, but like
they seduce men
and they're born
when a woman
has an abortion.
When a woman dies giving birth
or when a woman has an abortion,
they come back as a vampire and they
steal the men away and they kill them
and they turn into beasts
and there's like things like that that are all like
women are scary.
True though.
Where's the lie?
So I thought I'd make like true to life
vampires.
Transform into a big old demon
and she will
eat blood and kill you. She's not a nice
vampire
and she has a little sister who is a very nice vampire.
Cute.
Are there names upon on Daki Makara?
Yeah.
Although Makalar
has like Kalari
which is a cheese.
Oh, that's funny.
And Deki is like
Dekini which is like
a demon of mythology.
So it sounds like Deki Makara
but it's actually two different references.
That's clever.
Honestly, these designs are both
fucking fantastic.
Thank you. I need to draw them more.
I need to draw them having Halloween
hijinks.
Does it make sense that you're brown?
Don't vampires spend a lot of time in the dark?
What do they need a melanin for?
Yeah.
What do they need it for? Just get rid of it.
It's just not historically accurate.
You made these Indonesian vampires
brown because
I don't know. European?
What about Europe?
I don't know.
I just am upset by the melanin.
I'm angry and I don't know what to do about it.
You know, if this one could be brown
any woman could be brown.
That's a scary thought. What if my lady
was black?
That would be really bad.
True.
I was thinking the same thing.
You said it better than I could have.
Duh.
Let's do a whole podcast we pretend to be racist.
No.
We already did. It's called the procrastinator's podcast.
The procrastinator's podcast.
Measuring Ben Skull before we crush her with a train.
It's called
the procrastinator's podcast
Season's 1 through 5.
Bonus episode.
The racism episode where we do a whole character
where it just says racist is possible.
Right?
Money maker? Alright.
Just throwing it out.
Upvote in the comments
if you want to hear us be racist.
If you want to hear us be racist
and we'll pay to see it.
I'll do anything for money.
Um...
Ah jeez.
I can't blame us.
Um...
Well...
You know...
That's it. That's it. That's all I got.
Crazy.
I joined late so I don't know
if this was a topic already.
There was a...
There was some funny
conversation
about a YouTuber called Boy in a Band.
No, I know who that is.
I've not heard anything about
that current controversy.
There's not a lot to say right now.
Um...
Hold on.
You've probably seen what he looks like before
if I get a picture. Oh, it's the guy with the red hair.
The guy with the red hair.
He's British but he didn't talk like that.
I don't know. Some groomer or something.
Yeah, it's right.
I mean, he's well groomed.
Yeah.
But don't stay in school guy.
I liked this guy's videos for a long time
until he just kind of like stopped
making good videos and then kind of just fell off
for a couple years and didn't upload but...
Um...
I've seen him before
somewhere.
Yeah, he popped up on my feet
again recently.
He made a song with high dubs at one point.
He made a song of PewDiePie and Jayden Animations
and he's been around.
Yeah, I vaguely remember that.
I found Jayden porn in the wild.
Like, organically.
Like, some just came
across my
screen all on its own
and I was like, wow, okay.
I can't believe it.
Like, just now?
I mean, I'd heard about it.
I just, it had never...
I'd never stumbled across it myself
but I did the other day.
It would be funny if a controversy was
boy in a band secretly
Jayden porn artists.
That would have been...
That would have been a fucking thing.
But, uh...
What I knew about this is
I know one of his exes made a video about him
like a year or two ago basically
calling him a dick.
Neglectful, whatever, sort of stuff.
Like, not a good partner
sort of things, you know, which is...
Yeah.
He does have red hair.
That does mean that you're, like, your edgy
dangerous hair in promos.
The new...
The new allegations are that
there's sort of, like, sex culty.
Like, he supposedly has
like a harem of, like, five to six girls
at a time who are mostly young,
some...
possibly, like, 17
or something. Well, he's, like,
in his 30s.
And that he's, like, super, like, controlling, manipulative
versus woman-to-be polyamorous when they don't want to
or something. The only
issue I have right now is there isn't
any evidence at all, but, like,
maybe that will come out, so I'm just going to wait and see.
Oh, if there's no evidence.
I mean, well...
There's no smoke without fire, but
you can light your own fire.
From what I've seen, it's mostly just
from one reddit post, and it's very well written.
Like, I'm inclined to, you know,
it seems very sincere. I don't...
It doesn't, like, seem at all, like, you know,
I don't get up or anything.
But their Imgur album
is just a bunch of, like, text messages
between two anonymous people
who aren't this guy, and they're just, like,
messages, like, oh, do you remember
when he said this? Yeah. Oh, do you remember
when his penis was small? Yeah. Do you remember
when he couldn't get an erection? Yeah.
Do you remember when he was dumb, and it's, like...
That doesn't prove
much, but maybe more people
come out, so we'll see.
The main thing I remember, like,
I've learned from the whole pro-charity
thing, is that
you can have, like, some weird
shit going on, and
people will, like, expose
that. But they will
add their own stuff
out of nowhere, and make it
so much worse than it actually is.
Yeah. Yeah.
So, like, I'm not inclined to agree with
this reddit post immediately. I mean,
not immediately. Could have some truth to it.
Yeah, like, there is some truth.
One of his
girlfriends, he dated, like, 10 years
ago, or over 10 years ago at this
point, maybe, was 17
while he was, like,
20... I don't know if he was, like, 23
or 25. It was in that range.
Which is... Is that in the UK? It's a bit
creepy, but it is the UK. It's not
illegal. Yeah. It's not illegal.
It's a bit creepy, especially, like...
But also, that was, like, a while back
there was less... I feel like there was
less awareness about...
Or maybe less consciousness about how creepy
that kind of thing was back then.
But, like, I don't know, like,
sure, like, he did that. That's a little...
That's kind of weird. That's kind of sussy.
But, like, that's not a smoking gun to all
the new allegations, right?
I mean, it may be sussy.
I mean, the new allegations are
that he's a controlling
polyamorous
boyfriend? That he has...
That he, like, prays on, like, young
women and uses his fame and money to, like,
use his fame into being with him, and then he treats
him like crap and kicks him out if they ever
cross him. That's what they're saying now.
Which, oof, is true.
I mean, of course he does.
Obviously he does.
Everyone famous does that.
I wouldn't be... I wouldn't be...
I wouldn't be shocked.
That's just what I expect from anyone who's
famous on YouTube or probably anywhere.
Yeah. Like, I think...
I mean, what's... I don't get it. I don't get...
I don't even get why it's a story.
Yeah. To be honest.
It's probably true.
But I don't fucking grab my pitchfork yet.
I don't care enough.
And some more concrete stuff comes out.
I mean...
I don't know. I mean,
the story would be
oh, he's doing stuff with minors.
Right?
He's doing illegal stuff
with people who are too young
to consent legally or
ethically. Right?
That's the...
That's the smoking gun.
Anything short of that
is like...
Oh, he's a bad boyfriend?
Oh, he's using his fame to manipulate women?
Well, I mean...
Yeah.
I mean, okay.
I guess I didn't know this guy.
So, yeah, I didn't know this guy at all.
So, it doesn't matter to me whether he's a dickhead or not.
I assume everyone who's famous
is a dickhead.
Assumption. Very good assumption, to be honest.
Yeah.
I mean, this guy stumbled across my feet
and that was my baseline assumption.
Alright, who's this dickhead?
Oh, he's a cult leader?
Oh, okay.
Does he make them
have hair like his?
That'd be...
That'd be kind of funny, actually.
He's got nice hair.
He's got a nice head of hair on him.
You know, you gotta respect
a nice head of hair.
You know what? I take it all back. I love this guy.
Absolved.
Nice hair.
Yeah.
How many sex crimes
is having nice hair worth?
How many can you get away with because of that?
Two?
Like one per follicle.
As many as there are stars in the sky.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd never...
What does this guy do? Is he a musician?
He was like...
He would like do like
funny like...
He's like, hey, I'm gonna make a
rap song about this topic
and I'm gonna do it really fast.
He would collab with people like Andrew Huang
or Rob Scallon
or people who did rap and metal stuff.
Usually just kind of like
here's a funny idea for a song
that has this restriction
and I'll just make it.
It's also known as having
not enough fame
as a musician to get by
so I go to YouTube.
Yeah, and he started like doing videos
like...
Like, hey, here's the man...
Oh my god, he had one video called
the man who would save in the world
and you've never heard of him.
And did you know there's this guy who's like
a real life Iron Man who
created PayPal and builds rockets?
Oh yeah, his name's Elon Musk.
No! No! No!
I mean,
how long ago was that?
It was 2015, to be fair,
like...
How many people knew about it back then
or knew about how full of shit he was?
So...
I couldn't have told you
that Elon was cringe
back in 2015 so I can't...
It's funny but I can't really judge.
I mean, I didn't know Elon was cringe until
around like 2018, to be fair.
Even then, I was late to the party.
Yeah, it's
just because it's only in recent years
that like...
His
bullshit, all his like hyper-loop
all his hyper-loop bullshit
and so on and so forth.
Alright, I mean, yeah, okay.
Pretty cringe video, bro, but like...
Was that around the time?
Okay, was that before or after
he went on The Simpsons and Lisa said
he's the most important inventor of our time?
I have no idea.
So this was like January 2015,
so...
Coming up on...
You know what? Okay, this actually really blows.
Even if it is before.
People knew as well.
This sucks.
Well, I watched this video in 2015
and I'm like, I've never heard of this guy
but wow, he is cool because I just, you know,
I just assume that a YouTuber
I like wouldn't like put a bunch of
information in their video.
Right.
Never trust anyone,
especially yourself.
Uh...
Oh my god, I don't trust myself.
All the comments are like...
Yeah, this didn't age well.
Yeah.
Uh...
It really, like...
Even if it's like...
Oh, this guy's really cool.
Saying the guy who is saving the world is a bit like...
It sounds like you're already buying
into the Kool-Aid, the hype.
Like...
It doesn't sound like...
If somebody was inventing something amazing
or was doing something really good,
you would be able to point to
more specific things
than...
He's saving the world. It seems a little...
A little over-bloated.
Damn, this guy's got 3 million subs.
This is a big channel.
Yeah.
It's sort of like maybe a tell-tale sign
that there isn't actually much there.
If like...
You're blowing his ego so big.
Oh wait, I just remembered.
There is one other cringe thing that he did.
He made like...
You probably see this a lot on YouTube these days
where people you're subscribed to
will put up community posts
with polls that you can vote on.
Yeah.
I don't really look at them, but yeah.
There's a lot on this.
So like, he put up a poll
that was like...
Asking his fans,
hey guys, so I got to describe these antidepressants
and, you know, I took like one
pill and it didn't work.
Should I chug the entire bottle?
You know, I feel like
that would be good for me, you guys.
You know, maybe it would help me, haha.
And then the results were,
yeah man, chug the whole bottle, do it.
No, David.
That is not a good idea, follow the instructions.
And it was like...
He's asking his fans
if he should fucking overdose.
Yeah.
Did he do it?
No, he didn't do it.
But like, he kind of like
romanticizes like depression
and suicidality.
It's like his quirky personality.
He does look like the type.
Yeah, it is very cringy.
I see.
This...
Oh fuck, I just...
I remembered because it's in the
recommendations of this video.
Either you two watch Action Button,
either you two keep up with that.
There's a new Action Button this week.
No, what's Action Button?
It's the Tim Rogers
YouTube review, yeah.
He did a...
It's a six hour long video about
Yasumi.
Which is a game that I had seen,
but I couldn't have told you the name of.
That's the one where you play as a kid
on summer vacation and you catch bugs.
Ah, Boku no Piku.
No, no, no.
No, Boku no Piku.
It's about being a kid on summer break
and you catch bugs and you live
with your aunt and uncle.
And that's the game.
Whatever, it's a pretty good video.
Although, a lot of the video
is going on a little road trip
and showing footage of his
like, hey, this is my house
that I grew up in.
This is my town that I grew up in.
Every time people talk about Tim
Rogers, they mention
that he goes on about himself a lot.
Does that add to the video
or is it just interesting because
you want to know about Tim?
I'll be honest.
It's butting up against the line of
aren't we talking a little bit too much
about yourself?
He's always riding that line.
He's a good presenter.
He's a good orator.
He's hearing him speak is entertaining.
Sometimes I am
find myself thinking, do we need to know
do we need to see all of this
vacation footage? Do we need to know
like all these anecdotes
about growing up in
Indiana?
This guy looks really funny.
Tim Rogers?
He's
debuted on
YouTube like last year.
Is this him?
What the fuck?
He was there.
Is that the Revolutionary War?
He grew up and trained the Revolutionary War.
He's been around a long time.
I mean, he's like
40, so yeah.
That makes sense. That adds up.
Yeah.
The math checks out.
New video
was pretty good.
He sort of had the breakout hit
with the review of
what was that dating sim?
The PCB dating sim.
Not unfortunately.
No.
The seven hour video
about
Tokimeki Memorial
and this one feels a lot like that
because it's another like
Tim Opines on what a game
means for like Japanese
a moment in Japanese
cultural history or
whatever and it's very much like
the game is contemplative
and not your typical
gaming fare so
a lot of
introspection.
A lot of like, hey look at this
video I took on vacation though.
Maybe a little too much this time.
I think he crossed the line a little bit.
But it's okay.
I forgive him.
And now you know.
I don't forgive him.
Okay.
I'm good.
I mean, he doesn't deserve forgiveness.
Okay, well.
There'll be just a sec. I need to pee.
Okay.
Well, that's my week in
YouTube news.
The new action button is
always an event.
The last action button was
Cyberpunk 2077
and that was like
late last year.
So it's been like the better part of a year
for this video to come out.
Feels like only
yesterday.
It cannot believe it's been that long.
But oh well. What are you going to do?
What am I going to do?
What are you going to do?
I'm going to scream and cry, okay?
Go for it. Yeah.
All right.
Shit.
Well.
I was out of stuff to say.
I was going to, you know.
I don't know.
I was going to relate like a
story of some shit that
happened kind of in my real life.
But it's a bit like
dour and a bit like
upsetting, honestly.
I have a little bit, it's like
should I even talk about it in public?
It's kind of a thing.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I guess I can sort of relate.
Hey, hey, Gabe.
Should I relate my
kind of like upsetting and unsettling
real life anecdote?
Oh hell yeah.
All right.
It's kind of blows. It sucks.
It ruined my week.
It blows and sucks. The full package.
Yeah. You wouldn't think you could do both of those.
Well, I don't know.
There's, you know, I just moved into this new house
when there's a bunch of other people
that live here.
And I sort of don't see them too much
of them. So like,
I've had a couple moments where it's like, oh, it's this person
who lives here that I haven't met yet.
Well, let me introduce myself to them.
Well, I don't know.
I had a...
There's a girl that lives here.
And I kind of had the first like, oh hello,
it's nice to meet you.
With her.
And I don't know.
I won't go into too much detail about it, but there was a...
I don't know.
She made a kind of upsetting
statement.
She sort of claimed that like
another guy that lives there is like
violent.
And she was like, oh,
that's bad.
Lives with her?
Yeah, that's what she said.
She threw it out really casually.
Like, oh yeah,
this other guy, what the phrase she used
was he has a quote unquote tendency toward
violence.
And I said, that sounds bad.
And she was like, yeah, but it's only with me.
That's only really with me though.
What?
Oh.
It doesn't sound like a joke.
It doesn't sound like a jokie phrase.
It wasn't a...
No, it wasn't a jokie phrase.
Good thing she can't...
Good thing they can't see your giant hit spinner
or else you'd be in danger too.
I don't know.
I'll be honest.
I didn't know if I should believe her
or if she was like...
Or if she was just making it up.
I'll be honest.
Part of me was like, am I being tricked?
Is this some sort of weird
like
power play?
Some kind of weird social engineering
like trick that
is being played upon me?
Would it be more likely that she just doesn't
have anyone to confide in
about that?
I mean, I don't know.
She was like, you can't tell him if he is violent.
He's just gonna be violent.
I don't know. There's like five people that live here.
Me
and one other guy are new.
I'll be honest. I related this story
the other day
at Kazi's birthday
and everyone was horrified with me.
Everyone was disgusted with me
because I did not believe women.
Because I was...
Yeah.
So I probably shouldn't have even brought it up.
I don't know.
It was just, I don't know.
Maybe I was too quick to judge.
Just the way that she so
casually said it
and then just immediately moved on from it
and did not give any additional details
just made me like
I don't know.
It just seemed really strange.
What would the trick be
if she were tricking you?
Like it was a...
I guess the idea would be that it was an attempt
to turn me against this guy
for whatever.
For some reason.
And I don't know what the reason would be.
I feel like it's easier to believe
that some guys are just
dickish and violent in general
and
super like next level mind games.
Because I've met a lot of
dudes who are just
violent dickheads.
That's pretty common.
Yeah.
But I mean
she didn't elaborate
or say what happened
or if anything happened.
I just don't know.
I feel like
she was a random
basically a stranger.
Hmm.
Okay.
Yeah, but
I don't know what to do with this information.
It's obvious Ben.
You have to be a hero.
You have to get your claymore and you have to go slay the dragon.
And go kill him.
Don't even ask one question.
Don't even learn who he is.
Just go on a rampage.
Yeah, just right in Hath, you know.
Hmm.
Oh well, I guess I'll go do that.
Well, all right, I'll see you next episode.
I'm going to go catch a case.
I'm going to go commit violence.
But righteous violence.
Yeah, I don't know.
This is completely ruined my week.
This is like so upsetting.
Yeah, sounds pretty weird
to happen.
Yeah, I was
I was very dismayed
with the reaction that I got
from
Kazi and everyone
when I talked about it.
I felt like a real dick.
But I
really don't know what to do.
So that's me right now.
That's where I'm at.
It's bugging me.
Do you feel like
it would be better or worse
if you tried to follow up on it?
If you tried to ask her
what she meant
or even talk to the guy?
I don't know.
I mean, if it's true,
if it's true
and I tell the guy
that she said that,
that seems like it would be bad
and it would make him angry.
Not to tell the guy
the truth.
Just to talk to him to see what he's like.
I mean, I have talked to him
a little bit a couple of times
and he seems fine.
He could be a monster in secret.
I don't know.
I don't know this guy well.
I've only met him
a few times
and I've just moved into
a house with him.
I can't really say
anything about him personally.
I haven't noticed anything myself.
I mean, here's the thing.
When I was talking to her,
the first thing she said to me
was she wanted to talk about
utility bills
and she asked me
if I would take over responsibility
of putting
the bills in my name
and I didn't want to do that.
And then when I said
I said I would ask this other guy
about it and she said
he has a tendency
towards violence
and so
I was like
hmm
what is
Is this a persuasion?
I don't know
this is why I was like
didn't know what she was doing.
I mean
I thought that my roommate Sean
had a persuasion toward violence
but that was in the form of when he talks
about hand gestures and I flinched
and that's it.
So
yeah
I mean maybe
it's
like did she like come out and say
I've been abused or just of this guy
like
the only thing she said is he has a
quote unquote tendency toward violence
which could mean
a lot of things.
There's a wide range of interpretations
right.
I wouldn't worry too much for now
just keep it on
just in case.
I guess what else can I do
yeah
I
I don't know I've had people tell
me stuff
in the past
like that very like
sort of emotionally charged
things like that and it has been
manipulation
it makes me wary
the lack of details
I don't know it just
it gave me a weird feeling
like it was a trick
but
maybe my instincts are wrong and bad
possibly
I couldn't possibly say having not
been there
true
well sorry to be a downer
I know this sucks I feel terrible
about it.
If it's given you a grief
do you think
you need to do something to stop
that or
I just don't know what I could do
or if anything would be appropriate
to do
yeah it's tricky
my first thought is like Oscar
to elaborate
but then I wouldn't expect her to
to elaborate you might get more
questions
I mean if I had been
in that original conversation
they were like oh they have a tendency to
be like whoa
like how come
should I be worried?
I'd definitely ask fellow questions immediately
but I think the moment's passed
yeah maybe I should have jumped on it
and like please explain
but I kind of she kind of moved on
from it and so I kind of just was like
okay
yeah maybe I should have asked to follow them
I mean you probably sort of like you know the other day when you said this
like what did you mean exactly
should I be scared you know
you know maybe
she's not around very often
like this was the first time
I've seen her I've only seen her twice
in the whole month that I've lived here
like she's mostly out of the house
most of the time
so I don't know when I'll get
another chance to do that but like eventually
I surely will
so yeah maybe that should be the plan
okay that's the plan
alright game plan
got it
alright
ah yes
sorry about that sorry about that it's bummer
lame
it's a real life moment
okay yeah unfortunately
well I don't have anything else to talk about
that's all that's all I got
I swear there's something
I have on my brain
but my brain is like dead
dude
I don't remember anything
oh you know what I could talk about this
I'm not gonna do it just because like
daily arts challenges in October
is
something that literally everybody does now
and it's so many
that I feel like I would be
too normie to do it myself
but I did have a cool idea
which I kind of started
one year and I didn't
do anything is
October
we draw dicks every day
that's a good one
I think I will draw like maybe
where is she going with this
I'm going right to the groin
that's where I'm going
drawing dicks
for one
for anatomy
practice and also ha ha penis
it's true
and also it's better fit
than like inktober
coctober sounds like october
it's just got to cut the front of it
that's what we should have all been doing from the start
I'm sorry
we moved on already but I just remembered something
I just remembered something about
that's the situation
I was asking another guy
because I said there's two guys that live here
me and another guy are both new
and I asked the other guy
not about what she said about this other guy
but I asked him about
the utility bill
I said something about like oh yeah she said
something about like someone else
was like
late on payment or something she said
because she said that the guy that she said
has a tendency toward violence
he had like not paid his bill
or something and this was why she wanted
me to take over responsibility
for like
taking the bills in my name
because this guy
had not paid his bills and I mentioned
this to this other guy
and I just said yeah she said that that other guy
didn't pay his bills and this guy's
immediate reaction to that was he shook his head
and he said like don't believe her
like I don't believe her
and I was like okay
I also think she's a tricky
I don't know why
I didn't follow up on it with him
I don't know
the whole thing gives me a really bad
feeling
yeah
you know understandable
what if this is a woman moment we don't want that
we wouldn't
we truly would not want that
I don't know
back to
October
sorry never mind
I want to do Cocktober I'd love to draw a dick
every day I have so many characters
with dicks so many other cool characters
I can give dicks
yeah it's like the perfect crime
except it's not a crime
you're allowed
everyone's allowed to draw a dick
it's a crime except you're allowed to do it
what if it was legal
what if crime was legal
that's like that's Cocktober
yeah drawing one thing every day
just doesn't work out
it seems so
as simple because how long does the drawing take
like five minutes
but you're always gonna I mean I
personally I'm always gonna want
it to be decent like presentable
of an image
so I don't want to skimp it on it
I don't want to have it be
a shit drawing but sometimes
I just don't have the time
I don't get around to it until 11 o'clock
and I'm like well
I'm sleepy
I gotta do something and then I do something that sucks
and I'm like fuck
shit
and it just makes me feel bad for the next day
or I'm like I gotta make up for yesterday
by making a better drawing and it just doesn't work
it's hard to do
like the it's so easy to draw
but so hard to draw for a month straight
yeah
I've never
I've never done ink tober
when I've sort of done it
I've only done maybe like four or five
drawings and then
no more
I will draw like
yeah I'm not gonna
do the whole month
but I will draw a few
don't know how many maybe even just two of them
maybe even just one
but that's gonna be my cock tober
you can find it on
at biggirlsquish on twitter
just one drawing
yeah
like unironically
it doesn't need to be a whole big thing
I don't want it to be for me
it could even just be like one big canvas
that throughout the month
doesn't have to be every day you just draw
cocks some days you draw a few cocks some days you draw none
and then you post the whole canvas
this whole canvas all October
that could even be another approach
and then you draw like a character
looking at them all being like
which one do I take
which one do I choose
how many do I have enough holes
oh shit gotta make some new ones
oh god what does that mean
I don't know
just cut yourself
hopefully not
shoot yourself
just grow extra titties
you know
oh that's what it means
oh
yeah
I've seen the porn
I know how this works
I haven't
well it seems Ben
when a mother and father love each other very much
they sometimes draw pornography
um
you mean
you mean that when two parents
of any gender
in this
under these woke skies that we live under
woke skies
anyone can be a mother or father
these are just terms
terms
it's all just words
at the end of the day
like you can have like a gay couple
where one is considered the mother and the other the father
I think that's
that's allowed
linguistically technically
yeah
under international law
and if you're a non binary you can say parent
you've got the whole gang
just wanted to be inclusive
good
when parents love each other very very much
they draw porn on you
understood
I do like mother and father though
because mommy and daddy are funny words
yeah
is there like a baby version of parent
I don't think so
baby version
what would a baby call their like non binary parent
they can't say mama
they can't say dad dad what do they do
cancel the baby
we've got to find a way for the future generations
to not get cancelled immediately
I know
these bubbies are
going to have a bad time
I think maybe
we should just make mommy the gender neutral term
that everyone uses
I know why you want that
I want mommy I need milk I need to be held
yeah
don't they just kind of don't babies just kind of
say like mama
or do they say mama because like they
someone teaches them to
they get taught in other languages they say other things
they do say other things
I think it's just
it's simplified in that way because babies
can make vowels
and then interrupt those vowels
and it sometimes sounds like mama
dad dad go ba ba ba ba
yeah I feel like I feel like the M sound
is probably one of the easiest noises for a
stupid fucking baby
to make to go
I mean who doesn't have to call
them anything
he doesn't have to say anything he can just
scream
well yes that's what they do
but like what would you teach your baby to call
you because they can't say your full name
that's too difficult
can you say
zuzu
can you say pee pee
pee pee would be good
pee pee is funny
I don't know
I don't know I'm not sure about that one
I don't know about that one
someone tells me that one's in use already
in use
like a restroom
yeah it's occupied
it's like wall street
I understand
wall street
it's occupied
oh right
of course
my brain just makes autistic relations
from one word to another it's bad
that's called pumice it's good
I get shit I need
one second while I grab a sparkling water
I imagine Ben saying
has like a bucket of sparkling water
and when he says grab he means
dunk his hand in and grab some molecules
I just need to grab those molecules
you know
I'm gonna grab your molecules Gib
yep that is
that is a frat I'd better believe it
oh no
I don't even know which molecules
exactly there's so many
I'm gonna be looking over my shoulder
saying which molecules are gonna be stolen
which ones are gonna be grabbed
you got a lot of that
that's 70% of my body
it's everywhere
yeah 70% is everywhere
that's the threshold
of everywhere
what
where was the 30%
no where
how can you calculate
30% of
the existence of the universe is
nowhere
no one knows
I don't know
what are you talking about
calculate the probability
of the quantum
superposition of the
wave form of reality
and the
information superhighway
yes
yes yes yes
got it
understood
you think we should go to voicemails
um
or yeah
I have one small thing it's another art thing
um
but it'll be pretty brief
go on
yeah sorry
I yesterday did something
that I've been meaning to do
for a long fucking time
which was update my character model
sheet
for my character failure
basically like just redrawing it
because
me and forays are both better at art now
and um
I think it looks a lot
fucking better
I'll just drop a little
comparison and chat
um it's
insane
the fucking difference at least to me
especially in the face
I mean you made like
really rapid art progress
um
I think it was last year or
whenever it was
you started drawing
specifically illustration progress
the original reference sheet was drawn by forays
before I even like
had started learning art
um
so I can like
show off like some of the comparison here
there it is
mainly the face just looks
a heck of a lot better now I think
well they look different
I mean uh
it looks more
feminine
which one's the new one
the new one is the one on the right
yeah
so the hair no longer wraps around the horns
oh it does I'm gonna have a
my reference sheet will just show that
it only wraps around sometimes like if it's messy
and I have a better way
of drawing that wrap around now
um
see the original was just by forays and since I've learned to draw
I've been able to
now do stuff
so that's a thing
she looks
she looks sad she looks like she's
less
her mouth curls up a bit
at a glance
she's like depressed
the small mouth just looks more
feminine
basically the eyes look a little more
focused I guess
the horns are definitely a better shape
I have a 3D model of them now that I use for reference
what I made
was that too
I think
my brain's fucking stupid right now
um
what was I saying
I forgot
I draw her mouth smaller when it's closed
but it still opens really big and scary
it's like a giant penis
so that's fine
for instance
as one does
yeah
I don't think I've ever done like a model
sheet
for referencing my own characters
I'm so lazy with that
like I draw them
and then every time I need to be like oh what does that character look like again
I just look at the previous images
they're always changing a little bit
like punk
I mean
let me find the first image of punk
she looks very different
from the way I draw now
yeah I would compose the full model sheet too
that was just for zoom in for the main differences
I've never really done
like yeah character sheets
I guess I did a phantom horn
character sheet for t-bat back in the day
but that wasn't like for my own reference
that was like to show people
like this is what the character looks like
it was for other people's reference not for mine
because the character looks like
whatever they look like in my head
to me and if it changes then like
so be it
when was the most recent time I drew punk
was it for the game
I suppose
I feel like I doodled her
I can't find anything
the only thing I have for this year
like really is the febubary stuff
which is funny
oh yeah
I've did febubary
and then occasionally I do a little doodle
and I say that
that's it
I haven't done a lot of art aside from the comics
I did the live stream image
it's not really the same
it's not really a punk image exactly
but I can't say I've gotten
better at art but I have
I mean this one looks a lot better
than the first one you posted
yeah
yeah I haven't done a lot
I haven't done that much art
well I guess I finished
I finished slime in punishment
that was pretty much like the only art I've really done this year
what were we talking about
we were just talking about art I guess
just talking about art
I hate that stuff
just kidding
I like this image
this is a great image
oh my god hi
hmm
it's like
if I played suburb I would throw my brisket plush
into the kernel sprite
and then all the imps would be brisket
and I would blush when I meet them
but they want to kill me
I saw this
scrimblow gib
and the big boobie mommy milkers
it's very good
very cute
very funny
disgusting imp
it has the eyelashes
it has the horns and the hair
it's grey
oh my god
yeah I hope
the griffs they're made of on your planet
is some kind of grey stuff
yeah
I forget the kinds of griffs they have
they're like gushers
well John has
oil and like cobalt
I think
oh yes that's right
the types of imp
yeah so I would hope that
they're named after stuff
so I would hope that yours would be something grey
like shale or
something like that
gravel
yeah dust is good
dust is good
dust imps yeah that would work
that would work just fine
and my planet is like
oh it's got dust all over it
so I gotta do the windy thing and blow the dust away
it makes more sense than John
actually with the oil
yeah why would oil
why would wind, why would breath blow oil away
doesn't
or no it doesn't know it's to clear the oil
out so that the pipes can
so the wind, the breath can blow through the pipes
yes that's it
yes yes that's it
I forget what my home stuck
like my chosen
thingy of thingy
my class bit
me
I remember it being like the page of
space or the page of void
or something
I like hope the best but
I don't know if I would be
I don't know if I would be it just because I like it
probably not actually
I'd probably be something that I don't like
like
blood
the bard of blood
blood sucks blood doesn't even do anything
at least car cat doesn't do anything
it's friendship though
it's bonds
is it though or is that just
fanning
I mean I think it's
implied heavily that car cat
is a good people person and he's good with
he likes the troll romance
and he's like easy to talk to
even though he's a little insane
he's got like relationship issues
which is like his blood
if it's like a relationship thing
there's clues here and there
like imply what blood is about
compared to all of the other aspects
that are not about that
okay I mean if yeah
I mean then he has that
blood packed with Jack Noir
oh right yeah and he cuts the
hand and it looks like the symbol
yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's hard to ignore
you're right
well I guess all of my art
skill my focus
has been on the pumpkin
family game but also
um this Clarissa comic
some of the little things I drawn
even though they're not even properly made yet
they're like oh that would be such a good
panel it's gonna be so fucking sick
when people read it I sure hope I don't
fuck it up in the process
of making it finished
I hope so too
I love cartooning
cartooning is good
should I dare I suggest
voicemails again
I guess
okay so I will
probably step out
for voicemails
oh yeah
because look
I'm sorry I bombarded you too much last
week with all those uh all those
sillies
all those silly ones
no I appreciate you taking over
the voicemail collection duties
while uh
ours was out of commission
no not the collection I mean
through speak pipe all those fucking
YouTube poops
oh right right
I mean those are great there was just too many
yeah there was too many like there's not as many
this week and I will say
um you don't want to
you don't want to skip
you don't want to skip these ones
they're building to something
trust me it'll be uh
good maybe I don't know
all right I
I promise I'm not wasting your time
this week with those
um also I'm not doing those anymore
okay
we like what was what was the one that
that cracked me up there was um
piano guy
the piano guy one was good
that one I really liked
put the thing in there
those piano notes have a whole
fucking story of their own but I'll tell it
another time uh you guys
yeah I'd love to hear it yeah all right you guys
have fun oh thank you thank you
for popping in it was nice to have you again
I'm glad to be here
uh you have fun if your voice smells
I will stop my recording after I go
bye all right thank you
bye see ya
see ya
uh and there he goes
oblivion fell
and there what is that
and there he goes
what is that from
in the end he'll yeah sonichu
and there he goes with a smile in his
step in the end he'll say
one girlfriend please
something like that what
that's from like
yeah the the end of sonichu one
when when like
after the story is done
chris and sonichu are just walking along
and chris is like yep
that was the first comic I drew
and sonichu's like wow father
and you're so talented
and you still don't have a girlfriend
and chris says like yeah
that's how it goes I guess
well off to the mall to try again
yeah and son and as he drives away
sonichu tearfully is like
ah there he goes
with a with a spring in his
step in the end he'll say
one girlfriend please
I'm
proud to have a brave father
I don't know what he said
it's just magical it's magical
it is pretty it is pretty
when it when it hits
when it hits it it hits
it's it's
it'll never it'll never lose
did you see that um that painting
of chris as the girl
doing the like patting yourself
on the head and going bleh
oh I did
you drew that I think I've seen that
artist around yeah I've seen that artist
around people kept I kept
seeing people retweeting it being like
um can we not please
um can we not uh
and like they were like
retweeting it as they were saying it
like oh this is so bad no we shouldn't do this
but like they're like
mean they're like actively
yeah I know Pete the whole the whole point
of that particular meme is that it's
juxtaposed with things that are not the cutesy
enemy girl going ooh
well it's like like like the U.S.
government going ooh ooh I blew up
something yeah yeah it's like
no the kind of the point
here is that she did like what she did
was really bad and like it's like yeah
oopsie
people don't get it
um people are memed um
um
alright uh let's um
let's look at
let's speak into that pipe
rather listen
let us let us put our ear to the
speak pipe um
the first
one oh I guess I don't have to post them
because uh
you have speak pipe open that's good
I think the first one is called
look out Benny boy
uh three two one
go
you're hyperventilating
he's coming for you
it sounds like someone's coming for me
oh god is he jacking it
is he jacking it he's coming
for me oh no
oh no
uh the next one is
called question
three two one go
not a question where's the question mark
yeah there's no question mark
sorry next one is called
MLP confessions
three two one go
I have a confession make
I could never get into my
little piano guy
I remember back in
2012 2013
when the fandom was starting
and blossoming and I heard about it
and I just could not see
what other people saw in it
like maybe it's because I was
an entire audience or maybe I just
wasn't autistic enough to enjoy it
which is weird because
I feel like I should have
been no fancy
piano guys
like it's weird
PCP has given me a lot of insight on the
fucking debacle that was the piano guy
fandom
and like I feel like I missed
out on something
but at the same time I feel like I missed out
on nothing so I'm wondering
now that piano guy is effectively over
what's the final autopsy report
I don't remember that question
like the original
what's about my little pony
I don't remember any of these originals
the piano guy fandom
will live on in our pianos
started with a bang
and it ended and it went out in a blaze of glory
short life cycle short but sweet
I like to go back
sometimes and listen to piano guy
it's nostalgic nostalgic for the good old days
you know the PCP started
as just a bunch of friends who just came together
over their shared love of the piano guy
those days are well behind
and we hate piano guy now
next one is called friends
three two one go
I got pretty big list of friends
and I'll like ask one of them to die
and they'll be like nah I got a girlfriend
sorry
and then I have another friend who's got like work
and that's like you know more reasonable
but he's like oh I have to work all the time
can't die and like you know other stuff
like that like just friends that are busy
like all the fucking time
and I'm so busy with any of that
and I just want to hang out with people
and I rarely ever die
so I gotta make new friends
to hang out with but then I try to ask people
and they're like no I'm piano guy
everyone's fucking piano guy
how do I
fix
the world
help piano guy
I guess I'm just going somewhere
I'm a sucker for
die
the next one is a vocaru
it's called the oatmeal hour
three two one go
one two
oatmeal
Kirby is a pink guy
one two
oatmeal
because Kirby's very cute
one
one two
oatmeal
Kirby is a pink guy
one two
one
two
one two
win
oh
We're so happy there's something you can't, because he's such a pink guy, curvy in hails
The payoff I think
Sick that was great nice nice little nice little number. That was a nice little number
Worth it worth every penny
Next one is called enough three two one go
Okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna stop with the the fucking shitty
I'm just gonna kick of
Just messing around with audio distortions and fucking shit up on audacity recently. Hope it wasn't
Too much of a derailment
And I hope you enjoyed the last one that probably played shortly before this one
We're car in it
Made all that music in like a day
How's good it was a good. Yeah, it sounded really good. Oh
Oh
Hope he didn't I hope he didn't feel too dejected
That I got that I got
Frustrated with his voicemails for a minute there
Love you blue in that. Oh, where is that guy? Where is that guy anyway? You know, whatever happened to that guy? I don't know
Yeah, I only know oblivion full not oblivion
Oh, yeah, they're different. Well, I don't know. Well, that guy sucks
Next one is called those searching for amusement to be like three two one go
Mary with a
What I mean, Mary with a Mary with a
Mary with a nice New Zealand accent Mary with a Mary with a
Is it they mean the the artist? Oh, it's not an artist. Okay, whatever the whatever guy
The producer I didn't think that was a is a better name for it. Maybe something like that
I guess so
Sure next one is called wandering air explorer of the West three two one go I
Was exploring the rural roads west of Boston when I happened to come across one Nate nutting road a
little further down
There's another road gay road
So what I'm seeing is
We know the approximate location for the headquarters of the League of Nate fuckers
Nate nothing and gay road
Well, there you are
Okay, next one is called Ben
three two one go
You know this
Airlines of yours that are no longer there
Why don't you scroll them back like you could just build them into existence?
I understand because I was tricks is for that that your hair line is
Basically promised, I mean he or she did curse you
It's soon as you
Decided to shit on him right for yourself, but even so
you know
This person is saying that Trixie cursed my hair line
Yeah, well the first thing he says is you could just will it back into existence. That's what he said. That's true
I guess I don't know why I didn't think of it like that
You just got to do a Dragon Ball Z. You just got to go
I don't know. I don't know. Thanks for the advice guy
Next one is called. Hey, you suck on pronouns by the way. What the what the fuck is that?
Yeah, what the fuck was she what the fuck was he or she and then and then he after that like
You're you're you're you're in shambles. You're in shambles my guy next one is called a Gibbs layer
three two one go
I mean, oh, I'm not slain guess. It wasn't as funny as saying die. Yeah
Yeah
You could have just all it took was one word
next one is called
Don't dope smite and no, thank you
Three two one go
I
See the CEO of a large central exchange of cryptocurrencies
Will go into birth all the supply like the Joker
Which means supply and demand the less is more you buy. No, it becomes a one dollar and only
Yeah.
At least.
Did you understand that?
Something about buying into a cryptocurrency
because they're gonna burn the cryptocurrency
or someone's gonna burn it.
I don't know, that doesn't make sense though.
You can't buy it and then have the thing devalue,
but you have like, it's not like gold.
You having a lot of it, whatever, it's stupid.
Yeah, I don't know.
Don't do it.
Just don't do it.
Next one is called,
Hey Ben, new fan here.
How is being bald and what does that mean?
Nothing.
It's just a joke.
It was just a joke.
Ha ha ha.
You fell for it.
Next one is called,
Happy Birthday Ben.
Thanks.
Next one is called,
They Are Back.
Oh.
Three, two, one, go.
I love how you guys always engage
with the question,
doesn't matter how stupid it is,
like, what do you two think about pineapples?
Pineapple.
Interesting.
What about segregation?
I see, very interesting.
Wait, what do you say about segregation?
I think he just said it was interesting, very interesting.
Or he asked us what we think about it.
Oh, I think it is bad.
I think that pineapples and segregation are equally bad.
I wouldn't eat segregation on pizza.
Hmm, I would,
I would segregate my pizza though.
I would keep pepperoni on one side.
You segregate it whenever you cut it into eight.
Exactly.
Keep the pepperoni on one half
and no pepperoni on the other half for the vegetarians.
No, no, I'm a calzone girl.
I got a no segregation on the pizza.
One pizza, curl it up, eat it like a ice cream,
like a big old ice cream cone.
Segregation and pineapples, they're both,
they're not back, they never left, baby.
They're here to stay.
Did I tell you, I had a pineapple on a pizza
a little while ago and I thought it was pretty good.
When we had it at Radcon three, I didn't like it.
But I had like a, from a better pizzeria,
not that long ago and it was like cooked better
and it was good, I liked it.
And it was with pepperoni.
It wasn't ham and pineapple, it was pepperoni and pineapple.
And it was well cooked so the pineapple
kind of like melted in.
Ah!
Does it still taste sweet?
Cause that's the reason I wouldn't like it.
The reason I didn't like it was because,
like when it was still in like chunks,
it's kind of like has like the fruity,
pulpy texture of it and the sweetness is in that.
And it's just kind of weird to chew on.
The one that I had, it was like cooked well enough
that it sort of melted.
It almost kind of melted on top of the pizza
and it worked much better.
Yeah, see, for me, it's just anything sweet.
And like a main course just feels wrong.
Like a main meal, it has to be savory or spicy or, you know,
it can't be sweet.
Sweet is for dessert only.
It doesn't make sense to me that you would have sweet things.
Like if there's a curry, but it has like dates in it
or raisins or bits of stuff.
And it's like, it's sweetness, that's not right.
That's my take.
It needs to be handled with delicacy.
Decent with decency.
And in modern societies, it doesn't have.
Since we just don't have, we've lost the nuances.
We've lost the nuances of adding sweet to savory dishes.
The next one is called YouTube 321 Go.
There's nothing.
Terrible.
The next one is called Evangelion Bad 321 Go.
I don't understand why Gendo was so abusive to Shinji.
If my wife died under circumstances that could have been my fault
and the years I spent with her were the only time
in my life that I felt truly happy,
I would have simply moved on and found new happiness
by raising my son.
Gendo's behavior simply makes no sense.
Zero.
Can't relate to it.
Bad show.
Why not just be a good dad?
Then Shinji would smile.
Hey, Misato, why just not be a pedophile?
Why not simply skip that part?
Is she a pedophile?
Does she come onto Shinji?
I can't even remember.
Yeah, they make out.
Misato?
Well, don't they kiss before his final Eva mission
or something?
I mean, it will depend on if it was on the cheek or not.
Maybe she says that they'll fuck afterwards or something.
She implies it.
I mean, she is very openly adult around Shinji
and Shinji's just whatever.
Yeah.
It's mostly her being drunk, though.
I don't know if she did a pedophile, but she may have.
I mean, I don't know if she did a pedophile.
She kind of comes on to him,
but it's sort of like,
I don't know if she was into him.
I think she was doing it to get him to do something,
to pilot the Eva, basically, which makes it okay.
Yeah, of course.
Just like Gendo's behavior was also okay
because it led to Shinji piloting the Eva.
At the end of the day,
at the end of the day, you've gotta punch that alien.
We need Shinji to pilot the Eva
by whatever means necessary.
I saw a good reply to that thread.
Somebody else, quote, treated that idiot's thread about it.
Because in that thread, the guy says,
it doesn't make any sense
that Shinji is still going to high school
while he's piloting the Eva.
And this thread that I saw, quote, tweeting,
it was like, wow, maybe it's not a mistake,
that that's weird.
Maybe the fact that the character is at once
both involved in this fate of the world,
hyper-military science organization,
and also going to regular high school,
maybe that's not a fuck-up,
maybe it's deliberately weird.
Like that, it never even answers this guy's head
that the creators of the show
might have realized that and done it on purpose
and thought about it.
Yeah, it's like strange, isn't it?
Hmm, yeah.
Maybe he should be a normal kid
and go to school and have friends
instead of everything else.
Now, I gotta drop out of school
and pilot a robot because robots are so fucking cool.
Why didn't they, he could have had a private tutor.
What, you think Nerve couldn't afford a tutor?
They could have had a private tutor.
We didn't have to keep going to high school, man.
Doesn't make any sense, logistically.
Man, high school sucks.
True.
Next one is called What Would You Do
If You Were Trixie, Suicide.
Next one is called Ben's Weekly Reminder,
Play Delta Room Chapter Two, okay.
catch up on one piece, okay.
Next one is called, well, it's a Twitter link.
Um, what's this?
Throw a moment to gaymail.com.
Power isn't determined by your size,
but the size of your heart and dreams,
total combat losses of the enemy from February 24,
is this about the war in Ukraine?
This is, yeah, Ministry of Defense of Ukraine
quoted Monkey D. Luffy in a tweet
when they are talking about how
they've killed so many Russians.
Oh my God, they did.
What the fuck?
Is this real?
It's verified.
DefenseU.
Gov.
Ukraine, yeah, this is a verified Ukraine
government organization.
They quoted Monkey D. Luffy.
Okay, sure, I guess.
So they are reporting 59,000 eliminated personnel,
plus bunches of vehicles that have either
been abandoned or destroyed.
That's funny.
Are you worried about nuclear war, by the way?
About nuclear war, I mean, I was more worried before.
Russia was like failing so heavily.
I feel like all of the Russia's failings
of logistics and just having good equipment
and having soldiers that are willing to fight,
it sort of speaks to a lack of like funding for these things.
I feel like Vladimir Putin definitely
wanted to win by intimidation.
And I feel like the nuclear thing could also be intimidation.
I don't think he has enough nukes to threaten everyone,
compared to how many anti-nuke defenses
the rest of the world has.
He might use a nuke in Ukraine.
I think that is possible.
Yeah, I was reading about it last night,
and it seems like if nukes are going to get involved,
they're going to be probably tactical nukes in Ukraine,
which is bad.
Tactical nukes in Ukraine, it would be horrible.
I don't want that either.
But I don't feel like it's like, oh, nuclear annihilation,
doomsday approaching.
It would just be like Russia would do that.
And then having done that, they would be destroyed
by literally everyone else.
I don't think Vladimir Putin is silly enough
to actually do it still.
I was reading a couple of articles about it.
And the consensus seems to be that even Russia's allies,
India and China would not like it if Putin started nuking people.
No.
So it would be bad for Russia.
I mean, Putin might be inclined to do it anyway,
just for his own reasons.
But it's not in Russia's interests to do it.
None of this has been in Russia's interests,
which is, I guess, the precedent that he could do it.
He could completely and permanently tank
like Russian's credibility as a nation going forward forever.
If he does this, he does a nuke.
Because he doesn't have what it takes to back it up afterwards.
Yeah.
I was worried about, like, oh, am I going to get nuked?
And like, yeah, it's probably, we're probably not looking at a,
like, they're not going to jump right to nuking the American mainland
or even anywhere, like, yeah.
It would be like a combat nuke, if anything.
Yeah.
And even that.
He's going to hold out for as long as possible.
Yeah.
I, like, I'm having to do it.
But I think, I think.
Because it's the threat of it that is, like, of the effective bargaining.
Yeah.
And nobody believes him.
And, like, I feel like he knows that nobody believes him.
Yeah.
So he's like, he doesn't have much else he can do at the moment.
I feel like what's most likely is that Ukraine will eventually push back
the Russian forces to the border.
And once that's happened, Zelensky might try to get a peace thing going.
Because I don't think Ukraine wants to invade Russia.
They have no reason to.
So I kind of expect it to just go like that.
I don't think Putin would use a nuke if he couldn't follow it up.
I don't think he can follow it up right now.
I mean, he definitely can't follow it up.
No, like, you just destroy it like he is.
And then, like, you still get pushed back because the army
and the rest of Ukraine is still strong enough to do it.
Yeah.
The consequences for doing that, I think, would be pretty bad.
Next one is called More Voice Males Like Last Week, Please.
Three, two, one, go.
Well, OK.
This guy likes what they heard.
Yeah.
Well, guess what?
You did get more voice smells like last week.
So congratulations.
Next one is called I'm So Happy Voice Males Are Back, Thank the Lord.
Three, two, one, go.
It's zero seconds.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
But there was a cut.
It's so stupid that people use these to just deliver a, like,
eight-word long written message and no voicemail.
But oh well.
Next one is called Wong, Wong, Wong.
Three, two, one, go.
Was that like a stuttering Chinese man morphing
into Arnold Schwarzenegger at the end?
I thought it was.
Was he attempting to mimic like a voice, like audio fuckery, like stutter, like?
I don't think so.
I think it was just a racist voice he was doing.
Maybe.
I mean, it was definitely that.
But there's layers.
I felt like maybe he was attempting to mimic the sound of like a record repeating or like
it having been edited to sputter, I'm not sure.
Next one is called carbon offsets are a scam and your NFT is fucking bad.
Three, two, one, go.
Carbon assessor fucking bullshit and don't do anything you goddamn moron.
Why did I, why are you calling me that?
Why are you so mean?
He's talking to carbon offset stands.
I don't know.
Carbon offsets.
A carbon offset is, I assume it's something.
It's when you do something stupid, they say they'll plant a tree, they'll plant a tree
or something.
Okay.
Sounds good.
Maybe.
Yeah, it sounds dumb.
This guy's probably right.
Next one is called death of a Ben St.
Oh, yes.
Okay, let's see what this voicemail, let's see what's behind this link.
It's a YouTube one minute 24.
Okay.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Probably can't.
I don't think we can play this.
I think.
No, because it's got a song in it, but we can put the visuals up.
Yeah, we can put the visuals up.
This is to say montage of Vinny's drawings of me.
Oh, he think he drew new ones for it.
Yeah, these are new.
He illustrated this whole song about me.
Wow.
It's probably not going to be the same without the music.
You're so sad.
Wait, this is death of a bachelor?
I was thinking of a different song.
Is that you in the orange dress?
I don't know.
Don't look like me.
No, it's a tricksy.
Oh, it's a tricksy.
Yes.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Excellent.
Funny.
Thanks.
Thanks, Vinny.
I liked it.
Yeah.
Next one.
How many?
Not that many left.
Hey, Ben.
New fan here.
I'm single if you're interested.
Nope.
Not even going to listen to the voice?
I did listen, but it's zero seconds, so there's nothing to it.
Oh, the last one is I didn't think when I sent it,
avoid getting copyright strike.
It's VVVV mute the vid, but still watch it, please.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm playing the audio.
Be sure to mute the death of Ben saying the video in case,
like, am I going to copyright on the channel?
Yes.
I didn't really think about that when I sent it.
That's okay.
We can put the link in the description and people can watch it themselves.
Right.
I mean, yeah, definitely we can't play the audio, but okay.
Got it.
I mean, I guess that's it.
I guess we're done.
Yeah.
What a week.
It's so weird.
At the end of a week, I don't remember too much of what happened,
but it definitely days passed and days definitely passed.
Days.
Days definitely passed.
It's getting colder.
It's getting October.
It is getting.
It is getting colder.
October fast.
I had to bust out my space heater.
I had to turn off my air conditioner.
I might actually have to take it out of my window soon if you can believe that.
Oh.
Yeah.
But I don't know, whatever.
It's fine.
The colder weather means I can actually wear, like, clothes.
Like when it's hot, I can just, all I can do is wear like a t-shirt because anything
more and it's like, it's going to make me sweat.
But when it's chilly, I can actually make an outfit, which is nice.
Can wear a jacket.
Can wear a cloak.
Yeah.
You can wear a cape and a cloak hood.
Exactly.
Boots.
And wear a robe.
Wear a whole costume.
Wear a whole pumpkin man scarecrow outfit.
If I want, I don't, but I could.
I kind of like the idea of a punk helmet of some kind.
Like if I pad it, if I make it like warm and fuzzy and not like a pain to wear, it could
be like a warm thing.
I could wear it every day.
You can stuff it with straw.
And people will be like, what the fuck is wrong with you?
Well, that's your practice for wearing something outlandish in public.
True.
That's what you said you wanted to do, right?
On Halloween.
Yeah.
Just wear something stupid.
Oh, you know what?
I could cosplay a scraggity-acty.
The scarecrow OC that has the big straw tits.
You could make some straw tits if you put your mind to it.
All I need to do is believe.
I'm trying to think if there's anything I want to say before we end the show for this
week.
I don't know.
I'm going to keep grinding.
Yeah, just keep that Sigma grind set going.
I'm going to keep that Sigma.
Oh, there's a new folding ideas video.
I saw it.
It was good.
Yeah, it was pretty good.
Made me want to try it almost.
Part of me was like, what if I tried this?
What if I tried this book method and did it?
But I think it probably doesn't work, as he explains.
They don't actually do it anymore because it doesn't work.
Oh, as a method to like, I mean, I guess getting a ghost writer is still a thing that's possible.
Yeah, all the steps of the process are still possible to do.
I think it's probably not super effective anymore.
If it was super effective, they probably wouldn't be selling the method.
No.
Yeah, very, very, very funny grift, very funny grift.
The people who get into those grifts and they've always got YouTube influencer faces and hair
and clothes, there's always that sort of person.
I don't know why, but it just reminds me of, I don't know.
I imagine that that's the grown-up version of that bratty kid who does not get disciplined at all.
Like, oh, that kid is such a brat and they turn into one of these people.
Yeah, it's like, whatever they can get away with.
I think they're so clever because they found a cute little loophole.
It's like, this is for people that don't have the time or inclination to learn new skills because anyone could do that.
Like, that's me.
What a intriguing prospect.
I'll buy it.
Thank you.
I am the target demographic.
You mean if I put money, I can just get free shit and get my own money from putting money in?
If I just pay some money, I can get stuff for free?
That's crazy, dog.
Yeah.
Good video, though.
Yes.
I like Dan a lot.
Did I watch any other good videos this week?
No.
Never.
I feel, it feels bad.
I feel like we haven't gone long enough.
Not even two and a half hours.
The comments are going to be furious.
It's hard sometimes having stuff to talk about.
Yeah.
I mean, I mostly had the last of us thing.
Aside from that, I'm just working on stuff.
Sometimes it's just a week goes by.
Well, let's try and manufacture something.
I hope my video will be done soon.
We'll be dropping in the very near future.
Maybe not before this week's episode comes out, but not too long after that, I think, is almost for sure.
Oh, you know what?
I can talk briefly about RuneScape.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, please.
My challenge run has been continuing, and I got bored mining coal, so I switched over.
Now I'm shopping down U-Logs, U-Trees to get U-Logs, and that's what I'm doing.
U-Logs.
I haven't thought to make a video.
What about me, Logs?
Ah.
Never thought of that one.
Yeah.
It is one of those, like, I haven't got enough of an interesting thing to make a video about it, so there's no third installment yet of the RuneScape thing.
But when I have something to talk about it, I'll be like, and here's the update.
Wait, was there a second?
Oh, the second one was about the runite, right?
Yeah.
Like mining runite, or for the first time, it was like a milestone in my RuneScape career.
Not that it's a career just sort of like, since I was young, I was wanting to do it.
I've got a feeling this is going to consume the rest of your life, kid.
Oh, my God.
You're going to be at this.
This is the grind, the new Sigma grind set.
I kind of want, I kind of luckily Outer Wilds, but I haven't, just haven't, I haven't clicked on it yet.
But I want to, because it sounded really cool.
You described it in a way that made it sound real neat and nifty, so.
You should click on it.
Definitely want to check it out.
As soon as, as soon as this is, we finished here.
No, I gotta get worked.
Maybe, maybe after I edit for a while and I feel like I can't do anymore.
I'll use, you use it as a, as a carrot on a stick.
Yeah, yeah.
For you, this is the morning.
Yeah, pretty much.
Makes sense.
I often have the thing where like after the PCP is done for the day, I like get nothing done
for the rest of the day and I hate that.
I fall, I fall into the trap of like, I already did my stuff for the day, even though I then
have like most of the day left afterwards.
Yeah.
I mean, for me, I always classify weekends as like no work required.
Oh.
In fact, in fact, no work allowed.
I can't, like, I can't do it.
Yeah.
Other than.
So it's like forced rest and it's, it works.
I don't feel stressed during the weekend.
Other than.
And then when Monday comes around, I'm like, right, let's try and do something.
That's good.
Other, other than Sunday for PCP, I don't really distinguish days of the week.
Like my, my Saturday is the same as my Monday pretty much most of the time.
So, you know, it's probably healthy.
I think it helps.
It's probably healthier to have.
Yeah.
A designated weekend.
Cause it's, this is what I was saying a few, like weeks ago, the whole resting being very
important.
And if you're thinking about work, you're not resting.
And so like having a routine where it's normal and accepted and good that you don't work
makes it easier for you to rest on that day.
Instead, I will sort of just kind of work on a day that I can make myself do it and
I'll just do that for as many days as I can.
And then there will eventually come a day where I'm like, I let, I let something else
distract me and then I don't do anything for that day.
And then I'll get on a, on a, on a roll of like, okay.
So for the, for the next few days, I won't do anything until eventually I feel bad enough
and I'm like, oh God, how many I've wasted like three days.
I haven't worked on it in like four days.
Like, uh, terrible.
What a waste.
And then I'll.