Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
Hello, and welcome to another episode of the PCP, The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm Ben Saint, and with me today, I have Tom Oliver. Thank you for joining me, Tom.
We're all about melodrama today, apparently. I would like to ask you, what is to be done about the Israeli-Palestinian conflict? Your thoughts.
I think we just need to line them all up in like a big line together, and then you just got to get like one semi-attractive looking woman to walk up to them, and then just be like, have a Red Bull, and they'll all be friends. That's what TV has taught me.
What? Wait, Red Bull doesn't make friends, it gives you wings.
Well, if they're wings, they'll all-
No, no, no. I think you're right, but it's got to be Mentos. It doesn't matter what comes, fresh goes better in life, and then like, oh, an Israeli, someone in the Israeli Defense Force, you know, he's like pounding-
That's the fresh maker, not the peacemaker.
He's like beating a child's head in with the butt of his rifle, but then like, you know, his little, like, his emaciated little, the Palestinian kids, like, emaciated little brother is like, wait, sir, it holds up a Mentos?
And he goes, ha, ha, ha, ha, and he takes some, and then they're like, ah, forget about it, ah, you little scamp. And that's- I could see it, I could see it.
Why aren't we in charge of international relations? We can get this all solved in a day.
The Mentos Trio. The Mentos Trio could have solved, could have, we could have had peace in the Middle East back when I was like 14.
Have I- Wait a second. I've mentioned the Mentos Trio before. Have I ever explained what that was?
Maybe. I'm only here for like half the episodes now, so.
That's true. That's true. Okay, I think I mentioned this once, but let me tell you about a period in my life.
When I was like- I'm going to be so embarrassed if I have told the story before and I just forgot.
But when I was like 12, 13, maybe a little younger even, I went to this summer camp.
Not a camp, really, but like a program for gifted children, because I was so smart.
That's what your parents told you, huh? That's what you're going?
I don't know. It was called College Academy, and it was basically like kids during the summer.
It was like- it was sort of like a mock college, like you would pick your classes, and then in the course of the day you would go between classes,
and then you go to lunch, and then you go to two more classes. It was sort of like pretend college for kids.
It's like a prepare yourself for the future kind of thing.
And you, a future cartoonist, needed this desperately.
Well, I had potential back then.
But on the bus ride to and from College Academy, I don't know, there were these older kids who I thought were so cool,
and like a couple years later, some of them would graduate, and eventually I joined their inner circle,
and they called themselves the Mentos Trio, and what they would do is they would sit at the back of the bus to College Academy,
and they would buy Mentos before every bus ride, and they would write- they would take paper, like a pencil paper,
and they would write like Mentos the Freshmaker on paper, and they would wait for the bus to stop at a red light and wait for a car behind the bus to pull up close,
and then they would like flip back and like look through the windows in the back of the bus and slam the paper on the back window,
and they would give thumbs up and big smiles and hold the Mentos like, yeah, Mentos, the Freshmaker,
and just see what the car behind them would do, and that was it. That was the Mentos Trio.
And these are the people you thought were cool.
Listen, they had passion.
You know, I can't deny that. This sounds like something out of a webcomic.
This sounds like something that could be in Tales Against Troll or something, and I would believe it.
It does. It's pretty zany. It's pretty wacky.
Ben, do you think it became a cartoonist because your entire childhood was just something out of an early 2000s webcomic?
No, no. I thought it was normal back then.
But sometimes you get good reactions, though.
Sometimes there was one guy who flipped us off and then peeled out in a U-turn, like he was mad.
Most of the time, people would either just ignore it or sometimes people would give thumbs up back.
That was the most common thing, as you might expect.
Yeah, you're just playing the long game to get those golden reactions, either positive or negative, I suppose.
Gotta wade through the shit.
Ah, it was good times. It was good times.
I think they thought I was a loser because I was a little kid, but then a couple of them graduated and they were like,
well, we have to let Ben join because there's no longer three of us.
Oh man, can't be the Mentos duo. That's just not nearly as good.
That's just lame, no. The people behind the bus would laugh at us.
The balance between base and cringe is that three-person dynamic.
That's it. If there's only two of you, you just look like some weird lone losers, right?
But you can't get a third person to join your little Mentos cult?
Three's a crap, so then it's the cool thing to do.
For just two people, just like, oh god, those sad, pathetic young men.
It's just a tray, and what were the shooter's names?
I know, I don't.
From the Columbine, the Columbine shooters.
Why do you think I would know the shooter's names from Columbine?
I don't know, they're famous.
I know the names of the last five Ultraman, I don't know, the Columbine shooters.
My knowledge is very fucked up.
It was Trey Parker and Matt Stone, I believe.
Oh, right, that was the duo that you joined to become the Mentos trio.
And who then went on to shoot up Columbine, famously.
Yeah, you know.
If you want to get a show on Comedy Central, you got to really prove that you're committed to the bit.
Good times, good times.
Okay, so now, that's pretty much it.
There's nothing else to say about the Mentos trio, but that was the deal with it.
I was not familiar with that story, so you at least never told me it before.
Good, good, good, good.
Me and Gib did the bonus episode this week.
We did the Minesweeper challenge.
We did the Minesweeper, I guess, race or battle or whatever.
Which you can see for $5 a month over on patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
I got to say, I think that that bonus episode, it has twists and turns.
Was it better than the Dark Souls race?
Well, the Dark Souls race.
You have to say yes, we're trying to sell this right now.
No, I could say that I can waffle and I don't have to commit to anything.
I can say, well, it's apples and oranges.
Well, it's a different kind of quality.
It's better than the Yellow episode, for sure.
It's better than the Dark Souls race.
It's better than the Pokemon race.
It's better than what's the most viewed video on our channel.
I don't know.
It used to be the DigiTrixie calls Mumkey, the one where she explains why Mumkey was kicked.
That was the most popular for a while.
For a long time.
For a year or more.
That explains a lot, I guess.
And then I think finally, we were like, guys, we don't want this here.
This sucks.
All the lectures that are on here had less views than that.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, that might be right.
That might have been the most popular after the lectures, actually.
Okay, okay.
That's a little better.
Why the most?
Oh my God, it's both your lectures are the most popular.
Yeah, by a wide margin.
Oh my God, am I the king of this channel now?
That was a ground-breaking piece of content.
It was the video that set the trend.
You know, it was.
It was.
Man, it'd be really great if there was another one.
If there was a follow-up to that, God, it just seems like it's about time.
If only that existed.
It is time.
I've been feeling bad about that.
I have...
Well, I have...
I hope I'm not giving the game away here.
But I mean, I need to get my secret project done
before I want to release that.
I feel like...
I feel a little bit like zonked out.
I feel a little bit like...
I don't know what's going on.
I don't know what's going on in the news.
I don't know what I should be angry about this week.
The last two days, I've done basically nothing except work on that.
And it's...
Which is good.
Which is what I should be doing.
I've said this before, but it's probably stupid.
Objectively, it's probably stupid that I haven't released that yet.
But there is a reason why I need it released in a particular order.
Maybe not a good one, a reason that anyone would agree with.
But there is a reason.
At least you have a game plan and you're sticking to it, I guess.
I do.
The commenters will let us know if they respect that decision in any way, shape, or form.
I do think that...
I think originally I wanted...
Okay, I want to make posting that an event.
I want to attach with it an announcement that I was going to do.
Maybe some kind of...
I was thinking I will read every issue of Sonichu on my Twitch channel
to raise money for charity or something.
To make a big event out of it.
I don't know if I want to do that anymore.
Part of me is just like...
When it's time, I'm maybe just going to say fuck it.
Just put it out there who cares.
It could be fun.
Depends how much extra effort it would require.
You'd have to have special guests, Christine Westin Chandler, to show up.
To voice themselves in the comic.
She's been on my channel before.
I know. It's not outside the realm of possibility.
If you really wanted to raise money for charity, that's what you would do.
That would be the power move.
I don't know about it.
I don't know if the crowd that would be attracted by Chris being on a thing would be very likely to give anything to anyone.
I feel like people within your sphere, though, would be doubly invested in a situation like that.
Maybe.
It's possible.
Every time I do or say a Chris-related thing,
there's a new crop of people that show up to be like,
Chris, get a job!
Chris, get a job, Chris!
Fuck's sake!
It's never going to happen.
I don't think so.
It's just unhirable.
Some people are unhirable.
Some people are just dedicated to other people
need to get jobs, raise kids, and have families.
Some people are angry when people don't do that.
These people come out of the woodwork
when Chris is being discussed on the internet.
It's funny how these people are berating Chris
or just doing the same thing over and over again,
wasting their time chasing an impossible goal
when they themselves are chasing the impossible goal
of getting him to stop doing that.
We're getting her to stop doing that, I should say.
So they're both committed to the same hubris.
They're like Batman and the Joker.
They're two sides of the same coin.
One can never defeat the other.
That's true.
They need each other.
It's a symbiotic relationship.
I mean, it's kind of true.
Without the trolls, what would Chris be?
I mean, so much of Sonichu is about dealing with trolls.
It's true.
Sonichu would be nothing.
What she conceives to be trolls, yeah.
It makes you think really thought-provoking.
What else was I gonna...
I'm like, hey, what's...
Tell me something.
Well, I did it.
I did the thing.
I watched the Snyder Cut of Justice League,
because it came out on Friday.
I watched the whole thing, all four hours in one sitting.
I have been hearing about the Snyder Cut.
And I don't want to...
I mean, I didn't see the original movie,
so I'm not gonna watch the Snyder Cut either.
I would not watch it if you did not see the original.
In fact, no one should really watch it at all,
but it was just one of those things where it's like,
I'm so curious as what...
I saw a Stereo's Coconut on Twitter said
that he did think the Snyder Cut was better than the original.
I agree. I think it was better.
It was more, as strange as this to say,
it was more cohesive just because there was one person
in charge of the vision than the studio meddling hodgepodge
that was the theatrical cut, because of course I saw that too.
There is a video by Foldable Human.
Do you know who that is?
No, but that's a terrifying username.
He used to use a little cardboard box puppet
as sort of his mouthpiece, as sort of his avatar.
He just dropped Dan Olson.
He's dropped that for a long time,
but I think that was originally why he was called Foldable Human.
Now it just sounds lovecrafty and terrifying.
You know, I've never thought of it like that,
but I guess I could see what you mean.
But he made a video about folding ideas.
Folding ideas is what the channel is called.
Oh, okay. I've heard of folding ideas. Yeah, yeah.
Oh, okay, okay.
Well, he made a video about the Snyder Cut a year or more ago
saying it doesn't exist.
There is no completed Snyder Cut.
So I don't know.
People have been calling for the Snyder Cut for years,
but the Snyder Cut now, it's not something that existed all along.
It's like, it must have been something that was made in response to the outcry.
From what I've read is that only, like, okay.
So the original Cut, I think, was under two hours at the theatrical release.
And almost, like half of it was just new footage they re-shot with Joss Whedon.
And then this version that just came out is four hours and two minutes.
And only five minutes of that was new footage.
Everything else that was replaced was footage that was cut from the original version.
So there's, like, I think an hour and 45 minutes of footage from the original version that got cut.
Does the Snyder Cut not include the Joss Whedon stuff?
No, none of the Joss Whedon stuff is in the Snyder Cut.
It's all just the original stuff.
Because, like, there was, like, over two hours of shit they cut from the theatrical release
or in place with the Joss Whedon things.
And then they re-tweeted a lot of stuff.
So, yeah, it was, it's kind of dumb just because, like, you, it's like, okay,
for four years people have been clamoring for the Snyder Cut.
And they release it and it's clear that you watch it.
It's like, oh, this was a part one.
So it kind of ends super open for, like, all this new stuff that you just know is not going to happen.
And, like, the five minutes of new footage was, like, the cliffhanger ending of this movie.
It's like, so you recorded a stinger for a movie that you know is not going to get made?
Like, it was really fucking weird.
Hmm, I see, I see.
Because, like, spoilers, at the end, like, Martian Manhunter shows up and he's like,
hey, Batman, I'm Martian Manhunter.
I'm gonna help you fight.
And Batman's like, cool.
And then it ends and it's like, oh, I can't wait to never see this movie
where Martian Manhunter exists.
Awesome.
I saw a tweet from Brianna Joy Gray.
I think she was watching the Snyder Cut.
And someone said, she said, like, I guess Martian Manhunter shows up
and Ben Affleck goes like, who the fuck are you?
And she said, like, thank you.
I was wondering too.
And then she said, Martian, the name Martian Manhunter is so descriptive
without being clarifying at all.
Yeah.
Like, if you don't, like, if you don't know who that is.
This cut of the movie would never have worked in theaters
because it just drops a ton of, like, comic lore without any explanation
and doesn't try and make it any way approachable.
Like, Darkseid's just there, like, trying to get to Earth
and he's like, I need to go to Earth.
It has the anti-life equation.
And, like, they don't explain what the anti-life equation is
or what it means.
It's just a bunch of, like, CG monsters talking about this thing
for, like, two hours.
And it just assumes that, like, you've read comic books,
like, you know what the anti-life equation is
and why Darkseid wants it, right?
And it's pretty funny.
That's, I mean, I guess that's what the hardcore fans want.
So, like, it sounds like, it sounds like some people
will be pretty pleased about that, I guess.
I mean, like, in the original, in, like, the theatrical cut,
like, that came out first, the whole back end of the movie
is, like, the main, like, throwaway villain guy Steppenwolf.
He, like, sets up a base in this, like, abandoned, like,
Russian town that has, like, a couple people in there
and the whole fight is happening while they're trying
to, like, evacuate the people that are living in this town.
I think some cute little fucking, like, one-liners
and, like, funny scenes of, like, the Flash pushing
this truck away of, like, these, like, old couple
and then Superman's, like, carrying an entire building
and he's like, oh, I feel shitty because I'm not a strong
Superman, like, dumb shit like that.
And the Snyder Cut, there's, it's just an abandoned town
and nobody's there, so they destroy the entire fucking thing
in this fight and it's so much, such a different tone
and, like, of course, everything's shot in the dark
in this version and in the original theatrical cut
it was all brightened up and stuff and for some reason
when Superman comes back, he wears a black suit
but they changed it back to the normal colors
in the original theatrical cut, but in this one,
he's just wearing a black costume just because
Zack Snyder, I guess?
Was he given the comics or...
I mean, he did have a black costume in the comics.
I don't know if that was a reference to that or...
It was just strange because there was no reason for him
to wear another costume because, like, in the movie,
they go on to, like, a Kryptonian ship
and it has, like, his normal costume in there
but, like, he just wears black because I guess it's cooler?
I don't know.
The whole movie's in 4.3 also.
It is cooler.
That's probably the weirdest, most jarring thing
because there was a bunch of articles.
4.3 is like...
The Snyder Cut is?
Yeah, the Snyder Cut's in 4.3 aspect ratio,
not widescreen.
Why?
I think it was because originally it was shot
in a different aspect ratio for IMAX theaters
and, like, instead of, like, trying to adjust it
for 16x9, like, because I think widescreen
or IMAX is taller or something, I don't know,
I didn't look into it too much, but, like, yeah,
it's all in 4.3, the entire thing.
Speaking of...
Not to force a subject change,
but speaking of 4.3 aspect ratio,
I've been watching a lot of, or I've been mostly listening to,
a lot of Ross's Game Dungeon recently, you know that?
From Accursed Farms, the YouTube channel?
No. What is that?
Well, I mean, it's just, like, videos that a guy makes
where he talks about games, and, like, a lot of the games
that he plays are, like, a lot of older stuff.
It's not all older stuff, but a lot of older stuff.
Like, stuff like the Commodore 64 or the Amiga,
but also stuff, like, older classics, stuff like,
like, Deus Ex, the original Deus Ex and stuff.
Weird, like, point-and-click adventure games.
He plays a lot of point-and-click adventure games
that I've never heard of.
The reason I heard about this channel was because
when I made the lecture about Jennifer Dane writes,
a lot of people, I talked about that old game she made,
Boppin, and I guess Ross's Game Dungeon had,
from years ago, Ross's Game Dungeon had an episode about Boppin,
and a lot of people had heard of Boppin before from that.
I see.
Okay, Ross is very...
He does, like, text stuff.
He says he's not good with computers,
but he's way better with them than me.
Like, he will, like, emulate games,
and he will, like, go into the code
and, like, hack it specific...
I don't know if it's hacking, but, you know,
he will modify the code to make games, like, play in widescreen,
even if they, like, natively run in 4.3.
He, like, hates games that don't run in widescreen,
and he will, like...
He will take, like, pains to make these, like,
old, like, Windows 32-era game,
like, 3D games run on widescreen.
I don't know.
He's passionately against, like, shaders
that cause aliasing on pixels in games.
He gets, like, upset about that. I don't know.
Oh, like, like, anti-aliasing?
Like, smoothing out the pixels and stuff?
Yeah.
That's a huge pet peeve of mine, too,
but I've never gone and, like,
tried to put something in 16x9 that's in 4.3.
I don't mind the anti-aliasing.
That doesn't bug me too much.
Every time I play Doom, and, like,
it has the anti-aliasing on by default,
it smooths out all the sprites, and I'm just like,
no, I want my pixels.
Wait, so, no, no,
what he hates is when
like, um,
is when the pixels aren't smoothed.
Oh, my God.
What a monster.
Like, when, well, he'll, like,
there's a video, a clip that he shows sometimes,
there's, like, power lines,
and there's wires going between the power lines,
and the pixels on the power line are anti-aliased,
so they're all, like, individual pixels,
and they kind of, like, fizzle and, like, pop in and out, right?
As you move your field of view,
and, like, the tiny little wire moves across the screen.
You know what I'm saying?
Uh, sort of.
Uh, okay, I don't know.
I would have to find the screenshot.
It's just the low resolution.
They were just fucking with it.
And, like, a texture looks like it's all, like,
staticky, right, as you move,
because the pixels are, like,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like pixels.
I like when old games look fucked up.
Yeah, I mean, it's good.
You have to, that's, like, part of the aesthetic.
Ugh.
I don't know, he'll play these fucking, like,
20-year-old games and be like,
ah.
Why does this not look like a modern game?
I have to, I have to, I have to, though,
he's like, this isn't good.
I gotta go in and, like, modify the game's code
and, like, lock the game to, like, a higher frame rate,
and, like, overclock my fucking processor
to, like, make the game run at 60 frames per second
when it originally ran at, like,
10.4 or whatever.
Uh...
Sure.
I don't...
He has, he just has such a completely, completely...
That must be a nightmare.
I know a lot of, like, early 3D games,
they would tie all their physics to frame rate.
So, like, you would have to, like,
completely, like, redo the whole physics engine
to get it to work.
He has such a completely different way
of engaging with the medium of video games.
That is an idea.
That is, uh...
I want to say autism, but no.
It's something.
I don't know.
It's that weird laser focus that people have
about certain specific things.
Yeah.
I, um...
I've been, I guess, I guess, binging it
because, um, I...
Have just been trying to...
Because I've been trying to crank out work
on the thing, on the secret thing,
and I just...
I've found that that's a good thing
that, like, I don't really need to pay attention to.
You know, that's, that's the hurdle.
That's the problem, is you want,
you want content to put on
to just be noise in the background
and the danger is that, oh, it'll be too interesting
and you'll find yourself having to, like,
pay attention to it instead of the work you want to be doing.
You know, I do that all the time.
I was doing that with critical role
and it just got too interesting
and so I just tabbed back over to it.
You just got to listen to, like, music.
Just, like, lo-fi, instrumental.
I don't like music.
Just something to occupy the sound space.
I'm just...
Music doesn't do that for me.
Music doesn't, like, occupy...
I mean, sometimes it does.
Sometimes I'll use, like, rainy mood
and I'll just put on, like, you know, like a thunderstorm,
like, on loop for, like, 30 hours and just do that.
Well, I use that to sleep.
I do that to sleep sometimes, too.
Just, like, some sort of ambient noise.
I don't know, just, like, real silence bothers me.
It's, like...
It doesn't bother me if I'm...
If I start working on something
and I actually, like, get into working on it,
it doesn't matter if, like, it's quiet or not.
I don't even notice.
But, like, when I'm starting,
I feel, like, it's, like, harder for me to start
because I feel, like, oh, it's quiet.
Like, my mind isn't occupied.
Like, something is...
I need something.
It's, like, the fact that there's no noise
or is, like, distracting almost.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess that's how I'm gonna describe it.
I find that, like, in the beginning,
I need something to, kind of, like, occupy that part of my brain.
Then I'll get into it for a while,
like, usually within, like, a half an hour to 45 minutes,
my brain will start to drift, regardless of what I'm doing,
unless I'm, like, stuck on something.
If I'm having, like, a problem, like, my brain will just laser-focus
on trying to get that fixed while, like, raging.
But other than that, like, my brain always starts to drift.
And if I have something that's interesting on the background,
like, you know, like, Critical Role or, like, YouTube videos or something,
I'll just, like, drift back towards that
and forget what I was doing.
And then two hours later, I'm like,
why am I watching Best of the Worst Episode 75 for the fifth time?
I should be working.
So, like, music is just the safe thing,
because, like, I'll just open the tab,
and it'll be the little raccoon walking on the sidewalk,
and I'll be like, yep, she's still walking,
and then I can go back and do what I'm doing.
I'm supposed to be working.
Oh, it's so bad.
Now I'm supposed to be working right now.
I woke up today at 11, and I was like,
oh, I got, like, four hours to work on my secret project
before the podcast starts.
But then I didn't, and I went and got food,
and then I don't even know what happened.
The podcast is just the worst.
The podcast is a nightmare.
It fucks up your whole day, right?
It really is. It does for me.
It's in the middle of the day, so it's like,
it's not like you can get it out of the way early,
or it's not like you can wrap everything up before it at night.
It's just like, no matter what you start,
or when you start it, it interrupts it.
Yeah.
It's like, lately, I've seen a couple of, like,
you know, haha-relatable comics
that I have been, like,
yes.
I do, it is relatable
about, like,
I saw one that was, like,
you know, oh,
only I have to do something
in four hours.
Guess I can't, I can't do anything.
Yeah.
And the podcast does that every Sunday to me.
I can't do anything before, because, oh,
in, like, six hours from now, I have to do the podcast,
and then afterwards, like, oh, well,
I have to go to sleep in, like, five hours from now,
so I can't do anything.
I've been, like, trying to push myself through that,
but something that helped me is, like,
after I did the PCP,
I would usually also record the bonus podcast
I do for my patrons on Sunday as well.
It was, like, another hour on top of that,
and, like, I got to move this to another day.
Yeah.
I missed my
patron
podcast this month. I missed it.
I failed them.
But it's okay,
I made an announcement. I said,
yes, I missed the Q&A, yes, I missed the podcast.
However, however,
I'm going to do another one
after the secret thing is,
after the demo of the secret thing is done,
the, like, the semi,
the patrons only, like,
early version is done.
And then I'll do a Q&A
where I talk about that specifically.
So I have a plan.
It's all part of the plan.
I missed sending out the
merch package for this quarter
because I've been doing all these secret projects.
So I just said to everyone
on that tier on Patreon, I was like,
I'll just do a double, a double size
next quarter.
So in April, you'll get two t-shirts, two 3D prints,
four posters, and a bunch of other stuff
instead of the two and ones that I usually send.
I wanted to complain
about
problems I was
encountering on the work,
on the project with patrons
because, like, I'm only
talking to patrons about it.
But so I went into my Discord
because I have a patrons-only channel
and nobody was in there and I was like,
what is this? And I realized
that Discord patron integration
had been broken for, like, months.
What? Is it really?
Well, not in general,
just on my account.
Oh, shit, I rely on that too.
No, my account had just, like,
I had set it up before,
but, like, I look back and it just, like, isn't
there anymore. It, like, it didn't know
that my, it didn't have my
server attached, it didn't have the, like,
patron roles attached to it.
So I fixed that
and then I, and then
it dragged a bunch of people, like, into
my server who I think had been in there
and had left. I think they, like,
weren't interested in
but they came back
and so I had a captive audience
that I could complain to about,
ah, it's too hard, though.
It's too hard.
Half of them just, like, what the fuck are you talking about?
I haven't been in here for six months.
I got, um,
I got some, I got some helpful,
I actually got some helpful feedback from a couple of them.
Oh, yeah. It was pretty, it was good.
It helped me, it helped me cope.
I was seething, at first I was seething,
but afterwards I was
successfully coping, so
that was an improvement.
Excellent.
Uh,
yes.
I have too many secret projects right now.
I'm working on three
and a half secret projects all at the same time.
How do you,
you can't work on three at once.
I know, but, but I'm trying anyways.
It sucks.
What?
Why would you do this?
Because I only have
eight more years left before I turn
40 and I'm gonna kill myself
because no one should be allowed to be that old,
so I gotta, I gotta make these last,
this last,
less than a decade count.
We're gonna, we're gonna look like Prince Harry by then.
Oh, God.
Don't even say that.
Have you? Okay.
Every time I go on the internet,
I go on Twitter and I realize like
19 year olds are conscious.
I'm just like, I am irrelevant.
I am a fossil.
I should, I literally should be dead.
It's the worst feeling of all time.
Yeah.
I mean,
yeah.
Um,
it, it, it, I know what you mean.
I wouldn't, it, it wouldn't bother me.
It wouldn't bother me
except that
I don't
I don't know how
to, I don't know.
If I were still like
doing my, my work, whatever, doing what I do,
it would be fine.
Except that I feel like I haven't found any
new audience in a long time
and that really bothers me and I don't know what to do about it.
Well.
I'm not growing.
The fact that I'm old, the fact that I'm old doesn't,
doesn't bother me too much
except for the fact that oh, I've, I've gotten this
old and yet I feel like I have not
grown in a while. Ben. Am I,
am I stagnant now? No, it's because you're doing
the same thing that I am because it's the reason I haven't
grown in any fashion either
in the last like couple years is because
we're both doing secret projects.
Nobody knows what the fuck we're working on.
The way
to be successful is you have to broadcast
everything you're doing constantly.
That's true. That's true.
That's true.
My secret project,
I guess, I guess when mine is
done, I can probably hype it up to a certain
extent. I could see maybe
I could see maybe getting a little bit
of word of mouth buzz. I'm not keeping
my secret project secret until
it's done. I'm just keeping it secret until
it's at a state where there's something worth
presenting because especially one
of them right now is just so early
that it would be boring
to even talk about.
Well, I think mine
I think mine isn't actually going to take me.
I mean, if I were if I
keep working at the pace that I've been working
on the last couple days, I think
I think that like the early
version will be done this week and the
the final version
I mean who know. I mean, you know
it's one of those things where like I
could work on it for another year
and just keep like adding stuff, adding
stuff, adding stuff, but like I won't do that.
I think mine are going to take at least two years.
Oh, OK
mine's not like that. Mine's not that big.
It's a nightmare. Yeah.
That is a nightmare. Oh my God.
And that's like the first the first of three
like I have three projects I'm working on
right now, but the biggest of the three
is the smallest of a three part larger
secret project that will probably take 20 years.
20 years.
You can't you can't plan 20 years.
I'm not I'm not even thinking about the rest of it, but just
like thinking about like how slow I work.
There's not even going to be. Yeah, like I'm dead
in eight going to be in America in 20 years.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
So that's never going to happen. So I'm not thinking about it, but.
Speaking.
Speaking of the collapse of America.
I did I did something.
I did something a little crazy.
I did something a little wacky. Oh, yeah.
I sold my Bitcoin.
Oh my God, really? Why?
I sold because
because I bought
some last month
with the plan that I would hold
until the stimmy thinking that the stimmy
would cause a bump.
Which didn't really happen,
but it went up anyway.
But you know, it was up to almost 62
and then it went down to like the mid 50s
and then it went back up to like the high 50s
and I was looking at this kind of wobbling
and I was like,
I expect a crash at some point.
I don't know if it'll be immediate,
but like sometime this year,
I expect that it will drop significantly.
And I think
I've gained a little bit.
I've gained I've made a little money
from the rise.
And the last time,
the last time I held,
you know, I could have just held and held and held,
but I also could have just sold
earlier and I would have made money there too.
The reason why I didn't make money earlier
was that I held too long.
And I was thinking maybe like, maybe now is the time
to like sell.
So I can lock in what gains I've made
and wait for,
I mean, it could be wrong, maybe there won't be any crash,
but if there is, maybe now is the time
to try and like beat it out.
So that's what I did.
I sold at about 58
on down a little bit since then.
It's at 57.4.
So I feel
I feel like,
I don't know.
I feel good. I feel good having sold.
I'm like, I'm kind of done.
I'm done with it for now.
I don't really
I don't understand why Bitcoin is so valuable
other than it was the first like the novelty
of it because like everything that's
happening in the crypto space seems to be built
on top of it.
So like, yeah, like the whole NFT thing
we're talking about last week, that's all built on top of Ethereum
and things like that. Like I was watching some stuff
about Ethereum in general and they were saying
how like Ethereum was built because
Bitcoin wasn't sophisticated
enough to build more
applications on top of it.
So Ethereum was built because
Bitcoin sucked and
for some reason, Bitcoin's worth like 60
times the amount and
it makes no sense.
Yeah, I think the common sense answer,
I think the obvious answer is the right one.
I just think it's the first one that more people know about.
Yeah, and that's it.
I think like
even though the first one
it's less sophisticated. Yeah, I think people just
don't understand crypto like including me.
So like anytime something cool with the blockchain
happens, I think people just attribute it to
Bitcoin, even though it probably has nothing to do with it.
Yeah, for sure.
Because I'm sure if you talked about NFTs to most
people, they'd be like, oh, the Bitcoin thing.
It's like, no, it has nothing to do with Bitcoin.
I don't know that until I go deeper and like started looking
at it. So I don't fucking know.
I keep thinking like maybe I should just
like start investing hardcore in Ethereum
because I feel like that's set to blow up
soon. But
this is the first time I've opened
my stock portfolio
in like a week and a half
and you know what?
I just stopped caring.
I'm in the red right now. I feel nothing.
It's okay.
Dogecoin is up
to 0.57.
So that means I still have up almost $300
of my initial investment.
Dogecoin...
Wait, is it up?
It looked like it was very gradually
trickling down.
It's trickling down right now.
From the last time I looked at my portfolio
it was at 0.5 last time I looked.
Now it's at 0.57.
Wait, what is Ethereum?
I'm trying to find my...
Okay, here's my
Ethereum to Bitcoin. I don't care about that.
What's Ethereum to USD?
Show me Ethereum to USD.
Ethereum is 1,796 currently.
It is...
Okay, it's...
It had the exact same bump
as Bitcoin did. They move almost
in lockstep.
On the 14th they both had
a pretty substantial little jump
and then hold and then like an equal drop afterwards.
That's why I think
people just
equivalent all
crypto stuff with Bitcoin. That's why
all the coins, all the altcoins
seems to just mirror it.
I don't know.
This is not legal financial advice.
I have no fucking idea what I'm talking about.
I'm just looking at tiny graphs on Robinhood.
It is literally
just that when people are
investing in one crypto
they are likely to invest
in others at the same time, right?
Is that why they move together?
I feel like cryptocurrency
reminds me a lot of Linux
and open source in general. It's totally open
so everybody can make their own versions
of it, but that just makes it so complicated
that most people don't understand.
It's like trying to explain
to somebody the difference between
Linux Mint and Debian.
Aren't they Linux? It's like, yeah,
but they're different in this way.
It's like trying to explain the difference
between Gabogubu and Dubugaba.
It's like, you know,
some people just don't understand what these things are.
Including me.
I just know that they're different. I don't know how.
Hey, guys, what's going on?
Hey!
We're talking about stupid shit.
We're talking about Bitcoin.
I sold all my Bitcoin.
Oh, you fucking fool.
It's going to go to the moon.
You fucking paper hands, paper hands.
It's going to...
I think it's going to crash sometime this year.
If it's going to crash, I want to be there when it happens.
What's GME at right now? I haven't looked at that.
Maybe down to like 30 or 40.
GME is still at 200 bucks.
Holy shit. You want to ride that rollercoaster?
Yeah, GME like fully recovered.
It makes me so mad.
For reference,
the money that I made
back from this latest Bitcoin rally
made up for about half
of what I lost in GME.
I was hoping it would fully recoup it,
but I would rather recoup half of it
than wait for a crash
and lose everything like I did last time.
If GME
tanks again, maybe I'll buy some.
There's apparently more life
in this fucking...
Whatever.
I would say something, but
what the fuck do I know?
I sold my GME at 50 bucks,
so don't listen to me.
Obviously, I'm an idiot.
I was saying like trying to understand
GME is like trying to understand
why a slot machine lands on all sevens.
It just seems completely arbitrary.
I mean, I know that the
second rise had to do with
the previous
president stepping down and a new one
taking over, but I have
no clue why that would cause the company
to quadruple in value.
What's so special about this guy?
Maybe he's a good president,
a good executive.
I think before he became the president of the company,
he bought a fuck ton of the shares
and then I know
they landed a big deal with Microsoft.
They got a big cash
infusion for Microsoft and now they have
this partnership where all
Xboxes sold through GameStop,
they get a cut of all digital sales from
that console and shit like that, so there's
a big deal they're working on right now.
Okay, that makes a little more sense.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah, I don't fucking know.
Money is dumb and I hate it.
I mean, I love money,
but I hate how much I love it.
I love money, but I hate markets.
I like markets
for non-essential
things.
I think markets are good in the abstract
when they're not tied to
an inelastic
demand, things like
food and healthcare.
What are these things you're saying?
I'm talking about
I love rubber bands.
I'm doing Voshism, I'm doing market socialism.
Vote for Biden.
If I use
words big enough that I've heard on live streams,
people will think I know what I'm talking about.
I'm sorry, I don't have an opinion about that.
Vosh hasn't done a stream on it yet.
I won't.
I refuse.
Unironically, there are tons of people who think like that.
I know, I know.
For a minute there,
I was on a Destiny kick and then a Vosh kick,
but I'm over it.
I haven't even been keeping up with my favorite
breadtuber, Big Joel.
Big Joel?
Big Joel, I love Big Joel.
Big Joel and Destiny got into a big fight.
That was pretty funny.
I didn't watch the stream,
but I saw Big Joel's tweets about it
and Destiny seems like a huge asshole.
Destiny was being
a huge but
he was just sort of...
As far as I remember,
it was Joel having a take
on something and Destiny
they had a back and forth
and they disagreed whatever, but afterwards
Joel was like, well, that was that
and I don't agree with Destiny
and Destiny said Joel was a fucking
scum-fuck piece of shit for
saying that on Twitter afterwards.
Like he's a lying scum-fuck
and I was like, Destiny,
you are using words that are so
overblown for the situation all the time.
I saw the tweets
that were posted afterwards and it seemed like
cause he was trying to be conciliatory
on stream and then he got off and said
this sounds so... I guess if you want to
care about your fucking CD player
or something, I think there's something like
you know what? I'm talking about this
and I realized that A
it meant so little to me
that I barely remember the circumstances
and B, I don't give a single fuck
so I...
I'm invested in Big Joel
I'm pro-Joel and anti-Destiny now
so I'm committed, I have a team
I've been going back and forth on Destiny
I mean, for a while there
I thought after that big row
he and Vosh had about
where Destiny just seems so
unreasonable and so unwilling
and I was just like
you piece of shit
I don't like you now
and then I watched another video of his
where he was like
converting like a
right-leaning person's
perception of... That's old Destiny
That's where Destiny is good
Old Destiny was good
No, it wasn't old
It was a very recent stream
So almost like people are nuanced
and you can agree with certain positions
and disagree with other positions
I mean, that's like
if he's talking to a right-winger
then obviously he seems good
in comparison but then he talks to
like a socialist and he's like
but actually, you know
Deadly Force should be used
by the state
by the state in support
of capital or whatever
It's just that I feel like
his methods of
being the way he is
speaks more to
right-leaning people
and gets them to engage with ideas
they wouldn't otherwise engage with
more so than like other
like Worsh
Worsh does it as well but
when Destiny talks to
a right-leaning person
they're more likely...
Is Destiny the first stop
on the alt-left pipeline?
I think for a lot of people he is
because like
the whole John Tron thing
got a lot of people who are just fans of John Tron
and not political in any way
to like
at first they were mad at him
but if they actually watched it they'd be like
oh John, that doesn't sound right
then they start to doubt
the people they idolize
and then that gets a lot of people thinking different
If I can't trust John Tron then
what's left for me?
Well, I was so hesitant to like
hate on John Tron
at all, I didn't really do any of that stuff
and he was funny
cause like it's John Tron
cause it's John Tron, like he's not a bad guy
like he's a funny guy
he's just a chubby funny guy
He's not technically a white nationalist
he just says the things that they say
He would never say anything terrible
he can't like
he can't have like any like fucked up ideas
or anything
because if he did
that would mean that such things
they're like deeply ingrained in our culture
in a way that's like invisible and insidious
and that would be fucked up
It would
So I think Destiny has
has worth in that
aspect of like moving people to the left
generally on a lot of other things
he's kind of
an annoying asshole
He's a lib, it's literally just the problem
is that he's a lib so he looks good
in comparison to right wingers and bad
in comparison to lefties and like that's
it
So when he's talking to
a MAGA kid or whatever it's like
he got the dunk in
I don't think he's like a terrible person
but it's like
stances in
like no but I would
early on
hate Destiny as a person
because of the way he would interact with people
and that's not a good way to hate someone
you know like you should hate someone
having
disagreements but like being able to
have fun with them anyway because they're
kind of he's alright
when he's a human being
he's not like the worst person ever
like I've flipped flopped on
the extent to which
I hate a person
like Destiny and like you know what
ultimately he's just a guy
I shouldn't get too worked up about
Destiny this or that
Exactly
I just I reached a point
I reached a point where I had
heard enough I had heard enough
fucking debates on the internet
I know everything already
I unsubbed from all the debates
I blocked all the recommendations for them on my
YouTube and literally the next day
I felt better because I didn't see
bad ideas anymore
I was like oh my god
this is a great idea
all the time people spend
listening to debate bros on twitch
would be better spent
investing in bitcoin
doesn't take that long to do that
you should take the more
time you spend investing in bitcoin
the better your results will be
I promise
I just I just see instead of seeing
Destiny and Vosh stream recommendations
on my YouTube I just see like
every episode of best of the worst now
I'm like ah life is good again
this is great
can you block certain channels on YouTube
yeah you just like click the little dots
on the thumbnail and you go don't recommend
channel and it's like okay
I've never done that
but I might start doing that
it's incredible because every time you see like some
stupid viral video that like somehow got back
in the algorithm you're just like never show me this again
what really bugs me is twitter
twitter has started recommending me
like topics
it didn't use
did you install the better twitter plugin yet?
no I'll do that right now
I'll do that
it keeps recommending me
it tried to get me to follow Elon musk
as a topic the other day and I have never
been so insulted in my entire life
I have never been more disgusted
um
you can tell it to not
recommend you that topic anymore
but it will continue to recommend you other topics
I think the only
the only like weird thing about the better twitter plugin
is that when it blocks stuff
it doesn't like get rid of the space
it's just a gap of like
what would be there and it's just blank
which is kind of weird but it's also good
because it gives you a moment to be like wait a minute
you can appreciate that the software is doing something
what am I doing with my life right now
I'm just like scrolling for the last 15 minutes
and now I'm just there's just nothing there to distract
my brain I realize what I'm doing I'm like
I have better things to do in my life right now
so it's kind of a power move in disguise
yeah
better twitter hide retweets
refresh oh it doesn't even need to refresh
wow there's nothing here
it's all gone
your entire time on it just destroyed
better twitter is
is just nothing
yeah that says a lot
it's a better version yeah
makes you think thought provoking
uh
oof
Gib did you forget about daylight savings time
I didn't forget I was
I was having a wolf I was wolf
pilling my parents
I don't know what the fuck that means
that sounds terrifying
that sounds terrible
you know wolf peck I must have talked about it before
no it's a band
like a funky like
contemporary funky comedy
not comedy but like really good musicians
um and
I don't think you've ever mentioned this before
I've definitely mentioned it but maybe it didn't stick
because it wasn't that interesting at the time
but like wolf pilling
is when you show people
wolf peck live at Madison Square Garden
concert and then they go oh
oh it's so cool
and good and then they love it
that's
that's how I was doing that I was busy
oh I
I clicked over to it and there's a guy
going into
a little saxophone and oh yeah
like okay
oh it is a tiny saxophone
it's him and
he's he's plucking he's plucking a violin
no no it's a mandolin
I think
oh okay
yeah that those are
another guy I'm not sure
what his name is
but I know these guys from from youtube videos
I found them I was looking at music
music's cool
wolf peck is great
they do lots of instrumental and funky
and soulful
stuff that's wholesome and cool
and they're very very very talented
go listen to the wolf peck
it's like wolf peck
but not
oh he's he's really going he's really going
on that mandolin
oh yeah
they're having a battle oh they're
they're battling oh they're riffing
okay
I get it so we put that on the tv
and my parents were like wow
like what years this is
1970 because like
you know music these
days sucks
they couldn't even believe it was 2019
culture death
yeah yeah yeah
I've never
making real music in the year of our lord
it's because it's like
my parents they don't use youtube
and so much new cool music
is on youtube but it's not like on tv
they would never see something like wolf peck ever
but people like me who are hip and trendy
do see it
I'm all in the know on the cool
new bands that are around
like wolf peck and
loose coal and
stuff
damn
you must be popular
no
despite all my music knowledge
despite everything
my existence is meaningless
ah cringe
but also based
what else
before you showed up
we were talking about
all our secret projects and shit
and um
shit like that and not saying anything
because they're too secret to be discussed
yeah it's a great topic for a podcast
super interesting
did you see my little Clarissa animation
I made
it was on twitter
she gets a gun out
I just thought that was nice
but if you haven't seen it
I will grab it
I need to learn to animate so bad
oh wait
oh I see it
oh yeah
I wasn't feeling so good over the last week
so I didn't really
manage to do anything
but I just picked up
procreate on ipad has
like a animation assist thing where each layer
becomes like an onion skin for another layer
so I just
did a little thing and I was like yeah it's pretty good
I guess I still have like skill in that area
the follow through on the holster is really good
oh yeah didn't you like study animation
like at school or something
like I got a degree in it like or something
oh my wow
weird
it's almost like I have
should be incredible
but I'm not I'm just sort of alright
hmm
the
it's good
follow through
did she get shot in the head at the end?
yeah she does
damn
I wasn't sure if it was her
shooting her own gun and being like
or okay okay now I know
I have been
I have been I think
I've been more productive this week and the reason
why was because I have
I had a game of Noida
that went really really far
and it took me a long
I spent like a day and a half just like
having the most
the most the furthest game of
Noida I've played and when
when I finally died I was like
I'm sick of this shit
uh no more
and I haven't played Noida since
and it's good
because you could that shit can
eat up your whole day if you let it
that's video games
I mean that game
it took me it literally took me like
30 hours and I think I just stayed up
for like 30 hours straight
oh my god
just becoming just becoming a Noida god
uh uh
by the end I had like
I had these like teleporting wands
with like modifiers to make the teleport
spells like have really low duration
so I would just hold down
the button and just like
machine gun out like short
teleport spells that would just make me like
like across the screen like
so I could just like shoot across the
entire world
uh in in in like
a minute but like
because like you can't really control the direction
I you're like spazzing around
the screen you're like up down left
but like generally
sort of making progress in a left word
or right word or upward direction
uh
and uh
just going around and like shooting like
I had a wand that would shoot out like a big
like shotgun spread of black
holes that would just eat like
all the terrain in front of me and I was just
like going through these caverns
just like
just like just annihilating
like literally annihilating all the terrain
in front just like just just just going through
the world just erasing it behind
me it was pretty cool
um but then I touched some polymorphine
and I died uh which is
pretty much the only thing that can kill you
at that point in the game uh and that's
what happened wow sad
sad yeah
boy but I'm
but when I but after after like 30 hours
sunk into it when I died I was kind of like
I'm glad like thank
you I'm free I'm free and I
hate this game now uh
uh for a while anyway
uh my the spell is broken
uh
for how long
all I had to do oh it turns out all I had to do
uh to break my noida addiction
was just indulge
it so hard
that it uh
that uh I don't know
things just fix themselves
for no reason yeah
yeah basically it's like
cigarettes you know
you gotta smoke all these cigarettes now
you gotta smoke the whole
you gotta smoke the whole carton
and then that'll teach you
kid
that's definitely how it works I've saw it on TV
oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I uh I
found this um
well I didn't find it somebody
posted it and I was like oh that sounds like fun
um it's a
geography what is it
online dot satara dot com
it's a it's a guess
we'll find where the country is
on the map every single country
on the earth and click on it
and you get three tries before it just tells you
where it is and if you get it right
immediately it it's like
bright it goes white but if you get
it wrong um it becomes
red and you have to fill in the the entire
world and I played this
and I realized how pathetic
my knowledge of geography of
particularly Africa is
I'm like Africa was just like
you know you don't learn about African
there's so many countries
in Africa and like they're so big
there's no way they're like
the same country they're not
even slightly similar there's so much
you know landmass there
so I went on like a on a
geography learning binge
I went to I went to
just a random like
country in Africa that I got completely wrong
didn't know what it was what the flag was
whatever some of them I thought
were like in South America or like
fucking
Middle East or whatever I'm just I'm done
it was so so embarrassing
and I picked a flag I picked
a flag and then I just
Wikipediaed it and then I just looked
into it and then
I feel like I want to do that for every country
that I got wrong I just want to know the shape of the country
the flag and a little bit about
the culture of it and like the history
yesterday I was looking at
Mali which is
like North
West Africa
and that's like
got a cultural
like story about
like an emperor who
appears to have inspired the Lion King
I'm not sure whether that's true
but he was called the Lion King
he's like the emperor of Mali
of the Mali empire
and he was like you know all that stuff
and that was cool and then I was looking
into like what was the rape of
Africa actually like what happened why did that happen
and I looked into like
how Africa was
divvied up between European nations who were just like
curving up the land to get
resources because of a economic
depression they thought well we'll just
we'll just rape Africa let's do it
and they fought over Africa
why not and they split it up
and that's where some of the weird borders in
Africa that are completely straight lines that's
the Europeans I mean all of it
before before
Africa was like
divvied up into those countries
they had like empires that overlapped each other
there were no like the entirety
of Africa was not
owned by any individual like
country wasn't like split up
which is weird to look at as a map
because it's like there's a big
blob there that is no one's there
apparently there's not even
no borders no government or nothing
just little
smaller blobs that don't even fill the entirety
of the landmass of Africa like what the fuck
I've never seen I've never even considered
that you can have a world where
the borders don't technically like
line up to touching each other
but that's like the ultimate like
if you
if you try to conquer the world and everybody's
got a stake and everybody has a flag and
everybody's fighting eventually all the borders
will touch
it doesn't didn't need to be like
that now this is just interesting I'm just on
a big learning curve learning time
that's why I posted that tweet of me
learning it was so fun
to learn so much I felt so good
about it
I'm on the site
right now
it gave me a bunch of like hard balls
right off the bat
there's so many countries in the world
what the fuck is San Marino
yeah it includes like tiny
islands that are technically their own nations
as well like groups of islands as well
so like
Lichtenstein
Lichtenstein is in the middle of Europe
I think
it is it's between
I thought Luxembourg was Lichtenstein
I think it's between
Switzerland and is that Hungary
oh god
oh god I thought I knew
I thought I knew everything
okay Latvia I know where Latvia is
Netherlands I know where Netherlands is
Luxembourg
it's one of these cities
it's this tiny little thing yeah yeah next to
something okay I'm
I'm a fucking genius
so I wanted to
I would encourage everyone
to go to this link and play this game
see what you know about the world
because it's fun just like
having some reason to look into
something because there's so much information out there
and
learning is fun I didn't know that
yeah you hear
about learning
fucking Bulgaria
Hungary
Slovenia
these aren't real
they're in the Eurovision Song Contest
and we always lose
UK always loses the Eurovision Song Contest
because they hate us
what the fuck is that
it's a
a song contest that is
it's like the Olympics
but for singing and in Europe
it includes Russia and Australia
so it's like
Europe's got talent
I guess Russia is Europe
it just like stretches all the way to
other parts of the world
Russia's so big
Cyprus
yeah Cyprus
oh it's a tiny little
why is Cyprus
considered Europe
it's like south of fucking Turkey
yeah Turkey's in the Eurovision Song Contest
as well
I guess Turkey is considered
part of
the Middle East slash Northern Africa
why is Turkey
not part of Europe
but Cyprus is that's insane
the only ones in Africa
I remember getting was Egypt
South Africa the Central African Republic
for obvious reasons because they just
tell you where they are
and then like Algeria
and the rest I didn't know
what the fuck is Andorra
that's sound oh
I saw Avatar
I remember Andorra
Europe why I know where that is
because it's funny
okay it's between France
and Spain
then we'd be like talking about
things that nobody can see
well that's what I do every fucking day
when I wait okay let's check out how Bitcoin's doing
oh 57874
yeah our podcast is really good at those kind of things
actually wait I wanted to go down
I wanted to go down because I sold
ooh 866
I keep forgetting Chad is in Africa
I thought Chad was like in the Middle East
I know
I mean I know that one
I know that one because it's a funny name
some of these
these European countries
are made up I don't believe
in
no that's not Slovenia
that's Bosnia
Herzegovnia
okay sure
Slovakia
no that's Moldova
Italy
that's uh
that's like
I don't know I give up
I give up too hard
United Kingdom
never heard of it
I know that one
Bosnia Herzegovnia I just clicked it but I forget
Switzerland BAM
Albania um
I'm like
fuck
I'm like almost done so I got okay
Vatican City done Estonia
no there I've been there Austria
it's one of these two yeah there we go
Czech Republic okay it's the other one
Iceland
done Ukraine I know that one
Ireland BAM
55% I'm a fucking god
I'm a fucking god
of geography
here wait I'll post
Eleazar
put my map
in the episode so they can see
so they can see how good I did
at geography
is that just your that's more
yeah just your okay yeah
you can do like um yeah
the North America South America
different areas I did the like the entire world
thing and I got like yeah
I don't know 13%
the first time I was like oh god
embarrassing
I'm sure I would do
I would probably be pretty good with South
America
I would I mean
yeah the Middle East and Africa
I would probably struggle with and like Southern Asia
I have two fucking knows
who fucking knows about all these
I just have one big country like America
you know
why not just make one big
big old big old country
that's bigger and that's better
in my opinion
your ideas have merit but I don't like
the cut of your gym so you're gonna die
now
solid
to follow
what the fuck to follow
to follow oh I actually got it in the third
such a place
it's an island in Africa
no it's an island near
fucking Indonesia
I see
Vietnam I know that
I actually
don't know where
Vietnam is exactly or like what it looks
like
it's just the low channel and it's on the coast
oh okay
that makes sense
um
alright
um yeah anyway
let's move on from
where is the country
thank you all for learning with us today
yeah yeah thank you all type in the comments
how much you've learned go learn something
and then come back and say I learned this
this is an educational podcast
here before someone said I learned Ben's
bad with Bitcoin
no no no no you're gonna you laugh
now but the dip is coming the dip
is coming well here's here's the thing
if you do one thing and I do the opposite at least
one of us might get rich
hmm that's a good idea for a podcast
you guys just always do the opposite of everything
each episode someone's always
right and you call it the always right podcast
if you
always right
somebody yeah one person
that'd be so bad like one person buys
tons of Bitcoin the other one
wait doesn't sells it doesn't buy
it doesn't
buy something else
it's like one of us made the better investment
one of us was right
Christ you can either buy
or not and if you don't
and it goes up you feel
sad
wait okay well they would be like okay
one person invests like
I don't know maybe a thousand dollars
into Bitcoin and the other
person just has a pot of like a thousand
dollars USD
and then
yeah yeah you just you start with
a pot that you pay that you
set aside for yourself and then
once one
sells when the other buys and and vice yeah
you could do it it would be great
uh
the PCP the only podcast where we
have ideas for better podcasts
on our show one ends up rich
and the other ends up poor and then
the rich one buys the poor one
into servitude and then
let's play channel
and then and then well
and then they get a new guy in to be the
new other guy
he's got to buy in his own pot and then
the goal and you know whoever wins
that contest buys the other
two and it's just like a rolling ball
and like each time
a new person ends up owning all the other
ones until they become
a multinational corporation yeah
and then and they start a let's play channel
and then they start a they start
a service they start like a like a video
streaming service like Polaris or something
or a network
some shady some shady fucking pyramid
scheme yeah the pc pyramid
scheme the pc pyramid scheme
that's right that's right
ah
um how
how far are we in we're an hour
and should we start voicemails
I don't mind
uh I don't know
if I have anything you just you just got here
I just go yeah I don't I don't have
that much to talk about either oh yeah
there are yeah I'm floundering
fucking gorillas you ever heard of
gorillas the band
oh I thought you meant
the apes
the primates no no these are
two dimensional
they're these big
man
beasts
they're pretty crazy
oh favorite primates favorite primates
say
um
favorite primates
yeah
there's so many to choose from
gonna have to go with human
probably something like a
maybe like maybe like a lemur
is a lemur a primate yeah yeah
monkeys and apes and all that
lemurs are pretty cool
lemurs are yeah I like lemurs
because I think monkeys
and apes in general are pretty ugly
but lemurs like just look like a
they're sort of like a cute like
cat looking thing so I think they're like
less off-putting yeah they're sort of almost
squarely
yeah and they're in the Madagascar
film
I don't I don't like monkeys
they're they're kind of gross actually
they are yeah okay
all right I got that one candy valley thing going on
you know they do
they do
predictably um my favorite is the gibbon
mmm
I didn't see the text on this game
yeah that's me
Mikey going to get his gun
just
the way they hold their hands up
he's pretty good
such long arms like whoa
I gotta put them somewhere otherwise they'll drag on the ground
do they not have tails
no gibbons are like
they're like teddy bears
that's pretty good
he's got his fucking like ice climbers face
yeah he's got like a
like a built-in parka
built-in
just reminds me of all the way
back in the day on the furry
episode of the pzp
where one of you guys said that my persona
was an orangutan and I've never forgotten
I think that was me
I think it was you actually
because you're lanky
I know to this day I'm just like oh no
this is why I can't ever go outside
no one wants to see the orangutan
in the store
I'm sorry
orangutans
I promise it's not because
you're as hideous as an orangutan
I'm pretty close though
look at these guys
they love each other
incredible
I need to find my orangutan gf I guess
oh these guys
God look at them
ew
this is what you see when you see me
I thought they were bigger
they're so short
there are probably like different types
I think the kind of orangutan that have the
weird like flesh
like side head
things
maybe I wasn't thinking of an orangutan
what is king louie in jungle book
what kind of monkey is he with the really long arms
is he an orangutan
he's just an idealized disney orangutan
and not the real nightmares
we have to share the earth with
why do some of them look like this
what is that going on there
that is incredible
I feel like it might be an alpha male thing
like the alpha male grows those on the side of its head
and then everyone else is just normal
is that really what happens
like a lion's mane or something
maybe some different types
I'm gonna go learn some stuff
hashtag learning
this is just a learn podcast now
look at things the viewers can't see
and talk about them
the name orangutan means
man of the forest in the Malay language
man of the forest
in what language? in Malay
Malaysia
flanged male bornians
Sumatran and Tapanuli
okay so some orangutans
are called flanged
which means they have the flange
okay okay
the flange look at this
this guy
these are the same type
adult male
and female Tapanuli orangutans
so I think it is a male female thing
that orangutan has a sick beard
I'm gonna give him that
pretty powerful
hmm
you know I'm turning around on this
I wonder if this is where ginshers came from
hmm
oh wait a minute look at this
okay these ones
are flanged in an unflanged male here
oh it's like
circumcision
some of them have their flanges cut off
and then they lose sensation
oh no
are you just saying that
where are you reading this
no yes some orangutans
they do facial circumcision
it's like a
they've learned how to use tools but only for that
yeah some
orangutans are the original
Hebrew rabbis that invented the practice
actually
oh
that's where it comes from
we're learning a lot today
and
yeah I can't
I can't really make out a clear rhyme or reason
to like which
ones of them are fucked up in the face
they're not fucked up
they're just big
I mean compared to the other face that's an improvement
let's be real
we have mumps
a little bit
control f
flanged
okay
adult males may develop distinctive cheek
pads or flanges
younger males do not and resemble
okay so
I don't think it's all types of orangutans
males get the flanges
but only the males get it
and like in some
strains of the
that is bizarre
I wonder what the evolutionary advantage of that
is that cause it to stick
okay okay they may exhibit
males become sexually mature
around age 15 they may exhibit
arrested development by not developing
the distinctive cheek pads pronounced throat
pouches long fur or long
calls I don't know what a call is
until a resident
dominant male is absent
the transformation from unflanged
can occur quickly
flanged males attract females in estrus
with their characteristic long calls
which may also suppress development in younger males
what the fuck
are you fucking kidding me
that doesn't sound real
what you're what this is saying
is that in a fucking orangutan tribe
one like the fucking patriarch
orangutan has a flanged face
and all the other males are just like
they go unflanged and then if that like
top flanged guy
dies then like one of the other guys
is like I'm the new daddy
now and then his face will
fucking transform
and then you giant rat
how
becomes the new giant rat
how that's like that's like if humans
like there was just like one muscular
guy and if he died someone randomly
in your town just became muscular
wait look at this this is insane
listen to this
unflanged males
wander widely in search of estrus females
and oh my god
and upon finding one will force
copulation on her
the occurrence of which is unusually high among mammals
females prefer to mate
with the fitter flanged males
and seek their company for protection
non ovulating males do not usually
non ovulating females do not
usually resist copulation with unflanged males
as the chance of conception is low
resident males may form
consort ships that last for days
weeks or months after copulation
homosexual behavior has been recorded
in the context of both affiliative and
aggressive interactions
holy shit
so is this like we officially
learned too much on this podcast now
if you don't have the flange
then you're basically
an incel orangutan
yes it's literally
virgins and chads it's real
it's just biology guys
that's what we've learned today
guys if you're a chad put like flanged
in your bio
if you're flanged
if you're flanged all the
fucking bitches
want your dick and if you
if you're unflanged you fucking form
a fucking roving rape gang
or you have to kill the flanged
you gotta kill him so you can
become the new flanged
I wonder if
that happens I wonder if
because I know in like silverback
in silverback tribes
like the younger males
will like challenge the silverback
for like dominance
I wonder if that happens in orangutans
is it weird that nature
literally puts a target on the face of the
alphas of orangutans
like it just leads your fist
leads your fist directly
well that's why there's such chads
because like they
you know the only way to be the coolest
is to be
susceptible to like
assassination
that's like the power move
his chad hitbox is twice as big
flanged grow
what the fuck
I'm trying to find
Ben you said you played so much noida
you just couldn't stand anymore
we're overdosing on learning right now
to the point where I don't want to learn anymore
no we could always learn more there's always more to learn
okay I'm reading about
their social life
adult males are dominant over sub adult males
yeah okay
orangutans will form traveling groups
between different food sources
consort ships
between an adult male and a female
social grooming
is uncommon among orangutans
well that's good
this knowledge makes the plan of the eight movies
so much more scary
they might just be like serial rapists
but at least they don't groom
each other
you wouldn't find them on a discord
okay it seems like
maybe they don't
really form like big
tribes so maybe it's not
like one
flanged male
like sort of dominates
the gorillas have like the one silverback kind of like dominates everything
I think orangutans
like more live on their own
so maybe it's not so much that like the
they start out in a jungle by them
they build their house
and
they kill creepers
all man
they go to the nether
and they play minecraft
they play some minecraft and monkeys
orangutans play minecraft
orangutans disperse
and establish their home ranges by age 11
females tend to settle close to their mothers
while males disperse much farther
but may include their natal birth range
within their new home range
they enter a transient phase
which lasts until a male
which lasts until a male can challenge
and displace a dominant resident male from his home range
both resident and transient orangutans
aggregate on large fruiting trees
the fruit
yeah okay
so they have like individual little areas
and then a village where they all eat fruit
they all kind of
individual zones that are theirs
but they all sort of like
they all sort of consort with one another
in like a wider range
are you saying they all get on jungle twitter
and fight each other just like we do
they all
yeah which is way cooler
as god intended
exactly
I don't know so what do we think
has this made us more or less inclined
to return to monk
it's a real mixed bag I think
yeah it's
their strengths and weaknesses
I like
relatively low levels of testosterone
interesting
I like that they just kind of like
they hit
they hit like adolescence
and then they're like well I'm out
and they just go and like find a little like
tree clearing and like this is my now
but like they still kind of like
hang out
with like you know
orangutans around and they have like neighbors
and like oh hey
can I borrow a cup of sugar
it's the equivalent of having
full diamond full enchanted
diamond armor
all this learning about
orangutan society really makes that first
gift with the heart wipe kind of insidious
oh yeah that he's an
unflanged
god he's manipulating her
yeah
orangutans communicate with various sounds
males will make long calls
to attract okay by call they mean like
an actual like they're yelling
what else would they be
get on like an hour long phone call
I don't know I thought maybe it was like a term
for some part of their anatomy
that like humans don't have
like a waddle or so
I don't know maybe
males will make long calls but they'll attract females
and to advertise themselves to other males
what
just to let them know like hey guys don't
don't fuck around I'm here
these are divided into three parts
they begin with grumbles climax
with pulses and end with bubbles
what did you say
I said the call
begins with grumbles
climaxes with pulses
and ends with bubbles
both sexes will try to intimidate
conspecifics
cons intimidate
with a series of low guttural noises known collectively
as the rolling call
when annoyed an orangutan will suck in air
through purse lips making a kissing sound
known as the kiss squeak
mothers reproduce
mothers produce throat scrapes to keep in contact
with their offspring
what
they
my son you haven't
you haven't answered my throat scrapes in months
what are you doing
are you eating well
infants make soft hoots when distressed
orangutans are also known to produce
smacks or blow raspberries
when making a nest
okay
so they just make a bunch of weird
a bunch of weird
sounds all the time
they're fucking kissing noise
they just sound like freaks
that's gross
they are freaks
they're demons
they're deem forest demons
they don't want to return to monkey anymore
so tom that's you basically that's you
by the way
I've just become more and more subtly insulted
by ben's comment from five years ago
I read this and I
uninformed by all this information
I read this and I think Tommy Oliver
yeah you know
what can I say
he's been known to
produce smacks or blow raspberries
when making a nest
you know I mean
yeah
he caught me
he's been known to begin with grumbles
climax with pulses and end with bubbles
hasn't everybody at least once
just me
it's relatable
it's like
orangutan relatable comics
is like oh that feel when
that feel when your mother
is throat scraping at you
oh god
I'm trying to
I'm trying to force copulation mom
I'm not flanged yet already
oh are you flanged yet honey
no mom
I'm working on it
I'm finding a dominant male to challenge
god
this is fucked up
this is too fucked up
ehhh
learning
voicemails
yeah save me
ok
wait voicemails might be even worse shit
yeah it just so happens
that all the voicemails are about orangutans
and there's a complete coincidence
never ends
do you have them open are we ready to go
oh yeah yeah yeah
you gotta look at it
you gotta look at the voicemails
there's more than one page
yeah let's
let's keep a brisk pace up on these
please
alright the first one
is munchie crab rave
are we seeing this
ok 3 2 1
go
I had just finished chucking a bang energy
it was a new flavor
power punch it tasted like the sweetest
syrup you could imagine
I thought I'd take a look
at munchie's channel
we live some old memories
we watch an episode of arm retrieval
only to see
it's all privatized
lost to time
like slime
like permanent rain
like pseudointellectual vlogs
magenta filters on them
I'm not asking for an apology
I'm not asking for forgiveness
I just want an explanation
that you're
you're talking about munchie's channel
I don't know
anything about that
we're not in charge of it unfortunately
in fact I didn't even know the whole channel was privatized
I didn't know that arm retrieval was
privatized I didn't know that
I learned that
but
Ethan's channel does have
a cool
thing from it
you can find that
munchie just didn't want
his stuff online anymore
that's as much of an explanation
as we can give
yeah that's
pretty much all he said to any of us about it
it is what it is
yeah
I think munchie's experiencing what we all were
happy we didn't
because we were like seven years older
of our entire teenage life being on the internet
for everyone to see
just hurts
I guess that's true
yeah
I would probably not like to see
some of the posts that I made
on like accounts that I had
when I was like
yeah
oh well
it's his content
it's his content to do
what he likes with at the end of the day
yeah
okay next one is called
misbendering
not a huge deal I just
want to talk
okay three two one
go
so I think Ben was kind of
dismissive on the podcast last week
when he was like
he misgendered this person on
Twitter and they
were like hey my pronouns are in my bio
I didn't read your bio because
if you called them she
that's because
based on either the way they look or their actions
or something you assume
they were female I guess
and it's like a fucking
it's a fucking meme to be like
did you just assume my gender
it's nothing but
if you do assume someone's gender
because of the way they look or the way they're acting
and they're like
that's not correct
you know that
can be upsetting to people if
they think
they're being perceived as this other
gender and demonstrably
they were because of
the way you referred to them and I don't know
in cases like that I think
you do have to have some kind of
compassion for other people
I think you should probably
apologize in situations like that
to give a sincere apology I would have to
feel remorse
why would I feel remorse for a simple
honest mistake
I wouldn't so
there we go did I make a mistake yes
do I feel bad about it no
not really
sure
there was no malicious intent
sure there was no malicious intent
but like
I think the issue is the response
when you make a mistake of
something
it's fine to have made the mistake
so long as you say oh sorry
just any indication that you
I acknowledge
that I did make a mistake
I acknowledge that
I just think it's like
I don't know
good polite
to say it
I didn't want to be polite to this person
I know but like
cringe though
little cringe
I don't
just don't think so
I think it's pretty
value neutral you had one
tweet worth of context for this
person and based on that
tweet which was completely gender neutral
and the profile picture which seemed to be
if I recall like it was pink it was pink
it was like some character right it was
some sort of it was pink and it was a
pink character and also they
had not not that this makes
it any less of a mistake because it was
but like they did the reason why I assumed
is because they had a pink
avatar and they had
they had like the two female
symbols like interlocking
in their bio
like the I guess it's the lesbian symbol
or something two female things
like linked so you know
this is why I assumed it wasn't a
it wasn't a Ronius assumption it's a fair
assumption to make there was a
mistake made I think
people's problem with this interaction
why we're still talking about it three weeks later
is because your response seemed
dismissive and not
like
actively
apologizing
I think the thing is this person was not
but the thing is that the person who was
accusing you wasn't trying to be like
oh by the way you're mistaken
it was like you just
basically
did a hate crime feel bad about it
and like when you're putting the back foot like that
it's like fuck that
it's not even that
it's not even that it's that
I just
I think an apology
an apology
you give an apology when
you feel bad about
something you did and you want
I mean there's there's a there's a there's like
a sincere reason
and you can do it because you have
realized that you were in the wrong
and you want to express
that you have changed
right or you can give an
apology because you want to
reconcile with someone
and you want to let them know
that you are sorry so that they will forgive you
and
one I don't feel any remorse
for making
a simple honest error
I do I I don't feel bad about
that and I hate
this person and I don't care
if they forgive me
therefore what is the what would be
the justification
for making an apology I can't think of one
I can't
I can acknowledge the error
which I did my response did acknowledge
that I was in error I feel like that
is all that is called for
I disagree but I can't
I don't know how I would frame my
I don't know how to say it
I think the problem is optics
just I mean I don't I really don't
care but just because we have the class
I really don't care either it's an optics issue
because you already had people making assumptions
negative assumptions about you during this
discussion that you were like some crazy right
ring person
and by not like immediately
capitulating to like
the gender question to just reinforce those
assumptions where if you would like
actually made a response like oh I'm sorry
I didn't mean that like it probably would put everybody
who had made these assumptions like
challenge those assumptions and made them
slightly reconsider even for a second
day apologizing would have done
wouldn't have done anything in the grand scheme of
things but like in this micro
exchange that for some reason were all
really focused on
it probably would have been a better move
from optics perspective
to be more
transparently apologetic
well I mean if if
by that you mean that
I would not be receiving
voicemails saying um you should have apologized
then yeah apologizing
would have prevented that one thing I
would would say is like
the
disagreement you had with this person was based on
the other thing you said not that you
um
you know misgendered them that was just an extra aside
um I think
it's
to
to you know stay true
to you know yourself and say well
I don't feel remorse so why would I need to apologize
I don't want them to forgive me
it's
nah I can't
I can't think of the right way to say this
I'm gonna I'm going to like make
the wrong point and then you're gonna get the
right idea I need to like write it down
but like it's very subtle
God
I'm stupid I hate being stupid I hate not being
able to quick wittedly
think of an entire argument
out of nowhere
I feel I feel I feel pretty
rock solid on this I feel like
based on based on what an
apology is and what function it serves
one was not necessary in this
situation
by definition I have
I've laid it down
I'm lodged
my logical brain
has uh
it's cracked the case
I'm so fucking angry
with myself I can't figure out how to say this
God
alright next voicemail if I can
say and then come back next week
okay okay
okay
fine
next one is I will never fucking forgive you
well three
three two one go
you fucking fools you fucking cretins I hate you so much
I'm really behind the podcast but
fucking I left the voicemail
talking about mind sweeper saying oh mind sweeper
online has no guessing mode where you won't have to
guess and then the whole like rest
of that episode and then the next episode
talking about like oh mind sweeper you
have to guess you're always going to
come into scenarios where you pretty much just have to guess
and no that's literally Ben is like oh
oh mind sweeper is a game where you
make educated guesses no if you think that's
what mind sweeper is you just don't understand
what it is the vast majority of the time you are
very far back exactly where the bombs are
it's very far by we very specific
scenarios where it's just impossible
to figure it out exactly and you can
write an algorithm to prevent those scenarios
from happening when you generate
a map and that's what no guessing mode is
oh my fucking okay I tell you these things
because I care because I care about you
and I care about mind sweeper
and what do you do you dash my hopes
you crush my heart you stab me
in my fucking soul and you say no
mind sweeper oh you just
you don't heed my words you just
go along playing mind sweeper
in the dumb stupid infuriating
way where you do have to guess because you
don't you just don't listen why don't
you listen what's the point of this guy
what's what's the point
fuck you mind sweeper great
fuck you okay two things
why don't you listen to the podcast
this guy would this guy would really
get'll appreciate the bonus
episode yes patreon.com
slash the procrastinators
where the newest mind sweeper
challenge play mind sweeper
and it's good okay we like
mind sweeper
I like mind sweeper now on I appreciate
it now on a deeper level yeah
so please
donate to the patreon
and watch that but also
the no guessing mode I've tried it
um I don't like it
there's something annoying about
the first one like I haven't tried it
you go to no guessing mode you click
is like an X this is the first
thing you click and you actually
cannot click anything else you have to click
this space so often it opens up
like a three by three
space and from there it's like
oh god I don't know how to figure
myself out of this one
it's so it's so small I like
the freedom of being able to click randomly
and get lucky to get like a bigger
start or to go to all four corners
so that when I get to those places
you know the likelihood
that I have to guess
at the very end is minimal
I can do
expert mind sweeper now quite easily
and it's fun
and
you don't mind the
the fact that sometimes you have to guess
the no guessing mode is just worse an experience
because even though you don't have to guess
uh it's less
I don't know it's less fast paced
I have to start really slow all the time
I like going to the corners first
it's just good it's just easy
uh based
uh based though
what
yes
next voicemail is called
store brand Eleazar
three two one go
my name
is Eleazar
I live
in Argentina
I set the league
of name fuckers
in application
and made a nine
this isn't
the first time I tried
oh
how many tears
I've cried
uh
based
damn
imagine getting rejected from the league of name fuckers
yeah that's pretty rough
the seediest
most slovenly
low lowest gaggle of
miscreants
imaginable
better luck next time
elia zedie
uh next time
next one is okay I'm better now
three
three two one go
okay I expunged that from my system
I saw that Ben realized the error of his ways later
and I just hope that you all can become people
who find wisdom in the numbers
patience in the minds and solace in the free spaces
because mine is
is a beautiful deductive puzzle game
just like picross these are two
titans that deserve the love
and respect of
everyone who has a computer
these games
are fucking
based
thank you
we also play picross in that
patreon bonus episode
it's true
there's a little bit of bonus picross content
as well
if you're into that sort of thing
dude squares
like wow
that was a good bonus episode
that was a lot of fun
um next voicemail
is called uwu crimes
three two one go
I'm sorry
I didn't mean to murder you
uwu I just
have a little bit of bloodwurst
relatable
this guy is seething
and coping
and I am
here for it
okay next one is called ben apology
three two one go
I am extremely
sorry I
forgot to do
something very important last week
I know what it is
which was to remind ben to please catch up on one piece
ben this is your weekly reminder to catch up on one piece
thank you bye
it's so hard though
reading is just so hard
but you've kicked your noida addiction
now you have time
should you spend 30 hours straight
catching up on one piece this week
instead of 30 hours playing a noida run
I'm on a kick though
I'm on a really good kick of getting worked on
on my secret project
I'm gonna try and stick that out
I'm gonna try and ride that
ben you are a pro-crastinator
you cannot be working right now
Drew I have
defied my nature
I have temporarily put it aside
I think
it's gonna be
one piece though
I'll get around
to it
imagine the feeling of slaying this person
for actually
not giving him the ability to continue sending
these voicemails
he just wants
for me
next voicemail is called
FYI
3, 2, 1, go
Konnichiwa
this is Samurai-sama
so
Samurai-sama
notice some confusion
in the right
of this
Samurai-sama want to make
something clear
Samurai-sama
is a man
ok?
Samurai-sama character
he
Kasady-chan
ok?
until next time
fuck off you
ben no sentosa
sayonara
samurai sensei
that's like a zetsubo sensei
but different
did we make that mistake
did we
I don't remember
I don't think so
I know that Kasady is a she
and Samurai is a he
because Samurai is a character
by which I mean he's a real person
who dogs me
in real life
I guess I might have made
I might have made that mistake
because when I think about it
I'm not sure how to
with the
using pronouns to refer to a character
played by a trans person
who is the other gender of the character
there are no pronouns
there are no pronouns or just
what even is a pronoun really
when you get right down to it
what really is a pronoun really
when you get down to it
what even is
a
pronoun crastinators
the pronoun crastinators
there it is we did it
we got there
the pronoun
okay whatever next voicemail
is called radcon4
over one year later
three two one go
there was some confusion on this
Ben and co the day that
we recorded that thing about
radcon4 was the
anniversary of it
yeah we're over a year lads
I knew that
that was the whole point I thought
or I knew
it was around I didn't know
whether it was the exact one year anniversary
but yeah this is the
the pronoun
cast
yes the pronoun cast
about radcon
that's what they're talking about
next one is called victimless crime
in quotes three
two one go
this is a message to
younger or more impressionable listeners
of the podcast who don't know better
and this is coming on the show before but
don't shoplift
don't fucking do it it's a joke
if you do it you're gonna get caught
and you're gonna get fucked really bad
if you do get caught
it's gonna happen the people in this podcast
are fools
they're naive idiots they don't know what they're talking about
it's a joke don't actually
shoplift don't be stupid
alright
I mean definitely don't
getting caught would be really bad
so definitely don't get caught
if you get caught shoplifting
you have done it wrong
and you have done it you have fucked up
I don't condone getting caught
shoplifting
yeah I mean I would never do it
because I am scared of consequences
and I would assume
it would fail
like it's not a thing
I would have pulled victimless crime
I think
the implication here is that the victim
is the person who will get caught
and get in trouble which is true
that is probably the main victim
of shoplifting
the real crime is getting close
yeah
the real crime is punishing someone
for stealing from a faceless corporation
I would feel super bad
if I was like shoplifting is morally
neutral
well I will do it then
and then they did it
and then they got caught and there were
terrible legal consequences for them
that would just be awful and terrible
and not worth it at all
I would say that podcast told me
to do it and their mom gets all pissed
I knew podcasts were the work
of the devil
I don't know how young
and impressionable our audience is
I feel like most of them
are like
super young
they wouldn't all be late teens and up
obviously
don't shoplift
if it's
difficult
just
I think what we've said in the past is
what we've said in the past is that
shoplifting from a large corporation
is not a morally wrong thing
to do it's just a shame
that you can get caught for it and that sucks
I wouldn't condone it
myself I know Ben might
because Ben's like more into it
than I am
I would say that it's morally neutral
it's neither good nor bad
well yeah
I would just
I've never been caught
shoplifting so
I don't even know
what would happen
it probably depends a lot
on who catches you
and what store you're at
and whatever
so I don't even know what the consequence
would be
I feel like in certain stores shoplifting would be so much easier
now because everybody has to wear masks
so they can't identify you and a lot of stores can't chase
after you so what are they going to do
some kind of mask came and stole our shit
most stores can't chase after you
the only one who can
arrest you for it is if there's
a plainclothes police officer on the scene
the store cannot
apprehend you
and hold you against your will
or like tackle you or like that's completely illegal
they basically have
the store itself has like
no I don't know they might hire
someone who is like a
I think there are certain credentials
some people can have that do like allow
them to do that on behalf of like law enforcement
but like
a store employee can't a normal store employee can't
like
seize you and stop you from leaving the grounds
and like punish you or whatever
they simply don't have the authority
so I would say if you do get caught
shopping probably the thing to do
is try and lie your way out of it
and if it doesn't work just run
and like
almost in most cases
they will simply have no recourse
again I have never had to do that
so I don't really know and I guess I'm talking
out my ass
getting in trouble with the law is scary
because it's the law
so for that reason I wouldn't
suggest trying it
yeah
the potential consequences are usually not
worth a couple of dollars you might save
on something getting a rap sheet in the first place
getting a criminal record is super bad
and definitely not worth anything
you can shoplift
I think if you're the sort of person
who is able to listen to the procrastinators
podcast
then you're probably not
in a position where you need
to shoplift
really probably okay
what do you mean by that
well you have access to the internet
you have
time to listen to such a stupid
podcast
this is like you're doing
the same bit that that streamer
did that girl who said like
if you have time to watch my stream
you have time
to donate to me to donate 5 bucks
to subscribe
instead of that I'm saying you probably don't need to
risk a criminal record
I'm not saying donate to the podcast
I think it's a better message
I'm saying that
I would say
I would suggest
that anyone listening go out
and shoplift right now and then donate
whatever they saved
to the patreon
is my
I don't know
I mean
I'm sure there are people
listening right now who are in economic
distress
I'm listening and I'm in economic distress
that'll be true
for a lot of people
but I mean those people still
it would be probably
it wouldn't help
them to get fucking arrested
like the amount of
money saved
sometimes proportional to the
largeness of the thing you're stealing
like if you try and steal a fridge
that's gonna be a little difficult
if you try and get the steal like a candy bar
you can probably put it in your pocket
steal small
things that have a high price
per ounce
like fucking diamond jewelry
yes for example
things like cheese
things like cheese are like
pretty high
in a grocery store
I would say cheese is small
high in calories and relatively high
costs per weight so it makes a good thing
that you can just slip into your pocket
and pretend you didn't realize you had
or something like
like steve
vanilla extract
or a tiny little bottle of vanilla extract
might cost like 12 bucks
but you just pop it in my pocket
and it's like well I just won't pay that
for instance I mean I'm just
thinking off the top of my cup here
not like I would know or anything
not like I thought about it
all these examples sound like things that you would
probably eat on the daily
they're so specific
they're so stevia's keto
no it's not
cheese and stevia both keto how interesting
hmm
like I said I haven't been going to stores
I just order my groceries now
but if I did I don't know
probably wouldn't be worth the risk at this point
um yeah don't do it
I guess that's my
probably don't do it
probably don't do it but if you do
I won't think you're a bad person
but it's probably not worth it most of the time
okay there we go
next voicemail
is bring back tectonic improvements
and gamers tavern
three two one
go
hi I'm calling to say
that you should bring back tectonic
improv and gamers tavern
okay and as you well know
that one concerned
caller is equal to one
billion listeners easily
which means you should really
take this advice
very very seriously
okay again
gamers tavern and tectonic
improv
okay one done an episode
together
um
I know tectonic was with cheesy that one time
no I don't
I think tectonic was on
twice
the one tectonic was on
first
gamers tavern might have also been on that one
I don't know
yeah I remember but yeah
those guys are cool
we could have one of them back
recently I haven't had
guests in a while
shocking realization
three two one go
guys I think the nape fuckers
are gay
like they just sound really gay
no
I don't know it could just be me but like
I just get like gay vibes from them
that sounds
very silly
that's ridiculous listen to yourself you sound
you're insane you're crazy
you don't know what's happening yeah don't you realize
they're all female
right
gay
what a concept
next voicemail is called mark
24 three two one
go so if you guys haven't already
you should totally check out the game ever hood
it's like psychedelic undertale with
guitar hero bullet hell battles that's
fucking sick
is that the dug tenable
no no it's ever heard
yeah I thought he said that but ever hood
is another thing okay what's the dug
tenable one never heard
well done ever heard never yeah
this looks like a rhythm
game it's good I see the under
I see the undertale reference
reference
is this a video game reference
oh it is
looks kind of neat this looks kind of cool
I've heard the fuck about it as well
wait I'm gonna do like a
something I'm gonna do a thumbnail
show me a
yeah this is flowery see
that's flowery that's flowery right there
honestly yeah this is a little
to undertale actually
it's unapologetically undertale
this is it almost
seems like the amount
to which this is referencing
undertale is like part of the joke
or something
I just think it's a marketing strategy
I think it's a marketing strategy maybe
I mean people are talking about it so it
clearly worked it's like undertale
with guitar hero with guns
it's like even the font for the game
it's like hey it's the undertale font
basically but we just it looks exactly like
undertale of yeah
which is fine they even have I guess undertale
is like a they do have someone looks just
like Gino the art for this guy
is Gino it's that's Gino
it's ridiculous our boy
okay pretty good
all right
is undertale like
has it become sort of a
sort of genre like a pseudo
genre no undertale likes
are those a thing
I was that's what I'm thinking are they I mean
they are this one clearly
I feel like in a way
yes but then it's more that the
undertale and like Lisa
and earthbound are all part of the same
earthbound are
G genre earthbound like
would be
weirdo weirdo RPG
yeah I it's probably
that like that genre
of weirdo RPG
is the is the group
but then like undertale is such a like
influential
piece of it that it has
like it's its own influence
I say that it's had a lot
of influence on other like
subsequent games in the
name I got a name so for
earthbound likes that are undertale
adjacent we call them
other tale
mmm that's good
I dig it that's that's cute
that's cute
this game looks kind of this game looks
kind of neat though would you sacrifice
your humanity to receive
immortality yes
everhood trailer yes of course I would
in a heartbeat answer
100% defy humanity
you I mean part of you part of
being human is to be mortal so like you
just necessarily give up
now that see the thing they
they say they don't tell you is that the
part of humanity they take is
your IQ
they take all of your IQ
oh no
no I'll just
become flanchless orangutans living
forever cursed to wander looking for
they take your flanges away but you can live
forever
who would want to live without flanges
this is
this is the plot of my new other tale
game that's coming out that I'm working
on is it's going to be like
you start you're a humble
little rice farmer
until one day
a fucking a fucking goblin
goblin shows up
a goblin appears
and he steals all your equals
your rice he's skilled no he steals
all your IQ points and he scatters
all 100 of your IQ
points to the far corners of the
earth and you have to go get
them
how do you even get the first one
here that's the toughest
one that's the toughest one
you gotta that would be a funny idea
the game gets easier as you go instead of harder
yeah the first thing is the most difficult
part of the game the final boss
is like learning how to walk again
like the
the first one is maybe like
you just like gotta like mash
one button
just pound a button like a thousand times
and that's the only thing you can do and eventually
the game's 50 hours long but the first
point back and now you can move
jabbing one button over and over again to get your first IQ
point that's like right in front of you
then there's just two hours of the rest
of the game
that mischievous goblin though
the IQ goblin he's just like
haha I've got the points
I will send them away
he's very
sinister
next voicemail is called
the entire thing
three two one go
I've had was the
voicemail kind of wish
the pcp
fellas would do a super best
friends and just make a video
telling everyone they
don't enjoy slash
they can't work with each other
anymore instead of trying
to drag this podcast
along off
legacy alone watch
as I ingest this entire
cock
hey yeah
was that a cookie I sounded like a comment
that may have been posted I haven't
read yet it might be
it sounds it sounds like
sort of an amalgam of all
the of all the sorts of
comments that say like
I used to I used to
like the podcast more the podcast
should just die
or whatever I think the
obvious thing missing from this analysis
is that we still
can work together just fine
we're still here the podcast
you're listening to we're here doing it
we're doing it right now we're making
it happen we're proving all the haters wrong
does anybody has anybody have
any dissolutions at this point that Nate and
Trixie and munchie don't
like being on the podcast
is that still unclear
what I feel like
a year of doing this should make it pretty obvious
what is the pcp
if not a podcast
persevering after all
the person ever less
podcast
nevertheless we persisted
mmm
uh this guy
this guy is a fucking bitch
and I hope he enjoys that cock
okay
same
yeah next one
is called bringing it back
three two one go
at work today a man
tried to circumcise himself
he didn't finish the job
it's really alarming
agreed
that sucks
well
why would you do it to yourself
get a professional
well you can um
you might uh it might be
you know you can always
it's good though
it's good to go to your genitals with a knife
I mean what's the harm
because I mean at least
at least it hurts
he didn't do enough circumcision
right but that's okay because you can always circumcise
more
the real danger is doing too much circumcision
because you can't
reduce the amount to which
you were circumcised later
so I would I would advise that if you
want to be circumcised
do it in little pieces
just do it like cut like just slice off
a piece of your foreskin
and then come back with a knife
and chop up the next like the next millimeter
of it and then just
every time the last one heals
why would it make a sound
that's the sound of the butcher knife
hitting the hitting the
what you call it the chopping block
the cutting board
chopping cock
chopping cock you might say
um little baby steps
baby steps
baby 12 steps to the perfect
circumcised cock
my new novel
book
self-help book
available on amazon
I wish
next
next voicemail is called
animorphine time
3, 2, 1, go
Ben why aren't you in the
animorphine time podcast
uh discord yet
there's a discord
I guess like I guess like I didn't know there was a discord
I guess I could join the I haven't listened to it
in a couple weeks
uh
I could I I bet if I asked they would let me
be a guest on there maybe I don't know
they had
one they had
they had a guest
or a pair of guests
that were really annoying most of the time
they're fine but there was one episode
animorphine time that had two guests
who I just couldn't stand
they were it was a married couple
and
the wife
just kept shrieking
every time her husband
said anything the husband was very much
like very dry since if humor
deadpan delivery and every time
he said anything like
I wouldn't say darker edgy
but he would he would be like sarcastic right
every time he said anything sarcastic
the wife would just start shrieking
I hated her
I hated them so much
so my goal would be to be better
than them
I feel like you'd be like hey can I talk about
animorphine you guys on a podcast
we did this whole big video about it
there was some sexism
and edgy jokes in that video
sorry you're cancelled
they would um
you know I saw
I was randomly recommended a video
from a youtube channel
that was talking about animorphs
and he sort of offhandedly
mentioned your lecture and put up like a thumbnail
it wasn't a huge channel
or anything it was um
I think it was recommended
to me after watching a James Tullos
video someone else was just
talking about
someone else did like an animorph some
like series
retrospective you know
one of those
um animorphine time is pretty funny
uh I don't know
I don't know if they
follow me on twitter but like I don't know if they
know who I am or what the pcp is
or anything
but whatever
ok
next voicemail is called
large nose man
makes his move
3 2 1 go
hello
it's me
the large nose man
I'm calling in
from the outside
of Nate
Bestman's house
today's the big day
I'm going to make spicy
salts look like a joke
when I'm done with Nate
Nate
oh no
hey
large nose man is rooting for you
oh wait spicy salts
I thought he said something else
I thought he was talking about something else but uh
no instead he was talking about the worst
possible thing
very funny very funny reference
more more power to you
uh spicy salts was
the uh well
it's like it's like a
the race shooter
or a serial killer
who like inspires like copycats
like he he's like the
the platonic model
to aspire to he's he laid out the
blueprint for the rest of us
the rest of us need only
need only perfect his
formula
based
next voicemail is called
I Have Solved Mario's
Picross 3 2 1
go
I have developed a full proof method
to beat Picross all you need to do
is get Mario's
Picross on emulator or with the
switch SNES collection
and then before
you pick a square you just
make a save state then you click
the square and if you blow up
we'll then just load your save state
and pick another square and just keep doing that until you win
and that's how you
solve Picross forever
I'm a genius
that's so much smarter than you Gib
uh
I can't believe I've been
bested so easily
you're all like oh well you can
logically deduce that to this square
and this square no
detective shit
waste of fucking time
I'm here doing detective work and that guy's
going in guns blazing and getting the job done
instantly with no problem
you're playing LA Noir and he's
playing Grand Theft Auto
yeah
if you yes
uh
next one is called Easy Money
3 2 1 go
ayo can this dick
fit in your mouth
hmm
I don't know I didn't know how big it is
it was an audio show
most dicks probably
could
just geometrically speaking
next one is called Hi Ben
3 2 1 go
I
am going
to fuck
the best guy
ever because
his butthole
is supple
just like his brother
wait
oh the fucking modulator
okay
next one is called Hi Ben 2
let's try this again
3 2 1 go
that was way better
the modulation just added so much
sound quality
and the dog squeaking as well
the squealing
the squealing mammal
don't incentivize those kinds of things
did you hear that shit Tom
oh oh yes
oh yes
the next one is called The End
and its own reward
and okay the email attached is called
an end to cluster punk at
sad.time so
I'm prepared to cry
3 2 1 go
could enjoying the process
be its own reward
I think yes
yes
I think
I think this is
the end
of the bear
suck
if you want to call it that
how far we've come
to an end
in so short a time
in fact the only things that are good
are things that stop immediately
and they never come back
I wonder what he's going to do next
just like
my wand
just like my teleport wand in Noida
that shot the really short teleport bolts really fast
that made me go
you get an end really fast
and that makes it good
next voicemail is called
bacon bacon surprise
3 2 1 go
why
he's 10 feet wide
and armed to the teeth
cut this big bacon
bastard
best to the bear and me
okay I was wrong
it's not over
it's just totally wrong
that was only the beginning
so the bacon man
is that what
it's a bacon man
is it like a redditor is that what they mean
I think the bear
has the edge
being a carnivore
wait bears eat meat right
I mean I know they eat honey
they eat fish out of the river
and they'll kill humans
sometimes
bears eat anything they don't fuck around
okay
even spaghetti
even spaghetti but not macaroni
cause they've never heard of such a thing
I know that feel
next voicemail is called
the monopoly man
who remember promised
was it 2,000 doge coin
to whoever made the best
league of nate fuckers video
so let's see what he has to say for himself
3 2 1 go
ho ho ho
this is the monopoly man
fuck are you
money
I'm here to tell everyone
that whoever becomes president
will not only get 2,000 doge coin
but also the rights to nate's body
the league will entrust him
with his health
and thirst
ho ho ho
this was the monopoly man
good luck everybody
such a long pause
I thought it was over
it's like he had to check his script
to see that
he had to turn the page
ho ho ho
well I guess the stakes
have been raised
next voicemail
is called
btorish from
umineko
3 2 1 go
hello it's me v3j
from umineko I'm here on my disney interactive
let's sing microphone for the we
I'm here to ask you have you read my video game
if not should die
okay goodbye from umineko
btorish goodbye
thank you
no
I have not read your video game
I'm sorry
btorish
umineko
what is this
I know
I've heard of it
I think it's a manga
it's a japanese dojin
soft visual novel series
okay
it's what the
it's what Beatrice is from
it's what that name is from
but where's the game oh wait it's a
yeah yeah visual novel video game I think
I like that being on a we
microphone that was good
yeah I
think this caller might be
disappointed because I don't know
anything about it
lol
uh guys
I thought there's
why did everyone shut up
yeah I thought there was a problem with the call
I was like everyone's one saying anything
what the fuck okay well I guess
next I guess next voicemail
I thought that awkward's pause out
no no no no
there was another one too there was another
long awkward pause before
keep it all in
it's all part of the experience
you know who cuts their awkward pauses out
the pizza party podcast they do
we can't stoop to that level
it's dishonest frankly it's despicable
say in the comments if you
watch only for the awkward pauses
I need
my I appreciate naturalism
naturalism in my podcasts
I need to feel
the pain
the pain that the podcasters
are experiencing
uh the next voicemail
is called ben taint
three two one go
did you know come is keto
yep well for me
that's not good enough
I must have Nate's come
so I may enter the most
true ketosis
with Nate's come
I can make the best
keto gummies
all out of commies
but there's still
one problem
I don't have Nate's come yet
to get it
I'll have to join the league
of Nate fuckers
they're
they're still working on
getting it
I think the bureaucracy
the administration of the league
is too much red tape
they can't get anything done
they all have
different ideas
of how best to fuck Nate
they can't vote on anything
if they all came at the same time
but if they all came to Nate
at the same time Nate doesn't have that many holes
it's not even gonna work
it would be
all the dicks
they would just clog
they would just bump against each other
it would be like
the thing with mr burns
and the diseases
and the germs too many germs
that they can't get all squeezed through the door
so there's so many
Nate fuckers that Nate is completely
protected
complete virgin
they just can't fuck
they can't fuck
I wonder if Michelle is in the league
who do you think started it
I don't know
the league seems to want to cuck Michelle
but I mean they could
she's like the shadow
there's like a hooded figure
Michelle's part of the Nate Chastity brigade
there's a hooded
maybe there's a hooded figure
who appears only in hologram form
who leads the league of Nate fuckers
secretly Michelle under the hood
I don't know
we'll never know
this really is a tales gets trolled
so I gotta go now
so many faces
do you ever wonder what it's like for that one person
every week who's not subscribed
who just stumbles upon an episode
and gets to this portion
what the fuck is wrong with these people
I have
nothing but disdain
for anyone who isn't subscribed already
every episode is someone's first episode
I seek to pun it
I don't know if that's true
I'm not sure if
maybe
no
no no every episode is someone's last episode
that's what that's the actual
that's definitely true
the turnover rate
is just astronomical
next voicemail is called
Phrygian Meetup
3 2 1
go
so when are we getting the files from the meetup
it's been a year
maybe you could just dump them somewhere
I don't know
on that subject though
being some of the guys from the meetup are getting back together
and having our own radcon next week
so PCP fans
we'll have some new lectures for you soon
20 bucks says I get mine out before Ben
if you do it next week
yeah you probably will get it out before me
if you're fast
I mean good luck
and godspeed and
I am praying for you
yes
cool
people do lectures
people doing their own lectures is cool
I like it
we should find
the meetup footage
I need to talk to Victor somehow
Trixie has it right
she was the one who was collecting all the footage
at the end of the day
I guess she must have it
I don't know
what a fucking nightmare
we're gonna have to
bang on the door again
we've been banging on the door
she just doesn't give a fuck
we're gonna have to reach out to Nate
and or Victor and just be like
look
you guys both have a head on your shoulders
you guys have a sense of responsibility
please help
I'm not even sure what it is
that she's got
well just to find out
you mean the film from the meetup
the meetup behind the scene
thrust the behind the scene stuff
okay
yeah
because at the end of every day
because she brought
her desktop to the house
and we would just dump all the footage
that we had onto there
because she was supposed to be putting the behind the scenes up every day
big mistake
that was the plan
things did not go according to plan
nightmare nightmare nightmare
um
okay well
we'll try to do something about that
maybe
do our best
next one is called
mind sweeper gone rogue
three two one go
demon crawl
is a mind sweeper
roguelike
demon crawl
oh let's see
fascinating
oh look it's mind sweeper
but there's treasure chests
let's get
what makes it a roguelike
and not
just a series of mind sweeper levels
nothing
i think mind sweeper itself
could be classified as a roguelike
it does have perma death
that's true
and it's procedurally generated
interesting
looks vaguely interesting
yeah
next voicemail is called
digital monster x
and there is an image attached
um i'll post it in the
on the thing
it's a picture of some digivices
i guess
there we go
dude those look sick
yeah these are like
is this the new version
that released like last year
i didn't even know there was a new version
but it's black and red
that's my favorite color combination
because i'm an edge lord
it's got bielzomon on the cover
who's fucking murdered leomon
it was fucking sick
the one in the bottom
who rode around a motorcycle
who was dressed in leather
and he fucking murdered one of the kids
didgymon in cold blood
and she cried about it and was awesome
is it the one with the big blue wings
and the gun
okay the voicemail
digital monster x 3 2 1 go
an english version
of the digital monster x was just announced
so what's the difference between that
and the version 20 of which tom has
well first of all the english version
of both are gonna be way cheaper than the japanese counterpart
so now you have two options to pick from
however
here's the thing with the version 20
you get a raise 2 digimon at a time
and you have 10 aches to choose from
evolution branches
meanwhile the dmx only lets you raise one digimon at a time
you only get one egg
but the evolution tree and all the things in that branches
far more than any of the version
20th eggs
and finally it has like an rpg quest mode
so if you're fighting a 20th versus a 20th
or an x versus an x
they have a little mini game you can do
so there's a little bit of skill in fighting
but if you're fighting a 20th versus an x
not so much
so if you do a royal rumble you're probably gonna want to stick
to all 20th's
or all x
and I believe the version 20th
is the more beginner friendly of the two
however if you do the 20th
you enjoy it
but you want something new I then highly recommend
checking out the x when it comes out
I gotta watch a review
on that um
digimon youtubers channel
what was his name
oh god I don't remember
I can't remember his name
it's not out yet
but when it is
digimon digital monster
x is a brand new digital
monster virtual pet which is focusing
on x antibody
digimon
I don't know what that means
several mechanics from the
digimon pendulum x series
also make a return such as the xai
system this is gobbledygook
yeah there's a ton of
digimon vpets that came out in Japan
like one version before
these re-releases came out in the states
there's a lot that I don't know about
all I know is I just
went to Amazon to look for one and then they're related
there was the detamers d-arc
that I had
like three of back in the day and they're all gone now
and they're selling used for $573
uh
digimon's were so much money
cause it's like old and discontinued
is that why it's expensive
thousands of dollars worth of digimon merged
that just got lost when we moved houses
back in the day and it really hurts my soul
to know I could like pay off my student loans with
digimon toys but I can't
cause they're gone
oh no
I wonder if, I mean I had
I had an old digimon
from back in the day
it's no way it's worth anything
like the old
pre-pokemon ones even
those are worth a little bit
hmm
maybe I should look it up
the next voicemail is called
well it's just an image link
and this is the image
attached it's a drawing
of a bird man
looks pretty cool
so voicemail in 3, 2, 1, go
telling you that bandits from far away
seek to plunder your fortress
and steal what is yours
what do you do
um
bird, bird men
are warning us that bandits
are going to plunder our fortress
uh
DM I'd like to make a sleight of hand check
to try and steal pickpocket from the bird man
no you don't
you don't say
DM I want to make a sleight of hand check
you say I'm going to try
to pick the bird man's pockets
and then the DM says
okay make a sleight of hand check
did you see what I did there
that's how you fucking do it
you don't
talk in mechanical terms
the DM tells you the rules
bitch
I tick limitarily
lays an egg
and then I make an omelet with it
um
DM is the bird man
sexy
you got the image
oh I guess I have to choose myself
uh okay no
his head is too small
and he has no pupils
he has no pupils I don't mind that so much
DM do I believe this bird
do I believe this bird's claim
or do I find it dubious
okay alright I guess
you can make a sense mode of check
we're not the DM we gotta wait till next week
to know what all these options are
I will
okay my
uh I mean
I don't care I don't care what this bird man says
okay we'll just we'll maintain normal
fortifications we're always on guard
we're always on guard from bandits right we run a tight ship
uh
this is not helpful we all take
watch and shifts at night you know to make sure
that nobody syncs up on our encampment during
the evening we will
redouble our usual efforts
at repelling invaders
bird man you are
you are dismissed
get out of here
no does he have any weapons
maybe he could help us defend
defend our uh our encampment
is he armed? no
does he seem to have any arcane
gifts that could help
I don't want him in the fort
he's not one of us
why are you speciesist
is he who knows
I don't
in this world it's killer be killed
I think he's more likely
trying to pull some kind of ruse on us
well that's why you have to
see if we can leave them first
I dare not say the mechanics name
just in case I set you off again
but
fair enough
I don't believe it
believe it or not
believe it or don't believe it
I'm still like well what whatever
whatever
no
okay that's my take
wait I gotta
roll a d20
I gotta see what I get for my insight
I like it it's hard
it's hard and it's annoying
but I like it when like
I got an 18 plus my modifier for insight
I think
when you do a sense motive check
it's better if the dm rolls
I feel like the roll should be secret
like you shouldn't know like oh I got a great roll
or oh I got a terrible roll
because then you know what's real and what's not
but I mean
we're limited
I feel like it helps with immersion
if the dm rolls does all the rolls
but it also it kind of like empowers the player to feel like
their stats are doing well
if they know what the roll is
so it really depends on what side of the equation you want to kind of
it depends on the roll
I don't do this for like an attack or something
or like most even something like picking a lock
I would let the player roll but for something like sense motive
like
if the entire party rolls sense motive
and you know you get a bunch of rolls
I think it's better if they don't know what they rolled
because then all they know is who believes
and who doesn't
and then all they can do is like okay well
this guy has got a good intuition stat
he's like usually pretty perceptive
maybe we should believe
him because he's more likely to be right
but you never know
sometimes it could be wrong
I think that's the best way to do it
usually an insight
something that's just a character
and two it's like internally
so even just like having the roll be
announced is difficult
like that's kind of like
the struggle with table top is like
even knowing that you
had to make a roll for it at all
is sort of giving the game away a little bit
I think that
if you think about it the numbers
the rolling of the dice
is to offset
the fact that you can't literally
do these things in real life
if you have charisma
like not in real life but in the game
you roll a high number
if you don't know what you rolled
and you have to convince your party
of something
if you don't personally have charisma
but you rolled a high enough how are you supposed to
like you can't really convince them
with your real life stats
I think
that in a case like that
you shouldn't be able to
just like make
I think it's better if generally
you don't like roll charisma
checks to convince your party of things
because then you
if you make a really high roll
then that ends up forcing other players
to play their characters
in a way that they don't actually want to
unless it's like a physical check
that just happens naturally
like if the players believe you or not
it's just a matter of you being able to convince them
at the table
that's a point where the rules
kind of break down
where the rules and the role playing
kind of clash with each other
and you sort of have to choose which one
you're going to prioritize
there
some character just imagining
you have to convince a guard
to let you in
let me in, you want to let me in
and it's like not convincing at all
but they roll a really high number so it works
and then everything seems a little stupid
well at that point it's up to the DM
whether they want to allow it to happen
or not
the DM has the last say
even like in a situation where you roll a nat 20
if it's like I'm rolling
to like fucking insta kill God
like you're not going to get a success on a nat 20
because like with skill checks
a nat 20 isn't an instant success
it's just 20 plus your score
because you can set up a debility check
like that outside of damage
to be like 47
or something insane like that
that you just can't clear
if they were trying to lie their way in
and they just said like let me in
cause you want to
I would probably be like as the DM
I'd say like that's not even a lie
like you just fucked it up
it doesn't matter what you roll
like you simply didn't do the thing
it still depends on whether the roll is
for the
like how good the lie is
or like the stupidity of the guard
in question
I think letting the players roll
even if you know that they're not going to
succeed just helps the game feel more
feels like they're actively participating
you should definitely
you should definitely make them roll
sometimes when there's
like literally no purpose to it
just so they don't know
what's real and what's not
yeah that's a good
that's a good DMing
if you roll a 20 on a strength
and they're trying to push a boulder
it doesn't matter how strong
they roll they can't push it
too big
unless they have like some kind of like superhuman
strength score
but like most normal characters won't
like you can roll a nat 20 on a strength check
and be like your muscles flex real nice
and everyone thinks you look cool with the rock doesn't
it's DM's discretion but I think
if you did that and you roll the nat
20 I might be tempted to be like
it is physically impossible to move this boulder
but it just so happens that it was
sitting on some like unstable ground
which kind of gives in and the boulder moves
like maybe
it depends
there was an interesting like uh like simplified
rule set for tabletop I was looking at
that was based on 2d6's
and it was like under under 7 was
a failure
and 9 was a yes but
so like you succeed at what you have to do
but something bad happens
and then like an 11 or 12 was just a straight success
I thought that was pretty interesting
that is interesting like that's like improv
yeah the yes yes but
that's cool
it's kind of like
I like that because it follows the like the rule
of storytelling that it's not like
it's it's like
what is it like that there's that tray parker matt stone
talk where they talk about
the columbine shooters
yeah the columbine shooter
it's it's not yes and that's the improv thing
it's like
they're talking about like a story has to progress
according to like
and then
because
and then and then and then it's and then
so therefore
you know it's like one one
leads into the other and there's like some sort of
I don't know
I guess it's not quite the same
never mind
next voicemail is called
Sam 3 2 1
go
hey guys
so this is the first time I'm
doing one of these
so my apologies
if
correctly or you're doing good
incorrect format
but I'm in college
and
because of the virus and all
I don't have any friends
pretty lonely
I'm stuck in a room all day
I was just wondering
if you guys had any advice on how to
make friends in college
or how to meet new people
I mean to do it
I hope you all have a great day
I mean I the whole
the whole virus situation is
a little bit
nobody knows how to cope with that
yeah I mean obviously
we didn't have to deal with that when we were
in college because there was no
coronavirus at the time
I mean I can give you the usual
fucking
advice under normal circumstances
it would be join
groups, join extracurriculars
join like study groups for your classes
or whatever
chat with your classmates after class
and I don't know
see what they're up to and
make
not to
I'm going to sound a little salty
but making friends in college is so fucking easy
it's so easy
and if you can't do it in college
then you might as well just fucking kill yourself
because that's the easiest time and you're fucked
uh no
that was a terrible thing
a terrible thing I just said
the thing is like it's easy to make friends
in college because like you have a bunch of people
the same age it's easy to find
like people who are pursuing the same kind of
general goals that you are because
there's tons of like
clubs and stuff but
in the current situation
that's all undercut
the point of college is like it's a bunch
of people of like a similar background
generally who are all
convened together to spend years
doing structured activities
with one another like it's the
it's like the ultimate like
like acquaintance building
engine
uh after school
out of school it's like
nothing is like that anymore
if it wasn't for the internet I would have made a single friend
from 2011
to now
because I haven't I literally haven't made a single friend
in the real world in the last decade
I made
uh I've met
I've met some a couple
people in the real world but like not
yeah mainly I've made friends
that I originally knew through the internet
uh cringe
um
oh man
yeah the coronavirus
with not being able to like
physically be with people
from college is probably
I'm sure the coronavirus
is making it ten times harder
than it's supposed to be so
yeah I mean college makes it
easier but the coronavirus makes it way harder
so maybe it balances out
at the very least if you have like zoom
groups or discord groups or whatever
for your classes talking
those I just really all I can
think of yeah joining clubs
and groups is good there's
one that you want that doesn't exist
try starting one and uh
I would say what happens nobody
shows interest and you're in the exact same
position you're in now so I would say
get vaccinated
early if possible
I know that's not possible for everyone
and then
after you know after the coronavirus
is dealt with to whatever extent it can be
be I don't know
this is hard and I don't and I
struggle to do this as well but like
just try and like be
out of your room
be out in places
I know it sounds stupid it sounds
like what's the point of that like what I'm just gonna go
and like stand somewhere like yes
to a certain to a certain extent yes
you should just like leave your room
and go somewhere
any literally anywhere anywhere other
people are simply for the sake
of being there there's just like a commons area
where you could like get snacks
and just tables like sit and like study
and do stuff like out
of your room I spent a lot of time there and I would just
like run into people I knew from class because like
it was right above the cafeteria so when people would
get food they'd walk by there and I would just say hi
it was a good place to kind of just like
naturally start conversation with people
that you like had seen around
so something like that when the weather gets
better just being outside
if you're on campus like just working outside
doing some studying outside and like
just just kind of like reaching out
to somebody who you've seen in class
and you might have an interest
in striking up conversation with even
if like you don't know
exactly what the conversation is
going to be about just like putting yourself
in the situation even though it feels like really
scary of just like saying hi to somebody
you'll naturally get better at doing it
so it'll be
easier going forward each time to talk to
more people
yeah
I think that's pretty
good advice
I think we've pretty much solved this guy's whole
life now
I think he's good
you're welcome
Sam
let us know how it goes I guess
the last voicemail
I think is called
download ruffle
3 2 1 go
boy download ruffle
it's a flash emulator that can install your browser
as well as your computer
preserve flash as much as you can
download ruffle right now
okay
I like playing the old flash
video games online
so is what I'm hearing
that if you have ruffle
you can play old flash games
is that
it seems to be saying
so it's basically just someone remade flash
it's probably like some sort of emulator
I don't
I mean
what's the difference
yeah flash player emulator written in rust
yeah it just emulates
the flash environment
but it's written
I assume it's written in rust but it probably
works with the html5 so it runs in modern web browsers
without
I mean flash is just a program
flash is just software how do you
emulate software don't you just
wouldn't you just have
written the software again
it's I mean it's the same way you emulate
like a super nintendo I guess
super nintendo is a software
well it's hardware and software
sure and like you're emulating the hardware
and the software that it runs
in order to run the applications
and you're just emulating
the software of flash player
I guess so I guess so
well that's I mean I'm glad there's a
I'm glad there's an alternative
I'm glad there's a plant based alternative
to flash
does this mean I can read old homestuck
maybe
I don't know
wait does old homestuck even exist anymore
I mean the MS Paint Adventures
got like redirected to homestuck.com
so I don't know
actually if all that stuff is there
but I think a few pages have like
you can go to the top right and like
switch to the flash version of the page
like cascade
which is way way better
than the video
on the ruffle homepage they have a
version of alien hominid running in ruffle
you can just play alien hominid on here
hell yeah
that's pretty based
download ruffle I guess
well we're at two hours
and 50 minutes
and eliazar says keep it under three
hours so
I guess it's time to die
we did it
join the fucking patreon
at patreon.com
check out all our
fucking what do we have like 40
30 bonus episodes
there's a lot
the newest one of which is the
mind sweeper pick cross
challenge which was a lot of fun
yeah it was me versus ben
seeing who could be the best puzzle
person
it takes twist
there are twists and turns
and then
send us a voicemail at speakfab.com
if you think you got something
to say
bucko
anything else
I have wait I have one thing
I have one thing
that I do want to mention before the end of the episode
and it is a little personal
project it's not my project
it's a project that I am involved in
and I think maybe some people
would appreciate knowing about it
there is a comic anthology
called the kato anthology
that is being made
they are going to be kick starting it soon
and they are looking for submissions
and I am submitting I am going to be one of the submissions
I am going to be in it
but they are looking for submissions
and they are believe it or not
they are paying they will pay you money
if they print your work
they will print your work for you in their anthology
and they will pay you for it
and you keep all your copyright
and all that
pretty neat
I don't know
comic artists are always looking for this kind of shit
would I be able to
post something
like a lot of ghosts
you could submit
anything you had made
and I don't know
I am not one of the people making it
so I don't know what the criteria is
I mean yeah
I saw you tweet about it but I haven't watched the video yet
I posted a tweet about it
I will put a link
please put a link in the description
to this video
from the kato youtube channel
announcing this anthology
they have like contact information
for like where to submit and stuff
all in there
and I should disclaimer
I am I guess
something involved in the production of it
so this is not
I guess I
what's the word is it a conflict of interest
and if I were a fucking
if I had for a comic artist
lol I would want
to get paid to have my shit printed
so uh okay that's all
goodbye
anything else
no that's it
okay
then I will die
now
goodbye everybody
okay that's the end of the episode
goodbye
bye