Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
The show on the internet about a bunch of people who make stuff talking about stuff.
I'm the best guy ever, and today we're joined by Digibro.
I'm alive, for you, I'm alive, for you, I'm alive, I'm alive, for me, we're all alive.
That's true.
Which after our podcast yesterday, Mumkey, that's a good sign.
I can't believe it.
That's very true.
Though this will be a week and one day when this goes up, but no matter.
Okay, let's get right to it.
Alright people, topic for today, incest.
Uh oh.
We're talking about incest.
That's what it is.
So let me get, let's get some dictionary definitions off of the urban dictionary, of course.
Okay, there's two dictionary definitions that are good for this.
Okay, first one.
Having sex with members of one's own family, fine.
And the second one is, it's very direct, the way the British royal family keeps itself
permanent.
I like that a lot.
One of the few times the urban dictionary was actually funny.
Yeah, they did it good this time.
Well shit, fam.
Let's just launch into it.
Literally, fam.
Oh yeah, that's true.
Very well said.
Um, okay, where do we start with this?
I do want to say that I'm the one who said we have to do this episode because two weeks
ago we had the fetish cast and all the comments were bitching, Mumkey, why didn't you talk
about your fetish is Mumkey?
I said, fuck it.
You know what?
Let's just do a whole goddamn episode about incest so I can just get it all out there.
So I beg completed and got this to happen.
And I was also demanded to be on this by Mumkey.
So Mumkey, since you wanted to, since this is your podcast and you tend to get short
changed on the dialogue in these, why don't you give us the big intro?
Oh boy.
Well, I do have a big incest related story about my personal life that I've been waiting
to tell if we want to just start off with that or if we want to wait for later.
Let's do it.
Now, let's do it now.
Oh, okay.
Okay, folks, this is going to take us all the way back to my freshman year of high school.
The story of how incest changed my life forever in a either positive or negative way that'll
be up to the viewer to decide.
First of all, the question for you folks at home, let's go around the horn.
And I mean, you guys, not the fucking audience because I can't reply.
Do you think it's okay?
And I was under the impression that it is okay after reading Harry Potter.
Do you think it's okay to date your best friend's siblings?
That's a tough one.
Yes.
You know, it's a sticky situation.
Is it possible to do it right?
Yes.
It is possible.
It can be done.
I mean, I think it's definitely okay.
But if your best friend has a problem with it, then it's going to cause friction in your
relationship.
Yeah.
Like, yeah.
My siblings who won't care.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
Fuck my sister.
I don't give a shit.
Well, that was one of those situations.
I was in.
I was a freshman.
My girlfriend was a year younger and we met because I my best friend to, I guess, will
call Harper because I have a Harper Lee book right in front of me.
So my best friend Harper, you're older.
Is it to kill a mockingbird by chance?
No, it's to go to the only two because I stole a copy of Ghost at a Watchman from the
store I was working at because I was like, oh, there's a bunch of controversy.
I wonder if this is even worth it.
And then I never even opened it.
I just have it sitting on my shelf to kill it turns out it's the prequel actually.
Yeah.
Well, I guess Finch a little bit racist, a little bit racist.
It's not actually a prequel.
It's like the original incarnation of to kill a mockingbird that she wrote and realized
it was shit and then scrapped it and used the same characters to write a better book
because in this one scout is like an adult, even though scouts like a child and to kill
a mockingbird.
But enough about that.
There's no Atticus scout incest unless you go to a certain part of Tumblr, which I have
definitely been to.
So I'm dating my best friend's younger sister, two years younger than him.
I'm just picturing Scout now.
You're dating Scout.
I'm dating Scouts.
Very tomboyish.
Yes.
And her older brother, Bo, Bo is, you know, not in appreciating this.
Are you picturing like your imagination of Scout from reading the book or like the movie
version of Scout?
My imagination.
Like this little girl with like a bob cut and stuff.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, you know, me and the girl, we're dating and like, I'm 15 and she's 14.
So she doesn't really want to do any of, you know, the sexy stuff.
Like we can kiss, we can hold hands, we can hang out, but she don't want to touch that
dick.
She don't want to show me those titties.
She don't want to let me go cave exploring if you know what I mean.
So imagine my surprise towards the end of the relationship.
I find out that this girl has cheated on me, not only with my best friend, but with
her own brother.
Whoa.
Dang.
So that's two major betrayals, girlfriend cheating on you and also, oh yeah, my best
friend slept with my girlfriend or whatever the fuck.
They actually fucked them.
They didn't sleep together.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
So that's two major hurdles for you to get over.
What did they do if not sleep together?
Well, that's the thing.
The third thing is, you know, I'm always, you know, you know me, I'm a pushing guy.
So hey, how about you touch my dick today?
Yeah, I don't want to.
I don't want to do that.
So I find out that she gave her own brother a big old handy in the living room down when
the parents are upstairs sleeping, give him a big old handy, make him come all over her
hand, show off those titties.
Me, what does Mumkey get?
Not a damn thing.
I guess she only likes her relatives because I didn't get shit.
I can only assume where this is going.
Because I know where my mind is going is that you jacked off to this image forever, like
ever since this is all you've thought about.
It was heartbreaking and it was demented and I'm still friends to, I guess, Beau Harper
Lee Bow, whatever we're calling him to this day.
And I don't talk to that bitch because, oh boy, do I want to go and I guess I have to.
I guess I have to.
It was, it ruined everybody's life.
It ruined everybody's life.
Because she told this to me like out of guilt or something and nobody else knew.
And the other important part of the story is that their Mum is the most hardcore Christian
woman in the entire world and we would all hang out because every Wednesday after school
we would go to their place like a big group of friends and then they would take us to
church and we would do like the Wednesday night church thing.
And I was already well into my atheist years but I went just because it was fun and we
did not do any of the church things, we just fucked around because it was great.
So I'm like, okay, this Mum is probably not going to be okay with this happening.
So I guess I'll tell somebody who can tell somebody to tell her because I'm not letting
this go by, baby.
Also there was like a speech competition sort of thing through the church where like all
these church people would go to like the big arena area in downtown Des Moines.
Did you do a speech about how this girl gave her brother a hand job?
No.
Is that how you're going with this?
So like by speech I mean like it's different types of performances so you can do skits,
you can do music or whatever.
And me and Harper Lee, we did an atheist duo Christian rap performance and the judges
fucking loved it and we wanted trip to Michigan because we were so good and then right after
all of this emerges and the Mum finds out and fucking places both of them in solitary
confinement and like sets up nanny cams all throughout their house to make sure that their
kids aren't fucking anymore.
And so I lost myself a trip to Michigan and she wouldn't let us go because of this.
Hang on, did you do the rap thing with the girl or with the guy?
With the guy.
Okay, that's what I thought.
Women don't have talents.
I still know the lyrics if you want to hear a little bit of it.
Yeah, yeah.
Jesus the one turned a fish into a ton, turned water into wine and he also healed the blind
by just spitting in the dirt it can make blind eyes work.
If you got a problem he could do a miracle for you.
And that's most of it.
Hell yeah.
The crowd was pumped, they were fucking chanting and dancing and shit and then the black judge
said yo that's some good shit and we wanted trip to Michigan.
And that man went on to be Kanye West.
What were you going to do in Michigan?
So it was like the regional part of the contest and then Michigan was like the nationals where
we would perform our rap in front of like with all the other rappers.
We're like these two pasty wide guys who aren't even Christian doing this shit.
Man what a tale, what a yarn.
So you're still friends with Harper, did I assume you would know if this ever happened
again?
Does he still fuck his sister?
Well the thing is after this came out and the mom fucking laid down the hammer that
girl is now the most sheltered, like hidden from the society, hardcore Christian person
I've ever encountered and I don't even think I could speak to her.
I would have expected the reverse, I would have expected her to go like full fucking
slut or something.
No I think they went pretty hard on her, I think that the parents fucking ended her
life after that shit.
See this is good because this ties into our larger discussion of incest.
No one's life should be you know in a major way curtailed or changed just because they
happen to give their brother a hand job one time.
It's not that big a deal everybody, it's all, we could all relax about that shit.
Well I'm curious right now, I know Monkey's an only child, I have a younger brother, oh
that's right.
Pachi, of course.
Why do I keep forgetting about Pachi?
You've got a younger brother, I've got two younger brothers.
Nate's got an older brother, a younger sister, Tom you've got two younger sisters, right?
So most of us, I feel like there's gonna be a big difference in like the perception of
incest between me and Monkey and Nate and Tom.
Yeah I definitely think so.
I'm sure that's true.
And I also think that it comes like your perception of it is not just affected by like whether
or not you have siblings with the opposite sex but also just like how close you are with
your family and in general.
So I'm very curious to hear- I think I might surprise you, what we'll say, yeah.
I want to know, as I know, well anyway, I want to hear from Tom first.
What do you think of this, because I don't know what you're coming into this with at
all.
Yeah, I mean, I guess as someone who has two sisters I can't even fathom doing that, like
you know, I mean, I don't have any attraction to them, they're good people, I'd go to war
for them if they needed me but I wouldn't do that, sorry.
Well just so we're clear, I mean, you know, only some of us have sisters but we've all
got a mother, we've all got a mother everybody.
See that's where I draw the line.
Not the best relationship with this mom though.
That's true, that's true.
And all that sexual tension dude, you know, it's, uh, shut the fuck up.
Well the thing is, I don't think any of us would fuck any of our actual family but I
think the way that you feel about your family affects how interested you are in incest porn.
So like I'm wondering, Tom, do you like incest porn at all, any of the different relationships?
I don't find any of that particularly arousing or interesting.
I've seen incest stuff and to me it's completely, I guess it's just neutral because my view
on incest in general is that I feel like we just need to stay out of people's bedrooms
in general as long as there's consent, that's fine, I don't really care, it's not my business
and I don't see the harm in it, I think there's way worse things to do than to fuck a family
member if they're both consenting and of age.
I mean, yeah people are gonna think it's fucked up, sure but I don't really care, if that's
what you wanna do, that's what you wanna do, if you can fuck dudes who are women, why can't
you, that seems relatively banal in the grand scheme of things that we've allowed to become
culturally accepted.
So I don't see any sort of controversy about it, I think probably if you wanted to have
a kid with a family member, that's when I'd start to draw the line because then you're
talking about genetic issues at some point.
Whenever I bring that up, people always tell me that like, oh actually it's not really
that common, it's a pretty unlikely thing and you know, at some point, we're kind of
making a calculation, are we prepared to enforce a rule to say yes, you should not have kids
with your siblings because there is an increased likelihood of genetic problems or whatever,
but is that really our business, if they wanna have a fucked up retar baby?
I mean, we definitely let people with genetic problems have kids.
Okay, here's the thing, we let stupid people breed.
Why do we allow that?
Yeah, that's the thing.
Well, here's the thing, I don't think it should be illegal, but I think it's ethically irresponsible,
so I guess you have to make the distinction between what do I find personally ethically
wrong to do and what do I think should be legally prevented.
If you have, I don't know a good example, I don't know if Down syndrome or anything
is hereditary, but if you had something like that and there was an equal chance you were
gonna pass it on to your kids as incest has of a genetic defect, do you think it's also
ethically irresponsible to have kids if you have Down syndrome or something of that nature?
You know, is it unethical to have a child with Down syndrome like at all?
Because that is a person who's alive and can live and stuff, so it's not like it's
like evil to have a person with that and they're pretty much just gonna live their life and
probably not really hurt anybody and die, but they're kind of like a burden on the state
or on their parents, on their parents, I guess, but there's nothing like immoral about it,
it's just like we don't really want to incentivize it, I guess, you know?
Maybe, I guess at the same time though, it's like this is a person who has no say in even
being born in the first place and it's like-
True, true.
You're purposely and knowingly hobbling them with a lifelong incurable condition and like
do you have more responsibility to do something about that because like it's not just you
saying like I'm prepared to deal with the consequences of having to raise a child with
this condition, it's like I am willingly, you know, kneecapping them with this condition
and I know it's going to happen, it's going to make their life more difficult and I'm
gonna do it anyways.
You know, just to make that question even more frustrating and complicated, like it's
not exactly like if you do one thing, you'll have a baby who like might-
Okay, like if you have the genetic potential for Down syndrome and like you have sex or
you have a kid with someone else who is also likely to have that and then you have a kid
with Down syndrome versus like if you have sex with somebody else who that's less likely
and then you don't, it's not actually like you're changing the baby that was born, it's
that you're just making a different baby.
So actually in like the moral implications of that are that what you're doing is you're
sort of just choosing to not give life to one person who would just live a life with
Down syndrome and you're instead choosing to give life to a totally different, separate
person since like, you know, the same sperm won't probably be the thing that impregnates
the same egg.
This is fucking with my head dude, like, this is like a really philosophical way of thinking
about childbirth that I've never considered and it's fucking with my mind.
That's me baby.
It's a lot to think about, it's a complicated multi-layered issue because like the ethical
ramifications of taking a position are complicated.
Every woman you don't have a kid with is a kid you are choosing not to exist.
It's true.
Interesting.
By the way, let me just, I don't mind being totally clear on here, I fucking love incest
in my porn, I'm so all about it, I think it's great in most of its forms.
I like Mother-Son, I like siblings, not as much into Daddy-Daughter, that can get a
little strange.
That's the interesting, that's why I was interested in leading up to this podcast because we've
discussed incest plenty of times in the chat and we were talking about it in there.
You like Mother-Son and I like Daddy-Daughter, but not so much the opposite in both of our
cases.
Yeah, I would like to hear this from both of you because I'm into siblings and cousins,
but when it comes to parents, I think it is horrifying, so I would like to hear both
of you justify this.
It's the fantasy.
I don't mean you're going to fuck your mom, Nate, I just want to know what is, is there
any logical thing behind it?
Before we do that though, Monkey, when you think siblings, who do you want to be the
older one?
Boy or girl?
Doesn't matter.
Doesn't matter at all?
Okay.
Both have their benefits.
I like the big sister.
I definitely like the Onesan or whatever.
Okay, because I'm more into little sister for the same reasons, I think, as I am into
Daddy-Daughter.
What's interesting to me about that, Nate, is, and I think I know, this is the best logic
I can come up with and this is going to sound real gay for both of us, but I'm an older
brother and you're a younger brother and you're closest with Ben, I'm closest with Victor,
you know?
Yeah.
So you're the Daddy and I'm the son in this sort of, in this-
No, what I'm saying is that you would be interested in older sisters because of the fact that
you were closest with your older brother and maybe you've always had, in your mind, what
if my older sibling who cares for me and stuff was actually a hot chick I could fuck, you
know?
Yeah.
Because that's how I think of little-
Sure.
Like, if my little brothers were a hot chick I could fuck, like how much better would my
life have been, you know?
That makes sense to me.
Yeah.
Well, see, that's kind of what-
That's a sound bite right there.
That's what I was going to say that I like about, like, mother and son stuff.
What I like about the mother and son stuff is that it's actually pretty similar to the
older sister thing.
It's that like, okay, so you're just going about your life and you've got a mom and
like, she's a woman, you know?
She's always a woman and that doesn't change and it's like, always below the surface is
this question that like, you know, we totally could fuck.
We totally could fuck if we wanted to, you know?
No, it's not.
I'm trying to say, is that?
I've never-
Well, no.
It means it's possible.
God damn it.
You keep saying you when I think you're talking about us.
Well, I can't speak for you guys, but it's not, you know-
Please don't.
It's the fact that like, there's a woman just in your life all the time and society says,
you're totally not allowed to fuck her, but then you could.
You totally could.
And I'm saying you in the sense of in this fantasy, you know, hentai verse.
And that's it.
Which is similar to like, the older sister thing.
And like, you know, there's like the, it's a little different, like the old, the mom
thing is more like, oh, dad's always away.
No one's here to satisfy me.
I'm a woman.
I have needs, blah, blah, blah.
Then they fuck their son.
Whereas with the older sister, it's more like, the sister, I always picture like Kesha when
I think about this.
Like, oh, she-
She's like-
A black woman?
Kesha is white, dude.
Kesha's white, dude.
Oh.
She's fucking Mick Jagger's daughter.
She's fucking a number sign in her name.
I thought it was a black person.
I think so.
Let me double, I could be wrong about that, but, but like the point is like, she comes
bombing and drunk from the club.
I'm getting a hard no from someone who knows Kesha.
Okay.
All right.
Fine.
Maybe I'm wrong.
But so she comes bombing in from the club.
She just collapsed on the ground.
She's like, yeah, I was out just like clubbing and, and I'm such a slut.
Look at me.
And she's like, you're trying to impress her little brother and little brother's like,
oh, whatever, dude.
And she's just like, no, you don't understand.
Like I do this because, because I want to get your attention, I want to get your attention
because you're always there.
You're the guy who I really want to impress.
And then they fuck.
And that's, you know, I, I, I, uh, I don't dislike like mother son or sister, older
sister, but like if it's older sister in both cases, I prefer if the son is like at
least a teenager.
Oh, yeah.
I can't stand the show to shit.
Yeah.
Like, because it's always those tiny dicks don't do it for me.
The tiny dicks don't do it.
And just like the woman being like just like massive and smothering, like that's definitely
a different fetish is like just wanting to be like tiny and to just be like encompassed
by a woman like how in those ones, it's always like a little show to and then like a mom or
sister with like just giant tits and like a huge thick body that's just like covering
the little boy to the point of like, you know, and that I feel like is a whole different
thing.
That just reminded me that after the fetish episode, somebody did make art of hippo as
Jesus in the pieta and it's really great.
Oh, yeah.
It does.
I don't hippo is listening into this podcast.
Yeah.
I don't know if he wants to be in, but I've gotten the impression he's more into show
to than we are because he seems to like those big women.
So I think yeah.
He likes the big encompassing women it seems like so he can type in the chat if that's
how he feels.
I'm not entirely sure.
Yeah, there you go.
It's good.
There you go.
Okay.
You've got the word the official word from on high.
He's good.
Everybody.
We've got confirmation.
Yeah.
Hey, Nate, I have a question for you since you don't like a mother's son.
I do.
I do like.
Okay.
Well, since you do as a kid, did you watch Malcolm in the middle?
I did.
I did very much because as a kid watching that in the way that Lois would terrorize her sons,
I think that is what scared me away from ever even thinking about something like that
because it's terrifying.
Well, you know what?
Okay.
I feel like with something like that, I don't feel like that even necessarily would have
like drawn me away from it because the whole thing is like, this is like a fantasy.
But like, like what if like my mother was like this, like super hot slut and she needs
sex desperately and I'm a man, God damn it.
Like, you know, like you're putting yourself in this, in this fictional situation where
like if your mother was like this kind of person, then you know, it would be sexy times.
Okay.
You know, so yeah.
So it's like a departure.
So I can see why like seeing a like a female, not role model, but like a female character
or like a mother specifically acting in that way, like as like a terrorizing, you know,
bitch of a mom would, would like turn someone off.
Well, there's that episode where she, she walks around the house topless and I was wondering
if you.
Topless.
Episode one.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure that's episode one.
I was wondering if you were into that.
Um, I remember as a little kid finding it, you know, eyebrow raising like, oh, what's
going, what have we going on over here?
Yeah.
And I remember distinctly, she opens the door and Malcolm's teacher is there and she's
not wearing a shirt and she's like, the teacher's like, uh, no, no, no, she's like, they're
just boobs, lady.
And I'm sure yours are much nicer than mine.
I remember that.
I remember that very nice.
And she's like, no, no, I swear they're not.
They're really not.
I think, uh, well, I'm not that into like, uh, mother, son, but I am totally into moms.
Like in general, like, like, like in my porn, I'd prefer it be like if a guy is hooking
up with someone who is a mom, that's harder to me just because I don't know, there's
a fucking that kid.
There's something like, like, I like to feel the baby inside when I'm, you know, I didn't
say pregnant.
Well, I'm taking it to that place for some reason, whatever I see, whatever I see, like
mother, son stuff, I always have this like weird feeling like the mom is being irresponsible
somehow.
Oh yeah.
That turns me off a little bit for some reason, even though I like the daddy daughter stuff.
It's definitely a bad idea guys, to fuck your son.
Yeah.
Moms should definitely not have sex with their kids unless absolutely necessary.
Important PSA from Nate Bestman.
Yeah, that's right.
Unless absolutely necessary.
I definitely put that caveat in there.
That's important.
I shouldn't have to think what the reason for absolutely necessary would be.
Like if they've got a gun to my head, man, what can I do?
I did have a gun to your head question for you, Nate, but I think Digi wants to finish.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Oh, no, I think I said, okay, Nate, incest question for you.
Okay.
Gun to your head.
You have to get a handjob from one of them.
Ben are your sister.
Well, obviously my sister.
So fuck off.
I'd get a handjob from Ben immediately.
I don't even need the gun.
Don't even need the gun.
I'm just looking for an excuse.
Nate, do you think your sister is hot?
Well, I don't want to be rude to her.
Yeah, she looks sort of like me so totally.
You know, I don't want to be, it's weird for me to even think of her in those terms.
She is a perfectly attractive young lady who I have deep respect for.
That's really the extent of it.
I feel like I know of a lot of stories of like siblings who do end up doing more sexual stuff
like if they're close in age when they're much younger, you know?
Sure, sure.
Me and Victor never did anything like weird together, but we did look at porn as kids
together.
Sure.
Like we would, and just like, I don't know, I sort of tried to teach him how to grind
his cock against the ground, which is what I was doing, but he didn't seem to get it.
But like, I definitely have known lots of sisters who've done stuff like that as kids,
you know?
Yeah.
Lena Dunham, my hero.
It doesn't count if your sister's a fucking baby.
Oh, I think it counts.
That's the thing.
I feel like incest, when you have close siblings and you're all going through that sort of
pubescent age together, it would almost be weirder for me to think of it never happening,
you know?
Like if you're like a year and a half apart from your sibling.
Or even twin-cessed.
Yeah, or even twins.
Sure, sure.
And you're like eight or nine.
I refuse to believe there's any twins who haven't fucked.
At that point, it's just masturbation.
Yeah, they've definitely done something together.
You can't be twins and not do anything.
Because you're experiencing it at the exact same time.
Your bodies are both changing.
Both of you are quizzical about it and you're extremely close with each other, so who else
are you going to share this with?
Yeah, that's the thing.
If you keep that in mind as you watch The Sweet Life of Zack and Cody, it really has a different
narrative that's forming before your eyes.
For me, a lot of my incestuous fantasies come from that age.
Discovering your body and being like, who can help me understand this?
Who is in the best position?
It's not a stranger.
And the schools don't teach you enough.
Society doesn't teach you enough.
You're just quizzical about your body.
Who's going to help you learn about it but your big brother?
Who's going to help this cute little girl figure out?
Who else but Lena Dunham is going to take this burden off?
Why is she so hot down there?
It's interesting.
I have a different approach to it.
I notice in the stories I gravitate to, it's more like the mom notices like, wow, you've
really become a man.
You've really become a man now with them.
That sort of angle.
I get that too.
That's interesting because we're looking at this from very different age ranges.
When I think I like little sisters and daughters, it's just like a lolly thing for me.
I'm picturing age 8 to 12 and you're probably picturing guys age 16 to 20 or something.
Yeah, something like that.
What turns me on about the little sister or the daughter is that they look up to you.
It's someone who's really close to you, who looks up to you, who thinks you're the coolest
person in the world and all they want is to be close and make you happy.
I'm with you and I feel you on that.
That particular idea sort of strikes me as sort of emotional manipulation.
You really shouldn't fuck your 8-year-old sister.
It's just more sage advice from Nate the Best.
It's not the best idea.
It's a fantasy.
That's fine.
I feel like I'm doing something bad which I don't find attractive.
Yeah, well, the best part about incest is that none of us would do it with our real siblings.
Right.
I don't know.
If Patchy came over and I was kind of drunk, a bro job.
What's going to happen?
A bro job.
What was the thing I was saying I wanted us to do?
Cock handshakes.
Yeah.
Which someone then pointed out to me is just jacking each other up and I legit had not
put that together when I came over.
I was like, no, you just grab the cock and shake it like you're shaking a hand.
You're just masturbating them and I'm like, oh.
I always thought it was sort of like entwining the dicks together and then kind of gyrating
against each other.
That's how I was interpreting it.
No, I was just picturing everybody, like everybody standing in the circle, grabbing each other's
dicks and just giving it a firm handshake like once.
Just like, hello.
Just one pump.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, shit, I don't know.
Still on the table for Radcon 3.
Yeah.
We got plans.
It takes a lot of preparation.
So where do we go from here?
Hippo says you're leaking a first leaking.
That's correct.
He's correct.
First leaking.
We really covered the main stuff there.
I just wanted to talk about there's so many different varieties of incest.
I don't know.
You know, Mumpkin mentioned sort of like more distant family members things like cousin
fucking and stuff, which is actually kind of socially acceptable, you know, depending on
how far away they are.
Yeah.
I mean, that's how anime gets away with all of it, is that it's always a cousin.
Unless you're looking at, because that shit pisses me off because I feel like you're just
trying to get,
They're being fucking cowards.
Yeah.
Just commit.
Well, it's because they want, because the appeal, again, the appeal of the little sister
is that she looks up to you, she's been with you your whole life.
She, and she wants to ride the dick, right?
But then it's always like, oh, but she's not actually my sister.
It's really my cousin, but she still calls me Oni-chan because I'm like a brother to her.
And I'm like, you don't get to have it both ways.
To me, that's just cheap.
Did you got to help me with this real quick?
I've been wondering for a long time now.
Is it actually a thing they do where girls just call guys that they're really close with
Oni-chan?
Yeah.
How legit is that?
Anyone, any guy in the age range of a teenager to a young adult is an Oni-san.
Right.
Oni just means a male of that age.
Does that mean brother?
I thought specifically it was...
Well, Oni can also mean brother, yes, but it means both.
It's like Oji-san can mean uncle or it can mean a man in like the late 20s, early 30s, middle
age.
Oji-san is middle-aged man.
I said, oh, G-san is grandpa or old man.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Okay.
All right.
Speaking of which, what are our thoughts on grandparent incest?
Is that what you guys draw the line or is that...
You know...
Okay.
Grandma's are out.
There are some hot grandmas out there, but to me, a hot grand...
There's some people who are into grandmas, you know, like a fat, flabby, old woman.
Not interested.
If a grandma is still keeping it tight after all these years, that's hot.
Yeah, like Mumkey's grandma.
We can all fantasize about Mumkey's grandma.
Mumkey's grandma is more a standard grandma.
I always think of the grandma from Majlis Chopping Arcade of Inno Bashi.
You know that one?
You know her?
It's been way too long since I've seen her.
Yeah, whatever.
Yeah.
I'd fuck a grandma.
I'd fuck my own grandma.
That wasn't the question.
Uh-oh.
Oops.
What I was going to say is, well, grandmas are less on the table.
There's one porn.
I don't remember what the fuck it's called.
It's by this guy, Yosino, who does all this great 3D porn.
He's got one where it's these two super old grandpas fucking their super young granddaughters.
I've always got the sense from it that they're doing it out of respect.
Like, oh, these are the patriarchs of the family.
We want to please them because they're fucking old and they deserve it.
Oh, oh.
The girls are doing it out of respect.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, no.
The girls are like, oh, we respect our grandfather, so we're going to fuck them.
They seem to be enjoying it.
They're like, this is cool.
Isn't that typical of Japanese culture?
Yes.
That's why I've interpreted it that way.
Yeah.
I'm not entirely sure if that's what the actual plot is because I don't read.
Hey, man.
Cultural relativism.
What can I say?
It's all on the table.
It's all good.
It's all fine.
I can't criticize.
I need to look up what that's called.
I've got it on my computer.
But you guys can talk.
Well, I, yeah, I was going to say the whole, like, I like that sort of thing in my porn
kind of like you're kind of obligated to like fuck within the family sort of thing.
Like kind of like the Targaryen thing, you know, it's like, I don't know, isn't it kind
of sexy that like Daenerys was like raised with her brothers and she's like, and they're
like, yeah, you're going to fuck your brothers.
You're going to do this.
You got no choice.
It's pretty hot.
I'm just saying.
What about Cersei and Jaime?
Like that's, they're like a perfect.
They're the opposite though.
I really like their incest because of the fact that they are grown adults and they've
like had the kids and everything of the incest and they're still like completely in love
with each other.
Like it's really interesting to me because usually you see it as like when they're younger
and then you kind of assume that eventually, I don't know, they stop when she marries the
king or something, but no, they're still fucking doing it like in their 40s.
That's pretty cool.
I agree.
And I can't believe I didn't even think of this until right now, but, uh, or a emo or
a fucking emo.
Oh, Mago Zen Pen is the name of that old man fucking.
If anybody was really, really needed that.
Yeah.
I'm looking at it.
Can you send me a link after this podcast?
Uh, no, I've got it downloaded.
So just look up.
Let me just tell you, let me just tell you my general feelings about or emo.
Okay.
So or emo is this fascinating story about a boy who wants to fuck his sister and she's
dumb.
I think she wants to fuck him too.
And like she slow, like he slowly through this doesn't even start to describe the plot
of or emo.
It's close enough.
It's the things that matter.
Neither one of them wanted to fuck each other at the start of the series at all.
They, it was a subtext.
Okay.
But the point is they get to that place and like they develop all these friendships over
the course of the series and then slowly, but surely this is like or emo is where like
incest is at its worst really in like fiction stuff.
It's like what happens is that he's built up all these friends, he's made all these
connections like in the first part of the show when like it wasn't just about the two
of them fucking, you know, they just, whatever they develop relationships with lots of these
people and they just live life and do good stuff and all these other women come into
the guy's life that he could choose from and slowly, but surely in the second half of the
show, he just one by one kills off all those other girls and is eventually just left with
Kirino.
He has sacrificed everything else in his life, all these other relationships for this incestuous
relationship that's going to be a huge problem with a 15 year old girl that is obviously
not going to last and like it just ends with like they kiss and then they break up.
And it's so like, when I look at that, it's just like this guy threw away all this potential
good shit in his life for this relationship that he also threw right in the trash and
that he should have known from the start like wasn't going to go anywhere.
I thought they got married or some shit.
They, I mean it's like different in the manga or like the novels versus the anime or something
like in the anime, which is the thing that I watch, which, which made me want to die.
They just kiss and then they're like, okay, we're done.
Okay, we're done.
And there's some subjects like, ooh, maybe they'll keep dating in secret or something.
Or like, why?
What the fuck is that about?
Orimo is the dumbest way to do because, okay, the, have you seen Genchi Ken, any of you
at all?
Yeah, I've seen the whole thing.
Yeah.
So you remember that early on, there's like a discussion about incest where, cause Madarame,
the character who is my, my, my boy is a big, big into little sisters and lollies and shit.
And uh, Sasahara, the main character guy, he is not into little girls at all.
He's all into big, beautiful bitches and big, big, big boy.
He's my boy.
Yeah.
Hippo kind of guy.
He's a big titty boy.
And the reason for that is that he has a younger sister who's like a gen guru who he fights
with all the time.
And so he sees it as like younger sisters are completely disgusting.
Like he's not even slightly interested because he has this contentious relationship with
his.
And um, my friend, Don-san, who is the one who like got me into like deeper, deeper Otaku
shit, you know, he was very much the same.
He had a little sister.
He argued with her all the time.
He thought little sisters were totally out of the picture.
And the funny thing about it is that the way Kirino's relationship with her brothers portrayed
early in the show is exactly that kind of relationship.
Like they're at each other's throats.
They don't like each other.
Like it felt very realistic.
And then the show somehow bends over backwards and pretzels itself to make them end up together.
That's the whole problem right there.
It's just the most earth shattering like reversal of like an actually good idea that just fucking
makes me want to die.
It's nuts.
It's fucking insane.
And like it's weird because like if that's what the dude wanted to do all along, like
why did he take this like weird circuitous path that was actually made sense and was
like the total opposite of the, I don't know, it just, it baffles me to this fucking day.
Anyway, now that you've derailed us with Oriibo for it.
It's relevant.
It's the most interesting thing that happened in an incest related thing to anime.
It's probably the most famous incest anime that's out there other than maybe Kiss Ex-Sys,
which I don't think those are his real sisters in that show.
Yeah, I think you're right.
Have any of you guys seen the shitty Adam Sandler movie?
That's my boy.
No.
No, I have not.
It was the first time and I've, I've never been into Game of Thrones or any of that.
So it was the first time I'd seen incest propelled in the mainstream, at least in the US.
The plot of the movie is Andy Sandberg is the son of Adam Sandler and that he's getting
married and then Adam Sandler finds out that the fiance is fucking her brother and it was
played as a joke and I thought it was funny.
And I was the only person laughing in the theater at the big reveal and everybody around
me was like this, this awkward really like they're in awe and disgust and they're kind
of horrified by the film and that was the first time that I realized, oh maybe the mainstream
people are more horrified of this than I think because I thought this was funny for a shitty
Adam Sandler movie.
I think this podcast right here is probably the most positive that four people have been
about incest publicly ever in history.
It's quite possible.
Like even the guy who has no incest fetishes is like, yeah man, stay out of people's bedrooms.
Like granted, Tom is also the guy who wrote the, what's it called, Tom?
How do you want to describe it before I have to describe it?
How do you want to salvage the description of your, your, your Pony fanfic about underaged
or sex?
No way to salvage it.
Is this not the tricksy one?
Is this something else?
No, the one he wrote about Scootaloo having sex with a like 30 year old guy.
That sounds great.
I don't remember it, but that sounds awesome.
And it's good.
It was, it was a full novel.
It was, it was recede to why to claim, which disgusted me to this day.
I had no idea.
What?
But you wrote a full length Pony novel.
He wrote the full length Pony fan fiction.
2013.
Novel.
It's horrible.
Holy shit.
How did you not know that?
Looking up with an older man.
I don't know.
I guess maybe I just got confused.
And whenever like it came up, I just kept thinking it was like the tricksy comic for
some reason.
And I always thought, I always thought you were saying like you'd never written a book, but
here you go.
Here's your breakout hit, dude.
That doesn't count as a book.
That's not real.
It's not a real book.
Is the old man a human or a Pony?
It's still there.
It's all, it's all horse, gay shit.
Okay.
Good.
But um, no.
Um, but the older guy is also like borderline ex-be for Tom himself.
So what was that guy's cutie?
Everyone said that.
It wasn't even the point.
Yeah.
But he did come off as, maybe just because it's written from his perspective.
So it sounds like you.
Yeah.
Sounds like he was groaning curious for sure.
That's true.
That's, that's what.
I thought it was.
I didn't read the whole thing.
I thought it was good.
Well.
Yeah.
I don't know.
What was your, even your question?
Just.
I was just pointing out.
What does it have to do with what we were talking about?
I was just pointing out that you, that, that while you are not an incest family, you
are not an incest fetishist.
I cannot pretend as though you're like the normie here who also is okay with that.
Oh right.
I did it.
No.
Clearly no.
Sure.
Everybody go read that fanfare.
I don't remember what it's called.
Post a link in the description, Ben.
I know you're going to listen through it when you edit this.
Of course.
Ben, Ben can dig it up.
Hey, if we have, if we're not, you know, super into incest, we can just do 30 minutes
of questions.
Yeah.
I was just thinking, maybe let's just switch over to that.
I actually say more about incest.
If you got it, if you got a thing you want to say, yeah, go for it.
I don't know how deep I want to get into it, but because like, because yeah, you guys
talked about it as like a fetish.
I had never thought of incest as a fetish.
Like it was more just a tag.
Like it's not something I sought out.
I like it, especially like, again, like a older brother, younger sister stuff, but more
because like I mostly encountered it so much because I like lollies in general.
So I would come across a lot of that, you know, it wasn't so much that I was seeking
it out.
And so like, I wouldn't have said I had like a fetish for it until recently.
And that's because it turns out that while your girlfriend looks exactly like she'd be
your sister, that is, well, that too, and, and she's like way into that idea.
You know, my little sister's name is Grace and Ben's first girlfriend was a girl named
Grace.
I'm just saying.
But, but it's funny you say that because they were the dick show I was listening to just
before like earlier today was about how he was saying like, I couldn't fuck a girl who
had the same name as my sister.
I, Ben's got no problem with that.
I agree.
I agree with that statement.
I don't think I could do it.
That'd be really weird.
If I met a girl named Patchy, it would just make me harder.
But anyways, my perception of incest as a fetish has changed dramatically upon the realization
that you can role play that fetish.
Like all you have to do is just pretend like, okay, you are my sister and it's like you're
fucking your eight year old younger sister just because you say that you are.
And so you can have to put the age in there.
Could it just.
Yes.
No, I had to.
It likes the little age.
It's got to be fine.
She's got to be a little girl or else it's not who am I to judge.
I shouldn't butt in because if she's her real age, she's just my wife, you know, like
that's right.
Still be your sister.
It's not.
You got to compartmentalize.
All sisters aren't eight.
It's.
We can't question.
Yes, they aren't.
They are.
It's eights.
Eights when they develop sexually.
They don't develop.
Shit.
They are age eight.
Yeah.
Girls start developing at eight.
No fucking way.
I do.
There were girls in my fucking class in third grade who had tits, like real tits.
Like they started eight.
Girls start way younger than guys.
At eight?
Girls start around 10.
Girls start around eight.
They get their periods at like age 10.
First of all, you can start getting wet before you get your period.
So you probably.
Okay.
The more you know.
I've interviewed a lot of girls about their sex lives.
Yeah.
Keep going.
I'm learning things I need to know about.
This is good.
This is interesting.
No.
There was a period where I was trying to write novels and all the characters I wrote were
young girls.
So I interviewed a bunch of women about what it's like to be a young girl when you start
developing different sexual feelings.
Pretty consistent.
Like a fucking mom?
Who'd you ask?
No.
Like people online.
Like women I knew in the anime blogging sphere.
And you know, both girlfriends I've had.
So the answer I always get is eight.
Eight is about when you start thinking about sexual stuff.
And then.
Are we here on the PCB going to officially say the age of consent should be eight years
old?
No.
All right.
Mexico's got it right.
I put it like 15, 13, something around there.
The way my fantasy usually goes is you start at eight is when the interest develops.
But it's not until a few years later that you actually go all the way once their body
is ready.
That's when your dad takes you into the back room and he starts to explain to you and he
starts to feel you and show you how it works.
Right.
Exactly.
Okay.
Understood.
He knows what's up.
Yeah.
He knows his way around.
Which I do want to say, Digi, that something was just uploaded to YouTube that I think
might be the perfect example of the worst video that you could ever possibly see.
Do you know how you and your girlfriend have been doing that series of reviewing every
Pokemon and looking at the pictures and stuff?
Well, what didn't you know?
Our good friend of the show, future PCP member Psy, just uploaded his own version co-hosted
by Asperger and it's two hours of them reviewing just the first 60 Pokemon, so they're taking
their sweet time.
Yeah, I guess so.
They need to move it along, guys.
I think Digi would get a lot from watching that video.
It's two favorite people copying his idea and doing it twice as long.
Are they just like, why would I want that?
I'm confused.
Context.
What is the relevance?
What is the relevance to our topic here?
I don't understand.
Are you just trying to shout out that video?
Is that your point?
No, because I was thinking about how him and his girlfriend do that series and then this
just popped up in my sub feed.
I haven't actually watched it.
Two hours.
Well, they need to hurry their fucking asses up.
They should have covered every Pokemon in two hours.
Yeah.
I was just saying, I thought that would be like the ultimate video to piss off Digi,
but I guess I was mistaken.
It's hard to piss off Digi.
Anyway, we want to move to questions now.
Are we done?
Let's do it.
I got nothing else to say.
I don't want to go any deeper.
Hashtag legalize it.
Hashtag, you know, let me fuck my mom.
Yeah.
You know, just all the hashtags, you know, legalize it.
Give a check off to your mom.
At all.
I can safely say no.
Monkey.
Not even tempted.
No, never.
Tom.
Never.
Okay.
Here's the thing.
I'm just going to say that at some points in my life, I have acknowledged that my sister
is a girl.
I have been aware of that fact.
If you if you understand what I'm saying, I'm not saying that.
No, no.
I'm not saying that.
I'm not saying that when I was like, when I was particularly like depressed, lonely,
learning about sex, 12 years old, I jacked off to like every woman in my family.
I think every woman I've ever come into contact with, I've like probably jacked off thinking
about at least briefly, usually followed by immense guilt and realizing it wasn't a good
idea.
But yeah, I was going to say like to me, it's weird.
I felt weird sometimes.
Like I didn't do that.
But like I would like into my mind, I would force myself to just concentrate on like one
of my classmates, like one specific one and be like, yeah, now I fuck this person in my
brain.
Same fucking sick.
Actually, before we move on from incest, I want to take you all to the darkest side
of incest, the worst element of it that I hate that has affected me in a very in a way
that makes me sick and want to cry.
Have you ever had incest dreams?
No, anybody.
Yeah, I think I have.
I think I have actually.
Yeah.
How did that go?
I'm pretty sure I fucked my sister in my dream.
I believe I did do that one time.
Tom, you ever had incest dreams?
Yeah.
I've never had incest dreams.
So I've had dreams.
But again, I rarely remember my dreams.
So who the fuck knows?
That's true.
I've had dreams.
That's a terrifying thought.
Thank you for planting that into my brain.
I've had incest dreams and they are horrifying and they always wake me wake me wake up like
feeling like I want to throw up everywhere.
And it's like the worst experience of my life is incest dreams.
It's the worst part.
It's when you have to go clean up your underwear afterwards.
No, none of them are none of them are the sexy kind.
They're all like horrible.
All my dreams are nightmares.
Oh, really?
Like every dream I have is a nightmare.
So my incest dreams are all like terrifying and bad.
And I legit wake up like feeling like I actually am going to throw up like.
Well, hey, why is are you like in a sex dungeon being like raped or something?
What's what's so bad about it?
There was one where I raped one of them.
Okay.
That was horrifying.
I also dream about raping Victor, but I don't have the same reaction you do.
Yeah.
All right, let's move on to questions.
Can we all agree that if we could, we would fuck Victor?
I think we can agree with that.
Let me let me get it.
I'll be the questions boy today since I asked on the we're taking them from the PCP Patreon
chat.
If you didn't know.
What's the how much that the pay to get into the Patreon chat?
Just $1.
If you're a patron at all, you get into our exclusive patron discord.
It's the only place that discusses this show that is not cancer.
So true.
The comment section on YouTube, utter cancer, disgusting, deplorable cancer, the PCP fan
discord that I run discord cancer that existed before this absolute cancer.
Do not go there.
You will want to kill yourself.
Yeah.
The one that gives us money conveniently is great.
Because of paywall, man.
It's only paywall.
People give money.
It's true.
All right.
From tadpo.
He asks, how do you deal with backlogs after long stays away from the internet?
This is something I have a lot of trouble with.
I don't know about you guys.
You know, I like after like a weekend or something being away, just to look at my YouTube and
see like all the videos that have piled up, I don't know, nothing fancy.
I guess I really just try to just break it down and just ease into it one thing at a
time.
I'm pretty organized in the way I approach the stuff.
It's probably categorized it.
Or if there's like a show that I've missed, I just try to get all the episodes so I have
them at my fingertips and then I'll watch them when I need to.
I ended up leaving just a lot of shit unwatched.
Like it's I can't like it because they're still coming out.
You know, like I follow enough channels to keep me busy throughout the day.
So if I stack up a week of missed videos and then that day, there's also a bunch of
new videos coming out.
It's like, oh, this is never going to happen.
Sometimes I'll go through and I'll just cull the stuff that I'm like, okay, you know, I
don't actually need to watch like the new best of the worst, for example, or something
like that.
Yeah, I usually skip best of the worst, but I won't skip half in the bag.
But that's because it's easier to throw on in the background.
And like ironically, the stuff, the stuff I watch the most on YouTube is the shit I don't
have to pay attention to because I can just leave it running continuously.
The stuff that I actually have to concentrate on, I often end up getting to like way later
or I miss everything or I'll have a day where like, for instance, with hippo, he was doing
his imgavu a tuatij right when I was traveling the country and a lot of those videos were
longer and stuff.
And I felt like I had to watch them.
So I had like a whole weekend of just like all I did was watch hippo videos until I was
caught up, you know.
But a weekend.
Yeah.
Moving on to another question.
That never happens to me because I am never away from the internet.
And also most of the people I follow, like Nate, never uploads.
So it's fine.
Hey, man, Weagua is real.
I uploaded last night at 5 a.m. for you.
Yeah, me and Sheep overwatched it this morning.
And we...
Which make it 10 out of 10?
It was...
Let me say the best part of waking up is not folders in your cup.
It's Nate on your screen.
Oh, there you go.
And I love what you're doing with your Hillary Clinton fucking cut out.
It's great.
Oh, I've got big plans.
We've got big plans.
It's far away.
Yeah.
Monkey, here's a question I'm actually interested in hearing your answer in because you know
movies and actors a little better than the rest of us.
Cucked by the laws of aerodynamics asks, which actor would you have playing you in a PCP
movie?
Ooh.
Ooh, that's a good one.
Yeah.
We should cast the whole movie, all 10 of us.
Can we get John Goodman to play Gibb?
I just think that makes sense.
He's, you know, he's not even British.
Oh, no.
We use CGI and we shrink him digitally on the screen.
It's perfect.
That's perfect.
And lipo suction him on the screen too while we're at it.
I mean, do the actors have to be close to our age because I've heard that I look like
Martin Freeman and I would like to be portrayed by him, but more likely it would be like Elijah
Wood.
Elijah Wood's like 40 now, man.
Yeah, but he looks like he's fucking 15.
Yeah, he does.
Do you like Elijah Wood?
Would you have him play you?
Yeah.
He can play him.
I'm down with him.
I don't know if, I don't know if he like is temperamentally similar to you.
He did one movie where he plays like this creepy kind of serial killer guy.
So I think he can get into the demented state of Monkey Jones.
Actually, so I think Michael Sarah should play Davoo for sure.
Oh, yeah.
That's a weirdly good.
That's right.
He does look in like a weird way.
In a weird way.
Yeah.
Why does that work?
That shouldn't work at all.
It's the hair.
It's really the hair.
Yeah, I guess so.
Tom, do you know who you would have play you in a movie?
I don't know actors.
I don't pay attention to like popular culture.
I would just say Christian Bill because according to 4chan, I'm a Mexican Christian.
I can see that.
I can see you being perfect, especially like from the machinist.
I like how we're all picking guys like way more handsome than us.
All actors are good.
That's what movies are about, man.
Nate, you have an actor you'd pick.
Without a doubt.
It'd be Tom Cruise.
It'd be modern Tom Cruise would play me.
He's the only man strong enough with enough mental fortitude to handle the lifestyle of
the best guy ever.
I feel like you're more jacked than Tom Cruise.
Oh, no, man.
No.
Is he like Jack?
I'm working on it.
But he's a little short.
He's a little short.
Fuck.
I mean, like I'm probably the same height as him, actually.
But like for Hollywood, he's short.
I thought he was a really short.
He's a shit boy.
I mean, have you seen?
I mean, like Ellen Page to play mage.
I think Ellen Page is mage.
Is it mage like twice the height of Ellen Page?
Ellen Page is tight.
That is true.
John Goodman's playing hippo.
Who fucking cares?
Digitally shrunk John Goodman.
I just want the poacher to say, Page is mage.
It sells itself.
I feel like the only answer I can come up with is Jack Black.
It just seems obvious to me.
Yeah.
Not bad.
I don't know who else it could possibly be.
So it's got to be Jack Black.
I don't like it.
It's going to be a very interesting performance.
Unless you wanted to look local to play Jess.
A lot of people say I look like that dude from Always Sunny, whichever one.
Fat Mac?
Probably Fat Mac.
I forget.
Fat Mac.
Okay.
So I guess-
Who's a really like big buff, tough wrestler these days to play Jess?
Fucking Batista.
Oh, what's that guy?
Glorious.
Batista should play Jess.
Yeah, okay.
Batista.
Guardians, right?
But Batista, as he is in Guardians 2, should play Jess.
Like literally, it should just be Drax the Destroyer, like in the paint and everything.
It should play Jess.
Just with a wig on.
You have never seen anybody enjoy a character more than me and Jess enjoy Batista in that
movie.
Like, he's the greatest.
Hey, what's the guy who played, what's the guy who was an anti-Christ?
Willem Defoe should play Ben.
Yeah, totally.
That little goblin face going on, that's perfect.
Wait, who do we got from Munchie?
That's the last one.
Oh, Munchie should be played by God.
We'll see if he can fit it in his schedule.
We should get an actual gigantic baby boy to play Munchie.
Yeah, baby boy!
I think Munchie should just play himself.
Who else can be Munchie?
I think that's a good idea.
He's got time.
He can be in the movie.
Okay.
Is that everybody?
Do we miss-
Similar question from Orca.
If any person, fictional or non-fictional, had to join the PCP, who would you want on?
Who's just like an insufferable, intellectual, pseudo-intellectual asshole like Socrates?
If we're going non-fictional, I want Max Landis on this show.
Oh, man.
Yeah, he'd be good.
He's a perfect fit.
He'd be good.
We would never get a word in.
I would.
That's true.
It would just be me and him and Nate.
Yeah, I'm sure that's true.
And the podcast, we have to start our own splinter podcast so we actually say something.
That's inevitable anyway.
I don't know about fictional characters.
I want to get Donald Trump on the podcast.
Tyrion Lannister.
He'd be a good podcaster.
Trump would suck dick.
Trump would just fucking-
No, it'd be funny.
Trump's really funny.
Okay, Trump would be funny.
That's true.
But he'd fail at making his points coherently.
He'd talk in circles.
He's a natural comedian, a natural showman.
If you watch anything that's not political, he's really funny.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
Nate, considering how dedicated you are to Pokemon going to the polls, you have a moral
obligation to get Donald Trump on here and give him what for.
You're right.
Oh, I thought you were going to say Hillary, to have Hillary join the PCP, which is not
a bad idea.
Yeah, she's got those great jokes that would fit right in.
She's full of them, dude.
All right.
Here's-
Uh-huh.
Is that everybody?
I was actually going to read this-
I did ask questions on Twitter.
There was just one that I wanted to address, just because it was sort of a logistical thing.
It was at Fat Man Falling.
Just asks, when are you releasing this month's bonus episode?
And I just thought I'd tell everybody.
We generally release those just on the first of the month, like every week, every month.
So yeah, that's it.
That's it.
Okay.
So in like three days from now?
No.
Like, oh, when this comes out?
Yeah.
It'll be like three days after this comes out.
That's true.
All right.
So he asks, best and worst ways you've ever spent a shitload of money relative to whatever
you think a shitload is?
I know exactly what it is, but I've already told this story before, so stop me if I've
told this.
But like, one day, when I was young and I was really into Vampire Hunter D, and I bought
this $100 leather hat, you know, I already told this-
Is that the best or worst way you spent a shitload of money?
It's worse than both at the same time.
Well, kind of, but like, it's the worst because like, I never once actually wore it and immediately
regretted spending $100 on it.
I was just like a whim thing, but for me at that age, $100 was so much fucking money.
It still is for me.
It was a complete terrible idea.
I mean, yeah, it's a lot in general.
Monkey time.
Once every other month, when I finally hit the $100 thing for YouTube Ad Revenue, that's
a big deal, my friend.
I finally did it for you money for doing that thing.
You make more than $100 a month.
Well, only because of me and Digi's podcast, but then I just give him half anyway, so.
Really?
Is that true?
Yeah.
Do you know how many of those are demonetized?
Oh, no.
That's a good point.
Are they monetized because I used some song for like 10 seconds?
Well, yeah.
That's true.
But it's fine.
The worst way I've spent a shitload of money relative to what was a shitload at the time
is buying two different $130 Kanan figures for the anime series Kanan, which I'm scared
to even re-watch, but I've got like $300 in toys for it.
So just because you're afraid you've wasted your money on these fucking figures, you can't
watch the show again.
Yeah, the figures are broken now, so like it's a total wash.
Really all my figures, I have some level of regret for, all the expensive ones.
Just because they're so expensive.
But the best way I spent a shitload of money was buying several hotel trips in Rochester,
New York two, three months ago, $600 a week, but totally worth it.
People are, you know, I hear people say things like, what are you doing paying money to,
you know, for like, why don't you buy local pussy, dude, what are you doing, flying people
around and stuff, you know, as I'm arguing.
If the pussy that good, then it would work.
That's right.
I mean, last, I would say, if I had to pick another one, it would like another worse one,
it would be the second trip to my ex-girlfriend.
Sure.
The first one was worth it because it was $400 and I lost my virginity and that was nice.
The second trip, not worth it at all.
Should have broke up before that.
Understandable.
So, yeah.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Probably spent even more on that trip.
By the way, that just, your figure story reminds me about how I've been wanting, I've had like
a fantasy of buying like the perfect commune of figure for years and like they, there have
been a bunch that come out that are pretty nice.
And I'm always thinking like, yeah, it's one day I'll buy that.
I don't know why I just don't.
I just want to own it and build a little shrine to it.
The worst part about the two Kanan figures is that they're like jumping in opposite directions.
The idea is that the two characters are like shooting at each other.
So you buy both and it's set.
Which is a clever idea, except that if you have them displayed that way, you can't see
either of them.
Like they're both jumping away from each other and there's no way to make it so you
can see both of their fronts.
So it's the stupidest idea of a figure set ever and I hate it.
You know that just, this was another that's both related to figures and like a terrible
slash great purchase.
This was both a good and bad thing.
I know I've told the story before, but it's just like how I spent a billion million dollars
in like a Tokyo crane machine trying to win like the second half of my like CC or C2 and
Collins set.
A figure that probably cost $35.
I'm sure it was far less than the amount of money I spent.
But here they sit before me, link together in this sexy ass pose.
I'm looking right up C2's cunt.
It's great.
It's great, you know.
It's all good.
So that was both a terrible waste of money, but also it paid off long term.
All right.
Spooker asks, what are your most visited websites?
V, 4chan, V. That's like the number one I'm on on YouTube.
Tom?
Well, mostly I go to YouTube all the time.
I just I've researched tons of stuff on YouTube.
I have gone on Engadget every day for the last 10 years.
It's not an exaggeration.
Whoa.
What do they do there?
What is their thing?
It's just like a technology blog, but they're becoming super political.
So I'm like tempted to jump ship because it's starting to get gross.
And then let me guess, let me guess.
They love Donald Trump.
Oh, the best.
It's they're the most red-pilled site of all time.
It's great.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I don't really go to a lot of websites frequently.
I just kind of just does everything.
You know, Google.com because I've I've constantly needed to learn something and like Google has
got my back.
So it's yeah, very true.
My best friend of all time, monkey.
Yeah, I just go on all the standard shit.
I guess I also go to Reddit more than you guys probably.
Oh, we've got a redditor on our hands.
Folks, my fucking hero.
Well, I I'm one of those rare redditors who was mostly on the Donald.
So.
Right, of course.
I got it. Where else am I going to get real news?
Every other website is fake news.
Yeah, it's a conundrum.
I the websites I spend the most time on or without a doubt, YouTube and Twitter, because
that's where all my shitposting is.
But like, I just habitually like cycle through all my bookmarks constantly.
So I check my anime list every day and accept every friend request I get, which is like
three or four a day.
I check Gmail, obviously, Reddit.
I only go to Reddit for my own board.
I don't actually go anywhere.
The weirdest one I go to, though, is every day I go to GameFAQs and do the poll of the
day.
Oh, I did that for a long time.
I've done that for like a decade.
Like I've been I've voted in every poll of the day.
I feel like I'm going to go see today's really miss it.
Today's poll is, have you ever fallen asleep while playing a video game?
Absolutely.
And oh, did I ever tell you my nightmare story about how I had just caught a shiny butterfree
in the bug catching contest and fell asleep and the battery died and I fucking lost it?
Oh, no.
I wanted to fucking kill myself.
You should have.
I should have.
It was a nightmare.
It was literally the butterfree that cucked Ash out of his butterfree, the pink one that
stole it away.
I caught her, but I let her escape.
She slipped away.
Just like in the show.
God, shiny Pokemon horror stories are the worst.
I know.
I've only encountered one shiny Pokemon in my entire life and I was playing Pokemon Emerald
and it was a shiny wormhole, but it was before you got Pokeballs in the game.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
So evisceration.
Right.
That's the worst.
It was like the biggest cockslap I've ever gotten by God in my life.
I've got a shiny cottony in Sun and Moon.
It's the only shiny I've seen, but I got it.
I've actually caught kind of a lot.
I've caught like four or something over my career, which for somebody who just played,
I've like played every game through once, but I didn't like grind for any of them.
So I guess I'm kind of lucky.
Ben has never seen any, except for like red carrots, obviously.
He plays more Pokemon than both of us combined.
Yeah.
As far as I know.
It's just cray.
Yeah.
The game.
It's pretty much the coolest idea ever.
I fucking love it.
It's insane and nuts.
I love how low the percentage is.
It's great.
I love it.
Let's do one more questions.
Do we want to keep it going?
Let's do one more.
Let's get a big finish.
Okay.
The best question.
You want a real big epic finisher?
Yes.
You want one that's going to tear our fucking listeners' ears pieces?
I'm ready.
Crafty asks, can y'all sing?
Oh.
When I was a young boy, my father took me into the city to see a marching band.
He said something crazy story all about how my life got different upside down and I'd
like to take a minute to sit right there and I'll tell y'all to pretend it's all over
there.
I pulled up to the house around 7-8 and I helped to get to your home and told you later
to my kingdom.
I was like, why don't you let us sit around for a little while?
Let it go.
I want to change.
I'm not gonna stand here and wait.
hopefully Our wonderful editor will fade out at some point during that.
No, we're still going.
Don't cut it.
We're still going.
I guess that's true I'm just gonna say goodbye now. Bye. Bye. Goodbye. Fuck you
Sorry
My dick I'm jerking myself I'm sucking I am an asshole I am a stupid I've got a deadline don't want to do it