I won't bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Hello boys and girls.
Welcome to the big top.
It's The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
So we'll circus around here and there's no cheesy though.
It's a real, nah he unfortunately took his own life after that.
I don't know, that's not funny, that's not funny, that didn't happen.
After you bullied him.
Yeah, not after the Kickstarter failed, after I bullied him and said he was bad at math.
RIP.
Good morning, I guess it's not morning for you Gibb.
No it's not.
But I'm tired, just like I am tired every day.
Cause life is tiring.
You can think of another way to say that.
Yeah.
Well let me tell you what I'm sick and tired of.
Mega man.
Yeah, more nonsense with the stupid video.
It's not my fault, I swear it's not my fault this week, it really should have been at this week.
To briefly sum up why it's not out.
I finished rendering it, I uploaded it, and then I watched it through.
And there were a couple of small errors in it, but there were three really small errors that I noticed.
But they were all so small that I was willing to be like I don't care.
I'm gonna release it in its current state, fuck it.
But it has been, you know when you upload a video and it has to process and first it processes the video in standard definition.
And then it processes it in high definition, right?
Yes, yes.
Well, it's been processing it in high definition for I think like four and a half days now.
Which just doesn't seem right.
I think it's just stuck.
Sometimes it just gets stuck and I don't know why.
I mean, I would imagine it just takes a while.
How long does it take to upload fully?
Only like eight hours, ten hours.
Okay.
Yeah, I don't know how encoding is different, but like maybe it will just take a number of days.
Maybe.
I mean, I wasn't surprised.
I was expecting it to take a while because like it's in 1440p.
So it's gotta process it.
I mean, standard definition is 360p, but then it's gotta process it in 720 and 1080 and 1440.
So I was like, okay, it's a big video in a bunch of different resolutions including one of the highest res is available.
So I'm not surprised it's gonna take a long time.
But four days just seems excessive.
Is 1440p 2K?
Yeah, it's 1440 by 2560, which is the highest resolution that my camera could film in.
And also supposedly, yeah.
And also supposedly YouTube like compresses 1080p differently than 1440 and like 1440 looks better.
Not just because it's higher res, but because like 1080 looks worse than 1080 on YouTube,
but 1440 supposedly does not look worse than 1080.
This is what I read somewhere.
I don't know if it's true.
Like YouTube compresses 1080 more?
Yeah, like YouTube specifically compresses 1080 more is what I read.
Yeah.
I don't know.
But anyway.
So I don't know.
I guess it could just still be processing just because it's big and like maybe either way.
I started another render like like a day into the upload, I started another render because I was like,
I found those small errors and I was like, well, those are really frustrating.
I might decide to re upload.
Let me start another render.
So I started another render with the errors fixed and now it's been a couple days and that render is halfway done now.
Is that a smaller render without 2K?
No, it's the same render just with the errors fix.
And I'll tell you what the errors were.
There was one line that I said that got garbled because I accidentally I tried to correct for the volume and I accidentally shifted the clip like by half a second.
So I like say a word and then like I say I say the word like twice overlapping each other and it just sounds a little weird.
It's not even very noticeable.
And then there were two other times I meant to censor every instance of the word.
I shouldn't say only a few minutes into this video.
I shouldn't say the S word and the F word.
Okay.
Do you know those?
I'm not aware.
Okay.
Well, I won't admit the man.
I won't tell you.
But I tried to censor every instance of those words and I missed two S words.
I mean, I actually think it mattered very much.
This is why I was I was willing to ignore these.
I didn't care.
I was going to release it except that the processing hasn't been done.
So but I started another render and it's now halfway done.
So I'm thinking like I want to release it on a weekend.
So maybe the move now is just since I have to upload a new version anyway, because I think the HD processing is just stuck and it's not going to finish.
I might as well just let this render finish and then upload that version and then release that this weekend.
I think what I'm going to do is release it on Saturday, probably at noon.
Probably like the day after this episode goes live is my is my plan unless more of this same nonsense continues to happen.
But I mean, but eventually eventually this must resolve.
Eventually I will have a week where I don't say, oh, it's coming out this week and then I'm proven wrong.
Yeah, it'll know like it's becoming a meme at this point.
Yeah, I know.
It's been like I realized six weeks.
I mean, six weeks ago I posted on my Patreon.
I posted a Q&A update wherein I said the video is almost done.
Now, I didn't mean that it was like coming out that week.
I thought there would be like a few more weeks left.
So I thought maybe two or three more weeks from that.
So, you know, and it's been six.
Okay.
But anyway, the other thing, the other thing that's it's sort of amusing, but it's also a bit annoying is that a couple of people have seen the video already.
And I guess the reason why this happened is because I clicked that I wanted to automatically add it to a playlist.
And it did add it to the playlist and I thought it wouldn't add it until it went public.
But no, it, you know, unlisted videos can be part of playlist as well.
So there are maybe like 30 or 40 people saw it in this playlist and have seen it.
And there's like some comments on it now, even though it's unlisted.
I will, I will unfortunately, I think that's funny.
I kind of wish I could keep those.
But since I want to upload the fixed version, I will probably have to lose those comments when it goes when I when I publish the fixed version.
So sorry about that.
Early viewers, I appreciate your enthusiasm.
I really do.
Yeah, but they had to watch it in 360p, which looks, it looks terrible.
You can't even like see what's on the board behind me at 360p.
Unacceptable.
It is. It is unacceptable.
That's why I wouldn't release it.
Like otherwise I might have just like released it in SD and then waited for the HD processing to finish.
But like, I think, I think it's unwatchably bad.
I mean, if you're just listening to it, then it's fine, obviously.
But if you're trying to watch it, you can't watch it at 360p.
So that's, that's what's up.
That's, that's what's up.
For my week, I guess at the beginning of the episode, we just sort of like, we sort of settle on like you talk about what's been going on.
I talk about another Mega Man lecture.
I did it there.
And then it's, I mean, the only thing I've really been doing last week, well, there's a couple things, but it was a lot of not safe for work stuff.
So I'm like, well, I mean,
You mean drawing?
Yeah, drawing.
Yeah.
I did draw for cheesy a,
Oh, alien girlfriend.
Alien girlfriend.
I saw that because I am a patron of cheesy.
Oh, I saw that update on Patreon.
Yeah.
Yeah. So that'll be coming out when it comes out.
And that was fun.
And yeah, I've just been drawing a lot of dicks and tits and stuff.
There's commissions, right?
One of them was a commission.
There was a, there was another one that was similar.
But I've just been just, I just felt like it.
I just been drawing things that I want to see.
There's not really like a topic conversation unless you've seen them and want to say anything about them.
I don't know.
Are you posting them on big girl squish?
Yeah.
Do you, do you look a bit?
No.
Well, there you go.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Go to big girl squish.
If you want to see, I just finished this little like drawing of a five way between Vriska,
Kanaya, Rose, Terezi and June Egbert.
Cause like this, the John Egbert ghost trans is June Egbert fan thing, which is a cool idea.
They're all lesbians.
Vriska, Kanaya, June, Rose, Terezi and June.
Vriska, Kanaya.
Give that's fucked up.
That's incest.
Huh?
All trolls have the same mom.
You freak.
They never had any problem with it before.
If you draw any trolls can't have sex because they all come from the same incestuous slurry.
This is established in Canon.
They're just kissing.
Disgusting.
And their dicks are out, but that's all.
Yeah, I don't know.
I feel pretty happy with my progress on that front.
I haven't made a lot of progress on Clarissa just for various reasons.
Other things have been taken priority.
I want to get that done.
It's so close.
I haven't really worked on it for two weeks at this point.
Well, it's not going to get done at that rate.
Yes.
That's the truth.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry if that hurts your liberal snowflake feelings.
Sorry.
Sorry if that.
Sorry to bring harsh reality down on your tender little millennial head.
Participation trophy.
Yeah.
Where is my medal?
I drew like nothing for two weeks.
Exactly.
Soft.
Generation is soft.
Not enough lead.
Speaking of soft, did you see that selfie I took?
I was pretty happy without how I looked in that one.
Yeah, I think I did.
I think I did see that one.
You look like you just got out of the shower.
Yeah.
I just got out of bed and I was like, oh, cool.
Nice.
That's called liking the way you look and taking a picture of it.
That's a nice new thing.
That's crazy.
That's crazy, darling.
You ever done that?
You ever seen yourself and said, hey, cool.
Yeah.
Once or twice.
Hell yeah.
Okay, end of discussion.
It sucks sometimes when I'm like, I don't really have any like conversations to bring
or like things to talk about.
It's been a bit of a running theme plus few weeks.
I don't know about that.
I feel like it's been fired, but you know, for me, I don't know.
Other than like, I have this week, I didn't do much more work on slime and punishment.
That's the two things I've been working on is getting this stupid video published and
getting the slime and punishment book layout completed so that I can actually order the
test copies.
I didn't do that much on slime and punishment this week.
It was mostly, honestly, it wasn't even really working on the video because like the video
is done and all I had to do was watch it through again and make a couple of small corrections.
It's mostly just been ringing my hands and like just like sitting in like, you know, anxious
anxiety and stuff about like, I can't believe the video is not out yet.
I said the video is going to be out.
When is it going to be done?
Is it done in HD processing today?
No.
Okay.
Well, now what do I do?
Now how do I modify my plans?
Someone called Crow is looking in my patron discord advised me on some tips and said like,
Ben, you should make a trailer.
You should make a trailer and then premiere the video as a premiere.
And I think that's what I'm going to do.
That's what that's what patrician TV did this week.
This week, the 20 hour analysis of Skyrim came out and he like released a video advertising
it as well as like set it as a premiere.
And like, so like the premiere was set to release and while the premiere was set to release
this ad came out being like, it's coming this week.
So I think that's like kind of like bad for a 20 hour video.
Why?
Because like, I mean, I would assume there's like sections that you could skip to if you're
interested.
But if it's premiering, you have to wait 20 hours before you can start skipping through
the video to see the parts you want to listen to.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess, I guess, I mean, yeah, that's fine.
Like, I'm sure people liked it.
I think that's a long time to wait before the video is over.
That's the one thing I don't like about premieres is the fact that you can't use them as a video
like any other video.
It's like a worse version of any other video on YouTube.
Yeah.
I mean, on a practical level, that's true.
That actually I also like I checked out the premiere as it was happening and I well, I
like wasn't interested in watching it live.
I kind of like scrolled back to the beginning, which you can do.
You can you can rewind a premiere and watch it from the beginning if you catch it midway
through, but you can't fast forward past where it is in its air.
So I didn't have the time at the moment.
So I didn't I didn't watch it as it was airing, although I could have if I had the free time.
Yeah.
It's a it's a not a big deal.
I am and they're they're good for hype.
So whatever.
Yeah.
I think so I think I'm going to do that.
I think I'm going to set it as a premiere.
And then I think I'm going to release some a some some like trailers that will hopefully
get people like notified.
And I'm pretty sure I mean at this time, like I really think I'm not lying this time is
that it's going to be this Saturday the day after this video goes out.
I think that's when I'm going to do it.
I've been fucking around.
We're far enough into the video that I can say the F word now.
I've been fucking around with the making the trailer and I just can't settle on which
classic Mega Man theme to use as the music, as the musical backing for my trailer.
Hmm.
It's so difficult.
As a non Mega Man fan.
The obvious first choice for me would be the title screen of Mega Man 2 because that's
the most iconic to me.
Titles.
Mega Man 2.
Wait a minute.
Is that the same?
Hold on.
Is that also the Wiley boss song?
Hang on.
You know how like it starts slow and then it goes up and there's that intro bit of the
song.
Yes.
And then Mega Man appears at the top of the building is like it's all cool.
Yeah.
No, it's not the same, but it's very it's similar.
I think they share like I never thought about this before, but when you were humming it right
there, I was thinking that sounds like the Wiley's Castle song.
I think they share sort of a motif.
I think they're like a pitch shifted versions of each other now that I think about it.
I never noticed before because that one of the ones I was considering was the Wiley's
Castle one song from Mega Man 2.
Also Metal Man theme is really good.
Also the intro song from I think I think Mega Man 4.
I think it's 4 was the one.
Snake Man theme is good.
Also, I was also considering there's a couple of songs from Zero that I think are pretty
good, but like they're not they're not like hype.
They're not like hype and fun in the way that Mega Man songs are.
They're sort of like somber or mysterious, which is sort of a different vibe.
But I kind of think that would work in its own way.
Yeah.
So, you know, I like airman stage.
I've heard that in a lot of YouTube poops.
Yeah, that one's fine.
It's not it's not one of my favorites.
It's not my favorites.
Also, it's it's really funny.
I was I was going through the the song listings this week for this reason and it's really
funny how shit the music from one is like Mega Man one is like pretty bad.
Honestly, the music sucks.
And then suddenly you get to two and it's like classic after classic.
Yeah.
How does I'm trying to think because I know like at least cut man stage got burned into
my brain because I kept losing.
I forget how it goes though.
So I guess not.
I don't remember because it's not that good.
It's just not it's just not that good a song.
Also, I was talking to Tech Tonic Improv about the X series music and we I think we agreed
X2 is just is just bad.
I mean, it's not bad, but it's just way X1 and X3 just have like far and away better music
than X2 in my opinion.
The same composer.
I don't know.
I think so.
You know, I don't actually know.
But like three has all the music in three sounds like a hair metal like screeching like electric
guitar like and and but it's iconic but it's iconic.
Yeah.
Good good good stuff.
Good stuff.
It's been so that having that decision to make has been an excuse was an excuse for me to
spend like a bunch of yesterday just like going through Mega Man music and listening to it
and being like, yeah, that's a cool song.
Yeah.
That's a cool song.
So that was fun.
Still haven't made it.
Still haven't made a decision.
Okay.
I guess that's all I have to say about it.
Unless unless you want me to post the MP3s of the of some of the more offbeat picks that
I've been going over and I can tell Eleazar to play them in the episode.
Yeah.
Let's have a listen.
All right.
You know what?
I don't know too much about Mega Man music.
I'll do it because I can.
Let me see here.
Let me see.
Okay.
These are the I'll show you the classic.
No, not the classic one.
The ones from the ones from zero that I think are a little are a little weird as choices,
but I think I kind of like them.
Where did I post those?
Oh, it's processing just like the YouTube video.
It's still processing.
Okay.
There it goes.
It's called X the Legend.
Three, two, one, go.
It's like Dark Hyrule Castle.
I think this would be funny.
I think this is kind of funny and a trailer for the lecture with this music sort of implies
that like this lecture is like a big deal.
This is like the ultimate fucking Mega Man lore.
Like, are you fucking kidding me?
Are you handle?
Are you?
Are you afraid of all this content?
Yes, like dark clouds and thunderbolts and like big techs flying in like all coming soon.
Exactly.
Coming soon.
You are not prepared.
Okay.
Here's one.
This one's called Cyber Elf.
That is sort of, well, three, two, one, go.
This one's sort of like, what is this?
What is this going to be about?
What is it?
What experience am I the viewer going to have?
There's a certain like noisiness to the console with this music.
This is the Game Boy Advance.
Oh, yeah.
Definitely.
There's such a sort of like a noise on like, I mean, that's just what Game Boy Advance music
sounds like.
I was a little disappointed going through.
I wanted to pick some music from zero, but going through the tracks like not that many
of them are iconic.
There's a couple.
There's a couple that are iconic, but a lot of them just sound like kind of muddier than
like classic games and X games.
And I kind of think just the music on the GBA was just not as good.
It was quite good for a handheld.
I think it sounds a lot better when it's coming from the actual device.
That's probably true, yeah.
Like they managed to get, because those are on cartridges and they managed to get quite
a lot of like dynamic range into the songs on a GBA cartridge.
Definitely compared to a Game Boy.
Here's a good one.
This is Flame Mammoth's theme from X1.
Three, two, one, go.
And this one's kind of like get hype for a video.
Coming soon to a YouTube near you.
You pig.
Get ready to get hype to consume your sloppy fucking slave.
Actually, there's that screechy guitar.
This isn't even an X3.
X3 is even screechier guitars.
Oh, I thought it was supposed to be a trumpet.
I hear a guitar.
Actually, I'll play one more.
I'll play one more.
This is the one that I'm leaning most heavily towards at the moment.
This is the intro to, I think it's X4?
Not an X4.
I think it's a classic four or five.
I don't even remember which one this is the intro to.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, I've heard this one before.
Yeah.
Which one is this?
I think it's, is it five?
Because it kind of sounds like blues.
And blues is like the Deuter, not the Deuteragonist.
The secondary antagonist of five.
Yeah, this is a good one.
I think this is pretty iconic.
I had forgotten about this one.
I was going through the list.
I was going through the games and I heard this one.
I was like, oh my God, I forgot this song existed.
Oh my God.
How does such beauty exist in eight bits?
They just try really hard.
I guess they just tried really hard.
And you know what?
You did it.
But a musician, composer, could you just try a little harder, please?
Okay.
Yes.
Yes, I went to school to the piano.
I went to school to try hard at such things.
And so I am prepared for this request.
Mr. Boss Man of Capcom, sir.
Mr. Inafune, my lord.
Are you going to be like speaking or is it just going to be like text?
It's going to be, there's like a funny clip of the intro because I edited the intro.
So like the video starts with a little Mega Man 2 like boss intro jingle.
And then I like teleport down into the screen like Mega Man teleporting into the level.
And then I say a funny line and then it immediately cuts to like black screen with text.
And there's like a progression of text message being like premiering, you know, this Saturday,
an eight hour lecture.
And then so it's sort of like a cut, like a hard cut to like music and black screen text.
Also, I think I've decided, and this was the process of like a long iterative process for me to decide the title of the video.
I think the title of the video is going to be Every Mega Man Games Lore Explained in Obsessive Detail.
And I had to choose that adjective obsessive.
I considered many other adjectives.
I did like excruciating.
I like excruciating.
I probably overthought this, but to me excruciating implies that like the video is painful.
And I don't want to send these subconscious messages to people that like you will suffer if you watch this video.
Obsessive is self-deprecating.
It makes me sound like a nerd, but it doesn't necessarily imply that you will have a miserable time as a viewer.
Also, it's more commonly known.
It's a more common word than excruciating.
Spork pointed out that some people might not know what excruciating means, and I think that's probably true.
Yeah, I think obsessive seems too soft though.
You think so?
I think if you're like obsessive, it's not like exaggerated enough.
Maybe if you said insane, like insane detail, you're still self-deprecating.
Yeah.
I mean, the one about Pretty Little Liars was unhinged.
The Pretty Little Liars video calls itself unhinged.
Yeah, that's a pretty good one.
The Carrie Can Read video calls itself desperate.
A little freak talks about Mega Man.
A little freak talks?
I saw Carrie posted, when she made another sort of similar video later, and she posted it on...
She doesn't really use Twitter that much, but she made a Twitter update to announce that new video.
And the Twitter announcement was just like, hey guys, I made a new unhinged video, lol.
You know, the unhinged genre of video.
I've made a new one in that genre, and here it is.
I love those.
Oh, hell yeah.
I mean, I do.
I mean, I do love those.
It's a brand.
Yeah.
But unhinged.
Her video was not unhinged.
That was Mike's video was unhinged.
Anyway, I put a lot of time into considering such things, and I just wish it were over.
I just wish the nightmare were over.
As I say, I would have released...
Errors and all, I would have released the video already if YouTube had simply let me, but it fucked up, I think.
I think it fucked up.
I think it should not have taken this long.
I don't know.
So it's not my fault.
It is 2K in eight hours.
I feel like it's not that unusual.
I'm not too surprised by being multiple days, but I guess I'd have no experience with it.
Well, I'll tell you what.
I mean, if Saturday rolls around...
Ooh, oh no.
Because now I have to choose one of...
I was going to say I could just see what happens, and if this one does finish processing, I can just release this one.
But if it doesn't, then it's an error.
I could upload the other one, and I could set that one to release.
But if I set one to release, and then I tell people, oh yeah, here's the premiere, and then I can't just decide, oh well shit, it didn't work.
I got to release the other version.
Can you not...
They'd be linked to the wrong file when it doesn't actually end up erroring.
Can you not set a premiere after it's ready?
Yeah, I mean you can.
But I'm saying that if I release the trailer, or the ad for it, and then I switch which file, the link would be to the wrong video.
Or the one that had been up on my channel, showing as premiering in two days or whatever, that would then be the wrong video.
Because I would switch it out at the last minute for a different upload.
It just seems bad.
Can you just change the link in the description or whatever?
Yeah, I mean I guess I could.
I don't know what the problem is.
I mean you don't see a problem with like, you know, on your channel and your recent uploads, the most recent upload will be like premiering, it'll be a link to a video that's like premiering in two days.
And then when the countdown ends, like sometime before the countdown ends, you like take that video down and put up a new one to premiere.
Oh, but it's a different video technically.
I mean just anyone that had clicked that link would find themselves, you know, not linked to anything.
Right, but like I'm saying like...
I mean I guess it wouldn't be that bad.
Wouldn't you just like wait to see if both of them work and then choose which one to premiere?
Yeah.
Because if the one...
I mean don't do that unless...
I feel like that's the point where you make the decision on which one you want to show.
Well that's, I mean that's what I'm gonna do.
When this render is done, which should be another like two days I think, I will upload this version and then see if it processes any more quickly.
And if it does, I'll just use this one.
But if it doesn't and like the other one is still processing, then I'm like, well I have to wait for one or the other finish.
Um.
Hum-num-num-num-num-num.
No.
My goal this week is to try not to worry about it too much and just kind of let it play it.
Let's just kind of let it process or let it upload or let it be however it's gonna be.
And in the meantime, get back to the slime and punishment book because I was making progress on finishing that.
Finishing those files up and that was good a couple days ago.
I guess I did work on it earlier in the week.
Haven't for the last couple days though.
Ugh.
Well, you know how like Twitter people saying it's gonna be destroyed and all that?
Yeah.
I've considered like where I would go to post stuff.
I don't really like any of the possible options.
Yeah.
I made a Tumblr the other day and it sort of immediately sucks.
Well, as a viewer, you can't find anything.
It sort of puts you in a bubble almost immediately.
Click some things you like and then it just shows you those three things over and over again until you start searching for specific different things.
You mean tags?
Tags or genres of things.
They don't seem to show you a lot of new stuff to get interested in.
Because I clicked on like, I was like, I just want to see Ryska.
Who's on Tumblr making Ryska drawings?
I searched that, I clicked like on a bunch of things and then I'm only getting home stuck on my 4U section.
Well, yeah, I mean, what do you expect?
Well, yeah, but like that, like, I feel like the algorithm's a little too like pushing the thing that I've, like, I haven't put, given it enough inputs yet.
Like, why would it not be trying to show me new things?
You think Twitter shows you more un-requested stuff?
I don't know. It's just, as a new user, it feels like an uphill battle to find stuff if I don't already know what it is.
And I probably will not use Tumblr for that reason unless I stay there for ages and do all the backbreaking labor of doing my own algorithm.
I'm the algorithm. I have to find everything myself. I don't know.
I mean, I don't have a backup plan for besides Twitter. I did have an old Tumblr that I guess I could use if I wanted.
I remember deleting my old give and take or give and tumble, I think is what it was called.
You did?
Yeah, I deleted it at some point.
Why?
I don't know. I think I was, my mind, my thought process was if I really want to stop looking at this and checking it all the time, I need like a hard cut, like no more sort of thing.
So I took the ultimate plunge and deleted my account. It wasn't really out of any...
Why did you want to stop looking at it?
I think for productivity reasons. This was like a long time ago at this point. I can't really remember.
I'm like, I got to work harder and I always go to Tumblr every day all the time.
Got to turn that off and I couldn't.
But I made a new account and it's boring. I don't care.
Yeah, I mean, I kind of want to, I think I've been saying I sort of want to be on Twitter less and I think I have been, I mean, I haven't been tweeting as much.
I mean, I still look at it, but not like, I don't know, I just look at it like a couple times a day.
It doesn't take too much time, I guess.
Yeah, I use it quite a lot, honestly.
Well, I still use it, but I think I use it less recently, which is good.
And it's a trend that I think I want to continue because nothing good has ever come from it.
Hey, did you play any more Inscription?
You know, oh, I DM'd you, but we didn't talk about it on the show.
Oh, you did? Yeah, we did talk in DMs a little bit.
I got a little frustrated with Inscription and it was generally, here's my hot take and I know I'm wrong.
Okay.
But it's just sort of my emotional reaction because the core gameplay is roguelike sort of essentially like you have a good run and you do what you can, but most of the time you're not going to win.
And I'm a little brat and I don't like that.
I don't like it when I have a bad run, when I get the wrong cards offered to me.
Right.
But you know, that's a genre of game I'm just not into.
But I was frustrated because I liked the card game, but I felt like early on, at least, it wasn't telling me the extent of the card game.
Every time I died, something new would happen, something extra would be revealed in the mechanics.
And now I'd be like, okay, fine.
So I wasn't supposed to get very far because I wasn't able to, I didn't know about bones or I didn't know about this item.
And I'm like, okay, so the more times I die, the more gameplay elements will be revealed, I guess.
And I just got, it's sort of annoyed me because it was like, how many times do I have to die before I can play this game?
I ended up just killing myself a few times and being like, okay, finally, some story is happening.
And I think I know all of the game mechanics now, finally I can start the game.
And I just lost over and over again.
I mean, there's things you have to do by playing the game.
You got the caged wolf, right?
Yeah.
I mean, you got to uncage that wolf in the game.
I did.
You got to make that.
So I mean, it's not just about like, you just got to die a bunch of times.
Right.
I don't know.
And you found the eye, right?
Yeah, I found the eye.
You told me you found the eye.
Yeah, stuff like that.
You got to make it happen.
Yeah.
I guess it just gets a little, it's a little tough, the game.
I'm not very good at it.
Well.
I get to the angler and I just, I don't have a good deck built up.
Maybe I chose the wrong path to get here.
And when I, you know, on some of the things I was unlucky, I chose the wrong card out
of the three that wouldn't have helped me.
My totem sucked or like, you know, whatever it is.
And then I get there and I'm like, I'm unprepared and then I lose.
And I'm like, you know what?
Fuck it.
I just got frustrated.
Yeah.
I mean, I get it.
I mean, that's how you get better is you, you, you lose a bunch of times and then you
think to yourself, hmm, why did I lose?
And then you don't, don't do that again.
Yeah.
Like I said, I know I'm wrong, but there's a lot of variables as to my failure.
I feel like in any other type of game, like, oh, it's a Mario.
Why did I lose in Mario?
Well, I jumped too early and I fell down.
It's very clear what happened.
And I should think about my timing of that particular jump better next time that, you
know, my, my problem is very clear.
The goal is very clear.
And I know how to approach improving when it comes to a inscription.
I don't know whether I could have done any better with the lack of the draw or whether
like, like what, what exactly did I do wrong?
I don't know.
I drew, I didn't draw the right card.
So my deck should be smaller or bigger or have less of one type of card and more of
another.
There's just too many, too, too many different little things that it could have been that
I don't really know what I'm the hell I'm doing the next time I boot it up.
So I'm like, okay, I guess I'll just hope to be luckier next time.
I don't feel like I have like a clear goal of how to improve myself as a player.
And that's, that's the frustrating part.
Okay.
But I mean, you know, as you say, you know that that is not correct.
Yeah.
That's why I hate roguelikes though.
This is like it.
I just want to know.
I just, I don't like thinking about it.
Yeah.
I mean, uh, yeah, I, I mean, that's like the, the, the, the goal is to figure out through
trial and error, how trial and error is so much.
Okay.
So that's why I hate it.
I hate it because, uh, when you go into, uh, like on a high difficulty setting,
what do you mean it's the reason you hate uncharted?
It's not similar.
No.
It's the slightest, the, the, the fighting, the shooting segments in uncharted, at least
uncharted one, often rely on a lot of trial and error.
You don't know exactly where is the best location for you to be where the next wave appears.
The, the next wave can appear behind you.
They can appear in such a way that if you haven't moved at a certain time, you're
fucked and it's like, you have to play and in uncharted the scenarios, you know, the
waves appear in the same places, the same types of guys every time.
So you learn by dying over and over where you should be.
And I hate that so much.
That's totally an unfair comparison.
I just know it's just the concept of trial and error piss me off.
It makes me mad in inscription.
I mean, it's trial and error.
I'm not saying that they're equivalent.
I'm just an example of a different type of trial and error.
The difference is that in inscription, like, yes, you do have to learn the rules and you
do learn the rules by losing and asking yourself, you know, what, what made me lose?
How can I avoid losing in the future?
But your eventual loss or victory is the sum total, you know, it's brought about by the
sum total of the decisions that you made.
It's not, you know, you're suddenly presented with a new scenario and, you know, you know,
you got to choose.
Do I go left, right or center and, you know, right or center will kill you and left is
how you win.
So, I mean, stick my neck out for inscription a little bit.
You know what?
I learned and I was, I learned this and I was like, yep, makes total sense.
Inscription was made by the same guys that made Pony Island.
Do you remember Pony Island?
I remember us hearing about it.
Pony Island sucks.
Pony Island was an idiot game made by rubes for babies.
It's got the same sort of general premise, doesn't it?
It's got a surface level game and then a sub game that is secret and mysterious and ooh,
you got to find the clues.
A little.
I mean, I'll be honest.
Aesthetically similar.
It is aesthetically similar in ways that I feel like it's.
I'd want to not spoil anything about it.
I still haven't gotten to whatever big spoiler there is.
There are some thematic and like meta-fictional similarities between Pony Island and inscription
in a way that makes me go like, yep, I totally see how the same guy made them.
But it's funny.
There are some things that I think are a little dumb about inscription.
And those are the things that made Pony Island really dumb and made me hate it.
So I don't know.
I just thought that was made me nod and go, yep, I see it.
Yep.
I see it.
I think fundamentally in a game what I like is having all the pieces to the puzzle.
I love puzzles.
I love point and click adventure games where I can have all of the items in my inventory
and try and think what I need to do.
And the most frustrating thing in a point and click adventure game is not having clicked
on something that doesn't look like you can click on it or like I thought I already did
and you didn't have a piece to the puzzle that is the piece you need.
That's the most annoying thing.
Yeah.
And so when I feel like when I start a new inscription game, I'm like, well, I lost,
but like, I don't know how to proceed.
I guess I will just, like, I don't know.
I just feel like I don't know all the time.
I don't feel like I'm getting better by losing.
I feel like, well, I don't, obviously I will.
You don't feel like you're getting better by losing?
I feel like I will eventually, but it's the sort of thing where I need to die like 50
times before I'm like, okay.
Okay.
I'm not smart.
I'm not smart like that.
You have, you have not made it past the Angler?
No.
Okay.
I fought them like maybe five times.
There's not that many.
That's not that, that's not, that's not very many.
No.
I died, I died a lot more than five times against the next big guy after the Angler.
So, I have a lot of, I have a lot of patience.
I have a lot of patience for stuff.
You know, the fact that like I felt like I was learning something every time I played
Inscription really like made it not that painful to lose.
I mean, when there was a run that I felt like, yeah, I lost it because I just didn't draw
what I wanted to or the game just didn't give me like good map choices.
And it didn't give me the choices that I wanted to build the deck that I wanted to build.
I did have runs like that.
And yeah, those are really frustrating and discouraging.
But I don't know.
I guess most runs, usually there was something I could be like, oh, okay.
Well, at least now I know not to do that or like, oh, well now I know that if I do that
it's good or I should keep my eye out for this in the future.
I think it was, it was just like, I got a bit of a bad first impression of what the cards
in the game were like, because Gek was like the first rare card I got after beating the
Prospector for the first time.
And Gek costs nothing.
And that led me to believe that sometimes cards can cost nothing.
And so I was always disappointed when a card cost anything.
I'm like, dang it.
How do I play this?
My deck was full of things that need, like I'm always low on like, bones and blood.
And I don't know how to make that be better.
I mean, well, you made a death card out of Gek with a zero cost, right?
I haven't seen him.
Oh, unlucky.
Do the death cards stay even after you die multiple times?
Yeah.
Oh, well, I guess I have been unlucky.
Which is, it's a mixed blessing though, because if you make a really good one, then like, you
aren't guaranteed to see it in the next game.
It might not come up for a while.
And like, as you make more death cards, like, you know, the pool gets diluted.
So if you have a really, if you have a really shitty run, you might have really shitty cards
and make a really shitty death card.
There's like five cards called Fuck You already.
You usually death, usually you can make a pretty good death card there.
Death cards tend to be better than normal cards.
Yeah, I remember like one of my first death cards, it was like a zero cost, like four, six,
with like double strike.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
And then I got it like the next run and I was like, I'm kicking ass with this.
I'm invincible.
But then because I kept making more death cards, it got rarer and rarer for me to see that one.
I was like, no, I want that one.
Just give me that one.
I could win with that one.
Well, that's super discouraging then, because I'm going to die like way more than the average player.
But the other death cards, the other death cards are also good.
They might not all be as like, as broken as that one.
But like, in general, they're pretty good.
You can you can pretty much always make a card that's better than like baseline.
I guess that's true.
I never picked Gek.
I never picked Gek because it's like, what do you it's like it's just a one one.
Like what do you what do you want that for?
I did I realized that like, yeah, it's it's humble.
But if you can boost it and it can become very valuable because it's free.
I mean, I know the value of a one one when like, you just need to do one damage to stop something from killing you.
And the fact that it's free means that like, I could always play it no matter what's happening unless my board is full.
Yeah, like the low cost is really useful.
It is I've realized the value of Gek, but I don't yeah, I don't think I ever played it as I was like working towards getting my first win.
Just because I was like the stats just aren't very the stats aren't very high.
No, but a free a free a free cast is like actually really good, especially if you are like having like pay if you're like running out of blood.
Like if you're if you're having blood struggles and like you can't pay for anything, then a free cast is like, OK, that gives you one turn where you can basically like get to blood in one turn.
And that's good.
That's really good if you want blood blood.
I've been playing a little bit of Casey's Mod just here and there, not as much as before.
I'm almost I think I've almost like 100% like beat everything that like Casey's Mod has to offer, not quite, but I'm pretty close.
What have been going for an hour?
54 minutes.
50 minutes.
OK.
I don't know.
Wow.
How are we so bad at doing a podcast after all these years after all these episodes?
Well, I mean, it's just because same reason I'm same reason I'm just bad at everything.
Same reason that I just suck in general is that I just don't do enough to talk to have things to talk about.
True.
Oh, I guess I could talk about this, although it's a little it's not that personal, but it's like it's vocal training, like voice feminization.
Sure.
I've been avoiding it because it's sort of weirdly like scary and frustrating just in concept.
I've looked into it a little bit here and there and I'm like, do these exercises for like four months and eventually you might start to sense something is different.
And yeah, I think I want to do it.
I'm going to try my best to do some stuff.
Every day like larynx raising exercises and going or whatever you do and stuff like that.
But I think the most frustrating thing about it based on what little I've done so far is that I have no idea if I'm doing it right because it's hard to judge that when I'm listening to a YouTube video do it.
I try to copy it and they just don't go into enough depth as to what it sounds like when you're doing it wrong.
What it sounds like when you're not doing it right.
What it sounds like when you know how it should feel like I just need more information.
Well, you just got it.
You just got to lose.
You just got to lose and learn what you did wrong.
I got to lose over and over again.
I got to trial and error it.
I guess.
I don't know.
I hate that so much.
Yeah.
Well, what do you just like just starting that?
I mean, I'm not doing anything at the moment.
Like how I'm speaking now is just how I'm speaking normally anyway.
And I think over months and years, I've naturally spoken a little higher than I used to.
I think some people have noticed if you go back to older PCPs, I did speak with a lot more bass in my voice.
But I still, I don't sound like that feminine.
I don't think I want to do something about that.
And it's really, it's really, I don't know, it's just hard to approach because it's one thing is that it's difficult to stick with something when I don't know whether I'm doing it right or not.
I just have to trust that whatever exercises I'm doing are not stupid and I'm fine.
And eventually I'll see some results, but also making silly noises and trying to sound feminine makes me feel like an absolute fool.
And it's sort of embarrassing even when I'm by myself.
Yeah, I understand.
It's like some gender weirdness.
But I want to try it.
I want to try and get better at that.
It's just like going to the gym when you're a scrawny weakling and it's like, oh, it's so embarrassing.
I'm so weak.
I look like such a loser lifting the bar with no plates on it.
All the beef cakes are going to make fun of me.
And then they do.
That's the worst part.
The worst part is that it's true. It's all true. All the worst things you imagine.
So I'm not going to talk about it every week because I don't want it to be like a running like, how's your voice this week?
How's your voice stupid?
I don't want to do anything like make a big deal of it.
But hopefully, slowly and surely, I will sound more femme in my regular speech.
I suppose it remains to be seen.
Oh, I did watch the evermore video.
I forgot what you said about it last time.
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
It's a good video.
Interesting.
I don't know.
Yeah, what else can I say?
The Vampire Diaries video hit 10 million views.
Yeah, I saw that actually.
It's been recommended.
Oh, you saw it recommend.
I saw she made an announcement for about 10 million views on Twitter.
That's a lot of views.
I don't know if you've seen that one.
I mean, it's good.
I think I clicked on it once and I didn't know anything about Vampire Diaries.
Yeah.
And I was like, maybe I don't care.
Maybe I'm gone.
How long is that video?
Like two hours?
It's hours.
It's not even that long.
No.
Evermore is longer.
Yeah, but Evermore gripped me.
I know what the medieval fantasy is and the idea of a park doing all that stuff.
Wow, that's so cool and imaginative.
There's no way it could go right.
The Evermore one, it's really uncomfortable.
Especially the parts where they're like,
what really stuck out to me is the parts about the actors being way too intimate with the guests
and the sort of live-action role-playing element being way too personal.
I thought it was the other way around, the guests were being too personal with the actors.
I remember there's the part where that one podcaster,
that Evermore podcaster is kneeling before that one woman
and the woman is yelling at some other actor who's playing her husband or whatever
and she's like, what would you have me do, my lord?
Would you have me go to bed with him?
And it's like, is this like a kid's theme park?
There's a lot of incongruity with the subject matter being dark fantasy D&D
and a family outing place.
It doesn't really work.
It's just very uncomfortable.
Remarkable stuff, though.
Um...
Uh...
I um...
It makes me wish that I had more autistic hyper fixations.
Oh yeah, they're fun. It's fun to have those.
Yeah, I wish I felt some sort of compulsion to pursue some extremely niche interests
so that I would have some very obscure facts to turn into content.
That would be cool.
Do you not have that in obscure weirdo webcomics?
Not really. I mean, I know a few of them, but I'm not out here discovering more very often.
I mean, I guess I could.
Maybe.
Has it turned out that Ben Saint is the least autistic of the PCP and he regrets it terribly?
As I've said before, my brain does work.
But to what end?
I'm pretty sure I'm neurotypical as far as I'm aware.
You've got a normal head on your shoulders and you're sad constantly.
It's a classic tale.
And it's just not doing me any favors, man.
It's not working. Something's got to change.
You've got to go down the neurotypical path and become a landlord or something.
You've got to get six figures and then drink wine and go to the football.
I mean, I guess those are things that some people do.
I associate having lots of money with being neurotypical.
With having lots of things neurotypical people do.
Watch football, drink wine and have lots of money.
Yeah.
They have like a pad and they have a barbecue and they invite their normal friends over.
Different kinds of neurotypical people do all of those things in different measures, I suppose.
I should have just stayed in academia.
I should have just gotten my PhD or something.
That's what should have happened.
Is that impossible to go back and do that?
It's not impossible now.
I mean, I guess I could do that.
It's daunting. It's hard.
Even then, I would be faced with the, well, what are you going to write your thesis on?
I would say, I don't know.
Nothing matters, man.
I don't care about anything.
So it's truly, I'm truly doomed.
No matter what.
Do you let yourself get vulnerable a lot?
What does that mean?
Putting yourself up with, I don't know, like vulnerable facts.
Like in general?
Yeah. I feel like a lot of creativity comes from vulnerability.
Like putting yourself out there in a way that you would feel cringe about or otherwise be afraid of people knowing.
Um...
Are you a closed off individual, Ben Saint?
Yeah, I guess so. Yeah, I guess a little bit, yeah.
Yeah, I feel like that would be a good place to start if you want to start feeling stuff.
I don't even know how I would do that.
It's a little difficult.
I've recently learned a good way to understand yourself like that is to think of what truly terrifies you,
but where the consequences are not actually life-threatening.
Like for an example, I am scared of wearing a dress.
For example, this is a gender thing. I'm scared of being judged for it.
Wearing a dress is not going to do anything bad, so my fear is not in the dress itself.
It's the vulnerability, you know, the sincerity with which I present myself and the judgment that could come from that.
That's where the fear comes from is being vulnerable.
And so when you're afraid of opening up about something, like really afraid,
it's probably because that's something that you really want, sort of an innate sort of feeling.
And that's how you know if you think about how you feel about things.
That's how you would be able to point to something and say,
okay, I probably want to do that, and then you could pursue it.
Hmm, okay, okay.
Just a thought.
Thinking, all right, all right.
I'll process that a little and get back to you, I guess.
One of those things, I mean, I felt very like open more recently.
It's been nice.
Let's see, you're having a good time on Twitter.
Yeah.
Imagine that.
Yeah, it's hard.
It's hard to understand.
Oh, well.
Kill the part of you that cringes, et cetera.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, let's just go to voicemails.
God, I gotta fucking download them.
No, it's not voicemail.com, it's speakpipe.com.
Slash PCP voicemail, right?
Yes.
Leave us a voicemail if you got something to say that nothing comes out when they move the lips.
Just a bunch of gibberish.
They forgot about Dre.
Okay.
Dre Lamau.
Let's see.
There's a message here.
It said mjirlink, what do we got?
Hang on, which page are we on?
Page one.
Oh, my God.
This is cool.
Regiflex.
See, this works.
Although, what's different about this versus normal type?
Like, what isn't normal type?
Do normal types not have muscles?
The way I understand normal type is, like, thematically, they are critters who are not jacked.
That's a little scrawny.
That's so unscientific.
I know.
Pokemon is weirdly, well, not weirdly, it's like, it's not scientific.
It tries to be in some things, but a lot of it is just sort of like vibes.
There's no real difference.
It's true.
It's too vibe-based.
It's too vibe-based for me.
Fighting beats normal because fighting is the Chad and normal is the Virgin.
It's the Virgin.
That makes sense.
I can understand that dynamic easily.
I'm trying to think, what is fighting weak against?
It is weak against psychic.
No, it's not weak against dark.
It's strong against dark.
It's weak against psychic.
It's weak against flying and fairy.
I think that's it.
Yeah.
It's funny how normal is not weak against flying, even though the assumption you would make is
that fighting is on the ground.
They're strong muscles, but they're not able to attack something that's like dive-bombing them.
But normal is also on the ground.
It's also on the ground.
It's just weaker.
Yeah.
But they're fine, actually.
Yeah, it's a bit shit, I guess I would say.
Hang on.
Are there more pictures in this album, or is it just the one?
It's just the one.
I think?
I'm double-checking.
Yeah, it's just the one.
Okay.
Well, let's check the next one.
It's another Imgur link.
Oh boy, what could it be?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm a cuck, crazy, unhinged cop killer.
I like that they're using a pretty normal photo of you, but your teeth are gold.
My teeth are gold, yeah.
I got that sinister red glint in my one eye.
This rules.
This owns, I don't know.
Yeah.
All I can do is say how I appreciate it for being good, and that's what's happening.
Next one is called Two Best Friends.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey Ben, would you say Gibb is your best friend?
Same to you, Gibb.
Would you say Ben is your best friend?
Don't put us on the spot like that.
You're definitely a very good friend.
Yeah.
I mean, do I have to choose between you and every other friend that I have?
Yeah, it's not, best friend is, it's a very like, like child, like term.
Like when you're on the playground, you have like a bunch of people you like, but there's
one that you like most, and that's your best friend.
Your best friend, yeah.
But that's only because when you're at school, that is your entire world.
You don't really go other places and meet different groups of friends in other places.
I would say that like a best friend implies that like you're together like a lot, like
you hang out like a lot of the time.
Yeah.
I don't really have any one.
Essentially.
Yeah.
But like, you know, I mean, we don't, I mean, do podcasts once a week.
I don't know.
To me, a best friend is like you're over like every day.
Yeah.
You're over every day, you know, drinking wine, watching the, going to the football game.
And having lots of money together.
And then talking about your properties you own.
My dad has a best friend.
Like him and his best friend since childhood, you know, they like, they own a boat together.
They go sailing together.
And like, you know, they're like, they're like peas in a pod, like lifelong chums.
There's a quite a number of people.
I would never own a boat with you.
I'm sorry.
No, that's fine.
There's plenty of people in my life that I would consider very good friends, but no one
single one that is like a pea in a pod situation.
Yeah.
I do like to keep to myself quite a lot.
Okay.
Well, I'm glad we're, it would be so awkward if I was like, nah, not really.
And you were like, yeah, absolutely.
How much would that suck?
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm glad we're on the same page.
Next one is listen first bonus meme days.
How shower you long without.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben saying keeps on saying, ah, the eight hour mega man feed is the other mega man feed.
Where is it?
Give it to me.
I want the mega man eight hour video.
Is it, is it even real?
Is it in the room with you, Ben?
This guy.
This guy is having.
It literally is.
It is what?
Real?
No, he said like, is it in the room with us?
Like, yes, it literally is.
It's in the room with you.
It kind of is.
It's on your little computer there.
On my little computer here.
This guy's having the appropriate reaction.
More people should be yelling at me about it not being out.
Everyone's just much too polite.
Mega polite.
Mega.
But I did, I did, I did already, I did already say what's up with it.
So I won't go into it again.
Days how shower long you without depends.
I mean, I'll be, I'll be honest if I'm not going out, if I'm not leaving my house or
seeing anyone, I will just not shower because like, what does it matter?
So sometimes I go a little while, but I don't, but I don't let myself be seen in
that state.
No, absolutely.
I'm going out.
It's time to scrub.
Yeah.
I think I go like maybe two days though without showering just because my hair needs to be
wetted and it's just the easiest way to do that.
I mean, otherwise it gets way too frizzy.
I don't wash it every, every shower, but I need to wet it every few days.
They say it's like, they say it's like bad for your hair to wash it too much.
Yeah.
You wash all of the natural occur naturally occurring oils out of your hair.
The point of washing your hair is to get rid of all the dirt that's accumulated, not to
get rid of the oil because that's, that's important.
So, so they say that's what the conditioner is to replace the oil, replace the oil while
your natural oil comes back.
Right.
Yeah.
That's what they say.
A shampoo conditioner is a scam because like the point of the shampoo is that it strips
the, it strips the oil off.
So, like, it doesn't make any sense to like have, oh, a thing that puts oil on the hair,
but also the shampoo that strips it off.
Yeah, it just doesn't seem to do much.
Yeah.
All right.
The next one is another Imgur album.
Oh, it's another, I think someone sent the same thing last week.
Vat of slime in the new Sonic.
I mean, it looks pretty cool.
I haven't seen this last week.
This maybe is a discord or something you saw.
Maybe, maybe it was.
Yeah.
No, no, no, I think it was on discord.
Someone sent me this.
It wasn't this same picture, but it was a picture of one of these tanks in the new Sonic.
Looks like pretty good slime.
Pretty slimy.
Pretty nuclear.
Damn, look at that.
Look at that reflection in the, in the ground.
I've heard the Sonic game is pretty empty and kind of janky.
I have, I haven't seen that much talk about it.
The little talk that I have seen has been like people being like, ooh, should I get cautiously
optimistic?
Oh, should I be cautiously optimistic about the release of this game?
Since the release, I've seen people saying like, yeah, it's bad law.
Whoops.
Yeah.
Breath of the Mild.
I'm sure that's been done.
Oof.
Oh, right.
It's open world, right?
That's like the thing about it.
Yeah.
What if you could go in every direction and, and it was not a curated experience?
Or at least not as curated.
Oh, I think that, I think the same person also sent another slime that they just, they just
sent two of them.
Let's, let's take a look.
Oh yeah.
Now we're talking.
Oh, it looks so small.
Yeah.
I think the back stone there, I thought was like a curb and then there was dirt and this
was like a little 3D model that had been 3D printed, but then that's in game and that's
real Sonic.
Yeah.
This looks like, this looks like we're looking at like one foot of space here and Sonic is
like an inch tall.
It's something very toy like about it.
Um, I just be like the consistency of the dirt.
Like that just looks like any rough dirt.
It's like, it looks like a little garden patch.
Anyway, uh, next one is called Manchigo Mitch.
Uh, three, two, one, go.
Hey, it's me, Manchigo Mitch.
Yes, another beloved character.
Fredo, you owe us money and you know what's going to happen if you don't pay an artist
the money, we're going to draw your kneecaps broken.
We're going to artistically render your kneecaps broken.
If you don't pay us the money.
No, that would be so embarrassing.
Capiche.
That's a very, that's a Chris Chan threat.
I like that.
The only two examples were the same example of the kneecaps.
I mean, what else?
We're going to break your kneecaps in drawn form and we're also going to paint them drawn
kneecaps broken.
This is, this is like a Chris Chan threat.
If you make Chris mad, she'll like put you in the comic and draw you being executed
by firing squad.
And you don't want that, do you?
Uh-oh.
Uh, next one is called Paneer Pauly.
Three, two, one, go.
Where is my money, Cheesy Manfredo?
Yep, yep, yep.
That's right, it's me, Paneer Pauly.
I'm with the mozzarella mafia and you owe us money.
I don't know what the words mean.
Paneer is a cheese.
Let me tell you what we're going to do to you.
We're going to take you.
We're going to age you.
We're going to stick you on a shelf.
We're going to flip you over for six months.
And then in six months time, you'll be six months older.
See how you like that.
No.
Twice before you screw us over again.
Out.
Paneer Pauly, out.
God.
We're going to age you.
We're going to put you in a meat smoking rack.
You're going to get fucking smoked.
Terrifying, terrifying.
Don't fuck with these guys.
You better get them their money is what I'm picking up.
Uh, next one is called Return of the Kring Us.
Three, two, one, go.
What's a PCP?
It's me.
Kring is the third.
I cringed at the cheesy for making a cringe kick starter.
And now I'm banging cyberpunk edge runners and chainsaw man.
They're very good.
Cool, man.
Keep, keep biggin.
Keep on biggin.
I think I might have mentioned last week that I mean to read chainsaw man at some point.
I still haven't done it.
It's the big zeitgeist anime of the moment.
You got to do it.
It's the moment anime.
I guess that I hate the moment.
I'll wait until it's not popular anymore and maybe then I'll read it.
Uh, cyberpunk edge runners, I have no interest in.
I mean, I didn't play the game.
I've heard that it's good.
I mean, everyone hated the game, but people say the anime is good.
So I'm sure that's fine.
I'm sure me not playing the game would be no impediment to me enjoying it.
I'm a little confused.
I haven't looked into it at all.
So the cyberpunk 2077 is different from whatever the anime is based on?
Well, 77 is the game.
The edge runner is, I think, I don't think it's, I'm not sure if it's like the same characters,
but I know it's set in the same world.
That's pretty much all I know about it.
But is it also a game?
No, it's an anime.
But like, is so people are playing the cyberpunk game?
No.
They're watching the anime called edge runners.
But edge runners has a game?
I thought it did.
Cyberpunk 77 was the game.
And then cyberpunk edge runners is the anime.
Spin off, I guess?
Spin off, I guess.
Spin off? Well, spin off, King.
But I don't know.
It doesn't look great.
Nothing about it appeals to me much.
So I'm probably not going to watch it.
Next one is Im...
It's another freaking Imjurling.
Wait a minute, did I download that last one?
Yes, I did.
Let's post the link, boy.
Let's do it.
Ew.
Oh, it's Ben Garrison.
It's Ben Garrison.
Oh, my God.
There's a little Ben Saint on there.
Hey, this is great.
Hey, this rules.
Endless War is...
Slimecorp is squeezing the teats of Endless War to get slime.
Yep, I mean, yeah, that's...
The slime cow.
This is amazing. This is fantastic.
Yeah, it's so true.
It's so true, it's so true.
It's sad but true.
This is our society when you think about it.
Scary. Look at his scary face.
Oh, my God.
Oh, there's dollars. Look, there's a couple of bucks.
There's a couple of bucks.
Oh, there's dollars underneath the slime in the bucket as well.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Slime is money.
Slime is money, as they say.
Yep.
I hope I never said that before.
Next one is...
Oh, God.
Endless War says map, right?
Why did... Oh, because you retweeted it as Endless War.
Right. This was...
KillerDog tweeted this in response to JK Rowling,
which was really funny.
I like this response a lot,
so I retweeted it on a bunch of different accounts.
Endless War liked it.
Endless War liked it and retweeted it.
That's an endorsement.
Retweets are endorsements.
It's funny. It's good.
No apologies.
Ben's Weekly Reminder, play Delta in Chapter 2.
Okay. Ben's Weekly Reminder, catch up to one piece.
Okay. Wait, was it last week that I said that I actually should do that,
so we could talk about it on the show?
Yeah, it was.
We could talk a little bit about that one piece as a corner,
as a little corner of the podcast.
Yeah. I was right that I should do that,
but nevertheless, I didn't.
But soon, perhaps, I should...
Maybe this week I'll do it, if I don't forget.
It's on my to-do list.
Next one is called You, 3, 2, 1, go.
I mean...
I wonder who he's owing it to.
Is it us?
Yeah, it's the PCP, so it's the time of your life.
Oh, well, I'm glad you had the time of your life watching the PCP.
Every single week you have the time of your life, right here,
on the Procrastinators podcast.
I know I'm having the time of my life.
Yeah, because my life is being timed.
My life is passing me by, so I'm having time of my life taken.
No, is it?
Okay, all spoilers.
Favorite character from inscription?
Oh, the butler.
The penguin.
I have an answer, but...
Can you speak in tongues so I don't understand?
How can I say it?
Okay.
No, I can't really say that.
That would give too much away.
It's the big green monster.
With the teeth.
It was you all along, the player.
You're the monster.
There's a dragon.
There's a little gremlin.
The blue one.
I know what that is.
That's a smurf.
That's all I'm saying.
My favorite one is the blue one, and I'm not going to explain why.
The game is run by little Jinjos from Banjo-Kazooie.
Okay, next one is called the funniest fart you've heard.
In the fart compilation where it made Jerma cry tears of pain from laughing so hard.
Sounds like it must have been a real humdinger.
He was trying to do like a bit while...
He was doing a bit where he's playing the part of a gym guy at the gym,
but he's got headphones in his ears, and headphones are blasting really loud music.
Somebody said, do a fart compilation, so he tried to act like the gym guy saying,
hey, you need a spotter?
But he's got the loudest fart compilation you've ever heard blasting out of his headphones
so the camera could pick it up, and he couldn't do it without laughing,
and he ended up crying on stream.
It was very, very, very funny.
Oh, sad. Oh, sad. Couldn't do it. Pitiful.
He tried. No, he got pretty far.
Cringe. I could have done it. I could have done it easily.
Okay, next one is, Ben, prove you are a good ally right now.
Give, give, a compliment.
His hesitation is saying so much.
It's too hard. It's too hard.
You can do it, Ben. You can be a good ally.
You don't want to get canceled, do you?
No, I don't, no, I don't want that, so...
What's, I mean, what's a good one?
That's a good one. God ask me.
Yeah, okay.
Give your, your very...
Try to think of a rule. Okay, you're, you're a...
You're, you're, you're very sincere.
You're very sincere with your, when you,
when you emote or express a feeling,
I just, it's very, it's, you always do it with sincerity,
and I think that's cool.
Well, thank you.
That's a good quality for a person to have, in my opinion.
Yes.
So there.
No, fuck you.
Next one is called, an idea.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
So a video of Ben jump-scaring Nate shitting his pants
is the way to get Nate back on the PCP.
Was, was that the point?
Is that this is how to get Nate back on the PCP?
Yeah, that's what they started with.
Oh, well, I mean, it would add him to the content
and that it would be a video of him being scared
to the point of pissing and shitting himself.
So, I mean, it, yeah, it would be against his will,
but I mean, it would work.
Yeah, I see no, I see no downsides.
I think he's cracked the code.
Oh, next, next one is called, another idea.
Three, two, one, go.
Put Ben in the walls.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
I mean, I think it would, I think it, I think it might work.
It's just crazy enough to work.
So a little plush of Brony Curious.
We need one of those.
Yeah, that's the part that's hard.
That's the part that might be impossible.
I don't think I've ever seen a fan made Brony Curious plush.
I do not recall such a thing.
Well, we'll just have to do it ourselves.
When life gives you lemons.
You make Brony Curious.
Next one is called, did I download that one?
No, I downloaded, last one I downloaded was 34.
So I got to download an idea and I got to download another idea.
Okay.
Next one is last very, very, very important idea.
Three, two, one, go.
Here is how we bring back all the other PCP members.
We don't.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I'm clapping.
Next one is called, at my wit's end, three, two, one, go.
It's insanity.
How could anyone think the earth is around?
There's no evidence.
There's no proof.
He's right.
It sounds like you're at your wit's end.
There's no proof.
Oh, you've seen the curvature of the earth.
Yeah.
Well, how do you know?
How do you know that that picture?
What's the evidence that this picture is real?
You see, I like curvy women and so I get a bono whenever I look at the earth.
So, you know, that's my evidence.
What's the evidence that all those photographs of the earth from space showing it being round
are real?
Prove that those aren't just fake.
You can't.
Nobody can.
Oh, no.
How do I know?
I mean, how do I know that some demon is not living in my mind manipulating my brain in
order that I simply experience and see evidence of the roundness of the earth?
But how do I know that it's not just being manipulated by a malicious demon in my mind?
You can't do it.
Well, what if the demon isn't so bad after all?
No, he's bad.
No, he's bad because Democrats put him there.
That's the demon talking.
Your mind is compromised.
Your opinion of the demon is incorrect.
Exactly.
The demon would want you to think.
The demon wants you to think that it's good that he has made you want to get vaccinated
against the coronavirus.
He wants you to think that that's OK, even though it's clearly not.
Next one is called a real genuine voicemail.
Finally.
Wow.
Finally, a real voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
We've been had.
He played on our expectations.
Fuck.
How could we have been so blind?
Is he going to twist at the end?
He's just clearing his throat.
Don't worry about it.
OK, no.
No.
Yeah, he's just clearing his throat.
He's just building up to like a really amazing.
Oh, no, it's over.
OK.
Next one is called me.
Three, two, one, go.
Do you think having a passion is necessary for a good life?
Yeah.
I mean, what else are you going to do if you don't have one?
You're just going to be miserable like me.
If you got all the time in the world and like money, passion is like what makes you feel
like doing anything.
Yeah.
So like, oh, you're really like pomegranates, got a passion for those, not passion fruit.
You got a passion for pomegranates.
So you wake up in the morning, you get yourself for pomegranate.
That's a passion.
That's something you would live for.
Hypothetically.
Just like in Hades.
Yeah.
That's why they use that.
If you don't have passion, then you'll be dispassionate about everything you do.
You could see every single fruit and you would just say whatever.
Yeah.
And that's not a life.
That's when you're a skeleton, you do that.
Yeah.
Because you can't eat them.
All right.
There we go.
Question answered.
This one is called VVV the comic.
It stands for Vinny VVV.
My favorite part of the week.
We'll see.
Okay.
So I'm playing the guitar.
You're playing the guitar.
My guitar.
I'm saying Ben.
Ben, you're vaping like a lot.
Ben.
It's too much.
I've missed making gummies with his ingredient.
I enjoyed for the first time in months.
I think it's 13 ingredient and I'm overjoyed for the first time in months.
Also, your teeth.
What are you doing?
I'm smiling.
I'm smiling so hard you can see my gums.
Oh my God.
I've never seen you smile before.
No.
You wouldn't have.
This is what it looks like.
Tragically.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then we've got.
Shit.
Wait.
Who's the driver is?
Error.
Yes.
That's right.
With the hogs.
Yes.
Ben expels a lot of vapor like a lot.
You good now?
Whoops.
That'll be your deposit.
Dang it.
What?
Just because I vaped a lot?
Just air it out.
You vaped so much that you dissolved the roof and it fell off.
Oh.
Bummer.
I'm not.
I'm nonplussed about this.
And I'm sad trombone.
Look at my face.
Look at my chin.
Look at that pig.
He's looking back.
He's blushing a little bit.
What's he thinking about?
I think he's embarrassed for me.
In the next one, are you holding a little pink mushroom?
I think that maybe I'm doing makeup.
I'm looking in a mirror.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
You're.
Yes.
That's right.
Putting on eyeliner or something.
Yeah.
You can see it in the next one.
It's a mirror.
Oh.
And then what are you doing, Gib?
I'm drawing on my eyebrows.
Why are?
You melted them along with the roof.
You silly freaking billy.
Oh my bad.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I wouldn't say that.
Fuck you.
It's so out of character.
Yeah.
I know.
And I'm not mad.
It's just the wind blowing on me causing me to put more effort into keeping it looking
good.
You do look good.
No.
You've done it.
You got him.
Thanks.
You made it look so easy being yourself and doing what feels natural.
Where is this going?
I do have to steal myself against my fear of rejection.
Rejection from society and all that.
Being myself in earnest and having that dismissed or thrown back in my face.
That hurts more than what it used to.
I'm going to throw up.
Yeah.
It's the choice to put it out there.
Oh God.
There's another panel like this after this.
I get it.
I respect the hell out of it.
I'm just kind of absorbing it.
The earnest vibe from you.
It's cool.
I wish I hadn't complimented you on being sincere.
I wish I'd picked something else.
Oh, okay.
The dialogue continues.
Oh, speaking of cool things.
I've been experimenting with some goth makeup styles.
Goth gib, huh?
Lol, yeah.
I haven't taken pics of myself.
It was just like things I've said or anything.
But I've been looking at different things I could do.
I love the goth look.
I never entertained the idea of buying makeup and doing it though.
I brought some makeup.
Would you be willing to let me put it on you?
Well, I wouldn't do that.
Yeah.
I've always wanted to look like a cool goth guy.
I've never had the confidence to do it.
Haha, I got you Ben.
Lol, what are friends for?
Lol magic.
It certainly is.
It's so cringe.
Haha, yes.
Okay, all right.
Getting off the highway.
Thank you, Irarre.
Here's where I'm dropping you off, fam.
You're welcome, gib.
I'll send you the receipt, Ben.
Your pain.
Your pain where Ben St. lives.
Sure.
I forgot to draw the dialogue bubbles.
I started to have fun drawing the darkness wherein Ben St. lives.
In the darkest main.
So here's what it said in the last panel.
Ben, we're a few blocks down from where I live.
I'll guess we'll have to walk it.
Irarre, I would have driven us to your house had you not dissolved the carriage.
Yeah, probably.
Well, this is the saga continued.
The saga fucking continues.
People tuning.
Keep it up.
Viewership skyrocketing as people tune in to the cliffhangers of what's going to happen
in the next VinnyVinny VG comment.
Where's this going?
Truly a mystery.
Thank you again.
Thank you for another installment, Vinny.
I am on the edge of my seat.
Let's see.
Have we gotten any more?
Okay, the next one is the last one.
It's called a complaint from a very disgruntled fan at RFCK.
Three, two, one, go.
On episode 334 of the Procrastinator's podcast,
Given Take mentioned building a tower all the way up to the moon
and then jumping out of it and landing on the moon.
And I cannot believe.
I simply cannot believe that Ben Shane would not bring up the fact that this exact
concept has already been carried out in season three of RFCK Endless War.
When N1 of the slime corp industry went to the top of this big tower,
the slime corp HQ tower and jumped out and landed on the moon and got the red change.
Ben Shane, I will destroy you.
Fine.
Thanks.
Thanks for the voicemail.
Yeah, what was that?
That's right.
That did happen.
I'm sorry.
I was thinking about Mega Man.
I was thinking about Mega Man and how the orbital elevator through the Jacob project in X8.
That was just the first thing that came to mind.
I kind of miss knowing all of the lore of Endless Wars, like many cool things that happen.
I remember there was something going on at some point with like the ends of slime corp and 7 and 1, whatever.
I think that might be, yeah.
They were fighting something or maybe I imagined it, but there was some sort of event and it was cool,
but I didn't really pay attention to it.
Yeah, I think that was the season three finale.
I think that's what this disgruntled caller is talking about.
There was, gosh, yeah.
I'm probably not the best person to explain it, but I understand.
Yeah, N1 went to the moon and got the red chains.
And I think N1 turned out to be another death furnace himself.
Or maybe that was N0.
Ah, shit.
There was another death furnace that like sort of, I don't want to get it wrong.
I remember there were red chains and there was another death furnace and he was one of the ends.
It was either N1 or N0.
And I think, yeah, there was like an ARG thing where I think players had to like ascend the tower and like battle him.
I think that was it.
I hope I'm not making a fool of myself.
I mean, there's more to it, obviously, because I was not like following it super closely.
I just kind of heard about it after the fact.
The devs like did it all on their own.
Yeah, I remember like every so often there would be like a broadcast by one of the end operatives.
And I think it was a girl who has glasses, scientist girl.
Yeah.
And she said stuff and then there was like the little twink boy with the yellow hair or something.
Yes, the one with like the colorful outfit.
Yeah.
They would have like cryptic things talking about stuff and things.
And I think around the time I was considering like extending and finishing like Red Noir,
I was trying to think, how do I incorporate all of this stuff into Red Man's stupid mystery show?
But I couldn't figure it out because there's ARG stuff and I'm like, I'm really bad at ARGs.
I'm not patient at all.
At the moment, the shit, I hope I'm not behind, but I think the current meta is about like relics.
It's about like uncovering like ancient relics, like excavating them from the ground or something.
Actually, that was a while ago.
There might have been more developments on that front that I have not.
The last I remember hearing was we're uncovering ancient relics.
That's the thing.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
Disgruntled, disgruntled caller.
That was the last voicemail.
Oh, no.
Wait, no, that is.
I re-spreshed, but it did a thing.
I definitely had passion in those days when Endless War was just getting off the ground and we were getting it going.
I was waking up every day being like, yeah, time to work on the Endless War code.
Yeah, time to work on getting Season 2 launched.
Time to work on adding slime oids, lol.
Everyone's going to think this is so silly when this feature's done.
Those were the days.
Those were fun days.
Yeah, those were good times.
Well, anyway, that's the show.
I think days like that could come back.
You think so?
Yeah.
Maybe?
I don't know how.
I don't know how to reach that.
You've got to do what Mufasa says.
You've got to do the remember who you are, Simba.
Look in the clouds.
Look in the reflection.
It's you.
It's Ben Saint.
Remember who you are.
Yeah.
And then also do something about it.
That's the part that Mufasa didn't mention.
I think I remember who I am.
I think so.
I don't know what to do about it.
I don't know how to deal with that problem.
Yeah.
It's not really my place to tell you exactly what to do.
I don't really know.
This is the...
The soon to be concluded Ben Depression arc is...
Next week it'll be over.
Oh, no, don't say next week because it will never be next week.
No, it'll be the end of the month.
End of the month it'll be over.
The dramatic conclusion.
Everything changes.
The total status quo.
Shake up.
It's coming and...
Unless something really terrible happens to screw up the schedule.
Like, yeah, no, it's basically done.
No, it's basically done.
I think I'll feel a weight off my shoulders when the video is out.
For sure, yeah.
We'll see how I feel after that.
Premiering...
If you check my channel for a trailer that will announce when it's coming out,
I'm expecting that I will probably release it on Saturday tomorrow,
the day after this video is live.
So if you're free tomorrow, maybe check out the premiere of my Mega Man video
that I keep saying is coming.
Well, one of these days it will and I think this is it.
I really think we're there.
I think we've arrived, so...
Oh, yeah.
Just fucking watch it.
Fucking watch it, leave a comment.
Puts my Patreon.
And push the procrastinatorspatron.com
and also the procrastinators.
And of course, pledge the procrastinators Patreon.
We should do another bonus episode.
Yeah, what about...
Hey, you know what was fun?
Hey, I don't know.
You know what was fun?
Streaming this week.
Streaming was pretty good.
Yeah.
That was nice.
Had a good time.
We should...
Oh, we didn't even talk about that.
I guess there's not that much to say,
but yeah, we did stream for the first time in like two or three months, I think.
Yeah.
It had a little bit of an internet hiccup with like weird settings that...
But like it was quite stable other than that.
My...
You know, my internet.
Well, supposedly someone came and looked at my internet yesterday.
So, I mean, I guess we'll see going forward if my connection is better and more stable
and it's not as...
And it will stop fucking up.
I can't say with certainty right now, but maybe.
Anyway, we should stream more because it was fun.
Had a good time.
Make a main video.
Anything else?
I don't know.
A big girl squish.
Okay.
Twitter.com.
Yeah.
Based.
Okay, I guess that's the end of the episode.
Do we even make it two hours?
We're not even at two hours?
You know what?
It's the good old days.
It's the good old days of the PCP.
One hour episodes.
One hour 54 minutes is equatable to one hour.
It rounds down.
Yeah, it rounds down.
All right, that's it.
Short episode, but I hope you enjoyed it.
I won't belabor the point any longer.
See you next week.
See ya, everybody.
Peace out, goodbye.
Goodbye.