I'm sorry darling, I'm listening to the PCP right now, it's so addis-
I'm mad as hell, and I'm not going to take it anymore!
And we got Nate Boy.
Maybe it's deeply repressed inner rage. I can relate to that. Hello everyone.
It's like when the anime girls kind of smile and they're like happy and hello, but then
you see the aura.
It's like that dope sakura, like inner sakura. It's inner mage. Inner mage is rage. So there's
mage and then rage.
On the inside.
She's called leaf, he'll stop changing my lore.
No, I'm making the lore right now. It's new, it's brand new. HD remix changed all that
code and it made the aspect ratio change the gameplay.
From its natural Lithuanian into English is now, lethal is rage now.
It's also a bit crunched and bit stretched and re-resed and re-uploaded and resized.
60 FPS.
Featuring Dante from the Devil May Crackers.
Well, okay, Tom, you're actually mad about something we want to hear about.
Alright, alright.
So what's that?
Let me tell you my story. This is like the pettiest rage, but it is rage and it pisses
me off. So I, as you know, me and Digi have this I Am Games channel and so I've been slowly
but surely acquiring more gaming things just to make the entire process more easy to do.
Like I spent all this time getting like a dedicated streaming thing set up and we have
like a server that has like 8 terabytes of storage so we can easily dump footage and crap
on there and any computer can access it and all that stuff.
But I'm also bringing all my game stuff because despite the title of the show, Digi is not
games, alright? He's not good at video games so I'm going to have to pick up all the slack
to make our show title not bullshit.
I Am Fraud.
Yeah, yeah, exactly. So I, the reason it's called I Am Games and not we are games is
because I'm the only one who's games.
I Am Games and not so games.
Exactly. He's not games at all.
This show is counterfeit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Give us money anyways. So um, brought all of my games over, brought
all that shit but one of the things I kept forgetting was my switch dock because initially
I just put like the essentials in my car because I'm like I'm never going to use the switch
dock because I don't have a TV in there.
So but then once Digi's like just come bum at my house I'm like fine. So then all of
a sudden all this shit I ignored is now necessary again.
Yes.
I was thinking of maybe doing a video on Splatoon 2 for I Am Games and why it's like
I'll play the best multiplayer game ever and so I needed a pro controller but I didn't
want to spend a lot of money because I knew I wasn't going to use a pro controller all
that often because I find the Joy-Cons very comfortable.
Like if I, I like kind of just sitting on the couch without the grip and just having
one in each hand just kind of chilling and be like yeah I'm just playing a fucking video.
Do you use the little stand and prop it up on a table or something?
No, I mean if I'm playing like in handheld mode I will just put it on the TV in the dock
but when I'm just kind of chilling like on the couch I'll just pull the Joy-Cons off
and I won't put them in the grip. I'll just hold one in each hand and just kind of just
relax.
Wait but where's the screen? But where's the screen in this situation?
Oh that would be in the dock on the TV.
Oh oh it's oh okay alright.
Yeah so that's when I'm playing it in docked mode. In handheld mode I'll just play it in
handheld mode.
So I was like I need a new controller because I know in case Digi wants to play he wanted
an actual controller and if I want to play Splatoon 2 well for footage I'm gonna have
to like actually have a real controller.
So I went in to Walmart because I just happened to be there and I'm like I'm gonna get a controller
while I'm here but they're like $60 and I wasn't feeling that but I saw they also had wired
versions for $25 and I was like that's way better and it's like a Splatoon version of
the controller. I'm like this is like systematically relevant everything and it looks super fucking
cool. I'll put a picture up and I'll put it in the show notes or whatever so you can see
what it looks like because it looks dope as fuck.
So it's like alright and it's like Nintendo like made like a cheaper version for poor people.
I like it so I bought it and then I brought it home and I unboxed it and I realized I
made an error and the error is that it is not a Nintendo branded controller. They just
they used the Nintendo Switch logo and used the exact same design packaging as all the
other first party Switch accessories to make retards like me think it was first party and
then they have their logo is called Power A but it's designed on the package to look
just like a Nintendo logo because it's in like the kind of like rounded design. So when
you just look at it quickly like I did it reads exactly like a first party controller
and it has like all the right logos and everything on there and I was totally fucking livid because
I gave these motherfuckers who I don't even I haven't even tested this yet it could be
a piece of shit and I have no idea. It feels nice but but it's not Nintendo and I don't
buy third party controllers because they're always trash.
Okay so you got got by the marketing but it's possible it still works well.
It could be good. I don't know. I know I can definitely tell by holding it it probably
doesn't have like rumble or anything built in because it's very light but I don't really
care too much about rumble as long as the aiming is better so I don't look like an idiot
trying to play on IM games but I'm mad because it looks so cool and it has all the Splatoon
logos and it had the Nintendo Switch logo on the packaging and it looks straight up like
a Nintendo thing but they fooled me and I'm gonna burn this company to the ground. Power
A I'm coming for you. I'm gonna use my fucking power to shove it up your a-hole.
I definitely want to see a picture of this in the show notes or whatever.
Yeah I will.
Sounds fascinating.
I think like third party control I mean clearly they're they're being sneaky fucks and that's
not good but third party controllers are often you know good enough and I have a story.
I'd like to know whether it whether or not like update us on whether it works.
There's a sweet spot between the like just the up price because it's first party and
the like low point of just like an actually shitty right.
I have a small story also like so me and my boyfriend we have a
Xbox controllers for our PCs and they're pretty good but like they're getting on in
years and the wires are just like disconnecting from time to time so we decided to buy some
new controllers and we found some sort of like slightly cheaper ones and we bought them
and it turns out they were third party even though they looked exactly like the original
Xbox.
It just they didn't have that here.
Yeah they didn't they didn't have the X of where the Xbox was supposed to be the box
controller.
I hate when they do that to me.
The thing that amazed me.
Oh wait.
Yeah.
Just quickly and both of the controllers have bugs in them and it was so annoying.
Wait.
Actual literal bugs like creepy crawlies are like when one of them had like the button
was to it's like an actual like ant farm.
Now that would be cool.
I wouldn't complain about that.
Why would you not complain about that?
But I like ants and ant farms.
This is a cool thing.
I would like to have an ant farm.
Then you should be on the next bonus episode made.
Just all I'm saying.
I won't say any more than that.
I know.
I will be.
Shit.
This is for the viewers mage.
It's for the viewers.
Yeah.
My thing that pissed the reason I was so pissed is not because it's a third party controller.
It's because I was purchased under false pretenses.
If I said oh it's a third party controller that's why it's cheaper.
And it was like you remember back in the day when you bought like a mad cat's controller
because you were like 10 and your parents wouldn't spend the full money you're like at least
I know what I'm getting into.
It's clearly has like that obnoxious mad cat's logo with the paw and like the claw marks.
And you knew it wasn't legit.
This was lying to me.
And that's where my disdain comes from.
And you bought this in Walmart right?
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
It was with all the Nintendo accessories like all like the official controllers and
everything and right there it was just sitting there.
It wasn't off to the side.
It was among them.
It makes me think even the people who stocked it were confused.
I would not be shocked.
And I'm ready to go to war with this company.
Power A I'm coming for you.
You're gonna die.
I just want to say that fucking mad cats every time mad cats gets brought up I always have
to say my funny little little quip that mad cats is good and I don't know why people hate
it.
That was very funny.
It's funny because it's true.
I've had like the one PlayStation 2 controller that has survived since I was a child is the
mad cat's one.
All the others broke.
Well okay.
And the official ones died.
Yes.
Really?
I had to buy a new one.
They're still going strong.
Kind of recently.
Except for the ones that I smash in a rage when playing Soul Calibur 2.
I was gonna say is it because the other ones were launched through the TV in a bout of
impotent rage at Dark Souls or you know some other game.
That's on my diet.
That's unrelated.
That's not that's you know.
No they survived all of that.
It was for other reasons.
Other reasons.
Yeah.
Okay.
Those ants all over them.
They took them out of my picnic basket and they.
Hey I do want to say though the the the I know I say this all the time but like my Nintendo
Switch pro controller it's like the actual on-brand one.
Like I actually love it and it's one of my favorite controllers ever.
Man.
It feels great.
Okay.
Here's actually a question about the pro controller.
The pro controller itself has the analog sticks like on the same side right.
Like they're like on each side and then the buttons are below it because like.
No actually no it's set up the way that switches with like on the left the the the thumb stick
is up top on the right down below that is that is the proper way to have those.
That's one thing that still pisses me off about PlayStation controllers that the analog
sticks are too close to each other and I'm not five and my hands need more clearance
than that.
This controller has them set up properly which is why I'm okay with it.
They're offset ever since the OG Xbox did that that should have become the standard.
I think that PlayStation just got so like the layout of the PlayStation control is kind
of like on brand.
It is.
I think they just don't want to change it.
But I still don't like it as much and that's as a hardcore Sony fanboy.
That's my one point of contention.
It's like you got to give props to for Sony to like for implementing the DualShox system
because they invented it and it's totally awesome but like they got a little bit it's
like when you invent something but then someone else makes a better version like you want
to stick with this like one that you made because it's like the special one that's special
to you and shit but really there's probably better ways to be doing things that other
people figure out.
There's like a third party that did make a PlayStation 4 controller that is just an
Xbox controller that works in PlayStation and I'm very tempted to try it at some point.
Well that's dope.
Maybe some but I don't play shooters on PlayStation so it really doesn't matter at that point.
Tom let's please play Splatoon with me online.
I want to play Splatoon with someone.
Do you have Nintendo online since you have to pay now?
I got the one week free trial that I probably already like I was complaining about the fact
that I had to pay for it on I Am Games and someone DM'd me yesterday and said oh I have
the part they're like family plan just give me your email and I'll add you so now I have
what dude.
Yeah they just they added me for free.
I'm like you're a fucking hero.
Adopt me and get me on your family plan too.
I want to be your son sir.
Maybe you should you should you should ask them I'll see if they said they have like
three slots open and nothing to do with them so they might actually put me in your slot
friend put me in your fucking slot I will wait to hear from you whoever you are out there
because I was I was about to buy it the other day and you know what like it's $20 for a year
like it sucks that we have to pay and it's utterly retarded but like okay I can afford
that I can afford $20 and you get NES games which I guess but the NES lineup is really
shit but at least it's something.
It is it's more than absolutely zero I guess so I mean I would just emulate any of those
games but you know whatever you know sometimes you know there's a thing where like that we
have infinite games our disposal via emulators basically but like I don't actually play like
any of those games just because I don't think about them and I don't like come up that's
it's Nintendo can just prompt me on my switch when they like hey we just downloaded like
I don't know Excitebike for you I've never played Excitebike that's in Smash Bros.
Let me see what the fucking excitement's about.
It's funny because me and Digi were talking about this on IM Games about how yeah when
emulators like became a thing and I did the same thing with my DS because I had like the
flash card that let you just like down I love my flash card on my DS yeah it's just like
you play a game for like 20 minutes like oh I wonder what else I can play and then you
get spoiled yeah fucking spoiled when you never follow through but when you were 10 and you
had an N64 you played Star Fox 64 for years because that's all you had and you had to
make it work.
I see this as a possible death of humanity like that like access to infinite information
will make us all like not give a shit about anything.
I call it death by decadence we've become so fucking privileged to have all this entertainment
at our fingertips so we don't value any of it anymore.
That's what killed the Roman Empire as I recall something like that.
By the way Gibb appears to have just died oh excuse me oh no I really hope he didn't
restart his audio because I don't feel like editing more than that.
It would just be his internet.
Well okay well let's let him go and we'll see if he joins back.
I did have another subject to bring it's a totally left turn from here.
Go for it man.
I'm done.
I rage is vented.
I feel better.
Good.
So I just got back I took me and the lady and the dog went to a place nearby at her at
her suggestion a place called Findlay Market in Cincinnati it's like a it's like an open
air market and it's very similar to I think it's Quincy Market in Boston Tom you know
the one I'm talking about that that place Munchie takes us to and we went to it's got
like that Dix last resort and all those whatever the market is in Boston I can't remember Findlay
Market is like that in Cincinnati and I just we were there and we were there for like an
hour or two and we walked around we had the dog it was fun and like the point I'm trying
to get to with this was I had such a wonderful time just like being out among normal human
beings and like experiencing what it's like to just be a normal human not trapped on the
internet you know just slowly seeking or allowing my life to have away into the electronic data
sphere.
Um everyone was just like cool and we got delicious food and it was just a great time
and I saw human beings like being nice to each other and I'm just like the internet
is so shit uh like Twitter and all these like people sniping each other with like uh fucking
videos attacking other people and and all that stuff I hate all that hey get hey welcome
welcome.
Don't you hate it when you disconnect at the exact moment where you think you like people
have stepped aside to let you speak and then you say something for a while and.
That is unfortunate.
Do you want to finish a point or anything?
Uh I was just gonna ask uh how big can a Nintendo family be on the online thing.
I believe it's up to eight people.
I think you guys have three.
Oh.
Oh eight.
It's eight.
Yeah okay.
This man should legally adopt me.
Yes.
That's what should happen.
What's happening now then?
Well give I just brought up that I just got back from this place called Findlay Market
which is like remember that open-air market in Boston that we all went to and hung out
with that Munchie brought us to you know.
Uh yeah.
You know what I'm talking about.
Well whatever like I had been there before when I was young but I just remember I associate
with Munchie now um but like I went to I just found one Michelle found one uh from a friend
uh in Cincinnati called Findlay Market and like I just had such a great time just hanging
out me and her and the dog walking around and just like doing stuff we're gonna go dude
okay here's an amazing thing it's pretty close to the University of Cincinnati which
is like a pretty pretty nice thing it draws a lot of tourists and stuff.
There are just this is real this is real there are just electronic scooters around this market
that they just leave for anyone to just use and when you're done you simply just like
leave it on the sidewalk you don't like put it anywhere specifically and just walk away
and you're done and that's it and then someone else can just take it and use it for a while
and apparently the system just like works great and I guess they don't get stolen extremely
quickly.
So this is me a story I was told by my sister's boyfriend's husband actually right now.
Do you see her boyfriend's husband?
No my my sister's boyfriend but he's a husband now I remember they got married.
Oh right.
Yeah so so like her boyfriend has a husband it's a very complicated relationship.
Yeah.
No.
Anywho so so in the opinion they apparently had a similar sort of setup system with orange
bikes and that they were gonna you know all you just gonna take with the bike and you
know you place it down and someone else can use it yada yada but apparently it backfired
so badly because all the bikes got stolen and repainted and I just I just thought what
did you expect?
Google does the same thing.
That's what I would expect too.
The thing is though they're actually like this scooter thing is like specifically for
this marketplace Finlay market but around UC University of Cincinnati like there's a
system of like these red bikes because it's like red is like the color of UC and whatever.
There's like tons of like these red bike rental booths where you you know you put in quarter
and you take like the bike out or whatever and then you just return it to like because
there's lots of stations to like dock them.
So those have like a pickup and drop off point these scooters do not which is true like who
charges them at the end of the day.
I know they're not but every time you say scooter I just imagine people on razor scooters
and shit and it's evidently funny to me and you know what you know I know I'm on a tangent
here but this just reminds me of like before we went you know I did I mention that for
Michelle's birthday I bought her like a boosted board type electric skateboard yeah it's called
it's an Adam is the brand but it's dope like I just for fun I just put on my helmet went
outside and just like skateboarded around and had such a great time.
Just like doing things in real life is like fun and good you guys I just want to let you
know.
I can't believe you that sounds that sounds terrifying to me.
It's great.
I love it.
Maybe.
I'll consider that.
Dude okay it's like imagine Pokemon Go but like without the phone and just like but you
leave the real life there and like that's what it is like imagine that I don't know about
that.
I actually did regret not bringing my Pokemon Go.
I mean I I don't know my general like location in the world is like kind of boring if just
to walk around electric skateboard you can make it fun by just scooting.
Yeah but there's like this is like Casey Neistat just does what he does he has his electric
skateboard and he's he's it makes everything more fun maybe Casey Neistat has been called
a professional fun haver which I think is a very accurate title man but I like him.
Like it's just like everything around is just suburban houses for miles because we're on
the edge of London.
Literally dab on them on your electric skateboard as you cruise by it's just it's just nothing
much like like if I went into London if I went if I went into London then I would be
like I can see like stuff happening like there's people and there's buildings and it's cool
and there's a river.
I love rivers.
I love looking at the river.
I love looking at the river when when the sun's going down and it's shimmery shining all
over it.
That's good.
Oh that reminds me while I was heading back home to England I was in London waiting for
my train and I saw a guy that looked kind of like you just a little bit taller and I just
I dropped kicked him.
No he was on the opposite side of the of the track so you wanted to drop kick him but you
didn't have the opportunity.
Got a running start in this fucking power kick.
Launched across the track.
I stared at him like with squinty eyes I was like is that is that hippo is that no that
can be hippo.
Oh I saw I saw Digi in May out at just at this market and by that I mean there was just
a big bearded guy with Lenin shades and some girl with him and I was like there they are
that's them.
Disgusting.
Shout out to all these fakers at the King Richard's Fair right now I believe is where
they actually were.
Oh King Richard's Fair going on.
I think that's where they are right now they went to some sort of medieval fair and I was
supposed to go.
Oh that's dope.
That's dope.
We should talk about that.
Yeah.
I love where King Richard's Fair is going.
I went once back in a day when I was a wee lad and it was the funnest ship it was super
fucking cool.
Yeah.
Jousting is awesome and it should not have gone away.
In fact we should have just adapted to the times.
Yeah we do that now on electric skateboards might do.
I was going to say we should just have people in fucking cars or motorcycles jousting.
Yeah that's it.
That'd be fucking sick.
Like modern.
That'd be a good video game so how much would you make that make a video game that's just
like jousting 2089 or something or like you get like shiny red boxing gloves on a boosted
board you go as fast as you possibly can and it's like that'd be dope and you just try
to knock the other person out.
Tony Hawk's pro jousting.
Let's do it.
Hell yeah.
Hey I think I've told all my interesting King Richard's fair stories but like that's
where I got my ridiculous $100 floppy vampire 100D hat which is a complete goof.
I have to get that hat sent to me by my mom sometime.
You really do.
It needs to be in the next raton.
And take a picture with it.
Oh actually my mom is coming to visit me soon and she's bringing a certain key shaped item
that's of particular significance to me which I cannot wait to have for various purposes.
I can only imagine.
Yeah.
Or is it a key shaped item or is it a key shaped item?
It's a key.
No it actually is a key shaped item because it's distinctly not the key shaped.
That would be more of like a sword.
And what was I going to say?
Whatever.
Get the D hat while you're at it.
Oh King Richard's fair.
I was just going to say about that.
Did I talk about that time that me and my friends were at King Richard's fair.
We were in high school at the time.
I was like 15.
And like just like one of the court gestures at the fair comes up and is like hey my strapping
young, young, young, young lords.
How dost thou wish to partake of this quest to be knighted by ye old king?
And we're like yeah Nibba whatever you say.
And so we did this quest.
It was a scavenger hunt.
We had to go around.
It was me and like two of my friends.
I think Colin and like Nick or something.
I forget who I was with.
And we just went up to like stall vendors and they would give us quests.
They would give us little tasks to do.
But the thing was like they were definitely making them up as they went along.
They just like had like a stamp or something we had to get from them.
And so go kill that guy.
Kill these homeless people there then mucking up the joint.
They were things like do a jig or like like sing a song.
At one point someone just said like hey sing a song.
And by the way I had my really long hair at this point so I already looked like a strange
cryptid individual.
And this one lady who was like the beer wench or something she asked us to sing a song and
I was like guys what should we sing?
They're like I don't know.
And so I busted out a rendition of Yellow Submarine.
A rousing.
I don't know it was like the song of note at that time in our lives for whatever reason.
So I think we sang it at Boy Scout meetings a lot.
So I sang Yellow Submarine and the lady was so impressed by my rendition that she was
like dude you should like work here.
She like broke character and like told me I should like get a job and I was like well
thank you.
I appreciate that.
You could be like what's it called a minstrel?
A minstrel yeah I could definitely be a minstrel or a game wizard.
And if you took that job you'd be singing Yellow Submarine to this day at that fair.
That's true.
I'm trapped.
I can't.
Think about it you could have been in real life all the time.
So the end of this tale is we went around we did like 10 of these incredibly humiliating
tasks.
One was like run as fast as you can around the entire fairground.
So catch me like age 15 with my longass hair sprinting at top speed around these like knights
Gestures and wizards and just you know people in like weird steampunk and goth clothing because for some reason those people are attracted to
medieval fairs
And and then you know we got all the stamps
so we go to like the the ceremony at the end and we were like we're waiting for a while because we go to like where like the
end line is and
Like this guy's like yeah, the like the nighting ceremony is at you know X time. We're like, okay
Well, we'll just chill and so the the a horrible realization dawns on us as we
Like the people start to file in as the as the rose like in front of the stage where the person's gonna come out begin to fill with
Incredibly young children
Five and six maybe up to like ten and we're just kind of standing in the back like what what is what's happening right now and
Outcomes like the king which I believe is the actual like guys playing the king of King Richard's Fair
He's just like oh my noble knights
Thank you for doing this quest come forth on stage me hearties and be crowned lords of
Cinder or whatever. He loves Dark Souls
I would say Dark Souls theme Renaissance fair that would that would be incredible
So you are like the oldest people there
We were like by ten years or so the oldest people doing the whole thing six like I like the fucking court jester played the ultimate prank on
Us by getting us to do this fucking nighting ceremony that was for babies
And no one along the entire time said like aren't you guys a little old to be doing this like this is for actual babies
Why are you but no this me and my two friends were deeply humiliated we walk up nighted like yeah
We're so good at doing quests and being cool guys
And we get knighted which was fine. I guess that's why until this last past week. They never went to real life ever again
That's right. That's exactly it. Yeah, it was deeply embarrassing, but you know, it's okay, but you're a knight now
Yeah, it does and I'm a literal knight now
I I want to what's the I want to exert my my right to
To say the thing we're allowed to fuck a guy's wife after he gets married, you know, because you're the Lord or whatever
It's called America
We're bringing it back, baby
That's the main conservative platform I think to reinstate that policy. I agree. Um, yeah, well, that's my story
Speaking speaking of real life in general a little bit of a follow-up to last episode where I was talking about like the cgp
Gray thing of like getting rid of distractions internet-based
Things such as websites and podcasts and stuff
I have stopped listening to all podcasts including hello internet even though I really like it and
I've downloaded this thing onto my onto my computer onto chrome
Which is like a a task focus assistant thing which
It doesn't block sites. I can still type them in but when I go there it immediately comes up with a notification saying
You're not supposed to be here
Here's what you're supposed to be doing and it lists the tasks that I've listed for that day or any tasks that I have not finished
And at the moment my task is do bail jpew stupid idiot and that keeps coming up every time I go to Twitter and I'm like, ah
Yeah, you know, I could I could click like right click on the top right and find the thing to settings and then I'm like
Match Twitter from the list of sites that get you know blocked or yeah, yeah, but then that there's too much effort
So I'm like fine like and I it has been helpful in just not
Making me go to Twitter and and read it and stuff
We should we should steal that technology and make our own
Application that does that and called the like the procrastinators branded anti procrastination tool and when you go to a site that like isn't the
Why did you just play you're supposed to be working right now?
Yeah, we actually should but
But like yeah, I mean we definitely should because this this app is insidious. It's it's really it's really
It's got a devious twist to it
because
After a certain amount of time after a certain amount of like site blocking activity
It jumps in and says well, you know, we've blocked sites for a little while
But if you want to block sites forever, you're gonna have to pay you're gonna have to pay a monthly fee
That's so fucked up that it would do that and I'm like I'm it's there's so many other apps that do what you do
With just a little bit less flair, but they just they block URLs and that's fine
And this one just had a nice like
Focus task list built into it and they expect me to to not go to something else
Like why would it's it's stupid? I'm not gonna pay money
I'm not gonna pay money for the privilege of me being unable to go to certain places
Yeah, it's tough to motivate that I
Don't I don't think that thing would work on me because I have like an incredible
Rebellious streak of like when you'd someone tells me not to do something. I'd be like screw you. I'm gonna do the thing now
You just need the opposite that you're like, yeah, fuck you mage
You're not gonna work on your shit today. You're like, yeah, watch me bitch
This reminds me. I don't know. Maybe this will be gross for people. I don't know
It's not that big a thing, but it's like this reminds me when I was young like I to this day
I still bite my nails a ton and it's it's gross and I always say it's the worst thing about me that I bite my nails so much
but
In fact, I'm doing it literally right now. I have a peak. I have pliers not pliers
What is it nail clippers? No, they're not nail like I have like a little edge trimmer's
It's a tweezers. I have tweezers in my hand right now. I was picking in my hands with I'm gonna put it down and stop doing it
Okay, but what I was doing or what I was saying was like when I was young my mom really she was good
She tried to head this off at the pass and like stopped me biting my nails then because she knew if she got got me when I was young
I wouldn't do it, but it's way too late now
and so she bought the stuff that was like
Like it's it's nail polish that just like tastes bad
And the point of it is just you put it on your nails and when you taste it you're like, oh shit
I shouldn't be doing this right now. The problem was you got addicted to that taste
Basically, it wasn't that I like would it was addicted, but it's like biting my nails is like super fun
Like I love doing it. It's just like it's super fucked up and strange, but I get a like picking a scab
It's it's just something I can do anytime and it's really gross and disgusting
But I do it anyway
And so like this this was just what it's supposed to do is remind you that you need to stop like that
This this nail polish is designed to just remind your brain like hey remember you shouldn't be doing this
Don't do this unconsciously, but my will to do it is active and powerful
Because it just is fun being the basket
We're just like this is now painful. This is a challenge. I need to overcome it kind of yeah kind of yeah
I all right
I may have said this on the rebellious spirit mage on this podcast before but yeah the way to combat any and all like nail
fidgeting like things yeah is to start playing guitar
Because having long nails is absolutely, you know the wrong thing
You can't have long nails at any point and you know get into a habit of just cutting them
Really short all the time my nails are already incredibly short though because I just how do you so much?
Yeah, but also a better way to keep them short. I actually tutorial on Phil Collins
No, yeah, it was no wasn't Phil Collins
It was I was confused him with this other guy that my dad likes from likes from like main or something
She had I can't remember but he the point is he had a long thumbnail for picking them strings on the guitar
Some nail he was signed by fucking Apple records. He like met Paul McCartney. What's his name?
He's like rockabye sweet, baby James Taylor. That's it. Okay, just want to remember that name
Okay, I actually if a funny that hippo brings up like the clipping of the nails thing
Because like I I also used to have like a nail biting problem not too big
But it was a bit of an issue
But the way I grew out of it is because it is when when I turned like 12 or 13
I realized when I grow out of my nails, they kind of look nice
so I decided to start growing out my nails and I never buy with my nails since and I grow out my nails and they look
Really cool and like scary and I like that
there's some of this much under reported female privilege because because there is a societal
Expectation to look not disgusting and terrible unlike the ghouls that are men in the society
You were given an incentive to improve your nail hygiene unlike me
I mean, I just it just looked nice for me personally
I mean, I thought that people expected me to look nice. I already had nice nails
So I guess I was born with the privilege of having
I never like bit my nails
One time one time I heard that that was the thing and I tried biting my nails and it was like that
How do you supposed to get a grip on that? That's that that's too much. Oh, you just get in there and you fuck
I just know but like instead of that
I would I would pick at my nails with my other nails, you know, yeah, okay
I would rip them off like that
We're talking about biting nails because when I was a young lad in like second grade
I thought that my nails were
Deformed and the reason I did is because everyone around me bit their nails and I didn't I thought that's what normal nails looked like
And mine always looks like different and I was like why what what happened?
Why are my hands so fucked up and it took forever for me to realize? Oh, I'm just not an autist like everyone
That reminds me of you ever watch you know report of the week, you know report of the week the youtuber
I do not enlighten me. Okay. He's a very pale strange cryptid of a man
Who wears a suit every day of his life vastly oversized ill-fitting suit and slicks his hair back
Yeah, he loves vintage fashion. Yeah, that guy and he does he does fast food and energy to drink reviews. Whoa
And I love him. It's hello everyone. Welcome to running on empty
Yeah, that sounds like him that's the sort of shit he does with his life for some reason
But I mean he's got like a million subscribers or whatever, but the point is
He he famously among his many quirks and strange things about his appearance and a personality
Is that he has very long fingernails and they people describe those vampire ish and skeletal
And it at some point it's a bigger issue
You know, I guess not but okay, maybe vampire
Vampiric dammit. All right, and he made a video addressing it at some point
It's like well, I just happened to like having long nails. I'm just there's no need to fuss
There's no need to muss. I just like my nails this way and that's all there is to say
He is a weird guy, but I like him a lot I like him a lot
He occasionally beefs with Anthony Fantano in a completely one-sided way
Nate since I know you had long hair. Did you ever had like the quirk of like?
Chewing on your hair, you know, I know some people did I never had that I never had that I had that for a while
I don't know how it got out of it, but I'm glad I I did that a little bit
I didn't chew on it, but I just would put it in my mouth. Yeah. Yeah
When I was young, this is just semi-relevant when I was a very young
I had a blankie and would suck my thumb
Excessively and paired this blankie with me everywhere. This is such an embarrassing episode
This is fine. I was so young. I'm not embarrassed by it at this point
Last week so we can this is last week. Yeah, I'm a totally different person
What is embarrassing though is that I would do weird fucked-up shit with that blanket like like shove it up my nose a little bit and like
Yeah, it was weird. All right. All right get this was the weirdest thing about that blankie
Here's what I would do like I had this blank since I was like born and so he got completely shredded over the years until there
Was just like a tiny little square with a bunny in the center remained
And like here's what I would do. I remembered very well in my left hand. I would clutch it in my hand
I would suck on my thumb and I would here's my okay. This is weird
I would take like one of the bigger fragments of cloth. I would kind of turn it into like a big loop
I would put that loop
It you know because if my hands clenched my thumbs in my mouth and in that loop
I would put in my nose and I would breathe through the loop and that was pure bliss as a human
My life when I was like five. Yeah, I just want to
Sometimes just one how these series of events played out that you happen to do that the first time and got positive
Like feedback and like this is something I'm going to continue to do
I think it was like an evolution of behavior patterns where I just tried a bunch of shit and then like that one stuck after a while
I mean, I don't know. I also try shot at my nose
Since we're sharing weird habits, I have a question like for you guys and for everyone that's listening out there
This is something I used to do like do you know like the sort of like
Back in the day do they even do those like sort of white glue sort of thing, but it wasn't like strong
I don't know
It was just like white glue and it didn't stick too much to you
Well enough, but you know, they let kids wait. Did you like you like use like a stick to spread it around I
No, no, no, no, like I would like I put it on my on my palm and I would spread it around and I wait for it to feel it
Yeah, yeah, I wait for it to drive it and then feel it and it looked like skin
Oh
That's the thing that I did on occasion, but not very often my friends didn't know off and I was like, oh, I guess I'll try it
I should do that to my dick and make dick molds. It was sick
That's not that's not an accurate
We called it PVA glue and and and there was all it was always used
When it was as a child there's always in school like sticking things on paper because you know, that's that's basically
That's like 90% of schooling is sticking things on things
And so like you had two choices you had the Pritt stick which was like the the the squishy tube of glue that you could like it twist
stick, yeah, we the Pritt
Pritt was like the brand name I guess and and then they'd have PVA glue and
That's my story
Okay, I just I mean I don't want to say like the same thing may said because yes, I did
Try to dissuade me from doing that because they were concerned I might get like
Addicted to the to the smell of the glue because that was a thing
I think I was more I was more interested in the than the peeling of the skin glue
Yeah, there was this one time where my grandpa was showing me like
you know model making with the glue and like
Little plane because he was an RAF guy and he has like little model plane thing
And it was like we were we were building it together and I had the glue thing and it was one of those like smelly types of glue
In a little metal tiny little metal thing and I was sniffing it and I was like this smells really good
And I I said to my grandpa like do you know how nice this smells grandpa?
Like I had no idea it was a bad thing and he got really upset at me
And I was really sad and and afraid that I had mucked up so bad that I was doing something illegal in front of my grandpa
And I didn't even realize
And from that day on I never had a grandpa he disowned
He jumped in that little model airplane you flew away never came back
I
Was thinking about the nails again
I I still have like a bad habit of like biting them
But only like if I break one of my long nails and it's like uneven it drives me crazy
That like if I don't don't have like scissors near me, then I'll start
Yeah, it's just just right. It's so insane enough enough gross disgusting nails
Let's move on to my topic that I have okay
Adventure time ended
Yes, I did I haven't been keeping up with it for a while and I've decided to re
Watch the whole thing and I'm in sort of the middle of season two
Season one and season two are like the best thing I've ever seen like this surprisingly perfect like
I would recommend anybody who has not watched adventure time in a long time to go back and watch all of season one
It's all killer no filler ten out of ten like the best cartoon I've ever seen in my life
Wait, sorry, I I was distracted during that please repeat all those words
Adventure time is good season one is the best cartoon on TV. How much of it did you rewatch?
Did you rewatch the whole thing? I I rewatch all of see I haven't gotten around to all of it yet
I rewatch season one and I'm in halfway through season two and it is ten out of ten cartoon
I
Would you say where's the drop-off happen like season five season six? I I have no idea
That's why I'm rewatching to find out but like
I'm just saying like like though. There's a reason that cartoon contributed to like every cartoon in the world
In that style I was watching it as I came out and it's just like so fucking good
It's it's the writing like surprisingly you think of a adventure time
You think oh, it's just wacky and funny and and it looks very simplistic
But like everything that that that's all wrongs all misconceptions. You've all remembered it incorrectly
It's it's got it's got brilliant writing brilliant comedic writing and the animation at least in season one and the beginning of season two is like
The reason it looks so simplistic is because they want to do so much with the animation that if it was more complicated
They wouldn't be able to do it on the budget. They had yeah
So they do some really impressive looking incredible stuff because there's only so many lines and colors
They have to put on let's let's lay it on the line. Let's lay it on the line
Let's say you have to obliterate
Adventure time or Steven Universe and everyone involved in either's production
Who do you kill? Who do you?
I'll kill Steven Universe. Yeah, I think the problem is if you obliterated adventure time
You'd kill a bunch of people who work on Steven Universe as well. So you wouldn't get either. Yeah, Rebecca sugar worked on adventure time
She did. Oh, well, okay in that case we definitely are
Cuz it's
It's it's just it's hard to explain
Exactly why it's like so perfect, but it's
It's like it's it's from the the perspective of a child
I think it's the the writing is so good because they know how to write good episodes like every episode is a great episode
but like
They understand storywriting in a way that they can do matter and they can do matter properly by having the story just go in a different direction
Like at the last second or like they can they can like the first episode of season season two
Finn and Marceline like Marceline's dad comes back and all that
He's fucking up everything and the thing fries episode
Yeah, why did you steal my fries and all that stuff and Finn and Marceline are going around adventuring and at the end
It's revealed to the Jake
You know for some reason was absent
But he was actually in Finn's pocket the entire time and he turns around at the end like like Marceline asks. Oh
I've been wondering what's with your your pocket
Yeah, Finn and then Finn goes oh Jake's in here and then Jake is like tiny he turns around he farts
And that's the end of the episode
I remember that I fucking lost my shit comedic timing. It's timing that wins
It's just it's just like you can tell these guys like they're not idiots
Even though they're writing something that seems like silly
Because through the entire episode Finn just has a pocket drawn on his shirt
And they don't address why at all until right at the very end and like you're wondering in the back of your mind
Like is that there's like a new detail on his costume they're doing now like he just has a pocket on the shirt
There yeah, it's it's a level of like they on the surface if you're not paying attention
It looks like a dumb kids show where people are just screaming and farting and is laughing and stuff
Yeah, and then if you pay attention there are things that you notice and the show recognizes that and acknowledges that people may be paying
More attention and they say they have like little jokes every so often that are meta in that way to do like it's just it's just really good
To do a little deep analysis of that joke in itself like so a layperson watch the episode like won't even notice that Jake's not there
They'll just say like ah here's Finn and like they if they could have ended the episode without the pocket without the Jake joke
And like it would have been like fine, you know, it would have been like okay
You'd be wondering where Jake is possibly but no one would really question it that much
but by adding that Jake thing it shows that they were in fact thinking of that the whole episode and
Like they they they do in fact address the the issue of why Jake isn't there
But they do it in this obviously absurd way because there was all these incredible
Death-defying things that happened in that episode the Jake would have absolutely
Invaluable to be to participate in and the fact that he just didn't is just like a humorous, you know
Yeah, goo like yeah, they have things that like if you're a pedantic like and why wasn't he helping it's because
He's a stupid dog and sometimes he's just an idiot. That's him. That's him
And I mean and Finn didn't even like ask for his help even though he probably could have used it at several points
But that's fine. It's just such a it's just such a fluid dynamic like re-watching it
You just you're just like your mind boggles at how perfect this the you know the the way they've made the show
For like for like, you know random adventures like anything they want they can do they can make happen because of the way
They've made these characters
Haven't gone back and rewatched adventure time
But I do and this is a little different
But like I have felt just the pangs and I have gone back and watched just bunches of Steven universe
And it's way better to watch on a rewatch because like there's no I know generally what's gonna happen
So I don't need to like stress about this is a waste of an episode
Ah, why aren't the series progressing which are like fine criticisms, but like the vibe of Steven universe
I find incredibly comfy so it is pretty comfy, but you know like in terms of like in terms of like like
The episodes that mean something
Like we I think most people who like Steven universe agree that the the townspeople are not that interesting enough for the time that they're given
Generally, that's true. Yeah
As well like he caused me to quit Steven universe and I only got back to it after
The episode with garnet aired and people were like losing their shit
I like the thing they do with Ronaldo kind of it just the meta because like
Ronaldo has an actual blog in the real world where he like reports on stuff
Yeah, keep keep keep it's like I don't know that's that that's just like Ronaldo in the show that much
But I like what's being done in a meta context
I think the funnest thing with Ronaldo is all the things he says that sounds retarded were actually straight up true
Yes, and you don't but I didn't want to get too much into Steven universe
I just meant to I just brought that up because like I would also like to similarly go back and watch adventure time
Because there was also especially when I heard it was ending and I watched like a video review
I talked about this last week of the of the finale like it gave me such nostalgia and I want to go experience that again
I watched yeah watch like the first two seasons so like I would like to watch the whole thing because yeah
I don't know why I thought I was no idea why I didn't like fall out of like favor with the show didn't do anything to piss me off
Same I got bored. I got watching with one of my friends and like then we stopped hanging out
And so I just stopped watching because I was like the thing we did is we just kick back and like watch that
That makes sense. Oh, yeah, but fuck it. I'm getting back. Give sold me on. I'm gonna check it out as soon as
Like what when I say season one is all killer when I say season one is all killer
No filler it I really mean it like every single episode is just
Muah, you know like muah like the like the you know like sick
Give you say would you say that adventure time style of like comedic delivery had any influence on you?
Cuz like I'm not I think about it things like bail statements
I've kind of have not like an identical tone
But there's there's a little like bits and pieces here in there that have like this. Oh, yeah
Esoteric kind of comedic value to it that I feel very there's some overlap there
I don't know whether I was inspired
I mean, I must have been inspired by it somewhat but I already had a similar sort of style of yeah before
Adventure time and it really resonates with me. So yeah, it's like it's just like that feeling of
Yeah, why not like fucking
Agreed yes, why just why not put a dank weed joke? Yeah. Yeah, this is why not
Even though it will get me thrown in jail for 200 years
Gotta suffer for your heart my favorite thing my favorite thing recently was watching those episodes is that the princesses and how they're all like
They're you know, they're all portrayed as like the dumbest sluts of all
When ice king when ice king shaved his beard and he became the nice king and all the princesses like oh, it's the new nice king
Oh
It was very funny. That's a very make-toe reading
It's just it's just they're so cute and like
They just do like they have dumb voices
If I were to make like my own show like if I had the time or like the budget
I would make it like very simplistic and I would do silly voices and that it would be adventure time
I would that's the show I would make if it's time is a great formula
Yeah, well give the show is ending
I want to know you can pick up the torch and make it make a new version of it do it. I will I'll literally make a show called
Something I probably won't check but someone in the description
Please post a guide to which episodes I should and should skip like I want to I want to comprehensive thing
So now what are the essential episodes? There probably is a list floating out there?
There I bet there is I bet there is did you a sandy wants when I do too I will say
Every episode of season one you have to watch. Okay, Julie noted Julie noted
Every episode season two every episode of season three. I don't know about season four and five
No, because episode season four and five is when I
Stopped but I don't like Tom. I'm not really sure why I didn't hate it
I was just like I think it was like the site
I was watching it on was this really annoying like ads everywhere some of the episodes were missing
You know, it really happens. You really happen to all of us and we're just afraid to admit it
We're ashamed to admit it
We all got into pony and that's all we did when it we threw our lives away and everything else stopped mattering and we all
I think I got into adventure time after
Really mine was I guess I watched I guess I watched season one two as they came out
So I was like way before remember remember that one pony reviewer who was like his O.C. was a pony version of Finn
Oh, yeah, yeah, that was my that guy was an intellectual
What if he's listening right now? I
Got nothing against the guy, but his O.C. was hilarious and silly
I do not like the idea. I have nothing against the guy
But I don't like the idea of taking another character making to it pony and being it
It's kind of son at you ask in its level of thinking like I like this one thing. Let's make this
I mean, he probably was like eight or okay, he probably was like 15 or something
You know, it was me you're probably right
Anyway
Anyone else got another topic. I'm ready to sort of to switch it up
Who of you have dual screens raise your metaphorical? I got dual screen set up right now right now
I
Know what why do you have space on my desk? I don't have I don't have space on my desk
And I don't have space in my room for a bigger desk, and I've always hated people with dual screens
I want to kill everyone. It's good. Oh, no
The reason I asked is because before I went to
Lofiini I got a second monitor and I completely forgot and when I turn was like, oh, I have a second monitor
So they're working with a second monitor and it's just it's like the best
I
Survive without a second monitor. I know I'm gonna level with you guys on dual monitors
All right, so back in the day
I used to my first like big like major desktop display
I had actually bought a 37 inch 1080p TV and that was my computer monitor and it was godlike
And then everyone got on the dual screen set up smoke. All right. I'm gonna I'm gonna switch this up
I'm gonna get two smaller monitors
So I have double the workspace and I hated it
Hated dual monitors because like I only ever worked with one of them
I never spent the time to like shift the windows over because it's like I'm just I'm just I'm looking at this one
And the other one's like kind of off to the side and I don't feel like turning my head. I'm lazy
Fuck it. I want to go back to my one big monitor
But I fixed that problem for me what I have now and this happened by accident is because I got one of those drawing displays
and so instead of having them horizontal I now have it in a vertical alignment and
Vertical is way better because you can see both of them at the same time just by looking forward because I have my 22 inch
Oh, wait, wait, wait, you're saying that you have them mounted above each other
Yeah, so what happens is I have a big 32 inch display now
I just got it's a 32 inch like QHD display and then under it on my desk
I have a 22 inch drawing display and because they're like I can see both of them right now
And I can just drag something down you can just drag it down
So it's on the lower one and it's so much easier to use because like your vision sees both of them
And it's like pure bliss and it's a 10 out of 10. Everybody should do vertical displays. It's way better than horizontal
Technology you're talking about
But I I use it I this is how I use it
But yeah, I wanted a second one just specifically because
When I draw I like to listen or watch things at the site at the corner of my eyes
and that means I cannot full screen my drawing
Program and that gets in the way of me drawing and it's really annoying and like then I have to make the screen of
Whatever I'm watching really tiny that means I don't see it so well
So now that I have the monitors I have like on one monitor what I'm watching and one monitor when I'm drawing and it's so good
I love I love it. It's good
I also end up using my phone for a lot of stuff just because it's convenient to like have that I don't know below
That's all I can do. That's all I can fucking do when I'm streaming
I have to have my phone with the stream chat because I can't do it any other way
So so Tom set up is technically
Like vertical, but it's like on his desk and in front of him give
Why don't you construct Casey Neistat style like get like a a wooden beam going straight up and like make a base
and hang myself from it and
Mount two displays one literally above the other and just like screw it if you want to be lazy
What you do is instead of doing that you can just buy a
Vesum out that basically it attaches to your desk and it has two mounting points in the back for two monitors
So you just take them and there you go on there
Then they're they're one on top of each other so you can just go
Vertical and not have to worry about desk space
Do it give do it
I'm stretching my my neck up right to where the monitor would sit on top of the other one
And it seems like a bit like that that hurts my neck just a bit
I need my friend Matt. He just bought and it's dedicated office space and his setup is transcendent
He has this like big L-shaped desk and he has a huge
27-inch wake-up Sintiq that he got for free and I hate him for it like a
$3,000 Sintiq someone just gave to him and he has that on his left side and that and he has like a big swivel chair
So he wants to draw you just swivels over to that
But when he doesn't need to draw he swivels back over and he has two 27 inch monitors with that
Vertical vase amounts with like that like rotate and swivel and everything so you can adjust both of them to any angle you want
And it's like literally you know god-tier
It's amazing because I just went to see him this week on Friday
I drove to New York and hung out with him and got drunk
We did a podcast, but I just saw this space and I was like I'd never want to leave here like this is perfect
like this is the best setup of all time and
I almost murdered him and stole his office because it was so good
Do you think do you think the the natural progression of stuff like this is eventually we're gonna be like, you know
You got like a sphere with a hole in it. You poke your head in the screen is the sphere the whole way around
Yes, it needs to happen immediately. Yeah, I suppose like the the logical extension is just like
Like augmented reality stuff where like you just put a little lens. You can already do that
You guys know about the Microsoft Holo lens. Have you ever heard about this?
I've heard the name. What is it?
Microsoft's like they have this thing where you put on a pair of like glasses and
It's tapped into like they have ones that plug into a computer
But they also have one that's just the computers built into the headset and how it works is that it overlays digital information
On top of the real world. So like they're like, oh, you want like you can play Pokemon go
Yeah, but it's like over your eyes and they actually had a demo very similar
But one of the things they did like oh you want to like
Because it senses where your hands and stuff are too so they had a demo where it's like oh
I want to watch a movie so they just sat down on a couch took two hands up and spread their hands across the wall
And it made a huge display that was the size the entire wall
I started watching a movie and then they could bring up like a little Skype window on the side that was like
I had like a 45 degree angle like based on where you were sitting that like had Skype
You could just use your hand to scroll through it and stuff while you were watching this big movie
And I was like that was like the big come. I was like, that's what I want. That's yeah
That's what I want fucking fucking Skype back
Yeah
But what you won't get any dank like gamer like login messages when you log into Skype unlike discord
That's what holds this thing to get
God
It was supposed to be our sign. It's just it's just such a millennial program with their login messages
Yeah, and I know that like they do a thing where they said submitted by so-and-so like they take like community ones
That's what they they give you the name so it's like if this one really bothers you, you know who to kill
I do think of you every time that one comes out exactly
Discord stop that please
Fucking hearthstone
Uh
mage what was
Everybody to bring it has to bring a topic forward for the for the topic list formless episodes. Do you have one?
I just did dual screens. Was it your screen? Oh dang. I guess I forgot
After you said it. Are you trying? I'm trying to catch one. I support this Gestapo tactics of calling everyone out to make sure they actually
I have another topic I can bring
Because at the controller owners when they came up last minute
I this is something that I've been wondering about and this is gonna get a little more like
Complicated, I guess and just like person what I wanted to ask is why do you think people don't own their weirdness anymore?
And a lot of explain what I mean by that. It's like yeah back in the day like like in like the early
2000s and shit like people were like really proud of being weird and like war like they've weird internet culture
Like that kind of shit and now it's like like people didn't want to be normal and didn't want to be accepted by society
But now it feels like that has like changed
It's like all of us like grew up and realized like oh, there's actually consequences for not being accepted by greater society now
That we have to be in it because we're adults and now there's like this whole like cultural movement of like
Everything I do needs to be accepted and I can't just be I can't exist on the fringe of culture anymore
My weird lifestyle has to come out of this. I don't know. I still I feel still feel like I'm like weird in the way
I have always been I just you know, I don't I don't say things like
Yeah, I feel like I'm still one with my weakness. I think I feel like this particular group is right
There's definitely pockets of people like us for sure
I mean anyone who listened to this podcast for more than ten minutes realizes
We just don't give a fuck but like I'm talking more like a like a larger cultural scale
Like the internet was just Lalex desorandum now the internet is just accept me
I'm going to change everything to make my weirdness become normal like before it was never like you wanted to be anything
But normal now. It's like everything has to be
I see I see what you mean Tom. I think it's mainly because of the call-out culture
That that's happening and like whenever like you step out of line and like oh, you're a bit egotistic
People start making videos. Oh, this guy is egotistic. Bring him down
Get his head that there's a lot of that. There's a lot of there's a lot of
Laughing at people's it like being slightly not normal and and that being okay
I guess I guess it's it's fueled. It seems to be fueled by teenagers who are like a bit awkward and and don't feel
You know, they're not sure about themselves. So they take it out by laughing at other people who are slightly weird
Yeah, that definitely happens a lot. Yeah
And like that happened back in the day, but like we like accepted that like, you know, you you'd be like, yeah
Of course normies hate me like that's why we say normally like I think this is like post
What's he called leafy's here? I think sort of culture because people got popular by making fun of other people and then other people
They have become popular by renting on other people. So it's the new cool thing to do
You say post game theory. No, no, post leafy leafy post leafy. Oh
I'm personally post game theory
I'm pretty game theory actually I like game theories
Game theory's got his positive points for sure
Um, I think personally a lot of this comes down to I'm gonna blame it all on the baby boomers personally
At least I'm gonna start I think it goes back to that and I I can't exactly trace at the moment the cause of why but I do feel
Like the baby boomers were quite helicopter-ish in their parenting
And you know, I don't even really blame them. I just blame the the world as it's changed into because it's like
I think that a lot that's happened is that like like baby boomers grew up in like the 60s in the 70s and
Like this was the civil rights time and they felt really
I don't know like they wanted to change the world and like make everything about like the individual
And they didn't like their parents who like fought in World War two and were very like I don't know like, you know
Blah blah blah give up shit for your nation, you know
Like the baby boomers are way more
Individualistic the first the generation I think that really
Took off and like there's a lot of good points to that
But I think the negatives is that people became very like when I say self self-obsessed
I don't mean that like they really cared about themselves
I mean that they valued the individual like so much more to the collective
But I think there's a feeling that like it's totally okay to let the collective burn
Just for for any infringement
Against an individual and I feel like the result of this has been that like they raised their kids in an environment
We're like any infraction was too much of an infraction
so like
Calling someone like a faggot on the schoolyard like has become a federal issue like a hate crime and like like I get it like
Okay, you could you could say that that's a hate crime like why are you like?
What's the reason to like
Call this person like a specific demographic, you know
Association that has a negative connotation in some circles like sure sounds like you just hate gay people
But you know the thing is a lot of people just use that word without any association to any group
So like maybe it'd be good to just kind of relax and and realize that this is more kids being kids than
You know like an actual group being attacked for their identity
The thing is with insults most people don't realize when someone is like shoots an insult at you
They usually try to get you where it hurts
So they use whatever you know, they perceive to be your weakness for instance like just a little hogan just these video about
The black guy who fucked his daughter who he really hated so we called him a very nasty term for an african-american individual
You cut out, but I'm not sure I want to hear that all over again. That's fine. Go ahead. Go ahead
But yeah, like for instance, you know someone on the
PCP like if they don't like me they're gonna like I don't know like call me the girl or use some sort of feminine insults that are usually
Yeah, aim that girl's just to sort of like insult me
They might not be misogynistic, but they think that's with how they're gonna get me. I personally don't care
So go ahead, but yeah, yeah, so like it's not about like if I call you sometimes people are definitely
Does that make me like that
The thing is it really involves what's going on in the person's head
Because if I call you a bitch because I just hate all women and here I am
Ah, here's a woman. Let's call her a bitch because I hate her like okay fair enough, but you can also use that word
To just mean like in particular girl
I don't like or you can mean it to say like actually like friend who I'm currently giving a rough attitude to so
And you can also honestly aim it at guys, but then the meaning is gonna be different
But yeah, yeah, like it's it's very much dependent on the person itself and like they might not necessarily be
Misogynistic or or just you know, whatever
Whatever aces do you give them is just that they're trying to be as offensive as possible is to hurt you
so that's not good, but like
People don't need to go to jail for saying a word
I think some people would respond to this and I would understand why and they'd be like
Well, if you choose to use that word anyway, despite knowing the context then that makes you, you know, whatever the particular thing is
You make the word so horrible, that's why people like to use it because it's such a horrible word
Yeah, I mean, that's definitely true, but like you words have the power you decide to give them
Yeah, that's true. And like I do not blame people for getting mad about words that they find offensive
But like I don't know. I just your problem like I mean, yeah, I mean it kind of is your problem and
But you know like we want to bridge gaps here
We don't want to say like if you can't take it
You're just like a pussy and then here we are just labeling you and throwing your opinion aside
What you'd want to do is like kind of like have a conversation with this person as to why you disagree
And we we've certainly made this argument quite a few times on this podcast
Happy to have like discussions with people that disagree with me
Yeah, as you do in the comments all the time on these and these podcasts
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, like I personally don't swear too much other than like the usual shouldn't fuck because those I don't even consider them
swear words at this point
Just like you're being raised like you can't say swears. They're bad. I just like what the fuck you talk about, you know
So some people fuck is the worst word you can say but like to us. It's basically completely meaningless
Take the words gay at some point. It was like quite offensive or just like, you know
Like you wouldn't sold someone by calling them gay
But nowadays like no one really cares anymore. You call each other gay like you guys call each
But at the same time like I went for the most part like
Of course by Hilary
But only from what I've observed like most people don't care anymore. I mean some people do but like you're the most parts
No one cares. It's definitely that like nowadays things like gay becoming like way more
Offensive nowadays is because of a very very vocal minority of people who are trying to get offended at
They're giving back the power to the word
Yeah, I know I feel empathy like let's say that like if you're gay and like you go to school every day and like people call
You gay because they just hate that you are homosexual like I took like I of course I understand like yeah
You're not gonna be too fond of that word and you're not going to enjoy it
But more important than banning the word is like making people okay with the thing because like they're gonna find another word to
Call him if they're gonna get if they're gonna get thrown in jail for saying gay
They're gonna find another way to make fun. It's not that hard culture just make up new insult
So I can it's gonna be difficult to stay ahead of that curve
You know, you can't just ban everything English English has enough words to sustain insults for like
I don't believe in that top-down approach as an effective way to like change people's minds
I mean, I'd like to I'd like to imagine that being like gayness has become more
accepted in in schools and stuff I have no idea to
Whether or not that's the case because only I only have the Internet
Yeah
But you know like I
Used to be a bit more like
not
Bigoted I guess but like it grossed me out
Grossed me out when I was younger because it was like what why would you kiss a guy? That's not true
I mean, I still find it pretty strange because like I it's not something that I want to do
But like it's nowadays, you know, somebody says they're gay for real not joking
And then you're like, okay, like it's it's no longer a big deal because yeah, like
You know the social justice warrior
Angle of like lots of shows and things people get upset and they can fight like like social justice warrior hate
Brigades like going around trying to get people censored and then things just appeasing that crowd
As the same I think yeah, you know things that are making gayness
More like normal and having gay characters. That's okay
That's actually good because it makes it so that people growing up don't find it as weird
Yeah, the the the Haprigays are separate, but like people conflate the tune
I don't like I don't like it when somebody sees like a
Like a gay character in a thing and they assume that it's social justice warrior crap and therefore
It's it's terrible to have gay characters because that's completely going against the
Like it should be okay. It should be okay to have one or the other
Yeah, yeah, I don't I don't like like people like high guardian spice, right high guardian spice comes out and it's like very
social justice warrior
Like appealing like it's dog whistling to the
It's it's it's got it's got all that that funny stuff and and it's like I
Don't see a problem with you know
The social justice angle
The the adding the adding of like I mean we don't know anything about the characters of story
But like they're having a lot of female writers
Too much for a problem with that specifically, but it's when it's it's just
It's just disingenuous
When you say like we are gonna have 100% all female writers in this and then if there happens to be a writer's room of all men
That's a problem. That's yeah, then then I get like whoa
Even universe like we all enjoy the show to some extent, right?
And it does have like those sort of people working on it
Like you know bit of ACW's bit of feminists, but like they don't shove it down, you know our throats there
Whatever beliefs they're making a genuine interesting show with whatever
Yeah, that's that's what I was trying to get at like even if even if
It's it's not the fact that it's a room of a hundred percent female writers
It's that they advertise it as that being itself a good thing
And there's no reason to believe that that means the show will be good. It just depends on how
So like if if if high garden spice just came out and it was like that's a pretty good show and it's got a hundred percent female
Wouldn't give a shit
Those those writers are good writers and that's just a good thing
I just hate that we live in a world and like this just is the real world and I get it
I think we'll never change
But like I want it to be that a product just gets made and then everyone just sees if it's good or not
And we don't worry about anything involved in how it was made or any like whatever like I guess if they it was made
Using the blood of babies because they ground them up and turn them into scripts. I mean, I guess that's
I don't know what the show's good enough. I don't think I care. I mean
Alchemist was made by a female author. Yeah sure was sure was yeah, and look look how popular that is only with women
No guys ever liked full metal alchemist
You know was weird though as I was reading through full metal alchemist
Strangely when I as soon as I found out it was written by a woman the next chapter and all subsequent chapters became shit
Oh, so when I reread the old chapter, they were also suddenly bad was a big it was weird
It was weird, but I haven't re-read it since I found out so I guess I guess don't do it
So that strikes me as weird like winery. Yeah, I don't know what's funny though
She's so violent and it's played off as comedic effect. I never liked that in anime
That's why I don't like Doridora much either punching guy through wall just and don't do not
Yeah, I mean I
Speaking related tangentially to the thing Nate said at the very beginning about like
Blaming the boomers. Oh, yeah. Yeah, you say that I think this is a like
I'm really tired of of Millennials blaming the boomers like the way boomers blame the Millennials
Not because anyone is like incorrect like I'm I think what you said was
Okay, I think what you said was correct and all that but like it's just it feels so cowardly that
Every millennial whoever disparages baby boomers and you know the things they've done never says it to their face
They say it on the internet a place. They would never find it
We never actually
Now get my dad in here munchie. Can we just can we pull up my dad, please in the phone? Yeah, okay
All right, dad fuck like like none of us would go like I can't call my grandpa and is like little model airplane
Say grandpa you fucked up the world
Like I can't say that to him. I'd be too embarrassed. I'd be too scared like oh, he's just not mad now
It doesn't matter. I feel like this is a very sort of American thing to do
Hmm, I just I don't
I cannot see I cannot see blaming my parents or my grandparents for whatever would happen because of the history my country
You know once well, I mean you can fact you factually blame your parents for 100% of the experiences
You've had in your life because they are in fact. Yeah, that's like I don't I don't have the hatred for baby boomers
That a lot of people seem to do the problem is that like so many people who blame the boomers
I think you can you can point as a cause at a causal thing to certain things like oh
This is x things fault. The problem is that what so many people who do that proceed to then abdicate?
Responsibility for anything that happens going forward and that's where the problem
Yeah, so what I would never like like the boomers cause problems
What are you going to do to fix it because complaining about it is not gonna help?
Yeah, but as much as it is unfair that they have put you in this situation
There's nothing you can do, but what you try and get out of it
Yeah, yeah, the reason the reason I said is it feels like American thing because like whenever they you know
They talk about the problems the boomers caused it seems like it's happened in America's like very American centric the problems are like
American history this happen
American history echoes throughout the whole world
So, you know, it's not necessarily just America, but it's still it still very feels like the people who post those are
Does the term baby boomer wouldn't that specifically apply to it an American generation like those economic conditions
America at the time is what caused the whole big thing in the first place
Oh, by the way, by the way, we're talking baby boomers are not the same as boomers because boomers are
30 year old
American gamers who are distinct from the zoomers who are the current like I don't know
12 to 20 year old American
Enough of these stupid names that sound too similar to other the stupid names
Kill all boomers and zoomers
But just kill everyone
Genocide
May the meteor hit the earth right now
I'm cussing me right now from Final Fantasy 7
Well, I don't know are we are we good with this topic I feel pretty comfortable going over to the to the
Different direction I was expecting I did not expect a social justice rant to come out of that
But that's that's fine. You know, yeah
Let me just finish the point on the actual thing because your original point was just about like why are people well?
What was why do people why do people not own their weirdness anymore?
Why are we pushing more towards acceptance everything as opposed to being like? Yeah, I'm proud to be hated by normal people. I
Mean, I like my response to that was like I feel like it's because we've made it so that people feel
Like people are less able to feel vulnerable and be okay with it
So like they're less willing to accept criticism and less willing to feel like they don't belong
I think like there's a lack of resilience. I feel in
Less conversations going on and more gotcha exposed you moments on that's that's that's a fair assessment
I'd say you like you can post something now
And like I don't know
I mean, you know, maybe this is a bad example
But it's like if you post something online then like way later
Someone can just use it like to get you because they take it way out of context because like everything's available online
Nothing is everything's like documented and able to be sorted through and like if you ever get to a position of like of
Prominence like people can dig through your old posts and like make a federal fucking case of like a tiny joke
You made yeah, I nobody had a problem with but now I
Hate the I hate that and I relish
I would I relish and dream of a day when I am at a an area of prominence and somebody tries to dethrone me by
Digging up my old tweets where I say the n-word a million times and then and I'm not gonna delete them and I'm gonna say
F you and I'm gonna turn my back on them. I'm not gonna do anything. I'm not gonna apologize
I'm not gonna say I'm not even if I get fired or from whatever it is
I I just don't I don't ever want to acquiesce to that stupid shit on a certain example
I do worry that in that situation
I'll I'll buckle because like I to feel like I'm not trying to say that you're just like acting tough or whatever
But I like I feel like I don't want to apologize either, but then like I wonder if I will push you out in that moment
It's like it's it's it's a thing of principle for me like it
Even if it's a stupid thing to do
Mm-hmm
I just don't want to ever let anyone who follows me or knows about me or here's about it on the news yeah to think
That because I know loads of people feel the way I do and they just they wish somebody would just say no
Correct, which is the to this to this mob of political correctness like whether or not it's a good thing to do
I just I wish you know what I don't wish it happens to me, but if it happens to me
I'm going to do that. I'm going to say no no way. I'll take a stand right here like ethically
I absolutely think there's a time and place to say the worst racial or other kind of slur that there is there's
100% a time and place when it's gonna be really fucking funny and
Totally awesome to say and everyone will laugh and have a great time as a result of it
So and that extends to every word and every possible thing
And like you could then if you just take that out of context like oh look at this evil person
Did this thing and it was like bad because they said a word that they're forbidden to say
My thing was because I think about this a lot too because I I mean I keep up with the news and shit
And like people getting fucking destroyed for for things
They've said that are innocuous that have become bad and my my whole thing is again
Cuz I've always felt like what if that ever happened to me and my thing is that I would not apologize
And I would not be tempted to simply because the people who are trying to take me down for this
I don't respect them and like nothing no apology at the damage has been done. No apology
I would say what would matter
The problem I'm not interested in their forgiveness anyway because I already hate them
I hear what you're saying the problem isn't those people and like those people are probably know what they're doing is wrong
But but like what worries me when I think about it is but there's tons of people out there who simply like
Accept what is reported like in a headline
Like so-and-so is racist and they will not read the article
They will not do the research to know that it's a bunk and that's okay
So you apologize has anyone who's ever apologized ever gotten a follow-up report be like actually this guy's not a racist
He said sorry like the damage is done. Unlike. There's no apologies. Yeah, even if that even if they report on that
It won't matter because the people won't say you're already people see a headline people see a headline that says so
Prominent person is secretly a Nazi and it's like ooh interesting
I wonder how this person was disgraced and then you've got a same headline
Prominent person is secretly okay, and they just glaze over it because people like they love to see like tragic downfalls
Here's another that's why that stuff so like like anybody who's been accused of rape and is exonerated
It doesn't matter. They're still a rapist to those people
It doesn't nothing you're ever gonna do or say will ever change those people's minds because they they because at that point the people who are
Looking for people who are racist and sexist and bigoted or whatever
You are an our ammo in there like they're gone, right?
Because they're trying to gain more power and change social structure to put them in a better position
So the more people like you that exist the more it's so a situation to pop up and the more ammo they have to change
Social structure to their benefit absolutely true
And did you see the there was a comment by Norm McDonald recently comedian extraordinaire where he um don't know like he said a comment
I forget what the inciting comment was it was something about oh, we know it okay like he said
In like some podcast or something that like he
He of course he felt bad for like people who were like insulted by Rosie O'Donald her you know
You could possibly interpret it as a racist comment
I'm on I'm agnostic to that and then like Louis CK like they both
At Louis CK like you know flashes dick jacked off in front of women, you know, it seems pretty sketchy, but I don't know the details
What what he said about that was like
The what what Louis CK and Roseanne suffered as a result of that like was its own bad thing
And then people said that like okay, but what about the victims and he's like well
I mean yeah, they had their own bad things happen, but that's not what these guys felt so I you know in addition
I specifically feel bad for what happened to Louis and Roseanne and like that's an accurate statement
But they did not suffer the like the kind of social backlash is obviously very different from the specific kind of you know
Suffering such as it is that happened to the people that were you know quote-unquote targeted or attacked by Louis and Roseanne
but
And in respect people got real mad so he apologized about that and what he said was you would have to have
Down syndrome to not feel bad for the victims and I think that is like I mean sure that's I guess kind of mean
I guess
And then he apologized for that as well and he was apologizing for his apology
Ridiculous like there's the thing is like he just he just said nothing
It's impossible. Yeah, I
Don't know too much about Norma doll, but I have seen a few of you know funny things he's done
He seems like the sort of person who would have deliberately made that down syndrome joke in his apology because he doesn't like apologizing
And then he and then he went back on that and I'm like, yeah
No, yeah, I like the down syndrome apology if he just didn't apologize for that because that's like funny and it's own
You know, hey, I mean, I'm sorry. You're fucking stupid. That's a good apology. Yeah, it's really interesting
There's no way to win there. There is no way to win. It's interesting because like I just I'm like a huge
Audible fan like audio books and I just started listening to a book. I've always wanted to read unless you call the 48 laws of power
It's incredibly insightful. I love it. I'm almost done with it
And I'm probably gonna like listen slash read it again immediately because it's like trock full of goodness
But the introduction to the 48 laws of power is
Basically this big kind of like essay all about like how power is used and like how to look out for people who are you who are really
Effective at using power despite not seeming as such and this entire essay is literally just disgusting social justice warriors
Like if you ever wanted just like they're like, oh, of course
I'm like, I already kind of knew that going in but just hearing it after affirmed in a
Subject matter that's talking nothing about SJWs and trying to like be submerged them
Like just listen to the introduction of 48 laws of power. You're gonna be like, oh
Yeah, I am not saying I am not saying that the social justice movement is like
Deliberately designed and the people in it are consciously attempting to undermine
Society but what I am saying is if there were a force that was trying to covertly upend the Western society
This is what it would look like. I think there's a I'm just saying I'm just saying
Contention of people hiding behind the social justice movement to do that
It wouldn't be so unsurprising. It would not be unsurprising and the way that we've like just for example
We've basically labeled all women who claim anything as like in the social justice circles
Any woman who makes an accusation must be believed in some circles like wow, what an amazing tool
We've given to any evil women out there. This is incredible
They could they can really use that and this bullshit about no one would ever claim anything if it wasn't true
No, get that out of my face. I don't give a fuck. That's a shitty argument. There's tons of reasons why you would
So yeah, I just don't believe in giving tools that could be abused to anyone
I want everyone to be on the same playing field, but you know what whatever I'm getting all wound up about this
We all know the score here
Anyways weird
Let's let's come around a voicemail now that we've gone down that right. It's weird. Yeah, let's get into some truth
I guess some people who aren't afraid to share their weirdness with the world
our listeners
Absolutely, and let's see first up on the chopping block. We've got a voice message here from pig word pig word the friendly pig
What have you got for us friend go?
Then it's the fucking Ghibli cast gonna get to fucking pork a row sir
Oh, that is my shit. The only reason I watch Ghibli fucking pigs for life suck my dick
Well, okay, that's all right
I'm on the Ghibli cast as well. Oh, yeah, of course. I forgot that's a game show as well
so like I
watched pork a row sir like weeks ago and I
Think it's just
Everyone forgot no wait did you was doing like his month of videos at the next one. Is that next on the block?
I think it's next. Okay. I think it's next so so I just need to remind digi and set a date and say digi digi digi digi digi
Digi and and devu as well. Maybe I don't know what's going on with the view. I haven't heard it from him in a while
So which we're just gonna message them, but I do want to do that because that is a really good film
Yeah, it's probably my favorite Ghibli after watching it
Man, that's what I really wanted to jump in on and watch it with you guys, but I just don't fucking time
I gotta do other shit
Like watch and bully. Yeah, that's right. Oh, that's that's a little teaser for everybody. Yeah. All right
Next one. This is from your boy has a message for us. Let's hear it. All right. Hey fuckers
Just wanted to tell you I love you. Yeah, you're all my role models. Thanks. You'll suck
No, my question is why do I not have any friends?
Yeah, if you approach your your potential friends with like I love you you're great
No guys, I don't see any flaws in his approach. I think this really I I can't figure out
Just keep doing what you're doing, man, you'll find somebody eventually
I think I think your biggest problem is that we are your role models
That's an issue and I think you might be coming on a little too positively you got to nag a little bit more when you're no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you got it
You got to become good friends by being nice and then you can you can nag on people
I mean, that's that's generally true
The way you become friends is just to be like nice to them and then it's weird for a little bit
But then it's cool. You can hang out with us
You're all right, and then it becomes a thing like you want to go to a house and play Splatoon or smash
And then and then after a couple months after a couple months you can call them cunts all day
Yeah, that's true. This is how you get a girlfriend that you you say hey
Do you want to play smash not telling her that secretly what you're thinking of is?
And then she's given a verbal contract allowing you to do whatever you want sure once you smuggled in your own
That's how you do
Video games are you sent hashtag there it is
All right, here's one from Ronary Mishin Mishin welcome. What do you got? I?
Haven't talked to anyone in like over a week
So I'm wondering how long have you guys spent not talking to anyone ever in person talking to or like online
I guess he means in person has to be in person. I'm guessing just talk to us technically
So if that if it's online counts, you just broke his streak. Yeah, we reset the counter there reset the counter
I mean, I don't know. I probably have not gone a single day in my life without you know what now that I think about it in
College I think there were some days that I didn't talk to anyone
Yeah, I think the most has been like a weekend the longest I've ever been cuz like at uni
I would stay in my room and I I didn't really like my housemates and they didn't really like me, but it wasn't because
Like we had any animosity it was just like it was awkward the first time we met and it didn't stop being awkward
So it's just all I
Didn't but but I I would talk to I had friends at uni who are different and I would talk to them
But when it was the weekends, I didn't need to go in and so sometimes I would just sit at home playing video game
And and making pony reviews. Oh, yeah, that was that sort of time
Live with someone so I couldn't avoid the
You know the good morning sort of interactions, but if we discount those the mandatory interactions, yeah family members
Like I'm not talking like I didn't even have like proper conversations. It's like good morning
Hi and back sort of those things then probably like a few weeks. Maybe at some point
That's pretty long. Yeah
I went a few weeks in college because like what happened in college for me is that I was like dating my girlfriend at the time
And then we broke up and then all my other friends. I knew I knew through her
So I didn't want to talk to any of them and I actually I've lived on campus at the time
And I happened to be in horseman hall at my college and that was horse horse hall
And and this this was the only dorm on campus. I had single room dorms
So I lived on campus with no roommates at all
So for like two or three weeks at a time, I would just talk to no one and it was fucking sick
No one but the whores here in a man hall was it was there not even like classes you went to I had no friends
I didn't need to talk to them
So because this is like senior year
So I was just doing like senior portfolio and stuff and like no one talked to anybody doing senior portfolio because we were all like
About to die. So we had to do this entire big portfolio piece and get an art project ready for
The show we did at the end of the year, which I didn't find out because I didn't talk to anybody that it was actually mandatory
So like I don't care about doing stuff for a portfolio like a senior show to see like three people including my parents
I make things on the internet and they're like, no, no, this is like 40% of your grade. I'm like, oh
And oh, it's doing three days. I guess I should probably do something
Damn, did you get it done? I just took something I was doing on the internet just said oh, I was working on this the entire time
I made it work, but uh, no, like I didn't like I very rarely talked to the instructors at the point
I didn't need to and I would just like
Go to class then I would sleep during the day then it'd be up all night
I'd walk around the campus when no one else was awake at like 3 a.m. And it was fucking sick
Well, that's dope. I would say though
I feel like Mages situation is probably relatively common of people like who don't have any meaningful interactions day to day
And that's really sad. I would say
He didn't I would say fix this if your life is like this
It's not ideal and you're probably harming your mental health
It is as sick as it was it is better to have interactions with people
It's um, yeah, yeah, I am very lucky to have like brothers
Yeah, who are cool because we talk quite a lot like we often go on Pokemon me and
Hgb guy go and Pokemon walks together and we you know if we had something that was on our mind
We can talk about it while we're walking in Pokemon and it's like that's a really nice like very like not occasional like
Regular like deep conversation in real life, and that's that's nice. Yeah, that's good
It's good to have stuff like that if you can but if you ain't got brothers got to go go join a club
And I mean that sincerely I met a lot of great people through my anime club not a joke
Surprising like you might think you're fine, you know not interacting with people
But then you actually interact with people and you feel so much better about it
Swallow your special snowflake-ness and recognize that you are a base lowly human animal and humans are pack animals
And you'll be doing yourself a favor if you associate with you other humans life life is the sins
Yeah, you your social media goes down and then you cry
Alright, well that should be enough for him. Here's one from a house of Claude another message
Hi, I was in the sophomore year of high school
Well, I was an improv and improv club
We were playing a game called props if we don't know what it is you take an object and pretend
It's other things we ran out of props and
One of the girls said can I be a prop and I said impulsively all women are props
Water
He finishes he's drinking 95% of a liter of water right now
Wow, what a power move. Oh, yeah
No, he's gonna do it. He's gonna do it
I hate it. I hate this. There you go. Oh my god. Oh god. What a god. I just want to oh
That was nice
That was a good story. I liked it. It was a pretty good story
I
Kind of wish we weren't laughing immediately after he said that he called all women's props
Because I wanted to know what they responded with no, they didn't respond with anything. He simply replied
I'm going to drink 95% of a liter of water now. He did not okay. No, he didn't I'm telling you. I'm telling you
I was into it. Oh my god. I
Was not ready for some like weird like creepy incel comment, but no he fucking red-pilled the shit out of that
Well, I think we all pretty much that guy I mean the moral of the story
Clearly he's yeah, indeed. Here's one from a Tomasso Tomasso choco taco
Okay, all right driving through South Carolina. I found a place called a shit. You not cuckold landing
I just thought I should let y'all know just in case y'all don't have the location of PCPHQ locked in
I
Was gonna say it but then he said it cuckold's landing in South Carolina
PCPHQ southern division. I'm already on the plane. I'm already on the plane
Because it'll be a endless bounty of women available to fuck at all times because we will be the guys
We fuck all the cuckolds women
Yeah, I got I hope so here we go. He's one of David Bowie this one
Let's see what he's got for us
Question for a specific member of the PCP they might not be on that episode
So you might just be calling it for no reason and then the other members would have to answer for them
Which wouldn't give you a specifically satisfying answer for what you wanted to ask them
I like that one David
That that very true and very good very boy. Yeah, that was very yeah
It
Yeah, what it what was what are we supposed to do when somebody isn't on the episode and somebody wants a question for a specific member
You know at the member and then the reply in the comments on the episode. Well, you should do if you should do
Here's here's a solution if you have a question specifically for one of the members
You should start the voicemail with this is directed towards so we can if we hear it
We're for screening questions. We can know not to use that one if they're not on the episode
Yes, I generally that is a good thing
It's just like because the the PCB format is such that anyone could be there or not be there every single time
So there's no way to know
So, I mean the the flaw is just we screen them a little bit. I screen them really
I'm just gonna try to dump ones that don't use you know that person if they're not here. That's it
That's all we can do, you know, what else? What else is there to say about it?
All right, here's another one from a formal one spar. He's got another one for us
What's up?
Hello, you have a collect call from clear view mediocre security mental war
I'll take listen. There's no time. All right. I only had 24 cents for this non-net neutrality protected connection
All right, look, I'm not crazy. I need these timestamps to prove the conspiracy
There's a connection here that you're not seeing they haven't found out yet
I can still access my channel from the iPads in the rec room. I need time to have by October 15th
Time has expired. Thank you. Goodbye
Okay, good stuff. What's bar needs those Starfleet timestamps, right? That this is good. This is you see guys. He put
Just, you know, I like this. Yeah, he noticed that his his previous calls were being talked over because they were boring
And then he made them more interesting. That's very good. This is what we want. Good job
This is what we want. He deserves those timestamps. Yeah
And he's on his channel is like once bar weekly, I think and what's his uh, he's looking he's it was it it is Starfleet
Yes, all right anytime
From all PCB episodes send them to to one spar. He's probably on one spar Twitter. You can find them. I'm sure
But yeah, there's I wonder what this there's a connection. We're not seeing guys. What what could it be?
We need to find well. He is in an insane asylum now. So
Oh, wait
Shit, this may be a flaw in my plan
Here's another one from from Simon. Simon's got another one for us. What's up?
The voicemail's bit is bad
It only works on the dick show because he screens them and he has a high
quality IQ
Production value. Okay. Okay. And oh, but you're using the voicemail bit to say that the voicemail bit is bad
Isn't that contradictory? I hear I hear what you're saying Ben saying
Or whatever fucking
Who cares? This isn't funny. What I'm saying is fuck you. The voicemails are bad. Stop doing them
I just want to hear you guys talk about shit. Fuck off
I think that you are in the minority by not like them. I do it's interesting that if we if we had screened the voicemails
You're even the first one to go
I okay to be to be faith to leave clear
I do in fact screen them in that I listen to at least a portion of them and just decide quickly like okay
Is this one I'm going to show or not like is it we can't say that?
I mean a lot of you are going to bait the first couple seconds something that sounds good
I mean that's a risk we have to take
I mean if
If it like if they're able to make something enticing at the beginning and then deliberately make it shitty
Then it would be a joke and then it would be funny. So I wouldn't mind that I wouldn't mind that either
But you know, I think we are increasing the quality as we go and I think a lot of people like the same
Yeah, these ones have been good, but you picked the right you picked good ones indeed. Well, thank you. Thank you very much
I'm doing a little work on it. Um, all right. Here's one from somebody mage knows
This is from satan father of demons
Um sent in a voicemail
Let's see what we've got how embarrassing your dad is everyone's daddy, you know what I mean
Listen closely you fucks
If you don't listen to one of mage's wonderful dream stories, what's your episode?
I will smite you
Fuck
Oh, no dad
Oh, he loves he loves you so much. God mage, hit up your dad call to come play defense for you. How embarrassing
The cyber police are gonna come get us
Got any of these dreams for us or immediately mage anything to report? Uh, shoot
No time no time. Um, we don't want to we don't want to be uh, uh, what's the word?
We don't want to be supporting satan's agenda. Anyway, this is a christian podcast. Yes. I'm
Yeah, I'm a muslim
Did they I believe in a different satan
Right, okay, and this is the satan. Here's our last one from uh ultimatum juniper
Okay, what's up?
You mother
fuckers
Mage just wants a goddamn piece of candy fucking corn
She's been a respected member of your fucking misogynistic podcast
For decades
And y'all can't send her a fucking shitty piece of three cent candy corn
She got dammit airdrop that shit like it's east germany, bro
Make sure it gets there
Girl starving in all of lithuania that she owns and controls with her mob
So you better watch the fuck out
Ben mother fucking saint bestman
dick
Fucking relapse on the kilo keto lifestyle. He told me I should do it
And then I fucking did it and I just ate cream
For days and now I can't leave my fucking house and I'm shouting into this voicemail machine
Into the void
It's all right. We hear you. We hear you
I heard that too
Oh, we'll pass that fuck you on to ben
We'll make sure he hears that one loud and clear. Well, it's it's the middle of september now
So I guess candy corn will be available again soon
Oh, that's true. That's true. How are we?
People are already getting into the spook spirit
Guys get ready for fucking
Oh my god. Hey, wait a minute. Gib. I just want to say it would be pretty appropriate if the if the finale of
Of pump a.k.a pump the big spooker dropped on halloween. That would be a pretty incredible
ending wait, wait
Shut up. Oh shit. Wait. I didn't know that was a thing. All right. Well, it's it's it's not actually my secret plan
But it is a very good because that's when she was born. Oh, yeah, that's right
Oh, what was that? Was that tom if it's going to be halloween soon?
Does that mean you're going to be changing your twitter icon to something not halloween related? Is the gag going to continue? Oh, yeah
What's it going to be?
Oh, oh, yeah, yeah, I'm going to change it back to just hypocrite
Will this be one year? I it was like one year of having continuing to have the halloween
Twitter thing which I started in november last year
Right and pump who was born as a result of this, right? I will I will always be halloween except on halloween
Fantastic. Oh, excellent. Um, well, let's switch over to the questions real quick
We'll burn through a couple of these trash low effort, uh, you know questions and uh,
We'll just we'll do that show
Let me just read the pity question here from at noodle bombs
Uh, just ask when will we see the adventure time podcast? That was it just now. Uh, it's over just now
You you just heard it. We did it. We did it. You're welcome. Um, what all right. Well, so that's that what else is going on
Um, anyone looking in the in the main chat. I'll get some from here, but um
There's there's uh, there's not there's not a whole lot of pickings this
Really great. Tell me you posted in patron knowledge. Not the questions. Oh, they posted the wrong chat
Oh, true. That might have been why fair enough the same thing
You fool. There's there's several dream related questions
Oh
Our true nightmares, uh
This dream meme has to end the my dream is that we get no more questions about dreams every dream is to have more dreams
But I can't damn it ever since they cut out my mandula oblongata
um
This isn't a question, but it's in the questions box
Someone should draw all the pcp members as bugs from hollow knight and I agree. That's true. Someone should do that
That would be adorable. I love hollow knight art style and like the little bug bug designs. So that would be great
That would be great. I'm I'm weighing to hollow knight as everyone knows and just did the stream of it
What like two days ago? I remember remember when I drew all of us as like those furry rpg characters
I sure do. I was a spider. So yes, johnny is a spider
You know what's okay the biggest disappointment about hollow knight
This is literally the worst thing about hollow knight
Is that there is a big area that is spider themed and there is a big arena in the spider themed area
Yet, there is no fucking spider boss in the game in a game about fighting bugs
It's like that is obviously going to be like the biggest thing
Maybe it's going to be like I think it might be like for dlc because they're going to make a horn at dlc soon
But it's ridiculous. Isn't it isn't isn't it weird how how like
scorpions or bugs
Are they I think they're technically
They're insects. Yeah, they're like spiders
Oh, okay. So spiders count. I guess scorpions count too then. Yeah, well, they're not dogs. That's for sure
Um, I I've got a question here from eric sea bass
Uh, what kind of show would you make with a youtube red series?
Undertale irl all dressed up as the characters and we would act it out in on the set
I think mage would make a good frisk
Yeah, because she has the dark side to her true and she would kill everyone
Of course, of course, um
Did uh, uh, you don't strike me as a metaton though
You strike me more as a as a as a like an asriel or like you might you'd probably be flowery now that I think about it
Yeah, uh, uh, what was I going to say? Oh, apparently somebody told me that there was like a new boss in the switch release of undertale
Which there is pisses me off a little bit. Can you spoil me on it at all gib? Is it I?
Yes, it is
I don't know where it is or what you need to do to find it, but it is mu mu kissy cutie
Which is the anime that um
Alphys watches. Oh, you know what that's okay. Is it a good fight? Is it cool?
I don't know. All I know is that it appears briefly in the trailer. Oh, or in a video somewhere
I'll have to that's really he's just he's just like man everyone
Everyone who's played undertale has bought it now. I guess I'll just have to put a new content in the switch version
So all you fucks buy it again. See that's the thing
I played undertale a bunch and I don't want to play it again
Uh, nothing against the game, but I played it too much and it's it's not a game
That's replayable beyond like four or five times like after that. It's not really you don't get that much out of it
I don't know. I haven't played it in a long time
Like a I mean I'm still burnt out after making my video that took a million years. Oh, well you made a video about it
I I could I could potentially get the switch version
Uh, and we'll buy a switch and then get the switch version. Yeah, and then you know have a little fuck because I still
I still don't legally own
You know, I don't think I ever played it legally either now that I think about it
I bought it for PS4, so I paid my dues. Oh, there you go. Are we gonna get doxed is Toby gonna dox me?
All right, I got a question from you Toby first arrows on
It says how do you guys not believe in ghosts when you have met the lord of ghosts?
Well, there is a lot of speculation that he's just a man in a suit, which I I believe personally. I'm not aware of his conspiracy
Yeah, yeah, it's a big one a lot of people are thinking that I mean if if you're in the rowdy fuckers cop killers
Uh discord you'll you'll know
Um that the lord of ghosts was dethroned. He's no longer a lord
He's just the ghost. He's been he's been gang raped and destroyed by a group of slime riddles
On the steps of what he was like elected like the leader of of
He he was elected the mayor, but he he's not the mayor or the lord because he was a lord of ghosts before he became the mayor, correct?
Yep, he was the lord of ghosts
He became the lord mayor of ghost and then he was he was um impeached so hard that he lost all ranks and titles
With the with the discovery with the new menu item of coleslaw on the kfc menu that allows
The the denizens of slime city to attack ghosts at last we can get a foothold against the nega slime and me and my brothers in the
In the rfck we slayed the nega slime
And then we had to turn our mob like ravenous rage towards the lord of ghosts
Who summoned it to begin with with his endless rocks that bitch
And those goddamn busters with that goddamn ghost busting coleslaw
Now that's one for the swear jar right there using that word
Um, well all the questions are shit. So maybe let's just wrap it up here
We didn't get a lot this time. Uh, we did but we did tons of the voice ones. Which are the good ones anyway
Yes, poor tech space bros. They're all dead. Yeah, all right. I guess we're done everybody. Oh, that was good
I felt like there was a lot of good stuff there. We did it. We did
It was a solid one solid like the poops that I pooped. Um, because I eat only protein
You're right. I do need some salad, uh
So patreon.com slash the procrastinators is where you need to go immediately to give us $5 to get access to the bonus episodes
include a semi
Aunt bug hollow knight related a bonus episode that we'll be coming out
I think a couple days after this episode dropped, but we are very excited about it
so
You're gonna want to get in on that and there's like 16 old ones. So, you know, fuck you pay me
Uh, and one dollar to get into the bonus. What is what is 16 episodes divided by five dollars?
How much is that per episode? It's like nothing basically zero. It's basically zero at that point. You're basically getting them for free at that point
That's essentially true. So please do that or more. It's up to you dog
Whatever you want to do
And follow us at tpcrastinators on twitter for all the hot updates and question asking and shit if you're going to be a little
Non-paying bitch. So there you go. Uh, we'll see you next week
Bonus episode shortly after this episode drops. I think I'm like literally the next day. Am I am I wrong? No, it'll be
One two three days. All right three days from when this comes out. All right. I don't know why I care so much
But I'm just letting you know on the first is when they come out. Thanks for listening. See you next week. Have a beautiful time
Goodbye
Yeah
I'm supposed to be working right now. I'm supposed to be working right now
But I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
My dick i'm jerking
Myself i'm sucking
I am an asshole
I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't want to do it