Hiya.
No, no, no. It's just that it's called Hiya.
But it's a type of Hiya.
It's called Hiya, but I don't think so.
It's amazing how great it is.
If you put the weight in and turn it,
even if something bad happens, it's okay to put it in the book.
That's my opinion.
I've been doing a series of online online classes since I was a child.
I've been doing online online classes since I was a child.
The most important thing is not to fall.
I've been doing online classes since I was a child.
That's how you think.
That's how I think.
That's right.
I'm the best guy ever.
Last week was a mistake. I'll never leave you again.
I swear upon my Lord Jesus Christ.
With us today is Mumkey Jones.
Yeah, he's having a tough time right now.
Ben St. is here.
And Hippocrite is also joining us.
Yeah.
Fuck your enthusiasm.
Fuck you. Fuck the PCP.
Fuck my ass and suck my dick.
The PCP is what you got left.
It's all I have left is the PCP.
You fuckers have more subs than me now, God damn it.
It's true. Let's address this right away.
Guys, there's been a terrible event in case you haven't heard.
Mumkey's channel was in fact deleted.
It was destroyed from YouTube.
His main channel due to infringement of what was it?
Terms of service or something?
Wasn't it violent content?
No, it was. I made fun of Muslims one time too many
and they couldn't handle it.
I mean, that certainly seems to be the case.
His Sharia law video, in fact,
you were making jokes about how many subs you will lose.
You did in fact lose all of them as it turns out,
which is a certain kind of hilarity.
But it's quite sad.
So first of all, Mumkey's migrating his work
over to his Mumkey Jones 2 channel,
which is now just called Mumkey Jones, as I understand it, right?
Link in the description, of course.
We need to update all our links on the PCP.
No, I don't care.
Okay, alright.
Fair enough.
But, I mean, I don't know what's appropriate.
I guess, sub to his new channel.
If you like Mumkey shit, even if you don't like it,
support the man, because it's not right what's been done to him.
No.
Subscribe to his new channel, or his, you know, his most,
his current channel, his real channel, Mumkey Jones,
and give it to his Patreon, just to say,
fuck you, YouTube.
We support people who do things you don't like,
just across the board.
Anything you oppose were for.
Send YouTube your emails, and fucking tweet at YouTube,
and just fucking spam YouTube.
Is there a link we can use?
We can tell them to send shit to?
There's like a bunch of ways to contact YouTube,
but I don't know which one's the right one.
Incidentally, this will be a week ago,
by the time this actually goes up.
Yeah, I might actually have my channel back by this time.
It's funny.
The depth episode premieres tomorrow,
and the whole time I brag about how many subs I have,
so it's gonna be really funny.
It's gonna be really funny for people who hate me.
That's true. That will be an interesting arc.
Yeah, I can't wait.
I'm gonna avoid that comment section like the plague.
Well, if your channel's not back by the time this goes up,
and people want to...
I'll probably be dead.
Alright, and people want to complain about it.
Where should we send?
How should we protest to YouTube about it?
I think I can find the link where they can fill out a form,
and I'll probably put it in the description.
Can we put it in the description?
Okay.
And by the way, I'd like just people...
I think it will be most constructive to not just send them,
you know, like Islamic State videos
with like, you know, YouTube logo
shoot over the journalist who's getting his head beheaded.
You know, just like...
Those sorts of things will not be constructive.
Don't take the Trump approach.
Yeah, now that's evil.
Don't go crazy and tell them, send them death threats,
or what you've done is evil.
You want to just be...
You want to help...
This is real shit, people. Let's not fuck around.
This is real shit.
So be polite.
Yeah.
And say, you have made a mistake.
Please correct this, Monkey Jones.
Yeah.
This clearly was not hate speech of any kind.
It was simply criticism.
Right.
You know, in a satirical fashion.
So go take that tack, guys,
if you want to really help.
And I certainly do.
So there you go.
There you go.
Do what you can, people.
I guess...
Okay, so moving on.
Our topic for today is being prolific.
Whoa.
Being prolific.
Yeah.
So I...
Me and Nate have been doing...
And Monkey, really.
Monkey's always been quite prolific.
I did it once.
I did it once a long time.
Once in a...
T-Bap was prolific.
Every blue moon.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot about T-Bap.
Yeah, T-Bap was pretty prolific back in the day.
Before doing me and Mavva,
I always used to reminisce about how productive I was
during the T-Bap days,
and how much I loved it.
But now I've upgraded my most recent productivity memory.
These days, I reminisce about how productive I was
when I was drawing Brunswick.
That was my, like, golden age.
And I haven't been able to recapture it in a while.
You know, I'm sure this will come up a lot.
And certainly not to criticize,
because I love the work that you do.
Get the fucking...
Don't fucking criticize me.
You would say the same thing yourself.
And you did when talking about Brunswick.
Because when you started Brunswick,
it was a tougher art style.
But like you said,
you were able to get it out really fucking fast.
And then as you got further,
you kind of, like, you know,
you sort of developed more of, like, a connection with it.
Or you want it to be really great,
because you put so much time and work into it.
And, like, you start taking longer on pages,
and they get better.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, I started out with it,
like, I'm just gonna fucking blast it out
and not care that much about how it looks.
But, like, the further I got into it,
and the more important it felt,
like, the less I was able to do that.
So, like, yeah, like, early on,
I was like, I'm gonna draw, like, one,
maybe two pages a day.
And I did.
But then towards the end,
it was more like,
maybe I'll get a page done every other day.
And I mean, from the beginning,
like, the pages were smaller,
so there was, like, less to do on them.
So, like, it was, I don't know,
like, everything about that,
like, the way I approached Brunswick
just, like, led to, like, it getting done really fast.
And it was really good.
And I think I need to fucking,
I think I need to fucking, like,
maybe once champion's done,
I need to fucking take a minute
and, like, look at my life
and look at myself and, like,
maybe go back and...
Take a look at yourself,
then make a change.
Yeah.
And just, like, try and, like,
try and, like, see what I can take from that
and, like, put that in my fucking workflow, you know?
Like, try and replicate those circumstances.
I just had, like, an idea
while you were talking then,
just then, because, like,
I feel like you just need a project
that you feel, like,
you want to make more than you want to hone.
Like, you, like, like...
I disagree.
No, no, no.
What I mean is, like,
spending too much time on each, like, drawing
makes it take so long
and then you feel bad.
But if you had, like, a project
that was sort of, like,
you didn't care too much,
but it was sort of fun to do,
that, you know, that could be, like,
a good way to just get some...
Get yourself on that, like,
choo-choo train of just making things.
And I had an idea.
Oh, you mean, like...
You mean, like, take a break
from, like, the other stuff
and, like, do something
that's less, like, quote-unquote important?
Well, well, I was going to say, like,
doing a HD re-release of Sonichu,
like, just drawing the whole thing yourself.
God.
People have done that, actually,
but I see what you're saying.
That would take so fucking long, dude.
Well, I would actually say,
I think a strategy...
I mean, here I go,
shelling my own shit,
but, like, doing a, like,
maybe I'll actually draw a page a day.
Like, a challenge like that
that forces you into the play position.
I thought about it.
I can't do it with Champion.
If I start...
Not Champion, sure.
Not Champion, but something else.
If I started a new thing,
I could maybe stick to a page a day
for, like, a month.
Like...
I'd think about it.
Like, I could have done that
with Brunswick.
I could maybe have done that
So, yeah, it's a possibility.
I might really like it
if you did a comic version
of some of your recent
Nuzlocke adventures,
if there were any, like,
characters that stick out
in your mind.
Oh, what about,
what about Banana's Final Day?
Or, you know, like, that one?
Something like that.
You know?
Um...
Wait, you, sorry.
You said, like,
like, comic adaptations
of, like, pieces of the Nuzlocke's?
Yeah, sure.
Um...
Yeah.
That's a really good idea.
I really...
Please do Banana's Final Day.
Please, if you had to do it.
That's my favorite thing
that's ever happened.
Banana's Final Day,
or Banana's Big Day Out
or whatever I call it,
is my favorite moment
from both series.
This is amazing.
I'm here, everybody.
Oh!
I'm late.
But I...
Did we just start?
We've...
No, we've been going for
10 minutes or so,
but only because we already
have been waiting
for people such as you
to show up in the first place.
If you're...
Okay, if I'm too late,
I'll just go
if you don't want me here.
No.
But I'm here now.
No, it's fine.
Right?
I think, guys,
let's do a quick vote.
Who votes Jesse can stay.
Yay!
Stay!
I vote yay.
Yay.
All right.
Sorry.
I just got home.
I was at the happiest place
in the world,
the Gibraltar Trade Center.
It's a big, grimy,
dirty flea market
full of cool stuff.
We...
I don't think they're joined.
They can't.
But I want you here.
I want Jesse here.
I'm a weak.
I'm a weak man.
I can't hold on my own rules.
Monkey,
do you have any strong feelings
about this?
Oh, that's...
That's because the...
Let's give him 10% less pay
so I can get my money's worth.
The rules...
Okay, you're getting dark.
The rules document...
The rules document says
you can join late
and it's fine.
Like, that's...
Like, that's what the
explicitly written rules say.
Okay, I think that, like,
30 minutes late
should be the cutoff
for two weeks.
This is 25 minutes.
25 minutes.
That's very damn fucking close.
Yeah.
You're under the wire.
You're under the wire
that you put there yourself
slightly above yourself.
Just now.
Okay, we'll work on this later.
I don't care if you're here.
We'll figure it out.
By the way,
before we get too crazy,
let me actually read,
just for fun,
the Urban Dictionary Definition
of Prolific.
Just because...
Yeah, I think you'll find it
interesting.
Okay.
So here's the top definition,
Prolific.
Utterly, unexceptional,
absolutely average.
Person one,
did you go to that alternative
rap show on the weekend?
Person two,
yeah, it was prolific, eh?
This is the worst...
That doesn't sound right at all.
That's just wrong, yeah.
Listen to the next one.
This is the second one.
Prolific.
A dumb man's profound
actually means
fertile or producing.
I mean, I guess that
second part's true.
Okay, so they're saying
that people confuse the words.
And people...
I guess so.
And, like, the first one
is just that confusion
or something.
I've never been confused
on this word.
Does anyone actually think
this means mediocre or something?
Okay, whatever.
Well, I gotta say that
I'm actually pro-choicic.
Wow.
Nice.
Thanks, Ibo.
Just like my girl Hillary,
my hero.
It could be a statement that
people who play out a lot of stuff
evidently have a lower quality
since they, like,
do too much work.
I think that's what they're
trying to get at.
trying to get at with this.
Like, if you're prolific,
then you obviously aren't working
that hard.
Wait, what was the second one?
A dumb man's profuse?
A dumb man's profound.
Profound.
Actually means fertile
or producing.
Does that mean the person
using prolific in that way
is a dumb man or...?
Well, yeah.
If you use a word wrong,
you're dumb.
I would agree that
we're all dumb.
Yeah.
But not dumb enough
that we would ever
incorrectly, you know,
misspeak
or anything.
No, never.
Or use one word
when we meant another.
That should be our slogan,
not dumb enough.
All right.
Well, let's,
I don't know,
where should we take this?
Do we want to just talk about
the trials and tribulations
of being prolific
on millions or web?
Now, monkey is,
I think, consistently
the most prolific man here
when he's not doing
a big, big, gay event.
When his channel's not
fucking deleted.
Well, that too.
That too.
So, monkey,
why don't you tell us
about your approach
to your content?
Where prolificity
pertains to it?
I guess that's the word.
So, I have a
dry erase board
up on my wall
above my desk
and it has my
daily schedule.
And, well,
I don't really follow it.
I love it already.
I love it.
I got cucked.
But it's pretty much
like this.
Sunday through Wednesday,
I would do
work on main channel videos.
I treat it like
an actual job
eight hours a day
every day.
So, that's how
I crank out all this shit.
Then the PM
record the
I S M A podcast
AM
of Thursday.
Edit the podcast.
You have to
schedule this shed out
and treat it like a real job.
I love you, monkey.
This is perfect.
Go.
I've got a massive
erection right now.
Please continue.
Fridays are dedicated
to recording Let's Plays.
And then Saturday
in the AM,
you edit those mother fuckers.
And then Saturday
in the PM,
you record the PCP.
And there you go.
That's my week.
That's what my week
used to be before I decided
I'm going to kill myself.
And is that to have
Sundays off?
No.
Sundays I work on
main channel videos.
I don't get a day off.
Because my job
is making fucking
YouTube videos.
Exactly.
Days off are for
week faggots.
Every day is a day off.
I love it.
Days off are
literally a fake
meme.
A fake news
created by unions
to trick us into
thinking that we're
less cool than we
actually are
as human beings.
Weekends are for
if you've got a shit job
that I'm sure you're
totally into a weekend.
Weekends are for
people with bad jobs.
That's what they are.
It says that like
entertainment or the arts
is not a real job.
Fuck that.
If that person
has a quote
real job where they
get a fucking weekend
and days off
and get to go home at
5 p.m.
Fuck them.
They're the lazy ones.
They're scum.
They're nothing to me.
I work
fucking 25 hours a day
366 days a year.
Never had an off day
since before I was born.
Fuck you.
Die.
And the way that
I've been getting those
is actually every
PCP is recorded.
We actually talk
10 times speed and then
we slow down.
Except for today
when I can 10 minutes late
for the podcast
because I was at a flea market.
The happiest place.
The only day off
I've ever had in my life
and I still made it
to work on time.
Yeah.
On time.
What was the place called again?
Roughly on time.
Whatever.
Yeah.
That's great.
Jesse, what was that
place called again?
I just it sounded magical.
Gibraltar World Fair
or something.
The Gibraltar Trade Center.
Amazing.
I went today.
It's like my favorite
place in the world.
It's like an hour away.
Fantastic.
Like an airplane hanger.
Fucking grimy ghetto
flea market full of like,
you know, just like
vendors full of stuff.
Yeah.
And there's this huge
sign.
I'll post a picture
of me by the sign.
It's the sign of this
of this dandy gentleman
in like a bowler derby
and a brown pinstripe suit
with a cane.
And he's like,
welcome to the Gibraltar
Trade Center.
I'm Gibraltar
and welcome to my stuff.
You can buy my stuff.
He's my best friend.
He's my hero.
He's my father.
I took a picture
standing next to him.
And I went is because
after this summer,
after 37 years,
the Gibraltar Trade Center
is closing its doors
once and for all.
And it's the saddest thing ever.
So yeah.
So I called up my secretary.
I said,
we have to go to Gibraltar
every day this summer
before it closes.
Ben,
remember that trade center
that we went to
where I think we a,
we sold our original
NES with all our games.
Like,
no, no, no.
That's not that's
you're misremembering
because we sold our original
NES at a GameStop.
And I know
because they ripped us off
for an original copy
of Kid Icarus,
which they gave us
a measly,
miserly,
$1.
Parsemonious,
$8 for.
Fucking cucks.
And the one cent
for like all our games.
Probably could have got
like 30 or 50 for it.
Why the fuck
did we sell that?
Okay, but forget that.
But I do remember,
I do remember a flea market.
I do remember
the Gibraltar
trade center.
It sounds so funny to me.
And it's because
the World Trade Center,
that's the first thing.
I was thinking it.
I never realized
they got the World Trade Center
and not the Gibraltar one.
Yeah, true.
Nate, but I do remember
a flea market.
The Gibroni trade center.
There was a flea market
where we bought
Earthworm Gym 2.
Metal Gear Solid 1
and Metal Gear Solid 1.
Remember that?
No, but I remember
Earthworm Gym 2.
I remember we bought
Metal Gear Solid 1
at a trade center
because you're like,
my friend,
Stefan really likes this game.
We should buy this game.
That sounds like
something I'd say.
If I can add to
what Jess was saying
about an hour ago
before Nate and Ben
interrupted with
this stupid bullshit.
The point about
the wage cucks,
like, you know,
they go to work at 9,
they go home at 5.
Yeah,
like you get to
stop working at that point.
But when you're doing creative
stuff,
all day you're tormented
by thoughts of,
okay, what should I be working on
next?
What's the next idea?
What's the next video
going to be?
And I can't turn that part off.
It's not like a 9 to 5 job
where it's like,
okay, I'm at this place
and now I'm back at this place.
I'm at home all day
and I can't stop
thinking about things
I should be working on.
It doesn't turn off.
Yeah, it's true.
I can think like,
I can't do anything.
I just like,
I'll lay on the couch
and like try to relax
and play video games.
But like,
even when I'm relaxing,
I'm not relaxing
in my head.
I'm still working
in my brain.
You know what that is?
That's the comfort
of low personal expectations.
Like,
oh yeah,
it's not like
if I work harder,
I'm going to like
make any money today.
Like,
why would I,
why would I go in
and like put in an extra hour
to like get this project done?
I'll just do it on
fucking Monday.
Who gives shit?
And it does,
it does its own destiny
out here doing our own shit,
which is why it's so much better.
And especially like,
our particular branch
of entertainment.
Like,
I'm sure monkey probably
has this problem as well.
Where like,
I feel like I can't play
a video game
because I should be
recording it somehow.
Yes.
Yeah, yes.
Video games now.
Yeah, like video games
are like my,
they've always been
like my most beloved hobby,
but now they're also
just my work.
This is why everybody
should stream all the time
because streaming is,
is basically,
you know,
when you're being able
to play a video game
and relaxing
and chilling out with people
and you're not,
you don't feel like
you're performing,
you feel like you're
hanging out.
And also,
you don't have to edit anything.
It's,
it's so much better
than making Let's Plays.
I made Let's Plays for,
you know,
a couple years.
Nobody ever watched them.
Nobody ever watches
the live streams,
but at least now,
I can see there are a few
Hey man, 23 viewers
reliably turn into
Minecrafty every Friday
and over.
Yeah,
and she bovers like the,
the queen of the chant.
Yeah.
So,
but it's like,
even if it's only 20 people
on a,
on a YouTube view count,
20 people is like,
there's nothing,
but in a stream,
it's like, yeah,
I have 20 whole people here
and they say,
that's a party.
It's not,
it's not just video games.
Like I feel that way
about everything.
Like,
like watching a movie
or something.
It's like,
yeah,
I could,
I'm spending this time
watching a movie like,
man,
I could be making something.
I could have made this movie.
I could have made this movie,
but I was used to look down
and I still do
on people who kind of like,
in a,
just,
just like people who aren't
creators,
but like have a,
a social media presence.
Like they just have a
Facebook page or whatever.
And then they like feel the
need to like document
the cool shit they do.
But like,
I do a different version
of that now where I like
post to Twitter,
the things that I'm doing
that seem interesting
or relevant.
In addition to just my
thoughts and shit,
just cause like,
like when I was in
Anime Expo,
I just felt a desire
to post all this shit
cause it's like relevant
to you.
And,
you know,
it's a little different
from like the reason people
do it,
but I feel like it's part of
like my branding.
So I,
I can feel like I'm
accomplishing something
by doing that,
you know,
like I'm,
I'm helping my,
my business
by doing that shit.
It's cool.
My Twitter doesn't help
my business,
but I do enjoy it.
I don't know.
For a while there,
for a while there,
I was really on
Twitter a lot.
And I kind of,
I don't know.
I was doing something productive
cause I was like,
expanding my social media
outreach or something.
But I think it's,
it's not real.
It's like,
I don't know.
Like it's,
there's such a thing as too much.
You know,
there's not a real
return on investment on Twitter.
There is a bit.
Like I think it's good,
it's good and beneficial
to maintain some kind of like,
you know,
fan like direct line
of communication there
and like talk to people
and like get messages
and respond and,
you know,
show everyone
you're still here
and you're still doing stuff.
But like,
yeah,
not much.
Like a little,
a little bit goes a long way.
Yeah,
I feel like in the last year or so,
I've become like really good at Twitter
to the point where like,
like I've got more followers on Twitter
than people with more
YouTube subscribers than me.
And like,
it feels good.
You get that rush.
You get all the,
the favorites
and the retweets and stuff.
But like,
I would almost prefer to not be
on Twitter,
so I wouldn't tweet as much
because like,
like I have a vision for myself.
Like I long to be
one of those mysterious creators
who doesn't have
a social media presence
and like,
oh, people only know him
from his work
and that's it.
Like I show up out of nowhere
after like months or years
with a video
and people are like,
wow, he's back.
What a legend.
He's back.
I want to be that guy
and I can't because
I'm too damn good at Twitter.
I feel that.
Some,
sometimes it feels,
it feels a little cheap
for me to be like,
going on Twitter
and like just talking to people.
And it's like,
I should be speaking
through my work instead.
Like why do,
why, like why do I have to do,
why am I doing this?
But then it's like,
and like sometimes
like I'll fool myself.
Like I'll lie to myself.
Like I'll,
I'll go on this massive
tweet storm
or I'll make a big chain
of tweets,
making some like,
grand point
or like,
fucking philosophical
theory.
And,
and I'll look at it and like,
hmm,
maybe I'll just take these tweets
and format them
in the form of a video.
So I'll have content.
I'm never gonna fucking do that.
I don't know
why I lie to myself.
Once it's on Twitter,
it's gone.
It doesn't matter.
It's lost to the void.
It's kind of given you,
like, yeah,
since it's sort of published
in a way,
it's like,
yeah,
you get the endorphin rush
of having said it,
but without having said it well
in the format people
actually care about.
And the way that
will actually make you money.
I have seen you
take tweets
and turn them into videos
before,
or at least put them
into videos.
So,
what are your tips
to bring back
in a video form
if I can?
Well,
let's,
I don't know.
I think,
did we get off
our original topic here
a little bit?
I mean,
this is all relevant,
but let's focus
in a little bit.
I was asking
Monkey about how he
deals with his
productivity.
And he,
that's perfect,
Monkey.
Your scheduling system
is exactly what
I should be doing.
I,
like,
I don't have time.
So either,
like,
I've decided like,
I'll do a thing
where I'll be like,
I've devoted like,
like Saturdays and Sundays
are like this.
I just sort of think
in my head during the week,
like, okay,
Saturday and Sunday
are just pure
get YouTube stuff done.
Just work on that stuff.
But the problem comes in
that I don't organize
that time,
like specifically enough.
So I'll do things
like wake up in the morning,
like today,
and like,
you know,
okay,
I'll just spend like
an hour,
you know,
and so what,
what am I going to do?
Waste the whole day?
I don't think so.
Meanwhile,
so many Saturdays,
the days that I have,
like,
the most amount of time
to work on shit,
end up just getting consumed
by me thinking like,
oh, I'll do it in a bit.
Oh, I'll do it in a bit.
Oh, I'll do it in a little bit
because I have not structured
my time perfectly enough.
It's almost like
you're a pro Krastin.
Hey,
that's me, baby.
It's funny,
Nate,
that you still go through
that because I'm,
because you did me a math
for,
you had to do it every day.
And I'm doing
the,
my thing,
the Igmovo tourdage thing.
And every time I wake up,
I'm not even considering
not doing anything.
You know,
I've been working like
from 8 a.m. to
however long it takes.
Usually,
usually I finish
the video for the day
by 6
and then I try to
start the next one
immediately.
But like,
the idea that
after me a math
of her,
you could wake up
and then not want to,
not continue that.
That's,
that's,
I agree hippo,
Nate is a fucking
hack.
It all makes sense,
just in the context
of the way that
my brain works
because like,
I'm doing this thing
where I like,
like during me a
math of her I was able
to like kind of
be intellectually lazy
and just say,
Nate,
your whole life
is now making videos
and you are doing
nothing else.
And because of that,
I didn't have to actually
put in the hard work
of something
that will like,
pay off long term
of being able to structure
And like that's because I was able to just kind of relax into I've given up everything except making videos
Like that's actually kind of the easier way to do things than like managing your life properly
That's what it was like. That's what it was like drawing Brunswick
I would like wake up and be like there's no question of me doing anything other than just sitting down and starting to draw
Right, and it worked. I've never been good either at the scheduling thing
The only schedule I have is
Every every twice a week I stream and around that I just I have
I've mentioned this before I have like a pad of paper of like goals that I needed to get done at the moment
I have just like the list of video ideas. I have and once I've done one for the day. I just tick it off
but
The idea of saying okay for the for the beginning of this day the AM of this day
I'm gonna work on this I
It just doesn't feel right. I've made calendars like that before where I would say all right for this hour
I'm gonna do on work on this
But I never know like I sometimes can start at the right time, but I didn't never end at the right time
So the entire schedule is is fucked for the rest of it. So I'm like, ah, well, I've gone like over by three hours
I don't know what to do now. Should I say never next thing?
I've never been able to stick to a schedule
But what what what's worked for me is like just getting the day started on the right foot
Like if I get the day started and I'm starting to work
Yeah, then that's gonna be a productive day
But if I wake up and I'm like I'm gonna do something else for a while and then I'll start working like I might as well
Just give up, you know. Yeah, man
That's like my my Achilles heel as a as an as a creator and as a human being
Hmm is that I have like a hard time focus and like you said Ben
It's almost like an involuntary procrastination. We're like like when I get up
I cannot think clearly at all until I've like eaten and been outside and walked around a little bit
So it's like I'll sit down to work. It's like, okay. Well the first time hungry
So I go to eat and it's like well, I need some fresh air. So then I walk around food was a trap
They get back a trap. Yeah, then I finally get back and start to sit down like well now
I have to go pee so then I have to go pee then I go pee go back down sit down
Well, now I'm hungry again
So I go and I fucking I eat again and now I have to go outside again
And now I fucking remembered that like I thought of a tit so now I'm horny
So now I got to go sail around the world and find like a seaside brothel
Yeah, and then I fucking come back like a month later and finally sit down and it's like well now
I'm hungry again. You know, it's never ending. That's why you know, it's like two in the morning ain't done shit
Yeah, that's pretty much a similar problem to me
The only thing I find that helps is breaking my tasks down into tiny little bits. I like you should see me at work
I've got all these post-it notes that have all like my tasks broken down into like tiny little chunks
Like it's better at work because like there are people there who will fire me and hold my feet to the fire if I fuck up real bad
So I have no choice but to schedule my shit and that's great
Having deadlines makes me a thousand times better at getting the shit done
Even if I like am a big shitty procrastinator and wait until like the last possible minute to get it done
Which I've always done and I really want to fix about myself
But but like like I really I take every task. I have I have all these lists
I make it work and I really try to break it down into the smallest possible components and then just just itemize like okay
I'm doing this now then I'm gonna do this then I do that and I'm not great at it
Obviously, but I find that even if I'm like give and I like fail to
Like stick to the plan having these to keep me sort of on in sailing in the right direction of what I need to get done
Eventually like the little steps to do and really knowing like exactly what motions
I need to specifically do in order to get it accomplished is a big help to me
It helps me long term get things done. Even if I you know, no stick to the plan perfectly
Yeah, I'm
I was gonna say something and I blanked out something about Igma Vo 2 just something about video something about making videos
It's something about being productive or probably in fact
I've you you have been able to get like it sounds like at least one video done if not more
During your time. Yeah, if it's a blog I can get two videos done per day
It's like one of them's a blog and the other one's like I've edited video
I never managed that with with me a math but not even once I mean I have a huge advantage because I have all day
Oh, that's true. That is true. So it's it's not a weekend. I never did it, you know
Oh, no, I've been working all fucking week. Oh, every single waking moment. It's it's
You know, this is what I was gonna say the em
Cuz like all these problems of like you wake up and you're not sure you want to really start doing this
I oh, you know, I didn't finish that podcast
I'll just put that on and listen to the last bit of that as I wake up and you know
I haven't bite to eat and before you know it, you're clicking on the next podcast and you're like, oh, yeah
Oh, no, I'm gonna kill myself
but this month like even
Even just before the month I was trying to make a few videos like as a buffer to get me started
And they were taking more than one day each to make and I was like, oh, no, this is gonna suck
And as soon as July started, I was like, I have to do it now and the deadline that the pressure
It wasn't really stressing me out. It's just like well, I have to do it
I'm going to do it and I love pressure. I love pressure
It makes me a real human being it forces me to accomplish things. Yeah, I wish people put things on me and forced me to do things
It's so hard to self-motivate what I'm gonna do what I'm gonna try and do it's not gonna is not gonna happen
But what I'm gonna try and do is I'm gonna make one of one of the years
It doesn't matter when the year starts, but I'm gonna make 365 videos in a row
I'm gonna see what happens because if casey-nice I can do I mean he does the same sort of
Yeah, but what does he do? I thought he just like talked about what he did all day like hippo makes actual analysis and shit
That takes work. That's true. It does
I'm I'm a lot of the videos I've been making I'm like does that make any sense
I don't have time to check I just I just write it on the other hand casey-nice that has one guerrilla in subs
So, you know, it's it's it's like my ad sense has been going up quite a bit just because of the daily amount of videos
I'm happy about this. I like it's great. I like daily videos daily videos are great. I might I might do it forever
I hope you do
Being prolific. Yeah, is it is is um is addictive. It's it's cool. Yeah feel like you're really on top of things
I already miss me and math intensely and
You know, I want to go back. I have to go back hashtag max revive
It really is like like giving yourself a deadline makes you more powerful because like absolutely like if I have um
Like say I want to make oh, I don't know a 4th or July video
Like I'll tell myself. Okay. It has to be out on the 4th of July
So I'll work at it really hard and I'll get it almost done almost done
But if the as soon as the clock strikes 12 on July 5th, it's like well now
I'll never fucking finish it because I don't care anymore even if it's 99% done. It's like yeah, fuck it. I'm done with this shit
Yeah, fuck it. You'll you'll get a you'll get a 4th of July video on fucking August 22nd
This is not this is not quite the same thing
But something something that I really regret and I think has really hurt me was when I decided to release like half of
Champion because like the previous comics I released only like I released them entirely when they were done
And it was like a big surprise and it was like oh man. This is what I've been working all the time
Here's the whole thing
like releasing half of it really was like really
really killed my motivation a lot and
Because it's like it's in a way it feels like okay people have already seen it and it's no longer
It's no longer a surprise like if I had had if I had kept it to myself and just like sat on it and been like
It's out when it's done
I would have felt like so pressured all the time to be like well no one's seen it like as of right now
I've got like no one's seen my work
I need to finish it so people can see it and it would have been like even like I gotta finish it no matter what now
It's like well people have seen almost of it or a lot of it
You know like it can get the rest done and and it doesn't I
Took the pressure off myself, and I feel like I really paid for it. I hate when the pressure goes off
Yeah, I'm just repeating myself here, but yeah, that's I hear you I hear you one thing that's really confusing me is that?
Deadlines and pressure used to completely destroy me when I was younger
And I don't know when the change happened because like in school when they're doing something that you want to do
You know that's I guess that might be it but like I used to do I was I did like art at school
And I liked art and I was like yes making cool big things and stuff
But it was like every deadline of a thing I had to do was like oh, no, I only have seven days left
Oh, no, I only have six days left. Why haven't you done anything? Oh, no, I only have five days left
Oh, no only four days left. Why you just why you just just complaining about the number of days you don't have oh, no
It's done. Oh, I didn't do anything. Oh, that was depressing the whole time
I don't know what I am doing with my life, and that was just me the whole time forever through school
Dude, I and now deadlines are like good like I thought they were bad, but they're good
And I don't know when that changed and how you know
I know comparing that to like school work like
Deadlines were great for me because I never I mean sort of because I I was that kid who never did I always got pretty decent grades
I guess I mean whatever who gave a fuck but like I would get the project done like the night before I would stay up the night
Before it was due and finish it then this happened to me like every single fucking time
Including on my class that I finished like this January like as a 26 year old man
I was still doing I have not fixed this about myself and may never actually do so
But like finding myself doing doing this shit like I it's astounding to me
Like how much I am willing to just like drill myself into the fucking ground and like plan things to have
I plan things out ahead of time and work for months to finish a project that I'm just kind of interested in or very interested in
You know whatever as opposed to like at work where I just like whatever who gives a fuck school work. Oh, I don't care
God, I don't want to do this shit. Just like having the motivating factor of doing something for myself
It's like it's like I don't know it's kind of like kind of like that shit Davoo talks about we're like
Like if I guess like a sort of a political thing
We're like if if someone's telling you to do something if like just for example if the government is like telling you like okay
Restructuring people to like be these people to like fit into these boxes. That's what you're gonna be your whole life
Like as opposed to letting basically the free market like dictate what people are gonna be and let them like find something
They're good at and like find a way to make it work like not only will those people be happier at least in my own experience
I'm like at least ten times more productive
Because I'm doing something that makes me happy and I'm able to get more out of it
And I like I personally have way more to contribute to the world doing this kind of shit as opposed to you know being a fucking
You know wage-cuck automaton just just doing the shit that I'm told to do it's it's night and fucking day
Yeah, so yeah, but like but like the free market has its own
Downfall because like it because like look at YouTube right like look like YouTube is a free market
YouTube is a what might loosely be described as a meritocracy where like people get rewarded for unless you don't approve a sharia law then
Well on YouTube you get rewarded for doing what you know what there's demand for you once and that's why and that's why YouTube has become
So homogenized because everyone is everyone is incentivized to do the same thing and that's what the free market does and I mean
It's nice to say that like oh, but if it's not rigidly dictated if it's if it's if it's up to the individual to decide then
Yeah, you can do what you want to do
But like not everyone not everyone can be a you know an esteemed anime youtuber
You're absolutely right about you're absolutely right about that
I guess just in this case I'm more focusing just on this one this one thing that I notice is better about it
There are absolutely problems with I mean specifically YouTube or any kind of system that is trying to like or just ends up
We maybe intentional or not like steering people into like certain compartmentalized ways of doing things like that's what me a mafia
Was all about I would love to just spend all my time making gigantic like cinematic anime reviews the way that I've been doing
That's what I really want to do
But I realized that I can't do that if I want to survive I have to adapt to the world
I'm in which forces me to do me a mafia and you know what it won't always work out this way
But I found out that people actually pretty pretty pretty pretty positive about hearing me just talk about shit and doing that kind of like light
Editing stuff and that like it's it's brought out that something I see myself as being better at doing, you know
And it's helping me kind of find these other ways. So of course, it's not always gonna work out that way
There's going to be problems
But you know if you can be forced to experiment to like see how you fit somewhere that could be helpful
And if you just don't succeed at it then like yeah, it's gonna suck
But like you know you should find some other way if like the thing that the market's forcing you to do just isn't working out
Then yeah, you got to find something else which can be a loss for sure
But I just think that process is more interesting and productive and like
Yeah, like really productive like you'll get more out of the people doing it if you let them
Explore that shit for themselves instead of like box in the mint of shit
No, yeah something like that something like that I don't particularly like it when
When there's a person and he makes something really great and he gets a load of fans and then he
Consistently doesn't make something that's great forever and his fans continue to be there because of that first thing
I don't particularly like it, but I understand why it has to be that that way because oh no, are you calling me ego raptor?
No, I'm calling I'm calling everybody the same guy who does yeah
Because it's unfortunate when you just see somebody who used to be good
And now they're just doing something that is kind of homogenized and kind of boring and kind of whatever
But that's how they got to keep stay afloat and I don't like it
I like to crit before in Gava would to a ditch you get so mainstream. I look at my thumbnails and I'm like
I don't even know who I am. What is this Nate?
Are you saying that you're never going to make another video in the same?
You know epic vein as the tank and I'm currently working on it
It's just that I'm restructuring the way that I do things so that I can survive while doing this
And overall make more throughout my life
I'm just probably gonna break up my content between like doing those long-term and then like take a day and make like a smaller video or something
Yeah, I think that's a good thing to diversify instead of just like abandoning our only exclusively doing one type of video
Yeah, yeah, just trying to compensate for my own weaknesses
I trust Nate to be able to continue making big videos while still doing the small stuff, but I'm I
Don't know I don't know I just
Maybe I feel like I haven't made a big big video. Yeah
I kind of feel like the era of the big video is over on your way. Yeah, I
Mean even even me as a viewer like I you know more than anyone. I appreciate
the merit of the big gigantic videos, but
Man, even as a viewer myself. It's like I'd rather watch the five-minute video
Here's here's a weird dilemma that I that I find myself having like what I like I
Like it's easy for me like I look at I look at the landscape of YouTube
I look at how you know, it's all like vlogs and it's all like let's plays and it's all like casual like low low produced stuff
And I'm like man
Look at all like look at all the shit content like what I like what I think of as like real content is like worthwhile
Content is like scripted like narrow like narratively driven like like stories like fit like stories and fiction
It's like that's what I think is good
And like that's what I try to make as an artist myself
But as a viewer as a viewer
I'm I don't like I'm kind of pushed away from that like I don't eat like I don't eat like I don't want that for myself
Because it's like but I don't know if that's because of like
my like my like I don't know if that's because of like the YouTube landscape and like because of like culture
Like I don't know if that's me as a viewer or me as an artist because like as an artist
I'm like, I don't care about what stories other people are telling. I'm trying to tell mine over here
So like I wonder I like I hope that it's just me being like biased by my by my profession
You know like what I like I hope or I would like to think that like people that like a layperson
Like the masses like respond to that stuff well
But I don't know if it's true or not because technically I'm part of the masses and I find myself being like well
Whatever someone else will watch it if it's good someone else will watch it and enjoy it and like it
I and it'll get popular but if but leave that I don't but I want no part of it
literally my favorite show on YouTube right now is
Monkeys Yu-Gi-Oh, let's play that is without a doubt my favorite thing happening on YouTube right now
I don't even know how to play Yu-Gi-Oh, but it's my fight
It's my favorite thing and I can't explain it. It's it comes out like every other day or something like that
I fucking love it. He's just plowing through all the fucking
Like we're past where I even know who these characters are anymore
I don't know who any I for some reason something about it is just great
and it's so easy for me to watch like every morning as I'm coming into work and
You know, it's it's really great
But but yeah, let's let's talk about like the downsides of of being prolific or prolificity or whatever
Well, yeah, well you guys um, I mean you were talking about wanting to do more stuff like short videos like Mia
Maffavan gives thing and like getting them out more more being more prolific
I almost feel the opposite way where like I I kind of strive to be less prolific like I
Would I like my goal is to this for my patreon to get high enough that I can disappear and make one huge great thing
Project a month. Mm-hmm as opposed to like just just a never-ending stream of trash like I've been doing for all these years
I'm at a point. Thanks to YouTube fucking me that I'm kind of in that position where I'm like, okay
Maybe you know since I'm not gonna get 10 million views anymore
Maybe I'll just do two really big great videos and throw them up on the patreon and see what happens
That's something to try at least God your your video had just gotten like it was close to like a million
Yeah, I was right up to a million. They're like, you know, I know this guy. Yeah, yeah had it crossed over 900,000 yet
I know it's close. Yeah, it had
Well, uh, the um
Dair of a wimpy kid
That's that's a lot of views. Yeah, we'll see if I get it back and and if YouTube doesn't want to give me my
$1,000 in ad revenue, I'm gonna fucking burn YouTube headquarters to the ground
Yeah, they certainly deserve it
They're just they're just the worst. They're just the worst. Um, so are they gonna just gonna keep my money. What's the idea here?
Oh, oh, they're gonna keep your money
They're gonna keep your money just just like how right now we're having a little bit of I mean, I know this is getting inside
Maybe I should even talk about but like we're talking about those emails. I saw those emails today
Yeah, yeah, I'm talking like it's not a big deal
But like we're trying to basically get access to the to the ad revenue that the PCP has already earned and like they're
They're throwing up some real roadblocks here for us getting that money. They might just decide, you know what?
I think we're just gonna keep it. You know, yeah, that's uh, that's cool you guys, but and they're gonna they're gonna take that money
They're gonna build a paper mache cock out of it and fuck us with it. That's right. That's right
Well, and we're supposed and we're supposed to just thank them. Thank them for giving us this platform. Yeah
Thanks guys appreciate that
Well, okay, okay, but before we we go because we're getting pretty close to the hour
Let's let's talk about specifically more downsides of prolificity because that I did your depression
So you're like
It's easy for me to to be like really excited now that it's done, but like it was hell
I gave up sleep. I gave up sleep for for much of that time and just worked
I feel like it's way more depressing when you don't have any videos in mind and you're just sitting there. Yeah
That's yeah, that's true. I'd rather be stressed out and being like, oh man. I really need some sleep
I'd rather be like that than oh man. I really need to die like
I was the first one's better
I was I was just about to say not being prolific is what is what makes me feel more depressed
And then I realized something I realized something about the way that I am as a human being not not being like I think that not
Being productive causes depression and then I think that right rather than rather than
Product productivity making me depressed because it fucks up my schedule
I think that being depressed causes me to change my schedule to become productive to like to mollify
To mollify the depression because I'll go if I go a while and I'm not being productive and I start to hate myself
Then I'll like I'll have to like like with Brunswick like I was like and I was like the world is fucked
My life is fucked. I'd like there's nothing for me
There's nothing there's nothing for me in this world
It's time to just it's time to never leave my room and never do anything again and spend like all day every day
Just like drawing and that was like and that was like the fucking that like really helped and carried my problem
For a while. I that's true
I guess the only danger is falling into that kind of depression spiral where you don't make the change and start to make shit
It's like, you know, it's a gambit. I mean, I mean, I think the healthy
I mean, I think the healthy thing that that that nugget of
Hutsma from inside yourself and actually get shit done as opposed to you know, just killing yourself
I was gonna say I think I was gonna say I think the healthy about the healthy thing is to make that
Loathing my depression is like the opposite of that where I really love myself and my fear and like I just don't want anyone else to
Not like me
So my fear is that like if I take too long with a video or like too many days go by without a video for me that people
Assume I'm not working or not doing anything. Yeah, like sure like but my my biggest problem that like hampers my
Productivity is just like not being able to focus on one thing at a time
Like right now I'm looking at
11 Sony Vegas windows in my browser. Oh my all of different projects and like
Everything takes forever for me to get out because I can't focus on finishing one project at a time
I like I'll do like five minutes of work on on this window and then like get bored and zoom over to the other window
So like I'm just inching towards finishing all these different projects instead of getting one thing done and like my worst
Fears that people think that I'm just lazy or not working. I am working. I'm working hard all the time
There's just there's just no there's no results ever
And I don't know why not to be critical
But it sounds like the issue there is that little thing that get bored that get bored that allows you to you know
Just or that forces you I don't know. I don't know
It's more like run dry what I can't finish one thing before I start feeling guilty about not having finished the other thing
So I'm constantly like like a balancing my guilt for different projects and going from one to the other
That that you know that thing that monkey said oh just a couple minutes ago
You know about the whiteboard with the schedule, you know, that's inspiring to me
That's really probably what I need in my life more than anything
Yeah, I'm literally going to order a whiteboard as soon as we're done with this call
I want that I want that in my life
It reminds me it reminds me of those like you ever seen for like mangaka the like
Like the timetables of like how they spend their day and how like each hour is blocked out
Yeah, and they'll work for like 16 hours a day with like half an hour for lunch in the middle
And then like on weekday on weekends
They'll only work eight hours a day and then spend the other like and then like spend like four with their wife or something
And then on Sunday, you know, it's right back to it. It's like what what what's a better life?
What's a what's a better life really?
I guess is the question that sort of comes to mind when I think about this shit
Do you want to be somebody who like, you know as a nine-to-five, you know, it's it's fine and all but then on your weekends
Ah, you can chill out you can you can you fuck sluts at the club or do you want to be a content machine?
Where you spend 16 hours a day or more?
Bust in your ass and so the end of your life you say look at what I have accomplished look at
Terrible
The day is a bit is a bit much, but I do like the idea of working really hard
I mean I like time to make something that's so cool like I want to be I want to make a home stuck or a one piece
I want to make that yeah, the problem the problem with I'm dead the problem with the nine-to-five
Slog but then you got weekends free like that sounds fine to me because like but then like what are you doing with your free time on the weekends?
You should be working. Well, yeah, that's what I mean because it if you're not if you're not a content machine
Then like well what what what are those free time for what cuz like because if it's just time to just like sit there and like zone out
And it's like what's the point like what are you getting out of that?
I feel like people who zone out don't deserve that life off because
Yeah, they're not used to working so hard that they need a whole weekend of time off
You know what I mean, I mean my whole my whole deal is I want human advancement as quickly as possible
So I look at the landscape of humanity and I see all these people taking weekends off doing nothing
And I'm like get your shit together guys
I want you guys to discover your purpose in life and work until you fucking die to achieve it
You know be as happy as you want. I mean your shit together me like to me
Happiness is or like the closest way to time
No, no, no the closest thing to happiness that I found is just is just having a goal
Having a any goal and feeling like you're working towards and if you're working a nine five and if you're working a nine to five
Then like what's like and then you have the weekends off like if you're not using those weekends to work towards some goal
And it's like well, what are you doing? You know like you know you need you need to feel like you're progressing towards something
I think the normie answer would be like maybe a family like starting a family and
Yeah, that shit
Children kissing your wife. No, that's actually that's actually
That's that's a fine way to like to be a good parent
I think I'm not I'm not gonna I'm not gonna shit on I'm not gonna shit on the idea of being a family man
Like if that's your goal, of course not. Yeah, okay, but like I'm just I'm imagining someone who's just like you know
Like time off for the sake of it is not satisfying
Like if you're not if you're not using it to do like to do something that's like gonna bring you happiness
even if even if it's something as simple as like
You know, you don't know what you want to do
But you find you kind of like the idea of playing guitar, so you have a guitar and you just play it
You know play it a little you don't know whether that's going to result in a musical career
But it's something to be working towards it doesn't matter that you you don't need like an entire life plan planned out
Yeah, just need you just need an ideal
Like a goal a thing that you want to get towards and whatever people do
I think they're better off having like goals for it
You know like I'm going to do this for a while like even if this is a weekend thing
Yeah, yeah, like playing guitar like you said like to have a goal like you know what I'm gonna pick up guitar
It's pretty fun. Maybe one day you know my goal be like do a do an open mic and I just you know do that shit
I think you're way better off having something that you're like working towards then just I don't know not
Not doing that, you know
Yeah, if I ever find myself feeling bored then I will know that I'm doing something wrong
Because like I will definitely like I will always
Take off work to hang out with a friend or someone because that's important to me like it's way more important than work like
Like I almost live my life by the ethos if I can be with another person fuck work. It shouldn't exist. Well
disagree there, but alright
Yeah, but you know, but the opposite of that is that if I'm not working
I'd better be doing something worthwhile or fun or else. I should put my head in the toilet
Which is also fun
In a different way because I'm a fucking digital and that's what I do I swim in the fucking toilet. I
Don't know where I was going with that originally, but it went somewhere totally different somewhere superior
the story of my old roommate
Okay, my lifelong best friend who I lived with before I moved down to North Carolina
Mm-hmm. He worked at a kitchen
Eight hours a day and no joke every single minute. He was home when he was not work
He would just sit on Netflix
While staring at his phone and that was that's literally his entire life
He's just binging through shows not actually watching them and looking at his phone
He would he's watched the two Netflix seasons of better console. He couldn't tell you what
Staring at his phone. That's tragic. Yeah, when I think about his life
Like is ignorance actually bliss because he doesn't seem that sad, but it it looks miserable to me. Yeah, wait
It's hard to say. Oh, I'm very confused about what he's looking at on his phone
He's just like on Twitter or fucking Facebook or reading ESPN.com to see what his favorite Faggity football player has been up to
That's just stupid shit. I
Guess yeah, I guess it's not really a bad thing if you you're satisfied with with less stuff in your life
But I couldn't be you know, you know, I don't like that though
It's cuz cuz if this guy or whoever you know, I don't mean to show the guy specifically, but like shit on him
I fucking hate him any anybody who does that I think would be Nate. Hello
Significantly happier or or at least equally happy if they were like working to accomplish something and then like you know what and then they also
They're achieving something which is good for everybody. So like I think let's just do that
I think it's just because people like that haven't even considered or tried or been put into a situation where they're forced to
Work on something
You know bigger than just getting through the day and they don't even you know
They can't even conceive of a big old goal like that
So they don't feel like they're missing out when they're not doing anything probably which one of you was it that said that if you
Don't have a creative outlet. You're not even a human being because I agree with that completely
I think that was me. I fit so I feel I think I've definitely said that
I stand by it completely
Jesse's definitely said if you're not a creative person, you're less than
That sounds like that sounds like a much younger more foolhardy and arrogant version of me
So I would I would also define creative in this context as like if you're working to like I don't know crack some new
Mathematical algorithm just in your spare time like Einstein used to that's creativity
You know, that's yeah, if you're putting your brain to work in any way. I think it's creativity sitting fucking yeah
Yeah, the background is wasting your life away in my opinion. I want to be a zombie. I guess if it makes them happy
I don't know. I mean maybe that maybe maybe that's a simpler and like less stressful existence
Well, I would I like to believe I I
Like to believe that the highest of my highs are better than a person like that's very true
Yeah, I would say that they're kicking their their stress down the road until they die
They're like I've accomplished nothing. Yeah
That's what I was about to say like people have midlife crisis is when they
Yeah, like a normal life and they have no reason they have no idea that you could even do more and then they get to an age
Where they're like man, I haven't really done anything and then it all comes and hits them all at once whereas for us
It's hitting us constantly, but less, you know
Yeah, we're facing it. We're we're staring staring into that a whole life crisis basically
Life is like and fast forward and you don't even realize how much time has passed and that you haven't done anything
It's very true. I
That terrifies me deeply without yeah without that structure without that structure that the bullshit academia system like forces you into and like
Tells you as important to some degree that might be just as you get older time goes faster, but nonetheless
That's yeah, there's that but also the lack of structure just makes it real easy for like fucking weeks and months to go by and you're like
Well, I wasn't supposed to be doing anything. No one told me to do absolutely absolutely
So very specifically gives you like little tasks and things to achieve like okay
I have to finish this paper by tomorrow
But like once you're out there are no goals handed to you you have to come up with your own goals and most people don't
Haveing them. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, most people are like just
Really happy that they don't have to think of good goals anymore
It's like you haven't liked those goals because school sucks when you're anything when you're in school
Goals were interesting then people would probably continue to do them up when you're in because most people go to school
And they do the work just because like they have to do it to get the degree
So then you they graduate and they're like, oh, well, thank God now
I don't have to do any of those things anymore
But then but then you don't if you don't have anything that you are having to do then you fucking
You're headed for a midlife crisis town USA
It really reminds me of at least personally how I play video games because I love
Accomplishing goals in video games and it feels great. I love like
Achieving challenges and you know, there's there's some challenges to achieve in real life
If you want to if you want to take the time to do that shit
So it's like people, you know video games give people like an artificial world that allows them to like feel like they're superior and like
They're they're doing something when instead of doing it in real life because it's way fucking easier in a video game
You know, I still love video games
But that that that probably is a lot of the reason why people I know it is for me
They yeah, they buy the hot new game
And they play it all the way through and they complete everything and then they're just like well, I did it
It gives them a sense of empowerment. It gives them like like I'm in their own life. Yeah
Yeah, it's like it's it's goals for them to achieve and they've been starved for goals because they're not doing anything
So I hate that I hate I hate thinking about that. I hate thinking about the fact that like
To a certain extent video games or video games are just like a sort of like hamster wheel
That usually are supposed to like step up on and run and if you and if you press if you press the right buttons like
It'll tickle your brain and that way that you've been missing and then you're like, oh, I got it
Games are in a sense kind of like emotional crack because you get to just like experience the most interesting part of
Characters lives over and over and like accomplish these gigantic goals that you will never be able to do in your pitiful little real life
And it just it's all big it's a big like playcane a mechanism to make you think that you're happy as you're like living somebody else's life
When I when I when I think about that I feel like oh god video games
Oh, no, get them just get them get them away, but then but then but then some time sometimes I'm like
Yeah, I was just gonna say but oh man
Undertale wasn't really like I mean I guess to a certain extent it was it had some tough bosses
But it was mostly about the story which is not really the same thing I guess well
So I don't know I would tell like make it makes like intellectual points about like the nature of video games
Which is cool. You know games do that a lot my favorite video game of all time is without a doubt
You have to burn the rope on new grounds. Oh my god
It's this 30-second long game where you just you fucking go and you like you walk along this corridor
You grab fire you burn the rope and you slay the grinning colossus
And then there's a there's like a 10 minute outro a song about how fucking badass you are for burning that fucking rope
It's the greatest video game ever conceived and laughs at this whole idea of what video games and yeah
Know what the the the worst and most agonizing game of all time in terms of like feeling like a mindless hamster wheel
For me the worst in terms of that and also
Possibly the best game ever made which is the problem is the binding of Isaac because yes, man
I know the guy who made that he's pretty cool
Yeah
Yeah, I don't know about that
We should if you want to he we should you should hear our conversation with him on the bonus episode a patreon.com
The procrastinators are TP procrastinators. I forget our url. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah dogs with him the last he was on the last man. So it was great game
I I hate it because there's no story and there's no reward and there's there's nothing that makes it feel like a worthwhile
Experience whatsoever, but the gameplay itself is so goddamn perfect and flawless and beautiful
Like there are times when I will just fall into an Isaac hole that lasts for an entire day and I'll hate myself
Yeah, I want to die, but I just can't it's it's the worst drug of all that's kind of like
The Zelda Breath of the Wilds doing to me sometimes these days like that's what I did when I woke up this morning
Yeah, I just played Zelda a little bit. No big fucking deal
Of course, it's a gigantic world to explore an infinite goals to accomplish. So it's like fuck my fucking day
But the thing about Isaac that's interesting to me that makes that that kept me coming back is
Is like if there's nothing new to discover
I won't keep playing a game like that even if I really like it because I'll I'll get bored
But like the fact that there's like new bosses to unlock new levels to unlock new items to find
You know like an extra challenges to give myself to overcome is what I'm all about when you get that like when when
Two or more power-ups like combine in a unique way that you haven't seen before
It's like fucking heroin right up my dick
I just chasing that dragon forever, especially when you get especially when you get the boomerang bullets and the Ipacac
Exploding bullets so the
That's my thing I
Personally have fallen way down the Magikarp jump hole. I'm really loving training all these Magikarps
I'm really I fully I fully admit
I don't know
It's just something to do like when I'm in the car or just like when I'm just like sitting around when I'm when I'm
Yeah, yeah, what I'm driving when I'm on the toilet. It's just
It's it's like I fully admit that the gameplay is like just a just a completely shallow just excuse
It's just like a series of rigamarole. It's just it's complete rigamarole
Like the only thing that matters is your trainer level and everything else in the game is just a is just like a bullshit hurdle to
Jump over just to get your trainer level up
But it's just so fucking cute how all your how all your previous Magikarps the ones that the ones that survive the ones that
Don't get eaten by Pidgeotos or blown or blown to smithereens by Voltorbs
They'll just like live in your pond and swim around in the background
You can see them there and sometimes they and sometimes they come and give your and give your current Magikarps some advice on how to become a great jumper
It's really cute and charming
That's pretty cool. I guess
Gyaradoses you can't you yeah, yeah, you can you can make your you can like fuck up really bad and make your a
Magikarp evolve into a Gyarados at which point he becomes worthless and is discarded
Just like when I normally play Pokemon. Yeah, I don't abide that shit
Yeah
Well, all right, that's cool. I guess we we pretty much explored our topic our original topic being productive or prolific
I got it. I got it my final word on being productive is I got I got to get back there
I got a I think it's time
I've been feeling real bad for a while about not getting enough done
I think it's I think it's getting nigh on that time where I need to like I need to get back into that headset of like wake up start
drawing and
Then I'll be happier then I gotta drive a fucking comic
Yeah, that's been that's gonna be been every morning all right anybody else final points being prolific
In the comments say which is better me a mother or Igma vote who it is. Hey, it's not done yet though
Yeah, but
Who cares it's
Plus yours is the current one everyone's gonna like the current one so the old and busted one. Hey, I'm the original baby
I'm I'm I'm Bulbasaur. I'm Pokemon zero zero one. I'll always be the champ. Hell. Yeah, I'm Bulbasaur
Jesse Jesse's like quiet and then just he hears Bulbasaur. Yeah
Nate just got my vote
To me I really think Min Maphne I really trumps in Govo a to a ditch and me a math
I really math math. Yeah, man. Maphne is just is just is like it's like it's like one of those
Like what I it's like one of those brain activity charts. It's like, you know, man
Maphne is like a little tiny skull in Govo a to a ditch is like a little a little activity
Min Maphne is like, you know, just like fucking like angels shooting out of like a man with a brain light shooting out of his fucking head
Yeah, yeah, and like and like the eye the eye of Raj is like
Sure, the sheer brilliance of maybe never making a nuzlocke
My Christ consciousness is off the chart, right
The thing that really is puts it over the edges the maybe. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, like damn this guy's got it all figured out
Thanks
All right. Well, let's let's go to our questions if we're all set with this or is there we all good
We all set folks. I got one good, baby. Okay. Um, let me see. I'm just scrolling scrolling scrolling. I
Fuck I had a good one. Where the fuck did it go?
Nope. Nope
I gotta find something fast. Okay. Here we go at Moe entrepreneur asks what crimes have you committed?
What crimes?
What are you willing to confess? I dared to
To make a point that Shreela probably doesn't treat women very well, oh, that's true. That's a YouTube crime. That's a YouTube
How dare I?
That's it
No, I think we're all too good boys. We're the goodest boys on the on the whole planet. Um, I've
Crimes just just stop being crimes when we do them. Yeah, I've stolen shit before I'm not even I'm not embarrassed about that anymore
I've shoplifted stuff. I haven't I've been real poor. I
Wasn't poor. I would just eat a donut while walking around and was like, yeah, whatever. This is my yeah now
It's in my body. Yeah
It's part of me ever steal anything from digi when you lived with him
food probably no
only
Well, I
Well, after Victor after Victor moved out after Victor moved out
I ate a bunch of the food that he left behind but like he left it behind so I'm thinking so I'm thinking that's not stealing anymore
Yeah, I gray area
I still I committed once
Well, we've all done that. Yeah
I committed the greatest crime ever once and I'm ashamed of it to this day
I'll never atone for it shit when I was a little kid
When my grandma used to watch the news
I would just come in the room and sit down and turn on the Sega and not even ask her
You monster and I didn't even care
I had no remorse for my for my poor
Saintly grandmother and now she's dead and I can never apologize for this crime that I committed over and over again as a child
I ought to be stoned as his code of Sharia law
She probably thought you were cute, which is my religion now so I can stay on YouTube forever
That's right. She probably was so senile that she thought Sonic the hedgehog was the news
She did have Alzheimer's it was very sad
Here's another question at exile of itch asks who would win him? Yeah, I know that guy
He's a dead mining who would win in a fight Rhonda Rousey or Gal Gadot. I
Know
I mean Gal Gadot has killed there both women so they would both lose
Yeah, I don't know if Rosie has two kills under her belt
That's true. That's true. By the way guys. I just happened to read the other day
This is a little bit of a tangent, but I like apparently it's common
Like the world champion
Should they were working but like that the Australian like
National team like their best national team their female national team
Lost 7-0 to a 15 year old high school boy soccer team like
What is that what the fuck is happening here? These are like the best in the country. I don't know
I just was astounded the best in the country
You got it you got it man
Really like I want that clarified. Is it true?
Like I know munchie drilled it all into our heads and now he
But like I tried looking it up and I couldn't find this information in like there for for real
So I don't know if it was just like scrubbed the only munchie knows the truth
Munchie's the only source for fake news that I trust
Did you guys see that poster somebody made of the Wonder Woman with like the palestinian kid
Amazing way to go dude. I wish I'd remembered your name, but that was sick
I retweeted it, but it's like three weeks ago. So good luck. Yeah. Yeah
Okay, a new question. Here we go at
ZTM zero three two one asks thoughts on YouTube being pro Sharia law. Yeah
You know I approve I approve
Let's
Let's talk about this for a second. So Sharia law guys. It's not so good. It's not so good got some issues with it
Got some got some complaints. No, I've seen a lot
Ultimate way to live. Oh
Now that you've said that now that you've said that Nate the PCB is done for they're out for us
They're gonna we're gonna get flag. We're gonna get a band. Yeah, we're done. We're gonna get fucked and sucked
It's uh, I'm really curious as to whether they actually know it's about Sharia law
And that's why it got taken down. Can we just talk about this for a second? I mean whether it was just like oh
Sharia law is a controversial thing. You can't have that in a title
Destroyed. I mean was it as simple as that or but the thing is I I did a lot of research before I put up the video
And there are like outright hate mongers on the front page of when you search fuck Islam
Just saying the worst things you can imagine millions of views on the front page of search
I make a comedy video that doesn't specifically target any group at all for hate
It just like lists stats and shit and makes jokes about them instantly deleted within a day
Maybe it's just like somebody manually flagged it or something. Well, yeah, but like
Yeah, that has to be it like people in your audience like who subscribes to monkey Jones and then gets so upset about something like that
What if one really I've been getting pretty doing well on the red? Oh, no way? No, I know why the dive of wimpy kid
Yeah, that's probably it. I mean I'm I'm I'm almost positive that it's just like one
Muslim guy on reddit must have seen it and flagged it. Yeah, I bet it was literally Isis
But literally Isis like it was like that guy that I hate the most. Yeah, the worst guy
Yeah, the worst PCP character of all maybe Muslims really like Dyer of a wimpy kid
You really pissed them off
The Sharia law broke the camel's back. That's probably true. Let's just just examine this just for one second more
Okay, so so YouTube's thing is that they're SJW cucks, right? Like that's clearly that's clear where they're moving
So like so that being the case they support or are like totally in defense of
This belief system that says that women should like not drive cars or should be clothed when they're outside at all times
Here's the thing. What is up with that?
This is the most brown brown feminist video I've ever made and I got me banned
Like you're literally arguing to for women to not have to be forced to wear clothes like that cover their entire body
That's your argument beaten and raped by their husbands and all it's it's literally because like brown comes before women
Yeah, it's a progressive skin color. That's how Obama beat Hillary in 2008. Yeah
It's not a joke. I don't accept that Hillary won that election too. She's perfect
How long has she been the president?
She's gonna have 16 years under her belt
How do I even let her run for a third term? That's crazy. I don't know. That's one of the many mysteries
I'm trying to cover. She is in fact the founding mother of America
She wrote the Declaration of Independence. She is the alpha in the Omega. Yeah, you know as much as I hate to to get off
My centrist high horse for a minute. That is definitely some SJW cucky shit on YouTube's part. Yep
It's unacceptable for her once for once
Didn't deserve it
Yeah, I've been saying it couldn't have happened to a more deserving person
Indeed indeed. Well a hashtag justice for monkey. I don't know man. Hopefully that shit works out
We'll say sending in appeals every single day begging the stupid fucking interns who look at this shit to actually watch the video and tell
Me you wear the hate speeches because they couldn't do it. It's impossible
You're fucking intro bit
Monkey Jones, that's me. That's like my favorite. I don't know. That's line is fucking hilarious. You know, it was funny
I really like that. Yeah, I just I really get a kick out of the the bad monkey dancing in public scenes
Those are my favorite parts of all of your videos coming up. I'll survive
I don't even know how the song goes, but it was great
Okay, here's here's another question getting off that I guess at ice killer 159
My old friend the Excalibur Excalibur. Yeah, Excalibur that guy's cool
Would you say that DLC has overall been a good thing to happen to gaming?
No, and no, no not at all. Nope the fact
Well, I mean DLC as like the idea of downloading extra things is no, but the idea of purchasing it. Yes
Remember you can have like like a like. Oh, yeah, we patched we patched something and made it
I mean, I mean, I disagree with that. It's cool that we're no longer stuck in the days
We're like you have to buy like Sonic the like extra fucking cartridge to like plug your Sonic 3 and 2 so you can play as
Knuckles or whatever like it's cool that we've been unshackled from that
But also it sucks and it's not it's abused and I mean
I guess I guess I like the idea of DLC in principle
But I know that like companies do it in a shitty way that like just fucks their consumers things like Artorius of the
Abyss are like good examples of DLC that do everything right or like the Bloodborne DLC and shit
But like like the the idea of like electronic media and you know that you can just download everything and then endlessly
Put out patches everyone should check out a little video by by an old man called Endless Jess
Who who I forget the name? It was it was in the city, right?
City one. Oh, yeah, that's my second favorite guy next to furnace room. Yeah, he's pretty good
They're both good that video just really lays bare like the the agony that we all have to go through of how like
Video games will like be updating for a thousand years and like it was so great to just buy a fucking game
You put it in your thing and then you're playing it now and all the like I'm expanding from DLC
Just like electronic gaming like downloadable content and all that shit like it's made to developers
Super fucking lazy and like now they just don't give a fuck about like delivering like a complete package day one
Now they're like, oh, we'll just patch it man
Who gives a fuck like right now they are continually like tweaking Final Fantasy 15 to make it like the real game
And oh what we rejoice in like ten years when we've got like oh, we did it
We've got the real Final Fantasy 15
Meanwhile, I buy that shit day one and I punished for it because I care too much
About you know playing the game when it comes out the people who invest the most are the people who are punished the harshest
You get the worst experience. I don't like that structure people should be rewarded for supporting your fucking product instead of punished for it
I hate that shit. I mean I
Thinking about like the Dark Souls DLC. I bought
The Dark Souls one the prepared to die edition which had the DLC in it
So I mean I like the DLC
But if I didn't like it and I bought it separately
I would feel constantly bad that I had purchased that extra add-on when I didn't need to and with every other Dark Souls game
It's like now that I purchased this DLC. I better enjoy it
Whereas if it was just part of the game like I could just think of it as part of the game like I don't really like that level
I won't play that one. Mm-hmm, and it's I don't like that it it makes me think that at all
I don't like thinking about it
I don't want to be naive either because like I know game development costs are just shooting through the roof and like DLC is one
Way of like them them like you know compensating for that
But like all the problems I've said still stand and like DLC should never like
I don't know. Well, that's you shouldn't rely on it
That's the problem because because development costs are skyrocketing, but it's not like games are getting better
Right, you know like it's not like there's any real return on that investment
It's like that's that's the problem that should I have fixed
I have a not not DLC used as like a weird fucking patch to take to cover
DLC should only stand for dick licking contest with fine juggalette bitches
I
Agreed agreed. I actually have like a video about this that will not be out as we're recording
But we'll be out by the time people are watching this. Oh hell. Yeah, it's a rant about realism and
Video game. I think a lot of it comes from like the normie influx is gaming has hit the mainstream and people want like people don't
Actually get what's good about video games. They just want the shitty cinematic experience like they want to play
They're only picking up they're only picking up on the tangible details. Yeah. Oh my god
I just remembered I just remembered that last night last night
I had a bunch of shitty dreams and one of them was a terrible nightmare about me playing
I don't know. I think it was uncharted. I've never played uncharted
But I was playing what my mind imagines uncharted to be and I was just like oh my god the game plays itself
I'm not
Really
Who else had shitty dreams who's that Martin Luther King jr. Oh
Yeah, but he had one good dream that was good, you know, it's just the one dream was pretty nice
There was I was just gonna say his dream was Hillary's nightmare
Exactly there's this one. There's this one chart that gets passed around on V a lot
That's that's very misogynistic and it's very problematic and it's it's like a picture of like Mario
With just like a list of like years and then like what women thought of video games at this time in history
And it starts at like
1995 and it's like there for nerds and you're gay if you play them and it let just like go
That's that repeated like ten times until you hit like 2000
It's like oh what are those guys doing over there and then like 2001
Oh, maybe I can get it on this and it just shows it like slowly like creeping in and like like changing
And then the last ones are like we games are for us and if you can accept that you need to get the fuck out of here
Yeah, and um, you know, I don't actually feel that that's like a super accurate for all women or anything
But it reflects like the normie influx of video games guys. I had a dream
That I was at a place with my dad
And there was another dad with his littler kid than me
He was a little kid and that dad sent the littler kid to annoy my dad my dad turned around and he beat the shit out
Is that for doing that he didn't beat the shit out of the kid the kid did nothing wrong
Yeah, and I felt so proud and I then I woke up and I was like yeah, that young child's name was Trayvon Martin
He didn't do nothing. He didn't do nothing everybody
All right, I know
Doesn't
What the fuck are we okay the question let's get out of question here here's a simple question at Siamid
Simply says bug fuck
Depends definitely well, that's that's what we need to you know the bug wars are going on
But like we need we need to look forward to a better future where we can we get we and the bugs can love one another instead
You know, uh-huh. So yeah, so yes enthusiastic. Yes to bug fuck
There's a very me me Twitter that has been blowing up recently called spike the beetle and it's this
Oh, yeah, I'm speedal with the big the pinchers and they put like a pen in his hand and they let him paint
Oh, I saw that yeah, you know, I look at that beetle and I think this guy fucks this bug
I
Just want to give all the girls love and I want to give an unequivocal yes to this question because of Hornet from Hollow Knight
Who is the sexiest bug? I've ever seen and I love her and she's great and she's super cute. I love her dress
She's a fucking fish bitch fuck that slut. Yeah, if if a bug is a woman then of course
Who beat I still want to be gay with a man bug
Yeah, that would be unacceptable, but I like it like an armoured penis or whatever they would have
Armoured penis that sounds that sounds like a Mega Man X boss
Let's okay, let's let's end this thing. Here's one more question
Yeah, at 5 8 Keegan asks do you think YouTube has been oversaturated with reviews?
Delete all the channel
The problem is there's too many that are not good and they make I mean I would imagine they would make people think that what I make is
I think there's too many here. I think there's too many period even the good ones
Yeah, I agree. I agree. They need to all go away. So you know what everyone everyone look up a video on YouTube
called
Bill Hicks Hitler had the right idea
He just he absolutely loses it on a heckler and starts screaming about please God wipe these scum from the earth and like
It's it's like it's not even funny like he's clearly
Audience feels really awkward about it because he's really screaming at this guy like please God kill everyone
Hitler had the red idea. He was just an underachiever
That's why I feel about reviews and analysis videos on YouTube. I feel like Bill Hicks
screaming kill them all
Agreed. It's it's really just that
There's you know, there are good things to review
But I'd rather people make more good things to review than to review the good things
I mean
I only care does that because reviewing good things is easy and everyone does it and I do it and I feel stupid
I'm basically totally uninterested and people talking about specific peeps pieces of media outside of the fact of them like making a
larger point about like I don't know something that is
Actionable or you know like is good and smart in some way. I don't know. I don't know
You know what? They're entertaining if they're entertaining or they're a cool person
Yeah, then it will be good. It's it's about it's like ideally
It's about the person doing like making the review and like you like you watching it for their for their personality or whatever
And just like you like and the game itself or the movie itself is just like a sort of like prompt to get them on a
Thing it's like this movie or this game is like smart and good
And they're just like using that to attach themselves to it and make them seem good. Yeah, you know what?
You know, it's not even reviews and analysis. It's the problem. It's it's just please for the love of God be funny
Everyone. Yeah, isn't funny. Just die
I couldn't agree more
And with that I suppose we're done everybody
Thanks for listening
We will see next a remember to send more questions go to the you know at TP crass natives use hashtag ask PCP
There was the only questions we answer
So if you're not using that we're not answering your fucking question
So thanks for listening everybody and we will edge to the pledge to the patreon in here
The bonus episode with Florian talking about our favorite dogs. That's right
Which is now now, but should be up soon Ben getting on that
It's uploaded it's up the one that I but not okay, whatever. Yeah one that I ruined with road rovers at the end
We were doing so good
No, that was great. It's perfect everybody's to 10 out 10 thing go listen to it
May I pledge $5 to us?
patreon.com slash the pro crass natives give us your money
Hashtag justice for mumke
Hashtag just for mumke do what you can people do click that link. It's gonna be the description
You can do whatever you can be polite be productive be a cool guy. Thanks for this everybody and we will see you next time
My dick I'm jerking myself I'm sucking I am an asshole I am a stupid
I've got a deadline don't want to do it