Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm the best guy ever, and we've got The Boys, we've got Tom Oliver.
I am here to be on this podcast, but my audience is such a shit, so I'm going to listen to
like 60% or 70% of this podcast, so it's going to be fun.
I'm doing podcasts on hard mode today, I'm on New Game Plus, and I have all my extra
buffs, but I also have new challenges I've never faced before, it's going to be an interesting
experience.
Well that's great to hear, we've got Hippocrit here.
I think Pokemon Let's Go might literally be my favorite Pokemon game, and I haven't
played it yet.
I'm what going to fucking kill you?
I played it, well okay.
Glad someone else besides me enjoys it.
Ben Saint is angry.
What?
It's, shut up!
There he goes.
Uh, an Endless Jess.
It's me, it's me, it's Endlet G, I'm on the web because I am not free.
Help me out if you are so kind.
Patreon, come feed the swine.
Collab with Lady Gaga.
I can't resist a catchy jingle.
Oh my god, it's another episode of the Procrastinators podcast, and here we are today to talk about
it.
Who are you?
Did you introduce yourself?
What?
Well, I said my name, I suppose that's enough.
My reputation precedes me.
That's true.
You know, a bunch of know him well, finally back from the gates of hell, that's me.
I have a thing to kick start this conversation, it's not about Pokemon, let's go, it is in
November.
If only you had a thing to kick start my car, wait, I was thinking, what's that thing that
you have a crowdfunding?
Oh good, you are very good.
Crowdfunding.
It's 2018.
I've been a kickstand, like I have a motorcycle, it falls over.
No, no, no, you failed, you fell flat on your face with that one.
There are so many ways you could have gone with it, and you chose the only one that
failed.
All right, in November, for no reason, I went on a trip to two cities in Europe, and here's
my story about it.
I kind of wanted Munchie to be here, because I knew he would have things to say, such as,
oh good, so I wanted to hear him say those things.
Wow.
Yeah, but yeah, there's basically, it was the first time I had traveled alone to another
country for no particular reason, like I've traveled alone before to BronyCon.
For no good reason.
For no good reason, well it was a good reason, because I have reasons, but usually there's
like somebody there waiting to meet me, or like it's Radcon, so there's lots of things
I don't have to worry about, like I can't drive in America at all, so like I don't have
to worry about driving around when I go to Radcon and various other things.
And it was so stressful, like leading up to going, because it's like, it's a different
kind of feeling where if I just decide to call it off, nobody would be mad necessarily
Nobody is relying on me to be somewhere for something, I can just not go if I want to,
and that is like really, it tugged on me, because like I'm scared of traveling, I don't
like it, it makes me wet my pants, the idea that I might leave my toothbrush on the plane
or something strange, and I'm like, oh no, my passport, I dropped down the drain and
I can't speak to the locals to ask them to help me get it out, because they don't understand
me, like various things like that, and I was like, oh no, everything's gonna go wrong and
I'm gonna be stranded, and I could have called it off, but I ended up going and it was cool.
So it would have been easier if you had some kind of obligation, it would have been easier
if there were someone that you had promised this to, or something you had to do, but because
it was just a thing you wanted to do, and yet the fact that it was only your want to do it
and nothing else made you like, I could give you anxiety, like I don't have to do this,
maybe I shouldn't do this, I totally relate to that, that's why nobody follows their dreams
ever, and nobody should. Well, I ended up doing it, and it was very anxious anxiety
ridden in the first bit, but the reason I wanted to do it was various reasons, one to see a bit
of Europe before it gets locked off from Brexit, and we get like a big old fence, a big old wall
around the entire coast of the UK, we can't leave, also to play Pokemon Go, haha, we don't get the
wall, but you guys do, very offended. I was going to get like a Spanish Mr. Mime, and a German
Mr. Mime, I called it. Hadrian's Wall? Hadrian's Wall, that's a Roman thing. It's like two feet
high, isn't that the wall that sort of goes across like the middle of England? It was supposed to
keep the Scots out, I think, as the Romans built it, and it was kind of small and there's only a
little bit left, it's tiny. Hadrian's Wall makes me giggle. I'm sorry, I interrupted. No, no, it's fine,
it's cool. I expect it, and I feel bad when I don't get interrupted, it makes me uncomfortable.
Yeah, good. So I got like, haha, cool Pokemon, I got some fucking, some exclusive Mr. Mime,
some like, some bourgeoisie, like, special Mr. Mime, I got Senor Mime, and I got Hair Mime,
and they're gonna be like, you know, Monchi was saying, oh, I'm gonna go, you know, give all my
Italian Mr. Mimes over, and then Hippo's not gonna have any spending power in America, and like,
no, I've got special, I'm gonna go to France as well, I'm gonna get a legit like French Mr. Mime
as well, bitch, I'm gonna have all the Pokemon. So like, that was one of the reasons I went,
and then also, just to be more self-reliant and to be more independent, the ability to like,
going to another country is fucking terrifying, where they don't speak the language specifically,
and it's like, if you don't do anything, you're gonna die because you need to eat, so you got to
do stuff every day. A lot of people, a lot of people speak English though, in all like,
major metropolitan areas of the world. Well, alright, here's the thing, in Hamburg, yes,
because Germans don't have, they don't have another nation that speaks German, the German is just
their thing, so like, they understand that if they want to speak to anyone else, they'd better
speak English, because that's pretty popular, but in Spain, nobody speaks English, everybody is like,
like, they don't even have like a phrase to say, do you speak English? Like, they don't know how to
say that, they just keep speaking Spanish to me, and I'm like, I, I point, and then they're like,
they point, and they say something, and I'm like, I don't know whether you were saying yes or no,
or, it's scary, Madrid was scary, I went to Madrid, but it's also cool. I have anxiety about doing
anything, and travel is a big thing that takes a lot of time, so if it's, if I have to do some of it,
it's coming up, I'm like, what a commitment I have to make, oh god, but I'm not afraid of like,
I'm not afraid of like, losing anything, or, I don't know, I've, I've found that like, if you have
money, if you have money, nothing can go wrong, if you have, I was gonna say, the only thing I was
afraid of of losing when I was in Japan was my like, stack of, what, like, traveler's checks or
whatever, that like, was my money, if you, if you have like, if you have like, let's say $1,000 in
like, liquid assets that are available to you, nothing can hurt you, and everything, pretty much
invincible. I had a similar epiphany, I realized that the true meaning of life, the ultimate secret
to having a life that isn't like, too much of a disaster, is just have $10,000 at all times, no
matter how much money you make, make sure that you always have a safety net of $10,000, and that is
your, if anything goes wrong, money, and yeah, that's, that's it, that's all you need. I could not be
more with you, I'd pretty much, that's exactly how I think, yeah, 100%. My number is 500,
might actually, because that's how the whole thing about like, because that's about how much I need to
live another month. I was, I was saving up like, my whole thing about like, when I'll go, you, for
full time YouTube was like, I was thinking, I put a number at 20 grand, when I had 20 grand, at that
point, I'm willing to like, you know, take the chance and do stuff. And I technically have that now,
but it's like tax stuff. And I'm not saying like, everybody has $10,000 lying around, I'm saying
that's the goal that you need to get to, you're fine. Like, I recently like, why will these idiots not
have $10,000? This year, I accomplished my lifelong dream of like, seeing that number in my bank account
10,000. It was during, it took me literally 29 years. So I'm not saying it's easy, but I had 10k in the
bank. I had the however many digits that is, I'm so poor, I don't even know how many digits are in
10,000. Five digits. Yeah, and seeing that, I bought a car, so I don't have it anymore. But yeah, it
was a, it was good. And so now I know that that's what I was good. That's a great goal. Everybody
should have a big safety net. And I mean, everybody should, when they're young, be thinking about
like, okay, well, when I retire, I'm not going to be able to work. So I got to like, save up money for
that too. Those like the short term need to be able to survive. And the long term one, people keep
those in mind, you're in good shape.
It's interesting, because like, in the anxiety I was having like, day to day, a moment to moment,
wasn't necessarily that I would run out of money, because I had like, the reason I went to these
specific places, like one after the other was because I got really cheap flights, one wave from
London to Hamburg, Hamburg to Madrid and Madrid back to London. And I got Airbnb. So like, I knew
that I had money in the bank to spend on lots of things. If I needed to, it was just like, doing the
social stuff, like going into a place and saying, you know, good morning, or, you know, and, and, and,
and, you know, being able to do the, the transaction with someone.
And then dealing with the vicious blows that rain down as you culturally appropriated their language by
attempting to speak it to them.
Ultimately.
Yeah.
How dare you.
You guys ever hear about that? Some people get, they don't like the whole learning of their languages. I
know it's a minority, but wait, wait, wait, wait, that made me.
Who what?
Yeah, I've heard, you know, I'm sure these are fringe people, but I have heard the argument that
learning languages other than your native one is a form of cultural appropriation that should, should
do it.
It's, no, it's funny because like fringe weirdos.
Yeah, you know, it is cultural appropriation, but also appropriation is not a bad thing and never
has been.
So yeah, agreed.
More or less.
Yeah.
Oh, I hate one thing on this whole anxiety thing. You know what this reminds me of a lot? The thing
that I relate most to when I went to Japan, I definitely had this anxiety.
The thing that comes to mind for me with this conversation about being nervous and doing
stuff is specifically because like you just, you went there and like you were saying, you
wouldn't know like dates to meet.
You had no like people that you needed to do stuff for.
There was nothing you just, you went because you wanted to go.
And that reminds me of when I would go out to the club and go talk to girls because that is a purely
selfish act.
And it was in those moments of being in my mind, I knew this 100% purely selfishly wanting to meet
people and, you know, create friendships or get sex or whatever.
The anxiety was at my peak.
Because if they say, if they were to say the simple words, why are you talking to me?
The answer is, Oh God, I have no just, there's no justice on my side.
It's pure what I want to be doing.
And what a, what a sin that is.
What a sin that is.
What a sin that is to talk to, to be a social animal and do the normal thing.
Yeah.
Yep.
Those are, I remember those.
I have no, I have no, hey, galley and argument on my side and no utilitarian.
Well, I guess it reproduced.
Spread my ideas and jeans.
Oh, say that.
I like that.
Say that.
I should have said that.
I'm looking to spread my jeans.
I'm just trying to reproduce.
Spread my jeans, you know, gain, gain social capital, you know,
that I should understand.
Yeah, there was, there was a peak of this anxiety on the first day in Hamburg.
Um, well, the first day I got there was like at night, so I went straight to bed
and, uh, I woke up the next day and I was like, okay, how to find breakfast.
I Googled breakfast nearby and I found a place and it was okay.
It was like, I was doing all right.
But then it became, uh, you know, I was, I went into town and I was like, okay.
Google and type, how to find breakfast.
How to find breakfast.
Well, Google maps has a thing where like you click explore and it's like restaurants,
cafes and it's like, okay, I can do that.
I can do this.
This is easy.
So I went into town to just look around and take some pictures and all that.
And then I was like hungry.
It was lunchtime.
It's time to go find a place to eat lunch.
And I was in the center of town.
So there's a lot of big restaurants.
I was like, I don't really want to spend a lot of money.
Right now, I just want to find like something to keep me going for the moment.
And then I'll have a big dinner later.
But I spent a lot of the time just walking around, looking nearby the shops and the
restaurants and the, you know, the hot dog stands and being like, uh, there's not in
English.
I don't know what to do.
I go up to them and then they, I don't know what to say to them.
So I didn't go up to anyone.
I walked around for a really long time and then I saw a McDonald's and I was like,
okay.
Thank God.
I mean, first of all, no, I'm not going to go into the McDonald's as stupid.
I flew all the way here.
I'm going to have some, some fucking German Currywurst.
I'm going to have some, some legit Hamburg food, but I was, I was, I was dying.
I was, I was anxiety-ridden and I had like the, the lowest moment in my life.
I went into that, that McDonald's and I got fucking 10 chicken McNuggets.
Good old American.
On the touch screen.
Yes.
I don't even have to talk to anyone.
I didn't, I didn't have to talk to anyone.
I knew there'd be a touch screen in there.
I touched the screen.
I said, I got the thing and I just ate them and I felt like a fucking fool.
I felt like the biggest Rube in the fucking world.
I feel you dog.
Munchy would be flipping out right now.
That's why I wanted Munchy to hear.
And it's like, all right, that kept me going for like an hour because it's fucking
McDonald's and it's terrible.
Um, so like, I, I went home, uh, to the Airbnb and I was sitting in, in the
bed and it was a terrible room.
It was like three.
I was going to ask about that.
Was it just like a room in a house?
I mean, it, it served its purpose.
It was a roof over my head.
So it's fine, but like, um, it wasn't nice to relax in, uh, there was this, it was
a shared room.
There was three bunk beds and a TV and there was this fat girl, a German girl
who was like, every single time I came into that room, she was laying on one of
the bunk beds, the lower part on her phone, watching like really trashy German TV.
I didn't see her leave once.
I don't know what she was doing there and her boyfriend would come every so often
and sit next to her or something.
They would just both be on their phones and they're terrible German TV and they
never turned the TV off even until like one AM.
So I was like, I don't know what to do.
Do I beat the shit out of them and grab the remote and turn it off?
Or do I just, that was my first instinct as well.
Or do I just, uh, sit here with my headphones in, but with no music playing
so I could maybe sleep.
Since there is no objective good or bad, how could I ask them to turn off this TV?
That's a subjective value being able to sleep.
Well, the trouble is that nobody could beat up a German because they all have
tanks in their garage.
In this case, the girlfriend is the tank.
Got him.
So wait, I was, so I was in, I came after the McDonald's.
I was like, okay, that was a kind of terrible first day, but it wasn't even late.
It was like four PM.
And I was like, I'm hungry, obviously, and I'm going to need dinner.
I don't know what to do.
And I was just thinking, maybe I could sleep through like the rest of the evening
and through to the next day and then figure it out again.
Yeah.
And I was sitting there for like 20 minutes thinking, no, this is stupid.
I can't do this.
Oh, but I'm doing it.
Oh, I'm doing it.
I'm the worst guy of all time.
I'm the worst at traveling.
I can't do anything.
That was me, my first couple of days in fucking in Tokyo.
And eventually I figured out I could go to the convenience store nearby.
But like, I didn't know where it was the first couple of days.
So I sat there shivering, sad.
It felt very like very much like that.
I was like, this is the worst moment in my entire life.
And it's all my fault and there's no one to help me.
Oh, and I don't even have Twitter on my phone because I got rid of it.
And I can't scream on social media.
Oh, no, I'm sad about stuff.
And so, but I did the same thing with Google.
I Googled restaurants and I just picked one that was nearby.
And I said, I'll just go.
I'll just go.
I got my coat.
It was fucking really cold.
So that's why I didn't really want to go out.
And I went to this place and thankfully the lady understood that, you know, I just
said, I know, don't speak German.
She's like, oh, English.
I was like, yeah.
And then she's like, okay, uh, to have a seat.
And then I ordered a food and I had a beer and it was like this sour pork and it was
very German and it was a very German restaurant.
I had like authentic German food and it was really filling and it was fucking great.
And I, I really enjoyed my time and I like it.
And it was great.
I felt, I felt so good that the fact that I got over this stupid hang up of like not
being able to speak to Germans because it's like trying to speak to anyone, but also you
have to look like an idiot when you say, I don't know what you're saying initially.
Um, and I, I felt great.
I felt great after that.
And for the rest of the trip, I was able to get lunch and dinner without really any
problem.
And that's, that's my arc for that, that story.
Isn't it weird that in Germany, they, they, they have curry versed and even though curry
is like an Indian thing, but curry versed is a German thing.
I don't know.
I think it was strange.
It's just spicy.
It's cultural appropriation.
Yeah.
It wasn't curry versed over there.
I probably just, I went to one of that, those hawked stands where they were selling curry
versed in a little plastic paper plate and I had it and I was like, this isn't really
spicy and it's not very tasty either.
I don't get it.
I don't get curry versed.
But that's probably a bad example of curry versed.
Uh, but yeah, I got curry versed one time and it was like, I got it at like a street cart
and they served to me in like a paper and like a paper fucking, you know, one of those
like paper cardboard foldup things that you might get a serving of street French fries
in, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, it was fun.
Um, what the fuck's going on with the call?
Okay.
All right.
Let's, let's everybody's issue is flagging apparently.
I'm glad it's not just me.
Yeah.
Well, it's not, it's, it's you and Tom.
I, yeah, it does seem to primarily be a Jesse and Tom, because I don't think Ben
Gibb and I are having it, but nonetheless, that's, that's not good.
That's not good.
Uh, hmm.
Well, that, that's my story.
I went to a place.
I had an arc on the first day and then it was all right from then.
Uh, hooray.
Fantastic.
Well, what about, what about Spain though?
We didn't hear anything about Spain.
Oh, well, I went to Spain.
Basically, the gist is that nobody or pain here's, here's an interesting, uh,
parallel to like the first day in Spain.
So like I got to Madrid and Airbnb, very cheap, uh, in a very poor part of like the
suburbs, uh, like, uh, like a really cheap, um, council house estate sort of thing.
And I was just living in a room with a family and the family was nice and they
had a dog and the dog was scared of me, but he was a good dog.
Um, and I was like, okay, I got a dog, uh, a big fluffy one with big ears, sick,
a big fluffy boy.
Um, so I was in that room.
I was like, okay, it's lunchtime.
I'm hungry and the metro is like really long from the airport.
And I'm really exhausted and tired.
I'm, I can't go on the metro again to get into the center of Madrid to have
lunch.
I'll just see what's in the local area at this point.
I didn't know Spanish people don't speak English.
So I was assuming they would know a little bit.
I go into this bar, um, and there's some guys just at the front, uh,
watching the football going on.
And, uh, I go up to the guy and I say, uh, do you speak English?
And he says, well, I don't know what he says.
He said something in Spanish.
I didn't understand it.
He says, uh, nobody said senor.
Nobody seems to say senor in Madrid.
I guess that's just not a thing.
I guess, I guess that's kind of a fancy thing.
Like, oh, yes, um, madams, uh, it might be more of a Mexican Spanish thing.
Maybe.
Yeah, there's differences there.
So, uh, I was in this, this, this bar.
There's just like three sort of oldish guys who seem to be regulars looking at me.
And then the guy behind the bar and he's like, so what, what are you, you know,
he's saying in Spanish, what do you want?
Do you, uh, like he's trying to understand what I want.
And I don't know how to, to respond.
And I find a menu and I like, uh, I'm looking at it.
And at some point he just gets frustrated with me.
Like he knows food.
So it's like, he, he does like the emotion of like, he puts his fingers and thumb
together and he puts that near his mouth.
It's like, do you want to eat?
Do you want to eat?
And I'm like, I nodded my head and he's like, okay, fine.
It gives me some tapas.
And he says, go sit down with this.
I'm like, oh, yeah.
So, so, so let me get this straight.
You're sitting in a restaurant with a menu, but you can't read the menu.
No, no, no.
I wasn't sitting down yet.
It was like, I just walked into this restaurant and there's a bar in the front
and there was a restaurant in the back.
And I, I was talking to this, I was trying to talk to this guy.
He gives you like a, he gives you like an appetizer tray or something.
Like the equivalent of like a basket of bread or some shit.
Well, yeah.
I mean, it's tapas.
So it's like rice and I never had tapas.
I don't know what that is exactly.
It's, it's sort of like a small, it's like an appetizer for a drink.
Uh, you know, the sort of thing you eat while you're drinking.
So a little nice, little, uh, tasty thing.
And so he gave me that in a tiny little bit.
And I was like, okay, well, I'll eat this.
And then I sit down as a menu and I pointed a thing that seems to be
like potatoes with something on it.
And I'm like, I'll have that.
And he's like, okay.
And he's laughing at certain points.
I'm thinking, okay, I look like a fucking idiot.
These guys, they're just watching the game and it's complete.
Like this foreigner comes into this small, like residential area
that no English tourist would ever go.
And there's an English guy in here, just like being an idiot.
I was like, hey, this motherfucker, you're saying in Spanish,
making fun of me probably.
And I was like, yeah, you know what, it was so ridiculous
that I didn't actually care.
I didn't actually feel bad about it because it probably is really funny.
So like I had the food.
Did it feel like you were just sort of breaking all the rules of society
and therefore had transcended them?
Yeah, like it was so ridiculous a situation to me that I'd never been
in such an embarrassing moment.
There was like, there's nothing that could go wrong.
Like they in that moment, you cease to care.
Yeah.
And it was like a big difference to like, oh no, I can't possibly ask
somebody who definitely does speak English for a meal.
But I can go into now, I can go into Madrid, into a place where nobody
speaks Spanish at all and figure out how to get something in me.
And I was just like, yeah, just sitting there.
I was watching the game with them.
It was England versus Ecuador.
And then England lost, haha.
Haha, just like you in this social interaction.
Yeah, I was just like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I had another beer and it was good.
And then I went back and it was, it was a cool moment.
I figured out that I'm okay in the real world.
I can, I can survive it.
That was a very valuable thing to learn.
How was the potato shit?
It was potatoes alioli, which is I think like garlic cream sauce.
So it's just a bunch of potatoes with garlic cream sauce.
And alioli is like a garlic mayonnaise.
Oh yeah, that was what it was, garlic mayonnaise.
And yeah, it was just a big thing of potatoes.
And I was like, you know, that'll do.
That that's just that's filling.
Oh yeah, carbohydrates.
OK, and a happy, happy ending.
How long were you in Spain for?
I was in Spain for one day less than I was in Germany.
They'll have two days in two full days.
And then one day to get to the airport and leave.
Hey, you mentioned you mentioned a dog.
This allows me to segue into how much I hate dogs.
I hate pets. I hate animals.
I hate in the same way that I hate food
because pets are food just at a different stage of the life cycle.
They're all equally boring.
They're all equally topics for rubes to discuss.
You go, you go like your food thing.
Yeah, it is.
It is the exact same thing as my food thing.
So I'm going to go on the exact same tangent.
Like, oh, you show up, you show up to a place
and there's people there and you go, oh, hey, what kind of food do you like to eat?
Oh, you like you like fried chicken.
Well, I like roasted chicken.
Oh, what kind of what kind of you know what I kind of ice cream do you like?
Oh, you like chocolate with I like strawberry.
Oh, what kind of dog do you like?
Oh, you like fucking two hours with I like great days.
And then this is what people are like.
This is human society.
This is what leaving my house is like.
And I don't ever want to do it again.
I agree that those things like talking about what sort of stuff you like is boring.
And also, I don't know what the difference between dog breeds
are and why you would ever care about them.
It's just like, oh, it's fluffy.
That's all you need to know in my opinion.
Like, oh, it's a it's a half-breed Scottish bog
panel, like what does that mean?
OK, what's the what's the fucking point of that conversation?
Right? What's the fucking point of you?
It's small talk to break the ice.
We all know it's worthless and pointless.
It doesn't mean anything.
But yeah, it's just there to be filler.
I'll break your eyes with this ice.
Do I? Yeah, sure.
It's filler. I do.
I do agree that dogs are worthless creatures
and I don't respect them and nobody.
I don't stand by that.
I mean, I like dogs are like dogs on an individual basis.
Like, I've known some dogs who rise above the pitfalls of their species,
but very few.
Like, I've known like one or two dogs that were like quiet and friendly
and, you know, shut the fuck up and didn't shit.
But only, you know, but that's most of they just fucking yappy,
barky, fucking aggressive, stupid dogs are so fucking aggressive.
They have it's they have their moral,
their moral priorities are just ordered differently from ours,
which they have none.
Dogs have no more.
Yeah, that's not true.
When think when think no, no, no, listen, listen,
since good and evil are purely subjective.
Yeah, when something has different moral priorities than you,
it is evil to you.
It morally opposes.
I mean, that's your fundamental worldview,
making dogs object all nonhuman creatures and most humans objectively evil.
You know what the problem is with that?
That makes people in opposite political sides are correct that the other side is evil.
Both sides are correct about that.
The why is that a problem?
Well, I'd say that it causes some cause some commotion out in that ocean.
If you know what I'm saying, let me let me.
So I have a dog, Lord Sashomaru, and he's he's pretty good.
So the worst thing about Sashomaru, by far,
is that he's very emotionally needy and he hates to be alone.
And so when you're home with him, it's fine.
The problem is when no one's home with him,
because literally almost every time he will shit when we're when people are gone
because he's trying to punish us for abandoning him.
And this is confirmed because like I'll go out for 20 minutes to drop like Michelle
off at work or something in that way.
Does that work?
He takes a shit.
If people abandon me, can I shit and I'll learn not to?
It makes me so unbelievably angry.
Yeah, if it were if Sash were a human,
I would tell him to get the fuck out and don't ever talk to me again.
I mean, so would I.
But yeah, he is not capable of moral consideration.
So I have to just, you know, accept that he deserves.
Does he deserve leeway for that fact?
Well, I don't know.
Does that earn him more goodwill?
People with the minds of children deserve to be destroyed because they can't,
you know, like maintain themselves.
I wouldn't destroy them.
But I would turn them out on the street and shut the door and let them freeze to death.
He's my responsibility, but I was prepared to accept this life
when I when I, you know, took this burden on.
And he's great in every other way, seriously.
But in this one way.
And so yesterday, so we started when we leave, we have to put him in his box.
Because he's going to shit.
So he might as well do it in his box on some paper.
So yesterday I do this.
I'm out for 20 minutes, dropping off somebody.
He's alone for only that small window of time.
When I come back, he has shit in his box and smeared it around with his pause
on like the floor of his box.
And I have to like, so this is deliberate.
I guess this is definitely deliberate, definitely.
That's the worst.
That's the worst possible thing.
Because like, yes, my dog, my dog.
The family dog that we have now.
He's learned to ask to go outside to shit.
So he's good.
He's a good boy.
We're pretty good about that, but it's not about the shitting.
It's about it's about it's about the.
Yeah, like if you leave him alone for too long, if parents are watching TV
in the other room, he doesn't poop when we're around, he's good.
He will he will bark.
He will bark a little bit, but he's kind of quiet generally.
So like, I don't mind him so much.
The only thing, the only thing I kind of feel bad about is like
taking on my own walks.
And when I throw the ball, he just doesn't bring it back.
And he wants me to go bring it so that I can throw it for him again.
Yeah, yeah.
But like, in terms of like dog problems, I don't really have that many.
It's it's he's quite a good boy.
But that's also because my parents do a lot of the dog walking for for me.
Right.
So like, I'm not wholly responsible.
If I had to do the dog walking every day, morning and evening,
I would probably throw him in the into space.
Sometimes, you know, taking him for a session for a walk, whatever, is like a
fine, you know, like deviations like, you know, I could use a break.
I'll take five minutes.
But sometimes I'm in the depths of working and I do not want to be distracted.
I am focused on my task and leaving it.
And in those moments, especially when I know he hasn't pooped for a while,
I take him on, he will not poop.
And it's been like 10 minutes or something.
That's when the rage that I do experience in any other capacity in my life
got that dog rage.
Yeah, I get dog rage in a big way in those situations specifically.
And I'm like, Cecil, you you've got 30 seconds.
You need to poop right now or or you or you will never know what's going to
happen if you poop inside later after I've given you all this opportunity.
It's just, you know, he's a terrorist and he can't be negotiated with, frankly.
It's really infuriating and revolting just the amount of shit
that dogs get away with that other pets don't, like the amount of aggression
that people let their dogs get away.
Yeah, like no other pet in this world, if your cat attacked people,
you would like throw it against a wall or like get rid of it.
But like, I know people that are I know people that are totally fine
with their cat just attacking visitors.
I mean, like acceptable and they and they and they blame the visitors.
If like, if every time they can die, if every time you walked by someone's
house, like their other pets started making noise and yelling at you,
then they wouldn't want those pets anymore.
But for some reason, dogs are allowed to do it.
I hate barking.
If you have a dog and you allow it to bark, I want to shoot you in the fucking
head in front of your dog and give it to the bark about.
It's like, like Beanie, Nate, Beanie, who would just go nuts,
go into an insane, like some screaming rage.
Like every no, every time dad came home.
Oh, yeah, which was every day, multiple times a day.
And it's like, are you fucking kidding me?
Yeah, are you fucking kidding me?
I have friends who like, I don't want to go to their house just because
when you walk in the door, there's that like five seconds of the dog
freaking out and coming at you.
You know, that's just the person making a choice.
They care about this dog more than the impacts to lifestyle that I guess they're
going to suffer. Is the dog like vicious?
Or is it just like really excited?
No, it's just, well, like it doesn't, it's too stupid to recognize me right away.
So it needs like a moment to understand that I'm not a guy you bark at.
But like you walk in the door and like, even if it's just like 10 seconds
of a dog freaking out, it's too much for one lifetime.
That does suck.
I hate it makes me not want to go to that person's house ever.
Plus, I think like, oh, well, what the dogs are knowing now?
What's it going to be like later?
If I'm just like, being here, is it going to start freaking out?
Am I going to be uncomfortable?
It's going to be like, they're so stupid because it's like, even if it's a dog
that I know and like, like five minutes from now, I'm going to be like petting
you and it's fine.
Like you've seen me before, you know who the fuck I am.
Why are you barking?
Why are you doing it?
You stupid fucking animal, you know who I am.
Why are you making that noise?
I hear that's like beans.
Like every like, like how like beans, you've been living in this house for what?
Like a thousand years now and every day, the same person has walked through the door.
And how could you not have learned that this is a normal occurrence that is not
cause for alarm?
Man, I'm remembering that now.
Thank God Sessho is not like that.
He is quiet.
He's just fine.
That's that's the one that's beans is version of shitting out of loneliness.
Yeah, you know, it's such bullshit that all my life, people told
me and tried to indoctrinate me to the idea that like the stegosaurus had a
tiny little walnut brain.
I know that dogs have a smaller brain than a fucking stegosaurus.
I don't believe that the stegosaurus would ever attack me just for coming in my
friend's house.
Probably I got a friend's house.
If he had a stegosaurus a lot more, you can ride that guy.
It'd be awesome.
I mean, it wouldn't be comfortable because stegosaurus has those things on his
back, the place.
I mean, maybe maybe you could like sit between them.
I mean, it would be the most comfortable to ride a triceratops because they have
like that shield in the front with the crest in the back of their heads and the
three horns.
I thought a lot about this.
I thought a lot about what dinosaurs are best to have own ride and be Fred.
Yeah.
I got bit by the neighbor's dog.
Fucking.
Have that kind of dog.
I don't know.
Some like not even like a good looking dog either.
Like I'm so sick of people with stupid, goofy looking dogs.
Like he's got this like mutant and this big like this like curly white.
It looks like a like a cartoon poodle.
Only it's like as big as a big dog.
It's just the stupidest, fluffiest looking sack of shit I've ever seen.
Just looking at it makes me mad.
Listening to it makes me mad.
So I already wanted to kill it before it attacked me.
But like, you know, maybe it's your animosity.
I've fantasized about being attacked by a dog and just just clock it in the
brain.
Oh, dude.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, that's what that's exactly what happened.
That's oh, yeah, good.
I mean, when I when I walk by a house and the dog is bar and a dog starts barking
at me, I like I freeze up and I think like, OK, OK, I'm ready.
If the dog comes barreling, it's like the fence breaks and the dog comes
barreling out like I got to time my swinging back so I can just clock it in
the face right before it gets me.
You get that dog fighting fantasy every time one of them.
I do get the dog, the dog fighting fantasy.
I get that every time it's a dog that barks.
I'm just like, no, fuck you.
If you start shit, I will not.
I'm not afraid to put you down.
I get that you have.
I'll punch a dog.
Yeah, I'll punch a dog.
Like I get that you have teeth and you think that you're a badass because
you've got like sharp teeth and like a long nose and shit.
But like, I've got fists and feet and my feet have shoes on them.
So like, I can't even hurt my toes.
My fucking feet are too strong because of my shoes.
I can kick you or punch you.
I can headbutt you.
I want to headbutt a dog right in the snout.
We're wearing cloth armor.
We probably, we outweigh almost all dogs.
I want to like, if you have, if you have like a jacket on that can be,
that's like leather armor and like leather armor, you know,
they wear that in video games so you know it's tough.
Like if you're playing like a fucking, like a medieval thing.
So if you're like a cool, if you're like a cool punk rocker or something,
so I feel like when I'm in my leather jacket, I feel like, like plus 10
to power or armor or something.
Cause like nothing can hurt me.
So come at me dog, you don't have a jacket.
Yeah.
Like the most, the most armor that a dog would ever have is like a sweater.
But even that is not like a little bit of a sweater.
It confers a huge.
Like you've got a sweater, but I could totally take, I could totally take
this dog, but it's fucking, it's like Christmas sweater from grandma.
It's like, I can't penetrate it.
The sweater might protect you a little bit, but hey, I've got like a shirt
and a sweater and a hoodie and a jacket on all at once.
I'm like, I'm, I'm like a fucking walking tortoise tank.
Nothing can tell you.
I haven't had like the fantasy of like fighting against a dog,
but I have had like the nightmare fantasy of like, what if a dog is just going
to kill me and he wants to rip my leg off and he's big?
Like he probably just could.
Cause I, you know, I've seen, I've seen Game of Thrones.
I know what happens when your dog's upset and he's got a big sharp teeth.
They eat you.
Dogs like, they think that they're wolves.
And that's what, that's what pisses me off is that this, this, this unwarranted
esteem they have of themselves, where they think that they're tough and they
think they're like hot shit because they're like distantly related to
something that's actually tough and cool and scary.
You're not a wolf.
I don't have to be real cultural appropriation.
That is.
That's true.
The worst is Huskies.
Huskies are the dumbest breed of, of, of dog base.
I mean, maybe there's something.
And it's even more annoying because like, because Huskies are like beautiful
and you want them to be cool because they're like really cool dogs,
but they're also the most one of the most ill behaved.
They just, yeah, they're loud, annoying.
You know, I've often wondered.
So the only weapon that a dog, they're the jocks of dogs, they are the
retarded jocks of dogs.
Good looking, good looking, you know, you know, powerful retard.
Isn't it a bad, a bad design that like a dog's, so wolves have like, I guess
they have claws, right?
They could like, of course they'd hurt you.
Okay.
Good looking, no, no dog has that.
They are, they are.
But like, no, I just like that.
It's like a title.
It's when it, when it tries to bite you, like a dog or wolf, it's like brain
dome is right there.
It's right there.
And I feel like I could definitely get a few shots in.
You can crack down on your arm.
Yeah, you could just start punching it in the eyes, you know, something.
That's what I would do.
Yeah.
Yeah, like this fork, this take all but the biggest dogs, even unarmed.
This stupid, like giant poodle fucker from my neighbor that attacked me.
Like what happened was, because like I had just gotten my car.
And you know how like, if you've ever gotten a car, like the first week
something goes wrong and it's the most infuriating thing in the world.
Sure.
Right.
So like, right, like the first week I had my car, suddenly the door
wouldn't close and I came to find that like the latch on the door was like rusty
and it wouldn't like latch when I closed the doors.
It would like bounce off the frame when I tried to close the door.
So I'd have to slam it shut.
But then if I like slammed it shut, then I would be stuck in the car
and I wouldn't be able to open it again.
So for, so like I couldn't open the door and I would have to like crawl
over the center console from the passenger door.
It was so horrible.
And like this is a car that I just bought.
It was like, you know, massively expensive.
I was so fucking angry getting in and out of the car.
Like before I fixed this, I did eventually fix it.
But like, like I got out, I drove into my driveway already steaming mad
thinking that it would happen.
And of course it did.
I got out of the car, I go to close the door.
It's it's slams and bounces off the frame a bunch of times.
I can't fucking I'm bouncing it off the frame.
He's going boom, boom.
And it's like it's making like a loud noise every time it's bouncing off the
frame and the loud noise of bouncing off of it is making the neighbor's dog go
fucking ape shit, of course, because God forbid anyone else make a noise.
God forbid anyone but you, the fucking dog is the only one allowed to make
noise in this fucking world.
That's that's just tacitly giving it permission.
Yeah.
So like I'm trying to finally, I fucking am trying to like slam it shut.
And the fucking neighbor she has a door open, I guess, or whatever the fuck.
So the dog runs out, runs at me, literally jumps up and like bites a
chunk out of my arm and I fucking I threw it off.
The neighbor lady is like freaking out because like, oh, my God, my dog is
she's thinking that she's going to get sued.
I'm not going to sue anyone.
I'm just going to kill you, lady.
So don't worry.
Right.
I'm going to kill you and your dog and your whole family.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not going to get involved with lawyers or anything.
But so like I throw the dog off and I'm swearing up a storm and I'm yelling
and the lady's like, oh my God, what happened?
I'm like, shut the fuck up.
And so like the dog is like still barking.
And I swear to God, I had this moment where I just I turned
and I like pennant stared right into the fucking dog's eyes.
I stared right at it.
I just looked at it and I gave it a look and like the dog.
I think in that moment, the dog became aware that I am capable of murder.
And he feared for his life.
And he just like backed away with his stupid tail tucked between his legs.
It was it was it was, you know, annoying, but it was a little bit
uplifting to me to know that I could create a look on my face that
communicates to a lesser beast that I will fuck you up.
Got that you got that conquerors hockey.
Yeah, I was going to say, yeah, yeah, the ability to intimidate big power on
on a on a somewhat similar note to the dog fighting fantasy.
I have I have I think about what if my house caught fire?
Could I save my computer?
Yeah, good question.
And then yesterday, someone actually
remember Nuzlocke genocide?
Remember bananas, the masculine? Of course, it was that guy.
It was generally bananas, who was who was the names that he just tweeted
that his house caught fire and but he managed to save his computer.
And I was like, huh, I think about myself in that situation all the time.
So I like, you know, replied like, you know, glad you got the computer out
and also yourself or something.
Yeah, yeah, as an afterthought.
And yeah, I don't know.
I often often.
It would be very difficult.
I feel like I mean, I could I think what I would do if my house caught fire
and it was like in like the house is filling up with smoke.
And maybe I just have like maybe a minute, right?
Maybe it's like I need to get out as fast as I can or I'm risking life in limb.
I mean, I think I would probably just, you know, grab my computer tower.
Right. Unplug everything.
Unplug, you know, leave the monitors, leave, whatever, grab my hard drives
and my computer tower and run outside with that.
You know, the other stuff is like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Man, I would be like preserve the preserve the data.
I would be having a real Sophie's choice between my computer tower and my laptop
because like like the tower has like Vegas on it and all of my like working stuff.
And like my Vegas was is pirated for me by someone smarter than me.
So if I lose it, if I would never be able to get it back
because I'm not paying for it, I'm too stupid to ever pirate myself.
So like I would I would lose my career if I lost the tower,
which might be a blessing in disguise, but like true.
The but the laptop has like everything I've ever written for the last 10 years on it.
So like, do I save like 10 years of ideas or do I save the fucking machine
that allows me to put them into use?
Oh, you could get Vegas again.
Do you know like right in Google ducks?
No, I don't because I'm you know what?
I write I have the worst fucking system.
If something happens to the laptop, I'm totally fucked
because I write everything in this MacBook notes program.
And you cannot convert those to anything else.
You can't get them in like a real file.
You can't like move them to the to the tower or back them up.
I figured out I had to look up how to back them up,
but they're still in like a weird format.
I'm fucking so I guess I'm just lying.
I guess I'm fucking make it shit up, but the point is it's like
it's slightly difficult to back up the files.
It's like one extra step so I can never do it effectively impossible.
I have, you know, I have like a lot of the times I will
I have redundant copies of things like I have show on my computer.
I have some of the stuff is backed up for my old computer.
Some of that stuff is backed up for my old laptop.
Some of that stuff is backed up on Google Drive or, you know, in Google documents or whatever.
Yeah, I have no idea.
Like it's it's a lot of it is redundant, but I have no clue where I saved anything.
Like I have a bunch of email accounts and like, you know,
who fucking knows where like which account I saved what in.
Right. Right.
So like a lot of stuff probably would be recoverable,
even if my computer was destroyed, but it would be a huge hassle.
And then not everything, especially the newer stuff.
Yeah, I mean, I'm basically the same, but I do basically organize things by like category.
Like I've got like best guy ever, then I've got like a bunch of personal ones
and I've got like a professional one and yeah, so like I keep them separate.
I'm pretty good. I'm pretty good on that.
You guys's file management sounds terrifying to me
because I'm constantly paranoid about my data being deleted
because I've had too many bad experiences and I know it's a matter of time.
So what I did any of us long ago and thank God I did it when I did
because they don't do this anymore is the dropbox.
Right. I have all my important shit in Dropbox
and Dropbox is the best program ever made because what it does
is that everything's backed up to the cloud, but it also makes a local copy on your computer.
So it's always local, you never have to download anything,
but it's always being backed up all the time.
And then everything on Dropbox has revision history.
So if I ever accidentally save something I don't want to,
I just go to Dropbox.com and just roll back to the previous version.
And it's right back on my computer.
So it's the best thing ever made by even.
That's pretty good.
But here's that's pretty here's the problem.
The problem is Dropbox is only two gigs for free, which is not enough space.
So what they had back in the day was a referral program back when Dropbox was new.
It was like everybody you get to sign up for Dropbox,
you get an extra 250 megs on your free space.
And I'm like, and this is back in the pony days.
And I was like, I can abuse this.
So I go on D and I go on Twitter and I'm just like, use this link, just do it.
And now I'm up to like 25 gigs for free on Dropbox and that's enough.
That's enough for all my essential shit.
So I've screwed the system over.
And now every time I get a new computer or set something up, which is all the time,
I just download Dropbox and everything's there.
And I feel like God and I don't worry about files ever.
Well, I'm a little jealous.
That's pretty good.
Although, I mean, 25 gigs is not.
I mean, like I just I got a new I just got a new hard drive.
And I think it was Fat 32, that fucking villain.
The ultimate arch nemesis of the PC.
Yeah, yeah, because like there was some video files that I was moving
and I think it wouldn't take them because they were over four gigs.
Ugh, maybe it's actually like a squad.
It's the Fat 32 and it's 32 fat dudes.
Well, Fat 32 is evil and he's fat because he ate one through 31.
Can't wait for him to make his official debut in the Royal Rumble at Rat Cross.
The Royal Rumble. Hell yeah.
So, but I reformatted it.
You know, I finally finally I can use it now.
So I've got new space.
The problem is just choosing what I want to get off my main because
because like recording this, I only have like nine gigs free
on my main hard drive for some reason.
I don't know why that is because I had like 15 yesterday and I don't know what happened.
You got to download Windows, stat, Windows, directories.
You know what?
I'm going to empty my recycle bin right now.
Maybe that will help.
That's a good idea.
That's great.
But, you know, at work, you know, because I software program and all that,
we we we heavily and strictly control all file updates that get checked
into our our VCR or VC, whatever, our version control software, VCS, I guess.
Oh, you know, you know, Hippo, I do I do use Windows stat that you recommended to me.
It's great.
Yeah, it shows you like a visualization of your hard drive in terms of like how
much space is taken up by what and you can sort of like look.
Yeah, yeah. And I want that right now, dude.
It's the best it shows you like a grid and you can just look at like
the biggest squares in the grid and it'll tell you like, Oh, yeah.
This is, you know, HTTP colon slash slash pornography folder.
Oh, hell yeah.
Hell, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have a funny story with Windows stat, which is not really funny,
but I just find it in music because I'm a tech guy is that I bought this
like I bought a tower when I when I moved in with the digits.
Now I can have a tower again.
And I got this like HP workstation like super cheap because it's like old,
but it's still like super powerful.
It's one of those computers that used to cost like $6,000 when it came out.
So now it's only like 500, but it's still good.
So I was like, I'm poor, so I'll get that.
And it has 48 gigs of RAM and two six core processors.
Dang, that's not very much.
It's a lot. It's a lot.
It's a fuck ton.
Oh, oh, oh, of RAM, 48 gigs of RAM.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
So so I was using it and I realized immediately that I was running out of space.
And I'm like, how is this possible?
Because I have a 250, 60 SSD.
I should have space.
And then I opened up Windows that I was like, oh, of course,
what Windows does is every time what it does, it makes like a swap file
on your hard drive, like has like reserve space and it defaults to double your RAM size.
So I just have 96 gigs of my 250 SSD is a swap file.
And I'm just like, oh, fuck.
I guess when you have this much RAM, you need more hard drive space now.
And it was just like this huge fucking enormous square on Windows.
That like what in God's name is that?
And it's just like the fucking cache file that you can't get rid of.
I'm like, OK, well, shit.
I'm your fuck, dude.
Your fuck. But I have 48 gigs.
I feel I feel like I should mention just in case people don't know.
But on Google Docs,
documents that are just writing take up zero space.
They do. You can have an unlimited amount of those.
It's a very valuable thing to know, which is why I think, Jesse,
if you can, like try to copy paste all of those onto there.
Yeah, that's a really good idea. You'll never run out.
What if what if what do you know how like on Microsoft Word,
you can like embed music and stuff into documents and things like that?
What if you could do that on Google Drive and they still took up zero space,
just have this crazy piracy network where it's just like every MP3 ever in a document.
It takes up zero space on your drive.
That would be pretty dope.
Hey, hey, I've got the system works.
I've got an update for people from last PCP.
If you recall, Redaway, run every day until I'm hot.
Yeah, the program I'm doing now, I just want to give everybody an update.
I'm doing it so far. No flaws. Perfect job.
I am the best.
But I have something retarded to say about that.
When you when I first heard Redaway run every day until I'm hot,
I did Redaway.
I did not. I did not realize that the hot was your physical experience.
I thought you just meant run until you felt hot, like got hot.
Oh, I'm like, that sounds like a really pushy running regimen.
That'll take like a minute.
What? No. God damn it.
It's a lifestyle change.
Until you start to say, yeah, that's not like, whoa, that's enough, man.
That's initially what I thought it meant.
And I was like, well, I guess that will slowly get better as your endurance increases.
But but then I realized, oh, I'm being a fool because I'm not thinking of Nate that way.
Well, apparently, other people thought that too.
So OK, OK, OK, OK, well, no, it's about about changing lifestyle.
So so actually, a dude messaged me the other day.
This was yesterday and he sent me he heard of my epic tale
from the last PCP episode.
Wait, which epic tale about how I'm doing this, how I'm doing this.
OK, this is Captain Suppey.
I've heard the name somewhere before.
But he apparently is like a dope ass run boy who runs like,
I don't know, it's not professional.
He's not his college team or something.
He sent me a big old document illustrating how my efforts are are going to overtax my body
because I'm going to fuck myself up if I actually run every day as as like a noob, which I am.
And so he just broke it down into like a bunch of sections for like for your first
like two to three. What would he say?
Let me let me let me.
This is funny, actually.
Let me read like the little intro thing you put here.
Let me see. OK, so this is his intro paragraph, which is I like this a lot
because what he's doing is he's establishing why I should care about his opinion,
which is the most important thing with this.
So yeah, that's the stick.
That's the sticking point for me.
Yeah, of course, because like he could just be some fat nobody who doesn't know a goddamn thing.
But he says, OK, I want to preface this by saying I know my shit.
Oh, by the way, he wrote this whole thing yesterday while high
as he explained to me as he was doing it.
OK, so I've been a runner since I was 12.
I've done everything from track to cross country, have ran three half marathons,
have a 455 mile and an 1820 five K PR.
But I'm going to give you advice based on the fucking casual.
I know you are. Don't worry.
I'm not trying to have you break records.
I know all you want us to lose those annoying small but noticeable flabs.
So with that, let's just jump into it.
And then he just breaks it down for like a couple of weeks.
And he says to run like starts off two to three times per week
and then up to like four to five times per week and shit.
But it's good. And you see, I just I want to use this as an example.
People of even though my program definitely was not optimal, it was not perfect.
It got me going and it gets people.
I know I have an internet presence, so like I'm more likely to get things like this.
But like, maybe you know somebody in your life.
I'm just saying the the power of doing something as opposed to nothing
to get you moving in the right direction is a very strong thing.
I appreciate this guy's effort and his credentials do seem good,
especially if they're assuming they're true, which I don't know.
But on the other hand, you got to you got to think about our boy
Saitama, who just ran every day and became the strongest man in the universe.
So I don't know. One of these people.
So this guy wants this guy wants you to miss out on that.
Yeah, that's trying to sabotage.
You know, the one thing about this is I was saying this last time
and I still think this is true.
It's easier for me to just say I need to run every day like to myself as a rule
as opposed to, oh, yeah, I'm going to run like three times per week.
And I'll just mark those on the calendar because then like I might just fuck up and be like, oh, I feel the same way.
Do you have the problem that I have?
Do you have the problem of like universal willpower?
Do what I mean by that is that, OK, I'll just use an example.
Thanksgiving just happened a couple of days ago.
And broke Keto to do Thanksgiving.
I was doing right. Are you back on Keto?
I kind of thought you had quit.
I was I'm considering it still.
I'm trying to like I'm trying what I'm trying to do right now is before I just quit completely.
I'm just trying to cut out diet soda entirely because I don't know if it's diet.
So that's making me sick or just the diet in general.
And feel sick, Ben. So that's the priority, whatever.
OK, yeah, but the thing is the point of coming with like universal willpower is that
so I broke Keto to like, you know, be with family, have have food,
be a disgusting degenerate, eating sugar.
Yep. Sugar actually tasted odd and I didn't like it.
But that's great. That's a side point.
But but after that, like for the last couple of days,
I have like been significantly weaker, not only in my diet, but in everything.
Like getting to work takes more effort now.
Being like getting up at a decent hour, which has always been bad, is more difficult.
I rolled out of bed because I got a message from my phone,
which was Nate saying it's PCP time.
I'm like, fuck, it was like eight, like three seconds ago.
So just just just one breaking of like habit has ruined everything.
Everything's all tied together. It's the worst.
And if you want to be a god, you have to be perfect because that's what a god is.
Yes. I mean, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, as soon as you succumb to one weakness of the flesh,
it all comes crumbling down like that.
I definitely feel like the big way went out to Boston.
It's the way what what did you fuck up in Boston?
We went to Boston and we were playing Jenga
and I totally fucked it up last minute and it was it was sick.
Did did you lose?
I was the one who lost Jenga.
Yeah, it's my hand tremble because I had I remember I had a good move
where I hand trembled and it all went to fucking shit.
And Munchy was playing.
I was trying to do it to put way more pressure on me.
In we played Jenga in that in that like China Chinatown like bubble tea shop
and they had like all the the bricks for the Jenga set had like shit written on them.
And some of them just had people's phone numbers written on them.
And I just picked one up and called in in in the store.
Is it a local hot mom looking for a quick sex?
It sounded like no joke.
It sounded like a cutie Asian honey pie.
Yeah, it sounded like a cute Asian girl who was like really shy.
And like she was like, hello, like I didn't even hear any words.
Right. I heard like some kind of whisper, some sort of like vague whisper
of like acknowledgement that a phone call had been received.
And I just said like, hello, you know, I found your number on a Jenga block.
And I just wanted to say that you're that, you know, have a
they want to wish you a happy day and let you know that you're a good person or something.
And she just started laughing.
That's funny. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
She literally should have married this woman while you had.
I mean, I made, I took pains to make this not a traumatic or scary experience.
It was an oddly upbeat interaction.
Yeah, you've got her number, though, and she can't escape that.
It's true. I guess so.
I guess it's in my phone somewhere.
If I wanted to wait a little bit longer, then you just hit her up again.
You're like, so what are you doing?
No, why not? Remember that time?
Remember that time I found your number on a Jenga block.
Well, it's time to pay the pipe. Yeah.
She could be 45 or, I don't know, who knows, with these Asian ladies
sounding young when they're not, I don't know.
But anyway, hey, hey, Captain Suppy, I'm sure that he's like correct in his plan,
but I still feel a desire to do it every day.
So I'm going to probably keep doing that, at least for a little while.
Although my left ankle, something's going on there.
That's not great.
But it's it's it's the muscle.
It's not like the bones or anything.
I just I probably need to just stretch if I just do that.
Because, you know, my runs are pussy shit.
They're half an hour and I take a like a bunch of breaks.
And I just like, I'm tired, I need to walk for a minute.
So whatever, I'm working on it.
But I'm going to follow this Bible.
He sent me some good shit, some good shit.
Anyway, there's your update, people.
I am a good to be a god.
By the time I get to Hawaii, I need to be hot.
That's my goal. So I'm losing weight.
Keto Keto Keto story.
I went to Thanksgiving.
Didn't break Keto.
Well, I kind of did a little bit in the sense.
I mean, I eat I eat turkey and I eat like, you know,
Brussels sprouts and, you know, green beans.
You know, I basically just ate turkey and greens.
And the only questionable things ate where I ate pumpkin seeds,
thinking that they were keto.
But I looked it up later and they actually you have some carbs.
And all they, you know, I didn't eat that many of them.
So whatever. OK, that wasn't great.
But it was and then there were these things that there were these weird
things that like aunt Sonny made or someone made them.
And they were made of almond butter rolled with like some kind of seed.
And they had like they had some dried cherries in them.
And they said a little bit of maple syrup.
And I had one or two of those.
This is so they had a little bit.
Are they good? Yeah, they weren't they weren't super sweet.
Like they weren't sweet like a dessert or anything.
So I felt like these can't be too bad.
Um, yeah, they were all right.
I mean, I just really like almond butter, really like I love nut butters.
All about those nut butters.
Hey, listen to me talking about food.
I'm like some kind of idiot talking about a dog.
What a fucking joke.
Hey, hippo, why don't you fucking celebrate Thanksgiving?
Oh, why don't you?
Why don't you? Why aren't you thankful for America?
Because I don't care.
I'm not that thankful.
What have you made for for the rest of us?
I've got peanut butter.
You ever heard of George Washington Carver?
Inventor a peanut butter.
Have you ever heard of Pokemon Go?
I ain't never eaten a peanut butter ever.
What about freedom? We invented that.
We invented both slavery and freedom.
We invented bald eagles.
We probably invented guns.
That might even be true.
I don't know.
Oh, right.
I saw I saw Princess Mona.
All right, please, please enlighten me because we do.
Obviously, we don't celebrate Thanksgiving
because it is an American tradition,
but I don't actually know what I like.
It's something to do with the Native American.
It's literally a celebration of genocide.
No, it's not exaggeration.
I mean, that's just how it's started.
It's an exaggeration, but I mean, yeah, it is.
I was arguing with Michelle about this.
What you celebrate on Thanksgiving
is specifically the event
where the Pilgrims and the Indians work together
and were harmonious.
You're not celebrating.
Look, yes, there were genocides later,
but you're not celebrating that.
It was like that first year or something
when the Indians or the Native Americans
shared with the Pilgrims so that they wouldn't start.
So it was like a thank you
in the form of giving food from one to the other for like, okay.
It was like coming together with people.
It was like a thanks for sharing harmony.
Nobody really cares about the Pilgrims, though.
It's mainly like a celebration of family
and hanging out with your loved ones.
Well, yeah, I know that from watching
all those funny American cartoons about families.
Is there a Charlie Brown Thanksgiving?
Yeah, there's gotta be, right?
Yes.
I think I've only seen the most offensive video version
of that and all other Charlie Brown specials.
Is it, suck my big black ass Charlie Brown?
Is that, that's actually the name too.
There is one that is called that.
I think it's the Valentine's Day.
I don't know.
You know, there's a thing about Thanksgiving.
It's like a small gripe
because it's not really a thing
that has ever been like pushed.
But I get this feeling that on social media,
people don't, you know, they say thanks.
They say a funny meme thanks
because it's Thanksgiving where they are.
And it's like, there's this slight implication
that you should be saying thanks in general.
Like it's not about Thanksgiving necessarily
on the internet.
It's just about saying thank you for stuff you have.
And I'm like, well, I mean, I know it's Thanksgiving
because everyone talks about it.
And I'm like, I'm thankful for things,
but I don't wanna be involved.
It's not my culture.
I don't know what to do.
It would be cultural appropriation.
It's not even about like cultural appropriation.
I just don't wanna be associated with this American,
this gross.
I mean, yeah, I don't think any,
I wouldn't expect outside cultures
to like recognize American holidays or anything.
Yeah, I mean, it's just hard to like, to look away.
Imagine like you don't celebrate Christmas.
And then every year there's a lot of Christmas stuff
on everything and you can't really get away from it.
And it's like, I don't really wanna do about this.
I understand why I have to commit acts of terror.
This cannot stand.
We have to cease this, this oppression and bullying.
It's not bullying, I don't feel bad about it.
I was just thinking about it.
Cause like I don't wanna say,
oh, I hate being thankful cause I don't.
I like being thankful, but it's just, it's not the time.
It's not yet the time.
Rattitude is a virtue in my humble opinion,
but yes, I understand your point.
It can be annoying.
By the way, I've opened up this Winder Stat shit,
it looks insane and it's pretty cool.
I don't get it, but I like it.
It's like hover over the squares
and you'll see at the bottom,
it'll show you like what files you're gonna get.
You click on, you click on the squares
and it will show you where that file is and what it is.
Let's link this in the show notes.
Let me, I'm gonna give people a screencap
of my breakdown of my drives.
Hopefully this doesn't contain secret information
that you shouldn't know.
But like if you look on the right there.
Best guy air videos from 2013
that still haven't been made yet.
Yeah, yeah, kind of.
Look at this, look at this.
What do you think those,
the biggest ones here are those blue squares
on the top right.
What do you think those are?
I mean, I would imagine that they're probably
like system files or something.
No, they're not.
They're actually, well, I'll just tell ya.
Those are the video files
specifically of the Final Fantasy lecture.
That's what those are.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, sure.
That's dope, that's dope as shit, dude.
Fuck.
VLC media files, 1.4 terabytes, yeah.
This is so good, cause okay,
one of these is Tom's lecture backup.
So like that lower blue square,
that's the backup file that I was holding on to
of Tom's lecture backup of the Guilty Gear.
I could probably fucking delete that at this point.
Don't need that anymore.
I think anyone needs that.
That'd be nice space to have.
It's cool, right?
It's good to see it visually.
It is so good.
It's great.
You completely forget like,
cause every time I render any video,
I usually hand break it,
which reduces the file size,
but often I forget to get rid of the original.
Yeah.
And seeing that is like,
oh, that huge thing,
that's the podcast from a few weeks ago
that I forgot to delete.
I have so sick.
I have so many files from old PCP episodes.
Me too, me too.
Do not need to be saved.
They definitely are not necessary anymore.
Yeah, I probably have like 50 or more gigs of that shit.
Yeah, this is Tom Black's program.
Yeah, this is the Black Friday deal.
Get this for zero money because it's free.
Instead of buying a new hard drive for Christmas,
get this and get rid of old shit.
You know what though?
On this subject,
one other factor of this is,
I am terrified of deleting source files
and then the project disappeared.
Like I've backed up like all best guy ever videos in places,
but almost like all their components.
What if I delete like my audio from a PCP episode
and then like the episode is taken down
and we need to re-render it or something?
I feel the same.
Yeah, I have the same thing.
Yeah, I have all that shit.
I've thought about that,
but I also think having the original files
is something that you would need
if you're like the Beatles
and you want to remaster the fucking Beatles albums.
A PCP episode, it's not really that important.
You're right on that.
People have been able to download the MP3s forever.
That's true.
Things are saved in ways that...
Even if like our channel disappeared tomorrow,
like we would still have all the necessary...
Yeah, and also we'd also be still here.
We could just make new episodes.
We can download at our leisure at any point.
You know what though?
I'll give you the biggest example.
The most ancient thing I unearthed and like re-rendered
was at one point,
I can't remember what it was for,
but at one point,
because I still have all the original files
for best anime ever,
Gurrenlog in part two on my currently,
not my current machine, my old machine,
which is still hooked up.
Like I re-rendered a certain section.
Oh, you know what it was?
I had to re-render the personal fucking responsibility clip
for the Mia Maffova song that I did
for Mia Maffova last year,
because I wanted to render it without the backing audio track,
but I wanted to keep the visuals and stuff.
So that particular section,
I'm sure glad I still had that,
so I was able to reproduce it for the highest quality.
But like, even if I hadn't kept it,
all that would have changed
is that I would have used a clip
that just had the music in it
and then just kind of like fucked with the levels
to like lower it and shit.
Or you could have just re-recorded saying that.
I can't do that.
I need to preserve the quality of the originals.
Yeah, yeah, that would be like remastering fucking,
that would be like remastering a symphony of the night
and changing the dialogue or something.
He went there late in the year.
I don't know.
I feel like if you still have a microphone or a tablet,
you can recreate things,
like things get lost all the time.
I don't feel, I feel like...
Nate, I feel your same dedication
to preserving the original.
Thank you.
Yeah, I get it.
I get it.
Like I feel that way about the original versions
of certain video games where every digital version
sucks for some reason.
I don't know why.
All the remasters of Final Fantasy IX
have like really shitty background art now.
Yeah, I've seen those.
I want to buy the original just for that reason.
But like for videos on the internet,
like I mean specifically my videos on the internet,
I don't really care.
I'm sure people do care, but like if my channel gets deleted,
it would take a lot of my time and effort
to re-upload the files I have.
Yep.
I don't know whether I'd even try.
Damn, well, I mean,
I definitely don't feel that way personally.
But it would, I don't know.
Not everything that's on there
would I feel the need to resurrect probably,
though I'd want to.
I have zero backup of any of my video content
because I care that little about it.
Oh, God.
Oh, that's time for ya.
Hey, speaking of the lectures,
you mentioned the lectures looking at these files.
So here's something that I'm going through.
Here's something that I'm dealing with right now.
So over the last while,
I have been sort of talking to Laserbot,
a Camry Blankenship, the creator of Tales Gets Trolled.
And I friended him on Facebook
and like he knew he'd seen the lecture,
like he knew who I was more or less.
Yeah.
And we sort of start like casually talking,
like every few days we'd send a message
back and forth or whatever.
And I tell him like,
hey, it would be really cool to have you on our podcast.
And he was like, okay, cool.
Well, I don't have any internet right now.
I don't have a good microphone.
I don't have a good internet connection.
But when I do, I'm interested.
And I would like to talk about this new project
that I'm working on.
Well, it's not new.
He's remaking an old series
that he had on his YouTube channel.
I think I've mentioned it before.
It's called Micorat.
Right.
And I'm like, yeah, we can talk about Micorat.
Like I'd love to get you on the show.
I'm like, we can talk about whatever you're working on.
Just want to fucking chat and it would be super cool.
So that we proceed under that pretense
for maybe like a month or two.
And then fine, like I watch all of Micorat.
Like I tell him, like, you know, it's interesting,
you know, it's interesting to see
how you've evolved as of whatever, you know,
I want to know, you know, yeah, yeah, yeah, cool.
Let's talk about Micorat.
You know, I want to talk about
Tails Goods Troll and all that too.
Like, but yeah, we can get on, talk about Micorat.
We can promote the remake of Micorat.
And then, and then he's just like, oh yeah.
This was so infuriating to me.
He's like, well, I still don't have a good internet connection.
I still don't have a good microphone.
The best I can, the best I can do for you
is give you permission to talk about Micorat on.
And I'm like, I have not responded to this
because this is so infuriating because that's nothing.
What he's saying he can do for me is nothing.
I mean, you know, that's an acceptable amount
if he just doesn't want anything.
Oh, sure.
Okay, but then what the fuck have we been talking about?
He's like, he doesn't need to give me permission
to talk about his fucking YouTube series.
True, true.
I'm so fucking mad.
He fucking strung me along.
Well, that's understood.
For what?
You were the one doing all the work there
because we've been talking about getting him on possibly
or talking about his stuff for a while.
Well, look, I mean, if he didn't want to be on,
why didn't he just say, first of all,
I don't understand why not?
Because no one has ever heard of Micorat.
Okay, I think it comes down to this.
Sure, in the abstract, yeah, he'd like to be on.
I think it's just not that important to him,
which is fine, which is fine.
Oh, well fine.
And it would be nice if he had been clear with you on that.
Well then why did we even have this fucking exchange?
What was the point?
I'm so, I'm so annoyed.
I'm so annoyed about it.
I mean, the whole like internet thing,
like I understand people,
maybe they don't really have control over that,
but yeah, I mean, you got control over this other stuff.
I mean, if he didn't want to, then, you know,
it would have been nice to let you know a little sooner.
I don't know, I just,
I wonder if he even really has no internet connection
or if he just doesn't feel like doing this,
and that's just impossible.
How is he messaging you on Facebook?
Well, he said he didn't have a stable internet connection.
So like, whatever that.
I didn't have a stable internet connection.
I'm still doing the show today.
I would literally, if having no microphone,
if having not a good microphone is the problem,
I would literally buy him a microphone,
send him like a $50 microphone,
which would be good enough.
I feel this way a lot with people,
like I am a guy who when there's a thing I want to get done,
I find the points that are the issue,
we resolve them as quickly and efficiently as possible
and get to it, but that all hinges on the fact
that this is actually something people want to happen,
and maybe that's not the case.
Maybe that's not.
Well, yeah, and it's fine.
Just if he was not interested in doing this,
why did we proceed for all this time on the idea?
Here's the theory.
I don't think he's much of a podcaster.
Maybe he's nervous, and he just doesn't want to,
a lot of people wouldn't want to say that.
I'm not talking shit on the guy,
just some people are like that, so.
Well, I don't know.
I might give it another shot.
I might talk to him again and be like,
I don't know, I probably shouldn't give up.
Just level with him, just level with him here.
Yeah, yeah, I didn't respond to that.
This was a while ago, actually.
I didn't respond to that because I was very frustrated,
and I didn't want to come off as a jerk by saying,
okay, what you're saying you can do for me is nothing,
because that's what I wanted to say.
Because that is.
So instead you just put on the podcast
that you wanted to be on that he might listen to at some point.
His permission to talk about his work is nothing,
because that's something that I don't need permission to do.
That's true.
Because someone who already did a huge lecture
was sorry this whole thing in the first place,
clearly his permission is not necessary.
Yeah, but I don't know.
I mean, God, it'd be so cool, it'd be so funny.
It'd be so funny to have him on.
No one's here.
Because he's not anywhere.
There are no interviews with him or anything on YouTube
that I could find when I looked.
Give it an old college try there, Ben, one more time.
Yeah, I shouldn't give up.
I shouldn't give up just yet.
Look, I mean, if he doesn't want to do it, that's it.
That's fair enough.
There needs to be a bro talk here about,
let's get real behind this wheel, dog,
and just you want to be on this thing or not.
I want to talk about Micorat, right?
But I want to talk to you about it, sir.
I don't have that much to say about it on my own.
That's not the point here.
I feel you.
That's been on your mind.
That's been a thing you've been dealing with for a while.
A little bit, yeah.
I'm glad it's, yeah.
I was really looking forward to maybe getting Camry on.
I was a little bit crushed.
I was a little bit crestfallen when I got that message
being like, actually, oh no, it all comes tumbling down,
tumbling down, tumbling down.
I don't want to believe the man who made
Tails Gets Trolled isn't a man who executes
on his goals and dreams and ambitions.
So please prove us all wrong.
I will say the idea, okay, having watched Micorat,
the idea that he wants to remake it is totally baffled.
Maybe there's some core idea that he wants to really change.
That's what I want.
I want to know, are you just gonna re-remake it
or are you talking about a reboot with the same character?
Like that would make more sense
because I'm pretty sure that the characters in Micorat
are animalized versions of him and his brother
and their real life friends.
So like a reboot of it with the same characters
would make sense.
A remake would not make sense because I'm pretty sure
they just sort of like fucking rift,
sort of improv the whole thing and like, yeah.
We'll see, we need him on to answer these questions.
These are the questions I want to ask him.
Of course, of course.
Well, get on it, man.
Yeah, okay, I've been reinvigorated in my quest.
Excellent.
I had one thing.
I had just a thought, just a thought.
I was philosophizing, you know,
just riffing with my own brain.
What do you guys think about this?
This is my little philosophical thought
of the other day that I'm raising now.
I was thinking about why everybody is so upset,
specifically I was thinking about bullying.
I was thinking about bullying, but it applies to other stuff.
And I was like, the world hates bullying so much
and bullies specifically are vilified,
you know, understandably so.
But like, the whole world despises bullies intensely.
And it's because bullies are a very tangible thing, I think.
Like, okay, so you got a situation about a kid being bullied.
It's like, okay.
Everyone's been bullied in one form or another, right?
What I'm thinking about, I'm thinking about like,
how do we resolve like bullying?
Or you'll see how this extrapolates outward.
And I was thinking about like,
when you've got a situation where like,
let's say a weak little kid is being bullied
by like a larger kid,
like how do you fix this problem in the real world?
Because you got two, there's two options here.
One is that the outside world intervenes
and maybe like, separates them, punishes the bully,
does something like that.
And in some way, it stops the aggression from happening.
There's another way this situation can be resolved,
which is that the person who's bullied in some way,
like steps up or like proves that they won't be bullied.
They won't tolerate it.
You know, maybe fights back physically
or you know, whatever's appropriate for the situation.
And I was just, I was thinking about this equation.
And I'm like, man, the whole world just seems
like such a place where people want to do something.
The only-
To intervene?
Yes, yeah.
This interventionist mindset.
I think I see where you're going with this.
Yeah.
I was just thinking about how the,
the world has only, of that equation,
where there's two things that can change,
the entire world can only operate on one axis there.
And that is the interfere with the bully
and like stop them from doing the bad thing.
Yeah.
But it's, we have to admit that a big factor here,
a big way that this can change is for,
I mean, maybe like he gets like a talking with his dad.
He, you know, pulls up some thing from inside himself,
but the person who's being bullied,
they are the one, they change.
They change their mindset.
They change their, you know, internal mechanisms
or they just get like a really good lecture
from their dad or mom or whatever.
And then they're like, no, I'm not gonna be bullied anymore.
And then they fight back.
Cause most bullies, as I understand it,
they'll pick on the people who are like the weakest targets.
So if you just won't roll over, you know, theoretically,
and as long as they're, it's capable of some backlash,
like online, there's a different thing
where everyone's anonymous,
can't really fight back very well.
And I was just saying, so like people want,
the world wants to intervene and punish the bully,
but the better outcome really is that the bully,
the bully with two E's, you know,
like a trainee or an employee,
there's the bully and the bully.
Like the key blade.
So the bully E changes for the better, you know,
learns something and corrects the situation himself.
I mean, that can't always happen, right?
Some kids, like sometimes the size difference
might be so vast that like the small
and just can't fight back,
that he can't stand up to him in any meaningful way.
I'm sure there are situations like that.
I happily agree.
I mean, most bullies do not bully
unless they have a comfortable position of power
or anonymity on the internet,
which is a power in and of itself,
or in real life, like size or money
or like a job above the person.
Like bullies are fucking cowards.
They, in most cases, they only exist in situations
where the other person cannot fight back
because unfortunately, at some point,
a bunch of idiots got together
and decided that murder should be illegal.
And so there will never be any justice ever in the world
because you're not allowed to kill people.
So the world is fucked.
I hear what you're saying.
Like the point I wanted to make about this
was less about bullying specifically,
but it's that I feel like the whole world
is kind of possessed by,
like our actions are so guided by the fact
that we can only intervene on the one side.
We can't empower anyone
to change their internal mindset.
Even though that, I, like, let's say that this kid...
Is it like, you're risking victim shaming at that point?
Is that true?
And that people don't want to do that?
You can't make someone change their mindset,
but like, you know, others' actions
can lead to a change in attitude.
Like, by example, for example.
That's definitely true.
It's not like we can do nothing to change others' mindsets,
but we can't intervene directly in them.
It just often seems like those who fight back
are usually the ones punished.
You know, that, I suppose, I don't, you know...
And I think the way to fix that is that,
I think the way to fix that is,
just have no more laws.
Just like if someone is fucking with you,
you should be allowed to fucking cut their head off.
I don't think that's reasonable.
Who in their right mind?
Look, I don't know how much this happens.
Like, I don't know what kind of bullying is more common,
though they say bullying is on the rise,
but I think it's more like emotional
and like mental abuse and stuff.
I mean, that's the same.
Well, I'm talking, like, I guess that's true,
but if you've got a person who's, like,
you're a kid, you've got no friends,
like maybe you're a new kid at a school,
and like, there's a big kid,
and like, he's got like two or three friends
that always hang out with him,
and they just call you names every day,
and they call you names every single day.
Yeah, I saw Bart the General.
You saw what?
I saw Bart the General.
Right, right.
And like, if you like,
like, what happens when it comes to a head?
Like, you can't, I think this is more to Jesse's point.
Like, if you like, punch the kid one day
because you've just had enough,
I like, like, he never got physical,
and for some reason, well, okay, understandably,
it's harder to quantify like,
emotional abuse or like, mental bullying or whatever.
So like, you are the one who took it
to like an actual violent place,
so like, I feel like people are gonna be like,
oh, well, you're the real bad guy, thank you.
Yeah, I mean, society talks about it.
I mean, you should believe it.
I mean, that kid is wrong.
It is wrong to attack someone.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It is not, like, the thing that I hate
is that physical violence is held
as like, more dangerous, more bad
than like, emotional abuse.
It is, it is though.
No, no.
Yeah, okay.
It's because of the context of which people
like, take physical and mental abuse.
Like, you can't quantify it when it's emotional,
and because you can't quantify it,
you can't weigh the amount of physical abuse
against the amount of emotional abuse.
If somebody deserves to get punched in the face,
you can't like, you can't clarify that after the fact
and say, well, he did, you know, yell at you
as this specific amount, so one punch is okay.
Like, that never happens.
So like, everybody who is like,
the most annoying person in the world,
but they don't throw a punch,
can get away with that forever,
and somebody who throws a single punch is a villain.
Society says it's against bullying,
but the way that we, like you said, quantify like,
oh, because the person was violent,
that automatically is worse than the emotional abuse,
it's not, so like, you're almost not allowed
to stand up for yourself or be a man.
You're encouraged to be a rat motherfucker
and a coward and bully heroes.
There's like, if you think of like,
every TV show where like, somebody gets punched
and you're like, oh yeah, they deserve that.
Or like, you know, a Game of Thrones,
somebody dies and you're like, finally,
like, the things he's done, I mean,
in Game of Thrones, everyone kills everyone,
there's always physical violence,
but like, if somebody like, there was that moment
in the Harry Potter movie where Draco gets punched
by Hermione and everyone cheers at that,
they're like, oh yeah, cool, girl power,
and it's really cool and it's fucking sick, but like,
listen, it's like, Hermione didn't do a good thing,
but like, we all agree that, well,
we all generally agree that he kind of deserves that
and it's not like, she shouldn't be thrown
out of school for that.
Well, I mean, that's fiction, right?
In fiction, you can get punched in the face and it's fine.
No, the reason I was saying fiction is because
in fiction, you're reading it or watching it
and you can get a sense of like, how it feels
for the one person being bullied
because that's how like the narrative is like,
oh, this is the villain.
Yeah, you kind of can quantify the bullying in a book
where we can see their heads.
The only person who can quantify the amount
of emotional abuse in real life is the person being abused
and you know, an outlier and an onlooker
can't really gauge it perfectly.
Physical violence in the real world, you know,
despite how it looks in media is ugly and gross
and bad and like, in real life, a bully getting,
yeah, sure it is.
I don't know, I don't think that like,
I think the amount of emotional abuse someone would have
to inflict to deserve to get like physically struck
or injured is like, insane.
I mean, you know, like super hot,
like why is hurting someone's feelings
more okay than hurting someone's face?
Emotions aren't even real, dude.
Well, Bill Burr, I think summarized this well
in one of his little bits, which was like,
okay, you come home from work,
I don't know, you've been married to a woman
for like, I don't know, let's say 10 years,
I don't know, let's say you have kids
and you just find her like fucking the neighbor
and you're like, okay, like sure, it's not good
to like attack her or be violent to her, obviously,
would never condone it, but like,
you can understand why this is bad
and like what one's motivation would be
for like, you know, being physically violent here.
To want to be fit, yeah, sure.
In this case, it doesn't like, that's not justified,
it's not, you're gonna fix anything to attack a person.
And like, and like that's, that's,
I mean, God, like, I mean, that would be like a crime.
That's true.
And it would not be a crime.
It's not a crime what she did, on the other hand,
but it is bad and it is damaging in other ways.
And I understand we can't compare them,
they're kind of non-overlapping magisteria,
but I mean, yeah, I don't know, it's sort of similar.
It's sort of, you know, emotional abuse.
Yeah, yeah, it's sort of, I mean,
she's hurt, she's hurt this man emotionally,
so yeah, it's comparable there.
What are we, what are we?
You know what, what's the point we're driving at here?
I mean, there's a point is like,
do we want like physical violence to be okay,
or do we want like emotional abuse to be not okay
to an equivalent amount?
Like, it would be lovely if we could quantify
the emotional abuse and then deal out punishment properly.
Right now, what we're doing,
it just doesn't work, it's kind of impossible to do that.
We've already said, physical violence is out,
we can't do it.
And now, we're trying to do the same thing,
at least like Twitter with their,
like Twitter just made it a rule,
where you are, it is now a reportable and banable offense
if you like misgender or dead name someone,
and so that's like a trans thing.
So, like, so what they're,
I mean, the point of that policy is to stop you
from hurting people's feelings, and like, I get it.
God, I better fucking get my shit together
and start remembering that his name is Christine
Weston Chandler.
I mean, that he could report you.
It all comes down to like, we all are,
I'm sorry, she, whatever.
We all agreed that if a dog is barking at you,
you should be allowed to fucking punch it in the brain.
I mean, that's a, if a dog is emotionally abusing you
by annoying you enough,
then you should be allowed to be as violent as you want
and have a fucking dog meat sandwich for dinner.
I can't agree with that.
Now, you've found, yeah, okay, I do want to hurt dogs.
I do.
It's like, like, the reason you would go
to physical violence is not because you love to kill,
it is because that is the solution.
The dog will not bark as much if it sees you glaring at it
and punching it.
I mean, like, in theory, and when we'll have fantasies.
Dogs are the original bullies.
They fucking bark and bark,
and they act like they're tough shit, but they're cowards.
Well, like, a technical dog may or may not
fix the problem long-term.
Like, standing up to a bully, even physically,
that may in fact fix the problem long-term.
It might cause more violence.
You know, I don't know.
I mean, it might sometimes, yeah, it might scare them off.
It might create other problems, that's true.
It would make, like, okay, I don't think that you,
I don't think that you solve the bully problem
by, like, fighting the bully and hurting him
so that he's like, oh, if I fight this kid, I'll get hurt.
Like, I don't, I don't know.
That's a really clean narrative that you see in media.
You've changed the situation, but you haven't technically
solved it, it could go in other ways.
Yeah, like, it could just make him hate you more.
It could just make him even greater.
Yeah, it is, it is the cycle of violence.
I know that, like, yeah, in some cases,
it might fix the situation, but yeah, the cycle of violence.
Okay, you know what?
This is an interesting topic.
This actually was not my point at all.
And my main point was just that I would just,
I was thinking about bullying as an example of how,
like, outside people, we want to,
our only power here, if we, like,
see someone getting bullied,
all we can actually do to change the situation
is to, like, intervene personally
and, like, do something to, like, stop the bully.
We can't change what's going on inside the person
who's being bullied.
And I guess my only point is I think that's, like,
kind of an underserved and an underrepresented
important element that I just think deserves more
consider, I don't know what's to be done.
I guess it's kind of like, instead of just, like, shitty,
I could go on Twitter and, like, shit on Trump, I guess.
But, like, I just think a better,
even if Trump is the worst president, the worst person ever,
I just think a better thing to do is to, like,
think about, like, okay, guys, the world sucks,
here's what you can do to improve yourself.
And, like, these are the ways that no matter what happens,
you'll be in a better place to deal with it.
It's like giving someone a fish versus teaching them to fish.
Like, if you take the bully out of the equation,
the person who's getting bullied is still emitting
that kind of energy that attracts bullies,
and they're just gonna continue to get bullied.
Great point.
And it's like beating up their bully
instead of teaching them how to beat off bullies in general.
Beat them off, huh?
Or beat off your bully.
Guys, we found the solution.
Beat off your bullies.
It's what they're really looking for.
Love, love, not hate.
I pretty much love that.
I guess that pretty much sums it up.
Break the cycle of violence and beat off your bully.
With love, with love, guys, do it.
Yeah, I guess punching people is not the solution.
I just feel like the punishment for punching
and the punishment for emotional abuse
is skewed very far in harsh penalties for physical.
And I guess, after a certain point, there is a threshold.
There is a threshold beyond which it's like,
well, this guy's broken his leg.
That's fucked him up, and he's gonna break that leg again,
because the bone will never heal quite as strong
as the first time.
So that's irreparable damage.
That's kind of fucked up.
So there's a threshold beyond which physical violence
is always worse.
I mean, physical violence just aren't usually observable.
The small stuff is like, if a kid shoves another kid,
the kid who shoved should not get sent home,
and then the bully who was teasing him
should get off scot-free.
That's basically what I'm getting at.
Which is why I think they generally
write up both kids whenever there's a fight,
no matter who started it.
That's why I got sent home, and suspended
for getting punched in the face.
Classic tale.
You shouldn't have had such a punchable face their time.
It's your one mistake.
Big and ugly, and I was just asking for it.
What can I say?
It's right.
Teachers had been just clamoring for an excuse
to write you a pink slip and send you home today.
And he got punched perfect.
Now we can insult him as an injury.
I don't know.
I didn't have to do homework for three days.
It was fine.
That was a good decision.
I was glad I was able to generally articulate the point.
That's an interesting topic.
I just think the problem is that just to cap it off
is that we, as a society, do undervalue or don't put
enough weight on mental stress and emotional abuse.
But the reason we don't, and the reason it's such a problem,
is that we're all emotionally weak,
and our culture makes us emotionally weak.
And so the way to fix emotional bullying
is to strengthen everybody, to not be such a little bitch,
because we're all little bitches when it comes to our fee
fees.
And that's bullshit.
And we regularly, based on the least resilient people.
I don't even know how we would possibly do that.
Yeah, yeah, because I mean, and of course we do,
because it makes sense.
Those are the people who need protection.
But then the whole system caters to them,
and is that necessarily?
Then we get all this padding on everything.
And so people don't have as much opportunity
to build up resilience.
I heard a summary that apparently this
is true, that in the wake of Trump getting elected,
there were actually a large number of millennials suffering.
This is not a joke, actual, real symptoms of PTSD,
just from Trump getting elected.
I think I know some of them.
Oh yeah?
And I mean, you look at the world, it's like, OK,
things seem OK.
Like I know people who have mentally gone downhill
since the election of Trump.
I was actually assaulted by one of those people.
But I guess I shouldn't think of it.
Oh yeah, the subject of what?
Oh, that was when you were like, you
had a joke where Trump's a party.
On the subject of what happens when you stand up to bullying,
yeah, I went to a costume party, a Halloween party,
like around the time that it was 2016.
And I didn't really have a costume.
So I thought, oh, it'd be funny if I
went as a Trump guy, right?
So I put on the Make America a Great Again hat,
and I put on a denim jacket.
And I went around like, I'm a Trump guy.
Well, it was a party with a lot of young, early 20s women
who don't like the Trumper.
So a lot of them.
They can't bump to that Trump.
I got a lot of nasty looks.
And I got a lot of people yelling at me
to fuck off just for being there.
This one girl who was very drunk.
You would have gotten less attacked
if you'd literally gone to this costume party as a Nazi.
You would have been more beloved.
There was this one drunk girl who came up to me
and started pushing me and putting her hands on me
and hitting me and trying to scratch at me.
And I kept trying to push her off of me.
And I finally said, if you put your hands on me one more time,
I'm going to hit you back.
And she is like, oh, yeah, fucking.
And to test me, she does it again.
And I just fucking, I fucking hit her.
And you would have thought that I shot a puppy.
Like the entire party stops.
Everyone, it instantly became the most chaos I've ever seen.
The whole party descended on me.
Like three guys bum rushed me out of nowhere.
And like, I suddenly, I'm fighting three guys,
like a fucking Jackie Chan movie.
And the whole time that I'm fighting three guys,
she's also like pulling my hair
because I had long hair back then.
She's pulling my hair.
She's scratching me, screaming at me.
All these guys who like don't know what happened at all.
They don't know the situation.
All they know is that.
All they saw was that a girl got hit by a guy
and they were like, well, this will be a fucking night.
So they got a fucking white night and they got to come up
and I fucking, I fucking, there was,
I'm proud of this though.
Cause there was one guy who like dressed as,
there's this guy who like,
I think runs for president every year.
One of those crazy homeless people who like wears a boot
on his head.
I don't remember his name,
but his thing is that he wears a boot on his head.
And there was like a guy dressed up on a ass
and with a fake beard and a boot on his head.
And like, at some point in the fracas,
in the melee, in the brawl,
in the other fucking Smash Brothers words,
I fucking, at some point I threw a perfect uppercut.
And it was like, it was like a shuriyuken that,
and like I connected with this guy.
I was gonna say, did you say shuriyuken?
I knocked his fucking boot off his head
and his fucking, his fake, his fake beard went flying one way.
The boot flew the other way.
He like, he like went up in the air and fucking,
like I'm not saying that I'm like,
that I killed all three guys,
but I fucking connected with that uppercut
and that fucking boot motherfucker went flying.
And it was beautiful.
But yeah, I like, it was literally,
I started a riot by wearing a costume to a Halloween party.
I mean, I can see,
I can see how every step of that story progress
and why it progressed the way it did.
Here's the frustrating thing.
Here's what, here's why like,
you like, yeah, you told that girl like,
don't assault me or I'm gonna hit you.
She assaulted you and you hit her.
I don't think that was wrong.
But here's the frustrating part
and why the cycle of violence is a problem.
Like, justified or not,
you know that girl's story is.
Oh yeah.
A crazy MAGA Trump guy hit me at a possible.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
But you know what?
And that's the story she'll repeat for the rest of her life.
You know what makes it worth it though,
is that I heard the next morning
from my friend who's house it was at the party
that she drove home drunk and crashed her car.
Holy fuck.
So.
Not into any innocent people.
No, just into like a tree or a pole or something.
But yeah, fuck her.
Oh, but you fucking know.
This was only due to the severe concussion
delivered upon her by a vicious Trump supporter.
This was due to the PTSD,
the flash that you gave her flashbacks.
And she was like, she had to jump in that car and drive
because Charlie was in the fucking tree.
She had to escape.
There was an agent orange was closing in on her.
She had to fucking escape the car.
The true agent orange himself.
Oh my God.
It was full.
Yeah, she wrecked her car that night
and like ran away from the accident
and got picked up by the police later and got arrested.
So I win, I guess.
I guess at the end of the day.
She couldn't trump the stump
as she fucking ran into a tree.
It's true.
Oh fuck.
It's just, it's so,
there's no way to fix this problem
that people just read into situations
what they want to get out of it.
That's just what we all do and I don't know.
I just really like the imagery
of like a brawl at a Halloween party.
Yeah.
Like the scary people.
Yeah, all the ghosts and ghouls come out.
I was fighting off goblins.
Like that would be in like a Jackie Chan movie
or in some like hilarious movie.
Or like a Ninja Turtles movie.
Yeah.
You get the Casey Jones mask
and you got all the ninjas coming out.
You have like Freddy versus Jason
but they're like shitty Halloween costume versions
or something, you know.
Jason's costume is a shitty Halloween costume already
but fair point, fair point.
That's true.
Damn, that was a good story.
All right, well good.
Yeah.
Let's, let's.
Don't know what the answer is though.
There is no answer.
Don't know if we've, don't know if we've learned them.
I think we didn't find an answer.
It's kind of a funny story to fix.
That's the most, that's the best we can do.
You can't really fix human nature.
People are gonna want to punch each other.
There's a reason why philosophers have not cracked this code
over the, you know, thousands of years
of human civilization.
Cause it comes down to human fucking nature
as long as that's the same.
As long as people are selfish, willfully ignorant
and, you know, form teams, which we all do
and basically always will do,
this will continue to be a problem.
And social media has just made it that much easier.
So, you know, there's no fix in it.
It's unfortunate cause like I like being in a team
as in like people I like and like people
who I respect and trust.
Like, like I like being in that the team of people I like.
But the reason I like that is because there's a possibility
that there are people who are, you know,
like if we were all robots,
we would all be self-sufficient,
but we would have no friends.
And it would be like, eh, you know, as a human,
I kind of don't want to live in a world where I'm by myself.
Yeah, it sucks.
But it sucks.
Can't help that.
Oh, just as an addendum,
I looked up to clarify the name of the costume
the guy was wearing with the boot on his head.
The guy's name, so everyone knows
I'm not making this story up.
Is it Slavo, is it Slavo?
It's, no, his name is Vermin Supreme.
Oh, oh yeah, yeah, Vermin Supreme.
That's the guy who's dressed up as a doctor.
Yeah, I have heard of that.
Yeah.
I'm very proud of myself.
Oh, that's fucking sick.
All right, well, how about we get
to those fucking voicemails now, gentlemen?
Yeah, I think it's about time.
All right, let's do it.
We're closing in on two hours.
Okay, let's see.
How many do we have today?
We got 10, we got 10 here.
Oh, I know, I know.
Oh, and after the whole thing went down,
one of the guys who had jumped me in that fucking fracas
after it was all dying down
and everyone was trying to separate everyone
and it was one of the guys did that insufferable thing
that guys do where after a fight,
they try to shake hands and apologize
and I was having none of it.
I fucking looked at that guy
the same way I looked at that fucking dog.
I just gave him the look.
I gave him that, that Enlip G look of.
The conqueror's eyes.
Yeah, you should take your fucking hand out
to shake it, fuck you, buddy.
And I'd fucking said, fuck you and suck my dick
and I walked away and there you go.
And he sat there with his hand out
like a fucking goofball.
Oh yeah, I'm surprised it ended.
I mean, so relatively amicably,
like people were still able to like shake hands
instead of like the whole thing
just floating off and floating out.
Well, they tried, but I didn't shake their fucking hands.
Right, they tried to make it amicable,
but I was like oh hell no.
The only thing to do with me
is to fucking flee from this fracas and never return.
Does that mean they recognize their mistake at the end?
I think it's just like a self-defense mechanism.
Like they wanna be able to say,
well, I try, you know, I was a good guy at the end.
I don't know if they recognize their mistake
or if they just because my fucking boy,
butt chugger Cody LaRue came out
and fucking yelled at him because it was his house.
Oh, okay.
So, you know, you don't wanna incur the wrath
of the fucking butt chug, man.
He'll,
No sir.
He'll dunk your fucking head in the butt juice.
And there was a tub of butt juice at the party.
He fucking, it was one of those like when people make
the big alcohol concoctions with the fruit in them,
but it was labeled butt juice.
He'll fucking dunk it in there.
It's fucking sick.
I'm sorry, I just keep uncovering layers
to this fucking story.
No, it's good, this is good.
This is a tasty onion.
I just want more layers.
All right, let's visit in with our friend,
Racist Forest Gump.
Once again today,
he's got another message for us that we need to hear.
He's becoming a member.
Sure.
Yeah, basically.
Jenae.
I got a pile of Jenae.
Oh no.
What is it, Forest?
What is it?
Jenae.
The SJW Neo-Marx's, they found it.
What did they find?
What did they find, Forest?
They found, they doxxed me, Jenae.
They did, but they took my balls.
I was a racist.
They got it coming after me, Jenae.
No, Forest, that's horrible.
What are you gonna do?
I don't know, Jenae.
They outside my door with pitchforks.
With pitchforks.
What am I gonna do, Jenae?
You gotta run, Forest.
Run, Forest, run!
I just love hearing from racist Forest Gump
so much every week.
That is the perfect end to that arc.
He began the cycle a while ago,
but he wasn't prepared to finish it.
What's the, oh, fuckin', what's the Twitter alternative?
Gab.
People that could ban from Twitter.
Yeah, yeah, he better make a Gab account.
That's the only way, it's the only way.
Poor racist Forest Gump.
He didn't do nothing wrong, except for the racism.
Except for being racist, yeah.
All right, next call, we got...
He's defining characteristics.
The PCP Medical Consultant is calling in
with some updates for us.
Tell us how we're working.
Okay, look, look.
As a fuckin' six year medical student
listening to this podcast, I'm so fuckin' angry.
In episode 134, you are saying that
the goldbladder secretes bile.
It stores bile, fuckin' ass idiots.
Sorry, I'm sorry.
It stores bile.
Doesn't digest fiber.
Fiber is indigestible.
Fuck.
Oh my God.
I knew that.
Please, you are the reason people are dying.
Okay, okay.
I'm pretty sure that I corrected the appendix thing,
but yeah, I misspoke about the gallbladder.
I'm sorry.
That's where the pee is stored, as I recall.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, in the test,
the gallbladder's in the testicle,
and it stores the pee.
It's filled with piss.
That's why women...
Where does bile come from?
Okay, the gallbladder stores bile.
I don't know.
Where does the bile come from?
It's made in China.
It's the pancreas.
Is it the spleen?
It might be the spleen, actually.
It's the brain.
It's gonna come back, even matter.
Oh, it's all...
The brain is full of bile.
My brain is where you get all the skeleton from.
Perception is reality,
so it all comes from the brain anyway.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's true.
Okay.
All right, well, we're the reason people are dying.
Sorry about that, dude.
Thanks for calling in.
Let us know if we fuck anything else up.
Okay.
Yeah.
We're the reason people are dying.
If it wasn't for us, death would be a non-issue.
That's an tagline for the show,
the Procrastinators podcast,
where the reason people are dying.
Dude, that's really good.
Okay, here's our next call.
This is from Shraft Vortex.
Shraft Vortex.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I've been killing Rowdy's with him.
Oh, really?
Oh, you know?
Once in a while.
Okay, I didn't know.
Okay, let's see what he's got.
Hey, guys, just wanted to ask real quick.
Do you think that everyday situations
have been made to be political,
or do you think that they have always been
and are just talked about in that way way more often now?
Cool.
Discuss.
That's it.
I don't like this question,
because it's too big.
Wait, is he asking why everything is so political?
Though it is?
Yeah, yeah.
Because I said this on one,
but I wasn't recording because I was an idiot,
so I guess I'll reiterate the point that I made the last time
because I thought it was a good point.
I figured out why everything is so fucking political
and horrific nowadays, why you can't get away from it,
why everyone's sucked into the one side versus the other.
It's because you know that fucking guy on your Facebook,
you guys heard this story,
but pretend you're hearing this for the first time.
I'm hearing it for the first time.
You know that guy.
I wasn't listening.
On everyone's friend's list,
who's always posting like I'm depressed,
please someone hang out with me,
I hate my life and I hate myself,
and I'm the person who's always having
like a pity party for themselves on Facebook.
That's me, that's me you're talking about.
Everybody knows that person,
and we feel bad for him for a while,
but nobody wants to be that person.
Nobody wants to go on Facebook all the time
and make themselves into an object of pity
by saying how bad their life is, right?
But everyone feels that way,
and everyone wants, deep down,
everyone wants to go on Facebook
and just let it loose.
I've got problems and here are my problems
and I'm lonely and I'm sad and I'm heartbroken
and I'm miserable.
Everyone wants to do that,
but we're all kind of like we have that level of shame
where we don't do it.
So people all day are going around
with this thing inside them
that they just want to express their pain,
but they're embarrassed to.
So they have to latch on to some other way
to express their discontent.
And the most acceptable way to do it
is to latch on to politics
and make all of your problems
because of the opposing team.
So that's why all anyone talks about anymore
is politics and complaining and fighting about politics
because they're just sad.
I do think that you're onto something.
Yeah, it's become maybe a little more in vogue
to be political, I guess,
and a little more socially acceptable
and commonplace to talk about these things publicly.
However, I think that the issues that are politicized
were always political.
It just, they weren't as discussed in the same way.
Is it literally because like, you know,
millennial people who grew up with the internet
as it started are like now adults
and people just use the internet more?
That definitely adds to it, I think.
Yeah, because like...
Like now it's so easy to bump the ideologies
with different people because of Twitter and stuff.
Yeah, like it's weird to think
because internet has already, you know,
it's been around for a while
and people have been on it talking about political stuff
for a while, but it does feel like in recent years
that it's just more.
And I guess it could just be that Trump was a big upset,
like, oh, who saw that coming?
Like it was, it's not just a new politician
doing the same old shit.
It's someone that's like,
you get good boy points for saying the politicians are bad
and then suddenly once you get good boy points
for saying the politicians are bad,
now you want to talk about politics more.
Once you get one good boy point, it's a slippery slope.
You just crave more and more.
It's just way easier and way less vulnerable
to be outraged about like what the president is doing
or what insert political group here is doing
than it is to be like openly sad and asking for comfort
and help because your life sucks.
Yeah, yeah.
There's something to that.
Yeah, it's a good point.
Yeah, if you can just add your personal issues
onto political problems
and then you can talk about it guilt-free.
Yeah, exactly.
This is why.
And that's the other thing, like why I can't really,
why I, like people use the term centrist a lot.
I don't really believe that that's a thing.
I think it's kind of a straw man.
Like people's idea of like a person who is neutral,
I guess, is that they just think that like,
both sides are wrong about everything.
I don't think that at all.
I think that both sides are right about most things.
I think that every, and this is the reason
why I don't get invested too much in political issues
is because everyone feels the way they do for a reason.
Something fucking happened to them.
When someone is outraged about like Trump
and is saying that like all Trump supporters
must be rapists or like misogynists,
like yeah, you can say that that person is crazy,
but something fucking happened to that person,
to make them feel that way.
So you-
Some crazy guy punched her for no reason
in the Halloween party.
Like during the Brett Kavanaugh thing,
like I was pretty not into how it seemed like
there were a lot of pretty baseless accusations
being made, but like, of course people
who like had any kind of personal experience
are gonna be like, no, no, no, no, no, no,
we're gonna fucking air on the side of caution,
just as there's even a fucking hint
that there was some impropriety.
No, this man is clearly not, you know, and then-
Yeah, like I get it, like no issue is really
about the issue, like the Kavanaugh thing.
I don't even know what it is or what it is.
I'm assuming he like did something at a party,
like raped someone, I don't fucking know.
That's the accusation, yeah.
Like the issue that people are arguing about
isn't really about him, that guy,
it's about there's people who have been sexually assaulted,
who feel one way and there's people
who have been falsely accused of being like sexual predators
who feel another way and like they're arguing
from their own experiences.
The guy, Kavanaugh, doesn't fucking matter,
he's nobody, but people are saying,
this happened to me, well this happened to me,
so fuck you and we have to fight about it.
Yeah, and then everyone else falls into like,
oh, I hope that doesn't happen to me or like,
I'm afraid that might happen to me
and then they fall on one side of the thing.
So it's not both sides are wrong,
it's both sides are right, the world is really fucked up
and it's fucked up in so many like interconnected,
convoluted, criss-crossing ways
that like everybody can be right
in how they perceive the problems in our society.
Because it's all happening,
all the bad stuff is happening all the time to everyone,
every bad thing you could possibly imagine
it's happening to everyone.
That's true, that's what I said before,
like to every side, the other side is,
they're correctly being identified as evil
because they don't share their values
which makes them evil in their mind
and that's it, you can't argue with that, that's there.
I'm interested in like, why happy things,
like good things happening is just uninteresting as news.
Because anger is a stronger, like it's our,
there was a thing about how anger is the most vulnerable.
Yeah, but why is it a stronger?
Why is anger stronger?
Disasters happen fast, like good things happen gradually.
I think the reason why Gib
ties into probably like biology really,
cause like, if there's something good happens
to like your tribe of like a hundred Neanderthals,
like, oh good, my son was born, hooray,
whereas, oh no, we're being invaded by the enemy,
we're all going to be wiped out,
like that's gonna trigger like a stronger.
We need to be, yeah.
That's just a guess.
I agree with what Ben said too,
that was a good point about how like,
bad things happen fast and good things happen gradually.
Like there's no nice equivalent of a school shooting
where like someone comes into school in a trench coat
and starts hugging everybody, like that never happens.
That's not everything that's true.
Yeah, I mean, all the positive news stories you read,
like they're either boring, like, oh yeah,
that bill that was in town hall election, it got passed,
we did it, like that's boring.
Like you never see a volcano.
Or it's something dumb, like, oh hey,
the fucking Christmas parades in town,
and Santa this year is-
Oh, there's a cat who's a mayor of a town,
like it's next to you, right?
You never see a volcano erupt with doughnut sprinkles
and confetti.
Yeah, yeah, oh shit.
It's always lava, for some fucked up reason,
I don't know why.
Yeah, it is, it's always,
there's some reason it's always lava.
It's like trying something new for once.
It's always metaphorical lava.
He's doing video games, what the fuck, no.
You know, actually in Mario Odyssey,
there's a volcano full of like, gravy or shit.
Okay, all right.
This is why, left or right,
I don't think it makes sense to tie them into good and evil.
But I do kind of think you can link good and evil
to the top and bottom of this two A,
which is authoritarian versus libertarian.
Because I just think that the solution to all these problems
is for everyone to be self-sufficient,
not worry about what other fucking people are doing,
and just mind their own goddamn business.
I think that is just the best way to be.
Stop telling me what to do.
If everyone did that.
Like, let the racist be racist.
It would probably be good.
Who gives a fuck?
Because I got my shit going just fine over here,
they have no influence on me,
and those people can feel the same way
about these trans-degenerate, you know,
whatever's on the other side.
I mean, I mean, it's just,
if you let the racist be racist,
then they vote for fucking-
It's only a problem, it's only a problem.
If then authoritarianism comes back,
and they have leverage over the people.
Which they will vote to make happen.
I don't know, well, that's why I'm saying
that libertarianism is the good.
That is the way to be,
so that people don't have this shit hanging over them,
and there's no threat to anyone.
That's whatever.
I know that's idealistic and not practical,
but I'm just saying, that's what I've ever seen.
I gotcha.
How many fucking voicemails do we have?
We got seven more.
Like, four, like, oh boy.
We don't have to do them all that long, let's go.
Okay, next one, this is from Cholo Jones.
Let's see what he's got for us.
You know, I have a real problem with people just saying,
they're so irresponsible, they can't do anything.
They all just need to get a responsibility board,
get just a fucking white board or a cork board,
and stop being so gay,
and just write down all the things you get done.
And if you don't accomplish them,
you'll have something right there
to remind you of what a failure are.
You should get off your ass.
Also, I have a problem with,
did you think that animals just shouldn't exist?
You won't find that sympathy here.
Pokemon that are, like, you know,
just not quite as cool, because they're like the same thing.
You know, animals are Pokemon, is my point.
No, dude.
Did you use a known Pokemon, Robert?
You don't wanna collect all the animals.
Can you imagine how hellish that would be?
I'm gonna come down hard on the didgy side
of this today, animals against them.
I mean, me and, I'm with Carl Pilkington,
who thinks that animals are redundant,
and most of them probably don't need to exist.
Like, how many slow insects do you need?
Like, yeah, we've got the snail and the inchworm.
Like, what do we need both for?
They do the same thing.
You're not wrong, you're not wrong.
Shit, did I title this one wrong?
Oh, no, sorry, I've got the next one open.
Yeah, I like animals, so I'm on this guy's side.
They're cool, you know, mostly dogs.
Don't really care about the other ones.
I like me some chicken wings.
Agreed.
All right, let's just move on to the next one.
All right, let's fuck this whole gay shit.
All right, here we go, play.
This is from Free Patreon Money.
Oh my God.
I like this call already.
Answer this one.
Here we go.
All right, I have the deal of a fucking lifetime right here.
Sounds like monthly.
This is the epic deal.
I thought it was monthly for a second.
I like this girl, I like her a lot,
and we talk sometimes, we're friends.
And I wanna be her girlfriend, I wanna date her.
So give me some advice,
and if she becomes my girlfriend,
then this is what you receive.
You get Patreon donations galore.
I'll donate lots of money to every single Patreon
for the everything, all the links that are in the description.
This is one of her other links that exists.
I'll get all of the money,
and I'll do it real good.
Just give me some advice.
I want this girl so bad.
Okay, I know exactly what to do.
I know the answer to this.
So like, okay, she's a girl,
she's your friend, and you really wanna be with her.
And you don't know how to, here's what you do.
You don't, you fucking, you sneak it in a little bit.
You fuck, like a little bit at a time.
Like you just kind of, you know,
you're hanging out with her like normal,
and you're laughing and you're joking.
You're being cool, you're being your regular cool self,
like nothing's different.
And then like, you sort of slip in,
like you look nice, or you look,
you look, your hair is nice today,
or something that she'll like notice, you know?
Yeah, just to acclimate her to the idea
of seeing you as a sexual being.
You've gotta, you've gotta like,
and when you finally do like sort of pop the question,
like hey, you wanna kind of like be together,
like a fucking like you and me, and like a romantic thing.
You gotta say it, you gotta be casual about it,
and if she's not cool with it, and she's not okay with it,
you gotta act like it didn't even really matter to you.
It was just a dumb stray thought in your head,
and just drop it, and then like,
you maybe ask it again like six months,
but you know, if, whenever she rejects you,
just act like it doesn't even fucking matter,
and it's just dumb, because if you say to her,
all of a sudden, I'm in love with you,
and we really have to be together,
and I want you to be my girlfriend,
and I want to be in love with you forever,
that's, you're gonna be in a bad situation,
if you fucking do that.
You won't want that, you won't want that.
Don't do it, yeah.
And especially if you do that, and she says no,
and then you take it like, hard,
then here, you're really in trouble if you take it hard.
That's a bad look.
That's true.
Ask yourself this question,
and you have to be honest about this.
It's, am I, do I, am I willing to risk my friendship
with this person to date them,
or to phrase it another way,
it's like, is this person's friendship important enough
to me to not jeopardize the date?
It's like, do you want this person as a friend,
or do you really just want to date them,
and you're kind of just killing time
until you can get them to date you?
Yeah.
If you really want to date them,
and you're just being friends with them in the meantime,
like as the stopgap measures,
you should just go ahead and fuck you up.
The question you've got to ask is if they were a dude,
would you still be hanging out with them?
And if the answer is no, you're fooling yourself.
You just got to pretend to be really totally confident,
and just be like, yeah, agreed.
Hey, I want to go out with you, how about that, huh?
What, no?
It doesn't matter.
I'm just being cool, whatever, baby.
I'm just being cool.
Yeah, exactly that.
Write that down and practice it in the mirror.
Hey, guys, I'm just being cool.
Hey, hey, hey, I'm not trying to be weird here,
and I'm just being cool,
but I thought maybe it all in you and me,
and I'm just being cool.
Here's the thing, here's the thing.
On some level, I think that that might actually work,
because humans are very weak and susceptible,
and I think that if you insist that you are cool enough,
I think that some people will come to believe it.
It's all confidence.
Yeah, confidence is just a repeat.
You need to have the volume as well.
If you just repeat the association,
just repeat the association.
Me, cool.
Wait, what?
It gives it how long to be assertive and confident.
Oh, yeah, yeah, it's like me, cool.
Every time I've tried to be cool in that way,
people associate you with coolness.
Yeah, I've attempted little things like that.
But that's how advertising works.
I've attempted little things like that before,
but it has come always down to the fact
that I have a small, meek voice,
and it doesn't work, no matter what I say.
People, girls, and...
I have to be louder in order for people to give it to me.
Some people would find it cheesy and make fun of you,
but I guarantee you at least some people
would begin to associate you with being cool.
Well, it was like that time,
I think that's interesting.
That blessed interaction I had in line
to get into the food court or whatever at college,
when I was talking to my friends about,
I can't remember what it was,
something about like, I don't know,
I think making out, I think it was unrelated,
but whatever we had said,
the guy in front of us in line interpreted as this.
And he's like, turns out, I was like,
whoa, you guys do that too?
Just go up to girls at parties and ask them to make out?
One of them's gonna say yes,
and the thing is, he's right.
The thing is, he's right.
And I love that, man, he's a brother.
I mean, the drunk ones probably.
Yeah, well, I mean, what's your goal here?
Is your goal just to make out?
And that gets, sure, go for it.
If your goal is to form a relationship,
this might not be the best way to do it, or whatever.
What if you go up to every girl,
he's like asking them to make out,
forgetting that you are wearing your Trump hat,
and all of them attack you?
They'll say, I'll tell you what you do.
I'll tell you what you do.
Just go, hey, baby, I'm just being cool.
I'm just being cool.
I'm just being cool, I'm just being cool.
You're in New York City, walking down a lot of traffic.
Hey, I'm being cool here.
You just turn your cap backwards,
and they can't see they're making America great again,
and it's just really cool.
You come out of the voting booth,
just fresh after voting for Trump and your MAGA hat,
and you get mobbed, you get mobbed by SJW cucks,
and they're like, hey, man, I'm just being cool, guys.
I'm just trying to be cool here.
They think you're a Trumper seeing the front of your hat,
but you just, you turn your hat backwards,
and it's like, oh, he's just being cool.
He's just being cool.
He's in the backwards.
That's cool.
Now, that's what Trump himself should do.
He should get out of the podium.
Lib Tards hate this one weird old tip to just be cool.
Turn your hat on that MAGA hat.
Trump should give a speech next time,
like the whole nation is mad at him
for something that he did.
He should just be like, hey, I'm just being cool.
I don't know, I'm just trying to be cool.
Look, America, I'm just trying to be cool here.
I like, like, instead of saying I'm trying to be cool,
just to say I am being cool, I'm just being right.
Like, the declaration is part of why it's so serious.
I'm just being cool.
Look, I'm just being cool.
I'm not being an asshole.
I'm just being cool.
It's on the news.
It turns out President Trump is cool.
I swear, I swear it'll work.
Yeah, at last.
The human brain is simple enough.
He skates skateboard onto the podium.
I believe that the human brain is simple enough
that that would work and have its desired effect.
Yeah, I think so too.
I think so too.
I'm just being cool.
Did you guys see that guy?
There was a Democratic challenger to Ted Cruz
in Running for Senate during the election,
who like, Beto O'Rourke, that was him.
He literally skateboarded out, I think, multiple times
to the podium to, I think he's the genesis point
of this whole just be and cool thing.
It didn't work though when he lost.
I mean, people have been, well, it wasn't that cool.
Yeah, it wasn't cool enough.
Wasn't wearing a backwards hat.
People have been being cool since the beginning of time.
All right, let's move on to our next question here.
This is from Been There Since Day One.
What's the name of this guy?
All right, let's see.
Oh boohoo, I'm a Gen 1 PCB watcher
and I want the original theme back.
Yeah, me too, dawg.
Yeah.
Welcome to this show.
I want to do it.
Is this the same guy who did the megalovania
because he's good on piano?
Yeah.
Man, you know, every once in a while,
I remember that I put together some fucking dumb piano loop
that people cover and it fills me with the weirdest ride.
It's nice.
So, you know, I mean, not to poke holes in your story,
Mr. Been There Since Day One,
you know, we didn't have the theme song in the beginning.
Oh, Christ.
That was like 50, what was that, like 50 episodes in,
that we got that?
Maybe like, maybe not that.
Something like that, maybe 20, 30, I don't know.
Well, I do, I like, yeah, I don't understand people
that whine about the old theme.
I mean, I like the old theme song.
The new theme song incorporates it.
You know, maybe you liked the runner up better.
You know, I'm sorry.
I guess they could just think it straight up just sounds better.
I suppose that's fair.
I don't know.
You know, I think it's kind of funny how divisive.
I think maybe that makes me like it more,
just how divisive the...
I kind of agree too.
I will continue to use the runner up every time I edit.
That's fine.
That's fair enough.
Fair enough.
I am the rebel.
All right.
Join my team.
Join my tribe.
Next one.
This is from Mookies.
Mookies.
Speak.
Okay, Tom, I know you're there.
You're on every single episode.
You need the money.
I know you're a poor boy.
I love you.
Now, a long time ago, you promised that you'd be making a Splatoon 2 I Am Games video.
Where is it?
I need it.
Splatoon 2 is the best game on Switch.
Mario Odyssey?
Dog shit.
Breath of the Wild?
Okay.
Octopath?
Really fucking fun.
Fucking Pokemon Let's Go?
Meh.
Probably not worth $60, but fucking Splatoon 2 is the Switch.
It is everything.
It is the best.
I need that video.
Make it now.
Thank you.
I'm on your friends list on Pokemon Go and the nicknames, like the puns you give your
Pokemon, your buddy Pokemon, they're funny.
I love them and I love you.
Okay.
Bye.
Whoa.
Thank you.
I have something to say about Pokemon Go.
I don't know when else I'll get a chance to say this, but you know who I'm friends with
on Pokemon Go is none other than Russell.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
And he is decked out in Gengar Atalia.
He is all Gengar all the time.
He's real fucking scary.
So Tom, how about it?
Yeah, I'll get to it at some point.
There was a while when I was, I planned on doing it like God, like months ago, but then
I, they brought Nintendo Switch online, the online service up and I didn't have it.
So I'm like, well, I can't even play Splatoon 2 anymore.
Fuck.
But then someone generously gave me access to their family plan thing.
So now I have it again.
So I have like notes for a script kind of written up.
The idea is just like, it's the most comfortable multiplayer game ever and it's not gay and
it's fun.
And it doesn't make you feel like shit when you lose because it's just happy and good
and all the aesthetic and everything like, like, like the lobby just like, like you,
you go and do these fights and everything and then like go back to the lobby and everything's
kind of chill and everyone's just hanging out.
Like all the people you were just fighting just like populate the lobby and it's like
kind of reminds you it's just a game.
It's fun.
Don't, don't get mad.
It's not worth it.
Like you don't, it's just better.
It's the best.
It's fun.
It's comfy.
It's great.
And it began and ended multiplayer gaming.
Splatoon 2 was the Alpha and the Omega and it's great.
So there you go.
There's a Cliff Notes version, dude.
I got you.
I feel you on that.
Did you play the DLC?
You don't have the DLC yet.
I just want to go on record.
I beat the main game and I beat the DLC recently and I beat all 80 levels in the DLC and I'm
on the secret super duper uber final boss and it's so fucking frustrating.
It's a piece of, Splatoon kind of has terrible controls and I kind of hate everything about
how you play that game.
Oh, it was great up to this secret boss and now it's shit and I'm mad.
Your problem is you're playing a single player Splatoon 2.
Why would you do that?
I know.
I've never touched the campaign.
I don't even care about the multiplayer.
You don't care about the multiplayer.
Oh my god.
No, no, no.
The campaign is great.
I love the campaign.
Splatoon is worth it just for the single player for me personally.
The single player in Splatoon 1 was pretty fun, but I mean the game's about the multiplayer.
I literally don't care about the multiplayer.
I can't use the ink brush in the campaign.
It gives me the guns and I don't want to use the gun.
I want to use the ink brush because that's fun.
Well, in the DLC.
I want to use the roller.
Yeah, I want to use the bus story, the lore, the song at the end of the fucking DLC.
Can you beat it?
I played through the whole game.
The main story is about Marie and Callie.
Marie's disappeared.
I think that's her.
Callie disappeared.
No, Callie disappeared.
Yes, that's right.
I'm gonna play this and I know it more than you.
I just forget the names.
That's it.
The new Squid Girls or whatever, the black one and the little one.
I forget their fucking name.
Pearl and Marina.
Yeah.
You don't know anything about them, but the DLC gives them character and fleshes them out.
They like them now and they got cool songs and they're cool guys and the levels are fun
and it was a real challenge to beat it.
And this final fucking boss is just so fuck.
I hate Splatoon's combat system so much despite everything I just said.
It's shit.
It's a multiplayer game.
It's not designed for what you're doing.
I want 100% believe everything you just said, but are you telling me that you don't play
the multiplayer?
Like every once in a while I will fire it up for a little bit, but I weigh disproportionately
more enjoy to the single player than I enjoy the multiplayer every once in a while.
Incredible.
Which is just because I love the single player so much.
It's got so much style.
It's got so much personality.
I mean that oozes in every facet of Splatoon.
Sure.
Splatoon is aesthetically.
Yeah.
The aesthetic is unbelievable.
I love it so much.
It's so, it's perfect.
It is perfect.
The whole, the urban, the hip, the hip urban youth culture.
It's great.
Shit.
I cannot wait to play as Inkling.
The neon, the neon colors.
My one upset thing is that Inkling is in Splatoon, is in Smash, New Smash, but that
Octobitch is not like a, you know, not a costume.
Like an alternate costume.
I mean they could make it a fucking Echo Fighter I guess, but just make it a costume.
I just want the costume.
That's all I care about.
Because Octolingirl is an 8 out of 8 and I love her.
Agent 8.
That's her name.
Basically the second.
No.
Her hairstyle being different.
They just have different hair.
And her different eye makeup.
It's a huge difference.
Okay.
But anyway.
All right.
Fine.
Let's move along.
I will beat it though.
I will beat that fucking boss.
It's a piece of shit though.
All right.
Next, next call is from, oh wait.
You know what?
This is from Munchy.
It's this guy.
Enlightened history major.
Just saying how cool Munchy is for being in history.
I'm just going to skip that one since he's not here.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's go to the next one.
This is from, here we go.
This is a good one.
This PCP fan is calling in to update us on his current situation.
I used to be the biggest fan of the PCP.
Every day I would listen to Digi Bro's Toofless, gummy voice echo from my brain.
And when I say fan, I don't mean triple Joker LMFAO.
No, I was deep into that PCP war.
I was here.
Triple Joker's trip pretty deep.
I think that Collins played the role of me app on the world famous web series inanimate
insanity 2.
You're more just a Digi.
I personally find that to be underrated.
And there I say, rad.
Funny joke.
But back to my story.
I had this internet discord GF.
Oh no.
And one day I showed her the PCP.
All of it.
The entire PCP.
No.
Did you tie her up and make her listen?
And she sent me and said that this podcast is shit.
And will never be as real or interesting as the Jill Rogan experience.
Oh come on.
That's not right.
No.
Left me for a red pill to YouTube commentator who makes fun of autistic people for easy money.
And that's when I decided to drop out of school and become my own internet personality.
My own superhero from the depths of the underground internet scene.
And well now I'm homeless.
It didn't work out I guess.
Jinkling change on the sidewalk of Skid Row.
And I blame you.
This is all your fault.
Fuck you.
No, no, no, no.
The only response to this is the procrastinator's podcast.
Where the reason people are dying.
Next call.
Right.
Yeah.
We are.
This guy's not long for this world.
God.
She cut us deep.
Cut us deep with that.
We're not as good as the Joe Rogan experience.
How could we compete with Joe Rogan?
God damn it.
He's got.
I don't know.
He gets interesting guests.
We have too much hair to compete with Joe Rogan unfortunately.
That's true.
He's too powerful.
We can't beat him.
We gotta join a little crowd.
We gotta get Joe Rogan a PCPist.
Clearly.
Can we get.
Here's the idea.
Okay.
Joe Rogan podcast.
Next episode.
It's the entirety of the PCP is the one guest.
Oh, and every word is spoken by a different member in a circular order.
That'd be good.
Let's make that happen.
Oh, like the kids from code name kids next door.
Oh, yeah.
The lovely children from down the lane or whatever.
The delightful children.
God.
I loved those.
That's the best fucking show code name kids next door.
Literally great.
Literally insane pathos and character development.
The best.
I also remember when Digi was on inanimate insanity too.
What a weird, what a weird time.
Doesn't he still regularly do that voice?
I mean, I don't know when they last did it.
Well, I haven't heard about it in forever, but maybe.
He plays like the, what, like the fucking iMac Pro or something.
I gotta imagine that they wrote like tons and tons of scripts and he probably recorded
lines for way in advance.
Probably.
To the extent that they might still be animating new episodes with like lines that he recorded
like who knows how long ago.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, Joe, I have actually dreamed about Joe Rogan bringing me on the podcast and I'm
just, I think about that and I'm like, I am not interesting enough.
I have nothing to contribute to, to be invited on this podcast.
It's kind of funny how like we're focusing on the Joe Rogan aspect of this guy who's
I do listen to him a lot and blaming us.
Oh, I forgot about his whole girlfriend and his girlfriend ruined his life because we,
not because we were bad, but because we weren't as good as the Joe Rogan experience.
Yeah.
Have me on Joe.
We'll make it happen.
You know what?
This actually makes me actually sad to think that I am not an interesting enough person
to be on Joe Rogan's show.
Well, I was good.
I was just gonna be sad.
Like there's, that's, that's quitter's attitude and like what, why is it low?
Okay.
Well, here's the thing.
I guess that's a good question.
They had MKBHD on Joe Rogan and MKBHD is not exactly an interesting guy.
He just like, dude, he's got tons to talk about.
He just, he just knows about tech.
He just attacks you.
No, listen, listen, there's not, there's nothing interesting.
If there's nothing, like the people, I don't know what kind of guests Joe Rogan or anyone
else gets on.
Like anyone, right?
Yeah.
Like these people are not inherently more interesting.
They do all the same shit as everyone else.
They're only interesting because they have a cloud, you know, which let's be honest is
just an accident.
You know what?
It's just an accident of history.
They're interesting inherently because of their cloud and because people previously know them.
It's not that these people have more interesting experience.
We're gonna try and sweep all this under the rug and be like, Joe Rogan, whatever, Joe Rogan
on a good deal, it's fine.
And then next, the new episode is gonna come out and it's gonna be fucking laserbot on
the Joe Rogan experience and then it's all gonna fall into place.
Damn it, laserbot!
Oh, if Joe Rogan got fucking laserbot, I would fucking kill myself.
You know?
He's mine, damn it, he's mine!
You don't want your ceiling to be the H3 podcast.
You wanna strive for Joe Rogan.
I agree.
Which I think we've pretty, you know, this is maybe a little sad as well.
I think I've settled into a hierarchy of podcasts in my mind.
Number one is Joe Rogan.
And then quite a bit down there is the H3 podcast.
I've never listened to Joe Rogan, by the way.
Just putting that out there.
Yeah.
There's a lot of good stuff.
I don't know.
I recommend it.
It's on the Stone Cold Steve Austin podcast.
Now, there's a goal.
You know what's funny, though?
My years ago, my buddy Doug told me about how great the Joe Rogan podcast was.
It was probably four or five years ago.
And I was like, oh, who the fuck's that guy?
I don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
And now I listen regularly and I'm a huge fan.
I have never once spoken to him about this.
I should do that at some point.
All right.
Anyway, let's move on to that.
And he'll probably be like, oh, you're still listening to Joe Rogan podcast, bro.
I'm moving up in the world.
It's all about Harmontown now.
Yeah, that's true.
These fucking Big Shot podcast, they're fucking, I'm so sick of them.
No, I'm not.
I love them.
I love listening to podcasts.
I'm sick of them being bearded.
I really love Fat Man on Batman.
That's the only thing I hate about them.
I don't know.
It's the Kevin Smith podcast.
Oh, Kevin Smith.
Yeah.
Kevin Smith's, yeah.
I didn't know he was still doing it.
He does it, but now it's a video podcast and he films it.
Way in the past when he had Tara Strong on, and now I liked Tara Strong because of Twilight Sparkle.
No, no, on the Fat Man on Batman had Tara Strong because she does Spat Girl, I think.
And she's also a fucking Harley Quinn.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
She's like every female voice.
He does it now.
Like they film it in like this special bar with like an audience.
So it's like, they're standing up microphones and it's really, really cool.
That's a good thing.
That sounds cool.
I should check it out.
I just want to say for fun that the reason why this is solidified so much in my mind,
it's kind of like an alpha male dominance hierarchy thing that makes me think that Joe
Rogan is so much better than H3, even though H3 is pretty good when I've listened.
It's specifically that H3 had Bill Burr on who's like an equal, a contemporary of Joe
Rogan.
They're both comedians.
And that Bill Burr podcast destroyed Ethan's like status in my mind.
Because he just got so blown over by Bill who was just so, he was like so like not interested
in being there and was just like bulldozing Ethan.
It's so sad.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to like, you know, it was sad.
It's too bad for him.
It's sad seeing the difference between like a top comedian and a top fucking YouTube comedian.
You know, it is.
It's fascinating.
It is fascinating to see that.
I got to see this.
I want to see Ethan square him.
Not because I hate him, but I've never heard of this.
Yeah.
Check it out.
Ethan is, you know, I don't mind Ethan or anything, but he is pretty smug.
Yeah.
I suppose.
I think it would be fun.
Yeah.
It's interesting if nothing else.
It always like, yeah.
It always weirds me out just to think of like, all the comedians are like sort of, like
they all know each other, like all the big, like Joe Rogan and Bill Burr and Dave Chappelle
and Mark Maron and like, they all are like friends somehow because they've all like intersected
in their careers at some point.
It's just a weird thing to think.
I like these like totally different people who are all like huge, like A-list comedians
and show business guys are all fucking.
I kind of, I kind of covet that community of theirs.
It's pretty fucking cool.
And you know, I've thought a little bit about, I mean, I don't know.
I've been thinking about like, okay, where does YouTube go eventually?
You know, maybe it goes somewhere great.
Maybe YouTube is great forever.
The thought has crossed my mind.
Maybe one day I could like literally be a comedian.
I don't even know if that means like a stand-up comedian, but like, you know, something along
those lines.
I really love to do a stand-up night like you did, Jesse.
Yeah.
Just try it out.
Get out there.
I happened to log on to Reddit the other day on the comedy and someone had posted in the
comedy my bit on meeting women that I did.
Dude, no way.
Yeah, that's dope.
I watched it again.
I watched it back for the first time in years and like I was like blown away because like
I forgot that I did that and that it was so funny.
Like I think back to it like, you know, people tell me it's funny, but like there's no way.
Like I didn't have any planned material.
I fucking, I made up the whole bit like sitting in the audience before I came on stage like
ignoring everyone else's bit while I was like writing it in my head in my seat.
Like Cody looked over at me and he's like, are you like, okay, are you sick?
Cause I was like, I was like so in my own head like, like formulating what I was going
to say for the next 10 minutes.
So like I didn't, I never remember it.
I never like think of it as some like great thing that I'm proud of, but like I was watching
it the other day cause someone had linked it on Reddit and I was like, yes, this is fucking
one of the best things I've ever done and I'm really proud of it and like I want so
bad to do more of that and like I want to elevate myself beyond the, this muck of YouTube
because like it really seems like because of a lot of what gets popular on YouTube and
people are wise to the fact that most big YouTubers are kind of talentless narcissists.
I mean, let's be honest.
I mean, you know, I know what you mean, but I mean, like you've got, you know, like your
Logan Paul's like it's always in the news and that's what people think of when they
think of a YouTuber.
So like there's this like huge YouTuber stigma.
Like even if you're really talented and really funny and really good, if you're doing it
on YouTube, people just think less of you.
And like I think about that, um, that, uh, that guy, Jordan Peterson, who's like always
in the news and like he's always, you know, on everyone's big podcasts, he's like a big
deal now.
And like, yeah, he's a, he, he, people take him seriously because he's a psychologist
and he's like a doctor.
He went to like a real school, but like, but he's also a YouTuber.
So like it really makes you realize that you have to go do something in the real world
in order to carry that clout over to YouTube because YouTube alone has no clout because
of the stuff that's risen to the surface on it.
So people just like, you have to go out and be a real standup comedian or be a, or go
to college to be a real doctor to be taken seriously as a, on YouTube at all.
I know what you mean.
There, there's definitely something to that.
If you, if you, I mean, if YouTube's all you do, then what is there to you?
And it sucks because like, like, it's hard when, cause like to think that in a lot of
people's minds, you're just a YouTuber because YouTuber is YouTube is all you do.
But like in my mind, I never think of myself as a YouTuber.
I think of myself as like a songwriter and a rapper and a comedian and a director and
a fucking this guy and this guy and like all these different things I do.
And like, where the fuck else am I supposed to post that shit?
Like I, I don't really have much opportunity to post my work anywhere but YouTube.
So I have to live with this fucking YouTube stigma.
Well, it's, it's like the part of the problem is not just that normal people who don't really
look at YouTube, hear about what YouTube is in the news and they have a stigma is that
YouTubers don't like care about quality in their own community necessarily.
Like if you want to get a good, a big podcast, you bring on other YouTubers and other people
who are big, not necessarily because you're a big fan of them, but because you need the
views and you need to-
Yeah, cause like the primary focus is not to like necessarily like, like a fucking direct
like a Stanley Kubrick exaggerating example, but whatever.
Like his goals, make the best movie possible.
The goal of like a YouTuber is play the algorithm is make them, the goal, yeah, the goal of
YouTubers make the most.
Yeah.
And that's, that's a bad incentive.
I don't like that.
Yeah.
If, if, if we were incentivized to like, to collaborate between like the best of the
best and like quality was like more at the forefront, then YouTubers would like at least
within themselves have some sort of cloud and like as more people grow up with YouTube,
understand that YouTubers are not inherently, you know, terrible and the stigma would eventually
fade away.
And this goes to Tom's, to Tom's like proposed platform of like you can only post one video
per month on that platform, which means it better be the best possible video it can be
to, you know, get-
There's a, there's a term that is like, that has risen in popularity that everyone uses
now that drives me crazy and like makes me like a little bit frustrated every time I
hear it.
And it's sound cloud rapper because when people talk about like popular rappers or rappers
who are, you know, coming up, they, they always say the term with so much derision, like it's
so much lower.
Like, oh, one of these fucking sound cloud rappers, well, what the fuck else is a rapper
supposed to do to fucking get his music out there?
Yeah.
Where, where would you, where would you put your friends?
Not everyone is going to have a fucking like a record company behind them or like a fucking
P-Ditty, like promoting their shit.
Like, yes.
I mean, it's the same as, same as YouTube, same as YouTube.
You know, how much of this is just kind of-
You gotta post it somewhere and you're not, you can't just expect to have like a fucking,
yeah, like a, like a-
So like is every rapper now, so, you know.
Thought of as a sound cloud rapper and thought of as less?
I guess it's the same, I guess it's the same kind of stigma as like a self-published author,
you know?
And now the things are just so similar.
And we have so much control at like the low levels and we don't need like to be either
literal the top, you know, top 10 musicians in the world to like get on a major label.
Instead, you just publish and you know, probably can get more like, I suppose it's kind of
a dream that there's like a middle class of artists that can survive, you know, not necessarily
as literally the top, but that, because we have access to posting shit on YouTube and
soundcloud and all that stuff.
It's kind of created an atmosphere of more, you know-
Everybody has-
That's juvenile.
Amateur.
It's not, it's, there's no more gatekeepers, you know, content just flows and people will
find it and you can find your own little cult micro audience and subsist off that and I
think that's a good thing.
I think it's a great thing.
I guess I just, I get why because that exists.
There's been an erosion of like the clout of like any given profession, because like,
if you were like a musician, you're like, do you hear the new whoever?
They're going to be like, who?
And you're going to be like, oh, you know, they're like the new one who was fucking signed
by, you know, P Diddy or whatever, fucking Motown or something, you're like, oh, shit,
that's impressive.
But you're like, no, it's this guy I'm listening to on soundcloud.
They're like, oh, so that means nothing to me.
That means, you know, whatever.
I mean, it means more and I guess it means like culture, culturally, I think it means
more, that means more and more and like record label is less and less meaningful as like,
you know, as the, as the, the, you know, the undoing, like the removal of like limiters
on like, I think it's all just like, creating your own cloud, right?
Because like, I think, for example, Ben, like your work, right?
Like you make comics, and that's fucking sick.
And you have like physical books and stuff, people can buy them.
But like the thing that, that like, I think works in your favor is that like, you go to
thesaintcomics.com to read your comics, go to Trigomoitopastic, or I post them on Deviantart.
You know, like that's like different mindsets, but like, you can, you can use social media
as like an advertising platform, essentially to like get the funnel people to like a platform
you control.
And like, once you do that, like the image is all your own, and like, it gives you an
air of authority to be like, oh, they have a dot com, you know, like that's like their
place.
Yeah.
You know, I happened to tune into Market How Do the other day, as you were talking about
this exact thing about about, yeah, owning your audience and using social media, not
in itself.
Because yeah, I don't, I don't want my main platform, like a lot of people's main platform
for their art and stuff is like their Tumblr, and like, I don't want my main platform to
be my Tumblr.
I want to have my website that's got my shit on it.
Will fewer people find it there?
Yeah, sure.
But like, you know, the people that are going to only look at it on Tumblr, they can see
it on Tumblr, or I almost said Tinder, I almost said Tinder, but Twitter or whatever.
And you know, but the people who want to follow the links and like go and find my actual, see
my actual website where I do have full control over the experience and all that.
And yeah, I do think it gives it an air of like, yeah, I own this, this is mine.
I made not only the content, but the platform you're viewing it on.
It makes it feel more legitimate.
Like I have in the past said, I have a comic friend who makes comics, you go to stcomics.com,
and then they've gone and read it.
And it was like, yeah.
It's pretty great.
And the experience of going to a tailor-made like specific site is so much nicer than going
to a social media platform where you may or may not have an account and it's like...
Using someone's comic on Tumblr is like, it's annoying because you usually have to
read it backwards.
You have to like add in like hyperlinks for the buttons and it never works very well
and Tumblr just sucks.
This is something why I'm kind of interested like why I'm personally big on this like whole
web 3.0 thing that me and Digi keep talking about because like, I want the pendulum to
shift back towards people making their own websites because I think the internet's just
more interesting that way because like everything's a new experience.
Yeah.
It was interesting because I was talking to Munchie about this and he didn't understand
what web 3.0, like what we were talking about until I explained it to him, like there's
no servers, it's all peer-to-peer.
So like you just make an HTML file and instead of having to go to Bluehost and pay X100 dollars,
it just hosts on your own local system.
So like that financial cost of having to host a website is gone.
So then like it's still harder than social, but like you don't have to like pay a year
up front of hosting space and keep paying every year.
It's just like a torn and it just runs on your computer.
I think that's super powerful and really interesting.
You know, if I could bring up just one more fast, I was just thinking about this.
I'm thinking about the experience of being a YouTuber to kind of go back to that side
of things.
And I've been thinking about this for a while and it's that so maybe I've been a little
bit charmed by listening to so much Joe Rogan, he has a lot of comedians and they like talk
about their experiences and it sounds really nice because as a YouTuber, even working towards
being more of a YouTuber and putting more videos out, it's real.
I don't mean to be disrespectful to anybody, but I do actually kind of feel like a whore
in some ways.
Yeah, to a degree because like here I am, I'm selling like my inner self to a degree,
you know.
And like when I think about like podcasts are definitely there's an element of that
there for sure.
Like we Agua again, there's an element of that there and I compare that to like a practiced
routine of a stand up comic.
Like yes, you're going there, you're like doing your thing.
But what you're actually selling is like it's a product.
It's not literally like your soul being like removed from it's something that you've prepared
to distribute as opposed to like being like a daily vlogger and like to turn your whole
life into that.
I want a big, thick old wall between me and like the people who I, you know, sell content
to essentially and because I'm I really don't want to have that kind of barrier be like
thin.
I like having my my life, my private shit going on and it does make me a little uncomfortable
sometimes exposing a lot of my inner self sucks that you really can't have that wall
as much as you want.
You have to have a Patreon and in order to sell the Patreon, you have to have a Discord
server and in order to how different are we from like, I don't know, like Instagram
thoughts or whatever, who are selling their like private Snapchats.
Like in their case, they're selling like literal pictures of their bodies.
At least they're not selling their like inner thoughts, you know, they get to keep that
shit private.
And I I'm just saying that's a different sort of feeling, but there's probably something
enjoyable about that.
Now I'm not trying to like exaggerate and be like, oh my God, what was me?
This is so terrible.
It's just it's just a vague sense that I've been having and I don't know.
Let me know what you think of the comments down below.
Please like comment and subscribe, ring that bell and sub for so and sub for so but I'm
not only use up.
I'm gonna let's sub for so but like the part where only you subscribe.
Let's do that.
That sounds right.
That's right.
That's the way to do it.
That's the way to sub for so we got one more question real quick.
We are we are we are going in towards our last question.
Here and and we will wrap it up.
So this is from bad rap.
Joe.
Give it to us.
Soundcraft hero.
Here you go.
Hey, yo, it's me, the biggest piece of shit you ever did see open your mouth and let me
take a pee.
Don't work by the charge.
It's full free.
I like to stick my fingers on my ass just for fun.
So you better run.
I'm about to paint balls with my cum push my prostate with my thumb.
Boom.
Wow.
I'm the king.
Fuck with me.
And I'll knock out the ringing.
I don't play fair.
Kick your nuts and pull out your hair shut on your chest without care.
More like a bear.
So you better be aware.
I swear to be worse.
The wear and I take it down to my layer and tear off the skin and begin to touch myself.
Rip off your fingers.
Put them on my shelf.
That's it.
Yeah.
I'm I'm really like the Donkey Kong review.
Okay.
So far.
Yeah.
The new rap is on point.
That was a great follow up to that whole discussion we just had.
Yeah.
It was.
This guy.
This guy is selling his innermost stuff.
He really is.
That was a wonderful bad rap, Joe.
What a what a note to end the podcast.
I think there's no need for comment.
Let's just end it right there.
Ladies and gentlemen, thanks for joining us this week on the Procrastinators podcast.
Head on over to patreon.com slash the procrastinators where there will be a new episode.
I think tomorrow for when this episode is posted.
So the bonus episode.
That's right.
I worked all night making the bonus episode look great and I am still I have much more
to do.
It is going to be it is going to look be so sick.
Damn.
I'm fucking excited now.
So Ben's editing.
It's going to have good art.
It's a whole big thing that we did.
Get ready for it, people.
It's a whole big production that we did.
It's not it's not ASMR episode or you know.
This is this is instead of this is the opposite of the usual the usual thing that the bonus
episode is.
Let's see how we can ruin this episode on purpose.
This time we actually said what if we tried making it good.
Basically, so if you want to experience that novel.
So we're trying something new.
Get in there.
Quality quality at TP procrastinators on Twitter.
Oh, and you got to give $5 for the bonus episodes on the patron fyi and $1 for the for the for
the chat.
Oh, it's fine.
Give us money, please.
And that's it, everybody.
Thanks for joining us.
Oh, and of course the speak pipe link.
If you want to leave us a voicemail down in the description below.
But it's speakpipe.com.
I care.
It's in the fucking description.
I forget.
PCP voicemail.
That's the one.
Thank you, Tom.
Appreciate it.
Okay.
That's it.
Thanks for joining us.
We'll see you next week with another one.
Enjoy.
If you're a good boy.
Hello, and goodbye.
And goodbye.
Thanks for listening.
Later.
Bye.
Thanks for listening.
Later.
Bye.