I have rights, you have rights, even animals has rights.
So earlier on I got in two professors, an animal rights activist, and a woman with a hedgehog to ask them some questions.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the best guy ever and Mumkey Jones is here.
Hello everyone, I'm the nostalgia Mumkey. I remember it so you don't have to.
Classic comedy. Hippocrit is here.
I don't have anything after that. That's a good one.
That really stole the show. We should just quit right now.
What a great bit. You should start a whole thing about that. You should start a whole channel and branch out and make it a whole franchise.
I bet that channel would be awesome. I feel like you can incorporate wearing glasses into this character that you've just come up with.
Yeah, that Mumkey with the glasses. Yeah, that's a good one.
I'll do this great thing where I take a movie and I condense it into six seconds, and it'll be like Titanic in six seconds.
That's a pretty good idea. Tom's all here. I'm here.
And I guess Ben's here.
Talk about cultural appropriation.
That's true. Okay, so today we're talking about Animal Rights.
I just finished my Monkey Studies class 101.
For my Gen Ed requirements. Fantastic.
National Monkey History Month.
That was in February.
Ouch, harsh.
We're talking about animal rights. Animal rights.
And if you believe it or not, there is an Urban Dictionary definition for animal rights.
So let's take a gander here. Animal rights.
A philosophy that suggests, does that evape? Did I just hear a fucking vape?
No, of course not. Of course it wasn't.
The vape is here?
That would never happen.
Guys, I think we need to punish Ben for this vaping bullshit.
And I'm prepared to do a monkey siren every time I hear this shit to alert you all.
That sounds like a good idea.
If I hear a fucking vape, I'm going to go...
Then you'll all know.
This is just going to be a game of cat and mouse of how subtly can I vape before I said it?
I'm just going to be pushing the boundaries every time.
Like that monkey with the symbols in Toy Story 3.
Yes, exactly.
Anyway, excuse me.
Here's our definition. Yes, yes, excuse you indeed.
What's the definition of douchebag who vapes all the time?
Ben St. Look at that.
So animal rights.
It's rare that the definition is shorter than the word.
Well, it happens. Animal rights.
A philosophy that suggests some or all animals have the right to possess their own lives.
Contrary to popular opinion, animal rights activists do not ask for voting rights for chickens or pigs.
Rather, they ask that animals not be used for food, entertainment, medical research, or clothing.
Some activists maintain that there is a distinction between the sentient or self-aware animals,
and those with a large degree of self-awareness are to be afforded the right to possess their own lives.
Okay, a little bit more. Animal rights are also largely tied to dietary lifestyles such as vegetarianism and veganism
who would hoard the consumption of meat products in accordance with the principles of animal rights.
There you go.
In this podcast, animal rights means animals shouldn't be treated any differently than humans.
If you wouldn't eat a human, you wouldn't eat an animal. Is that what we're going with?
I don't think so.
I think it's more like should we treat them like decency.
That definition seemed to imply that believing in animal rights period means that we shouldn't eat animals.
I love animal rights period.
That's a little bit beyond the pale of what I would expect.
There's other definitions here.
Okay, we're going to come up with our own reasonable definition.
I think the animal rights in general is a broad scope as to whether animals, any organism besides human,
whether it deserves any rights at all to its own life, to its existence, whether we should respect it and its habitat,
whether it's all under the same umbrella.
I don't care at all.
It's the worst topic ever.
That's a position.
I'm glad you signed up for this episode, Hippo.
Yes, see you later, Hippo.
You wanted me to be here.
You know you wanted yourself to be here.
You signed up, goddammit. Nobody signed you up.
Mumki said he wanted me to be here. I don't know why.
No, don't tell them I see that I got you and Tom here specifically because I like you.
You have a Hippo who is your son.
Well, he's not my son.
He's your daughter then.
No.
He's my roommate.
Don't assume he's gender.
Hippo's listening to this podcast and shedding a single tear as he hears this.
Concecutive single tears.
I'm just his roommate.
Okay, well, let me take my position here and we can go from there.
I think that I actually, I was going to say my first thought was no animals deserve any rights at all, including humans can do whatever they want to animals and I do not give a fuck.
I've changed that opinion slightly because I realized that if that definition was if I use that, I don't actually think humans have very, you know, I don't think that human intelligence is anything particularly like special in the sense that it distinguishes us from animals.
We're just better at achieving our goals.
What I'm going to say is I think, yeah, well, you know, you're smarter than animals.
No, no, we are.
We are definitely smarter.
But for example, some humans have intelligence that is, I mean, not like animal level, but like closer to animal level.
So like, where does the, where does the cutoff lie?
I think even somebody with a Down syndrome is smarter than a gopher.
I'm not disputing that at all.
But what I am saying is there is like a measurable scale of intelligence and you say all animals don't matter.
You should take like like something like a dolphin, people say, right? Dolphins are generally pretty smart.
Yeah.
If you can measure the intelligence of a dolphin and say that it is worth keeping and I don't know what the standard should be.
But if we could figure that out, that should be the standard for whether or not we care about it.
I have a thought on this.
Dolphins, people like dolphins because, you know, they're like, they can do tricks.
They can talk.
They'd be like, and we're like, oh, that's nice.
You know, I like that thing.
I won't kill it.
And any animal that has, has made us enamored with it so that we don't kill it is smart enough to live.
I think it's just, there's no like a level of intelligence.
There's no like a data point.
There's no math number that we can attribute to any like on a scale.
What animals should we kill and what should we not?
I disagree.
I think, I think if we like animals to be alive, then they should live.
Okay, but just think about it for a second.
What you're doing there is just making an emotional argument for things that humans like.
Yeah, exactly.
That's my point.
I don't care about like, oh, what's the, we should try to like categorize everything and make it like a hard distinction.
If you like your dog, you shouldn't eat your dog.
But if other people don't care about their dogs, they can eat them.
It just depends on who you are and where you are in the society around you.
Here's the reason why there's a flaw in that argument.
Because what if humans were to someday meet some organism that was, you know, human level intelligence or higher, who knows,
but was just repellent on many levels, kind of like the bugs from Starship Troopers.
What if we were to encounter a species like that and just assume that they were bad and gross and we didn't like them,
even if like, so I'm proposing a universal standard for, we will care about a creature.
I don't know what those bugs are like.
Can they talk to us with language?
Yeah.
Well, they do communicate with each other.
Okay, a lot of them are just grunts, but they do have like queens and those seem to have like human level intelligence, if not higher.
Not like super intelligence.
Well, then she should be an ambassador and then people will be like, oh, I guess these people, these are like, this is a different race.
We should be treating them like a minority.
Well, that's totally true.
Yeah, so like terribly.
So like herd them into camps and cook them and eat them.
Yeah.
Well, okay, I think Starship Troopers is actually a great example of this because the whole deal behind Starship Troopers,
fantastic movie, everybody go watch it if you haven't, is that humans got into this war with the bugs based mostly on a misunderstanding.
A bug war, if you will.
It was in fact a bug war.
It was 100% a bug war if only Mochi was here.
I forgot about the bug war.
You should never forget about the bug war.
Every day, Ben.
Oh my God, I'm part of the problem.
That's right.
The Syrian refugee crisis wages on every day and you just turn a blind eye to it, Ben.
So too does the bug war.
Yeah, that describes me too.
Okay, so in that movie, okay, the point is that humans in that movie don't give a fuck about the bugs because they're gross and they don't understand them.
Even though like throughout the movie, there are clearly signs that the bugs are only defending their territory and are only like retaliating against humans because humans, you know, aggressed against them
and are like trying to colonize their solar system and shit.
So that's why the bugs attack humans.
It's based totally on a misunderstanding, whereas they could totally have gotten along or just left each other alone if they just didn't fuck with each other.
But it's like the propaganda of, ew, emotionally, we don't like these bugs.
And the propaganda throughout the film is fantastic at illustrating how nonsensical it is.
Humans just start stomping on cockroaches on Earth as if that's a fucking resistance against the bugs in space.
But you understand my point here, it's just that we need some sort of hard system.
I can alter my stance a bit to fit with that.
Say, for example, where there's like a bug comes and it says, no, we're intelligent, you idiot.
And then one of the humans is like, oh, they're intelligent.
Wait, we should stop killing them.
And then there's other humans are like, I don't care, I gotta go.
I'm gonna smash them.
Then at that point, it will be up to the humans to decide amongst themselves democratically or however they decide things,
whether that new species should be considered a beast or a potential, you know, new species we can talk to.
And that will be like, what I'm saying is a universal standard is to, you know, the amount of things we could ever find out in space, for example, is ridiculous.
I don't think a universal standard will count for the whole universe.
I think we should just take things as they come.
Well, I mean, you could separate it into different components.
Like if they are actively trying to kill you this entire race.
We're here today on the PCP talking about animal rights.
We're 10 minutes in and the scope of our argument has already expanded to a universal, extra galactic scale.
It has to though.
It doesn't have to.
Because I'm talking about a universal.
It really doesn't have to, Nick.
We can talk, believe it or not.
These arguments will apply to my thoughts on, like, why we can eat meat.
I like chicken.
So we can go back to that.
I like hugging chickens.
Well, sure.
Agreed.
But like, what about something like, you know, doing makeup experiments on monkeys?
Like, where do you draw the line on that?
How does the bug empire, Nate, help you answer the makeup monkey question?
Simply.
Simply because the same principle applies.
So, okay, monkeys are really, really retarded and stupid.
Monkeys.
Monkeys are okay some of the time.
God damn it.
Like, okay, the thing, why do humans, you know, care about dogs, right?
It's because dogs, A, are generally like loyal and they'll, you know, they like your scent and they get used to you and they like it.
And they're cute.
And they'll be nice to you.
Right.
And they're also like attractive visually.
They're cute.
Most importantly.
Yeah, they're highly attractive.
Most importantly, that they're subservient.
Like, if all dogs were, like, by default, like, vicious and you had to tame every single one.
We wouldn't like dogs.
We'd kill them.
They'd be like wolves and lions.
And also all dogs would have true.
Yeah, because they're pure of heart, unlike humans.
Yeah.
Unlike humans.
Okay, but here's the thing about dogs.
So, we, you know, we enjoy their company as a species very much.
We've bred them to be that way and, you know, that may or may not have issues, but assuming
that that's just how it was, no problem there.
But at the current day, like, people like dogs because they're nice to us.
But does that, and that's why we don't...
Discussing animal rights.
And that's why, like, we care about them in general as a species.
But, like, is there anything...
Do we know that a dog really...
What is the value of a dog's life to itself, you know?
If you kill a dog...
Is a dog not entitled to the sweat of his own brow?
I know.
I don't think that he is.
Wait, wait, I think if you kill a dog, I think it won't know that it's dead because it's
be dead.
Well, a human that doesn't know that it's dead either.
Exactly.
Yeah, so what's the standard for not being allowed to kill, you know, just as one example
of something you can do to it?
Well, you're allowed to kill a dog.
It's not like you go to jail for it.
That's not actually true all the time.
Yeah, there's laws.
There's animal abuse laws and stuff.
Right.
And we're here saying revoke them.
Trump, revoke that shit.
It's time to go back.
Make America great again.
Let me kill my dog.
That's the single greatest social issue facing us today.
I'm a one issue voter, guys.
I vote for whichever candidate will let me kill my dog.
But to get back to the point that Mumki was making about using animals for makeup testing
and stuff, like, okay, so clearly the animals don't seem to enjoy that too much, right?
They're not into it in general.
You could call that mistreatment, but how much should we actually care about the suffering
of any animal?
And in this case, you know, we're talking about a monkey, a monkey.
I would say we should only really give a shit if it is like at a certain level of intelligence
where it's like cognizant.
See, you're just making it more complicated than it has to be.
Am I?
Here's what I think.
Just appeal to your emotions.
If you like the monkey and you want it to be happy, then you should just let it be.
That's not good enough.
Here's the thing.
I would not paint makeup on a monkey's face and then, I don't know, like blast it with
a fire hose to see how much punishment it could take before the makeup or opposite.
I wouldn't do that.
I would feel like I was a shitty person if I did that.
Therefore, I think it's a shitty thing to do and they shouldn't do it.
I mean, that's why you feel that way.
Is it because you're anthropomorphizing that monkey and projecting the feelings that you
as a human would have if that happened to you?
Because they share like 99% of our DNA.
We share like 50% of our DNA with a fucking banana.
And I feel sorry for bananas and the monkeys eat them.
Yeah, I bet you do.
But, I mean, we understand faces and two eyes and stuff.
Monkeys have like a face, you know.
As a human being animal, as a human animal, we recognize a monkey's face and we think,
ah, he's got emotions.
He's got a face.
He's got a family.
I don't know that.
That's an assumption being made.
Yeah, but we're imperfect beings.
We're not robots, Nate.
We can't be robots.
You'll never be a robot.
We should strive for perfection, Dave.
We should strive for a better system.
It's true that we can't know that the monkey has feelings like our own, but we can't know
that about one another either.
We can't see into each other's minds any more than we can see into the monkeys.
We can make logical distinctions about what other humans are experiencing.
I'm just saying that it's more difficult.
Well, we can make informed guesses.
That's all we can ever do about anything in our entire lives.
And that's what we're doing when we say, oh, this monkey looks like it's in pain.
I feel bad.
Right.
No.
Okay.
But I'm saying, why should we care that it's in pain?
What is the standard we're using to give a shit about that?
I have an answer for you.
That's a real question.
Yeah, it is a real question.
Because when we decided this would be the topic, when it comes to monkey rights, and
I'm not even meaming here, it's something that I'm actually kind of passionate about.
And I knew I was going to get emotional talking about it.
And as we all know, when I get emotional on this show, I don't give the best arguments.
So I actually wrote something up that I wanted to read about monkey rights.
Okay.
If you guys are ready.
This is only applied to monkeys or this is applied to other animals?
Just for monkeys.
Other animals I don't care as much about.
But, you know, I got a thing for monkeys.
Does somebody have like a bird chirping in the background?
Sorry, my window's open.
You want me to close it?
I'll get that.
The bird is very distracting.
That bird was waning.
All right.
In present day America, the monkey is still not free.
The life of the monkey is still sadly crippled by the manacles of segregation and the chains of discrimination.
The monkey lives on a lonely island of poverty in the midst of a vast ocean of material prosperity.
The monkey is still languished in the corners of American society and finds himself an exile in his own land.
And so we've come here today to dramatize a shameful condition.
In a sense, we've come to our nation's capital to cash a check.
When the architects of our republic wrote the magnificent words of the Constitution and the Declaration of Independence,
they were signing a promissory note to which every American was to fall heir.
This note was a promise that all men, yes, monkey men, as well as white men,
would be guaranteed the unalienable rights of life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness.
Written by me.
Is that right? Written by you.
Yeah, exactly.
Good one. Good one.
So that's why I think monkeys should have rights.
I think I heard a similar...
Did I not hear a similar speech that one time?
I feel like it was, you know...
That speech came to me in a dream.
I said, I have a dream of this speech.
Well, I agree with that. I hate black people, though.
Oh, my God.
Of course, of course.
That's why I wanted to do the episode.
Now I'm done.
I'll see you guys in an hour for the questions.
Okay, can I just say, I want to clarify just one thing about the argument.
And it was just that...
So we don't care, right?
When you squish an ant, nobody gives a shit.
It does not matter.
Because ants are only bad.
They're only negative forces on my life.
They don't give me happiness like a monkey or a dog.
Well, right, but that's still kind of an emotional thing.
But even when you get to something like a spider...
But being happy is intrinsically valuable.
It's not just an emotion.
It benefits my life in so many ways.
If I'm a serial killer and I enjoy killing humans,
then that makes me happy, but it does not benefit everybody else.
Well, sure, but that's an offset.
That's an outlier.
We're talking like general humanity, not just the serial killers.
Well, but these are unanswered questions among human society.
I still don't understand at all what you're saying.
Okay, I was trying to get that.
I feel like you've got...
Yeah, go on, please.
Lay out your thesis for us.
Okay, it's very clear to me.
Okay, so we don't care if small insects or whatever die.
We don't spend a moment to consider their well-being whatsoever.
And yet we do when it comes to things that start to get a little bit more like us.
Like a hamster or a gerbil or whatever.
And then, of course, we get to like a dog.
Yeah, that's my dude.
And when we get to something like a dog or, I don't know, like a deer.
We hear about dogs more than deers and shit.
I don't know what the standard is.
So what I'm getting at is what exactly is the standard we're using
for how much we care about the well-being of these animals?
So your thesis is just a question?
No, no.
My thesis is I have the solution.
And what we should do is we should measure the intelligence of each of these animals,
make an actual determination about what their value is.
Alright, Nate.
But the thing is that applies to humans, too.
Let's just rank them all on a scale.
That's exactly what we should do.
And you should take everyone as an individual and, you know...
But there is no scale, Nate.
You can't just fucking measure everyone's IQ and be like,
oh, here's where they fall on the spectrum of worth.
What a brave new world this is.
But we have to.
Yeah, I think so.
What is your better solution?
My better solution is that you shut the fuck up.
I'm trying to solve problems here.
You said the thing about we don't care about insects.
I mean, some people do.
And if you anthropomorphize like an insect, if you watch it, you know,
you can be like, oh, look at him.
He's going to go get his lunch.
Like, you can make like little, like, you know, you can trick your brain into thinking of them as like...
You can be like Carl Pilkington and convince yourself that you saw a bee have a heart attack from overwork.
Right.
That's right.
Stuff like that.
My hero.
He is just the perfect example of this shit.
He's the cutoff point for what is not worth human rights.
He's just below.
He's just below the cutoff point.
He's right on the cusp.
So basically, it's not like universal that we all hate bugs, but we all like monkeys.
Some people hate monkeys.
It's not even about hating.
It's just about not caring about them.
Some people hate giraffes.
Some people hate hippos.
You know, it's just the way it is.
It shouldn't be about hating.
It should be about, you know, it's like whether we care about them or not.
Some people hate people.
Some people don't care about certain animals and they care about others.
The point I'm saying is that my stance when it comes to animals is that I think, you know,
I'll respect them.
I won't kick a puppy just for fun, but if he starts to kill me, then I will.
But if I want to eat that puppy, then I'll kick him.
Well, if I want to eat that puppy, I'll tell someone else to do it because I don't want to do that.
There are...
I'm aware that there are complications to this.
Like, you know, when a baby is born, like, it can't sustain itself, so is it really valuable?
Like, you have to take, like, the potential of the organism into account.
Well, there you go.
There you go.
You dismantled your own argument.
No, no, I didn't.
Real good there.
There has never been a case of, like, an ant getting intelligent enough to be worth caring about.
Why do you care so much about the value?
I'll tell you why.
Oh, I know why.
I'm thinking about the long-reaching ramifications of our current idea systems.
That is what I worry about.
I'm just like, let's get a good value now so that we can be ready for the future, whatever happens then.
Also, if you come with your little calculator, you can punch in the numbers.
Right, so we can hook up our brain storage spaceship and use them for faster than we can.
Just try to make gunbusters happen.
Try to make gunbusters happen, yes.
Is there just, like, do you have any humanity at all?
Why do you care about the value so much that it comes into everything you do?
I think that, like, the only ethical system that is coherent at all and isn't, like, hypocritical is...
Oh, fuck.
I had a whole thing and I cut out.
What happened?
I had a whole...
I guess we just couldn't hear him.
I had a whole thing and I said it and...
Say it again.
We can interrupt Ben.
It's okay.
The gist of what I was saying is, Nate, why do you care about the value so much when it comes to everything?
Say you had a dog and, you know, you punched in the numbers in your little thing.
You realize that it didn't have any value.
Would you just kill it right then and there or, you know, do you have any humanity?
It's not about just deciding to kill it.
It's about worrying about it.
It's about being concerned about its well-being.
That's the issue.
It's not like whether I'm just going to shoot things that I don't like.
That's just not something I do.
I just don't see why you care about, like, the intrinsic value of anything to the point where it comes into everything.
Like, hmm, should I worry about this?
If you're worried about it, like, on an instinctual level.
I'll tell you exactly why.
Because human instinct is not good enough.
We need logical systems to enforce human behavior in the right ways.
Hippo, I'm right there with you.
I'm right on board with that exasperated sigh.
You see, you guys think that, like, oh, well, how could you say that?
That's never been done before.
Except so much of human behavior today has been shaped by philosophy.
We're not, like, shaking our heads at what a rogue visionary you are.
Like, that's not...
Then what's the problem?
Then what is the problem?
Because you're just fucking talking a bunch of shit, man.
Everything I've said makes perfect sense.
I guess...
If the criticism is what I'm saying is too obvious, then that's great.
Then I hope that's...
It's not that it's too obvious.
It's just the way you're laying it out is just way too simplistic.
And it doesn't have any application in our life.
You're such an airy-fairy thinking about all these concepts all the time,
and then you come to real life, and then it doesn't matter.
None of it matters.
Can't we just talk about specific things like overcrowding on chicken farms
or, like, the way we treat a pig?
Like, these weird philosophical ideas that you have with Star Trek and shit?
Not when Nate's on the podcast.
You can talk about anything you want.
Nate's on the podcast.
I'm so sorry for leading the conversation down a path that you guys can't follow
because you're too fucking dumb.
You're little pee brains. You're little pee brains.
Just can't comprehend the next level shit that's going on up there.
It's too scary for you, Nate. I can't handle it.
That's right. I know.
It's tough, man. It's tough.
Well, let me give my spiel.
I think that the only thing that makes sense in life is to put yourself first
and to put your own needs above everyone else's.
Because if you don't do that, then what the fuck are you doing?
Someone's been reading a little Ayn Rand.
What was wrong with your guys' parents?
How do they raise these two monsters?
No, that makes sense, though, on some level.
Yeah, I'm willing to sacrifice of myself if there are people that are worse off than me.
Well, there's always going to be people worse off than me.
You can't help everyone. You can't do it.
It just doesn't make any sense.
You can't even live.
I think that unless you accept that I'm just looking out for myself,
you either just can't live at all or you're just going to be wrapped in hypocrisy
that you'll never solve and will never be acknowledged.
And I think...
Because you watch out for yourself. You do what benefits you.
You can help the people that you care about because helping them helps you.
And that all makes sense and is fine.
You can give to charity because it makes you feel like a good person or whatever.
That's all fine.
But ultimately, ultimately...
And this is just...
I really think I'm just arguing for basic human nature here,
which I think should just be the default position.
But I just think that's what makes sense.
And I think that that makes sense on a species level, too.
I think that humanity should just be...
Okay, humanity should put humanity's needs first.
And other speed...
Yeah, we can watch out for them because having them around benefits us.
But when push comes to shove and it comes down to it...
Yeah, I really think that we should...
If it...
To benefit ourselves, anything should go...
Anything goes and other animals just...
Fuck them, right?
Like, they got to watch out for themselves.
Even though they can't.
We're just lucky.
We're just lucky that other animals can't fight back.
Yeah, we get it.
But Ben...
So if you knew that your neighbor was viciously beating his pet dog,
you would say,
Well, I'm not going to get involved.
I guess that's fine.
Dogs should get beat if the guy wants to or whatever.
Uh, no.
No, that'd make me mad.
How does that benefit you?
Because it makes me upset that the dog is being beat.
So I guess it's on an individual level for everybody then
where if you personally don't want dogs to get beat, then go for it.
I guess so, yeah.
I'm fine with that.
Alright.
I think there's enough good people in the world to stop all the dogs
from getting abused all the time.
I would like to think so.
I like to think more people.
I think there is because if we appeal to the emotion,
most people feel that way about dogs.
Yeah, like on an emotional level,
most people are willing to eat meat
but also feel sad when they see an animal being harmed, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's fair.
Yeah, but that doesn't solve anything.
That doesn't help the situation at all.
It doesn't solve anything.
The problem, Nate, is that there is not an issue.
You say like,
Oh, the issue is like, you know,
it's not what animals we should kill.
It's like, which animals should be worried about?
Right.
That's not a problem.
That's not a problem that comes up in my everyday life.
I'm not wondering what I should be worried about.
Just because it doesn't come up in your daily life
does not mean it's not a problem.
I don't see how it's a problem.
That's just blinding yourself to things that you aren't aware of.
But that's the whole issue.
That you don't think it's a problem.
Because it could be a problem one day.
How could it be a problem?
Okay, here's how it could be a problem.
It is possible that every cow that we murder for us to eat
actually is a conscious entity
and is really upset about it
and we're just committing genocide every single day.
That is possible and I would like to look into that.
Okay, that's just one example.
But I want to apply that logic across the board
to make sure we do the right thing.
I'm pretty sure that cows don't like being killed.
That's why I said it's just one...
But that's the thing.
Whether we should give a shit.
Because if it just is reacting to pain
and it's pain receptors, then...
I think people react to pain exactly the same way.
I don't think there's too much of a difference between a cow and a human
when it comes to death.
Reacting to pain and our pain receptors is exactly what we do.
Then tell me, Gib, why do you care if a human dies
and you don't care if a cow dies? What's the difference?
Well, I don't necessarily care if a human dies.
It depends on who the human is.
I don't by default care about humans more than I care about cows.
I hear about people dying in the news all the time.
It doesn't affect me at all.
You would care if a human died in front of you
or if a cow died in front of you.
Yes, both the same.
Because it's death happening in front of me.
That would not be the same.
No, they wouldn't be the same, but they would both disturb me.
Yeah, they would both disturb me.
Seeing something in front of you is a lot different
from knowing that something happens.
I know slaughterhouses kill animals and I eat the meat.
I know people die in horrific wars
and I don't eat that meat.
I mean, they don't sell that meat.
But if I were to see either of those things in real life
I would get upset and disturbed and want it to stop.
But I don't see it in real life.
I don't see it all the time.
It's just out of my vision.
But just because...
Okay, the problem right now, Nate, is that you're thinking...
You are saying nothing of value.
If I don't see it, it's not a problem.
No, let's not.
The whole thing is that, Nate, you're talking again
from a grand humanitarian vision.
We need to set a precedent that sets all of human behavior
and elevates all of humanity as a species.
Where Gib is just saying,
I'm just trying to live my life and half...
99% of the time I don't give a fuck about any of this
because it doesn't affect me personally.
It's two different lifestyle choices
and philosophical perspectives on how to run yourself.
It's really what I was doing there.
I was just trying to explain to Nate
why I don't care about his issues that he seems to have.
You're not concerning yourself with the long-standing...
But that's not an argument against anything I'm saying.
You're just saying you don't care.
Yeah, and I'm explaining why I'm sighing
every time you bring this up because I think it doesn't matter.
That's why I was saying it.
It doesn't matter to you.
Okay, got it.
It does matter to me.
Every week, it's just...
Nate presents some grand vision
of how humanity needs to change right now.
That's right.
And we all just listen and sigh.
Nate just needs to start a new podcast called
Nate Fleet where it's all about creating a better humanity.
How are we going to be a guest on there?
The best future ever.
Can I be the co-pilot on that ship?
I'll have to figure that out.
I don't know if you're qualified.
Nate, just to bring this down,
let's take it down from the grand philosophy thing.
Let's look at some specific examples
and then you can use your philosophy.
The only reason I start grand is because you can write.
That's the idea.
That's good.
For example, slaughterhouses with cows,
they're kept in these little bins where they can't move.
They can't even step forward or sit down.
They're stuck standing all day to keep their meat nice and plump
and juicy and all that shit.
What's it called?
Kosher?
If you're going to kill a cow the Kosher way,
which is like the Jewish bullshit,
you have to hang it upside down and then cut it
and then it bleeds out and it's very painful and torturous.
What do you think about all that shit?
Is that okay?
Here's the thing.
I think cows are under the standard of intellectually caring about them,
so I'm fine with all of it.
Totally don't care.
It can go on all day.
See, I'm okay with killing cows to eat them
and I'm not trying to...
I don't know why we bought it in vegan shit at the beginning
because that's retarded.
I'm okay with eating chickens and cows and meat,
but I'm not okay with it being tortured in order to die.
I think you can just kill it in a second.
You don't have to torture that fucker like the Kosher way.
Well, here's the thing.
I think that I am logically consistent on this point
because I say I am not interested.
I do think that it is not worth worrying about the well-being of a cow
and that applies to every aspect of its life.
You can torture it.
You can do whatever you want to, chop off all its legs,
bleed it out for its whole life, fill its veins with acid.
Those are all equally things that I am not concerned about
about the life of a cow.
Just because it's not as smart as you?
That's correct.
But Nate, if you were there in the slaughterhouse
and they were like, hey, best guy ever, come here a minute.
On the one hand, here's like a bolt gun.
You're working at the slaughterhouse because, I don't know,
just shut up, stop criticizing me.
Here's a bolt gun.
You got to kill this cow.
Here's a thing that you could just jam a rod into this cow's head
and it would be dead in a second.
Alternatively, it will pay you slightly more
if you will hang this cow up
and gently slit its skin in some points
and you need to watch it bleed out for an entire several hours.
Like that scene from Reservoir Dogs.
You got to play the song and dance around and stab it and shit.
So we can assume I'll get more money for doing something way worse is the idea.
Yeah.
Would you just be fine?
Would you be like, oh, well, okay, it marginally benefits me.
So I guess I'll just do it this other way and that's fine.
Would you just be fine with that?
I hear what you're saying and here's the thing.
The issue is this is totally involved,
but it's not a sort of a part of the logical framework.
But okay, so to answer your question, I would not do that.
No.
And I think it is for a very reasonable reason.
Okay, yeah.
I am a normal human being with all my emotional societal conditioning
built into me, which just informs me that, yes,
these things are weird and gross and uncomfortable to do.
And I have never killed anything in my life.
This is why I feel like you say you're not being hypocritical with your point.
You're consistent on your point.
That's your job.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But you say you're not being consistent on your point.
But even then, as a normal human, you recognize that you will think differently
from your big philosophical idea that cows are not important.
That's a nuanced point there.
Well, I understand, Nate, that what you're saying is that, like,
ideally, logically, it should not matter what we do to this cow.
And whereas you can't divorce yourself from your human emotional response,
even though intellectually you know that it's fine,
but it still feels wrong because of lizard brain or whatever.
Well, I mean, I guess I can understand that point.
Well, here's where I disagree with you.
I don't think it makes sense to say, oh, here's a cutoff point,
because Carl Pilkington, who's just above the cutoff point
and a silverback gorilla who's just below it,
they're very similar to each other.
There's not a meaningful distinction between two things that are very close
but on opposite sides of that cutoff point.
I really think you have to look at it as a spectrum.
I am fully willing to look at it as a spectrum.
Yeah, but then the problem with that is that at no point on the spectrum
does the value become zero, except at the very end,
until you get to an inanimate object.
So even if it's a spectrum, then even like a microbe
has some minuscule amount of value
that should be taken under some minuscule amount of consideration.
That is true.
You never hit a cutoff point where you're like,
okay, under this, anything goes.
But I think that...
You just have to involve practicality.
But that's what your emotional response
that telling you, oh, doing this to the cow is wrong.
That's what your emotional response is telling you,
like, oh, even though this cow is not as valuable as a human,
it still has some value and I still have some empathy for it, right?
Well, the empathy just comes from us assuming that it feels the same way about...
Well, I'm saying that your logical response,
that your emotional response there makes logical sense
if you view it as like an intelligent spectrum.
Only to some extent.
The way it seems, Nate, is that you're going into these logical situations
with the idea that if you were a robot and you didn't have any emotions,
this is what you would come to the conclusion with.
This is what you would say.
And then, you know, on the other hand,
you have the reality that you wouldn't actually say that
because you are a human.
And I don't know why you have that non-human robotic way of thinking
even in consideration because it can't happen right now.
You're not a robot.
It doesn't make any difference.
Our law system already is a divorce from emotional stuff.
We already have systems in place to do stuff like this.
I'm sympathetic to the idea of viewing things unemotionally
and trying to come to logical conclusions without bringing emotion into it.
I think that makes sense.
Emotion does not mean best, by the way.
We're trying to come to the best solution
which may or may not be our built-in human emotional response.
You're trying to come to the best solution.
We were just talking about our opinions.
Okay, well, let me say one point that is two Gibbs points
to agree with what's Gibbs been saying.
All right, yeah, here it is.
Okay, here's the thing, though.
Given the reality of what human beings are,
if I met a man who told me that his hobby,
like he's a farmer or whatever,
and he has cows, his hobby is to like drain the blood out of the cows
and fill their veins with acid.
He liked to do it because it was fun
and he liked watching them scream and die.
If he told me that, you know, I would be,
my logic would still apply that, you know,
their lives don't matter,
but what does matter is the kind of human being
who would do that sort of thing
is a psychopath,
is not a person who, you know,
is a valuable member of the human race,
probably, probably, like they are a freak,
and it is logical that they might also do those sorts of things
to human beings.
And so you can logically form from that position
like, okay, this guy has problems,
I don't like him, I condemn his actions.
On that basis, you can still condemn, you know,
things that are clearly bad that we don't like,
even if, you know, like the things being tortured
are not inherently valuable.
Well, I want to say something about that torture
and the cow thing.
The whole thing with the kosher meat being,
you know, you have to cut it by the neck
and drain its blood until it's all gone,
and that's the only way Jews can eat that,
and halal meat is very similar.
And that I don't agree with
because to get the meat out of the cow,
you just need to kill it.
And to torture it like that is just, you know,
it's a religious thing.
You don't need to do that to get the meat out, though.
If you gave a Jew something that wasn't kosher meat,
he wouldn't be able to tell.
He'd have no fucking idea.
We could all agree that these kind of traditions are retarded.
Yeah, traditions are retarded.
So, like, what I would say is that if there's something like,
well, if you like beef, you have to kill a cow,
and I'm like, hmm, well, I like beef.
I like eating beef more than I care about
some cow I don't know dying.
So I'm okay with it dying in the least harmful way possible
because that's just the nicest thing to do
is just to hope that it's the least harmful possible
and they're not being tortured.
I think that's a lot of people's general stance,
is they like meat,
but they'd rather, you know, the cow lives a happy enough life
and then dies instantly without feeling any pain.
Yeah, I'm on hippo's side on that one.
You're definitely right.
Everything dies eventually, you know?
If you give them a quick death,
what have we really lost here, you know?
I mean, everything should die.
I think dying will be eternal bliss.
I just don't want to be tortured before I die
and I think animals probably feel the same way.
Do you think the cow will get 72 virgins in heaven, Momke?
Is he a lull or not?
Yeah, this cow prays five times a day.
Did he strap a bunch of bombs to his oven
and blow up the barn?
He was gonna. He was just about to.
If you don't do that, you don't get those virgins.
Damn it.
What if he died to feed some like ISIS fighters, you know,
like some real heroes?
Is Muslim cow a friend of Action Draft?
Absolutely. They're best friends.
He's like, you know, as we all know,
Action Draft is a globetrotting, you know, cinema superstar
and Muslim cow is his, like, token racial friend
that's in the movies.
Muslim cow is down there in Pokemon Hell,
just real salty that he didn't quite get the chance
to carry out his terrorist attack.
Holy shit, somebody draw Muslim cow.
That's my favorite character.
The day before he was gonna do it.
Oh, I get it.
It'd be like having a burqa on the cow
because it's a cow, because it's a milk female burqa.
Oh, yeah, I guess it would.
It would look like a big black something or other,
like a rock, almost.
I got a big black something or other for you, hippo.
God, I don't know.
Okay, I feel like I got out pretty much my whole position
on this shit.
Maybe there's some more specifics we can talk about.
Anyone got any things that really upset them?
I haven't said my position at all, and as the only vegetarian,
I feel like I have some problems.
Oh, that's right. I always forget that you're a vegetarian, Tom.
I forgot I have no respect for you.
Yeah, no, that's good.
Okay, lay it down.
That's the whole thing.
Despite the fact that I'm vegetarian,
it's not something I project out in the world,
and that's why I'm happy that everyone forgets,
because that means I'm not making a big deal out of it,
and that's a good sign.
I guess you're doing it right.
Yeah, right.
When people don't know, that's a good thing.
By the way, I do feel like it makes sense
for a lot of the emotional vegetarians
to project like, guys, you're killing cows.
Stop it.
Okay, but anyway, I'm sorry.
I think that if that's your position,
I just care about whether a person is consistent
in what they believe.
I don't blame the crazy vegans out there,
because to them, they really think
that all around them are mass murderers,
and they're like, what's happening here?
Where am I?
I get it.
If that's your view, that's pretty fucked up.
They're wrong, though.
Whatever.
Well, I mean, my perspective is just that
I think that ethical consideration shouldn't be given
on any basis of intelligence.
It should be on the capacity to feel pain,
because you don't have to be intelligent to suffer.
If you're feeling pain, it's uncomfortable,
it sucks, and I don't like it.
I don't know about you.
I try to avoid pain as much as possible,
because I fucking hate it, because it's the worst.
So I don't eat meat anymore,
because I'm uncomfortable.
I don't try and have a meal or anything
that I wouldn't be comfortable preparing,
start to finish myself in all the actions.
So I don't have meat.
I don't kill insects or shit.
I try not to, at least.
If there's a big spider in the house,
and someone wants to kill it,
I'll take it and bring it outside.
I have this innate respect for life,
and it doesn't make any logical sense.
It's not even probably the correct thing to do,
but that's just my perspective.
Can I hit you with a hypothetical on that one?
Sure, go for it.
So let's say you discover,
there's a big old mouse in my house,
and he's tearing up my shit.
He's eating all my food.
Would you put a mouse trap,
or would you just let him live there?
Because you can't catch that fucker.
He's running around like crazy.
That was actually going to be my next point.
There's exceptions when it comes to pests and stuff.
If you have a termite infection in your house,
and they're fucking everywhere,
or you're infested with mice,
because we've had mice in the house before,
it's a little different,
because now they're directly affecting your domicile,
and your health, essentially,
because if you have an infestation,
that can quickly spread disease and fuck you up.
At that point, it comes under the same umbrella
as self-defense.
If a dude came to my house with a gun,
and tried to kill me,
I'd be chill with killing him.
Oh, hell yeah.
So it's the same thing with,
if your fucking house is infested with shit,
and you're going to die,
you've got to get rid of that, too.
At the end of the day,
again, kind of like what Ben was saying,
you put yourself first and shit like that,
but I tried to just go through life
and not cause harm in general,
try to stay in my lane, so to speak,
actualize myself to the best of my abilities
without interfering with anyone or anything else intentionally.
So that's my general philosophy,
and that's why I don't eat meat anymore.
I don't kill bugs or mice or anything like that.
I try and keep that shit.
The thing with bugs is, I don't kill bugs either,
but usually because I can safely get them outside the house
or they're not bothering me.
If there's a spider in a very far corner of the attic or something,
he can stay.
Spiders are people, too.
But if there's a spider on my computer,
behind my computer, I'm like,
eventually I'm going to have to go back there,
so I have to get rid of this guy.
But killing him, there's going to be bug juice everywhere.
I don't want that.
So I don't kill things mostly because
there's no benefit to me killing them,
aside from a visceral reaction to stop something existing.
But generally, I like to not kill things
unless there's no other way.
Didn't there used to be a soft drink called bug juice
that had cartoon characters on the lid?
Bug juice is a thing I had at Boy Scout Camp all the time,
which was a cocktail of different fruit punch mixes and stuff.
It was never very good,
but they would just put whatever kind of juice shit they had around.
But they'd have Yu-Gi-Oh's head on it or some shit, right?
I can't speak to that. I don't know.
Does anybody remember that?
I don't even know what you're talking about,
but I'll take your word for it.
I remember watching Kids WB
and there'd be commercials for bug juice all the time.
I don't know. I just know it's like a Boy Scout thing.
It sparked my nostalgia.
It sounds vaguely familiar,
so maybe it exists.
I would ask Tom something about that, though,
about his pain stuff.
It's not really challenging you,
but I think I would just want to ask,
to be the most consistent with your philosophy,
would you say that the ideal version of that would be Jainism,
which is this religion that is 100% focused
on causing zero harm to any other living creature,
to the point where they wear masks at all times
to avoid breathing in bugs
and accidentally swallowing them and killing them
in that kind of way,
and they're always careful to not step on bugs or anything?
Would you say that's like the ultimate extreme?
I don't think that's going a little too far,
and the reason I think,
I always say when I explain my philosophy,
I always say it's like,
maximize your own happiness
without intentionally causing anybody else harm.
I think intentionally is really important
because lots of the times,
in order to maximize your own happiness,
you have to unintentionally harm somebody else.
An example I use a lot of the times
is if you're going for your dream job
and there's one position for it,
in order to maximize your own happiness,
you've got to shit on someone else's dream
by denying them the job.
If you're in a situation where...
Doesn't make any sense.
Doesn't make any sense not to do it.
Then all of a sudden,
you're basically causing yourself pain
and the whole point is to not cause pain.
So if you're causing yourself pain,
in that situation,
somebody's got to suffer.
It might as well be the other guy.
That's what the capitalistic system makes more sense
because you both try as hard as you can
and the one who is more capable
gets rewarded and prospers,
and that's what we want.
If there are unintentional consequences,
as long as you're not intentionally
or maliciously harming anybody else,
it seems to be okay,
because you're not...
I don't think it's okay
to be like,
if I didn't mean to do it,
then it's all hunky-dory.
There's obvious exceptions.
If you fucking brutally murder somebody
with your car,
it's like, I didn't mean to do it,
I should just be able to go home.
There's degrees of stuff,
but just as a general guideline,
you're trying to do the best that you can
without intentionally or maliciously hurting
other people.
I feel like a good general standard
is your life.
I agree so far as you can't
really actively try...
If it's unintentional,
it's unintentional.
You can't set out to do less
unintentional harm
because the unintentional harm is outside your control.
And yet, unintentional harm
is still just as bad as intentional harm.
So I don't know.
I feel like...
I don't think it's worth...
I don't think it's any worse
than intentionally bad than to do it unintentionally
in the game of things.
The reason that's incorrect is because
when people do things intentionally wrong,
that creates a pattern of behavior that you can
use to determine what their actions are likely to be
in the future.
You can say that they are both equally damaging
to the world, but you do know
when something is intentional versus unintentional
that that person is likely to continue
this kind of action, whereas if it was intentional,
that's not the case.
Despite the effects being the same,
I think intentional is always worse
for you.
If I'm talking more like a code of conduct
and less for physical ramifications
on the rest of the world,
and that's where I think
that distinction becomes important.
To go back to the job example,
there's a difference between me
going in for an interview and then you going in for an interview
and you winning out over me.
That was you just being the better candidate
or whatever. That's unintentional harm.
But if we talked
on the train and we're both going for the same job
and you fucking made sure that
I didn't get off the train at the right time
so I missed my interview and you got the job by default,
that's intentional harm.
You know that that guy is a bad dude, right?
You know if he's done that.
We're aware that this is a shady person and we don't want them
doing that.
I'm pretty confused because I've never seen a cow
go into a job interview.
We're kind of moving away from animal rights.
Haven't you read the far side dude?
Oh yeah, you're right.
Belly washers.
The drink was called belly washers.
On the subject of meat,
I want to say something like
some people will say
some people will be like, yeah,
I know it's bad that the cow gets killed for this meat
but the cow is already dead
so it's not bad if I eat it.
That's so stupid.
And I don't agree with that because it's supply and demand.
If you're buying the meat,
you're contributing to the demand
and you're indirectly but you're still
supporting this
system.
That's why I don't do it.
In terms of
practicality, it's like, yeah,
the deed's already done and you're just
consuming flesh but at the same time
you're contributing to the system.
You're leading to it happening more.
My mindset is that
if I was doing that myself,
I would be uncomfortable with it and therefore I don't participate.
But it gets a little more
complicated to me at least
when you think about the fact that
the cows that are being
slaughtered for this meat are being
bred specifically for that
purpose.
Their life wouldn't even exist without this demand,
right?
Yeah, in a sense.
So that's where I get a little, oh man,
it's too tough.
They're still living creature and they're still feeling pain.
What is the net?
Are we talking about that? That's when it gets tough.
How do you measure goodness?
Do you judge it by net life
enjoyed by all creatures on the planet?
You don't. You don't measure it.
Every baby that we do not have,
everyone should be out fucking all the time
to produce more humans to have more
enjoyment. You don't measure it.
That's not a thing that you do.
You don't measure it but I'm talking about systems where we do.
But if you're trying to come up
with a schema of what
is good and what
is a world worth pursuing.
I thought we were talking about cows though.
These are all relevant questions.
Keep it to cows.
Keep it to cows. Talk about what could be good
or about cows.
I think Nate's baby example is germane.
Well, it doesn't matter
because it also applies to cows.
Oh wait, germane means good. I forgot.
So just to
apply it to cows, if we got two cows
and you don't eat meat
so you just let them live out their lives
and they die, let's say they don't have kids or whatever,
then that's fine.
But if you are a meat farmer
and you take those two cows and you breed them
and you make a whole fucking fleet of cows
by the end. And so let's say you've got
like a thousand cows now.
But after, you know, how long does the cow live?
Let's say after like five years,
you slaughter them and kill them. Maybe that's a lot shorter.
I don't know. But you slaughter them and you kill them.
And let's say you do it in a generally humane way
not like torturing them like the Jews love to do.
And
you kill them and you sell it and whatever.
So in that equation, the one guy
had like two cows and they had a great life.
You lived with them. They were like your pets.
They were your buddies. And then they died
as opposed to a world where you've got now
a thousand cows who all had pretty good lives
but they did end violently as they were killed.
So like which of those
is a happier situation for the world?
I mean,
well, I'm not talking about the world.
I think it's happier because now people have
things to eat.
Well, let's just focus on the cows lives.
It's definitely the first situation.
I don't know, man.
I think there's something.
If a thousand cows
live okay lives versus two cows
living good lives,
maybe the thousand had more
to bind good lives.
We're talking about, I don't think,
I guess maybe my differentiation here is like
I don't think quantity
has anything to do with it.
Yeah, why would the...
That can't be true because benefiting
two people is better than benefiting one,
isn't it?
Can I just say, why?
God fucking dammit!
Can I say what I want to say?
Jesus Christ!
Why would one thousand cows
live worse lives than just two?
Why is that part of it?
No, it's just because we kill them at the end.
We kill them for meat after several years.
Is that it? Yeah, that's it.
I thought dying of old age is also painful.
It probably is.
Then what's the difference?
The time that was lived between the two?
Those two had a higher quality life overall.
They lived, let's say, 10 years.
This is like a hypothetical scenario
we're laying out here. No, this is totally
applicable to real life.
We're talking about how we should treat animals.
Well, okay.
Why is it okay to
arbitrarily kill something
after it's been deemed by someone
else that their function has been served
now they're going to keep going?
Well, you could argue that it isn't.
I don't because I don't care about cows' lives.
That's my position.
You do, obviously.
I think that's kind of ridiculous.
It's like saying,
what if the state took care of me and my family
and I had seven kids but once I turned
40 they fucking killed me and used my body
for medical purposes?
Just to Ben's point, Ben was just making a question
about which of those is a better world?
Which world has produced more joy?
Well, if all the cows had
a decent life, then by virtue
of the more cows having more of a good life,
they all add up to
something gooder. I don't know how you're measuring this.
We're talking about
1,000 cows whose lives is
not great, but it's
just good enough that it's not
terrible.
It's just worth living versus one cow that had
like, yeah, this cow had a good ass life.
You know what I mean?
What do you mean why? This is the hypothetical
that I'm laying out.
Fine, that's the hypothetical. I thought it was a different hypothetical.
But if that's the hypothetical,
I would say
that's stacked in favour of
the two cows having a great life.
But I'm just saying, if there's two cows
and they die of old age, and if you have 1,000 cows
that get killed, if they still
have a decent life,
it's better
to have more cows because
there's more meat and that
impacts more people
than two cows that don't give any meat.
Even if we're talking about just the cows,
I don't think it makes too much of a difference
if there's 1,000 cows or two cows
unless you explicitly say that
the two cows have a much better life.
Which is why I think it's a weird hypothetical
that there's only one answer to that.
Of course it's the two cows.
Alright, to me
it seems obvious
that 1,000 cows
from a logical standpoint,
1,000 cows living mediocre lives
is probably more happiness
overall than one or two cows
living real good lives. But hey,
that's just a theory.
A game theory.
Thanks for watching.
I think from that
sense of logic, I think
we should be making as many people as possible
and making as many cows as possible.
That's the logical application.
You could also say that because all those cows die
and that's sad, that we should have no cows,
we should have no people, we should have absolutely nothing
because then there'll be no sadness in the world,
there'll be no pain, there'll be no death.
I don't see how any of this fits together.
I'm getting really heated right now.
To go back to
my original point
which is what I guess we were trying to talk about
I'm thinking more along the lines of
not enabling happiness
because I don't think there's any way
to guarantee happiness
at least for human beings
that's up to you.
You can only set up potential
for happiness but it's your own actions
in terms of whether you're happy or not.
The kind of philosophy I follow
is about avoiding causing pain
and by that extension
avoiding suffering.
Tom, can I challenge your philosophy
with another question?
Yeah, I'm down to discuss. Go.
So plants and fish
are very similar in that neither feel pain
and you have to kill both of them to eat them
so why do you not eat fish?
I've asked myself that question
I think it's because
that's much more of just
a personal discomfort
because they're still alive and I wouldn't want to deny
something like that. But isn't a plant alive too?
I think it's just that fish
have eyes and we have eyes.
I've thought about that a lot because it's like
by that same philosophy it is still hypocritical
to have plants. You'd have to subsist basically on nothing
by nuts and berries essentially.
Nuts have lives. Nuts have potential for lives.
And as
Sonnet you discovered after he evolved
with his new body, nuts and apples
just won't cut it.
Is that true though? Do fish not feel pain?
How do we know that? I've heard that.
They're not smart enough to feel pain.
I just read it.
Let's just assume that that's true. I'm pretty sure it is.
I've heard it before as well.
It's either a very popular myth or
there's some science somewhere.
Even if we put in a hypothetical animal that's like that though
we could still...
Personally, the fact that fish don't feel pain
say if I was
vegetarian or vegetarian, I would still
not eat fish just because of that emotional
attachment.
Because they have eyes and a mouth and I'm like
it's a guy, it's a person.
I can very easily anthropomorphize a fish.
It's very difficult to anthropomorphize
a plant without making it
an animal with plant-like qualities.
At the end of the day, this philosophy
completely
comes into conflict with
the structure of how life on this planet works.
Sure.
We're all designed to
the entire planet
is basically one
macro-organism where we're all parts of it
and that means we all are interdependent.
You can only resist this to a certain degree
unless you just want to give up yourself and die
and then kind of go back into the soil
and become fuel for something else.
It's inherently flawed.
The ultimate act of vegetarianism is suicide.
It's not even
a joke when you really get
super deep into it.
This is why I don't go out and evangelize it
or try to make a big deal out of it
because to do it is definitely an act of hypocrisy
to a degree
the farther you go down that path.
Tom, it sounds to me
what you're saying is at the logical end
of vegetarianism lies
this rejection
of the systems that keep human beings alive
or allows
that's possibly true
along the vegetarian lifestyle.
I would challenge the vegetarian
ideology at its core
because I think that
and my whole argument at the beginning of this podcast
was a challenge to
why they think the way they do
and why I don't think that it is necessary
to concern ourselves with the lives of animals
at least to the extent that vegetarians do
or vegans or those guys who take it to that extreme.
Living itself
is kind of a selfish thing to do
because to keep yourself alive
you have to consume resources
and if you get a job
it doesn't get that job
it's a bitter struggle for resources
and position and status
and money and sex and all that stuff
and
that's why I really think that
if you don't
to live at all
is to look out for number one
above all else
and if you don't acknowledge that
I really think you're just kidding yourself.
Not to suck my own dick too hard
so I think the only difference between
our two positions here
is that we both accept that living is
a fairly selfish thing to do in general
so we agree on that
but you seem to be
okay at pretty much leaving it at that
whereas I am interested in continuing on
to try to
investigate the ideal situation
where we're causing the least harm possible
that's what I'm interested in from you
I am totally content with leaving it at that
there you go
that was pretty juicy
anybody got any more points to make?
I'll pull them up but anybody got any
more points to make?
I think frogs should take over as the main
species on earth
we have stupid podcasts that suck
and they
they've really shot themselves
in the foot by making those
I think me and Tom
need to go out to dinner and he needs to
prepare me the greatest vegetarian
meal of all time
well then fuck
Tom is good
Tom accepts the vegetarian lifestyle as shit
but he doesn't anyway
I was almost sold
that's the weird thing
I know some good vegetarian things
I like a lot of vegetarian foods
there are good vegetarian meals I'm just a terrible vegetarian
I actually like tofu
you know the thing
you don't even miss for me
I didn't even bring this up at all but I actually
would love to be a vegetarian
for the nutritional benefits
if you're a vegetarian you will
not be fat you just won't be
fat it's not gonna happen
unless you're like a shitty one
no come on
you can eat high fructose
corn syrup as a vegetarian
right yeah I'm revising that
here's the thing you can do for a vegetarian meal
you get a bunch of vegetables
and some olive oil and you put it all in a
pan you just chop it up a bit onions
peppers asparagus all sorts
of things you put them in a pan
and you just roast it you roast that for like
an hour or so and it's just great
no hypocrite sucks roast it there you go
but that just sounds like a side dish
like I'd still be hungry for them
no no it's a big deal because of the olive oil
dude just get a chili and olive oil
and garlic and pepper and all that
haven't you ever had like
haven't you ever had like vegetarian noodles
at like a Chinese place with delicious sauce
it's purely vegetarian but it's fucking delicious
and it's like a big ass entree type meal
I love those those are totally vegetarian
pasta noodle dishes with
vegetables are great
Nate the only food I eat is fried chicken
now you're speaking my language
would you
my snapchat is like
half just like videos of me frying
shit
have you ever like
eaten just the fried part of like
the skin like all the fucking time
I feel that I first need it
yeah maybe that's the only good
bit maybe you should just eat that part
yeah but they don't have extra
yeah I'm a vegetarian I buy
chicken wings and I cook them but I only
eat the skin and I throw the rest to my dogs
yeah
makes perfect sense
I just feel more comfortable that way
okay let's
let's answer some of these questions here
okay here we go
at tbob806
asks how do you guys deal
with stress
is there really any good way
to deal with stress
I don't know it if there is
the main way I deal with stress
is to not worry about people seeing me
get angry because if you worry about
that it's just an extra layer
an extra layer being embarrassed about your feelings
is retarded I know how Gib deals with
stress though Gib goes into
Dark Souls and kills an NPC
that's how he lets off steam
I like that system a lot
my reaction to stress
is to shut down
and go catatonic and not do anything
imagine Ben lying on the floor
emotionless
stress
does it work
no
that's not my coping
that's my natural reaction
it's me sitting at my computer
staring at a screen picking at my hair
just for hours
that's my stress reaction
the best coping mechanism
that I have with it is to
fight through it and do something anyway
and usually that makes me feel better
but of course easier said than done
accomplishing one of the things
on your task list when you're stressed
is I think the best way
it's also the most difficult thing to do
it's really hard
you're least motivated
it's why you need to have a bunch
of shitty projects that don't matter
like I have with the
risker drawings like I'm still doing
if I can't think of anything to do
I do that and I feel okay
if I get to the end of a day and I feel like I haven't accomplished anything
I'll like make a t-shirt
and that will be like
oh I did something today
okay what do we got here
how about at based
anime man says
wait no it's a terrible question never mind
okay here's a better one at our hero
our good friend hgbguy
asks this incredible question
you may only choose one
chicken or tea
that's your question
I'd choose tea by default
I would be really sad to lose
either one
well I can have coffees
who cares tea at chicken
my gut reaction is that
I'd really miss chicken but on the other hand
like other meats are good as well
whereas there's really no good substitute
for tea
Ben do you make chicken nuggets
out of a different animal
actually you make chicken tendis
can you make buffalo wild wings out of a different animal
I just yesterday watched
a video of
Chef John from foodwishes.com
preparing what he called city chicken
which is just pork arranged
to look like a chicken wing
and supposedly it's pretty good
so maybe I guess I would give up chicken actually
now that you said it
fuck you
I'm kicking you guys out of the chicken nuggets
fan club
I would definitely give up
I like tea but I don't need it
speaking of chicken nuggets you hear about the guy who got
the year of free nuggets from Wendy's
did he get all those tweets
did he get all the retweets
he has the most
he didn't get 18 million but I think it got
like 4 million or something it's the most retweeted
tweet of all time
did he have that agreement
ahead of time or like what was the arrangement
here did he just tweet like hey if I get
a million tweets what he did is he
he tweeted at Wendy's and said how many retweets
do I need to get a year's supply
free nuggets and they responded 18 million
so he quoted that
and said helping to get out I need my nugs
yeah
and he got like 4.5 million tweets and it was the most
retweeted tweet of all time so Wendy's is like
you know what we'll give it to you
that's fucking great that's fantastic
that almost makes up for the porn
the Wendy's porn yeah
yeah
wait I feel like I was gonna say
oh yeah the one misgiving
the one last misgiving I have about giving up chicken
is that chicken breast is like the cheapest
meat like all other meats
are more expensive than chicken
that's what would make me sad about giving up chicken
I feel like a lot of the time
fried chicken it's mostly
in the batter and I can do it
with other meat
I probably could
nothing beats chicken nuggets
with buffalo sauce baby
you can't beat it
some of that honey mustard
sauce
you gotta give up tea
who gives a fuck about tea
yeah
I drink tea every day
and even I know chicken
I mean how are you gonna bulk without chicken
come on
I enjoy chicken more often than I enjoy tea
I should give up the tea
it's better than tea
I like it
but I've already done this in giving up chicken
that's true
there's so many different kinds of tea
so many different kinds of chicken
I think
I could probably
if I wanted to give up meat entirely
it wasn't that hard
I did it in one day
Jesus Christ
how long have you been a veg man
I think seven years now
seven years
now Tom this is an important question
I forgot to ask
as a vegetarian do you still eat pussy
you know
that is my one flaw
I suppose
on the rare occasions I'm allowed
you hypocrite
okay here's another question
hey guys do you think
vegetarian women still swallow cum
yes
better
if a cow could talk
and would say like
take my milk go for it no problem
swallow my cum dude
swallow my cum
okay here we go
at Gergerad
says what is the ideal
breakfast of champions
especially excited to hear a hypocrite
and his take on English breakfast
also his name is toasty boy
is the breakfast of champions
in reference to anything
what's your favorite breakfast
that was the slogan for weedies for a while
right that's true
weedies is not involved in my breakfast of champions
I occasionally have
an English breakfast
with tomatoes
and mushrooms
and toast and bacon
I'm into that
it's all nice and greasy and cool
but I don't have it every day
because it's a lot of stuff to do
but yeah
English breakfast is my favorite
I don't know if
yeah English breakfast is good
every breakfast you eat is an English breakfast
I don't know if this is the best
well, Nate
I have two breakfast stories
one is
we went one year to like
Connecticut or something and we stayed at this
weirdly fancy hotel
we were in this hotel that was
really fancy for some reason
I think I do remember that
yeah
and there was like a big like painted mural
on the ceiling of the foyer or whatever
anyway it was advertised
that there was free breakfast
like free continental breakfast meaning like
some fucking danishes and coffee
and like a little like sealed
pouch of cereal or whatever
but I went to like this other room by accident
it was like a restaurant in the thing
and I ordered Lobster Eggs
Benedict thinking that
I remember that
thinking that this was the free breakfast
and they gave it to me
and then they were like yeah $35
I was like I'm just a kid
I don't have any money
and then like I don't know
I went and got mom or something
and like she was like
I think they gave it to me for free
because like I was a kid
so that was one of the best breakfast I ever had
the other one, okay the other day
a couple days before I left Digi House
we went out to Waffle House together
and Waffle House is kind of
is kind of pricey for what it is
like the food's not great
it's kind of shitty and it's not that cheap
but you can like
hash browns are like $1.75
and a triple serving of hash browns
is like less than three times
it's like $3 and you can get a topping
for like 50 cents a piece
and one of the toppings is sausage gravy
so go to Waffle House
get a triple hash browns
with sausage gravy and it is a huge
fucking bowl of hash brown
smothered in like
ladles full of sausage gravy
I was stuffed and it cost me like $3.75
that sounds amazing
it was amazing
everyone try it
that sounds pretty good
go and rip off your local Waffle House
by the way I fucking love sausage gravy
and I hate that they don't eat it
above the Mason Dixon line
yeah we do
I like never had it
in life until I was like an adult
we grew up in fucking Massachusetts
every gas station would have
biscuits and gravy available
to eat and they had sausage gravy
they don't have it around Boston
yeah biscuits and gravy was not a thing
around Boston
you could get it at KFC
but not like sausage gravy
it was like shitty
I remembered my actual
favorite breakfast I ever had
it sounds weird but it's
cold salmon
like cold salmon fish
with
scrambled eggs
but put in the microwave
it's very strange
but it's really nice
like cold salmon and hot
microwaved scrambled eggs
delicious if you have that
that reminds me of another breakfast favor
but it also worked good for brunch or lunch
which is a bagel with cream cheese
capers, onions, tomato slices
and thin sliced smoked salmon
or the locks bagel
is one of my other favorite breakfast
but you gotta have the capers
the capers really make the meal
trust me
I wanna hear what you guys think of this one
for the breakfast of a true champion
you sleep until noon
and then you eat lunch
I got breakfast of champions
I was gonna say I don't have breakfast
I intermittent fast but I also sleep all day
regardless of when I wake up
wait that's not the dietary intermittent fasting
of like the professional bodybuilders
that's not what you're talking about
I eat for an 8 hour period
I fast for 16 on the daily
and do you do this for like
the weight loss?
that's how I heard about it
but I just do it because
like fuck why not it's easy
I kinda do the same thing where
I'll eat for 16 hours and then for 8 hours
I won't
you talk about 18 hours
16 hours straight
like that's a big meal
no no just like you know every now and then
like sometimes they eat breakfast and lunch and dinner
like these random little meals throughout the day
and then 8 hours no eating at all
I don't understand what you're talking about
he's saying that he eats throughout the day
and then goes to sleep
I fast when I'm asleep
it's a fucking joke
Tyrone likes to pyramid his meals
meaning each meal is bigger than the last
I met Tyrone's dad the other day
he was a short Mexican guy
Tyrone's 6 foot 10 and 300 pounds
what?
that's some donkey
here's a question
at Vivian Flamer
at Vivian Flamer asks
will you validate me by answering my humorous question
that leaves little room for discussion
towards the end of your podcast please
no moving on
next question
at anime
people have weird names
maybe it is
oh yeah that's probably it
oh you got it good job
have you ever had any paranormal
or otherwise inexplicable
experiences
yes ghost
ghost I am a ghost
yeah you ever had a paranormal
thing happen to you
or just inexplicable
I went to Pokemon hell
how was it
it was hot
I left
it hurts a lot
trust me
I had a ghost
so my college
was real gay
I guess it was
the most haunted college
in New Jersey
it had some shitty little claim to fame
there were a couple of local ghosts
in different buildings
when I
first got there as a freshman
they had a thing
there was like a raffle
to see who got to go on this ghost
tour
where a tour guide would go around and talk about the ghost
and like oh my god this is a fucking
tale
we went around to different places
oh this is the ghost that supposedly he is here
and we went up to the top of this
administrative building
that is not a normal place
to go
and we were standing up in this kind of
conference room with windows
and
he is talking about the ghost
he is talking about a ghost of a woman
who died
and there is a lightning flash
someone takes a picture in a camera
and I swear to god
reflected in the window in this room
I see the image
of an old man in a poncho
standing next to a little boy
that looks an awful lot like a ghost
and I was like hey excuse me
I just saw a ghost in the mirror
I saw the ghostly image of an old man
in a poncho standing with a little boy
and he was like oh no that is not the ghost that lives here
and I was okay never mind don't worry about it
it is fine
and then
some fucking goth chick
was like uh
got all spooked and she was sitting on a radiator
and she was like uh and she kind of made a scene
about it and the tour guide was like
it is and she was like oh I felt something
but you know I'm very receptive to the spirits
you know I talk to ghosts
I talk to ghosts all the time
and then yeah and then she went on this big stupid thing
about her retarded beliefs or whatever
was it not because she sat on a hot radion
she went ah
she fucking she faked the whole
goddamn thing for attention
that son of a bitch
I need to ask so how
convinced are you that what you experienced there was a
paranormal event
20%
okay that is what I wanted to hear
I had a real one
if you want to hear my real paranormal event
sure sure sure
so one time me and my buddies we went to
Red Lobster and you know like they
for some reason in all these fucking places
you know Yorda Crab Legs or Lobster
they don't take the meat out for you
they are like here here is a $25
shore for you have fun
so I got all the meat out of my Lobster
and I had this shell sitting over there
and I found a bit and I think
there was a ghost in the shell
wow
fuck all of you
rap events gay bullshit
and not my hilarious meme
you just put the words
of a thing that everyone knows
it was just it was all just a shaggy dog
story
I'm starting my new podcast
I'm starting the pro labs and gators
podcast
there's a question that's not purely
this is a purely a vanity question
a facu
at facacababaca
god damn it
I don't know whatever
facucabobaca asks how do you like your steak
and I'm only answering this because I just had
the best steak in my whole life two weeks ago
at this rip my parents came to visit in Cincinnati
and we went to this place called the precinct
for the first time in my life they want to go to a fancy restaurant
so I got this
reservation at the place I never believed
There was such a thing as a good restaurant. I assumed everything was McDonald's quality or worse
And I got to this place and we had this it's famous for its steaks like a Cincinnati famous restaurant and
Had the fucking steak and it was just the literally the best meal I've ever had in my entire life
And it was I believe
Medium no it was medium rare. Yeah, it was me. I think medium rare is the way to go with stay
It was it was pink and juicy and so fucking succulent. Yeah, everyone go to the precinct
It's not a steak, but I just went to a place called Moxie burger yesterday
Which I'd never been to before and ordered the classic Moxie burger, which is it's a burger medium rare with bacon
like a cheese sauce some other like spicy aioli sauce on it or something and a fried green tomato and
I'd never had a fried green tomato before it kind of tastes like a pickle. Anyway, it was super good and
Medium rare medium medium rare is the point. Oh, I just I just thought of a cool thing to say. There's a good be a hashtag
Liking well done steak is the equivalent of liking Dark Souls 2
That's a comparison. I thought it's quite apt because people people garbage. Yeah, no people
It's mostly because people have come out and said, you know, I think well done steak is the best and I'm like, well
It isn't you just like it
So you're you're dumb. I
Agreed. Okay. Here we go. He decky camea said that as a boy
He would eat steak but his but he would eat American steak only he couldn't understand all the words like he couldn't fully
Appreciate the taste of the American steak which inspired him which inspired him to make his own steak as an adult and like
Deliberately leave out some of like the key ingredients so that the so that the player of the steak had to like piece the story together in their own minds
But you said he decky camea. What you mean is he did talking me is a I'm fucking
I was quite lost there. Yeah, fuck me now. Sorry. That's his first name. Whatever. Who cares to me is a key
Okay, here's a here's another question. Okay, this is a this is one
I've been mulling over in my mind for a long time at Mostafa was here asks. Is it gay to fap with friends? Yes
I'm not prepared to condemn it to gay. All right quick get out of here. You fucking there are situations
How do you mean there are situations?
If you're back-to-back if you're back-to-back
If you're back-to-back, it's not gay, dude
No, they're not gay
But why?
If you're not gay, you're still a fag
Just go to the fucking next door
Well, just go home
Would you be like would you be like like like two of you like backed into it like like back-to-back like fighting off waves of zombies like jizzing all over them
Right
That would yeah, that'd be okay. Look there was this this isn't this isn't actually like the full fap story
But it's like when I was a little boy
My friend showed me
Some hardcore you're gay you guys you guys all know a heatherbrook right though the famous deep-throat artist
She's a goddess
And and she was my friends showed me that and I didn't jack off with them
But I went to the next room and I jacked off and I just feel totally
Vindicated for that that whole event and I don't feel there was a shred of gayness in the whole thing
If anyone is gay, it's them for giving me a boner
That's gay to bring up a porn when around your friends one time as a youth
Me and a friend like like went to the bathroom
And I like was peeing in the urinal and I finished and then for some reason I decided to like jerk off into the urinal
Yeah, and like I was a little kid and like I don't know I like I thought it was cool
I was like hey, hey, I'm jerking off. He's like are you jerking off? I was like, yeah, I am
But you know what unlike Nate, I'm gonna get I was fucking gay and weird
One time at summer camp a dude just pulled out his dick and showed it to me and said like dude, isn't this sick
Is it I'm gonna be sick
Are you a doctor by any chance
We live in a mad world we live in a mad world a world of possibilities
Personally, I don't think we're gay
I don't think there's anything gay with a jerk in your dick while looking at a woman if your friends next to you fuck it
I got to agree on that
Jerking off to a woman is gay then you need to be a value in your own sexuality
Why do you got to do it with your buddy?
Watching the same porno dude. That's weird, too
The thing about is that the the the proximity of the dicks and the the awareness of both of you that there's some
There's a there's a live dick somewhere right next to you
What if we're both on our blind side it if you glance at it if you think about it then you're gay
No, what if I don't examine well if you're at a separate like it's I mean we're the same blanket
That's kind of just being gay with each other
I mean
What is wrong with all of you think about the historical context Tom come on like
If you're double-teaming a girl that's basically like masturbating only using a girl as a masturbation to tool
Right there
That's funny term, okay, but but also consider even more apropos is the old like nudie picture
Cinemas they used to have where everyone would go in and and fucking pee-wee Herman went and jerked off
That's a bunch of strangers, and I assume they're not like next to each other
I assume they're all like seated in they have a little cubicle like like that the people at the top jizz on the people on the lowest
That's called that's called trickle down economics
What if there's somebody at home who lives in a poor family, and they have to share a bedroom with like their brother
Are they allowed to jerk off are their brothers in the room? You know yes desperate times call for stealth situations
Yeah
Stealth jerking off is different
Totally different we've all
Okay, okay, yeah stealth I mean I mean I'm I'm imagining like you both got your dicks out like right conscious, and you're both like yeah
We're jack you're the gay one if your mind went straight to that
That that's that's why I brought up like the whole like awareness thing like do they know that I'm doing it or
Do I know that they're doing it if both of you know that the other is doing it, then it's pretty gay
Disagree what I'm not looking at his dick. I'm looking at the tits on the TV. Okay, you know what?
But it's stupid I wouldn't do it. I would feel let me ask you this is it gay to sword fight with your dicks is that no no
I think it depends on how you do it
It's only gay if your intention is to come from it. Yeah, I sort of agree. I sort of agree
Yeah, I guess
It's okay
Just like cuz if a guy grabs your junk it just starts groping you like you may in fact get a boner despite being totally
Heterosexual just from the physical stimulation to the same in the same way
Getting a boner in order to sword fight with a dude is totally not necessarily gay
But if the act excites you and the rubbing of the dicks against each other if that excites you that's gay
And just why touching it has to be
Maybe it maybe I said it right Ben I got a question for you physical stimulation is is is not gay then
Then physical stimulation of two dicks
Is
It's not gay if it feels good guys
Then I've got a test for you. Let's say your girlfriend wants to surprise you she says here Ben
I'm gonna blindfold you give you a blow job. Yeah, she does. Oh, it wasn't her
She had her brother do it
And you think it was a chick are you now gay? Well, yes for sure
Although I am although I am single now because my girlfriend is the intention is dead now
The whole thing about about sexual orientation is that it's a preference if it's if you don't know that it's a guy
Then it's fine. Yeah, so you just wear a blindfold all the time. You know as much and then sword fight all you want
Okay, we we plumbed the depth. I feel like we've learned a lot today
You guys are one piece experts has Luffy ever stretched out his dick like a sword and sword fight it
It has well he hasn't done that. Yes. Well. Yeah, but there's that one though. There was that one chapter where there's those
Yeah, that's right. Yeah, get get ready for this. What happened was stretched it. Yeah, I think they start the scene
All right now listen to this listen
So so Luffy once crash landed on an island of only women
He was found you know, he was hurt really bad a bunch of women found him unconscious
They brought him to a bath and they started bathing and they took off all his clothes and they were like oh my god
He's he's got like a mushroom attached to we got to pull this off
There was literally chapters of this girl. I forget her name Marianne or something stretch trying stretching his dick
Oh, it's so stretchy. Why wouldn't it come off trying to separate his dick from his body?
He's getting jacked off in canon one piece
And they do it because they don't know what a man is yeah, I don't know
Okay, it's pretty hot though. Nonetheless. It's pretty great. Now if it was a bunch of Amazon men would Luffy be gay. Yes
Not from that but because he was unconscious, but then when he woke up he would become gay immediately
Aware what awareness of sexual acts with men is what makes you guys. This is way more fun than animal rights
We should do a whole episode. What is gay? This is way more fun. Oh my god. What is gay is a great
Let's come back. Did you already did that on our social media podcast you faggot?
It was already decided that it's only gay if the balls touch that that's a pretty good rule one theory
We got alternative theories
What about what about if one of your balls touches your other ball is that gay? That's definitely
Yeah, gay gay. I'm gay right now
There's not a man alive who's not gay is
Nobody's gay. Oh
Here's our last question
At at pancake monster asks or at pancake monstay because I guess they couldn't fit the R
What PCP member would be the easiest to kidnap? I'm gonna say Ben St. I will email his address to you
I mean Ben St. Is just like ET only instead of Reese's pieces just take garbage and he'll follow and need it
Ben will that's true. Ben is Ben is very predictable. He's very weak-minded. He is very susceptible to suggestion and trickery
I don't think you'll have this trouble
I'm just like a deer in the headlights all the time
Okay, that's it. That's the end of the questions. Okay, we're done. Thanks for listening everybody
Make sure you send us more next Saturday at TP Krasnators on Twitter and thanks for listening
Hey, hey, hey, I want to plug. I want to plug my shit because I've been streaming lately
I've been streaming lately. I've been streaming lately over at Saint Comics on Twitch
So I've been I go there and I draw so if you want to check that I'll go fucking follow me there you idiots
Oh, well, if you're gonna plug streaming, I'm gonna plug streaming because I've been streaming a lot recently on the video games
At twitch.tv slash Gibbentake you go look at that
Subscribe to monkey Jones. Oh, oh at best guy ever. Oh wait best this guy wait and while I'm here
Also, everyone go check out me and my girlfriend Jackie's side channel. There's one video up there
It's Ben and Jackie's college fund get get it on the ground floor now
Before we take off and crush you all under our heels
Yeah, I gotta do that. We're credit at all. You won't regret it at all. Nate shrugs uncomfortably
You guys should do a comedy skit where she's gonna give you a blowjob blindfolded
Inspired by real events
Oh
Okay, we're done. Thanks for this everybody. We'll see you next time
I
Don't want to do