Hello, welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's just me. It's
just me again. Just Ben Saint, your host. Except, I've also got a guest today, Minerva
from Eldina Doublecast. Is that right?
Eldina.
It is I, Minerva P. Kelly, and today the P stands for Pro Crastinators. You can find
me on both Twitter and Tumblr at Doublecast, spelled with a 5 instead of an S. I have an
award-winning YouTube channel where I make bad content that gives you brain damage and
only makes sense if you read too much fan fiction.
Eldina.
It's true. It's true. I know. I know that it's true. I know you. I know. I'm going to admit
I haven't watched most of your videos, but I have, but I have seen the, I have seen and
would highly recommend it's the three videos, the when, when posting goes wrong, or maybe
they're not all when posting goes wrong, the one about the witch with the bones, the one
about the Hamilton with HIV, and the one about miscribed Harry Potter.
Everyone, everyone listening who has not seen this series or doesn't know about these dramas
is incredibly confused right now, but yes, those are the videos. Those are all when posting
goes wrong. Also, forgot to say this earlier. Pronouns, she, her, get it right.
True.
Ben was nice enough to invite an early transition trans woman on his podcast, so please watch.
Well, we have like, well, we have like five of those in our fucking, in our ranks now.
Beautiful.
Yeah, this is just, this is just par for the course. We used to be, we used to be a boys
club. We used to be a real sausage, sausage party here at the PCP, but it's all, it's
all got flip turned upside down now. It's all fucked up.
That's a, that's what it's, it's what Biden getting elected did. It's like buying it selected
and then you hear like the FBI knock on your door, they burst in, put on the cat ears.
And then they, and they erased the memories that don't even know. They don't know that's
what did it. That's what happened.
Never, never realized it was the coronavirus vaccine. I don't know.
It's five G. There's like five different angles we can take with this joke. I think the unironic
like non joke answer is that being inside all day and not being able to like, not having
to be out in society forces you to like do more self reflection and like turn inward.
And that like, I think that it like accelerates the process where it's like, if just like
more time for reflection, yeah, it's like, if coming out as trans for someone who's like
just starting to question their gender would normally take like three to five years, I
feel like you can do it in like six months if you can't go outside because it's just
all you can think about.
It's, it's, it's, I mean, I've definitely noticed the, a sudden, you know, just like
the price of Bitcoin suddenly this year, the rate of transitioning just, just skyrocketed.
Oh God, I want to, I should, last episode I was talking about my Bitcoin adventures.
Oh God.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I don't have much to say about that because I've, it's come to
an end. It came to a sad and ignominious end. I, the, the, the, the long and short of it
of my, of my, of my Bitcoin speculation was I invested way too much. I invested like way
too much of my personal savings in it. And then, and this was as it was like going up
and I'm watching it go up and I'm like, yes, yes, I'm fucking rich. I'm fucking rich. And
then it immediately, but I'm spending like 24 hours a day just staring at the fucking
ticker, just watching the lines go up and down. And I'm like, I'm like, I'm ready. If
it starts to go down, I'm gonna, I'm gonna sell. I'm gonna sell. Of course that's not
what happened. It started, it started to plummet. It started to plummet and I have weak hands.
So once it went down, once it went down far enough, I'm like, it's too scary. I can't
do it. I can't do it anymore. I sold it all. I ended up, I would, for a minute there, I
had made like $1,000, but when I sold, I had lost like 200. So, you know, it's fine.
It's fine. It's all, you know, easy come, easy go.
That's a, I mean, Bitcoin has always just been a casino. So that's pretty par for the
course I feel like. True. I mean, yeah.
I remember back in like 2012, when Bitcoin was first getting started, or maybe it was
like a little earlier, but that's when it came to my attention. I tried buying Bitcoin
or like setting up like a Bitcoin mine because it's. Imagine buying Bitcoin in 2012. Yeah.
That's the thing. It's like, I couldn't, because here's the thing, despite like making, I wouldn't
call it a career because I'm not like, this isn't my job. It's like a hobby that pays
well for some reason. But like despite, you know, doing all this stuff online, I'm not
actually tech savvy. Like I don't really understand how most of the stuff works. So I could not
get the Bitcoin mine up and running. Oh God, you were trying to mine it? Or I don't know.
Well, I didn't know like how to, it was, I couldn't figure out either a, how to buy it
because I was in like high school. So I didn't have like enough disposable income to just
go around buying Bitcoin. So I was like, what if I, but I heard like the way that you get
Bitcoins is you like generate them with like the algorithms or whatever. I was like, I wonder
if I can like set that up on my, you know, 2010 MacBook, which I think even if I had figured
out how to do it, it probably wouldn't have worked. But man, it's thinking back like, I
would be a very, very rich woman right now. I bought Bitcoin in 2012.
I mean, I don't really, I have no idea how one would mine for it. I haven't even looked
into it. I know I don't have what it takes to do that shit. In fact, I made a huge fool
of myself last episode trying to explain what I thought Bitcoin was. And I said at the time,
I'm probably completely wrong. Turns out, yes, I was completely wrong about like what a Bitcoin is.
A Twitter user actually underscore Dio, helpfully called me an idiot and sent me a DM. Got called
by Dio himself with a link to a video explaining more or less what Bitcoin is. So now I understand
it a lot better. The only reason I was able to buy it is just because like this like like two months
ago PayPal just rolled out a feature where you can just you can just buy it on PayPal. You can
just invest through PayPal. That's the only reason why I couldn't do it in the first place. It's
because it's because they made it. It's because they made it so convenient, even a fucking ignoramus
like myself could ruin could ruin their life watching the fucking ticker going up and down 24
hours a day. It was the worst thing. The worst thing about it is that I'm not even free. I'm not
even free just because I sold because now I watch it and obsess over it and look at like, oh, how
much could I have made? Oh, how much would I have lost? I sold it all, but it's still inside me.
You need to do like a clean break. You need to just go cold turkey off Bitcoin. You can't let
this dominate your life anymore. You're right. You're right. I can't I can't let it keep gaslighting
me. I gotta say I'm kind of glad that like I am not more drawn to like Wall Street bets and like
crypto investing and shit like that because like I am like infamously bad at making bets.
Um, my audience has been repeatedly mocking me lately because in basically
from the period of time after Bernie Sanders lost the primary up until like October,
I was making a long series of bets formatted as if Joe Biden actually wins the election this
November, I will blank. And it was always something really like embarrassing and ridiculous.
It seemed like a long shot for a while. It seemed incredibly unlikely. So here's what I ended up with
after my blind, unflinching confidence in democratic incompetence.
If Biden wins by the most expensive dildo on baddragon.com and display it prominently in
my home, subsist entirely off jack in the box tacos for a week, eat a whole lemon like an apple,
live stream myself cooking and then eating a tortilla filled with goldfish and Totino's pizza
rolls, get into get into Bandori. Uh, what I don't know what that is. It's a it's a anime like it's
it's like a it's like a gotcha game. It's one of those. It's the one one of the ones with like a
lot of girls by by a mug that says, don't talk to me until I've come in my wife and then film
myself drinking Mountain Dew gamer fuel out of it. Stick a bunch of Reese's minis on a slice of
cheese pizza and eat it. It goes on like this for a while. These are these are just like honestly
the only one of those that I think is that bad is the is the by the expensive dildo one because
I gotta imagine the most expensive one on bad dragon is like in the four digits. It's definitely
a few hundred. I haven't done the full map the way that it I was kind of uh uh what was I trying
to say I didn't quite understand how it worked because it's they don't have like oh hello someone
else just joined. Oh who's who's that? Who just joined? Hello. Gib. Hey. Hey Gib. Hi. Hello. Hey.
Welcome to the podcast. Hey. Well we're doing a surprise. We have two hosts now.
Yay. Woo. Ah it's a real podcast. No it can't be true. It's true. It's sad but true. I just wondered
in here. Don't don't give me that host job. Don't give me that that lady. Hey whoa introduce yourself.
Hello everyone. I'm Gib and take. I make art. She made it. Congratulations.
I don't know if you watched any of Minerva's videos that I told everyone to watch because
I like them a lot. I had a I had a five second like what a clicked link and I saw Pokemon
let's plays. I was like oh cool. I didn't have time. Oh my god you watched the let's play.
Oh I clicked I clicked on it for a few seconds. I was like okay cool it's Pokemon. I was about to
be very impressed because that's my LD. Elden a double cast famous a poke tuber just like just like
me. I well I was about to say I would have been uh hilariously surprised if you had watched the
Pokemon let's plays because that's my least popular content. It was just the first thing I saw.
Yeah I got you. Um where were we? Where were we? We were talking about Joe Biden.
Right let's let's get back to it. I made a bunch of basically that was a very long tangent I probably
didn't need to go on but the the short version of this is I'm glad I don't bet like actual money
because I would have lost a lot of money on the election. Right right um
you know what why are we talking about politics? Ah you know the pro cre- ah pee this podcast
gone too political lately. Well speaking of politics out of my podcast. Thank you thank you.
Out of you. You gotta keep me in line. Um speaking of speaking of uh gambling or whatever the fuck
betting betting on things. Nice nice. Uh my bit my bitcoin update I've lost six pennies. Fuck you.
Six pennies have gone down. Good good good. Since I invested it's gone up and down um I've like the
maximum like I invested one whole pound British sterling pound uh to the bitcoin craze so I'm
cashing in when it gets when it gets big I'm just waiting just waiting it out. It's just kind of
it's just kind of been wobbling like it peaked and then it dropped and then I got scared and I
sold and since then it's just kind of been wobbling like up and down around where I sold it at so
you know who knows who knows what could happen you know they say the market's bullish they say
the they say we're nowhere near the market cap so you know just keep holding on to it it'll go up
eventually just just keep holding just keep holding either it goes to absolute zero like zero of my
investment is is remained and then I will invest again because that means it's gone down or I'll
become the new Elon Musk you know. Yeah Christ true really the greatest accomplishment anyone
can have is being the new Elon Musk. He was on the Simpsons. No that can't be that's not that's not
possible. No you know the way it's true it's it's true and Lisa Lisa calls him like the
most important living inventor. Jesus Christ. That's how you know that's how you know Simpsons
is fucking over that's how you know it should have ended a long time ago that's the moment. The
nature of the Simpsons is that okay the Simpsons is kind of like supernatural for me and that you
can tell me literally anything happened on it I'll be like sure all right. Well sure because I mean
it's it's had like 40 40 thousand episodes. Yeah exactly. It's just like eventually they
exhaust all possible ideas. There is there is a clip or a series of images from the Simpsons
to express any idea that a human can conceive and hold in their mind. I saw one I saw one
one of the guys uh one of the two guys who host Anamorph in Time the leftist Anamorph's
podcast which I have been which I have been I have been binging this week posted a reaction
get to some shit about the like coronavirus vaccine you know like rising cases in the United
States and it was the scene it was the scene when Homer owns the bowling alley of when first he's
reading like advanced like business and then he goes down to basic like business guide and then
he finally just goes down to just like staring at a bowling ball and it was that with epidemiology.
Oh my god. And I was like the Simpsons is the truly the greatest the greatest cultural monument
that humanity has yet has ever erected or ever will erect. It's like there's there's a Simpsons
reference for everything and there's a SpongeBob reference for everything. I who who do you think
okay who who wins in a fight uh Homer Simpson or SpongeBob they're both yellow so that doesn't
give either of them an advantage. I feel like SpongeBob has more powers of like cartoon invincibility
like you can you can do basically anything to SpongeBob and he'll be basically okay where I
feel like Homer still obeys like some of the laws of like actual human anatomy and that if like
you kill you do something to him that would kill a normal person it would actually kill him.
That's true. Yeah it's just SpongeBob's harder to kill but he's so weak and he's also tiny.
He's weak and tiny. That's a good point oh right because in the the what is it in like the movie
when he's riding on David Hasselhoff yeah he's like really oh because he's the size of like an actual
sea sponge. He's the size of an yeah or not he's the size of like a table like a sink sponge.
All right because he he's he's a sea sponge but that just means he's a kitchen sponge that
lives in the sea. That lives in the sea yes exactly. It's self hilarious. I was thinking like if there's
like character archetypes you can match with the Simpsons and SpongeBob I'm sure there are but like
my first thought was like oh Homer would be Patrick though but then also SpongeBob I think he would
be both I think SpongeBob and Patrick combined would be Homer. He kind of is the shape of
Patrick but the color of SpongeBob. He combines both of their best qualities. Yes it's like it's like
main character like plot driving instincts from SpongeBob with the sort of raw like unfiltered
dumbassery of Patrick. Dude dude Squidward versus Moe. Squidward versus Moe. Oh god.
Oh well I mean is it a physical battle or is it a clarinet playing contest? That determines
everything. I mean Moe has a gun. Moe has a fucking gun. He would literally just blow
no no no no Squidward could like leap like splash out of the water and like like face crab attack
Moe and he'd be like ah I can't see. The most fucked up thing about SpongeBob is that Squidward
is an octopus. He's not a squid. That is but he's only got six legs. Does he? Because yeah he's got
his four he's got his four like leg legs and his two arm tentacles. I'm pretty sure every time
they do like a thing where they're out of the water and they show them as actual animals. Squidward
is an octopus not a squid. Also I believe that because they have actual squids in the show and
they have the pointy heads and his head is round like an octopus. Like he doesn't have the right
number of legs but I am like pretty sure this is a real thing and it's really fucked up. When he
when he moves to that like gated community with only other with all the other Squidward's yes
does it say that like there's their octopuses octopi or does it even like specify I mean it might not
even like say what they are it's just like assume that like yes these people are all just like him
whatever that means yeah I don't think they ever might be how they do it I don't think they ever
explain that we're just supposed to like infer uh everything about that location oh hang on
Steven Hillenberg designed Squidward with six arms because of convenience for simpler
animations Squidward was designed to have a large bulbous head like an octopus the creator
liked the way the creator liked the way the bulbous head on Squidward signified him as a
grumpy next door neighbor blah blah blah however due to the inconvenience of the original name
octoword the original name was octoword the name Squidward was used instead just because it sounded
better basically um that's a octoword isn't octoword yeah yeah yeah high five
ow well now we know uh you high five yourself and hurt yourself we've learned yeah I did
yeah I did it's exactly what happened pro gamer move get Gibb did you see did you see what uh did
you see what Christine Weston Chandler tweeted today I would never go to twitter.com oh Jesus Christ
she she retweeted the picture of your your picture of the slime coin with diamond tiara
and she she did and then she and she's said some stuff about coins and then she
and then she literally plugged my comic oh yeah you guys have like talked to her before right
yes yeah yeah a bunch of times she she messaged me she messaged me on twitter did I say this last
episode I hope I'm not repeating myself I don't think so I always get confused okay well she messaged
me like earlier this week or last week with just a picture of like a cool crystal that she bought
on some crystal website and said like hey look it's just like in Arizona uh uh you know and I
said ha it looks it looks just like the powder and that Christine turned blue and that gave
alternate timeline phantom horn his phantom his titular phantom horn and she said ha ha yes that's
correct and then she today she tweeted a picture of that crystal and then a bunch of like stuff about
slime and punishment and a link to my uh tapas page which I just this is what I thought was really
funny and then of course and then of course 50 people responded with like uh you know like uh uh
some pictures of like uh chris you're a fucking piece of shit and these are these are embarrassing
these are gross drawings people did of you ha ha you you fuck what a what a nightmare people just need
to I I propose we all just stop caring about Christine Weston Chandler like no I like her
though I mean I get I mean like the whole like how do I put this that I think she's funny the the
whole christorian thing and like all the people who like obsess over her in like the like stalkery
way that has to have too much in yeah there's a definitely a group of people who are far too
invested in the life and times of some stranger on the internet that happens to have written so much
you exactly like I uh christine is like one of those people where it's like because my series
that's like popular now in my youtube channel is when posting goes wrong which is about times when
people made posts that went wrong and like on one hand sonichu is like the perfect example of this
because it really was just someone posting some shit that got way out of hand and escalated to
like this insane internet phenomenon but on the other hand I so don't want to make a fucking video
about christian like there's already so many of them yeah a lot of them including yours are really
good yeah and then yeah on top of that I gotta see I've got a sequel coming out but ooh that's
exciting I've I've had a sequel like almost ready to go for like a year now but I'm just I have some
specific criteria that I want to meet before I release it but I mean but anyway right uh uh
yeah I got you um never but then the last never forget I said anything no it's it's cool
editor editor edit out everything no don't cut it cut all of it um one of my favorite uh gags on
a podcast is somebody says something like that and then follows it with editor cut that out but
you like hear the whole thing um so we we yeah I'm our we no our our editor never we he's not
allowed actually to cut anything out there's no editing in this podcast anything that he does cut
out anything that he does cut out goes to our secret bonus episode we say to him we say to him
please edit out the embarrassing parts and but but a previous message says whatever you do don't
listen to us when we say that and we've been cursed with constantly being embarrassing online
all are all are seeing all those embarrassing moments that were too embarrassing for the main
podcast are going in the collected a cut content bonus episode on patreon wow for subscribers only
yeah wow I had a dream I had a dream that our patreon had gone up and what a dream it was
yeah it was only a dream though oh okay well uh uh sorry I interrupted your oh no it's fine I was
just gonna say like that's like one half of his there's already too many videos about chris chan
and the other thing is that like um I heard a quote once from I think it was the down the rabbit hole
guy uh fred frederick frederick nudesan yeah frederick nudesan where he's who I was on a stream
with one time that does not exist anywhere on the internet anymore because it was deleted mysterious
um bummer but he said something to the effect of once you make a video about chris chan that
does well that's all people will talk to you about ever and yeah I would prefer that not to be my fate
um it yeah I mean it doesn't necessarily I think that's somewhat in my experience that gets you
big and noticed in the first place um maybe but I mean I mean I mean more I mean more people know
me from the the sonichu lecture than from anything else that's true but it's not like I'm inundated
with like it's not like I'm inundated with with people wanting to talk to me about it all the time
it doesn't it's not like annoying I don't find it that annoying uh I mean some I don't know maybe
sometimes someone will when I when someone knows me and I like I find that it's from that I'm usually
like oh that's fine I don't know I guess I would there are other things I would like think it was
cooler if people knew me for than that but like it's not a problem it's not a problem that people
know me from that that's my two cents on the on the subject I got you uh I don't know um
I don't know uh uh I just I just thought it was neat I just thought it was neat that uh she was
that she just felt like tweeting about my fucking uh uh slime comic and stuff today I think that's
fucking neat oh yeah I've seen the the the retweet of my diamond tiara slime corp slime coin pick
I really like that photo it's strange I mean I know she follows me but she very rarely interacts
with anything I post mm-hmm wait I will post I will post the picture in the in the chat uh because uh
because uh there it is bam oh it's loading sorry my internet's bad that's fine it's fine okay there
we go very nice gorgeous gorgeous gorgeous um okay okay so so uh I heard a thing uh Minerva are you
familiar with homestuck you ever heard of a homestuck oh christ you ever heard about this wacky
thing on the internet call homestuck it's kind of like undertale but better oh unfortunately
fuck you I don't I don't I don't I don't know I don't know what your problem is uh me me and Gibber
unironic homestuck uh uh uh stands home stand from from way back oh wow homestands are you are you uh
are you uh I don't know what are you I'm more of a spatula myself what's your what's your relationship
with homestuck um Minerva my situation was that I had a bunch of friends who were really into it
when it was first getting big and I like purposely avoided it because it seemed it was like I think
the length of it intimidated me but also yeah I it just didn't speak to me in that way where it
would justify me reading through that much and then years later I started my uh main series
what your favorite ship says about you and at some point I was like well I have to do a
homestuck video eventually because everyone kept joking like oh if you did a homestuck video it'd
be like an hour you can't do a home like that would be insane and so I was like well that's a
challenge um I ended up reading about half of homestuck I got about halfway through it before
I got sick of it and couldn't read anymore which when you say half do you know the actual whole
length of the thing do you know where the halfway point is yeah I oh god what how many acts are
there again there's six but the sixth one is so big technically seven seven is just a video
I think if you read to the end of act five I would say you you did it correctly yeah I think I got
a little bit into act six is where I end up okay that honestly honestly good place to quit I
specifically remember the point where I quit was uh what fucking character was it is Dirk the second
one Dirk is the the alt brother of Dave Dirk's autoresponder I couldn't stand the autoresponder
I was just like every time this thing shows up it wastes like a huge amount of my time and says
nothing I'm so like more so than car cat like I've had enough I felt that way I just felt that way
about a lot of stuff in act six Jen I felt that way about like most characters in in act six even
the ones that had been good before um yeah I like I don't I never like had any confirmation one
where the other but it always felt like act six was hussy like getting bored of the story he was
telling and wanting to tell a completely different story but still needing to finish home stuck so
he's changed focus a little bit made it much more about these new characters with their teen drama
and less about the adventure that had been happening up to that point and then he just
sort of finished it with a big fight scene okay but I bring it up because I found I saw posted
maybe on twitter or somewhere this thing this this blog post you remember the whole thing about how
they crowdfunded hiveswap and then they gave it to that development studio and the development studio
basically like took the money and ran and made some other thing oh yeah I remember hearing about this
I think that was only ever a rumor I don't think it was ever like
completely confirmed but I'm I feel like it's like it seems like it would be the case
but well that seemed to be the narrative and that's what I had thought happened this whole time
I don't know I came upon this blog post saying that like no actually it was hussy actually it was
hussy that like fucked them over in various ways and I didn't actually I admit I didn't actually
read through this whole thing because it's really long but um I don't know it made me I I hope it's
not true I hope that uh I hope that hussy is a good boy but uh I don't know maybe he's I mean it
wouldn't it wouldn't like be like shocking to hear that he's bad at managing things based on
like even after the the whole odd gentleman thing and like the creation of what pumpkin studios
or whatever it was called hiveswap still took a billion years and yeah I don't know there's a
lot of little things maybe hussy isn't that good at organizing a business maybe he's better just
making little comics and when it blew up the way the homestuck did he was like shit I don't
fucking know what I'm doing maybe he's still like that I don't know I would perhaps I would not at
all be surprised if hussy was kind of an asshole just based off of like how he came across in the
comic I kind of got the sense that he was like he was self aware about having a big ego but not
enough to actually do anything about it um which is not a great combination
yeah I can kind of I can kind of see that oh no it's impossible anyone that makes a thing that I
like must be only good uh but what if but what if when I'm making a big comic and I want to be
best friends with Andrew hussy and he says uh fuck you that sucks I don't want that it can't
happen no it can't be it will never happen hey hussy would never screw me over like he
screwed the odd gentleman allegedly he's good still don't know you're right I'll have to read this
it's it seems like it seems like the the major allegation here is that like hussy like paid them
the money and then like and instead of having them make the game they were supposed to make he told
them like do stuff for the act seven finale instead and then basically tried to tell them like okay
now that you've done that like like do the game as well seemed like he was maybe trying to like
double dip with his money on them or something that's sounds like what they're saying was wrong
and why like the project fell through and they didn't complete it for him that's how it seems I
don't know it's it's really long and I'm sure there's more here uh I don't know I thought that was
interesting and a little troubling uh because uh I haven't even played hiveswab have you played
hiveswab give yeah I did I did a review of it back when I was still doing those and I said in the
review I would eventually play the second one when it came out and have you played have you
played the second one is the second one out it's out now it's been so long that my of my
review channel career crumbled and I gave up in that time span well um owned indeed uh I don't
know the owned by the time the first one was like it had a few nice references and it was
decent uh looking and playing uh like point and click game but it didn't it wasn't like amazing
it was just sort of like oh yeah cool like kick started point and click adventure
somewhat interesting puzzles but yeah it was all right yeah the the best thing I could say about
it was that it could get more people interested in homestuck which is a better thing which is what
I ended up saying which would similarly the best thing about homestuck is that it can get people
to read problem sleuth which is a better thing valid no um no I would say I would say it's very
very good like more more consistently good and and easier to get through I'm I'm I joke I joke a
little bit I think it I think it's in some ways it's better uh but uh in in exploring all of the
little ideas that it comes up with and um neatly wrapping everything up at the end with a really
cool set of of events that like everything leads up to that point even though it seems to be going
in random directions the entire time like it's really clever I really like the the the structure
of problem sleuth how it manages to and he did it in just one year which is like incredible for sure
for sure did you do either of you see did either of you see the the drama the drama that happened
this week on twitter with um uh Lindsay Ellis and Sarah Zed who's I have I have Lindsay Ellis blocked
I'm mutuals with Sarah Zed so I'm surprised I didn't see at least some of this Lindsay Ellis
has me blocked even though we've never interacted we've never interacted I don't know why that's
super funny but I'm blocked by Lindsay Ellis for some reason you're on you're on the list Ben
I guess I guess I'm on the list uh um but uh okay all right so the the the drama with those two
and a third party who I will I won't I won't mention them oh anyway uh I don't know they were just uh
Sarah Zed I think tweeted that like don't do this like don't interact with creators in this way like
I'm getting like weird messages from someone and then Lindsay Ellis replied to that saying like
I think I think she showed screenshots of them and Lindsay Ellis replied saying I think I think
we both are like having the same problem with the same person I'm getting inappropriate messages
from someone that da da da da and then she posted screenshots and it had the the icon in the name
blurred out almost blurred out there was a little bit of the icon showing and people um people like
looked at the icon and looked at what it was saying and it seems like the person in question might
have been Quinton reviews oh my god yeah and and like the the basic gist of it I should I'm not
gonna go and find them but maybe I'll post like screenshots these particular screenshots in the
chat you're saying I kind of Quinton potentially Quinton reviews was messaging Lindsay Ellis and
this other person in a creepy way yes well the thing is the the way they were talking about it
it sounded like oh this it's creepy it's it's inappropriate but like the content of the messages
it's inappropriate in the sense that like it's a little too familiar and sort of comes off as a
little like desperate but it's not like it's not like it's not like creep shit like sexual
shit it's just like hey how you doing you know uh uh you know uh I really like you and I like
your work and stuff and then like months later like hey you never replied to my message haha
like what's going on I'd really love to connect sometime haha months later hey you know I don't
know if I ever burn this bridge at some point that's why you're not responding to me haha okay
but if you ever want to like okay and then months later okay well I guess sorry sorry for this I
apologize you know just like lame see that's not even just lame it's just sad it's not good
they they didn't call it creepy yeah it's it's just it's just a bad look like I was just like a
sad look just because he got back at him almost subscribers doesn't mean you're actually hot
shit no no you know I don't know I just they were the way they were talking about it made it sound
like this person was like being really I don't know when I actually saw the messages it didn't
it didn't seem I didn't it didn't think it was as bad as they kind of made it out to be and I kind
of thought then the whole thing like Quentin looks like a loser but both of them just kind of look
like they're catty and like they're just like gossiping about someone and I don't think it's a
good look for anyone involved uh I thought it was I think the whole thing was gross well I haven't
seen any of this stuff I'm trying to find it but um the idea of the idea of like highlighting an
anonymous message saying hey guys don't do this in their defense to their credit they didn't they
didn't like deliberately try and out this person yeah but yeah so that's that's good that's I'm
glad that they didn't but I don't know if they wanted to if they wanted to talk about this this
person who like they both don't like in their DMs like I don't know they could have done it in
private if they wanted to if they wanted to they didn't have to do it in a public twitter thread
yeah I don't know yeah I I think that's valid I mean I get it I get why she'd tweet that because
like yeah like people on the internet do not understand boundaries and sometimes you just
want to let people know like hey don't interact with your faves this way it's really weird and
uncomfortable because it's like some of these people like maybe you actually like could talk to
them in like a reasonable way but just because of the way they approach you it makes it really
weird and awkward and like okay this is someone who clearly like is gonna be like they're they're
like if not a stan just someone who like has me on a pedestal and I don't want to like deal with that
so I think it's like it's reasonable to like ask people to like have boundaries and like understand
this shit it's just unfortunate that you know they didn't fully take the icon out and the dude got
exposed yeah and like it's yeah it's it's funny it's funny that it was between I don't know it's
funny that it was Sarah and Quinton because Quinton's bigger than Sarah Quinton has more
subscribers and yet apparently he was the one doing the messaging and she was like hey you know
lay off just because you're a fan that doesn't mean I'm your friend or whatever well I mean that's
the funny thing about YouTube or like web content in general is that um you can have a fave who
actually because this is something I discovered when I got like YouTube clout is that you can have
a fave who has like way less engagement with you and is way less popular than you but you can still
have that weird dynamic of like looking up to them and wanting to like like get in with them as if you
were like you know um as if they had some sort of like um yeah edge over you in terms of like
popularity because like all of you mean yeah like all of the people who I was like a huge fan of
prior to getting my YouTube channel were just like people in the ruby fandom which is like a big
fandom but it's not the kind of thing where you get like capital C clout like no one has like
very few people have like multiple thousands of twitter followers because of that or whatever
so it's weird like being a fan of people who like technically have like fewer followers than me but
it's just like the dynamic still feels like it's there I gotta say this this whole thing
I don't know even if I would class it as drama it's just it's so I don't know mild
is this what passes for like news on twitter these days just like a little bit of a social
profile like some people looking not so great I don't know when when two when two kind of when
two big like YouTube people are like talking shit about someone and it turns out to be a third
like big person and that I don't know that seems like that I think that's gossip worthy it does
appeal to like the um fuck you it does appeal to like the tabloid sensibility of like ooh look
at what your favorite like youtubers are saying about each other behind their back like exactly
exactly just burn them all all the youtubers get them in a room get them in a tuba room yeah kill
them just anyone over anyone anyone over a hundred k subs uh hang them hang them from the gallons I
would say in my opinion and yes yes in a video game in minecraft I guess oh if I have to minecraft
I was just so boring it sucks it's the lamest thing you could ever even think about
I can't think of a lame or though you know what's good you know what's better content oh no no that's
even worse I love I love content I love filling my face with content I'm seeing that my I'm seeing
that my fave krogsmash I didn't realize he had passed a hundred k subs he's up to 119 subs
have I talked about krogsmash you know krogsmash you know krogsmash I have never heard of krogsmash
what's he do I think you may have do you know dwarf fortress I do you know the game dwarf fortress
I have heard of dwarf fortress well krogsmash is a dwarf fortress youtuber uh a a a dwoo
I don't know you'd call it sure um he does um you know he he builds fortresses and he'll like
he does like I don't know he'll like narrate the the games that he plays on the fortresses
that he builds and he'll like pick out little dwarf individual dwarves and like give them
little character arcs and do like art of them and stuff uh he's doing um he just concluded the second
annual uh splatter face tournament where he picks like random people from around his like
generated world to like come and uh fight in gladiatorial combat uh they two days ago the
championship bout came out and it was the greatest thing I've ever seen uh I literally teared up at
the end uh it's so fucking good I can't even believe it uh don't watch splatter face too go back and
watch the first this is my recommendation watch the first splatter face because the characters
in the second splatter face are like you know the ones that survived the first one come back and
you have you have to know you have to know all the lore you have to know like where the where
the battle beetle got his steel helmet and stuff like this is all this is all so crucial critical
dwarf fortress lore oh it's so some of the some of the some of the fighters in the second round
are so cool I'm not gonna I'm not gonna say who my favorites are because that'd be spoilery um
I'm always impressed when youtube channels develop lore that's more complicated than like
actual published properties like yeah did you ever look into siva gunner lore um I I've heard
about it I know I don't know anything about I didn't know that was lore I know that there's like a big
it's a big group effort to make funny video game rip music yeah what happened was when they first
started it it was just like posting high quality rips as they called it which were all very funny
mashups but what happened was over time to like mix things up I guess they started introducing
like plot lines to it where there would be like characters who like quote unquote run the channel
or take over the channel or something like that they kept adding like more and more of them it
got incredibly complicated and involved like I'm pretty sure like multiple universes and time travel
and like a a key element was smashing the motherfucking like button among other things it got like
complicated to the point where I could not even try to keep track of it and it's like on the one hand
is that like the best storytelling maybe not is it impressive as hell yes yeah there was what did
they do king for a day it was like a tournament they held yeah the public would vote on who would
take over the channel for a certain amount of time afterwards that was like one of the less
complicated things they did yeah I heard of that people I know were like involved with that
um I saw um I saw a new video from that channel that makes the knives you know oh yeah the knife
shines out of weird shit well I saw a new video I didn't actually make it out of smoke did he make
it out of feelings no he made it out of bismuth but the um isn't that an old video but the the the
video well maybe but the video was called making a knife out of bismuth to correct an injustice
and I I don't know what that means I assume it has to do with like the lore because I know I
watched like a more recent one recently and like there's like a story to them now like there's like
aliens and stuff and people in masks oh my god and uh yeah there's like a hot like a the main
character got like taken hostage or whatever knife channel is turning and it didn't even have anything
to do with the knife he was making knife channels like yeah turning into a shown in anime yeah
it does it has like plot lines now it's like an abstract
shit people love getting creative with stuff like it's it's difficult to like make the exact same
type of thing over and over again and so I'm sure like youtubers like that where they're known for
exactly one thing they're like I don't just want to make another knife I want to make another knife
and also this and then people get into it it's so silly that's definitely a real thing with
YouTube is that when your channel is like you make one kind of video and you make it over and over
again for like some people can do that indefinitely and I have a lot of respect for that but a lot
of people it's like you either get tired of doing the same thing or you have to find some way to
make it interesting for yourself by adding new elements or you just have to like move on to
something else entirely and people tend to not like that a lot of people on YouTube just want
you to make the same content over and over again forever it's I mean it does every every concept
seems to wear out as welcome I was like a subscriber of the hydraulic press channel
which is like oh yeah it spearheaded the whole like crushing things and seeing what happens
they were like the first one but they also one of the biggest and they kept doing those videos and
it they like iterate a little bit with like the types of things they they try to do but at the end
of the day you turn on the video like oh what is what is it this time okay let's skip to the part
where it explodes watch that five second clip and be like hey well that was satisfying I guess and
then I don't know it's just like I keep seeing them in my my subscription feed and I'm like it's the
same thing I know it's just gonna be another one of these explosion things under pressure
I don't care anymore on sub like they didn't do anything wrong I just got tired of the concept
and I I I know that they're not like changing it up enough you know it's different from like an
educational channel but would you want but would you want to watch it if it had like weird story
lines about like I don't know like a villain shows up with like a different press and like
it becomes like a contest about which one can crush things better it's not about one of them
steals the press and they have to go on a trip to Europe to retrieve it hey I think it's it's not
really like my job to figure out how to continually make that one concept interesting it's just that
I am tired of that concept and because there's nothing else to it I'm done I don't know how long
those sorts of things can last like either the creator burns out or the audience loses interest
and you need something more timeless more like rewatchable once you've seen something explode
you don't really need to see it again unless it was incredible
yeah I think uh that's true like some concepts just have a longer shelf life than others like
you know if you're just crushing things with a hydraulic press over and over again like you said
eventually it's like okay I've seen enough things get crushed by a hydraulic press to
know what all of the other things will look like getting crushed by a hydraulic press
just the nature of these concepts Krug smash has said that he has no plans to ever make any
non-dwarf fortress related content because like dwarf fortress has like such a massive possibility
space uh within it that being said he does like I mean the whole the whole splatter face like
tournament thing was probably was him like experimenting with like what else can I do
with dwarf fortress aside from just like building and running a fort and like his his new the new
fort that he's that he took a break from to do splatter face it's called um the watchful eyes I
think and it's like it's totally different from his other forts because it's not like a big uh
industrial complex it's just like a a group of like six dudes like trying to like for it be a little
like a a band of rogues out in the woods in a shack somewhere uh so you know he he there's there's
you can mix it up you can mix it up in in many different ways there's many different strategies
one can employ I suppose yes very wise I find it to be like especially punk to to have like a list
of concepts that you want to make videos about making all of the videos and then stopping
like um like uh what was it every frame of painting they stopped once they had enough
of their ideas out there in video form and because of that they are like a complete package
and I occasionally go back and rewatch all of their videos because it's like ah it's just like a
series it's a box set those were very good videos they were very good videos but how can it be that
that person doesn't have any more like ideas of like here's a concept from film that I could
you know explain or or or dive into and discuss I ate no film so I don't know but um I mean
I I I know what you mean about it's cool to just like have a start and a stop you know it's like
it's like in bakuman you know they start making the fucking the fucking athello or the black versus
white the angel of manga like yeah yeah whatever it is it's yeah and then they're like and they try
to keep going they're like no we we had a story want to tell we just got to fucking get in tell it
and get out and when it's done it's done and that's how you make a fucking masterpiece and everyone was
like oh that's true yeah that's true but it's weird to do that about every frame of painting just
because that doesn't seem like the kind of thing that is like oh yep I've said all I have to say
about film I have run out of opinions on film it's it's not like opinions it's like the the
different methods of I think it's sort of the purpose that they had was to like give people
like a a a like a an easy to digest snapshot of like as many different film techniques and
ways to think about film as possible in easy to digest like videos and in that sense like they could
come back and like technically talk way more in more depth for hours about other things I don't
know that that was their mission statement as far as I understand I just like that it was a mission
statement and they finished it I will say I think a factor we're thinking about there is that like
the guy who made those videos was like a professional film editor and as a youtuber who has a day job
and likes my day job and doesn't want to quit it when you're in that situation the motivation
to make more videos is dramatically lower it's like I can it's like I can just quit this whenever
like I don't need this it's nice it's fun but like I'm under no pressure which is like a good
position to be in because like youtubers complain about burnout constantly but the flip side of
that is that you can be comfortable to the point where it's like I lose nothing by quitting this I
can just stop whenever I want I want I want I want youtubers to be so economically you know
distressed that they are just forced to churn out content the same the same content that I know
and love with with as little variation as possible please this the safest path to financial stability
should be their only path to survival that's that's the optimal ecosystem for me a consumer of content
just keep making the same content until you die that you're not allowed to have other jobs
all the good videos already exist there's no there's no point there's no reason
that's true that's true nothing will ever oh wait I've just had a great idea actually forget it
then I'm gonna come I'm gonna come back to making videos I'm nothing I'm gonna I'm gonna
ever top splatterface 2 championship bout I'm sorry but we peaked exactly two days ago as a society
what was that what splatterhouse thing the thing he was just talking about the entire yeah the
crumb smash tournament oh yeah you know sorry it was I wasn't listening and I will never listen to
you ever I know yeah yeah oh very nice oh cool give just her drip or fortress and immediately
zoned out look I know what they started there's small people and they're in a fortress and it
sucks to be them because they die constantly shut up they have a great time they love they love
drink and they love industry and if you run your fort well they get plenty of both all right if war
fortress will probably die in like a in like a werewolf attack would they be one block tall
in minecraft yes definitely um yeah because everything is a grid so everything would be
equally like wide and tall and deep everything is a cube um I do want to say I think I mentioned
before that my my roommates and I started a fort a couple weeks ago and it was called fern relics
and fern relics had a terribly just this week actually fern relics officially died several
weeks ago yeah okay fern relics was beautiful it was like it was built into the sides of this canyon
that these like that these two rivers converged in right so there was like cliff walls facing each
other well um you know we were just going about our business trying to like build and then but
there was a main bridge went over the top of the canyon uh with you know the canyon down beneath
it and just one day for no reason at all people are just milling about going over this bridge and
one dwarf just suddenly the full moon comes out and he turns into a werehorse and this werehorse
just goes apeshit on this bridge and slaughters like half the the population like 50 dwarves out of
like a hundred are just like bashed in with his hooves or like hurled off the bridge and fall
to their deaths and and because we live in an evil biome the the bodies of like all these slain
dwarves and animals like start coming back and they come back down in the river underneath the bridge
and the other dwarves find them so scary to see these like these like crawling undead like like
living that now like are just hanging out down in the bottom of the river that they can't cross
the bridge because they'll be trying to cross it and they'll see one of these skeletons moving and
then they'll get scared and run away um so nothing can get done in the fortress anymore
and then uh my friend took it took it for his year and he sent the our military on an expedition
to a necromancer's tower from which they never returned
and then like a huge swarm of like a hundred fucking ghouls and goblins and zombies just
like swarmed down from the north and just devoured everyone and and and murdered them butchered us
butchered us wholesale so we had to abandon that fortress but we started a new one i think a little
bit to the east and the new one is called it's so fucking cool the new one is called steel father
and steel father is we're going to we're gonna build up our army we're gonna go back and we're
gonna reclaim fern relics we're gonna fight back the undead scourge and i'm so fucking excited
because all i wanted all i wanted to do when fern relics was find steel all i wanted to do
was get up a steel smithing operation and we just didn't have the minerals for it we didn't have iron
we didn't have flux stones so i'm it would be so sad and tragic if steel father doesn't have them
either but my fingers are crossed it should be okay hey it should be okay hey ben if if i were to
like buy i don't know where to get i guess on steam dwarf fortress um how how come you don't have to
buy it oh is it just a free i think you can buy it on steam but like it's just free also oh okay well
then there's no reason to not try it but um how like difficult is it to learn is it like like you
need to study up or is it just to jump in and see what happens okay there there's a lot to learn
but like basically it's basically you just basically have to get familiar with it and like
there are guides like the wiki just has a guide that will like walk you through like the the first
uh actually krug smash has a video called your first fortress which just walks you through
building a basic fortress and introduces you to like the basic mechanics it basically dwarf
fortress is just a series of menus that you just have to like navigate to do the things you want
to do and if you don't know how to do something you literally just like go to the wiki and look it up
and like find out how to access that menu and like that's how you do it um so you just kind of have
to play for a while with like the wiki open so you can like know how to do things uh and it takes a
little while like probably your first like fortress will just be a complete wash and end up like a
hideous monstrosity and you'll die but that's fine yeah that's just the way it is yeah i do like
yeah like base building roguelite type of things oh you should give it a try give you should give
it a try like kenshi if it was if it feels like kenshi even a little bit i'd probably enjoy it
our our our fern relics fern relics had a thriving mug industry like all of our best
stone crafters were making these like masterwork mugs and and and trading them with the other
groups and one of the relics that someone made was a bone scepter that was topped with a golden mug
and uh our our mayor was our our mayor was named muggin melville we gave him the name uh muggin
could he drink out of it i i like to think that you could yeah i like to think that you could um
and then like yeah mayor mayor muggin melville i think she like i think in the werehorse attack
she got injured and went into a coma and then like she was still in a coma when the undead
attacked and killed everyone and i think they killed her in the coma but then she like was
risen from the dead as a zombie and like her and the other zombies just started like beating the
shit out of each other and uh my friend john the for like one of the first things he did in the new
fortress steel father was he built over the well he built a statue of uh uh of muggin melville as
like a menacing undead as like a warning as like a warning against like this is this is what we're
fighting against you know never forget the tragedy that befell fern relics oh what a fucking game
the epic highs and lows of dwarf fortress it's almost as exciting as watching the bitcoin ticker
it all just comes back to bitcoin eventually i'm almost as invested ben have you have you mentioned
that you sold it all i did yeah at the at the beat that was like the first thing i think i
mentioned this episode sold it all lost 200 bucks uh sad sad times in literally like one day i went
from being up by a thousand to down by 200 it was that bad easy come easy go
shit i've exhausted all the items on my list oh wow already yeah already uh what i know somebody
somebody else take over somebody tell somebody tell me what to think um uh well uh i mean the
only thing i've been doing the past week is my secret project my my secret mysterious construction
which is going along swimmingly same um same aside from that uh i've been oh i did a minecraft
hardcore right um but with the biome set to one biome desert so the entire map is desert
and it's hardcore so i have to try and fend for myself without the ability to easily collect wood
and it's actually really fun um because it involves a lot of uh figuring out how like you
have to find a village so that you can get food from them and then you have to trade and it's more
about like surviving than it is um just you know because minecraft is so easy you can easily become
super powerful and indestructible in a normal map but in a big desert uh it's it's scary you know
i've actually been i've actually been going into the pcp minecraft server once in a while
and just mining more marble just because it's fun i don't know oh uh give a hat next time next
time we do a shekels for heckles i have a present for you oh oh in the game wow cool i uh i won't i
won't say what it is uh i said a diamond maron pan is going to be very mad uh but uh i'm gonna i
don't care but you're gonna like it you're gonna like it a lot all right no it's not a diamond
it's better believe it or not it's better than a single two diamonds yes exactly uh i've also
been playing a lot of noita i think i talked about noita before the like road the dungeon roguelike
that is also like a sand simulator yeah that one's weird yeah i think i think we talked about it last
time because oh yeah because you or was it on the stream that you said that it was that was the game
he was germa was playing when that thing happened when the when the debt was accrued yeah yeah it's
you ever um you ever play one of those like sand simulators like the falling sand games
uh oh no it'll be like a it'll be like a black screen and you can is lemmings one of those no
what am i thinking of no it's like you it's like you can like build up piles of sand and then lemmings
walk around no you fuck what do you mean said like you draw like you draw like you draw like a
metal like a line like a bowl or something and you can like drop sand and the sand falls and it's
like pixelated particle effects and you can drop like other kinds of sand like gunpowder or something
and then you can take fire and you can put the fire next to the gunpowder and the pieces of
gunpowder will start going and there's you can have like weird gases and stuff oh wait i think i
i played one of these when i was in like high school or something like that like a long time ago
i mean they're they're fun to like fuck around with yeah noita noita is like it's like that
physics system but it's built like these dungeons that you like have these magic wands that you
like shoot bullets out of and you like are going around killing monsters and stuff and collecting
gold uh noita is so fucking hard i thought i was like getting pretty far into it but i wasn't
i got to like the fourth stage like a couple of times but there's like there's so many like
hidden zones and like there's like there's like levels beyond my wildest dreams i have like barely
even scratched the surface of it i suck at video games so fucking bad it's so embarrassing i always
joke that it's so cool though i growing up i was like pretty much exclusively like an rpg kid like
i played final fantasy and pokemon and like a few other similar jrpgs and uh now my joke is like
final fantasy are video games for people who are bad at video games and that also applies to kingdom
hearts yeah yeah i mean i played i played after like i got the playstation i think i was mostly
like an rpg guy you know i hadn't i hadn't nes uh as a little baby so i was you know i played like
you know platformers a bit i like platformers and stuff uh i'm best at like turn-based things like
pokemon i'm a pokemon master because i'm just like i'm just you know i'm just so intelligent
just so i have it's didn't think so many steps ahead of the average the average person it's just
like you know invincible huge brain individual uh yeah i mean i i've always been like a proponent
of like it's okay to be shit at video games it's okay to enjoy games in a casual way and be an
actual casual like straight up because that's me i don't like games that are difficult it is okay
but i really like noida and it is like frustrating to me that i'm like bad at it because i want to
win it because i like it well of course there's always going to be frustration when you lose
and you want to get good at things that's that's not the same as like and i mean it um like
feeling compulsion to be good otherwise well i feel i feel like i should be able to do it
because i've i've beaten hard games before like i've beaten i've beaten down well and i've like
you know i beat the old like hell binding of isek and stuff and i've beaten i've gotten pretty far
in like uh i think i've i've looped a few times in uh uh what's that one uh nuclear throne you know
is it safe i'm not like a complete shit game i'm not a complete shit game well hang on those those
all three of those so i expect better of myself all three of those games rely heavily on good
drops for like upgrades or whatever in between rounds or and stuff like that's heavily luck-based
all three of those noita kind of is too like that's that's why those games are fun and frustrating
because it's it's not it's not entirely just your skill it's also what you happen to come across
if you if you're good if you're good though you can you can do well in most games like that even
unless you get like the absolute shittiest of drops like most most games like that and like
even shitty drops like a good player can still like make that that's the thing i think i think
those games they they feel compelling to get good at quote-unquote to get far in them because in
the back of your mind you're always thinking well i could have got luckier if i played exactly
at that skill level but i got better drops i would have got further so there's still chance to get
further and it's like ah i didn't get as far as i could have if i got the right things
and but that you don't have any control over that so you just keep playing over and over
hoping to get the the perfect the lucky yeah it's yeah it's a bit of a slot machine yeah that way
sure but i think you were right in the sense of like if you play through these games enough
eventually like some of that luck sort of gets evened out by the fact that like you always
you're you're you've just learned all the mechanics so well that you can sort of make do even if your
drops aren't ideal so it does getting it does still have that getting sorry sorry it does still
have that um element of like challenging but rewarding like very much the uh dark souls of
video games getting good at binding of isaac was not about like you know being like really like
twitchy with my fucking finger movements or whatever like shooting bullets and just like
getting good at binding of isaac was about learning like where and under what conditions
rooms spawn and like how to use like keys and like what what like the most net benefit you're
likely to get from the way you use your early like keys and bombs and stuff to like uh true there's
like which which yeah yeah but um so what's my point my point is that it's um i don't know i've
been like looking up guides noida feels like like i have learned about noida and like how
like its wand system works and stuff like that and like various like material interactions like how
you can if you put water in it in toxic waste the water will purify it and turn it into water
which is very helpful to know but even though i've learned a bunch i have not made it that much
further and it's i feel like i feel like noida is genuinely a like is maybe more luck based than
something else like binding of isaac but you can kind of like strategize around i don't know uh uh
noida's frustrating noida's really frustrating it feels i yeah you can you can die you can die
with like no warning in noida if you get if you fuck up your toast and then i get mad and i pound
my desk and my roommates say ben why are you pounding your desk and i say shut up
told you never to ask about what i do i i've been uh fixated actually on a specific puzzle game
um pit cross or nonogram or whatever it's called um on this website because uh pit cross
it's like a grid and there's numbers on columns and rows and the the numbers correspond to
filled in squares uh that are like in groups so if there's a one three one that means you
know on that column or row there is one on its own three together and then one on its own in that
order and so you have to try and use uh the numbers on the on the on the rows and columns to figure
out which squares are like colored in and which ones are blank and it's so it's so like this is
my favorite kind of of like puzzle game where it's like a lot of deduction it's like a charlotte
homes which parts are like like guarantee that this block is colored in and then once i know
that information what does that tell me about the rest of the board and you can slowly get all of it
but this this particular site it like it randomizes the board uh like random number
generation just like comes up with things like pit uh pick two what did i call it pictogram
whatever that sometimes that they're made of like pictures so they they they like pixelated
pictures and if you know what the picture is you can kind of guess which is something i hate
i don't like being able to guess i like to be able to deduce everything so i do this random version
and it's it's so satisfying getting so far in this thing but every single time i get right to
the end there are a few squares which are like absolutely 50 50 coin flips as to whether they're
blank or not and i have to like roll the dice right at the end and if i get it wrong um i it says
mistake one like one mistake you fucked up you chose the wrong devastation it's like and and if you
completely game without getting any mistakes you get a big like oh wow amazing perfect and i want
that perfect so bad but the fact is it's like i hate luck based games i hate any game that has
a luck aspect to it and this game is so good except for the final little bit there's always a
fucking coin flip sucks i used to be super into uh hearthstone which is obviously a very different
kind of game but it's another one of those things where it's like because it's a card game there's
a lot of skill involved but there is also a tremendous amount of luck um and people
bitched constantly about the luck element because everyone is a salty bitch about losing and it's
always the developer's fault um naturally i i kind of feel hearthstone was all right it it like when
you lose in hearthstone it feels a little different from other games because it's like you build your
own deck most the time at least yeah and um you know you can stack your deck to be filled with
things that would make it more easily more easy for you to win if you get the right cards or like
you can you can have a safer deck that has less cool things well i'm saying this there's an element
of skill that goes into the luck of the draw which makes it less annoying than like uh some like
card games that use packs of cards where it's just like oh i have nothing fold can't fucking do it
um yeah i mean it like isn't it isn't in the sense that like that's true but what usually happened
was from my memory it was basically you'd get a like list of decks that basically everyone was
playing and oh yeah the meta was terrible yeah and so you'd always encounter like the same
shit over and over again and like eventually people got to the point where they're like if we're
all playing the same fucking decks like at what point is this just like luck of the draw um the
actual answer there is like none of you are actually that good so yeah a lot of it does come down to
that but like you know everyone thinks they're a 140 IQ genius so when you're really good at a game
like that you're not even just like it's not even about the cards entirely it's about building your
deck in response to like what decks everyone else is using yeah and like knowing what their what options
they have based off of what they've played already basically like being able to calculate okay if i
put this out where the odds gets a counter to me um yeah like yeah i i i remember certain points
where i would be watching like creperion videos about stuff just because it was fun and he would
play so many matches and i would see so many strategies that when i played it i was like
okay the meta for hunter right now is this and i'm fighting a hunter what is the likelihood he's
going to do these things hmm how should i play this sometimes it works sometimes i can actually
outsmart them because i know that they're trying to do a certain thing and i'm just not going to
let them do that one thing even if it means i'm not doing as much damage as i could otherwise
so it's a bit of strategy with that but yeah i don't know when i when i lost control of what
the meta was and i started losing everything i was just like whatever fuck it never again
i don't want to buy hundreds of thousands of packs to get all these new cards
i have i have avoided my my friends play uh magic and i have since like last year or so i
i have i have i think i made up my mind like i'm never playing another card game ever again
i i don't have the fucking mental energy to the vote i look to like a whole new side hobby like
that i just i just i don't want it i don't want it in my life i love card games but extremely
valid like they do consume a lot of mental like brain space and uh that's not something that
you necessarily want to commit to especially because you also end up like dumping a lot of money into
it it's like yeah uh yeah i mean there's that too mo it's it's the it's the it's the mental
energy though that's the real killer because i know you can build like you can build like a
pretty decent magic deck for like not too much money yeah they have like and if you want it to
be like good then it like takes exponentially more and more money there's like a whole format
to get it past being pretty good in mtg that's just based around using cheap cards i'm pretty sure
yeah yeah there are i mean there are uh i mean most of my most of my friends play uh uh what is it
the Highlander or the Elder Dragon EDM EDM EDH no ED yeah that's it EDH yeah they probably listen
to EDM Highlander right uh no they listen to like fucking they listen to uh like fucking
some i don't know i was maybe they didn't that's the soundtrack in my living room has been a lot
of like old uh uh like snes rpg uh soundtracks which is good and i like oh yeah that's the other
kind i always think of like when like music that like nerds listen to it's like a specific
kind of EDM i'm not sure like what the technical name is for it but it's discord i'm howlin yeah
yeah i always i always think of it as i always think of it as the EDM that furries listen to
um fuck yeah i don't know if there's a specific name for that genre it's that like electroswing
which oh swing music that's been put a funny beat on it you know like caravan palaces
no there are the people who did that music video with the furries getting into a bar fight oh
i i've seen that that there's a lot of blood and and a gazelle with tits yes yes yes yes
that's the one yeah caravan palaces is like that their genre electroswing which is like EDM
with swing influence um but like the double bass but sped up or something yeah yeah i think i
remember okay i might be off bass here but i think like last week vosh tweeted that like
he likes electroswing like that's all he's just said hey guys i kind of like electroswing
and i guess there was a big backlash people got upset that he said that no that makes sense i mean
just like i i watch a lot of anthony fantano and he has said on numerous occasions that
electroswing is like the only genre of music that is just bad like there is nothing he can
find about it that is any good and so it's so funny i'm pretty sure i mean okay okay but people
would have said that people must have said that about new metal back in the day and now it has
its defenders right i mean i don't you know he can't he can't seriously mean that new metal has like
i mean here new metal has like a couple of good songs like i don't know the alien ant farm
cover of smooth criminal and i think i think there's a case to be made for break stuff
i don't know that that's that's a limp biscuit to this it's like okay i i hate learning about that
song because now when i uh use the phrase it's just one of those days the first thing that
it's just one of those days yeah that's what pops into my head i'm like damn it fred durst okay
well i've i've never heard i don't know what electroswing sounds like but i i know that i have
like some real basic bitch taste in music um for i mean my canonically my favorite song is uh uh
what's the word uh what's that wake me up what's the word when you make it high pitched
no what's the word when you make it high course the night nightcore remix of hillary duff's come
clean is my my favorite song so so i probably would also like electroswing i feel yeah is there
is there like overlap because it's bad because it's bad yeah i would say the overlap between
nightcore remix um the audience for nightcore remixes is also the audience for electroswing
which is i knew it which is also the audience for um euro beat remixes of stuff euro beat brony
yeah euro yeah yeah and by extension discord um is also the audience for like vocaloid music so
why don't really i don't really like vocaloid stuff i've heard like a couple decent vocaloid
songs and then a lot of the other ones just sound like the same but worse yeah i'm with you on that
i cannot get into vocaloid i've heard a couple that sound good but most of the time yeah it's like
the the like there's a choppiness to the vocals because they're like you know computer generated
so it's always gonna sound a little bit off i like jazz fusion that makes me smart that makes me
i just need a song to have a real good like catchy like really energetic driving beat that
hooks me and that's all that's all i really need that's all i really need in a song uh and hillary
duff's got it baby do you think do you think nightcore country would improve country that's just
caught in ijoe it probably would it probably would yeah i mean any song is better if it's
nightcore because it's just faster which means like you're getting a higher density of like song
dude what if what if what if you do nightcore vaporwave then it would be just be normal
yeah that's true night nightcore um what's that what's that one vaporwave song
the the only one there is oh lisa frank 420 well that's the album or is that the song the album is um
uh fuck i don't know i always but yeah that song that song is just like a slow down album
is floral shop and the song is lisa frank 420 the lisa frank 420 is just like the really slowed
down version of whatever that that other song is so yeah if you nightcore it you just get the
original song back but better yeah exactly i'm like all distorted let's audio artifact it yeah
audio artifact yeah yeah just all fucked up it reminds me of that post that was like um
i've had enough of these uh lo-fi anime beats to relax and study to where are like the uh high
energy anime beats to dance and party to and someone was like nightcore hell oh my god i found it
nightcore lisa frank 420 here we go um enjoy uh uh wait wait here we go
somebody somebody's got me covered when you listen to this oh this sucks
it's not even faster it's just pitched up oh that's lame doesn't doesn't accomplish the goal at all
this is awful no whoever made this is a fucking hack and that's why they only got 523 views
down vote i disliked this no thank you disliked unsubbed i'm gonna subscribe and then
what a disaster devastating disappointment f got my hopes got my hopes up so high just like bitcoin
it got my hopes up so high only to just come crashing down really just cannot think about
anything other than bitcoin today i have today it's been months i have i have i have we i have
wean like at the beginning of this month at the beginning of this week it was literally it was
like i was literally like i had that on screen constantly and i was constantly looking at it
so i'm like i'm like i'm like i'm like asymptotically approaching you know zero bitcoin engagement
but like you know it's gonna take me a while it's gonna take me a while to disentangle myself
thank you walk thank you very much i'll get there i believe in myself
so what else what's uh what's what's what's what's going on what's your life what's your
life like um so my current project is i'm working on uh a new when posting goes wrong about sonic
for real justice i don't know if either of you have ever heard of this did you post a tweet
with some screenshot of like your file folder yeah that's the research for that okay i don't
know what that is at all okay so in okay so in 2015 right uh there was this blog that took over
tumblr for like a hot week or so and it was like an insane like fever dream of an event
while it was happening um basically this post went viral so the blog was called sonic for real
justice right um with a number four i said no no no um it was spelled out but basically like
at the time on tumblr there was like a backlash to the proliferation of like sjw content
and so you started getting blogs that were like anti sjw blank or blank for real justice and so
where they were like either just straight up i think some of them were just straight up like
right-wingers but a lot of them were like uh lgbt exclusionists so they were like sure trans people
who were like really like particular about who's allowed to call themselves trans or like people
who thought that like ace people weren't lgbt or stuff like that um i understand yeah and but the
thing is because it's tumblr and everyone ran like fandom blogs people started like crossing the
streams so you'd get like anti sjw kyogre or like naruto for real justice so like as other
other accounts that other people were running yeah so people would like start a blog where it was
like them and a bunch of their friends like um was it a was it a joke or was it like these people
were serious a lot of these people were serious where they were like face claiming quote unquote
like they were basically rp-ing as like various fictional characters talking about why like
neo pronouns are invalid and shit sonics the name i'll keep this short and sweet trans male gay true
scum anti special snowflake what you see is what you get just a guy who loves adventure sit back
grab some popcorn and enjoy the blog yeah so that was the original i'm looking at know your meme
that was the original mod sonic intro what really took off was the mod shadow intro which i'll do
my best yes i'm my shadow male and the atheist anti sjw anti feminist anti gun control pro logic
i chose shadow the hedgehog as an internet persona as i relate to him when it comes to his hatred
of humans or in my case social justice warriors these sjw's think that fighting fire with fire
will accomplish something well in the real world it won't i hope that one day these pathetic sjw's
will come to their senses um and unsurprisingly that post was a big hit and then people went to the
blog and what they discovered was like a tangled web of uh mod drama where i want i want to say
that it's it's tagged with like hashtag sjw hashtag anti sjw hashtag sysphobia
hashtag hetero phobia hashtag racism oh yeah they put like every possible tag on their intros
to try to get more people looking at them um yeah very nice but they'd like they because basically
it was like they created a bunch of rules for like what the mods are allowed to do and like what
they're not allowed to do and like almost immediately one of the mods broke a rule and they kicked
him out and then they all started going back and forth where people were like justice for mod
silver we got this guy who like has never said anything like they kicked him out for not posting
and then closing the ask box and they're like all right you're gone and then everyone immediately
rallied to his side people were like so invested in this drama um i think in large part because
of the absurdity of it all and and it was all like how how serious was it so like um so this
is kind of like the big twist at the end so if you don't want to be spoiled for the eventual
sonic for real justice video you can dip out now i i doubt anyway but um yeah basically
like uh they ended up after like a few a couple of weeks doing this they stopped getting as many
notes uh like people sort of stopped caring about the blog and so they eventually just like pulled
back the curtain they were like all right this was a joke like it was it was a whole time um damn
but the funny thing the thing i find like super funny is that after they they took off the mask
and told everyone what was happening they eventually brought it back um initially as a
danganronpa blog and then later they switched over to yugioh but they kept some of the danganronpa
characters and now they're back to sonic but like there's still characters from various other
franchises hanging out as well so it's kind of all over the place very nice but very nice
what we eventually but like if you kept following them after all that time which not a lot of people
did what you eventually learn is like the danganronpa phase ended because they brought on a bunch of
other mods because originally it was only like i think three people and i think they added a
bunch of other people who then started like actual serious drama with each other because they had
like a bad breakup and they tried someone tried to like accuse the other person of being like an
abuser which is pretty typical like tumblr material sure and then i'm glad i was never on tumblr
you're i dodged the bullet i feel like you both did and did not miss out there was a lot of good
stuff there but i mean it's like twitter in that there's like a lot of like there's funny stuff
on there and then there's also stuff that gives you brain damage i personally think tumblr is a lot
less harmful to my mental health than twitter because like on tumblr on tumblr you make a
bad like you'll see a bad post and you can like rest assured that it's like some 17 year old who's
like never left their hometown oh whereas on on twitter you see a bad post and it's some fucking
op-ed writer for the new york time exactly or like a fail son with like three high paying fake
jobs like yeah so it's just a very different vibe you know um so like um yeah but we eventually
learned so right very sorry um so they eventually had to like kick those people out and like reboot
but eventually someone they when they went back to the sonic theme they started a discord server
and a bunch of their fans got in it and at least one person like made a post where they
after talking to these people like full mask off where they were just being themselves they found
out that like the mods were aphobes and so yeah they they didn't think asexual people are lgbt
okay and so got it basically the big joke with sonic for real justice is that this was a bunch of
people pretending to be a group of exclusionists uh starting ridiculous drama with each other
while face claiming fictional characters and eventually it turned into a group of exclusionists
just actually starting drama with each other while face claiming fictional characters so the answer
to was it all a joke is yes but also no yeah i was just pretending to be smart i was yeah i was
just pretending to be joking essentially that's yeah that's like you you you would have to i don't
know you that's kind of what i expected because like like obviously this is ridiculous when you're
when you're being sonic and shadow but also like why would you commit to this bit like i don't know
you would you would have to have some level of commitment to it i don't know it's or that just
seems like the most likely thing like um this is a joke but it's a joke about like what they like
it's funny to them because it's what they actually believe i think they did exaggerate like they
definitely are they that's the weird thing is that they eventually said that they were like only
pretending to hold some of their views in that like i think originally they were like a lot more
arbitrary about like these specific kinds of non-binary people are like
trans-trenders or too cute or whatever the term is and then eventually too cute yeah it's this is
this is the deep uh lgbt lore right here um okay but but eventually uh they like later on in the
blog where they weren't like um where they were being open that they were playing characters
someone was like yeah we don't actually believe in that stuff we accept all non-binary people
but it's because the eighth the aphobia thing ended up being legit it makes you wonder how
many of their views were their actual views and how many of it was the character it's it's just
such a urban such as like playing with fire almost like you know going around oh uh i'm playing a
character online uh he's racist and he says racist things all the time and he hates different races
but you know the joke is that that's so silly like who would believe these things like why would you
even call out post i mean i don't know i've never watched filthy frank um but i've heard he's funny
and cool didn't didn't didn't filthy frank didn't he have a have a redemption didn't he turn around
and be like didn't didn't he quit because like he didn't like people taking seriously the stuff he
was trying to joke about it was a combination of things he quit in part because the like
filthy frank voice did like actual damage to his vocal cords and he couldn't do it anymore
which makes sense if you've ever heard him talk um but the but yeah i think part of it was that
like the problem with doing a character where the joke is this is the worst guy on the planet
and you're supposed to laugh at him is that the audience for that is actually just the worst guys
on the planet because they were the only ones who can tolerate that content long term um yeah
and so it was it was both things and also i think he just got sick of doing like shock content um
because what he did after that was he became a fucking lo-fi indie artist who is now like super
successful and popular and so i think he probably always wanted to do that to some extent um and
like i don't know good for him for like getting like a quote unquote real career but also i have
as a as a lo-fi like no come on no i think he was pretty successful like like in terms of
like all internet jobs are fake jobs that's like a no it's he's like he charts like when he puts
out new songs and everything he like um every music's fake music's not even real unless it's
every so often someone will like dig up like it's fake until you make it nightcore that's how you
make it real oh my god can we get someone can we get someone to uh pitch up and speed up some of
Filthy Frank's tracks thank you might make it more listenable only then will i listen i'm of the
extremely i have the extremely hot take that um the music that Filthy Frank made as pink guy when
he was making like dumb meme music is better than his like quote unquote serious music he's
made as joji because like there's a million guys making like lo-fi like sad boy indie pop but
there's only there was only one guy making a song about um letting a dog lick peanut butter off his
balls and like we're not gonna we're not gonna get that back you know it was a moment in time
and it's passed exactly sad uh i never uh i never watched Filthy Frank either uh i just know him
from wearing a pink suit and i've heard that he said funny things he had a couple of funny videos
but like i said the problem with playing the worst guy on the planet is that it's kind of hard to watch
a lot of that content sure is he like an idubbbz or was he like an idubbbz type
or is it yes more extreme was it in fact i'm pretty sure he was like i'm pretty sure he was
friends with some of those guys yeah i mean i like idubbbz he's a bit of a strange guy but he's cool
oh
i'm too busy i'm too busy getting bitches in the real world to be watching all these uh
all these fucking youtubers yeah based yeah it's based based on you having zero bitches
i collect them and then i hang them on my shelf
tell me more tell me tell me more no fact no give us more content more content more content
you don't have any more content um then we're gonna have to move on to voicemails
and you know what happens when you move on to voicemails she gets weird and it gets scary oh god
i mean i'm looking forward to getting weird and scary because i'm just curious
i don't know now now they're gonna be lame and stupid this is only two modes of the voicemails
yeah historically historically they're usually lame and stupid so
should we do should we do some should we do some voicemails might as well yeah
okay uh all right yeah not nonchalant committal to voicemails okay i'm sure i'm sure our callers
appreciate the lack of enthusiasm that's fine all right no they love it they get off on it
okay so this one is called let me just scroll back to where where was it okay this one is called
why star bomb is shit three two one go hey dickhead here i've been thinking uh since the one
gamers to after an episode where they mentioned uh star bomb why i hate star bomb so much despite
locking dan's uh just as an artist and i think i found out the reason is just that star bombs
really shitty youtube video essays put to really unfunny songs essays like game theory is mario a
sociopath game theory can i stick my penis in a gerudo links bussy uh game theory doesn't
final fantasy seven have such a wacky plot i mean it's um i just really hate it it is yeah i've
never it's it's vile it doesn't have like a game theory vibe it has like the it has like the reddit
like epic bacon yes the epic bacon video game like what if mario's real like played out like in
like before the the before the 90s i i've never i've never like found themselves trapped inside
their favorite video games i was like raging like like foaming at the mouth at people like doing
mario in real life things uh before i was born i hate that shit yeah that's that's valid um
someone once described um dany sex bang as uh a dude who's like 40 years old and his entire
personality is that he has sex with girls who play legend is elda and that really does play out
in his music and i feel like he definitely got some good girls who play legends he definitely
got some good songs out of that devastating like there are limits you know you can only do that
shtick for so long before it gets old i have i have not listened to much the first time i heard
unicorn wizard but the first time i heard unicorn wizard i thought it was really funny but then
like the more the more uh ninjas x party i heard the more i was just like okay all right that's
it's very one note in in terms of like i don't know what he what he feels like he can sing about
and starbomb was even more like just like like locked in on like well let's take a video game
that's uh you know a Nintendo franchise and like i don't know i mean i think starbomb was like that
i think starbomb was like that on purpose starbomb was like that on purpose because i
kind of think it was made to be marketable it's made it's made to be like lowest common denominator
like video game humor it's just so it's so much worse than what they say on game grumps i just
it's exactly the same vibe as um do you guys remember brental floss i know of him a little
sort of yeah same vibe is him same vibe is like all like nerd core um a genre that i think uh
deserves to be made fun of um wait what's nerd is it just like referencing things that are cool
as in it's it's rapping about nerd things it's not a very good combination my i run a patron
discord server for my hardcore simps and someone in that server introduced me to the world of league
of legends hip hop oh no um which just reinforced my joke that it's called uh lol because you gotta
take twice the ls when you're playing that game i i totally i i believe it is there is there like
um i think the problem is like fighting game hip hop the the huh what i could i could i could see
there being hip hop about league of legends like i could see there being hip hop about like fighting
games because like the fighting game i don't know like the competitive the competitive atmosphere of
it i don't know feels like it's something you could write fucking angry raps about yeah i think i
mean if they have it for league of legends i would think they would have it for like
street fighter but maybe not maybe i'm no you can you can do it it's just fucking stupid i think oh
well so is all human endeavor to get right down to it in general as a theme is usually
stupid and lame but there's a few examples of like have you heard of protoman i got introduced
to them recently they they it's a mega man um they or they made two albums protoman act one and two
i can't remember what i think that was what i know protoman um and they were like prog rock like um
epics operas right yeah like uh like rock operas and and like the production was very good and it
wasn't just like listing the mega man characters it was like a story was being told with these
characters as like a base of inspiration and i was like okay you know that's actually pretty good music
but it's video game um but when you when it's when it's like when it's like music video game
like i i don't think it's like a a guaranteed fail machine to talk about video games in in songs
it's just like a lot of the time what gets people hyped up is just hearing the franchise they know of
and then the amount of like creativity that you need to put in for something like that to be
successful is so low that people often don't need to try and so they don't and so they just
i can imagine the league of legends hip hop is just talking about a video like a like a like a
match and something bad happened and they got fucked up and they died and they lost hate hit points
and they just sing about it for a little while it's like oh yeah i love league of legends i'll
click on like and subscribe and pay i think you're on to something in the sense that like
because you're just trying to get people who like the game to click on it by virtue of liking the
game the song doesn't need to be as well produced yeah because i think actually because while we
were discussing this i remembered the one example of like a dude who makes songs that's just that's
everything that brony's ever made yes um but that just reminded me of like the one example of like
people making music about nerdy things that was actually good which is fucking uh ken ashcorp
who makes songs about like hentai but somehow makes it like listenable and catchy so it's like
you can do this um but like but it's so easy to not it's it's so easy to not bother and still
succeed so it's like yes it's gonna be a lot of crap of that type exactly i think that's that's
reasonable i've heard of ken ashcorp i've never heard their i want to i want to hear like a sudoku
rap oh my god a minesweeper like uh well uh wait wait who was that who was that digimon
youtuber who i was we were talking about a while ago and like that guy wrote original like digimon
i don't think he wrote raps i think he made like heavy metal songs uh maybe he rapped i don't remember
you could do like metal heavy rap i could actually see doing metal about video games
more than hip hop about video games because like a lot of metal is already like the the lyrics are all
like like fantasy shit like a lot of there's like a long history of of metal that's just about like
dragons and like um like lord of the rings shit and i feel like it's like not that much of a jump
you know can't find his fucking name uh that fucking guy he was he was he was my hero i wanted to
love anything as much as that guy loved digimon fuck okay whatever uh commenters let me know
um next voicemail yeah yeah let's go okay here we go here we go that one wasn't that bad
that one was okay okay yeah we're on it we're on it we're on a roll we're on a streak of one
uh this one is called wall street bets oh boy three oh god it's a minute thirty fuck you wall
street three three two one go all right so ben i know you're really interested in bitcoin
i was bitcoin sucks okay terrible investment facts shout out would not invest it myself because
of the high volatility uh same with you gib i know you don't invest but you should actually consider
investing you misinvested that one way to make money you will have to be a capitalist in order
to utilize the tools in your tool belt for capital appreciation so the fucking thoughts
that first find your portfolio etc if you want any more information about this google
that's your best friend for it but also consider opening a account with robin hood not a sponsor
but not a sponsor no i don't even know how to start this podcast i didn't thank you for us today
who would be paying this motherfucker and you can still buy bitcoin with that okay is robin hood a
if you want to buy bitcoin for cheap well not cheap but uh have no fees because i didn't know
paypal has fees either and i was gonna never did buy it on robin hood no commissions at all
easily sign up and if you guys are for each other you get a free stock so everyone wins but
i want you to look more into stock investments uh really look into it and actually try to
maximize your returns he's right he's right i know that like over the over the long run
over the long run he's he's best to invest in the market itself this guy has the capitalist voice
i'm going to want i'm gonna give legitimate advice here if you actually want to make money
investing the way you do it is that you invest in what's called the vfi and x which is the vanguard
index fund which is basically it just tracks the s and p 500 and whatever the s and p 500 is
worth that's how much it's worth um and that's like the only good investment because as we have
learned this year uh the forces that be will do literally anything they can possibly come up with
up to and including killing hundreds of thousands of people just to make that number keep going up
and so that's great if you're that's a great idea and so if you're invested in just that
you're going to keep making money i'm literally going to fucking fuck bitcoin i'm putting all
my savings in no and the better right now that's like actually a legitimate strategy and the thing
about it is that it's like unlike bitcoin for example the reason why it's nice is that you don't
have to watch it and in fact if you do watch it that's actually a bad thing because if you see it
like yeah go down a little bit you're like oh shit sell everything and then it just goes back up
like two weeks later and you're like fuck so yeah it actually like takes that burden off you that comes
with a lot of like day trading and other kinds of investment where you have to like constantly
be thinking about it it's just you set it and forget it and you get like a little return
every year and it's boring but like you make a little money okay do you get more than do you
get more than you'd get from just your typical high interest savings fund yeah yeah definitely
more than uh than a savings account well sounds good i was i was i was considering i was looking
at like which saving funds give the highest like yearly return the other day and i was like there's
got to be something better there's got to be something better than like 1.9 percent i'll think
about it later yeah i never did this is more like five to ten i think depending on the year
yes i love money no i love money so much it's the worst thing ever no it's thinking about
investments and give me give me yours i just makes me want to uh not think about it it's what it
makes me want to think about it makes me want to just makes me want to go just makes me want to go
drown myself in minecraft just makes me want to go leap off a fucking skyscraper just makes me want
to go climb to the top of the slime corp headquarters and die on the fucking pavement of downtown new
los angeles city aka neo milwaukey in minecraft which you can do on the fucking pcp minecraft server
link in the description so literally in minecraft yes literally in minecraft yeah that's what i want
to do that's what i want to do um okay next voicemail is called what is this one called this is um
notorious revolutionary tommy j guest application oh boy uh wait wait a minute oh it's only 14
seconds okay three two one go hi i'm notorious revolutionary tommy j i'm applying to be a pcp
guest this is not a bit i've already sent ben a resume on discord i'm sending this voicemail to
make sure he sees it if there's somewhere else i should send it let me know see oh fuck oh this
is exactly the thing that we were talking about earlier was shitty voicemails no with uh people
who are like hey hey we should collab like do you want to be friends oh yeah yeah i know what you
mean um um this yeah this guy did i'm trying to find it i clicked off before the voicemail was done
but i think i get the gist um yeah this guy did send me a uh an application notorious revolution
a guest i was it like a resume yes it's literally a resume and i just i didn't i didn't respond because
i didn't know i didn't know how to respond i kind of feel bad i sort of don't want to like i sort of
don't want to rip into this guy too much because he's like very earnest you know what i mean yeah
he sounds a little young um he's i mean he is he's well okay he says he's a there's there's his
resume there's his pcp resume he is a soon to graduate computer science student uh and and
and i mean the thing about it is that like i don't know there has there has not we have never
accepted a guest on the show based on a resume yeah it's the it's pure nepotism it's pure nepotism
it's just do we know you or if not that do we watch your videos yeah i got um when i was doing a
podcast a little while ago i got an email from some dude who was like hey can i be on this and i
literally said like no it's purely based on just like people i like and already i'm familiar with
so sorry but yeah yeah that that's how it is uh there is no there is no application process
i'm sorry tom i i find this to be very cute that it is cute it is cute that's why i don't want to
be too hard on him yeah um i think better way to to express like like to get our attention i guess
if you want to be on the podcast you you can't really just ask and say like i i have opinions and i
i know matt and koff from rfck i mean is that what he said is that in here near the bottom
like i'm sure i'm sure he has his own rfck wiki page i'm sure you're cool on rfck.mirahease.org
but i i think wiki slash notorious revolutionary tommy j i think it would be like i don't know if
you wanted to be on the pcp and spout an opinion about something a better way to do it would be
through the voicemails i just just talk about whatever and then we could discuss it through
that i don't know if this is like this is this is adorable but uh yeah yeah i don't know the point
is we're not really we're not taking applications uh get get bent get bent tommy you know why don't
you go you know why don't you go uh take a long walk off a short pier you know why don't you go
jump in a mud puddle why don't you go jump in a mud puddle in my that's what my parents when i was
little when i was a little kid and my parents would say don't say mean things ben when you're mad
at someone say go jump in a mud puddle the current uh expression that i've seen used on tumblers go
touch some grass because people would use to say like go outside but the joke is like no one can go
outsides they're like just like wander like just a little bit outside just touch some grass you know
what but then they would just with saying haha i got my grass right here smokes blunt
one four twenty every day four twenty every smoke some grass okay next voicemail uh let me try and
find it here we go next voicemail is called cringis bingus oh my god three two one go
hey guys it's your favorite new favorite pcp voicemail lever cringis bingus oh no
every week i'm gonna tell you what i cringed at and what i banged yeah yeah i love it this
was a great bet i cringed at ben talking about how he bought so much bitcoin and then bitcoin
has been crashing for like a week and that is pretty funny and i cringed because ben dumb
and then i banged um i banged i i i banged the whole uh second half of the first season of
twin peaks i watched it with my friends i was banging it i was banging the show
i can tune in next week for more cringis bingus where i talk about what i cringed
actually good actually voice grail voice grail i was thinking i was thinking voice grail i was
gonna say it i think cringis bingus her voice grail jesus christ uh by the way we have a thing
where if we have a particularly good voicemail they ascend to the voice grail but if it's
particularly bad we banish them to voice jail oh bonk go to voice jail no no you're outvoted
you know what no this guy's going straight to the top yeah no oh yeah that was hilarious
what it reminded me of was that uh old fourchan post the uh what was yeah the weenus penis post
i don't know that one here i just found it i'll put it in the the server so you can see what
i'm talking about in this thread enemies that unnerve you any sentiently type anything about
why my weenus penis of course haha it's my weenus penis haha in this thread enemies that
unnerve me it's of course it's my weenus penis followed by like 50 replies of people just like
doing like what the fuck reactions yeah that's the vibe that this dude is giving me dude this is
lol so random and i like it xd taco i'm so random lost art cringis bingus i i don't know why he
cringed at me losing bitcoin i would have thought that was funny like i would have thought yeah it's
cringe for you but it's based for the rest of us i think so i'm honestly like this guy must really
he must be have a lot of empathy you know to see like bitcoin crash and be like oh no ben
oh oh that poor man you know i literally poor because he lost all his money truly a poorest
the purest of souls that would cringis bingus hey hey guys if you want to help me recoup my lost
bitcoin uh please go to patreon.com slash ben saint uh and i will invest it again no no no you
should have said you should bing all of my content oh yeah bing bing all my content give me that ad
revenue so i can invest it and double my money i will i will invest it in a volatile bitcoin
market i will not invest it in the vifx uh for guaranteed is that what it's called vifx vifinx
vifinx yeah no not not doing that that's too much of a sure thing that doesn't i can't i can't get
off to that uh next voicemail is is next voicemail is called uh next voicemail is called uh hippo
the gibby girl three two one go i would definitely watch a gibby movie about hippo uh as as a little
girl anyway you are a gibby girl deservedly no what's all right wait what that was my voice in there
i heard you what i don't even remember that conversation maybe that was on some other show
oh that was digi that was digi laughing i was gonna say that sounds like digi
there was no no it wasn't digi talking no no no i mean like at the end i was
yeah yeah near yeah near the end i hear did you laugh and then i hear you say no
so i i don't i guess this was from a previous voicemail i guess this is just a clip from a
previous episode great thanks for the voicemail oh thanks for the voicemail that's just a clip
of an old episode voice jail voice jail no no no no no yeah gibby yeah yeah
yeah uh okay okay whatever okay whatever the next one is called greg uh three two one go
one piece more like mid piece more like what's piece more like oh like without the o
ne piece what the fuck that sucks what the fuck what the fuck voice jail voice jail
bad bad no thanks okay good try next one is called unable to procrastinate three two one go
oh i'm supposed to be jerking right no i'm supposed to be this is our theme song by the way he's
not working instead just working i am on wagey inside the crazy being productive finish my
dead lord why am i so successful i'm supposed to be losing money i'm supposed to be wasting
my time but i'm not leaching instead improving learning and training nobody's stopping as i am
working my wealth is growing oh yeah feels good to be a useful member of society
records my child garlic house was he pretending to be bread garlic house at the end
i think okay i'm xrp like this was like illegal or something something's gone bad with xrp
there's some kind of there's some kind of litigation going on with ripple xrp um
i mean he rewrote the lyrics to be about someone who's a wagey and working bread garlic
house is not a wagey bread garlic house owns the means of production so i don't know i i don't
know aside aside from the bread garlic house um it's it is a cool problem to have that you just
you're too busy to procrastinate i think that's pretty good god i wish that were me as long as
you're not like sad about it i was working on my secret thing yesterday and i was just like
i really i really got into the groove of it like the whole day went by i got all kinds of things
done and it was like i'm like i'm like tired and it's late and i'm like oh you know like i don't
know i i didn't procrastinate as soon as bad actually you know uh uh uh it's good when you
do the thing you're supposed to do and the the you're welcome uh you can you can put that you
can put that on your tombstone and take that to the bank you can take that to the bank and smoke it
uh next voicemail is called where is it here we go it is called use your natural assets to
incept ideas into the common man oh no okay three two one go what's up pcp let me tell you a story
i am a six three blonde person living in the suburbs of japan so needless to say i stick out
now the other day i went to my local supermarket to do some grocery shopping and in the entrance
part of the store they have two hand sanitizer dispensers nice i was a fairly busy time of day
so we were a bunch of people entering the store at the same time in like a line with me at the back
as we were entering a single japanese man was exiting the store and used the hand sanitizer
dispenser on his way out upon entering none of the people ahead of me used the hand sanitizer
dispenser at all so i thought hmm now after doing my shopping the tables had turned and now i'm the
one exiting the store as a new batch of people enter so on my way out i use the hand sanitizer
dispenser in view of all the entering people so upon exiting i look back at the entrance to see
that everybody who just entered were now like queuing up at the hand sanitizer dispenser to
use it so basically i am a hero and a manipulative mastermind using my foreigners as a power to
do good do you all have any epic idea inception stories please tell us so until next time you
accepted the idea of getting all these easterners to use the hand sanitizer by using the hand
sanitizer that the store had put out for people to use am i reading this correctly i think which
is extra hilarious because the implication the implication here is that because he's white
they wanted to do the thing he was doing because they didn't care when the first guy did it i would
i would think that the fact that you are look weird would make them like less likely to just do
what you do i don't know i don't know if i agree with the conceit that if if if you see somebody
using the hand sanitizer if i do it if i see someone i'm like oh yeah i should do that because
it's like it's just sensible like you wouldn't if you're not thinking about it and then you see
someone do it you'll be reminded oh yeah that's probably a good idea yeah i i guess if you go in
and there's the hand sanitizer but no one is using it maybe you don't think oh i should go use it
yeah people just and maybe you see the first person go use it and you go oh okay everyone
it's like at a party you go to a party and no one's eating the food and no one wants to be the first
one to eat it and then but then someone eats it it's like okay i can have some nice um so i guess
that's true following mentality it's it's something everybody has a little bit of have i ever have i
ever incepted an idea into a crowd uh no i'd like to think i've i've sometimes done that but like
it's never been particularly like interesting just sort of i don't know i held the door open for
someone or whatever and that sort of made a queue behind me of people holding door open for other
people whereas before it was just being swung in people's phases i've seen that happen a couple
times but it's like you know whatever nobody wants to look like the less cool the less good person
so everyone gets manipulated into doing it i can't say i've had an experience like this i will say
though as a as a gaijin as a white person living in japan uh i appreciate this person
for um well wait are you a guy no no no i'm saying i'm saying like okay based on my knowledge of
gaijin um yeah because i have a couple of friends who live in japan um he said sayonara at the end
but i appreciate that other than that he did not use any gratuitous japanese throughout his message
where he really didn't need to use it um like he could have common he could have very well said
going going to my local super that's the grocery store he could he could have he could have started
the email with a voicemail konnichiwa yeah that's a that's a joke that's a that's a there's a there's
this samurai who is after me because i stole some sacred scrolls it's not a don't worry about it look
deep i shouldn't i i shouldn't have even brought it up honestly but yeah he could have done like
all according to keikaku and shit um and he chose to restrain himself he chose to contain the uh the
weeb instinct and i have a certain degree of respect for him even if i think this story is
kind of lame honestly yeah it's a little lame it's just that you did a thing and people saw you
doing it and we're like oh it's too bad i sometimes feel i i i know the feeling that i sometimes feel
a bit of pride when there's like something that people should be doing that they aren't and i'm
like well i'm gonna show them i'm gonna do it in view of all these people who i know are watching
me because i i have anxiety about that and i'm i'm certain everyone's watching me do this cool
thing that's good they'll think i'm so good and they never do they never they never pay any
attention it's all in my head uh next voicemail yes next voicemail is next voicemail is just called
ben three two one go
it's like i under water okay yeah right he just like set it through his through a blanket i don't
know i don't know thanks thanks for the voicemail i guess uh next one next one is called flat
three two one go
look the only way you can prove that the earth is round is you need to circumnavigate north to south
and you need to make sure you're going in a perfectly straight line
and you need to need to record how we're doing
this is so bad
i'm too lazy to look into it uh so i'm just gonna just add until until someone present evidence
otherwise okay i can't uh bro fix your fucking mic i can't why is sent like it felt like this guy
knows how to make a voicemail he's doing this on purpose um for some reason yeah i couldn't i
couldn't make out a word in that um but i imagined something funny that it was just like it was an
it was an explanation of how you would prove that the earth is round or flat or something i don't
know to me i was imagining garfield with his blanket covered over his face you know when he
does that yeah maybe he might have been just like on the other side of the room like talking
against the wall and also just like shaking the table that the mic was on i don't know uh whatever
no yeah next one is called uh where is it next one is called pancakes vote minor three two one go
oh jeez i didn't see you there hello i'm just your average vote minor down here in georgia
just trying to find those votes trump was asking for my slave in all day and night
mining and panning for those votes oh i hope i'm not too late i mean i haven't found any yet
but i found a lot of fools votes over there in the dominican machine deposit oh geez oh boy
we sure don't want someone who is democratically elected and to not become president that would
sure be bad i mean all trump was just trying to say is there's votes in them dare hills
i mean he's got him it's pro drunk oh yeah you just got to keep digging they're there that's
just got it that dang cheeto in the dang white house uh if you if you you can mine for votes
like you mine for bitcoin you just kind of you just kind of generate them you know the out of the
e-pair uh and uh there's exactly 21 million and uh how else would they like bitcoin uh
they're skyrocketing in value uh uh they'll never fail uh uh yeah the the votes they fell
that like the the vote carriers they were running and and then they anime tripped and it it fell
into like the abyss and now they're looking for them like it's it's it's it's all in the news the
votes the votes were being carried the votes were being carried by a girl with like huge tits
and she like tripped over something on the street and went blah and like blah and they all fell down
the drain in like three different directions yeah and then all the votes they went in all all
different directions and then uh like you the player have to collect all the different like
3d platformer collect all of the votes and then get them back safely in time you you are you are
you know it was a japanese girl with toast in her mouth was just running to the dominion machines
with like with like 21 or it was like 62 000 or however many you know votes for election rigging
votes for Donald Trump she's tripped she tripped and they scattered everywhere and now it's a
fucking scavenger huh no trump sama i went into the sea well it's it's just like it's just like how
in an endless war you can people you drop stuff into the sea and then you can fish it back up
uh you gotta you gotta go down to slimes end you gotta go down to the pier you gotta fish for those
votes you know turn them into old captain albert alexander uh uh something something uh lore uh
yeah uh uh biden biden biden okay cool uh next one is called did i post it already the next one
is called yes it's called why are women racist frowny face three two one go so i'm on tinder right
and i see this girl who says she likes cooking and working out and i'm like hey i like cooking
and working out and she's pretty cute okay so i'm a messenger and i'm like uh hey you want to go on
a date i could make you dinner you know wink and smiley face as you do and she's like ha ha
nah but i'm not really sure why i added you i only date black guys and i'm like oh all right you
know she she didn't like that cute approach time to time to be cool no it's too late let me try again
at that point hey girl you want me to smash that and she's like ha ha no but i am serious
what the fuck halisha you racist bitch why are women like this pcp wait i had a tweet about this
literally like a day or two ago wait wait but i think was the joke there that the girl was black
was her name did she have like a black name wait does that make a difference let me back what
what he's he said the girl's name i'm gonna have to play part of this i'm just i'm i'm curious
like she said i only date black guys and then he like responded as if he were a black guy was that
his bit no no the bit was that he just changed well let's show yeah yeah he gave her like a
like a stereotypical sounding like black girl name so no my tweet does not apply um yeah he's
just he's just making a racist joke i i thought he said Clarissa in which case your would tweet
your your tweet would apply yeah is that the tweet by the way was about the the genre of
white girls who uh who make a liking black cock a core of their personality yeah is that common
is that common outside of like porn it's more common than it should be that's for sure um there
is an entire i watched like a whole video about this the other day um they're like i've i've
used to back when i was uh still on tinder uh as a man no less i did encounter a few of them um
obviously did not actually get any messages out of that but i could tell well if they didn't like
black if these white girls didn't like black cock they'd be fucking dogs instead so we should
count our blessings jesus christ i uh one time i was at work and one of my co-workers was talking
like very casually about like taking a bath with her dog and i'm like why are white women like this
there's giving your dog a bath and then there's taking a bath yeah no no like taking a bath with
your dog i was like do you people have no about wait isn't that be extremely like messy and annoying
did the dog consent to the bath you fucking psychopath there's no reason to do that that
oh maybe it was a small dog maybe it was a tiny little dog because like i'm imagining like you
know you take a dog on a walkie get him back and then he's just like like running all over the place
shaking and then you try to bath him and there's like splashing everywhere it's like yeah i can't
imagine taking a like a bath with a dog they'd go insane they'd go all over the place if it's like
if it's like a little a little like chihuahua like a little doxin or something that's like handheld
maybe yeah but the size of a nintendo 3ds what you you just you just you just a multitask you
can like oh you can bathe yourself and your dog at the same time why not i mean you get my little
life preserve and i can splash on the in the other end even if it is convenient i still wouldn't do
it this is weird it's just weird i just don't want to you just gotta do that you'll get dog um stuff
dog dirt in your bathwater that's not good um um uh but to this guy um yeah women be racist indeed
women women be racist uh it's next voicemail wait what no say no no it's no come on say it no
it wasn't it wasn't it wasn't a thing i was gonna say it was just like i was just gonna say oh it's
true lol but it's like who cares this is stupid wall wall lmao uh next voicemail is called uh cross
source material and adaptations three two wait hold on
is it is it is it racist to say you only date black guys because what i think what i think the fact
okay i actually do this on this day the fact that she did add him means that she was maybe willing
to date him even if he's not black but she said that after he messaged her so i think she didn't
like his approach changed her mind and was like i only date black guys in the same way she might be
like uh no i have a boyfriend or uh no i'm a lesbian which is just like oh right i don't want to talk
to you i don't want to say no because that's sad that makes me feel like a bad and changing your
approach being like hey why don't we we could make dinner together wink and then she's like ha ha
no and then be like okay new approach uh baby let me fucking smash that put it doesn't that's not
gonna work it's transparently like you're changing your like that's a really weird
and like you're i don't know i think i think you just put her off i think this is what happened here
well what we have to consider here is the fact that this is a fake story that didn't actually
happen that he made up for the voicemail um because that could be a scenario make way more
sense because the punchline it's it's just to build up to the punchline that she has like a
stereotypically black name like that's it's just like a dumb black i don't even know how that's a
joke really it's not it's because it sucks you know what you know what i am taking this
seriously only date black guys anyway it's it's not even a is that a i don't know whatever
um like like like what about her being a black girl would have been a clue for him to be like oh
she would only like black guys and then and him getting upset is like the joke is like ah you
should you shouldn't have got upset because of of course she would like black men only because
she's black i don't get what the is that like reality does that happen the punchline the the
rug is meant to be pulled out from under us when we initially agree with him like yes this girl is
racist for only wanting to date black guys but then aha the twist ah but she was black and black
people can't you see it's just such a strength i don't think i think i mean either way the joke
sucks so i don't think it matters yeah okay all right we should move on i've given this i've given
i've got we wasted a lot of time on that guy too much time this one is called cross source material
in adaptations three two one go so i recently watched all eight harry potter movies and did
not like any of them and this got me thinking about whether or not reading the books would have
made the movies better seeing as i have not read any of them and that got me thinking about the
relationship between adaptations and the source material they are adapting should an adaptation
assume that its audience has read the source material how much should an adaptation be compared
to the original versus judged on its own merits and is your opinion of an adaptation given more
or less validity depending on if you have also consumed the source material discuss i have the
second one um i have an actual hot takes on this okay as for the second question uh everything
should be able to stand on its own if you need to have done other reading to get the most or
it should be able to be like acceptable and you know at least good you know
with potential room for improvement if you know but it should be able to stand perfectly well
on its own without needing to have seen the adaptations or like the source material or
whatever um i don't know about like whether your opinion matters more if you've read the book and
watched the film i think you could make a perfectly good movie that assumes that someone
has read the source material and like simply doesn't give a fuck about like anyone that hasn't
sure but then but then i would i would like personally i would just think of that as a
worse movie because there's plenty of ways to make an adaptation be perfectly good on its own
despite source material like lacking things from the source material if we're talking about books
that always happens books and film all right um i'm i'm gonna come through with some hot some
spicy opinions on this first of all i don't think you should have have to have uh seen the source
material in order to consume the adaptation because quite frankly i do not want my media to come with
homework uh but more importantly i think every adaptation should stand on its own
because the best adaptations are the ones that uh fully utilize their medium to the fullest extent
like for example the godfather is an adaptation of a book that like critically no one cared about
it was just like a decently popular piece of genre fiction but like it wasn't like the greatest
one of the greatest books of all time but it was adapted into one of the greatest movies of all time
because the filmmaking took like full advantage of the medium and created a piece of entertainment
that only works it like works better as a film like once you like the reason it's so good is
because of the filmmaking and not because of the story underlying it and so similarly if you're
going to do like a book adaptation a really good book adaptation would take advantage of the fact
that it is a book and not just try to you know like recreate a movie or whatever so i think and
like the same goes with like video games like a video game adaptations or like video games based
off of like other media usually suck because they're just trying to like recreate the other media
like point for point and it's like always kind of underwhelming um and like the few times that
isn't the case is when it kind of goes off in its own direction like knights of the old republic
or something like that so i think adaptations should be allowed to just be their own thing
entirely because they're usually better um when you let them do that yeah that's probably the
objectively right answer but actually here's what here's my uh dissenting opinion uh not really um
i don't know i'm i'm really i'm struggling to justify like what's what's like what's an example
of like an adaptation or a sequel or something that like doesn't that is like totally inaccessible
that is made to be totally inaccessible to anyone who doesn't know the source material
but like it's still good and i i mean it's obviously it's not gonna it's not gonna stand on
its own it probably won't be like you know it can't become like a timeless in a way that something
like godfather does uh oh you know what's gonna be cool though there is actually a good example of
this please give me one have either of you seen revolutionary girl utena i know we've talked
about it on this show a bunch of times but i've never seen it oh that's funny yeah so revolutionary
girl utena is a very very good anime one of like the best anime of the 90s highly recommend it but
after it finished um they decided to do a movie of it because it was so successful
and rather than do like a sequel or a prequel or whatever um the neon genesis avingelian end of
ava you you can't you can't you can't watch that without like knowing that's the plot that's another
very good example is that would you really think of that as an adaptation of a source material
though i think that's just like a different thing as a part two like a so it is in a different
medium my is okay correct me if i'm wrong doesn't end of avingelian because the last few episodes
of avingelian take place in shinji's mind isn't end of avingelian just what's happening outside
his mind during those episodes it's it's not it's not i mean you can interpret it that way
or you could say that end of ava is basically just like they rewrote the end of of of the first
one and they are like competing cannons with each other gotcha uh or something but something like
that yeah um what were you saying about utena though yeah yeah yeah so utena is basically
instead of like doing a sequel or something for the movie um ikuhara the creator utena decided to
essentially remake the tv show and like tell the story in like a slightly different way
but he's telling a story that was originally spread out across like oh god like 39 episodes or
something like that in like an hour and a half movie um and like it is the movie is an absolute
god damn mess it includes a lot of callbacks to the show that make no sense unless you've seen
the original um a lot of like dumb in jokes and shit there's like so many parts of it that are
just complete gibberish if you haven't seen the series but if you have like it's still a mess
but it's like a really fun ride and you can still like get a lot out of it but i feel like if you
haven't seen the original it's just kind of frustrating because you never have any idea
what's going on because it doesn't take the time to explain anything to you right and and but that
in that way then if you you haven't seen the original or rather the yeah the show it's bad
then like does it suck as a standalone piece okay but yeah i think the fact that it's bad
it's okay the fact that it's bad to one audience and good to another like like neither of those is
correct but i think this is like the closest we can get to the thing you were talking about of
like a thing that is good but also requires you to have seen the original because if you if you
haven't seen the original then the natural consequences that you're not gonna get whatever
you're supposed to get out of it and so therefore for you it will be bad i'm i'm sad that this question
wasn't really about harry potter because i like talking about harry potter i thought that's where
it was going uh i'm uh i'm uh more and more ashamed to be to have been a potterhead with each
passing day it was fine it was good it was good it was good it was kind of good it was kind of good
it was pretty good come on come on everybody everybody everybody knows everybody knows it was
good everybody knows that it was it was pretty good at least except like the weird the weird
ending was kind of done when you think about it for the the what am i thinking of age demographic
like for that sort of audience it was great it's a bit weird to get into it as an adult
i don't know why people um it wore out it's welcome like not i mean not for me i mean like
maybe after it ended it started still wearing out it's welcome for me before jk rolling went like
full transphobe um when she started just tacking shit onto it um and then yeah the thing that like
extra soured me on it was the phrase her mayony 2020 like as soon as people started saying
shit like that i was like i didn't see anyone saying that in earnest but i heard about it
whoa and i know this the sentiment is that like it was about them 2020 no it was about warren right
people that were like we should vote for warren because she's her mayony because she has a plan
yeah it was it was more just like there was a certain kind of person who's like really into
harry potter who would like relate shit in politics to harry potter and it became like a huge meme for
a while of like oh my god please read another book i mean that's just that's just particular
fandoms potterheads hoovians things like that single track mind annoying the stuff about jk
rowlings like the thing she used to tweet would they would range from being like actually irritating
to when she the time when she was like oh yeah there was a jewish wizard at hogwarts of course
his name his name was barry goldstein and i've never mentioned him before but he was there all
along uh you know duh um very obnoxious to like the other stuff like the thing about like wizards
would just shit themselves and then oh yeah like that was just fucking hilarious like that's great
most of it was just stupid not all of it was offensive but a decent amount of it was also
offensive where did the shit yeah it got yeah yeah did they did they act right i liked this somewhere
they would vanish it which i think means that it's just gone i'm not sure exactly how harry potter
magic is goofy it it's not mine system it has rules but the rules don't make any fucking sense
have you have you read them or like how familiar are you i read um so this became like a joke at
some point for me that i read the first six books and then never read the seventh and then watched
the first seven movies and never watched the eighth so i still don't know how harry potter ends um
oh my god um i mean i i it ends really weird it ends really weird yeah i hear the ending's bad
so i never had like the motivation i would say i don't know if i would say that it's just bad but
it's like it's just it's just strange and i don't know i don't know that's all i can really say about
it uh uh i was compelled i found it compelling as a kid yeah the last minute they introduce all these
weird like extra macguffins that end up being like fucking key it's the wizard world operates on like
it's all about rules like there's tons of rules but they don't make any sense and they're made up
completely as it goes along um yeah the whole yeah i never was like too um uh critical like
thinking of of the rules i just sort of like took things as they came like i you read them as they
come out and if you don't you don't like cross reference them you don't find contradictions
then it's just it's fun but like yeah clearly was made up a lot as it went um like retro retro fitting
the the various things from the the previous books as the horcruxes it's pretty i mean i don't have
proof that she was doing that but it feels like that all these things that just so happen to be
very important later right at the end there's like the rule that like you can't you can't make food
you can't make food with magic that's like a fundamental law of the universe you can only
make it with no food yes you can only make it with slave labor uh but it's okay because they like it
the the slaves like it though yeah they don't want the sock diving into the political implications
of harry potter is a podcast in and of itself you're right you're right you're right how many
is in uh how many more voicemails do we have uh four more okay cool yeah we're getting there um
okay next one is uh that face when you listen to a pcp episode three two one go
okay all right cool thanks for the voicemail thanks man voicemail uh next one is called
margar's return three two one go hey i'm back
he's fat god i didn't realize how much i missed him
oh i'm crying tears of relief i just i realized this segment has reinforced something that i
already know about myself which is i will laugh at anything stupid like i just have i'm an individual
with a very dumb sense of humor on dude don't poopy pee it's great don't call margar's pee
don't call margar stupid pee pee poo poo shit and come yeah i was on uh tumblr a while back and uh
someone made a post that was like um oh god what was the fucking post that they made it was something
about oh it was um everyone needs to stop playing gotcha games with boobs in them and i
reblogged that and then like a minute after i reblogged it the same person posted elden a
double cast will reblog anything with the word boobs in it and i was like fuck they got me
i would also do that we've all we've all got our we've all got our um what's the word
what's the word i'm thinking of vices weaknesses vices vices maybe yeah
uh speaking of peepee poo poo the next one is called once upon a midnight poop balls while i pondered
poop and bop this is gonna be so bad i assume that's balls cut off um okay three two one go
ah there he is
that's me
have developed the number one weapon to take down ben no sento sun once and for all
i will introduce samurai bottle three thousand
oh
all
ha ha
It's a robot, no explanation as to why the robot is good.
It's just a robot.
It doesn't have weapons.
It probably does the same thing as the regular thing.
You just said fuck all you.
That's all it had to do.
Alright.
That's well okay.
I guess there's plot development on that front.
Sure.
Oh god.
Last one is called 9 year old anime girl, huge titties, 3, 2, 1, go.
On the topic of cartoon character age is not mattering, I was watching this one anime where
this character was like 9, but her character trait was that she had the hugest tits in
the entire cast.
Is it the gray hair girl?
And it was really clear that the animators really wanted you to fuck this character
because her tits were so huge and they were like the focal point of every scene she was
on.
So yeah, just don't worry about it.
I want to fuck this 9 year old anime girl and I don't care what Twitter has to say about
it.
That's taken, that's really run in.
That's really run in with what I said a little further than I meant.
This reminds me of last time I said about the girl on My Life Me, I said she was cute.
This reminds me of another anime, which I'm 99% sure is not the one he is talking about
that also has like an elementary school or with giant tits.
That one is called Aiken.
Have either of you seen Aiken?
A-I-K-E-N?
E-I-K-E-N.
Wait, is that really old?
I think I may have seen bits of that.
Yeah, it's old.
It's an old OVA.
Yeah.
Pretty funny looking.
It's like, there was a period of time where this was like the go-to for like examples
of shitty anime boobs.
Like if you just wanted like a generic gif of like giant anime titties bouncing around
in nonsensical ways, you'd pull a clip from Aiken.
These don't even make sense.
No, they look terrible.
But I mean, this is obviously a matter of taste.
Oh, are you talking about the pink-haired one with the glasses?
Yes, yes.
She is exactly who I was thinking of when he said a nine-year-old with huge tits.
Radical.
So this show is awful, unsurprisingly.
For me, it's one of those things where it's like so bad that it loops back around and
becomes funny again.
So like, I get a good laugh out of it because it like, it sucks so hard.
And it's also one of those shows where like, this is funny because this loops back around
to the adaptation thing.
It's an adaptation of a manga, but the manga is like, had actually been going on for a
long time, but they only had like two episodes worth of OVA to do.
So what they decided to do was like, all right, let's just cut between like the very beginning
of the show where we introduce like the main character and then like some highlights from
later in the manga.
So things just start happening with no explanation.
You have no idea who anyone is.
You're just watching wild antics unfold on screen against the will of God.
Okay.
That one on the right, that one on the right in that picture with the short hair, her,
is that a boob?
That is that pink?
No.
Or is that like her gut?
No, that's just like her sweater, just like, it's like the wind or something.
She doesn't look like that.
That's not like how she normally looks.
That's all right.
That's she looks really weird.
Yeah, it's just a weird picture.
Yeah, it's it's just like an anime that like it never takes its foot off the accelerator
and it's just like that for two episodes and then it's done and oh wait, I've seen this.
I've seen this image before.
That is for making.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good stuff.
This is what I mean when I say like for a while.
Okay.
I've seen a bunch of these.
Yeah.
This was like the go to for like bad anime titties.
And if you think that that's funny, if you're like me and you're horribly immature, you
will get a good laugh out of Aiken.
I don't know about like watching a whole show of something like that.
Well, you said it was an OVA, so like, not that funny because I'm scrolling down the
Google image results and like, okay, yeah, I've seen a bunch of these gifts.
I probably used to see them on 4chan or whatever.
Yes.
This is like, yep.
4chan or like, I don't know.
Some other anime forum.
Something awful, maybe.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah.
But yeah, it's like, it's two episodes.
It's like an hour total.
When you combine.
Have you ever seen the fucking?
Have you seen Garzi's wing?
I have seen Garzi's wing.
Okay.
And if we're talking about, if we're talking about terrible OVAs, that's a, that's, that's
a good one that we've discussed here on the show before.
Oh yeah.
Garzi's wing is very funny.
It is.
It gets less funny as it goes on, though.
The fact that it was made by the dude starts off really strong.
It was made by the dude who created Gundam, right?
I don't know.
Maybe.
I think so, which like makes it funnier that it was that bad.
It can't have been like written by him, though.
It can't be like, he might have been involved, but it can't be like his brainchild.
There's no way.
The thing about Garzi's wing that it was just sort of badly made, not necessarily that
it was like, um, badly written.
Like the, the dub is really funny because of how bad that's, it says, but like, I thought
it was just sort of.
It was, it was, it's, it's largely the dub that is the problem.
It was written and directed by the creator of Gundam.
And also from what I've heard, while the dub is unbelievably shitty, the anime still
sucks even if you watch it in Japanese.
Yeah.
But I bet it's not like hilariously bad.
I bet it's not.
No, I think I've watched one or something and it was just sort of, it seems like they
didn't have a lot of money or something.
It's like, what is it?
That show ghost stories, the one where they gave it the ridiculous gag dub.
The reason why they did that was because in Japanese it was also a shitty anime, but
it was shitty in the normal way where it's just boring.
And so they were like, well, if this anime sucks, we might as well like make it suck
in a funny way.
Didn't we just, didn't we talk about ghost stories like last week or, I feel like, God,
time is just, time is just going in circles, time, it's cyclical.
There's no past, no present, no future.
We're caught on an infinite loop.
God, tell me something I don't know.
I've become unstuck in time.
Uh, hey, that was the last voicemail.
Yay, we did it.
We made it.
Um, how long have we been gone?
What was it, like three hours?
Yeah, a little bit under three hours.
Have fun editing.
Oh wait, you guys don't edit this shit.
Fuck you, yeah, fuck you, Eleazar sucker.
Um, well, shit, any final, any closing thoughts before we shuffle off this mortal coil?
Subscribe to my YouTube channel.
Yes, go check out Elden, a double cast.
Am I saying that?
Did I learn to say it right?
Yes, you said it right that time.
Double cast spelled with a five and seven S.
That's right.
And, um, send us a voicemail if you want, uh, at speakpipe.com slash pzp voicemail.
And uh, fucking go subscribe, make my, make my dream come true, uh, go subscribe to our
patreon at patreon.com slash the procrastinators, uh, for, uh, bonus content.
We got like, I think we're going to have two new bonus episodes coming up this week.
The one just came out, the, the gamers tavern, uh, retrospective, uh, commentary track, uh,
since the, we did, it was funny the first time.
So we did it again.
Haha.
Uh, anything else?
Well, what else?
What's, what's left?
Uh, big booby mommy milkers.
Don't fucking invest in Bitcoin, Jesus Christ.
Um, I'd invest in Titcoin.
No.
Titcoin.
That's the next cryptocurrency.
Let's go.
Invest in Titcoin, everybody.
All right.
That's it.
That's the, the, the show for this week.
Thanks for joining us.
Goodbye.
Good night.
God bless.
Good bye.
Good luck.
Bye.
Woo.