Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. Today there's
Gibb.
Hi. Hey guys. Read my comic at Gibbontake.site. It's good.
And there's Tom.
Hey guys. Read my comic at Gibbontake.site.
And there's Jess.
Hey.
It's me.
Hey guys. Read my comic at Gibbontake.site.
And there's me. Read my comic at Gibbontake.site. The rarely seen, extremely tired, bestie boy
did not sleep last night because I was under the spell of a temptress demon named Factorio.
And when I closed my eyes and opened them again, 12 hours had passed and I'd watched, like,
of half a season of Star Trek Voyager, which is not as bad as everybody says, and it's
no, it's not. It's pretty good.
And Voyager.
Star Trek Voyager, Ben. We're already recording, so I hope you're recording too.
You may have been. You will not be penalized, but you will be chastised verbally by me.
Fuck you.
That's a price he's willing to pay.
Anyway, Factorio, you build your little factory and you're doing just fine.
Oh, then you run out of coal.
Oh god, you run out of coal.
You gotta get more coal.
Your factory loses power.
What are you gonna do?
Oh, you gotta expand your walls.
You gotta build more concrete walls everywhere.
Oh god, did you know that in Factorio, when you develop more technology and you increase
the level of pollution?
Yes, the level of pollution is tracked in Factorio.
The monsters in the surrounding area of your base evolve and get stronger.
What?
The more fucking shit you do.
So that means more raids.
More raids on your base.
This sounds like a made-up game.
It's a nightmare.
I don't believe that this is surreal.
What the fuck?
What is Factorio?
And then you get your fucking, oh my god, then you get your laser grid running, but then
you realize by making your whole fucking laser grid defense system to attach to your electrical
system, if one goes down, they all go down and you're fucked and then you've got no defenses
whatsoever, so you can't leave.
You can't stop playing Factorio.
It isn't often.
You can't.
You guys, I waste my whole night.
Can't you save and quit?
It's literally, it's literally, rape is what happened to me.
It forces you to play the game because if you don't, you lose the game.
It's Sisyphus.
It's the Sisyphus ball and it's fucked up and it's cruel, but it is very fun and I
do like making purple potions to evolve my tech trees and stuff, so it's also kind of
cool.
Anyway, I'm tired.
Star Trek Voyager is better than people say it is.
Good topic.
Nate, you know who's cool?
Tuvok.
Dude, bro, Tuvok, episode's about Tuvok just being sad that he's away from his five children
and a hot Vulcan wife.
That always hits me right in the right spot.
God, I wish I had a hot Vulcan wife.
Oh no, and here comes another episode about how Nelix was traumatized by his home planet
being destroyed and his whole family dying.
Wham, my whole family died.
Give me a fucking break.
I don't know if you've seen it before, but there is an episode later in the series where
Nelix and Tuvok go into the transporter together.
That episode was not okay.
That was not an acceptable episode.
They morph into a single entity called Tuvix and he's like, he's all the logic and reason
of Tuvok, but with all of the retardation and autism and charm and the resourcefulness
and embarrassment and humiliating stupidity of Nelix combined into one great but horrible
person.
And then at the end of the episode, they have to essentially decide whether to euthanize
him by separating him back into his old selves.
And he's all sad about it, like, no, I'm a new entity, please don't kill me.
And they're like, no, we don't like you.
We want Tuvok back.
I really cannot impress upon people, and I think we talked about this in the PCP because
I just saw that episode.
I could not believe the way that they framed that in the episode as it straight up is like
Tuvix is like, he's working on the bridge or whatever they're like a Tuvix.
We order you to submit yourself for destruction.
He's like, no, I don't care if it's cowardly.
I get to decide if I live or die.
And every member of the crew, like one by one, as if it was a fucking, I don't know, like
walking down the aisle or something, they all turn their back on him as Janeway orders
him to death as he fights for survival.
And just, it was the most fucked up thing I've ever seen a Starfleet captain do, I think,
just order one person to die for the greater good.
What the fuck?
You can't do that Star Trek.
You can't do that.
They just fucking did.
A captain is not supposed to order people to their death against their will when they don't
want to die.
There would be times when my boy Chakote, yo, tum, tum, Chakote, me speak Indian tribe words
based, thoroughly based, when truly the strangest alien of all, the Native American.
When a captain does shit that puts the crew in danger and they're acting irrationally
or unfairly, there are many people on the ship who have the authority to remove the
captain from command, namely the first officer being the main one, but also the medical officer
and shit.
If he had, like, ordered, if Jan would order, like, the whole crew to, like, you know, commit
suicide or something, they'd be like, okay, well, that's not okay, but what if she had
just ordered, she ordered one man to commit suicide because she wanted the other two guys
back, personally.
That was a personal thing for her.
That's, like, there was no, you can't even argue that, like, oh, they're stranded in the
Delta Quadrant.
She needs a Tuvok back.
She had all the strengths of Tuvok.
That was arguable that Tuvoks was better than both of them individually and had, like,
both their strengths combined.
So, this was not, like, it's coldly, there was no emergency.
See, I thought they would frame the episode as there would be an emergency.
They, in this particular situation, they had to force them to defuse.
I guess that would make more sense.
That's what they usually do stuff like that.
Yeah, that's what they usually do stuff like that to get by it.
What if the fused person has a very short lifespan, but they just want to live it out?
I think Janeway's philosophy on this decision might have been that they need Tuvok and Nelix
to be separated in case the opportunity arises to also sacrifice Nelix.
You know what?
It all makes sense now.
You know, everybody b******s about Nelix.
I haven't even found him particularly annoying.
There's, like, one good Nelix episode where, like, somebody dies
and he, like, loses his faith in his stupid cat religion.
Oh, yeah, in the Great Forest or whatever.
Yeah.
He personally dies, experiences no afterlife and completely loses his faith.
Yeah, that episode was like a-
That was a tear-jerker.
That was a good episode because he-
Hey, wait a minute.
Nelix, Nelix.
Nelix.
Nelix, Brony Documentary.
Remember that?
Sounds about right.
Damn, I haven't heard that name in a while.
Jesse, did you beat the remake yet?
I did.
You did.
It is completed.
I'm halfway through and I've decided to stop playing it because I don't like it.
I don't think it's your kind of game, Tom.
Just, even though a lot of people like it, it just doesn't strike me as a Tom kind of game.
So boring.
Really?
The side quests are just the worst, the absolute worst.
Absolutely.
We are.
What do you mean?
Forgot to see it.
Ben, I said before, we're all recording this.
Well, that's why I said, Ben, we're recording this.
I hope you are too because we started ahead of time.
You know, that's why that was clarified.
Well, I'm recording now.
Okay.
You started early.
You're not supposed to start before 3.10, but that's fine.
There's no rule that we have to start at 3.10.
I didn't know anyone else was showing up.
We said, okay, if someone shows up, we won't pedal.
There are more guidelines than actual rules.
Sorry.
Well, in any case.
For the six previous minutes that I was in Audible.
Okay.
Indeed.
Right.
Tom.
Final Fantasy game.
The side quests are just so modern game design and I don't like them.
That's definitely true.
But Tom, I was wondering about this.
Why not just not do them?
Why not just skip all the side quests?
Are they skippable?
Some of them aren't.
Some of them are not.
There are some places where you have to do at least one, I think.
I'm in the wall market right now and Arith just got in her dress and it's just like,
you know, hang out around the town with Johnny Cloud while I just doll Arith up.
I'm like, oh, this sucks.
I hate this.
I think you have to do like one and then you can go back and trigger it or something to
progress, I believe.
It's pretty gay and I don't like it.
Do the squats.
Do the squats, bro.
I did the squats.
That was the first thing I did.
I destroyed it and I thought it was going to be way harder, but it was literally just
hitting a button in order.
Okay.
Yep.
I'm sick.
It was fine.
So the game is kind of set up in a way where you kind of feel like you can't not do the
side quests because it puts you in these chapters that are basically just side quest chapters
and it tells you don't go to the thing until you do all the stuff.
So it like guilt trips you every time you try and like do something and then it like
punks you because you'll do all the side quests and then you'll go to the next part
of the mission.
Are you sure you want to go inside already, Cloud?
I'm like, what do you mean?
I did everything.
It's all checked off.
You know, I wish they would change the dialogue.
So it's like, okay, wow, you've had a full day, Cloud, time for a good night's rest after
all that activity.
Yeah.
That would go a long way for me.
And the way that it's set up like that kind of makes it so that there's no real secrets
in the game because everything that is extra is right there.
It's a side mission that is given to you and you just know about it immediately.
You know, I think like the only actual like secret boss is the Bahamut thing, but that's
not even secret.
You just know exactly what to do with the whole game.
Just do all the guys.
You know, that's a spoil.
I do think there is one other thing beyond that that I've heard.
I haven't done it myself, but I'm looking into it.
I think there's one other boss.
Speaking of things that are in the game, it looks like I won that bet from last week.
What was the bet?
About whether you could have a date with Aretha Tifa or Barrett.
It looks like yes, you can.
That's not really a date.
Part two is now.
Well, I mean, there's like one scene Slimes send me a link that said Final Fantasy 7 remake
date mechanics and romance scenes and it says date event happens in chapter 14 at the beginning
of chapter 14.
A dating event will occur where Cloud visits Aretha's garden at night.
Yeah, there's one scene where the part where you're staying at Aretha's house, Aretha's
house.
I'm not saying Aretha.
You can't make me.
No one can do it.
We are staying at our house.
There's a scene where like inside your Barrett or Tifa, Aretha's in the garden and you talk
to them for like two minutes.
That's right, that's right.
It's not really a date though.
It's more like what are you doing out here in the garden?
Okay, tell you what's bad.
I will go back.
If it can be Tifa, Aretha's or Barrett, I'm pretty sure that's what I, that's it.
Well, okay, I mean, I'll have to go listen to the exact wording of the agreement.
If it's fair, if that's an accurate representation, we were talking about the gold saucer, but
if this covers that, I'll pay five bucks if I was just wrong about that.
It was ten.
You know, that's...
I mean, the term was that there would be a date.
There would be a date scene between...
But this isn't even a date.
It's one conversation.
But it's the same thing.
If there's a thing where you can get either Tifa or Aretha or Barrett with Cloud, that's
the new version of the same thing.
I mean, I thought we were specifically talking about the gold saucer.
Well, viewers, I don't know.
Go back and listen to the audio and draw your own conclusions.
I mean, I don't think...
Who won the bet?
I don't think in the written up bet that there was like it has to be the gold saucer
one, but that's what we...
We talked about it.
We nailed down our terms.
Exactly what we were discussing about it.
No, who gives a hoot?
I want my ten dollars.
Let's look into it.
You know what's really fucking goofy about Final Fantasy 7 Remake that I write in the
beginning when you're going on like the bombing mission, like the second bomb mission, Reactor
Five or whatever, and you're having all those scenes in the subway car, and I don't know.
Maybe it's just me nitpicking, and this isn't really a problem, but I just found it hilarious
that it's like all these normal-looking people in business suits going to work, and then
Barrett just walks in with a fucking gatling gun on his arm and sword has this giant, and
cloud has this giant fucking sword, and nobody cares, and it's just like, oh man, these terrorist
guys are pretty scary.
I would hate to run into them.
Hi, Mr. Gatling Gunman.
Good to see you going to work today, and it's just like, how am I supposed to take this
seriously?
You know, to be fair, it was always like that, but I would argue this is one of those things
that just gets weirder, the more realistic.
If this was a PS1 blocky man game, it would just be fine, but because this is so realistic,
I'm just like, these people would notice that there's a man running around with a machine
gun strapped to his arm.
I've always thought it was very strange that nobody comments ever about Barrett having
a big old gun on his arm.
But he has this photorealistic argument with the Shinra employee, and why would you call
out the man with the machine gun arm in a tiny and closed space?
Are you kidding me?
I also like that the Shinra employee looks at the man with the machine gun for an arm
who is very clearly obviously a terrorist, and says, I bet you support the terrorists.
As Barrett comes in to defend the terrorists in the conversation.
With a bunch of guys behind him who also have guns and swords.
And then it's like later, after you blow up everything and the big fucking robot guy
and you get back from your actor five, and the guy's like, I've broadcasted you terrorists
all over the fucking world.
Everybody knows who you are.
You just get off the train and walk around as cloud and nobody cares.
I'm just like, everyone was just paying attention to this epic fight, and they know who the
terrorists are.
They expose Avalanche, but then nobody cares.
They were on the TV.
Like what the fuck?
Why is this happening?
These people should realize that the man with the giant sword on his back, the only blonde
person in the entire world apparently, is now among you ridiculous.
I also like how it shattered.
It was really great.
It was a great logical change how the plate falling on sector seven did not matter at
all and absolutely nobody was hurt even slightly.
Everyone was fine.
Every single person made it out.
Were there people on the top of the plate who lived there, the above grounders who maybe
fell onto them and all the bourgeois died?
That's a good question that would have also been a good question in the original game
and is something that we could have seen expanded upon here and you know, I always wondered
because they said so many times, we're going to expand Midgar, we're going to add things
that maybe should have been there the first time.
Like hunting rats.
Like rescuing a little girl's cats.
Are you fucking kidding me?
One has to think, okay, gee, what are the ways in which you could expand a game that
takes place in a massive eight sector city of which we only previously saw sectors five,
six and seven?
I don't know.
Maybe show me the other sectors of the city.
Maybe let me explore.
Let's just stretch out the areas you've already seen to ridiculous proportions and destroy
the game's pacing completely and make every scene take 50 hours longer.
That makes a lot more sense.
I've been trying to absorb a lot of the people's reception and I think a lot of people just
love that like, I mean, I don't know man, I'm trying to give people the benefit of that
out here, but a lot of people seem to be like totally fine with just getting like, you know,
the same scenes, but now there's like more dialogue and like more expression and like,
oh, you know, Aris looks prettier now in while she's saying, you know, similar things to
before and then the time Janie show up and carry you out of the room.
The more I think about it, just like the more it totally blows my mind and baffles me that
they made the entire game Midgar and did not let me explore all of Midgar.
That was the last 20 years for, if not for that, we get the one extra area, the above
ground place of where Jesse's parents live.
That's one, I believe that is the one and only actual new area that we explore to any
degree and you know, hey, what is right, I forget, what is the difference between the
sectors that we explore in the original Final Fantasy seven is that like a five is where
Wal-Mart it is, five is Aris, and seven is Tifa's bar.
I just wonder like what the other sectors would be like if you did go to them.
Yeah, I've wondered that my whole life, would it just be the same sort of stuff or yeah.
What you guys don't realize is that Final Fantasy seven remake part two is going to be all the
rest of Midgar and just going to be more fetched by, and we never go back until way later.
Not now.
Now it's going to be totally different.
It's going to be Midgar too.
Yeah, you know, I will happily plant my flag though that like, I understand Jesse, I felt
very similar for a long time, however, I long since have thought that like, even if we did
explore that, that Square Enix would not fill those areas with anything good or satisfying.
So that, I mean, that's been my issue, so I just had no hope.
Another thing about this game that is incredibly silly is that it's trying to like set up these
tense moments, but then it seems to want to add gameplay that undermines those moments.
And I find it very funny.
Like the, you know, like you, you rescue Eris, I'm going to keep saying Eris because I'm
playing this game, but forgive me for my sins.
But and you fight the like the Turk guy and like the first, the guy is like, you have
to learn how to use the counter and stuff to beat him.
Yes.
And all the fucking crazy ghost men are in the house and you're trying to escape like
they're chasing you.
And it gets to a point where like you have to knock down a chandelier or something to
like distract them and like get Eris out of there.
And it's like supposed to be this tense scene of like making this one like distracting move
so you can both get out of there and they start shooting at you as you're supposed to get
away.
But instead of just making it a cut scene, you have to like slowly grapple on the ceiling
and you're just getting shot with bullets and they're doing like two points of damage.
I'm like, so this just I could just sit here for like 40 minutes and take like a tenth
of my actual HP and damage and they just won't move from this one spot tension deflated.
And it's just like, why, why do it like that?
Just have it be a cut scene.
There's so many things like that.
Like at a certain point, you get like melee weapons for Barrett and one of them is just
like a big stupid steel ball.
Yeah, I know.
But like in the cut scenes, you still have Barrett like threatening people with a gun.
Like I'm going to shoot you with this big stupid steel ball that does nothing.
Oh, I like this big like scissor hand one.
He would point.
Oh, he's going to cut you.
Barrett's going to.
Yeah.
I've also always thought it was, I mean, I appreciate that Barrett has some like melee weapons
because it's always been weird that like the biggest hulkenist roided out his boy is
like gunman.
They're terrible to use.
They're so slow.
Yeah.
And like the fun of Barrett is shooting.
Yeah, but yeah.
And in the in the original game, you didn't have that problem because it was all just
to turn base the same battle system for everyone.
So the melee attacks were just as quick and snappy as the gun attacks.
Were you were you disappointed spoilers?
I guess for Tom and other people, not really spoiler that that red 13 was not playable.
I mean, I kind of thought that was reasonable considering a little time.
He would have been playable for like five minutes.
So what would the yeah, who gives a crap?
But Jesse, tell me the ghost, the time, the final battle, you got to tell me what you think
I've been dying to hear your perspective.
I will say this.
I am not disappointed, obviously, because Square Enix did exactly what Square Enix does
and exactly what I knew Square Enix would do.
You wouldn't be disappointed if a crocodile bit you because that's its nature.
I'm not, I'm not sad.
I'm not angry at Square Enix.
You know who I'm angry at, Nate?
I'm angry at all the people who are only just now crying foul, who are acting surprised
by this.
Who didn't see this coming?
If you didn't see this coming five years ago, then it's exactly what you deserve.
I'll admit, I did not expect them to go this far.
I didn't think they would do this.
I don't know what this ending is.
I've heard a lot of people complain about it, but there was one person on my Twitter
feed who just like, man, I just finished Final Fantasy 7.
Love the ending.
Amazing twist.
Can't wait to see what they do in part two.
Did this person play the original?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, you know, there's a school of thought that I find reprehensible that any change
is good because it's new.
I played the original, you know, cool game, liked it, but now it's time for new things.
I like things that are different, not the same.
The same is bad and boring.
That's why I bought a game called Final Fantasy 7.
And that really, it opens up a can of worms on like, what was the expectation?
I feel like a lot of people are, you know, I'm so exhausted.
I've been thinking about this so much and like I, last night I was playing factorial
all night.
I maybe want to kill myself.
And then I wake up and I go and I watch like one guy's video.
This was the most sober take I've heard from somebody on YouTube.
Maybe I'll, maybe we'll get his name.
And the whole video, he was like, okay, I was, I did not want this remake.
I was scared of it and I knew it would not be good.
I was by the sky name.
Never knows best.
Yes.
That's the one.
And he gets to whatever he's talking about.
And he's like, oh, but actually the game won me over because it was like good at points.
And I was like, okay, like sure, the gameplay is kind of fun sometimes.
I agree.
But I'm like, okay, but how about he's saving his big point for the end.
And he does get to the end of his point where he's like, okay, yes.
Like the ending is like a nightmare.
The fact that they're like setting us free from destiny.
Like every logical aspect of my body tells me based on knowing these developers and what
screenings does.
Sure.
They're giving themselves free reign to write new stuff.
These people are not good at making stories.
We've seen for decades.
They don't know what they're doing this team.
So to be excited for a new story is nonsensical.
And yet, and yet I'm kind of excited for new stuff guys.
I can't wait to see what happens.
Why would you end on that point?
Why?
My final point was it will be bad, but there's no getting off this train we're on, which
is a cheeky little bit of reference.
I hate that point so much.
It personally offends me.
Like that's a defense of these choices.
Fun fact about that video.
That guy never knows best commented over the last week on my old Final Fantasy 7, you cannot
remake it will be fucking bad video.
And his comment is comment was damn it.
I wanted to use some variant of Final Fantasy 7.
You cannot remake in a video title, but then thought I'd better check to make sure no one
has done so already.
And here I am.
And five fucking years ago to truly ahead of its time really great video.
I loved it to not attend and watch it twice.
So that that review, which I think is still the best review so far that I've seen of the
game from anyone.
It was originally going to be called you cannot remake but he checked out and saw that I already
did that five years ago, which everyone should have checked and seen that I already did that.
You know, I'm seeing yeah, it's making the rounds and I'm even seeing people like attributing
it to people like, oh, how clever for of Pat from two best friends played who have said
that thing.
Yeah, I kind of said it five years ago.
I kind of predicted all of this and you didn't listen.
I warned you all and you didn't listen.
And now now that I'm right, as usual, every time that I'm vindicated and proven right,
nobody cares.
Nobody's going to acknowledge it.
That's all I want.
Just to make knowledge from the world that I told you so just once I've been getting
a couple of comments on my on my video.
Some saying, wow, bro, you were sure we're right.
And others saying this is embarrassing, you know, bet you regret this one now.
And you know, truly it is the duality of man.
I now that I've seen all this, I can't deny that I like had lots of fun playing through
I like, I'm more of a grindy kind of guy in this game was grindy as hell for the side
missions.
And I enjoyed zoning out and watching Star Trek Voyager while engaging in the gameplay
loop, which is pretty fun.
So I like all that stuff.
But but then the whole question rains is like, this could have been Final Fantasy 16 this
battle system with like new stories.
But the fact that it's a remake, the only thing that's relevant to that is like the
story.
That's like the most important thing.
And in my humble opinion, I think some mistakes were made.
So did you find this game to be, I don't know, do you, do you like it?
Is it good?
Are you a fan?
I'm just totally split lots that are good.
I mean, it has like moments of fun, I guess, in terms of the combat, even though I think
the game probably should have just been a standard turn based.
I mean, like by the time the game came out, I had been dreading it for so many years that
like I just didn't care anymore.
So it couldn't have possibly disappointed me or let me down because I was I was just
at a point where it's like, you know what, I don't fucking care.
I'm just going to take the fucking ride.
Fuck it.
And so I did and like again, none of the bad stuff surprised me in any way because it's
exactly what I expected.
So I wasn't like taking a backer like, oh, I can't believe they did this.
I'm like, of course they did that.
That's exactly what they would do.
Yeah.
So I was just kind of like being used by the whole thing.
And I mean, the game was fun.
So I guess everybody was right, but I was the most right.
It's I mean, I generally don't like the mindset.
Of like, you know, I'll accept this, I'll purchase this video game based on the fact
that they they wanted to make money again.
So they just gave it the name of a popular game and then everybody bought it because
it had the name.
And it's, you know, it's okay and it's not great and the original is better in a lot
of ways and blah, blah, but you know, overall, I endorse that this this business practice
and I will do it again the next time they come back with some thing that I recognize
I will buy it and say that it's okay.
And I'll just keep doing that over and over again forever.
That's what we're doing.
That's what we're encouraging.
You know, to me, the most the most offensive part of the whole remake, more offensive than
the Time Jannies or the fucking Kingdom Hearts fighting the big black guy for the beginning
of Kingdom Hearts at the end of the game, not not a black guy like Barrett.
I mean, a big black, you know, like a massive goo.
What's that thing called?
Yeah.
What's the fuck?
You know what I'm everyone knows.
I'm fucking talking.
Literally just that guy is the final boss of the game.
More offensive than that.
More offensive than like the Sephiroth and his stupid wing and a little sword fight with
him at the end, which completely takes away any mystique or power or, you know, threat
of him.
Some people are like, oh, I can't wait for them to read Victor.
They cannot do the rest of the game the way it originally was.
You already kicked his ass.
Now that this has happened.
Claude kicks his ass like in the first part of the game now.
Yeah.
Dude, what about the fucking Advent Children cutscene where he's flying around and cutting
fucking buildings in half?
I'm so confused.
Oh, yeah.
I love how like Nomura only has one ending of a game that he can think of.
It's Kingdom Hearts 2 flying through the buildings.
Yeah.
Whether it's a movie or a game, that's all he knows how to write.
It's just, oh, what do I do at the end here?
Oh, they fly through a void and cut buildings in half.
That'll be cool.
Do you put much stock into this thing that like, oh, it's okay that that happened, Jesse,
because it was in like an alternate dimension world where like, you know, it wasn't, it
was like an alternate dimension world, you know, they weren't in like literal Midgar.
They were in like fake wreckage world.
So it's like, okay, that Claude, and like it makes sense that Claude could like fly
and get what you're saying.
I fucking, who gives a fuck?
I just don't want to have this conversation is the main thing.
I don't want to have to think about these things.
I fucking like did a backflip off of a motorcycle onto another motorcycle in definitely real
Midgar.
I don't know if that really flies.
You know, it's like, there are parts in the story where it tries to do the advent children
flipping off motorcycle stuff, but there are also a lot of parts where it tries to be
more grounded and have like realistic physics.
And it's just totally clashes with itself because it can't decide whether it's an anime
or like a realistic, you know, cyberpunk dystopia.
It's part in the original, I mean, in the good one when Claude was in a coma and ate
shit and died and fell in a wheelchair into the fucking live stream.
That was now that was advent children shit.
I want to see.
I want to see him tumble, crippled down a fucking hill and his fucking wheelchair get
pushed by Tifa because she's been caring for him for too long.
She's sick of his shit because it's part eight of the fucking remake.
And it's the whole game where you just play taking care of clouds, retarded brain simulator.
And you know, at the bad end is where, oh, fuck, I'm sick of this guy.
He didn't even like me.
He chose areas over.
He did the era state instead of me.
So she fucking, you know, euthanized them and it's supposed to play.
Yeah.
Hilarious.
That's.
Oh, right.
My point.
More offensive than all that.
Even more offensive than Zach, you know, that whole shit, the cra...
More offense, the most offense, the one part of the game that actually made me yell at
my TV screen.
Oh, fuck you was Rufus Shinra's pants.
The pants, the design.
The whole damn guy.
As soon as I saw those pants, I thought, there's the Nomura I know.
That's my boy.
You know, but he designed Shinra the first time.
Yeah.
They're, what happened?
Well, I can tell you exactly what happened is he was new to the company and he had no
real authority and someone told him probably Sakaguchi or like the people responsible for
designing Midgar in the look of the game.
They probably said to him, this is the look of the game.
We are going for a Western steampunk, you know, cyberpunk, technological, modern aesthetic.
People have to be dressed like they would fit in the modern age.
The bad guys are not wearing like cleric robes or wizard robes or no one's wearing night
armor.
We're wearing like suits, like people wear in real life, draw the characters like that.
And the characters to just look like regular people for the most part in regular clothes
because that's the aesthetic of the game.
And because he was a lowly grunt at the time, he said, yes, boss, this is what I will do.
I will please my bosses and he designed them that way.
But deep down inside, he had a burning rage going, oh God, if only I could make them anime,
I just want to make them more anime.
And so now 20 years later, he has taken the reins of the company in this slow, insidious
hostile takeover, also that he could get to this moment and finally rectify that one mistake
and finally he can turn these characters into anime and have weird cut up pants that look
like they went through a paper shredder.
And so that's what he did now.
He's finally fixed his greatest regret in life.
He's made characters look significantly stupider.
Reno, his whole thing is that he's, you know, he's kind of lazy and slovenly.
So his suit is, you know, like it's open.
He doesn't wear like a tie.
He doesn't have his coat buttoned up.
That tells you all you need to know about the character.
Right there.
It's perfectly fine.
All the other Turks are buttoned up and they look spiffy and snazzy.
Don't you love how we've improved the pacing of the game by having Cloud immediately kick
Reno's ass in their first meeting, deflating all tension or narrative weight of Turks?
But it's not enough for him to just have his jacket open and not have a tie on.
He has to have like a weird anime sash around it.
Did you notice the weird sash?
No, I did not notice that.
I did not.
I'll take your word for it though.
Like his jacket is not an actual, it doesn't have buttons.
It's not just unbuttoned.
It has no buttons.
It just has a weird sash.
It's a small thing to complain about, I know, but really the pants is what just was like
a step.
That was crossing the line for me.
That was the point where I finally went, you son of a bitch, those pants are the worst
thing I have ever seen in my life.
How am I supposed to make this guy seriously as a threat when he looks like that?
God, I mean, Rude looks great.
Rude just looks like he always looked, aka good and cool.
He looks like a teenager at prom in 2007.
Yes, Reno does.
Rude is based in Red Pilled and Love.
Not Rude.
Yeah.
Rude looks good.
Love is black tie.
Black on black, baby.
What was I going to say?
The argument around Rufus's design in the remake, I think it really, it's such a great
microcosm of everyone's thought process because obviously this is detail that doesn't matter
that much, but it informs the character it's interesting, right?
It's like you say, oh, God, they changed his design.
What's that about?
Then the response is going to be like, oh, he looks fine.
What's the problem?
Okay, well, I'm actually looking at it and I just don't like it.
It doesn't really fit with the character, blah, blah, blah.
Then the response becomes, well, Nomura did it.
He's the one who designed it originally, so what are you complaining about?
It's the same people doing it.
Okay, well, you know, times have changed.
Nomura designed it when he had bosses and people smarter than him telling him what
to do, but now that he doesn't have people higher up telling him what to do, he can do
whatever stupid shit he's always wanted to do, and so now the characters look stupid.
It doesn't even make sense from a character standpoint.
Rufus is like this silver spoon.
He's the heir to the company.
He's dressed to impress at all times.
He would just be wearing a regular suit, wouldn't he?
That makes sense.
It's not a phase, dad.
It's not a regular suit that's white and cool looking.
No, he has to have silly, goofy, paper shredder anime pants.
Rufus Shinra has become Ben St. going to Hot Topic, buying those big ass pants with
straps and shit, going, it's not a phase, mom, goth is a lifestyle, and I will choose
to live by it.
This will be my governing policy when I take over Shinra.
I do think I would have really liked this look when I was a teenager.
That's true.
You would have appreciated it.
It looks big.
It looks big, bulky, and a skirt.
Does it look like a flowing coat?
To be fair, I want to point out that the original Rufus did not simply have pants.
He did have sort of like a long coat thing going on.
Okay, that's true.
It didn't look like this, but I mean, polygons would not have allowed it.
Indeed.
I mean, it wasn't this.
It wasn't like this.
This fuck.
This is some fucking Hot Topic bullshit.
Yes.
I mean, his design was a bit silly before, but we've just really taken it to 11 now,
and I mean, it just kind of looked like he was wearing a trench coat, which, yeah, yeah,
which was cool.
Well, it's like, he's got like a suit jacket over a trench coat, which is a little weird.
It is weird.
I fully acknowledge his design was kind of strange previously.
I just think it's clearly way more so and more Hot Topic-y now than it was before.
The case.
Indeed.
Well, there you go.
I mean, of course, and eventually, I don't know, the whole thing just comes back to like,
yeah, I mean, you know, you remake something and like you can't encapsulate like every
little detail of a thing in a, you can't just upscale everything and give them all the same
spells and stuff and expect it to be like the same experience.
You know what?
In that guy, Never Knows Best video, he made a chart that was very educational where he
pointed out that like product is made and then like divergent path, person interprets
product and then there's another divergent path, other person interprets product.
But then that other guy who interpreted it, in this case, the creators or whatever, then
they make a remake and then it is consumed by the viewer and the dichotomy between like
the different interpretations of the thing.
Like I just don't care.
I just don't care what any individual developer thought about Final Fantasy VII when it was
being developed.
It can be interesting to know, but I don't care.
What I care about is the product that actually came out.
That's the only thing that matters and it was good.
And this is the reason for all the issues that I'm seeing before me right now.
Well, actually, that's not even true.
When you just change the whole story and add literal fate deviation mechanics to a plot.
Okay.
The way that it was handled with the time janitors and stuff and like Sephiroth like
vaguely being aware of Destiny and Eris vaguely being aware, but they don't really say whether
or not they are or not.
They don't really explain it.
Fuck you, Eris.
Spit it out.
You fucking bitch.
Just say that you know who.
It's like that.
It was handled very clunkily and very terribly and badly because Nomura wrote it.
So of course it was.
Because they want to leave everything wide open because they don't know what they're
doing.
Right.
The concept of it itself, I don't really give a shit about either way because of course
it was going to be a new canon.
Why would you even expect anything else?
I mean the fact that a remake exists in the first place is itself an indication of new
canon because it's going to be different.
It was always going to be different to some degree and the fact that it's different to
a large degree doesn't change anything.
People are saying, it's kind of getting on my nerves how many people are going, oh they
falsely advertised it as a remake.
They lied to us.
No, they didn't.
You know, you're not going to find anyone more defensive of the original Final Fantasy
7 than me but this argument that they somehow falsely advertised or lied to people doesn't
hold water for me.
It just sounds like stupid.
I believe that a little bit.
I'm not one of these people who would sue them.
I just feel cheated by playing the product.
In order to believe that it was going to be an exact representation of the original,
you would have had to not pay attention to Square Enix for the last 20 years.
I don't think that, I think you're trying to give them a pass on this issue that just
because they've made bad stories, a remake, people have been bringing up the example and
it was a bunch of people like never knows best, whatever, people will be like I love
getting my expectations subverted.
Remember Metal Gear Solid 2 guys?
That was so genius.
This game, it could have been good, it was just done bad.
A sequel is not the same as a remake.
There are things you can do in a sequel that is a totally different situation from calling
something a remake.
When they remade Final Fantasy 4 in the 3D models for the DS, that was a remake.
Why didn't they change the story?
Why didn't they do that?
Because it's Final Fantasy 4 a remake.
Why did they change it this time?
I don't know because they don't want to gamble on making Final Fantasy 16 so they put all
their hopes on a remake and they cram all their terrible ideas into this because it's
what they got.
It's because they know it'll sell.
This is the rationale going on in my mind and I find it deceptive and duplicitous.
I do not think they deserve a pass in the same way that you can give.
I'm not giving them a pass, I'm just saying.
All this anger and betrayal that people are dealing with now, I have been dealing with
and coming to terms with since it was announced.
Since Advent Children came out in 2005, that's when I noticed that this train was going off
the fucking rails.
So I've just long since come to terms with this.
I can't muster the kind of gamer rage that so many are having over this because it's
like yeah, what did you expect?
I have been uniquely surprised by the particular way that this has happened.
I did not expect it so perhaps, I don't know, that's why I feel strongly.
There was a good point that never knows best brought up in his video that I agree with,
I think, maybe, and would like to expand on just to see if I agree with it coming out
of my own face.
So this idea of we're going to remake a little bit of the game first and then use that as
a springboard to maybe surprise people and tell a new story, okay, I can, you know what?
I can deal, I can vibe with it, that's fine.
Do your silly little fan fiction, do whatever crazy stupid bullshit you want, so go ahead
and surprise me in the next game, that's fine.
However, what makes more sense to make this deviation when they leave Midgar or to make
this deviation, oh, I don't know, at the part of the game where the disc changed, where
Aris dies, the most important scene in the game, wouldn't that make more sense to be
the point where the story of this first one ends and then you put a little stinger in
there that says, hey, maybe we can deviate a little bit, wouldn't that be better in every
way?
Well, that just gets back into the issue that is so easy for us to ignore now that this
is a tenth of a fucking game, that this is, you know, like, it's so easy to forget that
with everything going on.
And like, in some way, I guess the way they're doing it, like, okay, they've kind of given
themselves leverage because they are going to be doing just something different now.
But I mean, I just don't trust them, I don't trust the artistic integrity of these people
to like, they sat down like five years ago and said, here's what we're doing, guys, we're
making the first one at the end, we're including a scene where we say Destiny's Change and
this is our plan, we know what we're doing, they don't know what they're doing, there
is no plan, they just know that now they've given themselves the ability to do anything,
so they did not sit down, I guarantee you, and plan anything beyond like, guys, what
if we subverted expectations, what if we did that?
This is their guiding star, and they think it makes a good game, and they're wrong,
because there's a lot, there's like meaning, but I guess nothing means anything, right?
Like every story, it doesn't matter how good or what the point of a story is, it just matters
if it subverts expectations, that's all that matters, right?
I wonder if they're going to somehow, like, make Sephiroth like, turn good and be like,
we have to stop Genova, guys, she was the bad, Genova was bad, I'm on the team now,
and Sephiroth just joins the party, I'm just, I'm just spittballing ways that it could be
silly and stupid at this point, because I'm just entertained by it.
I think you're going to save Eris and kill Tifa, I think this motherfucker is going to
do the stupidest possible thing, I mean, hey, it's a new world, maybe, we can do whatever
we want, so let's save Eris and kill Tifa, that is the most obvious thing you could
possibly do, and I would put money, it's going to happen, I would bet, I'll bet anybody
ten dollars right now, Eris lives, Tifa dies, I will bet that happens, who wants to take
me up for ten dollars?
It's certainly possible, anything's possible.
Anything's possible.
I don't know, I don't know whether you can kill a woman these days, I don't know if
that's possible.
Yeah, I mean, Jesse, you've seen the end now, nobody died, as you said, forget that, every
Avalanche member, oh, sorry, we don't know, the millions of Avalanche members that are
out there, but the ones we're doing now, they're all alive.
Just this once, Rose, everyone lives, everybody, they're all fine.
I don't know, I said this somewhere before, but in Gernlagen, the show, there's an episode
where all the supporting cast from earlier in the show dies, and a lot of people felt
that it was abrupt and kind of cheap and kind of sucked, but they all died.
When they made a movie, it was basically a remake of that scene, like the second part
of the series, they just changed that scene, such that all those characters just live now,
they just changed it, and what did it do?
It just made people happy, who didn't want to see them die, and it undid a little bit
of the tragedy that moment, but whatever, they piled it on a ketan.
I think that is like the worst, most hacky decision ever made in the history of things
I like, and I mean, it's just exactly the same thing here.
You just don't get to do that.
It makes you sad when a character dies, but that's the point, you're supposed to feel
sad so that you can feel happy when the victory is achieved.
I'm hearing people make this argument.
I mean, yes, literally stories are, you don't need to defend these fictional people that
only exist in fucking bits and bytes, they literally feel no pain, they exist to serve
a story, but I've been hearing people make the argument that like, okay, okay, in the
original, the point of that story, like sure, Sakaguchi had a theme, it was life, right?
The theme of the game was life.
So it's about like, you know, the fragility of life, and you know, like the difference
that human beings can make with their life, and after death, whoa bro, maybe that can
do some shit too, hence the whole heiress dying thing, it was kind of important.
But everyone's like, oh no, no, no, now, see, it's a new thing, it's a remake, right?
It's a totally different story.
The new story is about changing fate.
Okay, well, for a moment I could put on my philosopher's hat, fate literally doesn't
exist in the real life.
So what am I supposed to learn?
What exactly is the point of this story?
There is none.
I mean, point of the story aside, as long as they are actually changing the theme.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, because one theme is good, one theme is bad, changing fate,
he didn't fall in SE 13, it meant nothing, nothing happened.
The thing that's different though is that in the Gurren Lagann thing, the story is exactly
the same, they just saved people to make people happy.
Correct.
Even though like it diminishes some aspect of the tragedy, which is a good thing for
a story to have.
So that was annoying, but far less important than changing something like FF7's deaths,
which are integral to the point of the story.
Yeah, but that's my point, is that if they are actually changing the theme and the story,
then the deaths are not as important as before.
In theory, I see your point.
It's just that when you change it to a theme that I would argue is inherently vacuous and
has no narrative weight to it, or meaning, like this idea of changing fate means nothing.
It means nothing.
I don't know.
And the fact that the original game is cast as the bad ending, you see that fucking Red
13 clip?
Yeah.
What the fuck is that about?
I was gonna say that.
You know, I saw an interview with someone who was working on the remake, and he's like,
well, the original game ended with everyone in the whole world dying and there's no people
left.
That fucking kinkase that retarded dumbass motherfucker.
First of all, it was meant to be ambiguous, and second of all, it wasn't even that ambiguous
because you heard like the children laughing at the end or whatever.
So like it does imply that just Midgar has been abandoned and people are still living.
You know who I know?
I just would 100% know that nobody, the world was not wiped out.
It's because if humanity was wiped out by Holy, what the fuck did it matter that Eris
died and any of that should happen?
Why didn't just we let Sephiroth win if the livestream was just going to save everyone
anyway and humanity made no difference anyway?
They're like, of course everyone survived.
It would be literal bad ending of no narrative weight if everyone died.
Of course humanity wasn't wiped out by Holy.
That would be the most nihilistic interpretation possible about how life has no meaning.
And I refuse to believe that was the point of the story.
Just the attitude.
I mean like even them changing stuff and like having a new canon and kind of like a rebuild
sort of story from here on out, fine, whatever, you do you man, even that is fine.
But just the arrogant attitude, the audacity of saying, like basically directly saying
the old ending was bad, the old story was bad, the new one will be good.
Oh my god, I'm hearing people now saying, oh my god this made me want to fucking explode.
I heard people say the old end, straight up they said like fans are saying the old ending
let's be real guys, the old ending was pretty bad, it wasn't that good, we got to change
it up.
I didn't understand what happened, therefore it's bad.
How can you even try to- Literally, I'm hearing this.
How can you even try to bullshit people and say that the original ending was like objectively
the whole world, everyone died.
Did you forget your own fucking sequel where everyone was perfectly fine two years later?
I try to ignore the continuity of that but you know what another point I was thinking
about, you know how in the, it's said in Advent Children that like geostigma, like even putting
aside the fact that Advent Children in order to exist means that humans continue to live.
Okay, but what about geostigma, ooh the planet was mad at everybody, right?
That's why the planet infected everybody with geostigma, literally wrong.
It was literally just Genova cells polluting the life stream and at the end Eris and the
life stream come back to cure everyone because they're good and they're not bad and humanity
isn't evil and toxic.
The point of Final Fantasy 7 is not that humanity needs to die, that's like the attitude Barrett
had at the beginning that he grows out of over the course of the game.
Terrorism is not good, don't kill people for the greater good.
And it's also worth noting that a big part of that development for both Barrett and Tifa
is that Avalanche in its first incarnation in Midgar was a complete failure and got all
of Sector 7 killed.
That's kind of important, but now everyone in Sector 7 lives.
Who's gonna argue to me, Maximilian fucking dude, all you fucking people who think this
thing is like good writing, it's so obvious that it's just, they just want happy endings.
How can you not see that, have you not been paying attention to the stories these people
write?
There is no 10,000 degree chess going on here, how can you not see that?
Maybe it's because you are invited to every Square Enix developer meetup and they tell
you like wow, your fucking videos influence me so much, they motivate me to keep making
the game.
Maybe that's corrupted your view of the game a little bit, I don't know.
And it already had a happy ending without being schmaltzier stupid about it.
When they say that the ending was bad, it's not that the ending was like sad, it's just
that it wasn't overly schmaltzier, the ending was tasteful of Final Fantasy 7.
It was just like, you know, cloud like sort of like overcame his anxieties and overcame
his trauma and he beat Sephiroth in a battle of wills.
They saved the planet, Eris's little holy spell got to do its thing, the planet did
its thing and they go oh, will it kill us too?
Are we just as bad?
Who knows?
But then everyone, and you know, it's just, it's tasteful is my point.
It just goes to show you cannot trust people to formulate a fucking coherent thought based
on the narratives of a fucking story or they'll just fuck it up.
They'll just not understand what has been, what was the point of Final Fantasy 7, do
all this stuff so that everyone dies at the end?
Do you think that was the point of the story, boys and girls?
I'm telling you the answer's no.
The answer is no to that question.
I mean, yeah, didn't Sakaguchi say a long time ago that he made the game, the whole
concept of the story was his way of like dealing with grief because like his mother had died
or something and like, and like moving on, like the story is about moving on and like
it's about life, it's not about death and nihilism and the whole world.
You want to talk about moving on?
How about we bring back everybody that died?
How's that for moving on?
That's not what I like.
Man, that's not what I was going to do.
You did it.
Oh, I hate Zak.
He sucks.
Zak?
I want him to die.
Is the most...
I mean, I want him to die again.
Why is everyone into Zak?
I don't understand.
I'm sorry I'm yelling so much, everyone.
I just got a lot.
I mean, like, I know that he died to begin with, but I mean, I want the concept of Zak
to die and go away.
People just get attached to characters because why?
Because they're nice.
Why?
Because they were eight years old when Crisis Core came out.
And so to them, that's the end all be all of the series and that's good.
They think...
Can you believe that?
People tell me.
Crisis Core is good.
People tell me that like, you know, oh, you know, you like the original, oh, spin-offs
don't matter, man.
Like, what does spin-offs matter?
Like, why are you mad?
It's just a spin-off.
It's not like it's fucking with the original game, bro.
It's not like, look where we're at now.
Look who we have to deal with.
Because this virus has been allowed to spread.
This is Genova polluting the life stream of the public consciousness of this fucking
game and everyone's thinking wrong things because they weren't in the original because
Sakaguchi has left the fucking building.
I'm not even trying to say Sakaguchi was like an angel and everything good left with him.
It's just that the atmosphere that created the original is gone and we've got something
else.
And I don't like it.
It's a totally different company at this point internally.
Fuck, what was I just going to say?
Something about Zack's sucking.
Oh, yeah.
There was one part, Hojo, at one part of the game, he said the letter G. He said G and
I had an ulcer.
I coughed up blood.
He specifically said, oh, oh, these soldiers, they're G types, not S types.
Oh, yeah.
And I went, there was blood all over my, gacked his back, baby.
Oh, I gacked.
All right.
I fucking, did you, did you enjoy the scene?
Why, what the fuck is the, why would Hojo just say when he meets cloud, oh, I know you,
you literally weren't a soldier.
Oh, yeah.
And then the time Janney's carry him away after he says it.
Why not before?
It makes, if you're trying to preserve the timeline, makes no sense because like the,
the idea is that they come and they, they, they prevent people from changing Destiny's
course.
They, anytime that a character deviates from what already happened, it does something different.
The time janitors show up and stop it.
Okay.
How are they deviating in the first place then?
I've been wondering that.
Like the, the answer has to be either Sephiroth is doing something with time shenanigans.
That would, okay.
Okay.
Why did Hojo do something different?
Why did cloud try to kill Reno this time?
I have been lacking my fucking brain.
Look, we, people, people are going to ask for 10,000 IQ plays.
The answer is these people are terrible writers and they don't know what they're doing.
That's the answer to the question.
You can spend all day searching the stars for the fucking, what does it mean, bro?
What are the implications of this?
None of it's there.
There is no substance beneath any of this.
The answer is they don't know what they're doing and they're fucking everything up.
I love how they're supposed to like preserve the timeline as it was.
As if it's not going to significantly alter the timeline to have everyone in sector seven
see a giant swirling tornado of cloaked grim reapers around the bar.
Like that's not going to alter anyone's lives that they saw that shit.
Okay.
Like they, Barrett gets stabbed by Sephiroth, right?
And the time Jenny somehow brings him back or what?
Yeah.
You know, I almost thought for the briefest of moments, oh my God, they're doing something
different and interesting and unique.
And I can't believe this happening.
I'm actually surprised they're killing Barrett in the first game.
Oh my God.
I can't believe.
Oh, no, no, they're not.
And I don't want to hear you fucking people being all like, did you guys know that they
were originally going to kill Barrett and like the whole crew?
Yes.
I've read the interviews.
I know that they were planning to kill the entire rest of the cast, except Cloud and
then Nomura talked them out of it.
Do not quote the ancient knowledge to me.
I was there when it was written.
Yeah, indeed.
Indeed.
It's just the time Jannies, man.
They save Barrett, but isn't it kind of important to preserve the timeline that Cloud not know
that he's a soldier or that he was in fact not ever a soldier, but he just hears that
from Hojo.
Shouldn't like an appropriate correlate wouldn't be like, okay, Barrett dies and then the time
Jannies restore him.
Wouldn't an appropriate correlate be like Cloud hears he was never a soldier from Hojo,
which he does.
And then the time Jannies like go into his head and like remove that vital piece of lore.
Instead, Hojo just tells him and he goes, oh crap, oh, well, I'll just pretend I didn't
hear that.
It's treated like he doesn't even consider it or think about it, even though that's the
biggest reveal in the entire game at the, during the fucking Cloud's interest.
You know what?
I just, I don't understand why people think this is so good, I am so confused.
This entire third act of the game, I mean, you know, the one good thing about it could
have been that people who didn't get a chance to play it the first time could experience
the story.
If you didn't play Final Fantasy 7, you would have no fucking idea what is going on.
Sephiroth is not explained, Cloud's backstory is not explained, and the calm flashback is
the next thing that happens narratively, so they could have like somehow done it there
and put Sephiroth after that or something.
Yeah, you know, I almost, like I was thinking, the whole game I was thinking, oh, I bet I
know what they're going to do.
They're telling everyone it's just Midgar, but they're going to go a little bit farther
and go to calm so that we can do the flashback and that's where it'll end.
That would make sense.
But like I thought for sure, surely that is the thing that makes sense narratively for
the structure of this game, but no, they didn't even think of that.
In my video years ago, I asked, I think the important question, who is this for?
And I think I have the answer and I think it's basically that like Square Enix, they
think everyone in the world has played Final Fantasy 7 and not only that, but has memorized
every story beat.
So they feel they can't do it again.
They feel that like, they feel like watching the comparison of like Jaws or whatever.
Oh, watching Jaws again, it's not like the pacing and all the subtle hints of the shark's
body and whatever.
That doesn't matter.
The fact that you know there's a shark and you know every story beat means no one would
enjoy watching that again.
So you can't remake it or whatever the fuck.
They...
Who do you think Sephiroth is if you're a new player?
Like I can't wrap my head around like how baffled you must be.
He's a guy.
That's all I think.
Sephiroth is just this guy, you know?
He's just a guy and he's pretty, pretty badass I guess, but maybe he's gay?
I don't know.
He just seems gay.
He's definitely pretty gay.
I don't know when that happened, when that change occurred, but at some point he did
definitely catch the gay.
Sephiroth is just like sitting in the back of that truck in the column flashback with
Cloud just like doing squats and Cloud's like, oh, I can't wait to try my new materia.
And Sephiroth just says, doesn't I shall give you despair.
He just says, what a green rookie, look at this rookie over here.
He's just like a dude, man.
He's just like a soldier who fought in wars, which by the way is still going on.
Wutai is not a tourist town as famously sung by Jesse in the Shinobi rap.
It's in fact, you know, a powerhouse.
Oh god, why are they changing things like this?
Sick, sick, deep cut.
That matters for Yuffie's backstory.
Yeah, exactly.
They should have just used my Shinobi rap as the template for this story because I told
them what to do and how to do it.
You know, I was very scared when they did the angel of the slum side missions.
I was sure that it was going to be Yuffie and I was like, oh no, what are you doing?
Thankfully it wasn't.
That was the one thing where they showed restraint.
They have that one girl who is like literally Yuffie basically, but she is, I looked it
up.
Not read the spin-off novel, whatever the fuck it is.
She's from a novel, boys.
So remember that guy working for Don Corneo, Leslie, he's also from the novel.
You know, he was like the one new character that I didn't hate completely.
I didn't hate him at first, but then the side mission just kind of dragged with him and
I was like, I get it, obviously this happened to you.
So obviously terrible anime writing.
But then he got to the part where he like stupidly monologued instead of shooting Corneo
and totally got fucked like an idiot.
I did like seeing Corneo cuck that guy and I was like, oh, Corneo actually did something
cool.
Yeah, good work.
I like that.
This is how he became a mob boss in the first place or whatever.
Yeah, so yeah, if you're a new player and you beat the game and you see this guy with
black hair and he's like walking past Eris and is doing all this like melodramatic sad
shit with this guy that you've never seen before.
You have no context for who this is whatsoever.
Like what are you thinking?
Like they think everyone knows who all these characters, they put themselves like, man,
you want to talk about like, you know, you know, if you're, Tom, you can relate to this.
In the past, when I've been making like games and I personally have designed games as a developer,
you spend like tens, hundreds of fucking hours, thousands of hours like working on like level
design and things.
There are puzzles, for example, that you implement into a game that you can solve because first
of all, you know things about how the game is designed and even more than that, you have
developed skills far beyond what like an average player might have.
It's like Square Enix is approaching this game design thinking like, like from within
that box, like, oh, everyone knows every aspect of this game and like every beat of the story.
Even though you think how many people love replaying Final Fantasy 7 once in a while
to just be like, oh my God, I forgot how good the atmosphere was here.
I forgot how good the like, you know, Reno's appearance was here and like the Midgar's
Alarm scene and the fucking, I don't know, meaning sang in the Mithril Caves and everything
about Rocket Town, you forget these little details, but they just assume you have everything
in your fucking brain and there's no point in being coy about any detail, even when it
was like the point of the narrative, the way you like subtly present Sephiroth throughout
the game, because spoilers, it's not even Sephiroth until the end of the fucking game
in Northern Crater.
Why did they make the motorcycle chase not fun this time?
I don't know, why did they make it bad?
I'm not going to lie, like I always love the original, you know, it was kind of hard.
I mean, I like the original, I just had a fun arcadey simplicity to it and now there's
a boss battle involved where you got to hit the guy's tires.
I did not like that boss battle.
That was one of the like, the two times I died in the game against that boss the first
time.
Yeah, I guess we'll give everyone else in the show a chance to talk now.
I guess we've...
Sorry guys.
One more thing.
It's cool that we just did Final Fantasy VII podcast remake.
We've remade the podcast about Final Fantasy VII.
Yeah, well, I had to redeem myself for erroneously calling it phenomenal the last time I was
on, because I was only five hours into the game then, and like immediately after that
point it fucking spiraled down into oblivion, into the exact same hell I knew it would,
but I was briefly lulled into complacency when I saw the graphics, I guess, and I was
like, ooh, this is nice though, I kind of like it, oh what a fool I was to have been positive
even slightly.
When I listen...
No, I don't care.
You know, the Genova fight, which by the way wasn't the original or whatever, who fucking
cares, there's a new Genova fight in Shinra HQ, we are also transformed into like a dream
dimension, okay, whatever, that's fine.
I mean, the Genova theme that plays there and like the phase that goes through and that
whole boss fight was kind of like my favorite part of the whole game, like you're playing
a video game, it's not like a cutscene, of course.
They do cuck you by doing the phase transitions where you lose your stagger bar and you have
to restart, so that's always fucking...
Oh yeah, the whole entire combat system is bad and sucks, let's talk about that now
for the next fucking hour.
It's the worst.
Once I got into the rhythm, I enjoy it, I do like it.
I kind of the same way I enjoy Final Fantasy XIII, it's very similar to Final Fantasy XIII.
It works really well when you're just fighting regular enemies, but like every boss battle
has some weird gimmick or some other stupid thing you've got to keep track of and also
the bosses are too large so the camera doesn't know what to do and the AI for your companions
is like the worst I've ever seen in a video game, I can't believe that this is in Final
Fantasy VII.
I mean, I guess that's kind of the idea to micromanage your party, but like, it's annoying
and dumb.
It's uncomfortable mixing though.
And Final Fantasy XII, which came out like 15 years ago, had the gambit system and it
worked beautifully, you could make sure that you knew exactly what your AI companions were
doing at all times.
Why didn't Square make that system?
Why didn't they just bring it over here?
The first thing I did once I figured out how the controls work, I know you have command
shortcuts, you can hold like, it's like Kingdom Art style, you can map moves.
The shortcuts are helpful.
The first thing I did once I figured that out was like, oh, I hate going into the menu,
thank God they put a system where I have to spend as little time in the menu as possible
because it's a really uncomfortable mix of having to stop things every two seconds to
choose the command or whatever.
I didn't mind the menus too much because I liked being able to just pause and pick targets,
especially when you're fighting multiple guys to make sure your hit goes to exactly who
you want it to go to.
So that was okay because it was kind of like the power wheel in Mass Effect or something.
You slow things down, you can tactically choose targets and stuff.
It was kind of similar to that.
I just don't understand why they even bothered with any of the real-time elements at all
because it was so not substantial in any way, shape, or form, you know?
We talked about the dodge.
The dodge is a true nightmare.
It's so bad.
I did a vlog on this game and I don't even know if I'm going to release it because I
just shit on the game and I just don't want to pile on with everybody else.
But it's like, the combat lacks the kind of like frenetic, reflexive nature or something
like Devil May Cry, but it also-
By the way, Tom, if you need permission, I give you my seal of approval.
I'm sure you do.
There is too much positivity about this game going on.
They need sober cold water.
Okay, I'm sorry.
But it lacks that kind of reflexive nature of something like a DMC, like a traditional
action game, but it also lacks the intentional tactility of something like a Souls game.
It's just like-
Nice term, bro.
It's just a turn-based RPG with tacked on movement because they were just like, people
these days are not going to be able to watch a bar fill up, so we got to make them actively
fill the bar.
And that's all it is.
It's so slow.
The ATB is so slow and the enemies have way too much hit points.
And the fucking, God, the barrier is broken in this.
It's totally so obnoxious and annoying because barrier like halves your physical attacks
and that's fine.
And in the old system, that was fine.
It wasn't too annoying, you know?
But in this one, anytime like an enemy is blocking or has a barrier, you have that feeling
of like your sword clunking off of them and like stopping you dead in your tracks.
It's so irritating.
That's the word.
Infuriating.
Did you guys-
Against the house.
Against the fucking house.
That happened constantly.
Yeah.
That was horrible.
You just, I don't, I didn't die against the house actually like was able to beat it,
but it was just like annoying and slow.
And it's just like, if it was just doing half damage and I was still attacking, like that
would be one thing, but it just completely ruins the flow that they're trying to build.
Another thing that's really annoying-
Can't build ATB either.
With the boss fights, like some of them have like certain like attackable weak points,
like the mechs and stuff, you can like blow off their arms and shit like that.
But like, it doesn't work because the attacks are so clunky, you'll try and hit an arm,
but you'll just end up hitting the body.
Like even in the first boss battle, where you have to attack the shield generator, like
half the time you're not even hitting it because like it's such a tiny target buried in the
back of the boss and you'll just end up hitting the body.
And because you have no control over the camera with the way it's set up too, it makes it
really hard to get in the right position.
The worst thing is that there are no iframes for anything, how many times have you like
lost your limit break because you get hit by something from off screen while you're
charging up your limit break?
How do you fuck that up?
That's 101!
How do you charge up my iframes?
What is the point of a Dark Souls dodge roll without the Dark Souls invincibility frames,
which is the whole point of the dodge roll in the first place.
It doesn't fucking function as a dodge roll.
It's just for basic repositioning for charge ups on boss attacks.
And it's just, it doesn't, it's so fucking shit.
Just because like the actual like sensation when you connect with something, when like
you do a braver and it connects, it feels fucking awesome.
When you do the triangle shot with Barrett and that final charge hit, it feels amazing.
Just make it be turn based so I can have this catharsis hits that works every time.
It takes so long to build up the ATP gauge and then you go to do something and it gets
interrupted and you go right back to square one and you have to do it all over again.
You know what is my, I think I'm probably the most positive of any of us about the
battle system because I do like it in many ways, but I obviously have many grievances.
And my number one, the most annoying thing is that when battle ends, your limit gauge
gets reset.
I must have played through the majority of the game using my limit break like three times
and only with cloud because you just don't get a fucking chance to build it up in a fucking
battle before.
Oh god.
I'm sorry.
The more I just can't stop talking about all the bad things, why, why, why, okay.
Why does the right stick control the camera and the lock on?
Yeah, it's unfortunate.
Locking on does not feel like it even works half the time and then you're constantly switching
when you don't mean to because you're trying to get the camera back where it goes.
There's issues.
Fuck it.
You know what the thing is, this idea that like an action combat system is like inherently
better and more tactile or whatever than the old turn based system, like the old turn
based system in Final Fantasy 7 felt snappier and more responsive and quicker than this
limp-wristed like half and half abomination that is like sitting in the middle between
turn based and real time, you know what I'm saying here?
Yeah, I was flipping shit on Twitter when I first started playing the same because I
just thought the combat was so bad and everyone was like, oh no, it's fucking good.
I just knew it's different.
They're going to try and experiment with shit.
I'm just like, but look, you put a dodge in the game, but everybody in the beginning
of the game has guns and they follow you when you dodge roll.
So there is no way to dodge the bullets that everyone is shooting at you in the beginning
of the game.
So the dodge is fucking useless.
How about instead of a useless dodge that doesn't work, how about instead of that you
have a fucking jump button so it's not infuriatingly annoying to fight any flying enemy in the game.
That's not good.
Flying enemies.
It's so bad.
Give me death.
Yeah, you have to switch the barret for that.
You just, there's no.
Yeah, you have to.
You have to.
When it comes to the, when it comes to the dodge, by the way, look, I could accept no
iframes, but what you just need to do is not give me a full like two second cooldown and
give me a bit more fucking distance on the dodge because they're so short and so much
cooler when you dodge.
The dodge is useless in the first boss fight when it does that charge up like electricity
AOE thing and you're like, oh, I got a dodge out of here.
You can't dodge far enough to avoid it so you get hit every fucking time.
It's just so badly designed and I don't like it and it's dumb and gay and shit and fuck.
You know, I've had a lot of fun with like side missions doing battles, but like the side
mission battles are okay because it works when you fight like mobs and ads and like regular
just enemies because you can like the damage output on your normal attacks is basically
nothing compared to, you know, the ATB attacks and yeah, but, but that small amount of damage
is enough to cut through like normal guys running around like on side quests and stuff.
You can play it essentially like an action game and when you're fighting melee guys
physically getting out of the way with the dodge role allows you to dodge attacks.
But anytime there's projectiles involved, you can't dodge them.
They're taking hits, especially with bosses firing like multiple missiles at the same time.
Our arena just turns into a death trap.
I guess.
Yeah.
I think all you do is block.
I don't know.
But the regular attacks once you're fighting bosses or like even like more of the stronger
enemies are essentially useless because like they have like 20 or 30,000 HP and it's like,
oh, I'm hitting them for 15.
Awesome.
Like it's just to fill the ATV gauge and it's just dumb and it's wasting my time.
It's about the stag bar.
Just be turn-based.
It'll be...
I don't know.
You know, that whole boss fight with the house, I know that everyone thinks it's so cool that
the house is back and everyone is praising that fight.
You know, I hate to give Super Eye Patch Wolf credit because I am deeply jealous of his
meteoric success, but he brought up a great point in his Final Fantasy 7 video a couple
months ago where he sort of went into the house and how it's kind of a really cool design
that in the slums where everyone is like poverty-ridden and has no homes, that like a monster would
evolve to look like a house, to lure homeless people in, like that's the idea of the house.
And like that is clearly the idea that they were going for.
It is a monster that camouflages itself as a house to eat homeless people.
That is...
It goes with the themes of the game.
The themes of the game are like poverty and class and all that.
It's not that anymore.
It's just a robot monster that Corneo keeps in his stadium for some reason.
That's dumb.
That's not good anymore.
Also...
Okay, that's the interesting you bring that up because as someone who didn't play the
original, I'm like, why would you make a robot house?
It made no fucking sense to me.
They put it in that part for fanservice without thinking of why he was in the original game
and where he belonged in the game in the first place.
How about that part where you're for fucking Hojo just stops the entire game and makes
you switch parties like 50 times for like 4 hours, flipping switches, having to switch
the materia back and forth every single time you switch?
Oh yeah.
As soon as I realized that I was like, I need 4 of every materia immediately so I never
need to switch with anyone.
Yeah.
That's life.
But man, it's really fucking cool when you use it.
And you hit three guys.
Oh man, it feels so fucking good.
Triple slash is so cool.
Triple slash is so fun.
I love it.
Yeah, that's the best part of the game.
It's triple slash.
It's the part I like about it.
Every time I use triple slash, I'm like, maybe I'll play it a little bit more.
Yeah.
Triple slash is pretty good.
I like Counter Strike.
Oh my god.
All of Tifa's moves are so cool.
It's so fun to play as Tifa.
You know what they didn't mention?
And I found out on the forums, or on a forum looking it up, you know how you switch to
Punisher mode with cloud and you hold down block and you'll counter?
Did you know?
Yeah.
Wait, is that true?
I didn't know that.
It automatically counters by holding down, you hold down guard.
He'll automatically do a counter.
What?
But someone said in the forums, and I mentioned it on Twitter and nobody knew.
If you tap triangle right when an attack hits you, you counter even in operator mode.
What?
I heard somebody say that.
I saw some, like, let's play or doing that.
This is not explained anywhere.
Yeah.
And I'm like, oh, there's a little bit of depth here.
There's a little bit of depth now.
If you time your things right, you can just counter everything with cloud and that's fucking
cool.
Well, you're not going to counter all those fucking rockets that the fucking house launches
at you or anything.
Fuck that.
Yeah.
I don't know.
All right, I have one more thing to say and then I'll be done.
Okay.
So you know that Sephiroth theme that goes like, those chosen by the planet, I believe?
Yes.
So right at the end of the game where you're in that little threshold and Sephiroth says,
hey, cloud, if you go through here, it's the end of the game and we'll have a final
boss fight.
Yeah.
So go to the vending machine and shop first, buddy.
I'm Sephiroth and I'm evil.
Go shop at the vending machine, buddy.
This is a video game and none of it matters.
Yeah.
That part where you're waiting at the threshold and it's playing that music.
You know, I didn't want to go into it right away.
I was kind of hungry.
I was kind of peckish.
I went out into the kitchen and there was some leftover asparagus from Dindin.
And so I just started eating asparagus and I just started shoveling this asparagus in
my face and just going mad with power, just ripping into this asparagus.
And in the background, the song was playing and I'm eating this asparagus like a dinosaur.
And then I just start going and I think you'd appreciate this, Nate.
I just started going, eat your greens.
Eat your greens.
All right.
I'm done.
I'm finished.
Yeah.
All right.
That's all.
I'm finished.
I'm done.
You're done.
I don't want to go to him at all.
Wait.
What?
No.
They can't just be the Final Fantasy fan cafe.
Why not?
It could.
I mean, what else?
Does anything else interesting happened?
No.
Oh, I hate Factorio.
It's too mean to me.
Factorio is not even a real game.
I don't even believe it.
What happens to him?
Yeah, that in the world, Kim Jong-un is probably dead at LeMell.
That school...
Oh, yeah.
And we could all worship his yes, queen and sister.
Yeah.
We can finally start simping for North Korea.
Ooh, yeah, at last.
Pretty sick.
Yeah, pretty good.
Yeah, you're right.
There's nothing.
This is going to Christmas.
All right, fuck it.
I got them right here, boys.
We've only got three.
We have a lowly three.
Wait, we're really doing it?
That's really it?
I'm fine with this though.
I got no objections.
I thought for sure.
Well, Ben, clean, baby.
Do you have nothing to say?
What the fuck do I have to say?
No, I don't have anything to say.
I just, I hate my life, and I hate quarantine, and I'm really depressed, and everything sucks.
I agree with all that, yeah.
And here I am, and I'm on the show.
Why not play a beautiful new remake of your favorite game, Ben?
And I come on the show, and then I hear all about this Final Fantasy VII remake bullshit,
and you think that's doing anything for me?
No, dude.
But no.
I'm sorry, bro.
I don't want to spread misery.
I do not want to do that.
Well, how's your animal crossing?
Fine.
I got more roses.
Yeah.
Hey, play the fucking jingle, I guess.
Show my rose garden.
I got like 25.
I don't think we got a jingle yet.
Pretty cool.
Did anyone make a jingle?
Were there no voicemails that were someone submitting a fucking rose jingle?
Ugh.
I don't think so, guys.
Okay, but we need to come up with topics that make Ben feel less sad.
We got a brainstorm.
We got to cheer up Ben.
Wow.
Yeah, it's got to, you got to, you got to eat or me.
It's like that episode, yeah.
Yeah, you are going to stick it too.
You got to stuff honey in my mouth, and tie balloons to all my limbs, and I don't know.
Well, so they do fucking like, shoot him.
I don't remember.
Shoot him with a gun.
Put him down.
Yeah.
He can't be sad if he's dead.
Ugh, it's true.
Oh, we're all going to die, guys.
We're all going to die.
It won't even be long.
Yeah, but Final Fantasy 7 teaches us that we can have meaning in the real world even
afterwards.
No, once we're gone, that's it.
You don't remember anything that happened and none of it matters.
But the remake teaches us you won't actually die.
Yeah.
No, it's not real.
You definitely really just die, and then there's nothing.
Cool.
Well, then what was the point of the remake?
What's the remake trying to tell you?
Well, I guess what's the point of life at all?
Maybe nihilism is correct, so maybe the remake is correct.
Oh, no.
It's way more accurate.
Yeah, you know what?
I guess I stand the remake now, because that's what it's like.
It's way more relevant to my real life experience.
Nothing means anything.
Consume, consume, consume.
Don't ask questions, just consume.
You know, at least it's on.
At least it's on.
No, it's not on.
It's to call itself a remake, and it tells me shit on me.
They're remaking the plot note as well.
That's all.
Do you guys put any credence in?
Okay, let's say.
Okay, no more.
Oh, God, I brought it back.
Oh, fuck.
All right, damn it.
I just think this is an epic meme.
No, it's not epic.
It's not epic.
It's not a meme.
It's not funny.
You need to die.
You need to die, mate.
I'm Japanese.
I can use English words, and they mean whatever I want them to me, because I'm not English.
Is this a legitimate legal defense with this pass and a court of law?
Yes.
Oh, it was actually Final Fantasy VII, Lee Make, not Remake.
No, it was actually Final Fantasy V, Remake.
Like those were not neuromanumeral.
It's Lee Make, not only because they can't pronounce R's, but because they give him some
Lee Way in the remake.
It's Final Fantasy VII, Remake.
It sure is.
It is to me.
That's the title of this episode.
Speaking of...
Yeah, that makes sense.
Hey, look at this.
I commissioned Kazi to draw my slime girl from Radiforce's Cop Killers.
That's pretty cool.
Not bad.
I like it.
I'll just be distracted by it.
I posted it in the chat.
Oh, fuck, what's her name?
I should remember.
It's Katie.
Katie, right.
Yeah, just some normal name for a slime girl.
I wanted that to be the thing, is that she's a freak.
Pretty aesthetic.
But she's a person.
You know, actually, Jesse, how do you feel about this?
I learned a tragic...
No, you're not talking about Final Fantasy VII.
No, you know what?
I'm trying to distract you.
Just go ahead, honestly.
There's no better week for me to have you guys just go.
I don't want to...
You don't want to hear from me.
Sure.
Better this way.
Agreed.
It's just that I was playing the original Final Fantasy VII a little bit, and I realized,
I was like, oh, look, they've got mouths.
This must be because of, you know, like, more polys, more fucking pixels on the screen.
Everything else is, like, sharp and nice, because I'm playing on, like, the PC rear-release.
Which, and by the way, I patched in the correct OG music.
It has terrible music.
You have to fix it, but I did that.
But now they've got...
I was like, wait, what?
They've got mouths?
Wait, was those not in the original?
And I looked it up, and they...
You talk about a hack remake in the true original.
The models did not have mouths.
In the horrible PC re-releases, they have mouths on the models.
And talk about disrespecting...
Well, I think we've been shitting on the wrong remake this whole time.
Yeah, that's right.
That's my point.
The mouths.
Just a note to Eleazar.
You guys may not have heard, but I was doodling on my guitar in the background.
Oh, I heard.
It was great.
I would like Eleazar, could you please max gain reverb so nobody can hear anything?
I wasn't even playing well, so it would be bad if people heard what I was doing.
But please do that anyway.
Side note, this is not about the game specifically.
Jess, do you know this guy, 4-8 Productions, who makes all these crazy...
He makes like the in-depth character material.
I think so, yeah.
Yeah, it's just that that guy...
Oh God, wait, I had a point.
But I completely forgot what my point was.
He's cool.
Yeah, he's not a bad boy.
I mean, that guy's a deep level boy.
He just released a mod that he and his community or whatever made for the original Final Fantasy VII that I maybe will play.
It seemed pretty cool.
Anyway, I totally forget the point of bringing that guy up, but anyway, shout out to that guy.
He's cool and I like what he does.
And if you like the remake, I will come to your house.
And it just won't be a pretty say, it's all there is to it.
Alright, I have one thing to talk about.
It might not last for too long, but that's whatever.
Neither do I, while having sex.
Oh yeah.
There's a guy I follow.
He makes a marble machine.
He's called Martin.
It's called the Marble Machine X and I was watching his latest video.
Is that the musical instrument?
He's got an extremely popular video of him playing the Marble Machine X, Marble Machine song with like a prototype.
And he's been spending the last three years or so building the next one, which is like more like stronger and powerful and can do more things.
It's very, very good YouTube series.
Probably my favorite thing on the site.
But the point is he has a latest video.
He talks about this idea of dopamine detoxing as a way to focus, which I have put into practice the last few days.
It's been very helpful for people like me who are dumb and stupid and do not work when I need and want to.
Tell me more.
The basic premise is that notifications like little plus ones, little comments, little anything is a rush.
It's very addictive as it's social media is designed to be that way.
And all sorts of things in life are addictive by nature.
You want to do them so that they can sell them to you again.
And that's, you know, it's bad for you generally to get so used to having a high level of dopamine in your system.
The idea he had was in order to focus, he needed to detox this dopamine out of his system so that he wouldn't go back.
So he would be more able to resist the urge and the temptation to like put on a podcast while he's working and distract himself and be slower while he's doing things.
Because some people, they put on podcasts.
I mean, I know I used to do this before I switched to music, but music is still kind of a bad thing where you can't do anything unless you have somebody's voice in the room being on a podcast saying things that you can't work.
It's impossible.
And it's not generally a good place to be in because you're going to run out of podcasts.
There's so many of them and not all of them are going to be the best thing.
But it's also just sort of a hassle that you could live without.
And I've been trying to work completely in silence with no YouTube, no Discord, no nothing.
Because I've done sort of half measures before.
I've like got rid of YouTube and Twitter and stuff and it sort of helps.
But I still feel this urge to be distracted by things.
And so I think the the idea is like on a long term plan basis is to at least while I'm trying to get this fucking Lord of Ghost comic finished is to
deprive myself of stuff for a long period as possible so that I can be used to being bored in a sense to you being used and able to live comfortably without needing to be looking at a media.
And it was pretty effective the last few days before the weekend started where I got like three whole pages done per day as opposed to the zero I have done in the last and since Radcon four ended I've done zero.
So in the last two days I've done three per day and that's pretty fucking good.
That's yeah, that's good.
Minimize distraction always seems like the right way to go.
And yeah, yeah, sounds like you're getting results.
Have you disabled notifications on your phone yet?
I did that like last year and it's very effective.
The only notifications I have active on my phone are text messages and phone calls, aka things I would actually care about.
I mean, I turned off notifications as soon as I installed any apps because I didn't like the beep happening and then be looking and it'd be like the sort of thing I would see on desktop and just do a click.
But with a phone you have to pick it up off the whatever surface is on and then sometimes you have to, you know, press the pin just to see that.
Oh, nothing is happening at all and I didn't need to pick up my phone.
So I've already had that completely turned off but I have now on my phone.
I talked about it before this app called app block, which I can set to limit my ability to use any like apps I desire for a certain amount of maximum time per day.
So I have a thing called, I don't know what it's called, it's just like a group.
It's got all of the possible things including like browsers so that I can't look things up and it just disables them after one and a half hours of use per day.
So I got one and a half hours and it's usually when I'm waking up and I just need something in my front of my face to like a shine a light at me so I can see it like.
But after that it's gone and I can't use my phone basically.
It's a very expensive paperweight.
I would do that except I have to be ready for when Gamergate 2 starts and I'm called to drop the bombs so I really can't detach from my social media presence.
It's not so much detaching from social media.
I definitely still post on Twitter and stuff.
You've seen those.
I definitely am going to be involved in Gamergate 2 guys.
Don't worry about that.
I'll make the time.
I've got a pager for that.
Okay.
That's right.
An exclusive dedicated device for Gamergate 2's beginning.
Yeah.
I just press the button to respond and it makes terrible things happen.
It's like it's like in the end of like Avengers where where the fucking Captain Marvel beeper goes off.
That's going to be.
Oh yeah.
The beeper only has one button and what that button does is send sexual harassment to girl gamers.
That's what it does.
It's the sole purpose of the device.
It's great.
It's just send harassing tweets to Zoe.
What is it?
Go home gamer girl.
It just posts that clip from that episode.
Epic.
The point though is that you can you can maintain a social media presence while blocking everything.
It's just you need to have you need to have like the dedicated time to do it and then you know get away as soon as possible.
Discipline man.
Smart.
So many likes and retweets.
Reminds me of those.
Those are those are my big money maker even though I get no money from them.
People like those four commas.
That's that's what everybody's about.
They like those four panel easily shareable comments.
I like them.
I always like them when I see them.
Yeah.
They're a treat.
You should pay wall.
Huh?
You cut out.
I throw up that pay wall.
The big red pay wall.
Oh I've already got a pay.
I got that pay wall for that fucking punk only fans which more people have joined since I posted the last one.
It's really funny.
That's excellent.
You have a bunch of people in my discord saying Izumi needs an only fans.
Oh lord.
You started something.
Our daughters are going to be whores of engine.
Is there like actually content on it?
There are two images that basically two sides of a ducky macro that I drew for fun.
Okay.
How can I engage with every person individually online and decide which specific content I want to pay wall from this specific person?
That's what I want.
I want pure adaptability.
I want to know when I've met a real cash cow and exactly how he'll be willing to give me if I can just squeeze it out of him.
But make sure that other people who I know I can't get any money from, I know that they can have everything for free because it's all good in the hood.
That would be the ideal consumer setup for me.
Alas, I lack the will or the power or the cowardice.
Anyway, onlyfans.com slash punk911, that's the URL.
Excellent, excellent.
Incredible.
Punk911 through 910 would take it, I assume.
Is it 911 or 9-11?
911.
Just making sure.
Because punk911 is a whole other thing.
Don't even worry about it.
Don't give that person their money.
I want to make my only fan that's punk711.
It's just punk hanging out of 7-11.
Just getting a drink.
Getting a burger.
What would she drink?
Probably not liquid because I would put her out.
Put her out and she'd die instantly.
Oil, yeah.
Oil.
Petrol, fucking explosive liquid.
Nitroglycer.
Picks up a bottle of fucking olive oil.
That's an energy drink.
Yes, excellent.
Well, voicemails?
I got them.
I got the voicemails.
We could do them.
We could not.
All right, I got them.
I got it right here.
Endless War, pin kick starter, still going.
Link in the description.
Still going?
Are we cool?
Are we more?
It will be going.
It will be going until not the Friday you're listening to this, but the Friday after that
and it will end at like, I think like 8 p.m. that Friday and we'll stream like end of
the campaign on Rowdy Fricker's Cop Killers.
Those end of campaign streams seem to be where it's at.
I mean, it works pretty well for the frickin' the other Radcon.
It sure did.
I'm gonna just do it again.
Are there new pins to tantalize me bad?
Do we have more pins?
Yeah, I think since the last time you may have checked, yes.
There's a bunch.
I mean, there's a bunch that have been like funded but have not been chosen yet, so there's
like more coming.
The Coatron is there.
Yeah, Cop Killers, Rowdy Frickers, Smyrg's Negus Slime Ghost, The Challenge Coin, Slime
Corp.
Another one by Smyrgan Labunguspe.
I don't know how to say that.
Oh, God.
Is that one of the girl on the treadmill?
Is that a reference to that thing?
You guys know what I'm talking about.
That laser set where the little girl gets all lasered and it's very graphic.
Is that what that is?
I don't know what the fun girl is talking about.
That's Goo Girls Limited in the style of the Portal 2 thing.
Portal 2?
Remember that?
No, great.
The little paper cut out people.
Is that like a remake of Portal 1 or something?
Yeah, that's right.
God, I hope so.
They have those little animations on the wall with the paper cut out people at a 45 degree
angle, like an isometric view.
Okay.
I don't know.
The point is it's the Goo Girls Limited logo.
Yeah.
I see Pizza Chan.
Pizza Chan is cemented here.
Pizza Chan.
Excellent.
The Podron.
An iron-on New Los Angeles City flag patch that one might wear on their arm, for instance.
Indeed.
Good shit.
I'm going to iron it onto my forehead.
There's a lot of really good shit here.
I'm going to have huge bags of all this hanging out.
There's going to be overflow.
I'm going to have hundreds of like, no matter what I do.
We're going to have hundreds and hundreds of like, undelivered-
When the kids come around for Halloween next year, you'll fill their bowls with-
Stick your hand in this bag and they'll stick it in and they'll get stabbed by the pins.
As they deserve.
Sounds about.
Okay, we can make this work.
But yes, so that's what's up.
A lot of fucking cool shit up for grabs right now.
Link in the description.
Had to mention it.
Can't let a week go by.
Go pledge for pins, everybody, if you want them.
And I certainly do.
You know, I forgot to pledge, but I should do it today because I know I want them and
I got to do that.
I mean, as more become available, I'm hoping that people will just up their pledges.
They're like, oh, I want that one too.
I want that one too.
And I mean, they get cheaper as you get more.
At like 50, they're just like five bucks a piece, which is like-
Oh, and you know what?
Now, actually, I'm glad you mentioned this.
Now is an excellent time to mention also that so on the Radcon 4 kickstart, you may have heard of.
Now, by the time you're hearing this, it'll be Friday the 1st.
So technically a day passed, the guarantee.
But I think we might have a little wiggle room potentially.
If anybody out there backed the Radcon 4 kickstarter and got physical rewards and has not yet submitted their fucking shit to the kickstarter,
do it now and you might get in under the wire.
We'll see.
If not, you might be fucked, but do your best.
Do your best.
I think most people are in.
I think there might be a couple of straggles as well.
So you will literally not get the stuff you earned if you just don't respond to that.
Yeah, we have to know where to send it.
Or else we just can't do it.
We won't even make it, because we're only going to make as many as we know where to send.
Right, because we're going to have to place an order soon.
That's right.
Who knows how long it's going to fucking take to get here.
So there you go, ladies and gentlemen.
The virus.
Your fate is in your hands.
Act quickly and decisively.
All right.
With that being said, I'm glad somebody mentioned that.
I was reminded of that.
I wanted to say that.
All right.
Well, anyway, let's do voicemails.
We got voicemails here.
There's only three.
A mere pittance.
Wow.
But they are selectively chosen.
Lot of shit this week, boys.
Lot of shit to wade through.
But I have chosen the ones that made me feel anything at all.
Very good.
So here they are.
That's good.
I like that.
Indeed.
And that still may not be a high bar, but it's something as opposed to nothing.
And of course, the link to leave them is the speak pipe link down in the description.
Click that and go ahead and leave some message.
All right.
Make it good, though.
Don't fuck around.
All right.
Here's the first one.
This is from Joe Pesci.
Joe Pesci has left us a voicemail.
Let's hear it.
Take it away, Joe.
Hey, bro.
Great.
This is Joe Pesci.
Hey, listen.
My question is, why don't, why come the bread galling out like Serena?
I fucking, that's my question.
If you don't have an attitude, I'll come down and I'll fucking bust your balls.
I have a good night.
Thanks, Joe.
Well, straight to the point.
Straight to the point, Joe.
Well, short answer.
We are in the works with a lot of political negotiation going on.
A lot of red tape we got to cut through.
I can guarantee you, though, it is coming.
It is coming.
It's in the works.
Won't be too long.
But I think before that, you'll probably hear a certain song about Brad.
So it won't come before the song.
So we'll see when that happens.
All right.
That's it, Joe.
Thank you for your no more contribution.
No more emails from that.
No more emails from that guy.
Okay.
Agreed.
He scares me.
I fear he's going to bust her balls.
All right.
Next up, we've got, oh, this is a simply titled Digi Bro interview.
Let's hear how it goes.
So Digi Bro, thank you so much for coming to this interview.
I'd like to ask a few questions about what's your inspiration?
You know, what gives you the drive to live?
If I want to live, I have to go find things to kill.
I have time to think about that now because I'm killing so much more efficiently.
I see.
So now that you have time to think about these things, is there a sort of revelation
that you've had with your identity?
I mean, like, what type of person would you call yourself?
I'm a caveman.
I have to hunt to eat.
Interesting.
So would you say there was a point in time where you first had this revelation?
Like describe the moment that you realized this.
What was going on then?
So I grab a rock.
I beat this board of death.
I'm like sick.
Ah, yes.
Now that's what I'm sure we can all relate to.
But I'm really wondering your anime YouTube channel was going pretty well.
This seems like a big shift in priorities.
Can you detail some of the thought process that has gone into that change?
Okay.
This worked out so well.
What other fucking rocks?
What other kind of fucking sticks have I thought of?
So let's fucking go kill some boars.
It's better than ever.
Well, you heard it here, folks.
That's all the time I'll have.
Thank you so much for stopping by, did you, bro?
It was a pleasure speaking with you.
That's literally what I hear from both sides.
Fine.
Next.
All right.
That was less funny listening back to it than I remember it being.
Well, thank you for your contribution.
Excellent interview.
I could hear the editing clips, so I know you put effort into that.
Well done.
All right.
Next one is our final voicemails from Ajax.
Ajax, go.
Oh, yeah.
It's about to get real, because it's me, your worst enemy, formerly known as H4Hotboy,
but is now Ajax the Invincible Overlord, the Chad with the most bad, the Deer with the
most milk cure, and after our battle with Terminal 7 clown aides, I've transformed,
changed form into my prime dad, Formation Alpha, and ever regularly begun wearing a belt
to everyday events.
But I'm not here just to be a survivor or a father figure that you've always wanted.
I'm here to declare that I'm the most linear and lexical of anyone in the PCP.
Now, that you impressionist lateral fucks don't know the first thing about a woman and
certainly don't deserve the affection of your crush or your anime waifu.
So that's why I'm not here just to red pill you, because we're beyond that.
I'm here to gold pill you, so you'll be as based in that because of me, because when
I was a grown ass man in the 6th grade, I read a graphic novel called Panhemonium, and
my head was spinning with all the messages of responsibility and loving your fellow
man, that I forgot everything but the main characters, cute, goth twink ass, and the
wacky line on the last page, brush your hair, comb your shirt and iron your teeth, wrang
through my head, and after a vision quest where I was sitting on a sinking ship, I had
to find it again, and only by googling demon twink graphic novel, young adult did I find
it after 45 minutes with the safe search turned on.
It can be done, you can live the dream and be nearly as cool as me, you just have to believe.
And for you, Nate, my worst enemy of all, watch out at the gym where I'll be going
monkey mode so hard your girl will file a divorce to marry someone who's cooler than you,
but not as cool as me, because marriage is wack, but not as wack as premarital sex.
Great, is that it?
Thank you, that's it, that's it.
No more voicemails ever.
Thank you, Ajax, for your contribution to this show.
We'll never forget you.
Alright, that's it, leave your stellar voicemails in this vein exactly at the speak pipe link
down below.
I'm sorry, I don't put you in just to roast you, it just sounded funnier when I was listening
to it before.
And your sleep deprived super before Final Fantasy 7.
I was incredibly sleep deprived before this episode, as I explained at the beginning, but
when you get angry and yell about stuff, it does wonders for the energy levels.
I will go crash after this.
Okay, but anyway, anyway, right, speak pipe, more voicemails, thank you, ladies and gentlemen,
we will continue to weed the weed from the chaff as we've done so diligently here today.
Hey, go to patreon.com slash theprocrastinators and give us money, because it's the end of
the show.
And that was a voicemail, and you can give us money to get bonus episodes, which when
you hear this, there will be a new episode.
Not today, but tomorrow, I think, is when we'll be releasing the next bonus episode.
That's 37 of them for $5.
Incredible, incredible.
It is.
Truly.
It is not, it's not.
The value never stops from getting more.
The value only goes up.
It's true.
And what else we got?
At TP Crastinators on Twitter, four more updates.
We got more rad con stuff, we're working on a bunch of stuff, we'll get it to you in
time.
There's not a lot of things, some big stuff that's going to take a while, so we'll keep
you posted on how that goes.
But yeah, make sure if you're a backer, you go to the fucking Kickstarter and you fucking
respond to the backer survey so we know where to send your shit and he tells what size shirt
you are or whatever, all that good stuff.
Beyond that, there's nothing.
That's the end of the episode.
We've done everything.
Nice.
Go to these guys' links, comics and kickstarters and all kinds of good stuff, YouTube's, there's
links in the description.
Go check them out.
And maybe check out, this episode was sponsored by the Final Nights at 7 Remake.
I've been paid to shill for it.
This is all a sigh up where I make you so mad at me being mad that you buy the game to
prove me wrong.
And I'm glad to be doing my duty.
Buy it from the Amazon affiliate link in the description below.
Indeed.
Should they buy it?
Do you want people to buy it?
No, right?
We're firmly anti.
Are we all firmly?
Well.
Last time there was a lot of precarication and uncertainty.
It's too late to be anti, it's happening, so I don't give a fuck.
I would not, I mean, I don't want to encourage this kind of thing, so no, I don't want people
to buy it.
But I mean, the game already is like the best selling game on PS4 basically, because they
wanted a remake of a game everybody already loved and nobody signed up for this shit
and they can pretend that they like it now.
No, no, no, no, no, I'm going to cut you off here, you're going to just repeat yourself
30 more times.
Okay, I will just say, not everybody's pretending, some people legitimately like it, just disagree.
Okay, there you go, there you go, there you go, there you go, there you go, there you
go, there you go.
And end of episode, we'll see you next week, everybody, more on that bonus side, so don't
forget to tune in to that.
Alright, goodbye.
I'm going to go watch the Star Citizen.
Good fucking bye.
Bye.
Goodbye.