Now, this video was just me throwing out my own personal opinion, with no intent to shove my thought down anyone's throats,
or to persuade anyone to feel bad for having different tastes from me.
However, that doesn't seem to be how a lot of people interpreted it.
Commenters, please kill yourselves and free me from this living hell.
If your comment is mean and snide, then you can just fuck off and die.
Why do you feel entitled to spewing your bullshit attitude?
You're rude and crude and I hate you, so kill yourselves please and be cool.
I pronounced the word wrong, I don't care.
I didn't represent you, yeah, no shit, I am myself motherfucker.
Think I got a bad attitude, well you ain't seen shit.
A shadow banned your ass to deal with it.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of the process.
I am the best guy ever and we're joined today by Munchy where his tiny ass.
I've made it an irreplaceable hobby of mine to just draw and doodle on Pokemon cards
and sell them at a profit at local schools and flooding the market with my own artistic mashup pieces
on top of Geodudes and Machobs.
Excellent, Hippocrates is here.
Commenter rules, more like commenter eulogy, if you know what I'm saying.
Yes, excellent. Tom Oliver is here.
I just woke up, but I'm here anyway, I'm going to do it, I'm going to comment on comments.
And Ben St.
No comments.
Because I haven't heard the whole podcast yet.
Oh excellent, that's a good one.
Incidentally, this is the procrastinator's podcast, a podcast with a bunch of internet boys
who are just here to talk about a bunch of stuff that we like, we all make stuff and we're all here.
Spread our intellect across the interweb.
I just looked at my hand and there's blood all over it, I should be fine, but I'm scared.
I think they're already fighting back.
Oh yeah, they're attacking from the future.
I will say I've bled on the PCP more times and I've bled off the PCP, that's not a joke, that's accurate.
Okay, I was going to say I've made your woman bleed, but I don't know why I was going to say that.
That would be hard to understand.
So today, we're talking about, it's Commentary Rules Number Two.
Commentary Rules Two everybody.
It's been a long time coming.
Yeah, Commentary Rules is one of our most proudest grace achievements from the past, from the good old days
when this podcast had a real good fan base and everyone was real nice and it was a great popular time
but now we're just surrounded by fools and geeks and goblins and everyone hates us now.
One of our seminal works for sure.
And just as a fun history lesson, I'm just going back, I've got it pulled up here.
That was episode 14 of the PCP and I think this is episode 85 that this is going to be.
Yeah, I think that's right.
Yeah, and that was on April 3rd of 2016 that came out, so it's been almost two years.
Look at year and a half, I guess, which is a long time.
We've been doing this thing for quite a while now, fellas.
Jesus fucking Christ.
And exactly what do we have to show for it?
Absolutely nothing.
Yeah, it's pretty sick.
The comments have indeed descended.
Our old selves would be so ashamed of our current comment section.
That's true.
You guys made a vow to ban all the people who disrespected and disregarded your Commentary Rules
and I think it's time we reinstate those rules and then stay true to our word.
You're not wrong.
I'm for savage law enforcement.
I'm for some excessive force.
With the release of the...
I've come to a new appreciation of respecting the law after the Mad Bull, you know,
Plebe and the Weeb has come out, so yeah.
Well, I mean, you were there.
It's not like now that you've...
Well, you just reminded of it, I guess.
The first time didn't do the trick, but the second time was really the charm for experiencing it.
To learn what Mad Bull was trying to teach us all along.
Let me tell you this right now, commenters.
After we're done with you, you're just going to be shouting Michael Brown in the fucking streets
because we're going to use excessive force.
You're going to be saying to the hands up, please kill me.
Before we get into any of the discussion about Commentary Entitlement and Commentary Rules,
I would just like to make a motion to ban any retarded offline analogies to like parties or shopping malls
or any sort of like non-literal, non-virtual, non-multiplayer focused first-person shooter,
like apartheid simulator.
They all get muddled and argued upon on the basis of their semantics
and they actually get to the point of the heart of the issue
and turn the entire thing into like a big old farce.
Let's keep things real, literal, and argue about things that are like comments in the real world
as they appear not in fantasy lands.
I don't understand.
I'll do my dance.
There was a lot of analogies made and we went around in circles.
There's an inherent difference between someone saying words and you reading text.
There's an inherent difference in which you keep the internet issues
in the context of them being on the internet.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, all right, sure.
That's our focus here.
That's what we do.
That's where we live.
Okay, understood.
So one of the reasons that we bring this up is because there's been a couple of discussions,
as Monchi just said, about a commenter entitlement.
Both Digi made a couple of videos.
He made one, people responded, and then he made a response to the responses to his video about that issue.
And Davoo also made one.
So you can go check out their channels if you want to see what they're talking about.
Yes, those videos will be relevantly linked in the description for you to go look at.
If you remember that, I'll put it in.
I'll log in and put it in.
Okay, all right.
Yeah, great.
Yeah, they're good context for this.
So that's sort of, there's been, you know, we've all evolved.
It's been like a year and a half, over a year and a half since the first commenter rules.
We've all grown, things have changed on the PCP and in our lives,
and we've all got new things to drink at the table.
And the hot topic right now is this commenter entitlement.
So I don't know, Monchi, you want to tell us what you know about this?
How do you stand on this?
Where do I stand on commenters as a whole or with commenter entitlement as described?
I guess specifically entitlement, but wherever you want, really.
I am a pro comment boy.
I'm one of the least, I guess, hawkish of my comments.
But then again, I guess that's because I'm the little guy.
I don't have a lot of comments to police.
But as a whole, I see a lot of good things come out of comments.
I like reading good comments, and I very rarely get bad comments.
And whenever I do, they don't really impact me as much as my other people.
I mean, I always want to salute you that despite the fact that Andrew Hussey
incessantly shitposts on every episode of Armour Travel that comes out,
you retain your strength and you're a respect for the law,
and you don't ban him out.
How would it reflect on me to destroy the person who's given me so much,
a.k.a. Brahmal, my favorite webcomic artist?
Yeah, commenter entitlement.
I think it's really up to the creator to do it every once.
I just like comments. I just like comments a lot.
So I don't like when they go.
I think I'm the only person who likes to see comments
and I would be sad if they were all deleted and disabled.
Well, all right, as a other, like, small-ish YouTuber,
I agree that sometimes, like, for me personally,
the comments on my videos are so few that, you know,
there aren't that many really bad ones and there are, you know,
there's quite a lot of good ones and it's nice to read all of them.
If I had a video that was, like, actually popular with hundreds of thousands of views
getting comments all the time, I would not want to see any of them.
They would be terrible and I would want to disable the comments.
Just because I've seen on other people's channels how absolutely terrible it is
and I can't imagine having that as, like, a notification stream for me.
I don't want that. So, like, I see both sides of it.
Yeah, well, you know, I mean, none of us are huge YouTubers,
especially on this right now.
Digi, of course, is the biggest of us who's historically gotten the most comments.
I currently, I think, anyway, have the second biggest channel.
Actually, Mage might be ahead of me at something.
I think she is. Last I knew.
I think she is. But in any case, like, the point is I am starting to get to the point where
I still actually get notifications to my phone every time I get a comment,
just because I enjoy reading them. And that's the thing.
I'm starting to get comments, like, every, I don't know,
every couple of hours I get a notification that I've got a new comment,
which is a pretty steady stream of them.
And I definitely get some bad ones, some annoying ones, especially when...
Well, here's what it comes down to.
Like, the bigger your audience gets, the more, like, normal randos
who don't really know your history or your thing and are just likeable,
are likely to take the least charitable interpretation of your content possible,
or a less one, you know, they have less context.
Like, for example, I just made a video about how I hate League of Legends.
It was inevitable that a lot of people who like League of Legends,
you know, want to protest against this and call me an asshole, call me a piece of shit,
say that I'm being a bully.
Absolutely fools.
Monsters, little trolls, little goblins.
And I don't like hearing them.
You know, I don't like hearing people insult me or tell me that I'm wrong and stuff,
but it's still worth it for me at this point to get the comments,
because I do see people agree.
And, you know, I get a little endorphin rush when I see a comment,
so I still like that. That's still fun.
I think I just want to say for myself,
the only reason I create any art or show my face in any public scenario whatsoever
or even wake up in the morning is so people can say that they like me
and that they think I'm doing a good job.
Of course.
That's the only reason I do anything in my entire life.
I think a lot of people agree on that.
Whenever I get a good comment, that validates me making the art in the first place.
That's the only reason I fucking do literally anything.
Well, here, let me counter-argue.
I don't necessarily agree with the subtext that I think I'm hearing
in what you guys, especially you Nate, are saying.
I don't think that a comment that disagrees with you is bad.
Not only do I not think it's a quote-unquote bad comment,
like a shitty comment by an asshole,
I don't even see it as like a negative thing,
because I don't know, that's discussion.
And if people are discussing your content,
even if they're disagreeing with you,
that's still like a mark, that's still good.
I hear what you're saying, but your biggest video is your Christian lecture,
and there are plenty of comments on that,
like look at these autistic assholes.
I love those. I actually love those.
You love them, huh?
I mean, it's really funny, and I'm not insulted,
because I know this person has no idea what they're talking about.
And you know, I am a big loser, so fair enough, fair play on their part.
I don't know.
I guess a little part of me is bothered by it,
but a much bigger part of me is like...
When it comes to the subject of mean people,
I notice a lot in my comic session.
A lot of people trying to be ironically mean,
and I guess I kind of parade that air around me,
so I guess I shouldn't be too surprised when that happens.
But there's a clear distinction in my mind
between a bad comment and a comment that is mean,
or a bad one, since it doesn't like the video.
It's completely fine, and I don't care,
and it doesn't even bug me at all when someone doesn't like the video.
I obviously, as I say before, I live for the compliments,
but you know, just because someone doesn't like it,
it's not going to be the end of the world for me.
What I don't like is the le epic, funny, mean comments
that are trying to be cutesy and get me to like them
by being rude and weird.
A lot of the time on Armitrable,
most of the time Armitrable comments are fantastic,
and I love them, but every once in a while,
there's a really weird, snooty comment that I don't understand.
That's one of the main things.
I understand a lot of the comments made by bizarre people,
and it really, I just want a comment section
full of people who not just like what I like,
or you know, like what I put out, I mean, you know, I would like that,
but I just want ones where I can understand what they're saying,
and you know, I think like, you know, the autistic,
look at all these autistic people.
I would get annoyed by that, but I don't think,
like if it was just, you know, some funny comment
that was negatively impacting, you know,
it was negative on the video itself.
I wouldn't get mad at that.
I don't think that's immune from me liking that comment.
It all just depends on the context of the comment, you know?
Well, I know what you're saying.
Yeah, I do, and I think that's a good way to segue into
like the describing of the actual entitlement phenomenon
that's been discussed recently.
So like, you're talking about not liking, you know,
certain people who post particularly like me-me comments,
or people like trying to bait out upvotes and whatnot,
and that's sort of the issue that Digi was talking about
and DeVue and whatnot.
So the specific discussion that's been about the entitlement
of commenters is that, so right now,
YouTube is built in such a way that the comments are basically
an intrinsic part of every YouTube video,
and what Digi is talking about in his discussion is that
things do not have to be that way.
There could be social, not even social media,
but there could be like video uploading platforms
that simply do not have a comment section
and contrary to people's belief,
that does not violate your First Amendment rights
or any of those ridiculous claims that some people say.
That's, you know, that's not how that works.
And if someone chooses to close the comments, again,
that is not violating your rights,
because as Digi says repeatedly,
you can just go anywhere else you want
and make a comment on Reddit, on your Facebook,
you know, whatever you want to do.
The platform specifically allows for comments to be curated
and for comment sections to be closed.
I don't understand how you can argue
that it's wrong to do that in any way.
All of us here are totally comfortable.
It's not really like that it's wrong.
I mean, most people, I don't know whether they actually think
it's wrong to close comments,
but they do think that it's cowardly,
because it implies things.
There's just like this arrow of like,
I can't take it, therefore, I'm closing the comments,
which isn't true, it's just I would rather not.
This is the big issue at the heart of this.
Do commenters deserve to have comments?
Commenters don't deserve anything.
The word deserve, the word deserve there is the critical one there,
because again, the commenting is honestly, it is a privilege.
It is not a right.
Someone has to choose to give it to you.
But hang on, I think Tom is going to say something.
Tom, did you want to jump in?
Well, I was just going to say that I feel like we're talking,
like, I haven't watched Digi's videos,
and I probably should have.
I just watched Davoo's.
But in terms of just what we're talking about with comments
and how Digi is saying,
like we need a platform where comments aren't a thing,
like YouTube can be that,
like you can have your entire channel have no comments
if you want to have your content presented in that context.
Yeah, but I think Digi's responding to the attitude people have,
where like they would call him like, you know,
a failure or a coward, or fighting their rights.
I mean, I guess my perspective on all this is that,
like, I would never close my comment section because
Yeah, but why does it have to be?
Of course they would do that.
Like, why can't we try and change their mind?
Because here's the thing.
Like, you're saying how people come into YouTube
and have this, like,
and they have like this expectation of comments.
But like, you're coming in here onto the platform of YouTube,
which is a social network,
which has this whole community aspect.
Like, you're coming onto this platform
and people are coming to you with the expectation
to be part of the conversation.
Like, that's why YouTube is successful
and that's why people like it.
It's because you have this, like,
smaller barrier of entry to, like, talking to a creator.
And while that's where you can argue the merits
of whether that's good or bad, that's the expectation.
That's why people are here.
And that's why people like comments,
is because they want to be able to be part of the discussion of the video.
You are completely right.
And I'm sure that played some role
in the growth of YouTube up to this point.
I couldn't agree more.
That's definitely a plus that draws people to this website.
That ability to relate to what people are saying.
And I think guys like Digi might actually be undercounting.
If there was a platform where people couldn't comment,
they might be less likely to actually get into it,
because, you know, they want to be part of the conversation.
Well, I mean, because you think of, like, something like Netflix.
Netflix doesn't have comments or anything.
People can't comment on, like, the content and stuff.
So it's a totally different feel in terms of, like,
a platform that versus YouTube.
It's like gun control.
Like, fucking comments are guns.
And as Americans, you have comments.
You have guns.
You can't take that away.
When people know they can have guns,
it's impossible to take them away.
But in countries that have never really had guns,
like the UK, I mean, we aren't clamoring for them.
We just, you know, they're just not a thing you can have.
You just really, really would like them.
You really like to be able to kill everyone.
Yeah, well, that's the thing.
I don't, I don't think about...
No, Toria's school shooter Hippocrates.
Why is guns in the UK?
I'm never, I'm never, like, thinking,
man, I really should, I really should,
to have a shotgun right now.
I really want that.
But it never comes up.
Well, the difference is just that, like, there's a...
I mean, it kind of isn't tried in law.
If I said no world, like, real life analogies, guys.
I know, but I thought it was funny.
But the point is, the point is,
comments are a thing.
Changing the public perception would be nice,
but it's kind of impossible to, like,
make people think that turning off the comments
isn't, uh, I don't know,
whatever, cowardly, or whatever they would think.
But it's impossible to change that completely.
But I think there should be some sort of, like,
you need, um, you know, 10,000 subs
in order to comment on this video.
Like, just some sort of, like, way to...
That would essentially be the exact same thing.
Because, like, 99% of people don't have 10,000 subs.
The majority of people who use YouTube
use it as a content consumption platform only.
Yeah.
So, right.
My problem with comments is that
they don't have one defined purpose.
There's sort of a weird limbo of, like,
sometimes, like, messages directed towards the author.
Sometimes messages, like, discussing the content.
Sometimes, like, meta messages about the comments themselves.
And, you know, a whole range of spectrum in between them.
Yeah.
It's just kind of a cluster of comments.
Well, that's just what happens when you have an open forum.
You just have people doing their own thing.
I know.
Well, I don't like it.
You know, it's not good.
I mean, yeah.
Well, that's why you can disable comments.
Just turn them off if you don't like them.
Yeah, but then when I'm a coward if I do that.
We all...
Well, why do you care how people perceive you in that way?
It's like...
But, Tom, that is the whole...
The point is not whether or not you can do it.
The nature of this debate is whether or not, like,
people should call you a coward for doing so.
That's, I think, the nature of this discussion.
It's not going to kill me if someone calls me a coward,
but I don't understand why they would want to.
My argument is, if that's the point,
if you have the ability to turn off comments
and you want to turn off comments,
but you're afraid of the backlash,
then you are a coward.
So, they're totally right in thinking of it.
I think I agree.
I think I agree with Tom here.
I think I got to chime in.
Yeah, but sometimes it's not really so much of,
I'm afraid of the backlash.
It's like, like you were saying,
you know, if the comments were gone,
people wouldn't, like,
maybe would not like your YouTube channel that much.
You wouldn't get as much traction.
You wouldn't grow as much.
Okay, then keep them on.
Then they're not good.
They're not good if they're helping you grow.
Then you need to just nut up, ignore the bad comments,
and let your channel grow.
I mean, how much they actually increase anything.
The way things are now,
like, comments are good for growth.
And, like, I don't know how they play into the algorithm.
I have some vague idea that, like, more comments
and more upvotes on comments
or something probably increases visibility
and feeds into the algorithm some way.
So, that's probably true.
But, like, then on top of that,
there's just the whole, like, people-like comments,
people-like the community aspect of it.
The community is fucking terrible.
Yeah, but I don't think it's fair.
It is entirely...
I'm trying to fucking say something.
Okay, say your thing.
I don't think it's fair that it's, like, across the board.
There's no good reason to turn off your comments.
And if you do, you're a coward.
Yeah, obviously, that attitude is shitty,
and it's not necessarily fair.
But, like, yeah, like Tom was saying,
you gotta just make a judgment call
of, like, are the comments worth it or not?
And, like, I don't think it's fair to be, like,
oh, well, comments are so bad,
but I'll lose out on the benefits by turning them off.
And that's not fair.
No, like, you can opt into that benefit.
You have to make your cost-benefit analysis
of whether comments work or not.
Yeah, they've got positives and they've got negatives.
And, yeah, I think it's kind of...
I'll just fucking say it.
I think it's kind of entitled for a creator
to come out and be like, oh, well, it's not fair.
It's not fair that there will be consequences
for turning off comments because you're benefiting from...
I agree.
Yeah, you're benefiting from...
You're gaining things from having comments on in the first place.
Like, you're opting into that system
because it has tangible benefits.
I'm not saying I shouldn't be.
I mean, fucking...
I know that, like, things have...
stuff has consequences.
Okay.
I just...
Wait, wait, wait.
I just am angry that comments always suck
and I don't like looking at them.
And there they are.
We should not...
I don't like it.
There's just nothing for them.
You're right.
We should not lose sight of the point of this whole discussion,
which was Digi propagating or pushing forward
a just a different website
that is just set up differently.
He's not saying change YouTube at all.
That's not his point.
It's that I wish there was a social media platform
that, you know, was...
Well, essentially, things like that already exist.
You can make a WordPress.
Like, I have a WordPress
and I put every video on Hippocrates on there
and there are no comments allowed.
Is it possible...
Is it possible Digi is just saying that
he wants all the benefits of YouTube
without the downsides?
Is that...
Is that what he's getting at?
Am I...
Am I turning against Digi right now?
It was a hypothetical, like, dream sequence
where he was just sort of like,
oh, wouldn't it be great?
But like you said, that does exist.
I mean, who wouldn't...
I agree, which is why it was so weird.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, you're right.
Does the argument then turn into...
Theoretically, there's two websites.
They're exactly the same.
But one has comments, like,
you just can't do comments.
And the other one is, like,
comments are always on.
Does the argument then become what is better?
They're not exactly the same.
It's like the sharing is the same.
No, I know.
I'm the same for the sake of argument.
Like, are we going to go into, like,
the empirical value of comments
and whether or not, like, on, like,
an intellectual level are, like,
are they a just cause, like, inherently?
And to get into, like,
remove the option of them,
is that inherently bad?
I guess that's part of the discussion.
The thing was, like,
I never really think about this.
I don't think to myself,
ah man, comments in general suck.
I really wish I could turn them off
without any downside.
Like, I don't think about that.
This is just, like, a thing that has come up.
And I'm, like, just trying to, you know,
think of what my position is.
But ultimately, in this podcast,
I think what I would like to do
is just to explain to people
why you should not feel like you should have comments.
Like, why, like, the community,
like, all the pros that people bring forth
of why comments should stay.
I want to slap them down.
I want to push them into the ground,
into the mud.
And just watch them as they slowly writhe and shake
until they're completely...
You're taking the munchy road
of knocking people down.
I'm really proud.
Yeah.
That's a dangerous road to tread.
I feel a little bit differently about this.
I too have never closed comments.
I have banned very few people.
Mostly, like, obvious spammers,
or, like, pushing products or whatever.
I mean, I would happily ban any spammer
who's just like,
hey, buy my book.
I don't know, like, buy my...
Subscribe to my website, guys.
Let's, like, not relate to the content.
It's like, no, get fucked.
You delete yourself.
Um...
Yeah, so that's an instant ban.
I don't know.
Like, the whole, like, concept of, like,
hate speech and shit,
like, people, like, being taxed.
I don't know.
That's all vague.
I don't understand it.
I don't know how I feel about any of that,
so I just ignore it.
So, basically, I just opt out.
I pull, like, the PewDiePie and say,
I'll just let people comment,
and I'll just ignore it.
They can say whatever they want.
Uh, you know, it's not my problem.
I don't feel responsible for it.
Uh, that's their world down there.
I thought PewDiePie turned off comments,
or maybe he turned them back on.
He turned the back on.
He turned the back on a little while later.
Uh, but, like,
do I feel like I want them to be part
of the videos?
Like, I don't mind that comments are there right now.
I absolutely don't mind.
I'm happy to see them there.
It's fine.
But, like, I really think of my work as my own,
and I don't like the idea of anyone feeling entitled
to, like, be a part of it,
because what have they done to earn that?
Nothing.
I would say that if you don't want people to feel like that,
you just better not post on YouTube, you know?
Like, if there was...
Yeah, like, I wouldn't be against another platform
that didn't have comments.
I mean, I don't...
I mean, I'm totally on board with not liking comments
and not feeling that people are entitled to them.
Like, when I was making my website,
I had people tell me, like,
Ben, you gotta include a comment section in,
like, in the website, like, on the pages.
And I was like, no.
Because for a number of reasons, one,
yeah, I don't want someone to be able...
I don't want any chuckle-fuck to be able to go in there
and put their thoughts about my work right there
and attach it to the content
and have it be, like, a part of the reading experience.
I think it's... I think it's crass
and attention-seeking to put something like that there.
Like, hey, guys, tell me what you think about my thing.
Tell me right here so everyone can see.
Um, it's a... I think it's a bad look
because, like, Ben, like, even a popular comic
will often have, like, empty comments
on, like, you know, pages where not a lot happens.
And, like, that doesn't look good.
So, yeah.
Especially, like, to have one on every page,
that really interrupts the reading experience.
I see that on a lot of, like, Dojin websites and shit.
And, like, those are funny because I don't take those seriously.
But on a real comic, I totally would not want that.
Yeah, I don't, like, for a number of reasons,
I was like, I don't want people
to be able to say whatever they want here, so no.
Right.
No, thank you.
Um, I forget where I was going with that.
That's how I feel.
You know, I'm like a fucking, like, kiss anime and kiss cartoon.
Like, you can scroll down or, like, manga something or other.
Like, there's some manga and anime, like, illegal sites you could go to.
You can see the thing, and then if you scroll down,
there is a comment section.
And to see people, like, like, I know it's illegal,
but it's like, it feels like this is the thing.
This is the show.
Yeah.
You're watching it, and then there are people down there,
and it's like, this somehow reminds me of YouTube,
and therefore de-legitimizes the thing I just watched
as, like, a real thing.
Because now I'm thinking of it as nothing.
I can understand, like, the feel.
In an aesthetic way, I get it.
It's like a slight sort of, like, feeling.
Like, I just don't like seeing a big old comment section.
It sort of casualizes the experience, you know?
Even before I, if I don't, I don't need to, like,
read all of them to know that they were bad.
I just see the comments, and I'm like,
Oh, God.
Oh, good job.
I have never gone this argument that, like,
comments then become part of the video.
Because I have never, not once in my life,
thought of comments as part of the video.
Well, you gotta think about it in terms of, like, the worst thing.
I think they totally are.
They totally are.
You watch the video, yeah, you watch the video,
then you scroll down to see what people are saying about it,
and then you fucking internalize,
you internalize the general consensus.
Like, people are having the discussion right there,
and you're exposed to it.
I agree that, like, having the comments there,
just, like, like...
Yeah, it can really color how you feel about it,
because, like, immediately you get to see,
like, what the general opinion is.
And yeah, I think that it kind of robs you
of your ability to form your own opinion about something.
Whenever I will watch a video, I will just full screen it,
and then I will watch the entire video,
I'll come to my own conclusions,
and then, like, maybe one-third of the time
I'll go and see the comments.
Most of the time I will not even, like, look at the comments at all.
Well, that's...
They are not factoring my opinion whatsoever
of the comments at all.
If I find a video interesting at all,
I always want to check the comments
and see what people are saying about it.
Why would I care about what other people are saying about it?
Well, well, much, I mean, the point we're getting at
is, like, if it affects, like, a lot of people,
then it's relevant to our discussion here,
and, like, the rest of us agree
that the comments do change things.
So we just have to go with the consensus, I guess, on this.
And people can disagree, but I think it's,
I feel safe in saying that, like,
you can see, like, the view count,
and the likes and the dislikes,
and all those things weigh in
and change the experience a little bit, you know?
They're all relevant.
Like, if you see a video with, like, five views,
you're like, what the fuck?
There's, like, a physical, like, line.
Like, you have to scroll down to see the comments.
And that, in and of itself,
makes it not part of the content of the experience for me.
No.
One scroll is, like, not enough to separate it, I don't think.
And even then, even if the comments are gone,
the like bar is enough of, like, a damper.
You have to agree.
It changes my opinion.
That is a fundamentally different aesthetic.
To be viewing a YouTube video with, like,
comments just below the service,
you can see the like and the upvotes
and the downloads and the number of views,
as opposed to, like, watching a video in a fucking movie theater.
And then going to the goddamn ghostbusters, like, forums
to talk about the new ghostbusters for me.
Okay, sure.
The like bar and the contents of the comment section,
like, put the video in a context, you know?
That's right.
And a lot of the time, some videos are just, like,
not visually that interesting.
So you will scroll while listening to the video
to read comments while it's happening,
because there's nothing else to do.
If we're expanding comments to mean the like bar
and the view count, then, yeah.
Then those impact me a lot.
Then I'll agree that that makes an impact.
Like, if you click on just some random video,
like a podcast, and you see, like, a massive amount of dislikes,
and you're just, like, wait, I didn't,
what's wrong with the video?
I didn't see anything wrong.
Then you'll listen back and be like, oh, that's what it was.
Now I understand.
It's the smash cut to Nate watching a eugenics podcast
seeing the message.
Wait, wait, wait, what was wrong with this?
Why didn't they like this?
What was wrong with this video?
Everything checks out to me.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, yeah.
I mean, I guess, I guess, I guess I'm the minority.
I thought I was going to speak for the unwashed masses,
but I guess I'm the native minority.
We're specifically talking about...
That's true.
We're just talking about if it's relevant,
if they sort of affect the experience.
Yes.
Which I think it's safe to say they do.
And I guess I don't think I don't think that at all.
But, you know...
Okay.
Well, considering that...
What we're explaining, saying, talking about is, like,
things added to the thing will affect,
and if the view count and the like bar is, like, does affect,
then it, you know...
I mean, it's so...
It's a moment specifically...
Assuming that the idea of something being close by...
Assuming that that is true, then I hate it with all my heart,
and it's the worst thing I could ever make.
I would agree that comments definitely affect the perception of a work.
Like, if you're watching a video
and you just have the video presented by itself,
then clearly that's one perspective.
But, like, if you're watching a video and then you scroll down
and immediately you see a comment contradicting things
or bringing up counterpoints,
then obviously, like, that's going to affect your perception of the work.
Now, one thing I will say about this is, like,
it's the same, basically, as, like, watching a movie
and then watching a review of a movie.
You beat me to it.
That's right.
It's the same sort of thing, except people in comments
are not the same, like, even a terrible review,
at least goes over the basics and has, like, visual aids.
A comment is just a guy going,
like, even the best of times,
it's a guy going, but, like, with a monocle.
Like, it's never actually as good as a review.
So, what Digi, I think, was saying is, like,
if you're going to make a critique of something in the comments section,
I would rather you make a more substantial...
I think that's a good point.
I think more people should be creators,
and if you want to bitch about something,
I think it would be more important to...
or better suited to making an actual product out of it.
I'll lay it out on the line, guys.
I'll lay out my secret ulterior motive.
One excellent reason why I didn't want a comment section on my website
is because I would much rather that conversation take place somewhere else
in, like, a public forum.
Or, like, on YouTube or something.
Perhaps a website specifically designed for that.
Perhaps patreon.com.
No, like, because if someone sees a comment section on there
and they're like, I have a strong opinion about what I've just read,
they'll go and just, like, fucking shit in my comment section
that doesn't exist to prevent this very thing.
But then, if they don't have that option,
then maybe instead they'll be like,
hey, something awful forums,
hey, 4chan, I just read this thing,
and it fucking sucked.
Well, that's exactly what...
That's exactly what kind of Digi was talking about, I think, in his thing,
which, uh, yeah, you know, which is good.
It forces people to up their game.
And I agree that people upping their game is good,
and I would like to see more of it.
Well, I guess that's all I have to say about that.
Fair enough.
That's what I want as a creator,
is for people to make, like, well thought out
and have a real conversation about what I'm doing, you know?
Right, which comments so often are not even close to that.
That is too shallow.
I'm actually pretty warm on comments in general.
Like, comments, like we've been saying,
are very much tied to the community aspects of YouTube,
which has both major pluses and minuses.
Uh, you know, people can feel more involved and engage in it,
but then it creates kind of circle jerky bullshit,
and like, drama is really popular, and all that gay shit.
But, like, for a show like Viagra that I do,
like, that is very much like a community engagement show.
So, like, to me, it seems like reasonable to have comments on that,
whereas, like, I don't know.
Like, something like my other...
Yeah, like, with one of those, like,
again, I don't really mind there being comments.
I don't really mind it at all.
But, like, that is, like, my...
It's like a movie that I made, and, like,
I don't necessarily think that your fucking worthless opinion
is relevant to this movie that I just made.
Uh, yeah, like, make a video response
if you loved it so much, or hated it, or whatever,
if you've got critiques or something.
You know what I mean?
Why don't just, like, disable comments for videos
you don't want to have that conversation on?
Yeah, like, there's some videos that, like,
like, is this video discussion worthy?
Does this deserve discussion?
Or is this just a game for two people?
And, like, we're talking about how there's a stigma to this,
but if more people did it, it would change...
you would affect the perception of the action.
Because, right now, the only people who disable comments
are people like Anita Sarkeesian,
who just get fucking trolled into oblivion,
and they don't want to hear it.
And it's, like, it is a way of just, like,
censoring and not having to see that stuff
or have it be a thing.
Some people have transcended it.
Like, TotalBiscuit doesn't, I think...
I mean, TotalBiscuit probably gets trolled for it to some degree,
but, hey man, no comment, so you can't see it there.
See, that's not being cowardly.
That's just saying, like, I don't want to hear it,
and I'm going to turn it off.
And if you want to do that, that's fine.
And, I don't know, I feel like the problem,
I think, for a lot of people who want to disable comments,
because that's not me, I'll keep them on no matter what.
I don't care.
But for people who want to not deal with it,
I think the problem is I don't want to hear opinions
or I don't want to hear these, like, dumbass comments,
but I also don't want to give up the endorphin rush
or whatever of people agreeing with me and sucking me off.
So it's like...
Well, we don't...
You gotta accept the good with the bad there.
It's like an all-in-all kind of approach.
I don't want to let the commenters off the hook,
because, I mean, we can talk about the community engagement
and all that, but we know that they love the power
of being right there.
They get to be right there up on the video.
And if they're good enough, oh, my shitpost,
my deconstruction in one elegant shitpost,
or this guy's a fucking cuck or whatever,
a thousand upvotes, yes, I have a tie to this man.
Okay, I totally agree, but don't you think
we have the exact same problem?
Like, that's why we're posting on YouTube,
but not like our own website,
because we want the power of having our voice being heard
and having an audience to project to,
and that's why we're all on YouTube.
Definitely, I just want to say,
and you're absolutely right,
it's just that I am superior to a commenter objectively.
I put thought into what I do, I work...
Even on my comments, you'll find more thought
than a 10,000 other comments put together.
Yeah, I mean, it really is like
we put more effort into making this podcast.
I mean, not much more effort than a comment, I guess,
because we're just speaking.
But, you know, someone has to edit it,
someone has to upload it.
It's a project, you know?
If more people turn their comments into videos,
I would care about them.
I would respect them more because they put more effort
into having a point.
Is that the real problem then?
Is it not so much commenter entitlement,
but commenter laziness?
Or, like, not wanting to...
I mean, the thing is that I've noticed
is that if you have, like, an other place,
like a Reddit, where you have designated four comments,
you say, go there to comment,
and even if you have a link in the description,
the vast majority of the people who don't go
are so lazy that their comments wouldn't...
You would never want to hear them anyway.
So, like, only the people who actually...
That's the thing.
...gave even the tiniest bit of a shit to click somewhere
would, you know, I would respect them for doing even that.
So why don't more people disable comments
and do that then?
Because then they're fostering better.
It's the stigma.
Isn't that your problem, though?
Isn't that your problem?
Like, at some point, don't you have to, like,
say, you know, this is my responsibility
because it's my content,
and, like, I have to take the hit
in order to foster the discussion I want to see?
I agree.
That's why I didn't disable anything,
and I probably never will.
At the beginning, I said, like,
I can see it from both sides,
but my channel is kind of small,
so it's not even a problem for me.
So my stance is that when it does become a problem,
I will switch.
I just don't need to yet.
Yeah.
Yeah, like, that's the thing.
We should think of this from the perspective
of, like, a big YouTuber.
Why should a big YouTuber have to allow this
and be called, like, a piece of shit for disabling it?
Like, from the perspective of someone like a PewDiePie,
or, you know, whoever, like, a big YouTuber guy,
like, PewDiePie's comments were filled with garbage,
and people, like, shitposting,
and not even shitposting,
but, like, advertising themselves.
Like, I've seen his comment sections full of ads
because it gets so many fucking views,
and you can just go comment,
and you're likely to get more hits on your website,
probably, than, you know,
like, making a fucking video yourself.
So, like, there's an incentive to shit up his comments.
So, like, it totally makes sense
why he would turn them off.
I totally get it.
But then, you know, the backlash from people was so strong.
He's like, okay, geez, fine.
Like, that wasn't him being cowardly, I think.
That's him sort of just cow-towing to what the mob wants,
even though the mob is not making any kind of good points.
How is that not cowardly?
How is what you just said not cowardice personified?
Because it's not, I don't know.
Well, he's making a business decision.
He's accepting an annoyance.
It's not about being cowardly.
Yeah, I think the thing is,
changing your mind, I don't think, is cowardly.
It's just like, you know, if the comments are annoying,
you turn them off.
But if the backlash is more annoying,
then you turn them on.
Like, it doesn't...
It's just whatever you feel is, like, the least bad.
Because the...
My comment section has been more or less great,
and I don't intend to ever turn them off.
But the moment they stop being...
Like, the moment it goes from, like,
49% bad to, like, 51% bad,
then I will immediately turn them off.
And, you know, as soon as they become positive,
then I'll turn them back on.
It's not, like, a one-time decision that I will make.
It'll just be whatever my mood dictates.
Yes.
I just don't even know if people, after all this discussion,
will still get the fact that you do not have a fucking right
to comment.
You don't have the right.
People make that argument every time a discussion like this comes up.
You have no fucking right to a comment section.
You stupid, stupid people who make that argument.
They don't.
It's not a fucking First Amendment thing.
I know we've already established this.
It's just...
Understand this point, people.
Like, I don't deal with the riffraff and the scum of society
that have opinions like that.
So sometimes I forget that there are people out there
that do feel that way.
And every time I remember it, I get a little...
I get the howling phantods and I gotta go take a bath.
I will never turn off my comments.
I mean, probably.
I could at some point.
But it's looking like I probably will never, ever do it.
But still, to argue any differently on this point is absolutely absurd.
And it makes me mad just to think about it.
It's not a matter of like, do you like comments or not?
Do they have a right?
Of course not.
This is not a government issue.
This is not will you be thrown in jail if you make a comment.
As has been stated by us, numerous times before in our past
we are giving you a platform to do comments.
And if we don't want you to have it, then why should you have it?
Which we won't take it away, by the way.
But we could.
It's like that comic by Vincent standing around Magda
and he's like, dude, I could kill you right now.
Isn't that interesting?
What the fuck is wrong?
That's us.
That's us right now.
The guest mini-so that I like never fucking posted anywhere.
I should do something about that.
Thank you for reminding me.
You're welcome.
We could close comments at any time.
Isn't that interesting commenters?
Don't you find that fascinating?
I do.
My opinion.
Are the comments going to be closed on this?
No.
I mean, I don't see the need to.
See, that's maybe inconsistent.
I don't see any need to, but you don't have a right to them.
Maybe we'll just for fun.
My opinion has never been...
I think I'll pin the worst comment I've ever seen.
I'll pin that one.
I never...
I don't want to get rid of comments.
I like the idea of comments.
I like the idea of fans or you know, trolls alike.
You know, to say what they want on, you know
on the things that I make.
My only problem is that there are bad comments.
Comments that are not thought out and lazy.
I want to make comments great again is my mission statement.
I don't want to get rid of comments or you know, remove it.
To be a charitable.
I want to just improve them, yes.
Right.
To be as charitable to like Digi's point of view as possible,
his whole idea is to improve the discussion across the board.
He clearly has, you know, the best intentions in mind
when he brings up this idea.
I, too, want to do what I can to improve the level of discourse.
So like, you know, if that actually would do so...
I think the main thing that has to happen for comments to be good
is for if somebody just like makes a silly, not very funny joke
and for plus ones, every time somebody pluses ones that comment
they get an electric shock and Google will determine
that it's not a very funny joke with it's like algorithm and shit.
So only really actually good comments will be at the top.
How do we define bad comments?
If only there were some sort of rules in place
that we could enforce with an iron fist.
Oh, oh yeah.
It's the fucking name of the thing.
We haven't even started talking about rules.
That's true.
We're in the weeds.
I mean, we got to define a bunch of parameters for you.
Can we just say that commenter upvotes and downvotes
are definitely fucking up comments
and that they probably shouldn't be a thing?
It gives the people the wrong incentives
to just be the least funny they could possibly be.
I don't think gamifying comments was a good call
because that becomes less about trying to just express something
and more like, I'm going to get the upvotes
because I don't have a YouTube channel
so my way of getting social recognition
is getting thumbs up on this platform.
The difficult thing is like, without upvotes
the comments are like, you know, newest first or whatever
because there's no top comment
or even worse, like the earliest first
which would mean the first comment is going to be first.
I don't think latest first would be that big of a deal.
I think that's fine.
Well, the only thing about it is that
people repost just to be like the top comment or something.
They'll just keep talking and posting to be at the top
because as soon as they do it, they'll be at the top
and it will make comments more...
That would take more effort on their part though.
No, what we can do, I've got the solution,
we display comments in alphabetical order.
That's the solution, that's how we do it.
Well then there would just be a load of A's before anything to say.
Exactly, and then it'll be A plus on every video.
And then every comment will just start with A-la-mow
and then it gets to the actual comment.
Perfect.
Incredible.
By the way, before...
Here, if you want to make a point, go ahead.
I was just thinking, like didn't you...
YouTube comments used to have like a character limit
and now they don't.
I'm just wondering.
I'm wondering if like it was like...
But I mean, the short, like you are,
like letter U, letter R, retarded.
You know, like that's short and sweet.
Character limits won't fix any of those kind of comments.
I would like more of those.
I don't want to be strung along
in like a very elaborate you are retarded.
I would like them to just be short and sweet.
Okay.
Well, you know what I wanted to say here.
I did want to speak on behalf of the commenters
in the context of this because like,
I really do get where they're coming from
because like I feel like I am in a risen commenter
over the years because my origins here
are from 4chan where I was a big shit poster
and a memester and whatnot
and I still am to this day and it's great and I love it.
So like, I get being a commenter on YouTube
and like wanting to like, like you were saying before,
your angle is you can try to make a comment
that's really good and people will like it
and I feel like that's like,
that's like the first job you can get
is like your starter job like,
oh, I'm going to work really hard on my comments
and make them good so everyone likes me.
And then if you find like, hey,
I'm getting good at like making things.
Maybe now I'll try making a video
and then you can like move up from there to making videos
and like in that way it could theoretically function
as like a stepping stone thing to getting you
to be like a more creative person or like, you know,
it's your way.
It like, it empowers the anonymous individual.
It gives them an ability to be recognized
for their, you know, a degree of contribution.
The problem is human nature does not actually reward
the most thoughtful, like valuable comment.
It rewards the most meme-y one
or the most insulting one or, you know,
anything of that nature.
That's the problem with the system
and because of that things don't work the way
we all wish they would with comments.
So that's just human nature.
That's just budding up against human nature.
We've got a steer human nature.
We can control it to a certain degree.
Like human nature is also to murder and rape
but we're working on that.
We're working on fixing those.
So we can work on this too.
We can work on self, Nate.
Would we like to start ironing out
the bullet point rules here?
I guess we should.
We've been doing this for a while now.
Before we get into the new, like the in you dash new rules,
let's just refresh ourselves
on some of the old ones I picked out
because I actually watched the, you know,
the old one in preparation for this.
Let's just go ahead and see if we have anything
to comment on or a change or redact here.
Number one, do not publish a comment
before finishing the fucking video.
Excellent rule.
Excellent. That is the golden rule.
If you've already done that, get killed.
Yeah.
Before we do this, would you like to start?
Would you make good on our promise
of banning people who do not abide by these?
Is that what we're going to do there?
I think we should.
I think we should for this video at least.
Who's going to turn to the time
to review all the fucking comments?
I'll do that.
If you want to.
Hey man, go for it.
For our warning commenters, you're being warned.
You should have watched the whole video
so you heard this warning.
If you violate the rules,
you may be deleted from real life.
You may be completely obliterated.
I think it's time, you know, it's no secret
we've gotten some riff-raff with our ranks.
And frankly, I think it's time we start, you know,
weeding out the weak from the poor.
Because we love the poor so much.
We talked about closing comments.
We didn't talk too much about deleting comments.
But I guess that's just where the rules come in.
Deleting comments is there's no problem there
and it's good.
Yeah, it falls into the same jurisdiction
as just closing comments.
Like if it violates the principles, you know,
ethically, there's definitely nothing wrong with it.
And I don't know.
Yeah, it's kind of got the same stigma about it
that like it's cowardly,
oh, you're censoring criticism.
But like once again,
since I don't believe that commenters
have an inherent right to their comments,
I don't think that any individual
has a right to say their particular thing.
And yeah, like comments aren't sacred.
Comments aren't sacred.
This isn't, yeah.
That's definitely true.
You're not obligated to be like a free marketplace
of ideas in your comment section.
Very true.
But, okay, real situation here,
someone makes a very thoughtful, critical comment
of a video and the creator deletes it.
How do we feel about that?
It was a good comment.
But it was a post.
That doesn't matter.
That's still the video and creator thing?
I guess it'd be like how I feel about corporations
doing evil things.
So you're calling it evil?
Well, it's bad, it's ugly.
It's cowardly.
If someone makes a good point shutting you down
and you're like,
oh, I don't want to be publicly one-upped like this,
I'm going to delete it,
then yeah, you're kind of being a little bitch.
But again, it's still there in your comment section.
That's what I'm here with in your rights, but it sucks.
I would say the problem is that again,
that's why if you have a nuanced point to make,
you should make a video so the person you're critiquing
can't just delete it right off their content.
That's the comment you're being stupid.
But I think that the stigma is there for a reason
that are people who would delete comments
because they challenge them,
regardless of how well or how nicely you put it,
or how constructive it is.
Yeah, they should be struck with the task for doing that.
I think that there should be,
like, that guy's fucking,
it's just the generalization of it.
If a comment is gone,
that doesn't mean that the person who got rid of it is
running scared.
It's fair to call them what they are, though.
They're like, I mean, maybe not hiding scared,
but I don't think that's a respectable thing to do.
To be like, if someone makes a point,
it might just be that you just legitimately think
their point is stupid,
but this is where we hit a little bit of a gray area
because if I make a video, I make a point,
and someone, like my League of Legends video, whatever,
if someone makes a point that, like, no, you are,
let's just say they're totally polite,
but I think that every single point they make
in their comment is wrong, but they're polite about it.
If I delete that, I would say that's me,
even if I just think that I'm right and they're just wrong,
that's me, like, still not, like, really giving their ideas
a chance to be viewed by people,
and, like, obviously, I'm not breaking laws.
You can do that, but I don't like that.
I don't like that.
Like, I think you should delete comments that are,
one, like, they don't have a point.
They're just being stupid, like, just, I don't know.
Like, I'm trying to think of a specific example,
but, like, if somebody has a point
and you don't agree with it,
but, you know, I don't think you should delete it.
Relate to the tone of comments.
Unless you're deleting everything.
Nice criticism is not constructive criticism,
and, furthermore, more broadly speaking,
you don't have to be a nice person to be a good person.
You don't have to be, like, a nice, polite person
to have your argument and comment.
This is definitely a devout rule.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And very accurate.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I'm just saying this was one of the rules.
I'm just saying that right now.
Oh, yeah, okay, okay.
I'm just saying, like, just because you, you know,
just because you're nice doesn't mean you're a good boy,
and, you know, vice versa.
Just because you're mean or rude or anything
doesn't mean you deserve to be obliterated from society.
That's a good reason, and because you are rude,
you probably are not doing good,
but, you know, it's not a rule here.
Just look at unlikely hero Ebenezer Screws
who has proved right to be a stingy old motherfucker
all along.
That was great. That was great.
I never forgot that.
Another one of these rules,
read the other comments before commenting.
So you don't say the same thing everyone else has already said.
Redundant comments are totally up for deletion.
If they're just redundant, why the fuck out there?
Those are out.
I don't think, like, sometimes there's too many comments
to read all of them, understood, understandable.
But you should scroll, like, a couple times to see
if, like, it hasn't been said recently, at least,
or if it's not a top, already a top comment.
Well, generally, this is, like, one of the most comment,
like, common comments things that, like,
this generally comes up for.
So, like, it should be obvious.
But, yeah, there's...
And you can just control F.
You can just control F here.
True. Like, get good, you know?
Yeah, yeah, great.
I'm getting quite a few comments on my League of Legends.
It's like, lol, this guy's just bad at lol.
And that's fine. That's fine.
But it is redundant.
It is redundant.
That's another...
See, that's not, like, a mean.
That's not, like, oh, I don't like you.
That's not why that comment's bad.
It's just because it's redundant.
It doesn't have any actual point there.
And it's a fucking lazy piece of shit.
I think the reason those comments are...
Like, the comments that I find most frustrating
aren't even the ones that are insulting.
It's because making a video is an act of communication.
So the most annoying things is when people misunderstand you.
Purposely or accidentally.
When they either...
Yes.
They don't understand what you're saying
and it's so obvious that they're wrong.
And it's just, like, that's the most frustrating part.
Oh, dude.
You will understand.
Okay, another...
Yeah.
That is a good rule.
Let's get into the new rules.
Wait, wait. Before you do.
Before you do.
About this, though.
Like, what...
Here's another real situation.
You wake a video.
Someone makes a comment, like, saying...
Like, no, I disagree.
But the way...
The thing they disagree with isn't your point.
But let's say that lots of people think
that you were making that point.
So it is, in fact, you who misrepresented yourself,
but their comment, like, misrepresented the point
you were trying to make,
does that make it viable for deletion?
Because you made the mistake, I guess.
I think I've been thinking about the deletion thing
since it came up.
And I think if...
Delete!
Yeah, very good, very good.
I'm gonna delete that from the podcast.
Aww.
I think it should be like,
you don't want any comments or you allow them.
I don't...
I feel like deletion should be relegated to things
like spamming their own channel
or like a link to a bad thing.
Or like something that is actively would hurt
or damage other people in some physical way,
like a punch to the face.
Get rid of those comments.
What if it's a microaggression?
Microaggressions are basically real life violence.
I love micromachines.
I love Megatron.
By the way, before we get into the new rules,
just another old one just for...
New rules for new males like us.
Exactly.
There's a blast from the past here.
That's very relevant.
Ironic, me, me, cutesy, like,
oh, because this guy said not to comment this,
I'm going to comment this.
Try and get these to go.
Those are gone.
Bye.
I'm sorry, but goodbye.
Delete those.
Yeah, those are awful.
We don't like them.
Stop, please.
Okay, okay.
Now we're getting into the new rules.
I really like understand, period.
Understand what...
Understand the video.
That is a great one.
I like that a lot.
That can apply in a lot of ways.
Yeah, exactly.
Like, if you don't understand,
or at least, like, like, you know,
there are good people who think they understand.
It's hard to know when you don't understand.
Yeah, exactly.
It's hard to know when you understand.
The way to understand is to get brain.
And to get brain, you need to think.
No, here's the real thing.
Being smart.
Here's like the actual thing you should do
if you're a commenter, okay?
If you're a commenter and you don't understand the video,
instead of leaving a comment with an assumption
of what you think it is
and making it idiot of yourself,
leave a comment saying,
I don't quite understand what you're trying to say.
Is it this?
Because by phrasing it that way,
that's a good comment.
It fosters a conversation.
And I'm much more likely to respond to you
to clarify my position.
If you're asking it as a question,
then making a declarative ignorant statement.
Now, asking questions is such a great thing to do
to get my attention.
Because I love explaining.
That's the reason I make reviews.
That's the whole reason I'm on here
fapping about my opinion.
Let me talk about my opinion more.
I would love to explain to you
the specifics of what I mean
if you have a question.
Now, I want to explain my point on understanding,
because this is a slippery slope,
but I think me and Ben are going to have a real talk here about this.
Like me saying,
I understand the video.
It is not your duty to understand the video.
If I have miscommunicated what I'm saying in the video,
then it is inherently my fault.
What I mean by understand to make a good comment
is that you just have to make an effort to,
and if you are intentionally trying to misinterpret
what I'm trying to say,
or misinterpret anything for your own benefit,
then that's what's not good here.
If you just don't understand, then again,
ask a question.
It is my fault that you don't understand
at the end of the day.
I agree with that,
and I think that makes the...
I know we're kind of joking,
but I don't think you can say you got to understand the video,
because if they don't understand, it's your fault.
You fucked up.
Well, right, but...
I think it depends on the terms of making an effort to understand.
I think if there's one or two outliers
who don't understand your point,
then you can probably be safe to say
that while it was your communication,
their misunderstanding,
it might be something on their part that they're missing,
but if the vast majority of people,
of your audience,
seems to be misinterpreting what you're saying,
then it's probably your fault
for not explaining it very well.
If you watch Mr. Betung's Mass Effect 3 review,
and your comment is,
Star Trek sucks.
You have missed the point.
At that point, it's like,
well, delete.
You're gone.
You're destroyed.
Yes.
Good.
You have to make an effort
to understand it on the level
that the original creator is trying to convey.
Also, if anyone ever comments that Star Trek sucks,
I will come to your house.
I'm not coming for you.
You will come for them,
and then ask them specifically which generation.
And no matter what, it's still a delete.
You just want to be clear.
Yeah.
I just need to fill in a little bit of paperwork
before another deletion.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
I have another rule.
Go ahead.
Don't take everything said so seriously.
I think there's an element of like,
it's hard to explain,
but you take someone seriously on the internet
in general,
and you're kind of doing it wrong.
But the points,
if somebody's saying something,
it's fair to say,
if they're just saying it normally in the speech,
normal speech,
it's fair to say that they mean what they say,
but you've got to try and think sometimes
that maybe they might be putting on a character
if you don't know what the character is.
I don't know.
I think I know what you mean,
and this is actually,
I wanted to make a similar rule to it,
so maybe we can combine ours a little bit.
And mine is like,
it's basically like,
give a reasonably charitable interpretation
of what the person is saying.
And so there's a lot of vague language there on purpose,
because what I'm trying to communicate
is that a lot of times,
things are said,
again, in joking ways.
I've made tons of jokes about,
I don't know,
how much I hate women or something in my videos,
and one could take that a certain way.
But friends of you will know those are no jokes.
Exactly,
and I would see each other once to realize
that I am not joking when I say these things.
But no,
I want people to understand,
someone could just cut that clip out
and say,
look at this clip,
this man is a misogynist,
he's the worst man in the world,
et cetera, et cetera.
That is being a bad viewer.
That is them nitpicking,
cherry picking is the word I'm looking for,
and they're not consuming it
within the full context.
So when I say a charitable reading
or a charitable interpretation,
it's considering the context.
I don't know, man.
What do you mean, Ben?
What do you mean?
I don't know if the viewer should be obligated
to have seen all your content
before forming an opinion about it.
I don't think it's unfair.
I think that's unfair
to the people making the content.
I think there is some degree.
Oh, that's not such bullshit.
You have to watch all their videos
and know their full context
before you can have a opinion about it.
No, that's why I'm saying a fair amount.
What you're saying,
I think we are,
maybe I'll allow me to try and clarify
if I'm totally off base, let me know.
But I think what you're saying is that
if you're a commenter,
and this isn't even just commenters,
this is like internet rules,
if you see something online
that gets your goat and pisses you off,
don't immediately have a knee-jerk reaction,
give them the benefit of the doubt,
and at least try and double check
and make sure what you're interpreting
is actually the proper context.
If it's not, you're making a big deal out of it.
I agree that good commenting
and good discussion,
yeah, you do need to,
you should at least have all the facts.
This rule comes with a mathematical formula
attached to it,
specifically for the calculation
of how to do this.
So this is a real rule you can apply.
And it's that a person's comment,
a person's comment is inversely proportional,
like credible or reliable,
inversely proportional to the amount
of content they've consumed.
So maybe I fucked that up.
What I'm trying to say is,
the more they know about the creator,
the more their comment should matter.
So like for example,
if like a crazy feminazi,
just as an example,
has never seen any of my shit
and sees me make a joke about women,
and then says like,
ah, I see this three-second clip,
I have decided this man is evil,
that person should be proportionately less valuable
of an opinion than someone who has consumed
all of my content.
I think you've got a bit of creator bias there,
because sure, that would make their comment,
like them having the context into you
would make the comment matter more to you,
but why should anyone else care?
Because that's how we arrive at truth
and the correct position.
I think from your perspective,
and I think what you're saying is like,
they definitely have a more nuanced understanding
of your character
and how you would phrase arguments,
but doesn't necessarily make it more valuable,
because someone can come in who's never...
That's some bullshit.
What are you talking about?
How can you say that?
Because someone can come in
and just watch one video,
comment on the topic of the video at hand
without going into like the best guy ever back catalog
and still have a relevant opinion.
But what can I do to solve this problem?
My catalog exists,
only they can make things more understood.
I have no power to further inform them
other than make the videos available,
which they are.
I think this is an inherent problem
with your chosen profession.
I don't think the commenters are at fault here.
I...
Okay, but that's why I'm talking about a...
not a solution,
but like this calculation of how much
someone's opinion should matter.
Okay, I admit...
I think saying opinion matters
is poisoning the well here,
because I was on board until you were saying that
the more people watch my stuff,
the more their comments matter.
I don't think that necessarily is the case.
But those people have the information.
Look, if you want to do like IQ test
to see the people with the highest IQ
who watch my comments,
I'm fine with that too.
But that's be practical, Tom, goddammit.
Come on, stop suggesting crazy things.
Yeah, I think my point was more about like,
like in general,
not to take everything you see at face value,
but I just had this thought a while ago
and I can't remember how I put it in words,
so it's kind of like muddled,
and I don't know whether it's actually
what you're saying, Nate.
Here's...
Okay, they could be slightly different.
Here's a broad criticism
of everything you've ever said, Nate,
in your entire life.
Sure.
I think, I mean,
you're putting your content out there.
You got to do that with the understanding
that it's there for the general audience
and the general audience consume,
is comprised of a broad spectrum of people,
some of which are real dum-dums,
some of which just don't care about
not acting like dum-dums,
and you just got to understand
you're going to get shit comments
and I don't see the point of complaining.
The way that I think about this...
Guys here, we just want to elevate the people who are dum.
It wouldn't...
They're not going to be elevated.
Those people aren't going to listen.
There's no point.
You just got to go with the flow.
You got to go into this being aware
and go with the flow on it.
I absolutely do.
Which is why, I don't know,
I feel like I could make...
To people who really know my content,
I could make all kinds of racial jokes
and be incredibly dark jokes and stuff,
but I choose not to do that kind of stuff
in my main videos for exactly this reason.
I don't expect everyone to have full context
all the time.
So yeah, I get it,
but I still think it is a purely reasonable thing
to suggest that just as we would treat
the opinion on, I don't know,
the rising ocean levels in the world,
we would trust an oceanographer
with his opinion on that more than a commenter,
like just a random man off the street
who runs a hot dog joint or whatever.
I respect the hot dog profession immensely,
but nonetheless, I think the oceanographers
were qualified.
I guess this commenter rule is white
until you think you know a bit more
about what you're saying.
I guess it goes back into understand.
Refer to my formula, everyone.
Refer to the formula.
When I say commenter rules,
and I say about banning commenters,
I want to clarify the fact that
that is all that I wish,
that they do not act like this in my vicinity.
I would never get Obama on the phone
and lock these people up for making a comment
that I don't approve of,
and there's no empirical objective law here
that they have broken and validated,
and therefore they are a bad person
who deserves to be ostracized for the rest of society,
for the rest of their fucking miserable lives.
They don't deserve to be ostracized,
but they do deserve to be Auschwitz-sized.
That's what I want for all of them.
All that I want here
is when I have the power,
which I do in this context,
I would like to use my power
in ways that I think is justified and good.
If I was CEO of YouTube,
I wouldn't ban someone for these reasons,
because the terms of service,
there's no law they're breaking here.
These are societal things
that I just wish that was upon the people.
And there are people who have turned it not dumb.
The old Fag PCP fans are incredible,
and they are great commenters
because they've listened to commenter rules.
Exactly what I'm talking about.
I've seen people become better commenters
because of that video,
and they take it to heart,
and so there's a real benefit to saying these things.
Maybe not to the swabs of the unwashed masses,
but if I could make one person think the way I do,
that's what I want to do in life.
I want people to be like me.
That's my goal here.
If you're saying that my rule is too vague
and impractical and won't,
like, I don't know, you can't enforce it or whatever,
it doesn't make any sense, then so be it.
But God damn it, I'll continue to dream.
I'll continue.
I'll never stop.
Ben, no matter what you do to me,
no matter how mad you hurt my feelings.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Your feelings are grass and I'm the mower.
I thought you were going to say catano or something cool.
Don't have been sick, dude.
I do always agree that it is usually the creator's fault.
The commenters do deserve leeway,
and they deserve the benefit of that just as much as we do.
But I think there's a compromise here that can be obtained.
It would be better if commenters were smart for their own good
because they wouldn't be retarded anymore.
It brings me back to, like, if I made...
I talk all the time about how I want the betterment of humanity,
but if I just, like, made a joke one time about, like,
yeah, blah, blah, blah, I want to literally kill all humans.
And, like, just for whatever reason,
that clip gets shared around and they're like,
oh, look at, like, evil mass murderer,
you know, wannabe best guy ever.
And then, like, a news story sparks because of that.
Like, that would be people being ignorant of, like,
what I actually think.
And it reminds me of the PewDiePie thing.
That's, like, what happened to PewDiePie.
People who didn't know shit about the context of the guy,
just, like, taking his jokes at the context.
Well, that comes back to just taking...
to giving a generous interpretation
to the things you have no context of.
When is something inflammatory like that?
I guess I would just say that the rules for a good comment
are pretty similar to the rules for just being, like,
a worthwhile person in general.
Like, if you run your mouth about something
that you have no context of and no idea what you're talking about,
then, yeah, you look like an idiot and your comment is bad.
Like, if someone is, like,
Nate said that women are bad,
then it's, like, well, okay.
Which I do.
But he does it all the time and it's a joke.
I mean, if they had more context and they were, like,
well, I know that he's making all these jokes,
but, you know, I don't like that he makes these jokes
for these and these reasons, and they have, like, a well-formed...
Like, that's two different stories.
Absolutely.
So just know what you're talking about
in the YouTube comments section and in life.
Just the other day, I got a letter on one of my weaguas,
like, from a girl who's, like, uncomfortable
with my, like, jokes about Hillary and stuff.
And I just explain how, you know, like, I think it's all good fun.
I'm not trying to hurt anybody's feelings.
And I, like, I just gave, like, a thoughtful thing
and a lot of people commented and said, like,
dude, we really respect you for, you know, treating it this way
and not just, like, shitting on her.
And I respect her for, like, not just shitposting,
but, like, this is two people trying to understand each other better.
And that's what I like as opposed to shit-slinging,
you know, just by respect.
And that was a comment that was critical of your content.
And that didn't mean it was a bad comment.
Yep. Yeah, it was a great comment.
I think that's something that's so lost on internet discourse
that I really wish wasn't, is that instead of just
immediately going to, like, trying to meme it out
and, like, shit on people, just, like, have that dialogue,
because then you're nine times out of ten,
you're gonna come to an amicable understanding of some sort,
even if they're still disagreements,
like, well, at least I understand where they're coming from.
Just, like, imagine you met this person in real life.
You would never say these sorts of things to them.
And, like, you know, like, guys like, like,
like, Mumki, for example, it seems to me,
like, the difference between us who, like,
are talking about rules and stuff, we, like,
haven't given up on internet discourse,
whereas guys like him, and, like, a lot of people
on 4chan are like, they're like, it's all a joke, you know?
It doesn't matter. None of it's relevant.
It's all completely goofy. Whereas, I think, at least,
I feel, and I think this is shared, that we think we can,
we can rescue this. Like, there is good to be found here.
I don't think we can... Yeah, yeah.
There is good. I don't think we can rescue it.
But that doesn't mean that it's worthless.
Fair enough. Fair enough.
I think it can be improved.
I think you can cultivate a nice place
on your own channel, at least. Yeah, I suppose.
Yeah, I guess, I guess I've seen that.
I think for me, it's less about trying to, like,
change everything on a macro scale,
and just, like, choosing the kind of people
I want to interact with. Sure.
But, you know, every, every one of these small changes
affects the large degree, you know?
I totally believe in changing yourself to better the world.
I'm totally in that, and I feel that applies to you.
Like, just to speak in defense of Monkey,
like, I think that his, his, his ideas are fine too.
Like, his comments are like a shit show,
but there's kind of, like, some funny shit there as well.
Well, that's how he likes it, and that's totally fine, of course.
Yeah, and he's the creator, and he wants that to be the case.
So there's no, there's absolutely no problem there.
I, for one, would not like those comments to be
on the PCP channel anymore, but that doesn't mean they're,
you know, like, like, the reason those were made,
is because they thought those were good comments,
because, you know, that Monkey likes them.
So, you know, I don't think they were made in ill will.
You know, all, all of the, like, mean, like,
fuck you, Monkey comments, all those are made in good will,
because that's what he likes, and that's what he promotes.
It's, it's a good time, or, you know,
I don't want, I don't want to speak for him or anything, you know?
But that's why this place is transpiring here.
It's a difference of, of ideas about how to approach this,
this subject, which is totally fine.
You know, you know, these are just boxes of ideas.
Just don't, don't, don't limit yourself to just one.
You know, atheism, Christianity, new age beliefs,
you know, just pack them all together.
Pick and choose and build your own theism.
It's great.
Yeah!
It's like, it's like you're playing Minecraft,
and these are your materials.
You can just build yourself a house, build yourself whatever the fuck you want.
That's what, that's what it is.
Well, I only understand things in Minecraft terms.
I think we understand each other pretty well.
Um, if there's, I mean, I think,
I guess we could talk all day about this, but...
Well, I have one more rule.
I was going to suggest going on to questions,
but okay, I don't mean to...
I have one more rule.
And it's, it's kind of a short one because it's,
it's kind of funny and silly, but it's, um,
please swear more if you're going to be pretentious.
Um, one thing I hate, like, like,
you know how, you know, in the early days of the Internet,
it was all like fuck, and that was like a big deal.
Sure.
Like people would swear and they could do it now.
They could swear in front of people,
and they could say swears and their parents weren't seeing.
And like that was the thing.
And there was swears everywhere.
And then it was sort of like, oh, uh,
swears are for babies.
Like if you really want to get someone,
you have to be a pretentious, know-it-all idiot
who just types a lot of big words from the dictionary
in the thesaurus, and you look like a cunt,
and I don't like you.
You're just really annoying me.
Side note there.
But a well-placed, a well-placed, um, swear word is hilarious.
If you had your really pretentious, annoying comment,
you know, smarmingly like brushing everything I said aside,
and then at the end said, get fucked.
It would make it better for me to read,
and I would be like, yeah, alright.
You got me.
Side note from that, I love big words,
and I hate this vilification of big words.
I like reading old stuff because there's big old words.
What does that mean?
Big words are fun and funny,
but if you use them wrong, the consequences are dire.
So use big words, but only appropriately.
You have to really understand the words.
You have to read them and understand what the synonyms are,
and then just, you know, pick one of those.
It'll be great.
I have a rule that may just apply to me.
I don't know if anyone else will agree with this.
It's being edgy for the sake of being edgy.
And keep in mind, that does not mean don't be edgy.
I am edgy.
I like saying kill yourself.
That's real good.
I like that.
But I think that, at least from my perspective,
there's a couple times where I think I see comments
in my comment section, especially,
where people will just tack on edgy, kill yourself things.
I don't think that's the tone of what they're trying to say,
and they're just trying to say that to look cool or cute.
This is just like, guys, you don't have to be mean.
Be mean if you want to, but you don't have to be.
That's not the thing that you have to be.
I don't like you more because you say kill yourself
or you fucking hack or something.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
It's like a foe, you're swearing or you're being edgy
for the comedy, but it's not right.
Can we compare that to a rule along the lines of,
if you're an internet tough guy, you get an internet time out.
Something along those lines, you know?
I mean, you know.
I don't know how to enforce that, but we'll find a way.
We'll find less harsh rules because they wouldn't ban someone
for being like this.
All of these rules are just guidelines.
Oh shit, I forgot.
We didn't really define, we talked about deleting comments
and turning off comments.
We didn't really talk about banning people from comments,
which I guess is we could simply say,
if you violate enough rules, enough times, or enough egregious ways,
then you're just eligible to get banned.
That's a long time offender sort of thing.
If you show a lack of good faith
and an indefatigable propensity to see big words,
they're cool and I'm great, I'm the smartest.
If you show a strong proclivity towards just shit comments
and not knowing what you're talking about,
then I think you should be banned and there's nothing wrong with that.
Agreed, very much agreed.
And so just like, you can be nice.
You don't have to be mean guys.
You don't have to treat the internet
as a sewer for poo poo words, everybody.
It can be a nice place, you know?
It can be.
It's difficult to be the nice person saying,
I really like that video thumbs up.
That's hard to write because your mom will kiss you
and then you'll feel bad.
Yeah, exactly.
And I only have one last one.
I don't know if anyone else has a rule.
I've been carrying this.
Thank you, everyone.
This is specifically for me.
This rule is in relation to ones.
A very integral part of my...
The people have been craving this one.
Yeah, I have a very...
I'm very torn with this.
In and of myself.
Because on one hand,
I like scrolling down the Deagle Nation lecture
and just seeing thousands of people
with just a wall of ones.
Just like that's it.
Just a wall, a title wave of ones.
Well, you know, sometimes there will be videos
that I also want to see the discussion of Deagle Nation.
And that comment section is really a beautiful mesh.
Because here's, I think, how you do it the best way.
You press one for as long as you want to,
you hold that sucker down,
you do some ASCII.
You make a big one out of a lot of little ones
and you ask you out of ones.
All that sort of great stuff.
And then you just do comma or enter.
And then type your other comment there.
I don't want there to be ever...
A lot of people, our contemporaries,
would not like a lot of the ones there.
But I like the ones. I like it when you press one.
Also, please make another...
Don't make another comment.
Make just one comment, please.
Can we put down the language for this one
as something along the lines of,
when you press one, you may also comment after said one.
Something along those lines.
You may also press two.
If you're feeling saucy.
You just call the rule pressing one is only step one.
Oh, that's a good one. That's a good one.
I like that a lot.
That's an invitation to keep going.
That being said, a press one, everyone.
Indeed.
Take that first step.
I just have a rule just to sum up.
I don't know if this actually was in the first batch of rules,
but again, just want to reiterate.
The rule is this comment section is not your home.
You have no rights.
Your ability to comment is a privilege.
I just want to put that in stone.
That belongs on their side.
Indeed.
Well, sick.
Questions?
Let's skedaddle on over to the PCP Patreon Lounge.
This is all the people who aren't bad commenters.
These guys are good. They're real good.
They have given us money and gone into the exclusive PCP.
You know what?
Even if they were bad commenters,
they've purchased annulments via their Patreon Lounge.
I was just going to say that.
That's exactly right, guys.
We should add this as an incentive.
You get an immediate comment or violation annulment
by pledging to the PCP Patreon without a doubt.
That's official.
There you go. If you want to cleanse yourself.
If you ever leave, if you ever sin again,
you just need to up your pledge and it gets refreshed.
Just keep that in mind, everybody.
Before we get to the premium delicious,
decadent Patreon Lounge questions,
why don't you read the dirty, disgusting,
malaria riddled, yellow fever,
you know, jungle fever, a Twitter question.
Sounds good.
The token Twitter question.
It is the token one at this point.
Everybody, just so you know, this is at at TP Crasinators,
our Twitter accounts, every Saturday when we record these,
around four or five, we send out the full thing
with hashtag askPCP.
Just send questions using that hashtag and we'll read them.
Here we go.
Where did that go?
What are some good Patreons to donate to?
I can think of only one.
Only one.
My one.
Patreon.com slash save me.
Obviously, the question is all of us.
But you know, if you've got some money left over,
obviously donate your entire wallet to us.
But if you have some left over,
that for some reason you can't give to us,
what are some other creators we want to give to us?
That's the question.
I actually have a real answer for this.
There's one.
What's it called?
I actually have been a patron for a long time.
I'm pledging $1 a month to Japanese emoticons.me.
They make like $7 a month.
So I'm like a significant percentage of their...
Would you give them five bucks or something?
No, I give them one.
I give them $1.
Actually, I used to use Japanese emojis all the time.
I haven't in a while, and that's probably a big mistake.
I should definitely max revive those.
I don't know, it's just a site with a repository of great,
hilarious emojis, or emoticons, rather.
And I just like, wow, they make $7 a month for hosting all this stuff.
If notable homeless man Ben St. can give to a patron,
so can you, noble viewer, noble listener.
True, indeed.
I have a little YouTuber that I famously on my Twitter
have recently eaten top ramen while listening to,
called Brain For Breakfast,
who makes some real cool CGP grave videos,
but they're better, and I like them more.
So there you go.
He makes superior CGP grave videos with CGP gray in them,
but his are better, right?
Yeah, he makes geography shit.
So there you go, I like him.
He's making like $200 or something.
So like similar content to like the...
Brain For Breakfast, yeah.
Educational country things,
and he uses pulling ball because he's a hack and can't drive, yes.
I love pulling ball, excellent meme.
Yeah, he's a good guy.
Anyone else?
I would never give money to anyone, so no, not for me.
You can't forget about the classic Dr. Wolf.
Oh, no doubt.
That was a joke, ladies and gentlemen.
Do not even think about looking at that.
I patron, or I used to patron, hot diggity demon.
I feel like that is like a good investment
because those cartoons are like really good,
early animated.
I appreciate the work that goes into them a lot.
I've actually been, you know, there's this one creator I'm following.
Actually, it's these two brothers I've been following since like 2013
and they've really gone downhill and I haven't posted in a while.
But I'm just waiting for the day they come back.
It's called T... I forget the name of it.
It's something long, you know, T-B-something.
Anyway, go try and search them up.
They used to do pulling reviews and I'm a real big fan of them.
I've been patroning them for a real couple of long years now.
Now they're just hosting some shitty knockoff content
from the Rowdyfuckers cartoon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know what's up with that.
What a bunch of bullshit that is.
But frankly, it's disgusting.
You know what?
I realize, sometimes I am tempted to give to patrons.
The only people I respect on Patreon, the only people,
are the people who make gated content
because they're the only ones who ever tempt me
to actually pledge that I love you.
Like me.
Yeah, I have been tempted to pledge you so I can see those pages.
Like me and my speed draw videos
and my early pages and my beta testing period
for the game that's out now on stcomics.com.
I'm a proud patron of patreon.com.
You are.
It's very early on.
And I love you a lot.
And I would love you too, viewers.
Yeah, if you pledged.
Yeah, I made a deliberate...
Well, I went out of my way.
I wasn't making the speed draw videos, for example,
but I was like, I should really make some gated content.
Stuff that people that aren't interested
aren't going to be mad that they're not going to see,
but people that are interested will be like,
yes, I'm getting my money's worth.
I'm actually getting something for my pledge.
And that's been pretty sick.
I don't know if it works, but hopefully...
You hear viewers, if you donate to patreon.com.com.
been saying he will love you more than he loves Munchy.
Only if you donate more than Munchy.
Which is a lot.
I think Munchy's donating about $100.
That's the number to beat everyone.
Is it also incorrect to say that the Champion Chapter 1
will be fully out when people are hearing this podcast?
It was out as of last week when the...
Yes, correct.
Yes, so by the time this post, it will have been out for a week
over at stcomics.com.
There's your warning, folks.
Stay away from that website.
But I'll be starting Vapor's Chapter 3 soon,
and that will probably be Patreon exclusive until it's done,
so if you want to see that...
Is this the one about the girl?
It will be about the girl.
Every single time Patreon comes up,
I don't like the fact that my Patreon URL is my name,
so I never say it.
I really should change it to Hippocrite,
but I don't know if I can at this point.
I thought the point of that was that you didn't want
you to tie down to Hippocrite.
I know, and that's the thing, because it's like,
what else the fuck will I use it for?
Just do Hippocrite. I think that makes sense.
And then you can change it again if you need to.
It will be Patreon.com slash Hippocrite.
The same as everything else.
By the way, the reason I brought up Gated Content
is I do want to salute the
various porn Patreon people
who I check in on.
Yes, that's right, everybody.
This is one guy, Pinoy Toons.
Pinoy Toons. I like him a lot.
He makes very sexual drawings
that I very enjoy with my penis.
It's weird.
It's this weird brand of pornography.
The very sexy pornography.
I would not agree.
That's right.
Shout out to him for Gating Content
within the demo of his porn game.
That piece of shit with the free version.
In the middle of a fucking sex scene,
he put the second part of it behind a fucking gate.
I hated him so much, but I honestly
respect him for having that audacity
to just fuck me over like that.
Like a piece of shit.
If you ever want to know what makes
my stomach boil and my hair fall out
and my fucking body turn to dust.
It's looking at the Patreon
who's getting paid the most
and having all the porn people
and having all the actual people
with real intellectual content
making one-fourth of the stuff
that the fucking disgusting porn people are making.
When is our wonderful red-pilled warrior Patreon
overlords going to come down
on those filthy porn makers
like they promised they would in ages ago?
When is that going to happen?
Are they not doing porn anymore?
I'd say they were changing their policy at some point.
You can't do any live action porn
and any
risqu drawn porn
will get you shut the fuck down.
You can't make risqu drawings
on this website.
Are you implying that you can make non-risqu drawn porn?
I don't understand the distinction there.
The terms that they said
is anything that was like
rape or B.C. Alley
or anything like French shit.
You're not allowed to draw.
You can do that missionary shit
no problem and that's fine.
What the fuck is that bullshit?
That's the weirdest kind of context possible.
It is pretty stupid.
I just love vanilla.
I guess they just want to make vanilla porn.
Well, cool.
The absolute cowards.
Across the board demolish them is what I say.
Anything even the tiniest bit risqu.
Anything that can be confused for risqu.
If you want to know more
I made a great video on my channel
where I'm talking about this called
Jack vs. Jack in it.
It was great.
Oh, I watched that.
10 out of 10.
Excellent.
Here's something that we've discussed
among ourselves recently a lot.
Too much to a heated extent.
From Jackboy
in the patron lounge.
When do you guys think the PCPHQ will happen
and then no
proper grammar or syntax
after we're just I'm gay?
Well done.
I'm glad you're comfortable with that.
He's here and he's ready to stay.
I don't know, dude.
Maybe within the next year?
I mean, plans are...
Keep an eye out around May of next year.
I'm just going to level with you.
The more money you give us
the sooner it's going to happen.
You're not wrong. It's true.
That is true.
I don't know how much you open your wallet
is when this shit's going to go down.
It is a major operation
to readjust our entire lives
if we're going to make this happen.
It's a big thing. It's going to take a while.
People need to get established
and financial security has to happen for a lot of people.
It will happen piece by piece, I am sure,
when it finally does start to happen.
It won't be a sudden change.
If you want that insider info
really the key players
you have to look with your binoculars
to see and digi
and wherever they go
then that's where it's going to be.
They unfortunately decide
the fate of our lives.
Yeah. Well, I am 100%
committed. It is my goal in life
so we'll see and it's just a matter of
the financial things being where they need to be
so more money the faster it happens
legitimately. It's not a joke.
It is my goal in life.
Any more questions?
I'm scrolling through. These are pretty bad.
These are not very nice.
They're not very choice.
I can check out the
Twitter if we want to go...
No, no.
They got there. We threw them their bone.
It's kind of silly
how the people in the Patreon lounge
they just throw away that chance of getting the questions
to us.
I don't understand.
No, that's a terrible question. Never mind.
Wait, okay.
We've been going a while. I'm ready to call it.
Let's do one more here.
From the Twitter.
Here we go.
At L33CH
I think it's like Leech.
With numbers and shit.
At Leech asks, should we have a public execution
of all crippled people?
Specifically to you, Ben.
Great question.
I'm leaning towards you.
And that's all for today.
No further comments.
Resounding yes. Goodbye.
All right. Well, okay.
On that front, thanks for listening everybody.
Make sure you pledge to our patrons.
Preferably, once you read a dictionary
or grow a brain or a soul,
please, so you can ask good questions.
Indeed.
I've said it before and I'll say it again.
They have money, but not necessarily
wit.
Slammed. Fucking slammed.
And of course, people, don't forget.
$5 pledge is getting access to all the bonus
episodes. There will be nine out
by the time this comes out.
So that'll be very exciting.
Very exciting.
All right. Bye.
Hang on. We got red bubble stuff.
You can buy merch. We got PCB logos.
We got stickers. Check out Hippocrates Twitter.
He's using those, putting them on things.
Extremely helpful.
Check out my Twitter for that information.
Yeah, he's using them.
Is there anything else I'm missing?
We're on iTunes and Google Play.
I do it every week. It's a lot of effort.
Listen to it so it's not wasted.
Thank you very much, Tom.
All right. Thanks for listening, everybody.
We'll see you next week.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Gross.
Yeah.
I'm supposed to
be working right now.
I'm supposed
to be working
right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.