And a one, and a two, and a baby on board, how I've adored, and a sign on my car's window
pad.
You guys like The Simpsons?
Not enough to get that reference, I guess.
Yeah, baby, yeah.
Okay.
Alright.
You guys ever watch, you ever see The Real Jims on YouTube?
No.
Oh, I do.
The Conspiracy Man?
Well, not Conspiracy Man, but like, that series of Who Killed Mr. Burns, all the possible.
Is that the guy?
That's his best.
Yeah, he did, though.
He has a series of Simpsons Mysteries, but he's pretty much stopped doing those because
he kind of like ran through them all.
He hasn't done one of those in a while.
Now he just does like, now mainly he does like, classic episode analyses of like, you
know, one like, um, um, I don't know, someone with a-
Simpsons Well-known Facts.
Yeah.
107 Facts You Didn't Care to Know.
No, no, he doesn't do those, but he'll do like a character breakdown, like he'll like,
give you the whole history of like, Barney Gumbel or Edna Krabapal, which is interesting
because like, you know, I stopped watching when I was like, you know, 18 or so.
Did you know that Edna Krabapal went on to fucking marry Ned Flanders?
Ah, well, wow, wow, he's out.
And then die?
Wait, Edna died?
Yes, because her actress died in real life.
So they sort of imply that the character died, too.
Oh.
So Ned Flanders, so yes, which sucks.
So Ned Flanders has had, his two of his wives have died.
Oh boy, oh boy.
Well, what do you know?
And I thought coronavirus was sad.
Oh.
But the Simpsons is even sad.
Welcome to the Procrastinators podcast.
It's 8, 9, 2020 and we are feeling, we are feeling fine this morning.
Um, uh, how's everyone, how's everyone doing?
How's it hanging?
Doing all right.
I have an announcement to make before I forget, because I just, I just checked and it says
nothing to, does not be plugging anything, anything for me.
It's for, it's for the podcast itself.
I would like to announce that the Procrastinators podcast, we have all our videos back as, as
has been well stated, but because of that, the migration is complete.
All of the Procrastinators channel is mirrored on library.tv.
So if there's ever any problems like that again, every video now and in the future will
be automatically mirrored at this link as I forget to go and show it on, show it on
the screen.
Eleazar.
Put it on screen.
Go up on the screen.
Eleazar.
Eleazar, please.
Thank you.
It's all there.
It's all delicious.
It even, it even took our, our channel banner and everything in the, I could mirror it all
that too.
We didn't have to set any of it up at just one click.
You can import your entire YouTube channel.
It just does it.
I, wait, I, I have not actually, why is it Procrastinators colon eight?
That's just a thing for the, the, the URL.
You can take that out of the store.
Can I, can I take that out of the store works?
Okay.
Library.tv slash at the Procrastinator.
How does this work then?
Cause all of this video stuff has to be stored somewhere.
Uh, well, what I did is that library is like this decentralized, you know, it's even got
the tags.
Yeah.
It's got everything.
And so you just log in with your, your Google account, you pick the channel and it'll just
automatically import everything on the channel and going forward, it automatically mirrors
everything uploaded to YouTube.
Well it lasts forever.
Uh, there's only one way to find out.
Yeah.
Just be alive forever.
Live forever and wait and see, I guess.
So they haven't, they haven't suffered the, uh, the other YouTube alternative fates yet.
So we'll see how long they last, but when the channel went down and then when all the
videos were down, you like the, you immediately were like, God, we should have archived it
on library.
Yeah.
I was like, what's, what's that?
Now you know, it's just, it's just a, it's a YouTube, an open YouTube site.
They have like a desktop app and everything and we have to open it up on the web.
It's crazy.
It's crazy stuff.
Yeah.
I'm watching episode 150, 185, Pokemon sucks right now from, from back in the day.
Forget that classic episode.
Yeah.
We were talking about, uh, Pokemon that sun and moon and or Pokemon go and or sword and
shield, you know, one of the many times we have said Pokemon sucks, who knows, who knows.
It's, it's pretty cool.
And if you have a YouTube channel and you're always worried about your shit getting bloated
up, uh, maybe something to worth doing, it's, it's one click pretty much.
Just make an account and click a button and then it'll do all the work for you.
And who can complain about that?
Sounds good to me.
Uh, we have a, we have a couple of episodes that have been like a handful of episodes
have been like restricted or removed.
You might, might re upload those at some point, like, um, and the end of end of YouTube
one was taken down, I think.
And, uh, what was the other one that was just, it was just like taken down like two days
ago.
Do you guys remember?
I, I said in the chat, was it a Ghibli cast or was it, yes, yes, it was the get one of
the Ghibli cast, the Ghibli cast got taken down for who'd fucking knows why.
Well, it was copyright, but like, yeah, yeah, whatever, but I feel like years.
It annoys me just sort of like when YouTube was young and it was like, wow, you can upload
video.
Wow.
You can upload so much video and, and it's for free.
And it's like, this is a whole 10 minute video on the internet.
Yeah.
And I was like, this would be a really handy way to archive video footage of things.
If you ever wanted to do that, if you needed to place to store lots of video, YouTube is
the place.
It is absolutely the, like the rickety bridge, like the wood is rotten, the rope is like
about to snap.
There's no safety.
You can't ever consider putting anything on YouTube and expecting it to stick around.
It may as well be a Snapchat video.
It's so temporary feeling.
Does it, Tom, does it mirror, does it mirror our streams?
Um, I'm not sure.
I can see the Radcon 4 Royal Rumble.
So that was a stream that turned into a video.
As long as they turned into a video, I think they get mirrored.
Oh no, but like, what about like, what about like, uh, uh, what was the, like, cozy, cozy
late night stream or whatever it was called?
They all still get married?
The late night casual stream.
Yeah.
Late night.
For instance, one like that.
It's right here.
Well that was only 33 minutes.
I didn't think I was awake for that one.
That was ghosting.
Maybe, maybe that's because that was one of the ones we re-uploaded because we had, because
they all died.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure about the, uh, the fucking, I mean, you can manually upload everything
that doesn't automatically give me.
What about the, what about, for instance, the, uh, the, the, the checkers for charity?
I think that's here.
If that's there, because that one is definitely a stream and not a, not re-uploaded a video.
I don't see it.
Oh, the mavericks are not here.
Hmm.
No.
Oh, no.
Well.
Fringe.
Well, okay, nothing's perfect.
No, nothing is perfect.
I, I personally, uh, uh, saved like every one of those streams that got deleted to a,
uh, I don't know if I have all of them like ever, but I have like all of those ones saved
to a, actually, I think it's to the same external hard drive that Vic gave me with the, um, the
radcon footage on it because it had a lot of extra space on it.
Uh, it's just so like, you couldn't really sell like a physical media print of the procrastinators
for post, posterity.
You couldn't like sell a Blu-ray disc with all of the content.
I mean, maybe you could fit it all on there if you had the podcast as audio only, but
like, there's, there's lots of the podcasts that have editing in them and there's, there's
you couldn't, you can't save like that much stuff, uh, in physical media.
It has to be digital somewhere and everywhere it feels so trepidatious.
What, what if we release the pro, the PCP, the PCP DVD box PCP DVD, that name alone is
pretty good.
I know, right?
Oh, that alone makes me want to do it.
Well, that on the fact that we could sell it for money, the PCP CD DVD.
I think it's time.
I think it's time we get started.
I want, I want, what about PCP VHS, VCR, please?
PCP 64.
Uh, thousands and thousands of cassettes.
Uh, I want it on laser disc.
Remember laser disc?
I remember from that, that one.
Yeah, that one, angry video game nerd video.
I had, Tom, you're not, you're only a year younger than me.
So I'm surprised you don't remember, but like my school had a couple of like fucking
videos on laser disc and they would, yeah, they had like fucking schoolhouse rock or
whatever on laser disc or like some like science documentary.
And they were just, well, I mean, does having laser disc means you're not shitty?
I mean, laser discs, when they came out were pretty dope.
This was, I mean, they just, they, this was like, it was like a CD, but like the size
of a record.
Right.
Every time I saw it, I was like, I can't believe.
They were powerful.
They, they were imposing.
They still are imposing.
You look at them now, you get pretty fucking scared, like, oh, yeah, they'll fuck, they'll
fucking kill you.
Yeah.
You'll die.
If you, if you even fucking think about laser in the title, you could discuss them through
someone's entire head.
Yeah, I think, I think so.
If you were, if you were committed, if you were really committed to the bit, right, I
want to talk about the last week, uh, last week I, I announced that I would be streaming
some draw streams on twitch.tv slash Gibb and take.
And I have been doing that the past week, every day for like eight hours each time.
Uh, I did it.
I did a bunch of that and I drew 53 pages worth of sketches.
53 pages in a week, even just sketches.
That's a power.
Is a lot.
That's incredible.
Is a lot and I'm very impressed.
Yeah, same.
I don't want to say, because I have, I have tuned in to see here and there, uh, what you've
been working on.
And, uh, I said in the, in the chat, but I'll say it again, your poses are getting really
good.
You're, you're, you're, I'll see you drawing like something and I'm always like, oh wow,
like, um, the fit, like I can really feel like the way the figure is moving in space.
And I'm like, good, I like it.
It's like the trickiest thing to do in drawing.
So.
Yeah.
I, I feel like that was, uh, I feel like that's something that I, that I picked up at some
point and, and like it was, I think I remember Digi being impressed at like at Bronycon, like
the first Bronycon that we all went to when we all did the, the comics jam.
I think I remember Digi being like, whoa, like there's like whole comic panels and like
there you can, you know, there's a sense of motion.
I was like, yeah, I have captured a sense of motion here.
Yeah.
That is an important thing to do, uh, when, uh, creating graven images.
Uh, uh, so I don't know.
Yeah.
It's like, yeah.
Dude.
Not only to do the draw, you know, do the drawings and occasionally be like, oh, I'm so fucking
based.
I drew that in like two minutes.
Oh yeah.
Uh, but also that I get to celebrate live and have people in the chat.
So I say yes, and I nod to myself.
Um, and it's like, I can go through like if there's a bit that I'm stuck on, like I'm
not sure how to get from panel A to panel B in the amount of space I have left in the
page or something.
And, uh, you know, I explain out loud what I'm thinking, what my, uh, my thought process
is, and it's good just for me to say that out loud so that I can, cause it just sort
of makes it easier to figure out the solutions.
And other people sometimes they, they give suggestions and I'm like, oh, that's a good
idea.
So it's like, it's, it's, it's great.
I, I feel accomplished having done that, um, the, the, the idea of it being for the
Tezuka manga competition, uh, I'm not sure still whether I'd be able to get it done in
time, especially now that it seems to be too many pages long, the story I have, I would
need to like cut out a lot of what I've done, uh, or like completely rewrite the story such
that it doesn't have as much stuff in it.
And I'm like, that's going to take its, that's going to take time in itself.
If I take the time to rewrite it so that it fits in 55 pages, I probably won't also have
time to finish it, uh, so that it looks good because the, the, uh, thing is like not accepting
unfinished works or drafts, so it has to look finished.
So I'm like, I don't know quite what to do at the moment.
I'm definitely going to finish whatever this is, but whether or not it goes into the contest
I'm not sure.
Part of me is like, I really want to submit something just so that I can say I entered
and, and whatever, but I don't know how, whether I'd be okay with like changing the nature
of things in order to make it happen.
Hmm.
Um, do you think what if you, you would, you would have to make like a Clarissa abridged
in which you kind of just go in and then like, just look kind of selectively pick like the
least important pages and like pull them out and like, I don't know.
Maybe that wouldn't work.
Maybe that wouldn't work at all.
I looked through it and maybe it would kind of work and you could kind of get the story
across.
I mean, I've looked through it and it seems like the biggest save would be like speed
running save is, is to change the size of some of the panels so that more of them can
fit on a single page.
That's a whole lot of like re, like, like moving everything around.
And yeah, every time you make it in adjustment, everything else would move backwards.
No, all you've solved it.
All you do is you just take, you just take the whole page and shrink it down to one
fourth size and just put four pages on one page.
And then 80 pages becomes 20 pages.
Of course.
Incredible.
That's, that's so stupid.
It might work.
Thank you.
I mean, it technically would definitely work.
Yeah, I guess for this next week, I'm going to see if I can finish all the
sketches for the thing.
I'm thinking it's, you know, the, the rate I'm going, it's going to be like 80,
maybe a hundred pages and then I'll be like, okay, I have all of the story.
I'll try and chop and change it.
And if I can, if I can do like squishing all of the panels to be.
That's just the thing though, I think what I'm going to do is if I, if I go down
that road and I try to make it fit in the right amount, it's going to be worse.
It's just going to be bad because of a lot of things just, they work like I
considered what happens when you turn the page and you see something for the first
time and what pages are seen next to each other.
And so if I move everything around, that's going to be lost.
And there's also some panels that cross over other panels.
So I can't move everything around.
So it's like, it's going to be like a shittier version, but a contest approved
version, maybe.
And then later I can make the real version, which is good.
And, and, and that'll be that.
Yeah.
I think I can do it.
Just, just cut it in half and just give him half of it and then just put it to
be continued.
I mean, I was thinking about that because like at 50 page 52 or 53, everything's
going well, you know, confrontations happen, but then Clarissa gets captured
and she's in prison.
There's like a shot of her in prison.
She thinks about where her horse was and it's outside like mingling with the goats.
And then it's the panel of her just saying, hmm, I want my hat.
I could cut it off there and that'd be the end like a comedy.
Like she just fails and she's in prison the end and I could submit that.
If you just put it, if you just put it to be continued, like, like, uh, I mean,
I think it's, I don't think it's allowed, but I'd probably do it.
I mean, it's not allowed because it's supposed to be a complete, they say in
the, in the rules, a complete story within certain amount of pages.
So it implied that it's, I don't think, I don't think you'd get disqualified or
anything for that.
How, how, how hypocritical of them, their entire business model revolves around
throwing could be to be continues at you.
I know it's week by week, but it's strange because like have to make a complete story.
I read, I was a few months ago, I was reading Tezuka submissions.
Um, the one I knew about was odors wanted, which was, or no, romance dawn,
which is a version of, um, one piece before one piece.
And that has a complete story in it.
But, uh, you know, it ends in a satisfying way with the, the, the villain
that was introduced is defeated.
And then they, you know, Luffy and Nami go, oh, her name was something else,
Ruby or something.
They go their separate ways and that's the end.
So it's like implied that there could be more.
So that, I think that's what they mean is that whatever is set up gets resolved.
But in this, the villain gets set up and, um, it ends with Clarissa in jail and
presumably nothing changes and she fails and it's a bad ending.
If I, if it ends there.
What about, what if he's the second half?
No beginning.
It starts in medius res.
Um, I mean, I guess you haven't drawn the second half yet.
Yeah.
I don't even know whether I'm, I'm probably more than halfway at this point.
There's like a fucking, what's the deadline?
Deadline is the first of September at 12 PM or AM, Japan time.
So, you know, none of this will matter.
None of this deliberation will matter if I can't ink 50 or so pages within the
three weeks or two weeks I would have, which is a lot.
Yeah.
Although an awful lot.
It is an awful lot.
I, I don't think I have the, the power in me to do, to go that quick.
How long, how long does it take you to, how long does it take you to ink a page?
Um, well, a lot of ghosts, what was I doing?
I was like 20 pages per week, a day per week.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's about that.
I was going really, really hard on, on, on that.
Um, the first, in January, actually.
Started the year, started a brand new world where I'm drawing so hard that my
hand breaks off and it's, I got a new hand now as a robot hand.
What's sick.
Teach me jelly, jealous.
Okay.
So yeah, I don't know.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm thinking, I'm thinking I'll see what I can do in this next week.
If I finish the sketches real early, I'll think about rearranging them and then
go straight into inking and, uh, see if two weeks, two and a half weeks or
whatever is enough to, to ink and, and do all of the final finishing touches on a
bunch of pages.
I'm definitely more productive on stream.
It helps a lot.
I, I found that streaming, it does keep me generally more focused on the task at
hand, but it also sort of gives me an out to not work.
Like, like the chat distracts me a little bit.
Same.
Yeah.
It's sort of, it's sort of a trade off for me.
I would say that at my, at my best and most focus, the stream is a distraction and
I'm less productive, but if I'm like struggling to focus on working on it,
then it makes me more productive.
I mean, I think the distraction is really just when I am like needing a break anyway.
And I just sort of glance over like, what are people saying?
And I see the same stuff.
And, you know, occasionally it can feel distraction, but like compared to if I
was just at, you know, at my own devices, I would be doing nothing.
I know this for a fact based on the like June and July is I would be doing
absolutely nothing and or playing a video game.
If not for this, for this, uh, these watchful viewers, these attentive viewers.
And people, people, people have like gotten a lot out of knowing that I'm working.
Some people come in and they say, oh, you're working and that's cool.
It makes me feel like I should be working like inspiring.
So I'm providing a service.
So basically I'm saying subscribe to twitch.tv slash give and take.
And you're, you're basically running a charity here.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, I saw you, um, I saw you get raided.
I did.
I got raided by, um, the hiding.
I think it was his name.
I don't know who that is.
The height.
I, I forget his name too.
Was it the hiding?
Yeah.
Well, I recall that name.
Well, um, I went whoever it was, I went and I looked at their twitch and I
watched the very tail end of the last video they had been doing before they had
raided you and I, and I, and I listened to him as he was like picking who he was
going to raid and I, and I heard him be like, um, he was like, no, not him.
No, not him.
No, that guy's an asshole.
Uh, oh, you know who's streaming right now.
Gibb and take.
I love that guy.
I used to watch his videos when I was like 15.
So I want, so I'm going to raid his stream and I want you all to
tell him that I love him.
Yeah, they, they were all very nice.
I, so wait, does he know, like what I was doing?
I guess not.
It just sort of remembers the channel name.
I think he, yeah, he didn't say anything about what you were currently doing
just that he knew you from your videos.
Man, what a fake fan.
That's really cool though, because it means like he's probably just remembers,
like, I don't know, the pony videos or something.
Yeah.
Potentially also the hypocrite stuff.
One, one or the other.
That's cool.
Was it for, for, for a brief tiny fraction of a moment there.
I had 90 viewers or 93 viewers.
Oh, no, no, hiding, hiding, hiding Kuhn.
That's his name.
I looked it up.
It's hiding Kuhn.
Yeah.
93 years is really fucking good.
I, I, I was in there and it stayed, it was still like,
stayed about 30 and then 20 and then 10, like, but slowly diminished.
So people stuck around for a while.
I was, I was in there and I was, you know, I think I had just, I had just subbed.
I had just, I like, I've like, I don't think I've ever subbed to any channel before,
but I was just, I was in the spirit and I had, and I had, and I had, and I had
filled up the cup with, with little unicorn hearts and I was waiting for someone
to, to drop something in and make them splash out.
And someone had dropped like a hundred bit in there and it had kind of worked.
I was like, this isn't good enough.
So I was like, okay, fuck it.
I'll sub and I dropped the one and it went and I was like, yeah, cool.
All right, I'm out.
Peace.
And then I left and I, but then, then I came back like a, like a little bit
later, just to kind of look and like it had gone from, you'd gone from like
somewhere in the tens of viewers to like, you know, you had like 90.
I was like, oh my God.
And the chat was going crazy and I was, I was curious.
So I, I looked up, uh, I looked up the guy who had sent them there to, to
try and get some backstory of how did this happen?
Yeah.
It was complete.
And then I found out it's a whole narrative tapestry.
There you go.
Uh, that's the thing.
Hey, I always meant to do this when I was streaming and I would usually
forget, but I would recommend, uh, I would recommend, uh, yeah.
At the end of your stream, just read somebody, uh, like just go to, go to
like the streaming tab, pick anyone and just, no, I only occasionally remembered,
but it's great.
It's a really good to do.
Everybody loves it.
It's fun for the viewers because they get to jump into some chat and go,
ah, spam, spam, spam, dab, dab, dab.
For instance, um, you know, the, the, the streamer, the streamer is
appreciated too.
And somebody, you get to follow each other back and then you get, oh, join
each other's communities.
Oh, join, join my web ring.
Oh, put your link on my fucking website or whatever.
Uh, that's called, that's called networking.
Add to my blog's Rolodex.
Go, go, go.
Oh, oh, uh, friend me on Facebook, uh, I'll be on my space.
Here's my link to my Friendster by my, by my, uh, by my mixtape.
I'll have to hire me on Fiverr.
Yeah, squirt me some of your favorite music on my zoom.
Uh, let, let me, let me read the, the quote from, uh, Das Kapital in
your, in your next bread tube video for you.
That's what they do.
That's what they, that's what they fucking do.
They all read, they all read quotes for each other.
Dude, speaking of Das Kapital as in capitalism, uh, I need one more
sub in my Twitch subscriber points to get a new emote slot for the tier one
subs.
The moment I only have one, it's just me, like smiling sideways.
You need one more sub.
Will it be unlocked permanently?
Yes.
I looked into it as like you, you get the extra emote slot.
And even if your subs go down afterwards, you have it forever.
So I need this to happen this month.
One more sub.
That's what I'm going to go for.
And then I'm probably going to put like the red man face or like the, the
Gibb and take, Rob, like face.
I would, yeah, I was in there and I was, uh, I was there and I, and I
bullied you into, uh, into giving us the, uh, the loyalty badge, the subscriber
badge, you had the, uh, you had the default star.
And I was like, what the fuck this shit?
And you, uh, you, uh, you gave us the, the, the red man.
So now every, every, every sub has the little red man face.
And I'm like, yes, yes, I love that.
Or is it every sub or every?
Yeah.
It's a sub, it's a sub thing.
It's a, it's a subby thing for my Dom, Gibb and take.
Um, excellent.
Delicious.
Yum.
Uh, um, yeah.
So twitch.tv slash Gibb and take go.
Actually, I think, um, by the time this is out, I'll be like wrapping up the last
stream of the week.
So you missed out.
You fucking idiot.
You should have already been there, but you can, you can follow right now.
Should have listened to the jack of all trades episode.
You would have known this was happening last week's episode.
But it's got like no views.
Fuck you.
Fuck everybody.
All the, all the crop of, of like 80 videos that came out this week have like
less than half their normal views.
It's a bit of a bummer.
I guess that's what happens when you have, when your subscriber's attention is now
divided between like 10 episodes instead of just one.
I hope, I hope they appreciate, I hope anyone who's exclusively a YouTube viewer
appreciates like the sudden glut of content.
Yeah.
Um, so they can.
Imagine like, imagine not having followed along at theprocrastinators.com.
For shame.
It would, yeah.
It's, it's funny because it's like, nowadays you don't, you assume websites
don't exist, nobody will ever think to Google theprocrastinators.com to find
out if there was a website that really exists.
So it serves, it serves its function perfectly adequately.
Uh, yeah, that's one word for it.
No frills, no bells and whistles, just, just straightforward content, you know,
the, could the content you crave at an affordable price, the placeholder graphics,
just nothing, nothing altered from the default WordPress template.
We should, we should replace the banner now that you mentioned it.
This is just a picture of a potted plant.
I don't know.
I feel like it's become a character in and of itself at this point.
We should just take that image and then like Photoshop us into, into it.
Like in, in like a, oh yes, we're going to add the potted plant to the group piss.
We are the leaves of the plant.
Like we're in the, each of us a branch, we've got like, we're in the
background, we're in the background and we're like, like, uh, fuzz out.
What's the word?
Like out of focus.
Yeah.
It's just kind of in the back, like looking through the plant, like, what's the
plant going to do next?
And the plant is weed.
The plant, the plant was a metaphor for weed.
Oh, beautiful.
Okay.
Wait, speaking, speaking of jack of all trades, guys, guys, I'm so angry at you.
That's fair.
I can't, I can't, thank you.
I can't believe, I can't believe how few voicemails you listen to.
Yeah.
That was weak.
It was weak.
You had like so many and you listened to, you listened to like six of them.
And, and you know what, and you know what, I don't know if you saw the, I don't
know if you saw the comment from crack, I had made, he made a couple of voicemails
and you listened to like one of them that doesn't make sense without the other
ones.
Well, that's his fault.
They weren't making it clear.
I let him down.
I let him down by not being on the episode.
And by the way, you were absolutely right.
The reason I wasn't on last week was because I was so hung over that I couldn't
function and I woke up and then couldn't, couldn't do anything and had to just go
sleep on my, take a nap on my couch until it was over.
It was, it was literally the worst hangover I've ever had in my entire life.
So much that I was puking just from how, I was nauseous and puking just from how
hung over I was.
Oh my God.
It's never happened before.
Ben, what is, what is beyond twisted?
Cause you've clearly hit it.
I, I got, I was, I was shwaisted.
I was, I was, I was, I was, I was.
That's it.
That's the only word to describe it.
But why?
I don't know because I'm stupid.
You're, you're always, you're all, I'm, I'm always hearing stories.
I'm always hearing stories of Ben being unbelievably
shwaisted and ordering chicken nuggets delivery.
And then you wake up the next day and you're like, huh, what?
I don't remember that.
Why did I do this?
Yeah.
That's how it goes.
I have like, I don't want to say you can't keep getting away with this, but
you're not getting away with it.
You're getting your due diligence, your comeuppance, but you just don't learn the
lesson.
Absolutely.
Um, no, no, yeah, you're, it's not like, it's not like this is consequence free.
Um, I'm finding that like, I'm very, okay.
I don't know if I'm just like, I've said this before.
I don't know if I'm just very good at not appearing drunk.
Thus, so that I can drink a, a lot before like, I become unable to drink anymore.
And therefore I end up with a lot of alcohol in my system, which impedes my
memory a lot, or if I just like, am very quick to reach the point where I don't
remember anything.
But it's, I've only, I've only seen you twisted a few times, but in those times,
what will happen is you will start drinking a lot quickly and we will all be
like, then stop and you're like, no, fuck you in the middle of taking another drink.
You're belligerent to the point of just like aggressive.
You, you're determined to die the only way I can describe it.
They're, they're definitely, they're definitely comes a point where in I get a
little, I reach a point of drunkenness at which I'm like, yeah, drinking is great.
I should do it much faster.
Well, that's the whole thing, the switch is so quick.
It goes from like Ben having a good time, having a drink to Ben being
belligerently like drunk and that sucks and telling everyone to try and help him
to fuck off and not metaphorically, literally fuck off and continue to drink.
Were you like that at Recon four?
Cause like, I don't know whether you were actually there was the one.
There was the first one.
The first night we all got pretty fucked up.
The first we streamed it, right?
Yeah, the first night we streamed.
I got really drunk and I threw up, but you know, I remember.
I remember all that, all that.
I didn't black out for any of that.
Yeah, you weren't that, which is you seemed quite amenable.
I think, I think, I think, I think because we were on stream, I had a certain, I had,
there was a certain like, I had a certain presence of mind about me.
Well, I'm like, even if I'm drunk, I got to behave myself.
I honestly think you probably drank less than, than usual because like when we hang
out and it's just drinking, like you don't stop, like there's always a drink going.
And on the stream, we could only drink when shots were purchased.
So that kind of like put a hot cap on you.
Because I knew that I could be forced to drink at any time.
So I was like, I better not.
I was like, this is work right now.
I'm on the, I'm on the clock.
You did tear through those beers, though.
When I, when I, when I'm getting, when I'm drinking.
Yeah, I get, I get belligerent, but, but, but, but I'm like, but I'm like funny
belligerent, right? Like it's belligerent in like a cool way though, right?
Like in, in an epic way.
We're laughing with like an undertone of concern, you know?
Oh, no. Oh, no.
That's hilarious.
But like, we know how this is going to end.
We know how this is going to end.
That sucks. That sucks.
I'm sorry. No, I'm like, I remember.
I remember how I feel when I'm like, when I'm, when I'm drunk and I'm like yelling
and I'm sitting like, ah, fuck you guys, like what I'm thinking is that
like I'm being funny and like it's funny for me to say these things
and to be like an asshole and belligerent.
It is in the beginning, but then we see you like actually dead and we're like,
oh, no, we can't stop you.
But your, but your concern is for my safety.
Oh, absolutely.
OK, OK, OK.
Well, that's better than. OK.
Yeah. It's not like every time you black out, you become a beast and you start punching.
He just starts punching and he just won't stop.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Good times. Good times.
So anyway, but but now look what I've did because of my indiscretion.
I let our viewers down.
The voicemails went on. Listen to, I don't know.
There needs to be.
We need to reinforce a meritocracy in the voicemails, you know,
there's too much of a communal thing going on.
Wasn't this was inspiring bad behavior.
We got to we got to have a strict policy of screening the voicemails.
So these people bring their aid game.
But that was gay.
Oh, it was. I was feeling very lazy.
But I'm going to cover that laziness up with an appeal to meritocracy screening.
Well, who's going to do it?
Who's going to do it?
None of us used to do it.
Nate used to do it and none of nobody else wants to do it.
And I think Anarchy is cool.
Yeah. Well, you weren't here.
So I know I was shamed.
I fucked up, you know, I fucked up, everyone.
When when Nate is here, meritocracy reigns.
When Ben is here, Anarchy reigns.
When when you are both absent, Malaise sets in.
It's it's like it's like Twitch.
It's like Twitch plays Pokemon.
Was it Anarchy versus democracy?
I think Nate's not democracy, but instead of democracy, it's like
monarchy or feudalism.
It's like feudalism, basically.
Was it order versus anarchy?
I can't remember what the fuck.
I think it was democracy because people were voting.
It was just democracy straight up.
All right.
All right. Yeah, they voted on which one.
And because Anarchy was just like every command goes through.
Democracy was like every so often.
There's a command every so often a poll is done.
Yeah, I just don't remember being called democracy,
but I guess I didn't pay much attention to it.
I do remember it being called that, I believe you.
What about Twitch plays Haven't Take?
Like to draw a line like up at a nine degree angle.
No, no, no, draw the left like down at like forty eight.
Has anyone has anyone tried to make like a drawing program on Twitch?
I bet you could. Yeah, it's like up up, down down.
It's like itch a sketch. Oh, God.
Communal itch, yes.
Yeah, that would be terrible.
Anarchy anarchy.
It just be scribble, scribble stream.
It would probably just be shit.
Yeah. You there would be no.
No, there'd be no saving it.
There'd be all noise, no signal.
There's some structure to a video game that helps contain the chaos.
Yeah, it's only because, yeah, there's like so few commands you can do at any given time.
There's only so many states that can occupy it.
Dude, do you remember that big reddit image thing?
Which one?
It's like a giant pixel art thing and each user can decide a color for a square.
And multiple communities of people, like you can only do it once every so often.
And people try to draw things.
And communities would come together to draw like the logo of their community on this massive communal pixel art something or other.
It sounds familiar.
I can't remember what it was called, but it was similar sort of like...
Like there was this cult that formed of like the abyss that started to draw black encroaching on everything.
And people were fighting against the abyss and like rebuilding their lost, you know, their destroyed stuff.
It was cool.
I remember that happening for a little while and then it stopped.
Hmm.
Based.
I never did it, so I don't remember.
I don't remember.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, Clarissa's cool.
I like Clarissa.
She's a cowgirl.
You know, that's nice and all.
But you know what's really cool?
No.
Personal finances.
Oh, I know where this is going.
Do you know?
Yeah.
Oh, I know.
I posted a big spiel about it in the cultural Marxism channel.
And then I, because it was on my mind, in my discord, I started a new channel that's called Mutual Financial Aid where we talk about how to get free money.
I applied for a credit card.
I've never had a credit card before.
I've always used a debit card, which when I tell people that, they're like horrified.
They're like, what?
What?
You haven't been building equity?
I'm like, I'm sorry.
You haven't been playing the video game?
My parents didn't trust me enough.
They were like, if you have a credit card, you'll build up debt and then you'll die.
And I was like, yeah, that's probably true.
So then for another like 30 years, I was like, nah.
But I just, okay, because I have an incredible credit score, I applied for the, I applied for the best credit card I could find.
All right.
How do you have a great credit score when you haven't had a credit card?
Well, I have, I've made, I think the major thing is that I've made all my student loan payments.
That's like been my major, the major debt that I've paid off and I've paid off every payment on time.
So that's probably why.
It's like, isn't it like you have a, you have good, you have a good credit score because you haven't done anything to fuck up your credit.
But you don't have a lot of like a volume of credit.
So you're not going to get approved for like any like crazy loans right out the gate because you don't have a proven track record of like handling credit well.
But your raw score, just based on the, the information that's there is still good.
Is that how that works?
I think so.
I think you have to have a credit history as well for like higher end, crazy loans and shit.
Hmm.
I don't know.
It's funny, like the one negative mark I have on my, actually, I could, I could talk about that.
I could, I could talk about my credit score for an hour and I will.
The one, the one negative mark on my credit score is like a couple of years ago when I moved away from Boston to move in with Digi.
No, was it for the, it was at some point, I had a subscription to Workout World, the gym, and I had signed up for like a year of, of access to it.
I had paid like, I had agreed to like $10 a month or like $20 a month or whatever for a year, but then a couple months into that, I didn't want to do it anymore.
So I canceled my credit card and they couldn't, they couldn't keep paying.
They couldn't keep accepting payments.
So I have like $140 that I owe to Workout World that made a little like five point dip in my credit score, which has like completely gone away now.
And it doesn't matter.
So I'm scot-free.
Fuck you, Workout World.
Workout World.
You'll never get my $140.
Hell yeah.
Doesn't even matter.
And then this is a, okay.
Do you want, do you want to know about this mysterious, this mysterious thing?
There was a, an account.
All right.
You go to credit karma and you see two different credit scores, one from Equifax, one from TransUnion.
They were both amazing.
800 plus.
I am, I'm a miracle.
I'm a wizard.
I'm like, fuck yeah.
But there's an account.
Like one of them, one day my, my, my account dips like, like a couple points, like three or four points.
And I'm like, whoa, whoa, whoa, it's almost good.
I can't let it go under 800.
Like that's bullshit.
I'll die.
So I, so I look and I see that it's this Bank of America checking account in my name.
And I'm like, I don't have a Bank of America, sorry, not check credit card.
I'm like, I don't have a credit card.
I don't have any credit card, let alone a Bank of America one.
So like, I file a dispute and I say like, hey, uh, this is not my, this is not my account.
Remove this from my report, please.
And they do, but when they do, my score drops 80 points.
I'm down to a pathetic, I'm down to a pathetic 725.
I might as well be living on the street.
Um, but it's only with, it's only with TransUnion.
Equifax still thinks that my account, that that's my account.
And I still have an 800 with them.
And I'm like, and I'm like, and so I'm like, I need to get that back.
I need my points back.
So I tried to file another dispute with TransUnionist.
Like, no, I didn't mean to.
That actually was my account, please put it back, but they won't let me because I guess
because of COVID or whatever, they like stopped accepting disputes.
They were like, when our office is not running, like we're not accepting disputes right now.
We will, when we're back.
And so for months, I'm like, ah, like, what am I going to do?
So finally, like the other day, like this week, I think they opened up their dispute center again.
So I filed a dispute and I'm like, please give me the account back.
And they're like, we can't do that.
You're going to have to contact Bank of America.
And I'm like, no, just, you had to just put it back.
And they're like, no, can do.
I'm like, ah, but it's not even my account.
It's a, it's a fake account.
It's, it's fraud.
It's literal fraud that I don't know how it got on there.
And I will just want it back.
So I don't know, please, please defraud me.
So I guess tomorrow what I'm going to have is I'm going to have to call Bank of America and and ask them like, why is there a credit card account under my name?
Is this real?
Did like one of my parents like get drunk and black out and start me a credit card account somewhere in El Paso, Texas when I was a little baby?
Or, or, or what is this?
And probably they'll be like, yeah, that's fake.
So I'm probably going to have to resign myself to a pathetic 725 credit score for the rest of my life.
The struggle.
But it's okay.
Because while I've got good, while, while I've got good, or maybe 725 would have been fine for this anyway.
Or maybe they checked Equifax and, and they use, and they use the 800 and that's why I qualified.
But I got, I got the best credit card.
I got a credit card, 2% cashback on everything.
2%.
Is it real cashback?
What's, what's real?
What's, what do you mean?
Because like my, I have a, I've had a credit card.
They don't, they don't, they don't say points.
They don't say points or anything.
They say cashback.
Cause like my card said cashback and I just have like points to use in like their proprietary storefront.
And I'm like, this sucks.
I hate it.
I don't think so.
Cause I've been, cause like, I was using a debit card forever cause I'm like, I don't understand credit.
I'm too dumb.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was me.
And my bank was just like, you should get a credit card.
And I'm like, fine, just shut up.
I'm never going to use it.
I think I got it literally just because it was like, if you spend X a hundred dollars, you get money back.
I'm like, I'm already going to buy something that that much.
I'll just do it for that.
And that was my plan.
Yeah.
Then my debit card expired and they've sent me five and none of them have made it to my house.
Even though the bank is literally right up the street.
So I've just been forced to use my credit card for everything for the last two years.
So I have no idea what my credit is, but I pay off my statement entirely every month.
So I must just be a God at this point because I've made every payment.
I've made every payment flawlessly without, even though, even though the last batch of shipping was put on my credit card and Nate sells and pay me back because he's literally dead.
And I'm mad.
I want that back so I can pay off my credit card in two weeks.
Nate has, Nate has not, has Nate paid back any of the Radcon expenses?
Like, are we still, are we still all due like for groceries and shit?
The only thing he's paid back that I know of is the shipping costs that I've paid the last like month because I was like, I need that back because that's like two and a half thousand dollars.
On my credit card that needs to be paid off like now.
And he was like, okay.
Okay.
But other than that.
So, so, so like, did you, did you buy any like food for the house?
I think I did, but I don't know if I even bother.
Yeah, I think what we were doing expenses tab.
What we were going to do is we were tallying up personal expenses of like, you know, anything that could be related to Radcon.
And then we were going to go through it after we had done all of the things that require money.
So like,
Well, here, here's the thing that nobody's been reimbursed for anything yet.
We're going to do everything.
That's what I wanted to know.
It's been reimbursed because like I asked Nate, like, when are we going to get, when can I get reimbursed for everything?
Cause like I wanted, I got reimbursed for all the costs I did for making all the rewards, but he did not.
I assume.
He did not pay me for the labor.
I have not been.
I paid for any of the labor and he was like, well, we're just going to wait until literally everything is done before I pay any of you back.
I'm like, but that's going to take like at least another year.
But okay.
I mean, yeah.
Do I trust Nate for another 12 months sitting on all that money?
I don't know.
I mean, I trust him not to fuck with it.
I don't, but I don't know.
Like something bad could happen and he could be in a situation where he needs to like blow all that money.
I don't fucking know.
I mean, it's, I mean, it's a dangerous economy out there right now.
I guess seems unlikely.
It's unlikely, but anything's possible.
Um, yeah, I, but okay.
But like, I think the real question is when are we going to open up a business account for the PCP?
Why are we letting him have all of this?
It's clearly an idiotic idea.
But if he paid it, but if he paid it out now, then what would happen if like, you know, the, the, the, the OVA or something ended up costing more than then we expect, you know?
Yeah, that's, that's why we need to do like all of the big expenses.
Well, okay.
Well, I guess, I guess if we, if we were just paying back like, like house expenses and like, you know, production labor, I mean, that's all stuff that needs to be paid out anyway.
I was only talking about the labor costs for the things I've already done.
Like that's set at stone.
Like I'm not, you know.
Yeah, I would support, well, but he already paid you the shipping cost, right?
Right, but none of the labor costs for doing all the work.
Okay, well, I would, I would support a motion to get you that because I mean, that's, that's a set in stone cost that is, that is non-negotiable.
So like it has to be paid out eventually anyway.
It just, just as much as like, you know, the dojin or the OVA expenses or anything.
Right, exactly.
So I would be in favor of that.
And maybe groceries and shit too, just like get that out of the way because like, why not?
Yeah, there's, there's a lot of stuff to, to hash out still, but like there are things that could probably just be taken care of.
I feel a good deal right off of everybody's mind just to be like, okay, that's settled.
And then we only have the costs that are still forward facing to worry about.
I'm still waiting for my, I'm still waiting for that.
And the charity stream raised $702 in donations and I pledged 50 of my own.
So I went, so after the stream, I went and just out of my own pocket donated the $752 to bail funds.
So I am waiting, I'm still waiting for 702, that's 752 minus my 50, 702 dollars from that.
But it had to come, it had to come out of AdSense, right?
So like it took like a month for it to go through.
So I think it probably would have paid out about two or three weeks ago.
So this, it should, it's, I should get that with this next round, which Nate is laid on by the way, but it's okay.
Cause I don't care that much.
Right, right.
Um, but, um, but, um, I, I just,
You were talking about the credit card.
I was talking, yes, I was talking about the credit card.
I feel like I made this analogy in the chat and I deliberately didn't explain it.
But so in, in, in, uh, Oolulilia, right?
Everyone knows his book, Legend of the Ten Elemental Masters.
Fewer people have read his other book, Secret in the Basement, but I have read Secret in the Basement.
Have I, have I talked about this book before?
No, I don't.
Do you guys remember?
I don't remember.
Maybe had, but I don't remember.
Well, Secret in the Basement, it's, it's pretty long.
Like it's a pretty thick book.
Um, and it is about this kid, teenager, Richard, who basically he has dreams and in his dreams,
he goes into his basement and this magical door opens and there's this wizard here who
sends him on this quest through all these video game worlds.
And the, but the funny thing about it is that like a lot of the book is spent like grinding
monsters and like going back to the wizard and like shopping for his equipment and like
spending his like in-game currency to buy like, to like, to min-max his stats and stuff.
And the big like items that he saves up for like, basically the items that mark like his
next step on the tier that's like, okay, I can kind of like sell back all these other things
to buy this one thing that will replace them almost.
And then I can start collecting like the next sort of tier of gear are these universal rings
that just like increase all his stats across the board.
So they'll be like the first universal ring gives all his stats like plus 10.
Second universal ring gives all his stats like plus 50 or whatever.
Anyway, getting, getting this credit card that's going to give me 2% cashback on everything I buy with it
makes me feel like Richard buying his next universal ring.
All my stats have been increased across the board.
My buying powers is universally increased.
I am a god now.
I can, I can kill, I can kill blue jellies with lightning too.
Like even without, in one shot, even without a critical hit.
Like that's how empowered I am by this.
Incredible.
I know.
It's, it's pretty cool.
It's pretty cool guys.
I've yet to use my credit card for evil.
I just use it as cash.
What do you mean by evil?
I don't know.
Like doing any crazy fucking Machiavellian schemes.
It's, it's not called evil.
It's called smart.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Um, like, like,
What are you talking about?
Like people use credit cards to like make like crazy upfront purchases or like they
do what was, what was the term you said that they were doing with credit cards if they
had a whole subreddit for?
Oh, oh, churning.
Churning.
I've not tried any churning power things.
I'm so fascinated.
I'm so fascinated by the concept of churning.
It seems like, I guess like if you're living a certain like level of lifestyle that's totally
feasible, it definitely wouldn't be for me because I would just be losing money.
The, the, okay.
Let's explain churning before we go any further.
Yeah.
Okay.
So the concept of churning is that certain, um, certain credit cards will offer you a sign-up
bonus.
That's like if you sign up for the card and you spend a certain amount within a certain
period of signing up, they will give you basically reward money.
And, you know, sometimes that's in like credit or sometimes it's in cashback or maybe sometimes
it's in points.
Okay.
A lot of them are in like miles.
I think a lot of the best credit cards in terms of pure value are the ones that give
you like frequent flyer miles or like airline travel points.
Um, like super useful now, but yeah, like I, even before like I didn't travel that much.
So like I'm not interested in that, but there's ones that just give you like straight up like
cash credit.
Um, and the idea of churning is like you go through, it's like you're churning through
credit cards, like one after the other, you get one, you earn the reward, you get the
cashback, you, you, you, you close the account, you move on to the next one.
And you just go through them and go through them and go through them.
Um, and, um, a lot of them are like, there's one, the seemingly the best and easiest one,
there's one that is, if you sign up and you spend $500, you just get $200.
Like that's the easiest one, but there's others that are like, if you sign up and you spend
$5,000, you get $500.
You sign up, you spend $4,000, you get, you get $400.
Like that seems to be like the ratio.
It's about one to 10, um, on a lot of these other ones.
So like you, I mean, if you're doing it successfully in theory, it seems like you can kind of just
sort of be getting like 15 to 10% of your money just back for free.
Right.
If you're already spending that much money in that, a lot of time.
Yeah.
The idea is that you do this on purchases you would have made anyway.
So it's just becomes free money.
Your net goes down like 10, 10% or so in terms of just like cost of everything you're buying.
Yeah.
Would you run out of banks at some point?
There is a, okay, apparently in the churning community, cause I was, I was reading through
the subreddit and I picked up some of the lingo.
In the churning community, there was a concept known as being under five 24, which means
that you have applied for fewer than five new credit cards in the last 24 months, which
seems to be the cutoff point.
And a lot of banks will, like that's when, that's when banks start to be like, I don't
know if I want this guy signing up for credit.
Like certain banks are more sensitive to churning than others.
Like a Chase bank, Chase bank, I get, or it's either chase or capital one.
It's like, if you're under 20, if you're, if you're not under five 24, don't even bother
churning capital one or chase.
But if you're under 24, if you're under five 24, you're golden.
You know, you can go right for the, for the AmEx Platinum.
You know, it's like, you're the sky's the limit.
I just, I came up with this idea.
I was like, wait a minute, cards give bonuses.
What if I just signed up for one, got the bonus, moved on to the next one and just kept it going.
This is, this is brilliant.
I'm a genius only to find that there's this entire subreddit dedicated to this exact thing
that I have, that I have.
I think there's a small victory in coming up with a established idea on your own
without outside influence.
I think that just,
That, that, that means it works because people do it.
And it means that you're clever because you didn't have to have someone tell you it.
You came up with it literally by yourself.
Yeah.
There's a moral victory there.
I think so.
Yeah, I think so.
Definitely.
Things like,
I think that when, yeah, go on.
Things like that sort of, I mean, obviously it is a loophole, you know,
sort of finding ways to get by and get money that were not intended, you know,
breaking the video game of life.
And like the necessity for stuff like that and normal people having access to cheat codes
is because the money is not, you know, easy to get a hold of the normal way.
It just makes me upset that all of these workarounds are even necessary.
I mean, if you're saying capitalism bad, I'm right there with you, my dude.
It's interesting how the banks are like, you got to be under the 524 rule in order to churn
cards, but if you're Jeff Bezos, you can put all your money into offshore accounts and
be totally okay with it.
Yes.
Okay.
This is the thing.
This is a perfect example.
To do, to successfully churn, you have to have good credit.
So like if you don't have good credit, like a lot of these cards that give like these
lucrative rewards, they just won't accept you.
So like if you're already in debt or something, like if you're not already sort of ahead of
the game, you're fucked, right?
So there's one example of how, you know, capitalism bad, inherently unfair, meritocracy is a lie.
And second example is that you basically, you know, like one of them is like, you have
to spend, you know, $7,500 in, you know, four or five months or whatever to get $750 back.
If you're going to spend $7 and a half thousand dollars over the course of four to five months,
then that's $750 of free money that you can get.
But if you are not someone that would be spending that much, if you don't have those
money or you're more frugal or you have to be or whatever, then that this option is simply
not available to you.
And again, you know, if you're not already ahead of the game, you know, then you fall,
then you're even further behind, meritocracy is a lie.
So yeah, I agree.
The reason why this works, it's the same concept as like, you know, in like a store, sometimes
they'll be selling an item and it'll come with like a cashback code or a coupon or something
and like you can buy it and then you can go home with it.
Yeah.
Yes.
That's it.
A mail-in rebate.
It's the same concept as a mail-in rebate.
Theoretically, if everyone were a perfectly rational actor, they would be giving this
item away for free and everyone would get their money back and the company, it could
not possibly be profitable, but it works because people like are not rational.
They will simply forget or not care or not, or not do it.
That's why mail-in rebates are mail-in and not instant because as a kid, I was like,
why isn't it just instant?
Why are they making mail it in?
Not realizing that mailing it in and having to do that hoop is entirely the point.
Yeah.
If everyone were a rational actor and worked on their own best interest all the time, these
cash rewards through credit cards would be completely untenable because everyone would
be churning them and everyone would just be squeezing free money out of the bank all
the time.
But people don't do that and people fuck it up and people rack up credit card debt and
get in debt and that's what they're hoping you do.
They put that cashback thing on there to make you sign up for it under the impression
that most people, and then they've crunched the numbers, that most people will either
fail to beat that or forget and therefore they're using the card now, they're making
their interest money and they've lost nothing.
Yes.
Yeah.
So that's why it works.
There's things like that, all of the, like when you're a little boy and you hear about
purchasing things with money and you're like, oh, I got pocket money, you think of it in
terms of you get a number of money and you can use it to get a thing and it's just never
that simple.
To do money correctly, you need to live money.
You can't just have it as a thing you do.
You can't have it as a currency that's in the back of your mind.
You have to be actively doing, you have to research money, like you would research fucking
how to make a computer or run a, you know, understand a car.
It's an extremely, like, I hate it.
I just want to, something's like cost one pound, I pay for one pound with one pound.
I have, on the one hand, I get it.
On the other hand, I have sort of found looking into this stuff to be sort of fun in kind
of the same way that like, I don't know, it's in the same way that I would, that like reading
into like, yeah, in the same way that reading into like a hobby or how to, how to maximize
your stats in some video game is sort of fascinating.
I mean, it's good for people that it works for.
It's just like, I really wish this video game was not tied to my personal well-being and
ability to live, you know?
Like not that I'm currently like actually struggling, but like, I don't like the idea
that money is so important and yet it's, you know, it's also a video game.
It's like, it's like learning how to parry in Dark Souls, but if you can't learn how
to parry in Dark Souls, you die in real life.
Have you seen, have you seen the Twitter account called accidentally left?
Yes.
From you.
From me?
I've probably retweeted.
Yeah.
The one for viewers, it's basically like people making, people making bad right wing
arguments in a way that accidentally like proves the left is best, Lamal.
And the one that's reminds me of is like, I don't know, it's someone says something
about like, but you know, housing, you know, housing is a human right.
Like people shouldn't have to pay just to have somewhere to live.
And someone answers like, oh, what about food and healthcare?
Should we decommodify all of those things too?
Lamal.
Uh, uh, yeah.
It's like.
Yes.
Yep.
Capitalism bet.
You know, for, for, for things that are necessary for human survival, um, uh, yeah, this would
all be fun.
Thought, thought slime, thought slime has a video about Minecraft where he's talking
about like the Minecraft market for like diamonds or something or some other, I don't know.
Um, and he's like, yeah, you know, people are in there, they're trading, you know, they're,
they're doing work, you know, they're, they're, they're trading their labor to create value
in order to trade for these other commodities.
And he's like, this is, this is what I think that like people that love capitalism think
that capitalism is really like, like people making like, you know, logical choices in
order to, you know, satisfy demands in like a low stakes environment, right?
Where nobody's like, like very life is tied to, to what's to this game that's being played.
And like, that's what people think it is.
Well, the people at the top of the top of the fucking thing, because you can't, you
know, like the, that's what it is for rich people.
They have no risk of like going bust unless they super fuck up.
So it is just a game.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And money, when you're, when you're, that's why these fucking billionaires don't
ever do anything and except sit on it.
It's like, this is my high score.
I don't want to fucking lower my high score.
I got to keep it on an offshore bank account because it's my score in this game.
It just keeps, it just keeps getting higher the less they do with it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's, it's, it's bad.
It's bad, it's bad that this, this stupid game that I have been playing,
that I've been looking into, into strats for recently, you know,
is someone's bad at it.
You know, maybe they'll die or maybe they'll just be fucks.
Maybe, maybe even if they don't die, you know,
they'll just be like a perpetual debt cycle or whatever.
And once they're in, like it's super hard to get at.
It's like, you know, once, once you're in the debt spiral, you know,
it's like, you know, you're getting, you're getting camped, right?
And, you know, campers are the billionaires.
They're, they're camping your spawn point, right?
And you, and you can't even, it's literally, it's like playing Counter-Strike.
It's like, it's like in 2020, if you decide I'm going to learn to play Counter-Strike
and you get in there and everyone who's in there has been playing Counter-Strike
for 35 years and like, they're all pros.
You can't, you can't fucking play Counter-Strike.
It's impossible.
There's no sense that you can't get good at Counter-Strike
because you literally cannot play the game
because everyone in there is so clutch, so pro, so ahead of the curve
that it's simply impossible to catch up.
You'll never do it.
Right.
I tried once.
I died every time.
And then I was like, I don't like it.
But I, but I had the luxury of switching to TF2.
You can't do that in the real world.
No, if only.
The TF2 is the, is the revolution that's coming.
Don't worry.
Don't worry, comrades.
We'll get them.
I can't wait to bonk those billionaires.
I can't wait to bonk them.
I can't wait to go up and poke them in the eyes like the three Stooges.
Can't wait to bake-stay them.
I feel like I was going somewhere else with that.
I don't know.
I feel like I had something I was building to on the subject of
churning and credit.
I don't know.
I think you were just introducing the idea.
Are you going to be churning?
Are you going to be personally churning in your life?
Oh, I know.
Wait, I remember.
I was going to say, I think maybe next year,
like maybe after maybe once the whole like COVID like pandemic
unemployment thing blows over.
And, and, and, and, you know, I got to look for some new,
I got to think of some new scam.
Maybe I'll start churning.
By the way, is there anything, did anything end up happening with that?
Did you, did you see what I said in the chat?
And should I?
I know Trump's saying he wanted to make it be 400 and then the Dems versus
conservatives.
This is six versus two or some shit.
So I follow this channel called Clear Value Tax,
who have like literally every single day,
they put out a video explaining like what is the status of the next stimulus bill.
Oh, I think I know who that is, but I haven't watched them in a while.
The Asian guy in the suit, in the suit and tie.
He's like, he's very, he has like, he's completely dry.
He doesn't like, he's like, this is your stimulus report.
This is your stimulus package update report.
This is your second stimulus check update.
This is your unemployment update.
This is your PPP loan status update.
I hope you're having a great day and happy Thursday.
So, and then it'll just like flip through his, his shit.
He's funny.
And he'll, he'll occasionally, the only emotion he ever shows is that he will
occasionally like, he'll say like the politicians say that they will be going on a
recess this Friday, whether or not they reach an agreement on the next stimulus
package.
And then he'll like kind of just look down at his notes and like shake his head like
and then he'll just keep going.
The only emotion he ever shows is dismay at the politicians.
Dismay and from my recall, certain moments of fatigue where he's just like,
there's just so much to go over right now.
Oh my God.
Sometimes he'll get a little bit exasperated.
Like, I'm trying to explain all this, like, if you really should know this already.
But so yeah, I keep up with that.
And all right, so the unemployment boost from the, from the last like stimulus package
ended like two or three weeks ago.
It was two, I think it was two weeks ago.
And the new, and like, so Congress was supposed to, for the next stimulus package,
they were going to argue about whether to extend it or cut it or reduce it.
And the Democrats wanted to extend it, same as it was.
Republicans wanted either to reduce it or cut it.
Generally, they were more in favor of just, just reducing it.
And Democrats were like, like, we, like, we want these things.
We won't budge on these things.
Republicans were like, we don't want to give you anything.
We hate you.
And Trump, Trump was just like, okay, they were supposed to decide, and they were supposed
to go on recess this Friday before, and hopefully they were going to settle on the bill before
then they didn't settle on the bill, but they decided, okay, we're not going to go on recess.
We're going to keep debating this next week.
But on Friday, because they didn't reach the, Trump was like, okay, I've decided.
Executive order, we're going to, we're going to go exactly in the middle.
We're going to do like, between what the Democrats and Republicans want,
which like, I guess as a compromise makes some sense, but it's not clear that he actually
has the authority to do that.
Right.
Like he's, like he's not really, the president is not really allowed to decide how money gets
spent. That's Congress's job. The like, quote unquote loophole that may or may not be valid
is that it's, this is supposed to be paid not with new funds, but with the leftover funds
that have not yet been spent from the old stimulus package.
So maybe it'll happen. But I think that they are, I think that this is just like a temporary order,
or it's only going to be an effect for, so like obviously it can only continue until
that money runs out. So I think Congress is going to continue to debate over it over,
like whether like a permanent bill for another more money in a real stimulus package next week.
So yeah, I don't know. This, this is it. This is,
I don't know. What do you think about that?
Well, I guess we'll just have to wait and see. I guess, so nothing's in effect yet then.
It's still kind of up in the air.
I don't know. I think so. I think, I think it's still kind of up in the air at the moment.
Like whether, like whether this will even go into effect.
And whether this will affect like the stimulus package that is not past it.
There were, there were some other things that he included in his executive order, like student loan,
student loan debt, it will, the suspension will continue until the end of the year.
There was another thing I'm forgetting, something about the PPP loan, which does not affect me,
so I didn't pay attention. I don't know. There were, there were some other stuff.
Oh, the, oh, the payroll tax. Payroll taxes are suspended.
And I have no idea what I think about that. I think payroll taxes seem bad,
but they fund things that I think are good. Like payroll taxes would fund social security.
So I don't, I think I don't like what a payroll tax is, but I do like what they are used for.
So them being suspended, I'm not sure how I feel about it.
Yeah. So that, so that was the executive order. By the way, I looked into it and it seems like
if the, if the stimulus package is passed and like the benefits are extended,
it will probably be applied retroactively. So like if you're, if, so if people are applying for
a unemployment like this week or last week or next week, right before anything gets passed
or anything is done, probably if a package is passed and like a pandemic boost is applied,
it will be retroactively that most sources that I found that had any sort of stipulation on the
subject said, yeah, that's usually how it's done. Interesting. So I don't know. So I don't know.
Um, wouldn't it be cool if we weren't in America and this wasn't nearly as big of a problem? Because
like we'd be on the tail end of this shit. Yeah. Didn't, didn't all Canadians just get like 2000
Canadian dollars like a month for a while? I think that's how that went. So that would have been
way simpler. Well, you know, America is just obsessed with means testing. They just up like,
oh, we have to have, we want to need paperwork to make sure that like you're, you have to be this
poor to qualify for something, which is like really reinforcing that whole like the, the mean,
means testing is supposed to prevent people who like don't, who have too much from like
qualifying for benefits they don't quote unquote deserve, but it really reinforces that whole
like welfare queen stereotype that conservatives like hate so much. That's like, it really, it,
like, well, like welfare really does not incentivize laziness so much as like
gatekeeping welfare behind like you must make this little money in order to get it.
Like that's what really incentivizes not working. Yeah, it's weird as well. Cause like
extremely rich people were also getting subsidies anyway, and in much larger amounts.
Right. But it's in like a different, it's a different way. Just if you're, you know,
if you're reasonable, but not like wealthy, then you can't have it. You have to be
bumfuck poor loser going to die soon in order to get it. It's almost like they're incentivizing
you to either be extremely wealthy or extremely poor that like there's some sort of neo feudalism
starting to take form or something. It's like, I mean, it's like, like those examples I gave
with the churning, like you need good credit and you need to be able to, you need to command a
certain amount of spending power or else it doesn't work and that free money is cut off from you.
But if you have those things, you just could just get free money. Like things like that abound,
right? In government and in business and in like every aspect of life, like the system of wealth,
the capitalist system of wealth just reinforces itself, you know, in all these different ways.
I uncovered two of them this week. And there's plenty more where that came from. You know,
everyone says like Amazon Amazon gets like, you know, Elon Musk is like, huh, Bernie wants to
give everyone shit for free. Elon Musk gets $4.9 billion in taxpayer money and subsidies,
just just for being him, just for owning Amazon. We just gave that to him, our money. He has it.
Elon Musk. You mean Jeff Bezos? No, Elon Musk. He said Amazon. Did I say Amazon? I'm sorry. No,
I meant Tesla and Elon Musk. But he gets that. And, you know, his defenders will say, oh, yeah,
but he gets that because like he cut a deal with, you know, whoever, like, you know,
oh, the California like, you know, gave him the subsidies because they wanted him,
his factory there, you know, because it would create jobs or whatever. And like, yeah, it's,
it's not these subsidies are not for no reason. Like he's not just getting them
for literally no reason. Just like if you're getting this free money from churning credit cards,
you're not getting it for no reason. You're doing it via a system. But like at the end of the day,
you know, it's still it's free money that you're getting just for being rich that only like only
a fabulously wealthy person like Elon Musk could could get access to. Sure. You know, or Bobby
Kotick, you know, you hear about, I love Bobby Kotick, the CEO of Activision. He also gets like
taxpayer money for Activision that he just pockets himself. I was listening to Jim Sterling this week
and I think I heard him talk about that guy. Yes. Yes, I know. Is he's like, he's like one of like,
he's like really rich, right? He's like very rich 1010 guys in America or something like that.
Some crazy shit. He's like a 10 like a 10s of billions there. Yeah, probably. Maybe hundreds.
I'd deck a billionaire if you will. I mean, probably probably not hundreds. Yeah.
Like a like a like a real Bloomberg level kind of guy. Like a just a real fucking piece of
shit if you know what I'm saying. Yeah. He definitely has a lot to do with making call of duty.
Well, what would we do without his expertise? I know all that incredible coding and art direction
skills he has. A visionary. A visionary. Really? What if we did the shooting but again? Oh, such a
great idea. That's literally where his input ends. Have you have you seen that? Have you seen that
meme that's like, I want I want shorter games with worse graphics made by people paid less paid more
to work less. And no, I'm not kidding. Yeah, I saw that quote. Yeah, I retweeted that yesterday.
I was like, yeah, yeah. You want the end market? AOC tweeted the other day. The billionaires need
the working class with the working class do not need billionaires. And I saw this. I think it was
an accidentally left retweet or someone else. And someone replied like isn't thinking they're
making an amazing rebuttal thinking this is an epic clapback. They're like, isn't Oprah a billionaire?
So basically you're saying Oprah needs the working class, but the working class doesn't need Oprah.
Think about it. Yes. Think about that for a second. Yes. I think I think that's true.
I think that's probably that probably holds water if you examined it seems cogent to me.
I it seems both sound and valid in my in my in my estimation.
Boy, oh, fucking boy. I I feel a little embarrassed to be to to have like that I that I find like
money talk interesting now, but I do. I've become I've become old. I think I think this is how you
know know your enemy, right? Right. It's like, I mean, it has the same appeal as a video game
of watching numbers go up. It does. And it's it and I the universal ring comparison is like,
yeah, I feel like I unlocked a new perk or a feat or gained an achievement or something.
I wonder if it's embarrassing to say because I know most people use credit cards and here I am
like, oh, my God, I got my first one, lol. But I got a good one. I got the best one. Hey, viewer,
I bet my credit cards better than yours. Do you get 2% cashback? Didn't think so.
The thing is, like so many people use credit cards wrong, right? Like you live off that.
That's that's what I was afraid of. That's what I was afraid of. It's like, yeah, like I grew up in
fear and it ruined their lives. So for for the longest time, I did not get a credit card because I
saw the damage they could. That's what everyone says. I was retarded. And I mean, I was right,
but not this way, apparently. That's what everyone says. You get a credit card, you'll run up your
credit card debt. You don't know, though, you'll have to pay interest. You'll you'll you'll fall
into a mountain of debt. Just don't buy things you don't have money for. Just just don't buy
things you don't have money for and just don't forget to pay your balance. How the only the
only two things are an easy way to keep track of the money you have before you make a purchase.
Do they make it easy or do they make it difficult? The reason why I was inspired to buy this to get
this card was because I was my friend, a doub, was telling me that he had just gotten a new one
and he was telling me about his, you know, perks and I was like, oh my god, there's perks.
And he was like, yeah, there's an app like like the credit card can just you can just get an app
for your card and you can just like make payments through the app on your phone. Yeah, that's what
I do. I just have a Google reminders that every on the three days before my payment date, it just
has a little notification like pay your credit card, you dummy. And I'll just do it right through
the app and then you're done. And like the way you do it is like you just, I mean, I know what
how much money I have in my account. And I just don't spend more than I normally would because I
just use it like cash and I already live very frugally to begin with. So instead of like pulling
a $5 bill out of my pocket or like throwing my debit card on there, I just use the credit card.
And then on the 20th of the month, I just pay off whatever it was, because it doesn't charge you
up front, like that's the whole point, you just have to make the payment. And you just wait,
you basically just pay your entire month's worth of payments in one fell swoop instead of doing it
as you go. I am, I am waiting for this is this is actually delaying the vapors a little bit
because I am waiting a couple of days for my card to arrive in the mail so that when I because I
because I ordered the books to be printed and shipped to me the 500 the final the final printing
vapors to his fucking coming. And but it's going to cost me $2,000. So I'm waiting for the card
so that I can use the card to pay for it. So I can get the 2% cash back because 2% of $2,000
is $40. So that's 43 bucks. You know, I'm not I'm not wasting that I'm not wasting $40.
Sure, sure. Fuck it, you can all wait another like three days put all the shipping for the
radcon stuff on my card. So hopefully that'll amount to something I've even looked into it.
But yeah, that was like almost three grand and shipping costs and material costs and all that
shit. So you still you still waiting for that? I'm still waiting for the last chunk of $462.
Okay, the rest the rest has been squared up. Thank God because that was a huge fucking thing
because I had to put like all the posters and all the all the packaging materials and all the
shipping. So like, there was like almost four grand worth of stuff on my card and I'd like max
it out and I'm like, Oh, no, this is bad. So you got a higher limit than I do.
Um, maybe my limits, my limits 3000.
You know, I think I think mine is as well. I think some of that I think some of that stuff
went through eBay. So that was just put directly to my bank and it's on all of it when I'm on the
card. I was I was thinking about right. Okay, I was thinking like, Oh, maybe maybe that's because
maybe that is because what you were saying before, like I have a high score, but my history is like
small or whatever my my or whatever you were saying before about like amounts. I still have
baby's first credit card. I think I don't think it's anything like fancy yours probably
smacks mine. I just got the one through my bank because I wasn't thinking of using it at the time.
Tom, you got to get you got to get everybody's got to get the city bank double cash card.
Yeah, I've heard that recommended. There's some guys I went on Forbes.com. I went on
Forbes.com and I read their article about the best credit cards in 2020 and this was the top
of the list, but they were like, Oh, you got to have good credit to get it. And I went and applied.
Got it. No problem. I couldn't even get the Amazon credit card. I was mad about that. Oh my
God. Oh my God. It's good. It's not bad. So I was very surprised because it's like, Oh,
that sucks. But whatever, I didn't save my $100 off my Amazon card, give you Amazon credit.
Yeah, it gives you like, I think like three or 4% back on Amazon.
Oh, yeah, something stupid like that. Okay, maybe I should maybe fuck the city bank double
cash. Maybe you should get that instead. I'm sure that the fucking interest rates are through the
roof. But I mean, I just just just don't have a problem with interest. So I just don't worry about
that. Don't accrue interest and you'll be just pay your balance and it's fine. I mean, yeah,
that's what I do. I don't I've never had any even not even the slightest tiniest temptation to ever
attempt making a payment and not paying off the entire balance never never even entered my mind.
No, no, no, no, no, no, like maybe if I was a kid, maybe if I was a kid, I had no and I had no money
and I had gotten a credit card with like a $3,000, you know, credit credit limit as soon as you hit
18 you start getting bombarded with those things they want you as soon as you're in college just
like start partying off your credit card and then they fuck you literally for life. Yeah,
because between like imagine racking up like 10 grand worth of credit card debt at 19 plus
you're already like 30 to 40 grand in the whole for college like that's how you get wage slaves.
God, I'll fucking mighty. God, I'll fucking mighty. Yeah, for sure. No, prop probably good.
Probably good that I never got one when I was like, well, I don't know. I mean, I was never I was
I was always pretty frugal. I would have looked at that $2,500 MacBook Pro maxed out and been like,
yeah, it's for school. It's for school. Maybe, maybe based. But you know what?
It's all good now. Now I got I got my new universal ring. I'm going to make it. I'm going to make it,
baby. So I don't know anything else to say about that. No, money's gay, but find your money's gay,
but I guess but I guess so am I. I guess I'll look into a credit card. I tried to do it before,
but I was overwhelmed and I, are you are you also a debit card card? Yeah.
Oh, don't be don't be like me. Don't wait until you're fucking one foot in the grave
to start to start building credit. I told I told my I was talking to my other friend
that I live with about this and he was like, yeah, yeah. No, when I was a kid,
uh, me and my friend, he told a story. He said me and my friend, when we were kids,
when we were in high school, we decided we wanted to start building credit.
So we both got credit cards and we would buy one Twix bar a week with our credit cards.
It's like 99 cents. I couldn't, I couldn't believe it. I, well, he doesn't, his credit
card is not as good as well. No, he has, he, I mean, he has a pretty good card. So I guess it
worked as fine. He's got one of the ones that's like, one of the ones that's got these weird
thing that's like the year is divided into quarters and each quarter, a different like
segment of things gives like a 5% cashback rate on, but everything else is like 1%. So it's like
during January to March, it's like, you know, a theater and entertainment. And then the March
to July, it's like, oh, travel and transit and gas and, and you know, whatever. So he's got one
of those things. So yeah, I guess it worked out. Lemau. Churning. Try it out, kids. The younger
you are, the sooner you should start churning. Are you paid for by JPMorgan Chase right now?
Because that sounds like terrible advice. I'm paid for, I'm, I'm, I will be paid by JPMorgan
Chase when I fucking, when I churn their asses. Fuck yeah. It's like, yeah, I'll fucking, yeah,
I'll fucking steal money from a bank. Like yeah, I'll fucking churn a bank and not feel bad about it.
I mean, that's the game, that's the game that everybody's playing. You're just below the income
threshold. You're not supposed to be letting the door. It's bullshit. Yeah. I don't know about,
I don't know about like seven, I don't know about like seven grand in four months. I don't know if
I can swing that one. No lower one. 500 in two months? Yeah, I think I can swing that.
I can get that free $200. No problem. No problem at all, sir.
Dab. Well, I want to keep talking about, I want to keep talking about credit cards because now
they're my new thing this week, but we can, we can move on.
Yeah. I don't even know. You can go to voicemails if, if, I mean, if we're all, if we're all ready.
Yeah. I got a topic, but I don't know what it's the right thing to talk about.
Bring it up. Bring it up. Bring it up. Bring it up. Bring it up. Bring it up. Bring it up. Bring it up.
Come on, please. Come on. You can't just say that. Yeah. Well, I was thinking about like gender,
right? It's, it's a thing that is. It's true. Debate. Debate. I was thinking about how gender is
similar to language in that words can be lost to time and new words can come into the common
vernacular and, you know, definitions of words can change in the same way that gendered things,
things that are associated with being masculine or feminine can also change over time and be
forgotten or rediscovered or new things can crop up. And I was just, yeah, I didn't really have much
else to say about it. I was just like, huh, you know, it is a language and that's, that's, that's
interesting. I mean, you know, you know, the pink used to be a baby boy color. You know that?
Listen, listen, as a cis male, nobody is more qualified to speak on the topic
of gender than I am. So my, so let me, so my spicy take, my spicy take about gender,
I don't even think it's that spicy. I've said it on Twitter and it didn't, didn't get a lot of push
back is that that's what, what gender, gender is language, like to me, like what gender is,
like gender just like being female, being female gendered to me does not then imply, oh,
in that case, she her pronouns, please, to me, the pronouns are the gender, like that's what it means.
So like it is a linguistic construct. It's not like, you know, it's associated with these things
that make, you know, come in and out of fashion for a gender, like wearing pink, wearing a dress,
wearing pants, suit and tie, whatever, short hair, long hair, blah, blah, blah.
But you boil it right down, you know, you grind, grind the universe down to dust and sift through
every atom and every, you'll not, you won't find one molecule of gender, right? Because it's just
words. It's just like, it's, it's just whether you call someone a he or she or a they and, and,
and that's why, that's why when someone is like, oh, read a biology textbook, oh, you got a,
you got a dick or a pussy, you're like, you fool, you have missed, you have missed the thread,
you've missed the forest for the trees, we're talking about language here, you oaf, get your mind
out of the gutter, we're simply talking about the words we refer to a person with, that's what's,
that's what's at issue. And that's why there's no like, even if you could empirically prove someone's
gender, which you fucking can't, or sorry, like biological sex, which you fucking can't, because
it's like so much more complicated than you think you rube. It wouldn't matter, because at the end
of the day, it's about the words themselves. All that other stuff is subsumed. It's under, it's,
it's, that's all, that's all secondary. As usual, a political conversation is, breaks down immediately
due to different, uh, uh, understandings and definitions used by both sides of the argument.
And so two people in an argument are arguing two completely different things using the same words.
Yeah. And it doesn't work. What does. Gender really confuses people. They just can't separate it from
biological sex. And they, they, they understand it to be a rigid thing and they can't imagine
the gender could be. I mean, that's what you've been taught. Yeah.
Yeah. What, what, what bugs me, what bugs me is like someone who's like that. So they'll, they'll,
they say that they understand. Because like in theory, even if you don't want to grant that it's
true, in theory, it's not hard to understand how like gender and biological sex could refer to
two different things. Even if you don't grant that they do, it's not a hard concept to understand
that they could. So they'll say like, yes, I understand that gender, like gender being different
from sex, but then like if, if you grant that, and if you accept that as, as the case, like
there is nothing, there's nothing more to argue about. Like there's simply no, there's simply no
case then to say like, oh, but you have a penis. I don't think people or whatever. Like you've,
you've already given, I think they just don't get that far. Well, they claim, they claim that they,
sometimes they claim that, okay, I mean, there's the people that are like, oh, this is cultural
Marxism. Oh, you've, you've changed the meaning of the word. Like, no, gender is the same thing.
Like, okay, that's one category of person. But then there's another category of person
that does like sort of pretend to grant that point, but then continue to defend their original
position that implicitly does not grant it, which is, which is like doubly irritating.
Yeah, it's like, I see what you're saying. Like, you have to, you have to, you have to
deal with the, you have to deal with these two different people and two different,
in two completely different ways. It's like someone saying, you know,
I see what you're saying and subtitles doesn't see what they're saying.
It's just that you just, you're just pretending to, to, to, you know, so that you can launch
into your own thing about, by the way, I'm right. I'm smart.
It's like, you like, you like pretend, you like pretend to grant the position, but then you
argue as though you didn't grant it. And it's like you never granted it in the first place.
Because like, if you, if you, if you, if the two people talking think that they agree on that,
but then you say like, okay, it's like, okay, we agree. Gender and sex different. However,
males have, men have a penis and women have a vagina and, you know, two plus two equals four.
It's like, what do you, what is the other person supposed to do? It's like, no, but
you, you just said, you just said something that should contradict that. And nevertheless,
you have said the thing. You were supposed, we were supposed to be past this,
but actually you, you like, you just snuck under the goalposts and like just went,
went past me when I thought we were progressing in this other direction. I don't know.
I've seen people do this before. Bad faith, bad faith argumentators, bad faith interlocutors
abound. Yeah. And I curse them. I curse them. There was a guy, I argued with a guy
on Twitter the other day, a dipshit who I have been seeing, like who I've been seeing,
a lefty Twitter, like saying has been annoying them lately, a fem, femboy lover 69, a great,
a great man. And he is a real piece of shit and arguing with him is so infuriating because he
literally, he doesn't even make arguments. He will, he will occasionally say, he will occasionally
make a statement of fact or what he thinks is that he'll, he'll say something about the
topic again. He was talking about communism. He was like, huh, communists are hypocrites
if they use Teespring to sell T-shirts. Right. That's, this was his argument. It was like,
cause, cause, cause Teespring is a company, is a privately owned company and therefore they
shouldn't do it. And his contention was that, um, it's hypocritical because it's like, yeah, yeah.
Like they're not forced to use Teespring. They could, you know, have a press in their home.
They could screen print themselves. And it's like, the problem with this is like, okay,
what you're actually arguing is that like screen printing or self pressing is better,
which is probably true. But the conclusion you're pretending is like follows from this,
is that therefore it's hypocritical to do it, which is, which is not, is not true.
I think what he's trying to argue, I think what he's trying to argue is that you're,
you don't believe in business or capitalism there, or there, but you're using a capitalistic,
endeavor to get your product. Therefore you're supporting something you hate.
And it's like, yes. And it's just like such a tired argument. It's like,
are libertarians hypocrites for paying taxes? You know, it's just like,
yeah, you can, you can believe something while being forced to like, we're all,
we're all live in the system, you know, and we can, we can, you can believe something even
if you can't practice it. This is like common. If he had said like, it would be better and more
in line with communistic values to, you know, self-produce, I would say, yeah, probably, but
you know, maybe they couldn't afford to press or like, you know, maybe like the quality of screen
printing they weren't happy with, you know, maybe market than just like your local area.
It's more convenient to be able to have people be able to purchase it themselves, you know.
Yeah. Like there are, there are trade-offs, like there are trade-offs for this. And like,
yeah, is it kind of unfortunate and maybe less than optimal that this is a privately owned company?
Yeah, probably, probably they would like to own the means of production in this case.
And I would agree with that. But that's not what he said. He said like, oh, they're hypocrites for
doing it, which like, you're an idiot. And you know, arguing with him about this,
the way he would argue is I would just like get to a point and like, we would get to the end of
like a string of like back and forth. And I would like say something. And he would just say like,
nah. And like, that would be it. That would, that would be like the terminating. He would terminate
the cut with just like, nah. Or he in the middle of it, he would just be like, you've already
been proven to be a liar. And I'd be like, where did I lie? I'm like, like, there's like nowhere
anywhere here has there been a lie. But like, that's his he would just say like, he just call
you a liar, call you a hypocrite, not like prove it or anything. But like, because he said it,
like, I don't know. I don't know. This guy, this guy is like, oh, he's only been on Twitter
a couple months. But he's like, he's such a prolific and vigorous bad faith argument maker
that he's got like 15k followers of like, yes, of like, scrambling little like knuckle
draggers who are just like, fucking hungry, who are hungry for the taste of boot leather.
Is it just debate people on Twitter? And he's here to provide. He's here to provide, baby.
That's all he does. I, he, I think he runs a blog too. I mean, I don't think he's like on
YouTube or anything. I just don't. Doesn't don't you have anything better to do?
I mean, this is working for me. It is. But it's just so sad.
It's it's sad. And it makes me mad. Like that he's making bad arguments, just the fact that like,
this is what you're going to choose to spend your limited amount of time doing.
I mean, I would imagine he's not that. I mean, any time, any time, any time spent on Twitter,
you know, what is wasted? That much is true. The two weeks I was off Twitter were the two
best weeks of like the last 12 months easily, just in terms of like, just mental clarity.
He's he's probably a teenager or whatever. He's also he's also probably he's also probably
like Armenian. You think? What makes you say that? Yes. Because
there's a there's a I'm not I'm not the only one who's noticed it. And I'm not trying to be racist
or anything. There's actually there's actually there's anecdotes. There's actually data. I've
seen data. I've seen charts where like, oh, I don't know. I don't know what he looks like.
But like, he reminds me of like, Glink, right? A little bit. Oh, there's there's a certain
trend. There's a certain trend among white people. And like Armenians are like, they are Caucasians.
So like, they are technically white people, even though they're like, you know, they have darker
skin. But there is a trend where in like, the more like kind of the less white a white person looks,
like the more like socially conservative they are. This is this is like true. And I know I'm and I
know I'm being a little racist here. But like, I'm this is this is data driven. Why Armenian though?
What do you mean by that? Oh, well, that's just an example of like, that's like, just a group of
people who a group of people who are Caucasian, but who are like, have like kind of darker skin
and sort of have the like, kind of Mediterranean look to them. I should probably like cite my sources
on this so I don't come off as like a fucking weirdo. Am I am I late? I feel weird. That feels
pretty weird. Does that feel weird? Should I cut this part? I'm not weird. I'm not talking about
just like, I wouldn't just say that I wouldn't just say this because I like met some shitty Armenians
that were dicks. Like, I'll admit, I'm not educated enough to know if you're bullshitting
pulling this out of your ass or not. I'm as a neophyte. It sounds kind of strange.
Does it sound weird? Oh, fuck, I'm racist. Oh, no, I horse, horseshoe theory is real.
Horseshoe theory is real. I've proven it. Um, um, oh, I'm, I'm googling, I'm googling.
Dark skin, white.
European. The only, the only time I've heard, it's right next to Turkey. The only time I've
heard of Armenia was knowing that Maddox was Armenian, I think, like his family was from there.
Okay. Well, I found one that says, this is not the same, but I found a report from the
Washington Post that says lighter skinned minorities are more likely to support Republicans,
which is kind of the inverse. Well, not the, it's sort of the obverse of what I was saying.
Oh no, I can't find it. I can't, I swear to God, I saw a graph. I swear to God, I saw data. I'm not
just making this up. I'm scared now. I'm scared to release this. Did you get the orange drunk?
Edit me out of this entire episode. And come up with a graph in your dreams. No. No. Dude,
Pixar didn't happen, Ben. You know what? After the episode, I'm going to go look it up. I'm going
to, I'm going to send Eleazar the graph and be like, show this on screen. Show this on screen
right now. Prove it. I have proved that I have data and data means you're not racist. I don't know.
Hey guys, Ben from the future here. I went and looked and I found it. I found this post about
the study. The post says, and I quote, darker skinned whites measured via a light reflectant
spectrophotometer identify more strongly with their white racial identity and are more likely to hold
conservative political views on racialized issues and support Trump. So there you go.
I'll try and find the graph. Eleazar, show the graph. I was kind of trying to be jokey about it.
I don't know if it came off like I was making a joke. I am sorry. I apologize for the discomfort
that you may be feeling that you may have felt about some of my less sensitive comments. I assure
you my discomfort was much greater as I will be flops. You will hear me flop sweating and
trying to fucking cope for the next several minutes of the podcast. So right back to it.
You know what? He just, this guy's just like, he's just fervent. He's just fervent in a way
that makes me think, I don't know. He's, you know what? Never mind. He just reminds me of
Glink. You know, literally he just reminds me of Glink. That's why, that's probably why I think
he's Armenian. That's probably why. Okay, cool. Is Glink Armenian? Yes. Fuck, I think so. 99%.
I'm like sweating. I'm like sweating that I've said something that I've said something that I've
said something nasty. How about the, I can't hear you. How about those, how about those voicemails?
How about, how about those voicemails? Oh God. Oh God. Oh God. There's a lot. There's a lot again.
Oh shit. Oh God, I gotta pull them off. There's like 27. Speak pipes? No, 22. I forgot there's
20 on page, on 25. All of them are going to be mad about me and Tom not listening to a lot of them.
What's, are they? What's the first one? The first one that I see is from Blind Gable.
Right? That's, uh, I don't know. I mean, what was the, the last one was left is
him in my PC. Yeah, that's the last one. Okay. Then, then we should start with Blind Gay Boy.
All right, let's, let's, let's do it. All right. Here we go. Here we go, baby. I'm ready.
Three, two, one, go. infamous homeless woman, did you know once wrote a song called sad gay boy
in which the titular sad gay boy goes to sleep at sunrise because quote, his weary,
bleary eyes can't handle all the light. Do you want to be a sad gay boy? Of course not.
So stare right into that burning colossus. Keep your cute little eye globes on that shit and get
right up in its business. What do you think did you wear shades? Get out there and stare down the
sun king. Whatever. The Procrastinator's podcast is not advocate staring directly into the sun
without protective eyewear. We did, we did though. We, we, we, we did advocate for that.
We were all twisted now that we're sober. Clearly not a good idea.
No, you were twisted. I was swasted. All right. All right. And I don't remember
anything of the sort. Cool. Cool. Jilted samurai. All right. Three, two, one, go.
Konnichiwa. I am a leader of samurai orderlyness. Benno Sento san, you bring a great dishonor
to summer. I know. I said a racist thing. I did races. I'm sorry. Jilted samurai. Ten
no year, Sento san, but you never return to samurai clan. Why? Why? Instead of you, Benno
Sento san, join the enemy, Antifa clan. I'm sorry. Fuck all you. Sorry, man.
Retro Benno san. But until you next time, sayonara. Sayonara. I couldn't, you know,
they just had cool looking armor. I like their color scheme better. I like the red and black.
It was edgy, for an edgy goth like myself. Sorry. I'm sorry. I deseed for a second.
What happened? You listen to the next one. Oh, my, my former sensei is mad at me for
joining Antifa. Don't, don't worry about it. Okay. He'll, he'll get over it. Okay. Next one.
My wee wee is in the blender, daddy. Oh, I can't wait. Three, two, one, go.
Yeah. What's up, guys? I just, I got a couple of things to say. First off, thank you to Nate.
If not for your Radcon lecture, would have never read One Piece. It's become one of my favorite
manga of all time. It's probably second to only Gunmul. You know, being in Australia, where, you
know, bushfires straight into COVID, shitty year, but you really help, you know, One Piece really
helped pick me up and I wanted to thank you for encouraging me to read it. Secondly,
hope everything's going all right with Digi. Thirdly, last time Endless Jess was on,
he was talking about how pro wrestling shitty now without crowds. I've been a pro wrestler for
eight years now. I've worked in about six different countries. Just got to tell you right now, Jess,
you're a fucking idiot. What the hell did you expect? Pro wrestling plays inherently to a
crowd. That's our job. We're working for live reactions without the live crowd. Of course,
it's not going to be a live reaction. What the fuck were you expecting? At the same time,
I don't know why the fuck you're watching WWE if you want good quality of pro wrestling. It's
fucking barely pro wrestling. And fourth and most importantly, Ben, go fuck yourself, buddy.
All right, bye. Cool.
The Australian pro wrestler cold end.
I mean, shitting on Ben, totally understandable. Shitting on Jesse for agreeing with you,
kind of strange.
Wait, what did he say that Jesse said was stupid?
Jesse said that remember when he was talking about how because of COVID,
WWE, they're doing shows without crowds. And he said it was dumb. And we watched that like one
clip on his MacBook where they were just like wrestling in an empty arena. And it was really
fucking weird. Yeah. This guy said like, of course, it's dumb. What did you expect? You're an idiot,
Jess. And it's like, what do you mean? But he's, yeah, okay. That's weird. Well, I don't fuck you,
in the blender. I don't think I don't think Jesse's saying, oh, man, it's bad now was in any way
him expressing surprise. I was more like saying, look how bad this is. I would send you to voice
jail, but frankly, you're not worth the paperwork. All right, next one is from sunny.
Three, two, one, go. Hello, everybody. I just got done doing one of my first well,
I'm going to call 100% completion runs of the shower. So I got a minute and 54 on a
shampoo conditioner, face wash and body soap. I got sub two minute time using the conditioner
because I use staying conditioner after I was in the shower. So I didn't need to rinse it out
or worry about the time it takes for the conditioner to be in. So I'm wondering if anybody
else is any more optimization of the speed run of the shower or this is like this is the kind
of fastest we're going to get. It's the shower speed run thing. Yeah, I haven't I haven't tried it
myself actually. I always like like using the shower as like a fucking like waterfall meditation
zone. I stay in there for like 20 hours. It's true. It's true. Not me. I'm just fucking I'm in
and out. I'm in and out, rinse off, get it get it done. It's too it's too hot. It's too fucking
hot to be showering these days. We just make it colder showers. No, that's that's terrible.
No, no, no gets the job done. Yeah. Yeah, it's not it's not good though. I don't like it.
No, no, very workman like actually I should be practicing my shower speed runs.
But I don't want to stress about it.
Like, oh, I don't I don't freak myself out. I'm gonna slip on some soap from from from overexertion.
I would not speed run a shower just seems not worth it.
That's like seems to dump a bucket over your head. I feel like the shower speed runs have like caught
on like like like we get we get like a relatively high volume of voicemails pertaining to shower
speed runs. It seems like something just autistic enough for our audience to latch on to.
You know, like why don't you just like get some soap and some water and like a bucket and then
just dump it over your head doing any percent completion run. That seems like the most optimal
way to do it. Hmm. Agreed. Agreed. Agreed.
Is someone try that and tell us what your time is? Yeah.
All right. Next one is Oh God, it's a minute 30.
Now you understand why we skip some of these.
Spit out that red pill three, two, one, go.
We can we can stop it if it's born democratization of the voicemails by playing literally every
message that comes into the inbox. But when you don't screen for voicemails,
occasionally some weird stuff's going to come through. For instance, the other week when a
young man left a voicemail asking the Jewish question. Now I appreciate everyone on the
pod attempts to argue against this question, but it was pretty clear that y'all were not
ready or prepared for that discussion. Why would this just leaves, you know, wide open spaces
for these far right talking points to be planted into the minds of your young and impressionable
listeners, which we all know that you have plenty of in the future. I would simply suggest
that whenever far right propaganda comes into your voicemail, you simply respond with this is
far right propaganda, not based in facts and logic. We will not justify it with discussion here.
For those of you who would like to see why this is simply not true, I suggest that you
go to YouTube and search Vosh answers the Jewish question, and you will find Vosh systematically
debunk and destroy this talking point with facts, evidence and logic. Thanks for all you do boys.
Uh, keep it up. Fuck Nazis. Okay. Yeah, I forget exactly what the thing was, but yeah, I guess I
don't I don't remember what the I do remember us talking about a couple weeks ago. I think I do
remember us talking about the Jewish question. I don't remember what we said. I'm pretty. Yeah,
it's true. It's true that like, uh, it's it is it is a far right talking point. Sure. I see he's
got a point. I don't think it's I don't want to say I don't think it's a big deal, but I think the
way we handle it pretty downplayed it pretty effectively. I mean, my my intent, my intent
was to to to, uh, I mean, maybe I didn't, maybe I didn't do it as thoroughly as Vosh. I don't know.
I haven't I haven't seen Vosh's Jewish question video, but, uh, my intent was to be like, oh,
the Jewish question, here's why here's why it doesn't make any sense. I don't know. But he's got a
point. This is far. This is far right propaganda is a pretty reasonable response to a lot of things.
I will I will consider that in the future. Mr. Spit out, sir. Okay, next one.
Plan B. Three, two, one, go.
So I haven't listened to the podcast in a long while. I haven't since I think around
episode 101, 102. I got a job around then and, um, haven't had any time to listen to podcasts.
But now I've been thrown back into need them because of COVID. So I figured what better way to
waste time than listening to the podcast. It's the best. The only one I've listened to so far
is Ben cast episode. Yeah, good choice. I think it's really cool that you guys have this voicemail
thing now. But I did want to say that a lot of the people that I've heard sound like pathetic
beta males with no girlfriend. And I just want to say, imagine how many less there would be
if we bullied them early and often, like they kill themselves. So no, I think,
or maybe I, what I was assuming is that if we bullied them, what he was saying,
that they would stop being those things. What does he mean we? What does he mean we?
Like we as a society? I guess. I feel like being bullied is where they come from.
Yeah. I mean, I don't know how seriously, I don't know how seriously to take this question.
Yeah, like, like, I think people, yeah, people become you, you, you, someone who is quote unquote
a beta male feels like socially uncomfortable because they're not accepted into society.
Right. Um, yeah, you're not, you're not conforming to a certain extent,
yeah, certain social expectations. You're given guff for that by the people around you.
And most people crumble under that pressure and further recede into these shadows of society.
And don't ever develop interpersonal skills that allow them to flourish in a more, uh,
conventional manner. So I feel like bullying people would bring the 1% 1 to 2% of people who
kind of like take that as a challenge and rise above it and make them stronger at the extent of
to the damage of the 98% remaining who would just be upset by it.
Uh, I, yep. It sounded like it actually sounded like a like a comedic sort of like,
you know, I agree. I think he was going for it, but I'm not laughing. So I have no choice,
but to respond as though it were meant 100% sincerely. You just, you just can't tell us
sometimes. Yeah. That's just the society we live in now. What's a joke and what isn't?
Who knows? It's a social construct. It's hard to know what it's a joke when the entire world's
become one. Next one is Callum. Three, two, one, go. Hey, so it doesn't seem fair to me that all
of the PCP members get to go to this $30,000 Radcon event, even though some of these members
only show up for like four episodes a year. It just doesn't, doesn't seem that fair to me.
What do you think? Well, the Radcon four, I think I'm trying to think like what exactly
he's referring to, like me, Nate, Ben, Tom are the most frequent, I think on the podcast.
Yeah. He's probably talking, I mean, Digi is, I mean, I wouldn't say he's on, I mean, he hasn't,
sorry, she hasn't been on in a while. But like before, like she has periods where she's on pretty
regularly. Yeah. So maybe, I think he's talking about, maybe Digi and definitely Jesse. I mean,
Jesse wasn't planning on being there. Yeah. That was like, that was a bonus. You know,
he had nothing to do with like any of the money or the payments he drove up there by himself,
completely separate from all of us. So Jesse's just a bonus. Like that was just icing on top of
the Radcon cake. Yeah. I think the thing that's like, the podcast is, you know, the show we do
together, but it's not the reason we have become popular enough to get a Radcon made. It's because
individually we've done good things. So like Digi being allowed to come is like, of course,
right. Like people were paid to see Digi hang out with us. We're doing better work outside
of the podcast. And even in this channel itself, the Radcon content is the tentpole stuff. And
this is just the glue sticking the Radcons together. Like, I don't think anybody would deny that.
I would definitely like it if the others showed up more because I like talking to them.
Yeah. Yeah, where is everybody? I don't know whether it would be like any grounds to exclude
anyone from a new Radcon if they wanted to come. Right. I mean, if Digi did a ton of like,
of the reward stuff leading up to Radcon and a lot of the promotion. So like, you know,
the regard. Like, like, yeah, Jesse was only like kind of involved because he didn't really do
any of like the prep work or like the other stuff associated. He was just kind of there for it. And
like we, you know, took we took that into account and everything. But like, yeah, Digi like helped.
Digi was helping with like, yeah, like, you know, looking for a house and all this stuff. And like,
you know, we were, we were like, yeah, maybe we don't all we all show up to the podcast as much as
one another equivalently. But like, we all we all chipped in and like, we're working on like,
making Radcon itself happen. So like, it was it was a collaborative effort among all. I mean,
I feel it was pretty fair. Not only that, the episode participation is all paid separately.
And so you're already getting paid for your appearances on the episode or lack thereof.
If you do not come to the, the procrastinators podcast, you don't get paid for the episodes that
are made through the Patreon. You don't get nothing. So if you use her up for zero episodes a month,
you get $0 for that month. So I feel like that, that calculation is already taken care of
pre Radcon itself. Agreed. We got a system. It's convoluted and dumb. It's very convoluted. I
was looking through the spreadsheet the other day and I like could not fucking. Well, the spreadsheet
was made by Nate and you can tell. I think it's just got some like, I think there's just kind
of some like random crap in there that's like not even like really data. It's just sort of numbers
in cells that don't relate to any of anything else. He has like notes for himself on the spreadsheet
that does the calculation. So there are some like extra fields. And I know it also has to handle
the other channels attached to that Google account. So there's some extraneous information
besides the PCP numbers themselves, they have to be calculated. So, you know, because, because
you're only allowed one AdSense thing per Google account. And so it's really annoying the way that
all works. It's, it's, it's, it's YouTube being terrible as, as it is. So yeah, makes sense.
Next one, productivity tips. All right, I'm game. Three, two, one, go.
Okay, tips to the PCP members here on productivity. If any of you ever feel like you're not being
productive enough, send a voicemail into this show, this PCP show, it'll really get you going.
Trust me on that one. Okay, goodbye. No, do not listen to this man.
We'll never know, though, whether he was telling the truth. He could have gone and made
the Mona Lisa too, right after this.
Imagine a sequel to the Mona Lisa.
I've never made it. Never. It was made on YouTube and MS Paint.
Oh yeah, we did that. Is that a reference to something?
What? Didn't, didn't we do that for a draw cast?
Like MS Paint drawings and some one of, I think I did MS Paint drawings.
We did. I was talking about the guy who did like the remade the Mona Lisa in MS Paint on YouTube in
like 2006. Is it good? It's like pixel for pixel, like exact copy.
Wow. Yeah, it's one of those videos. Pixel for pixel isn't that interesting.
What if he just literally took a picture of it and copied the pixels? Well, no, it's a speed
draw of him doing it with the MS Paint tools recreating the Mona Lisa.
Yeah, okay. It's impressive. It's impressive. It's one of those things.
Oh God, this next, this next one. No, voice jail. Let's wait.
He, no, that's what he wants. He wants to go to voice jail. He's, he's baiting us.
All right, then we'll just skip it. I'm tempted to skip it. Let's yeah.
Stop telling us, stop telling us about Persona 5.
Okay, next one. Consume product. Here's why. HBO Max Rupa.
Okay, I'll give this guy one more chance. Three, two, one, go.
Tom mentioned that streaming services are like bringing back cable, but actually it's kind of
not true. Like kind of true, but kind of not true. Here's why. Okay. So like on cable, you know,
it's only on your TV pretty much. And you get, you like, this show is on Tuesday at whatever
time. And this show is that, you know, you got, you got to like be at the TV at certain times.
No more of that shit. You know, streaming services, you can just turn it on
and watch whatever the fuck you want and watch it whenever the fuck you want, bro.
And there's like significantly less ads, which is great, bro. Like, come on. And also they're
like way cheaper than cable. Like isn't cable like, I don't know, like 40 or something a month
or whatever. I don't even know how many, maybe I'm actually wrong about this point, but like
streaming services are generally like, I don't think there is a streaming service that is more
than 20 months. Like, bro, they're pretty cheap. And you get so much bang for your buck and you
might be like, why buy things? Well, you feel better about it. You stupid dummy, bro. You know,
like, you work to get money and then you spend the money on things and you feel better than if
you pirated it. You feel better than if you pirated it. No, I feel better when I pirated it.
Give me a fucking break. In any case, pirating is illegal. Don't do it,
bros. Is this a joke? It has to be a joke. You had me go in there for a minute, buddy.
I stopped right before the end. What did he say? He was saying piracy is bad,
don't do it. It's illegal. And you'll feel better if you pay for the thing.
All right. No, he had me going for the first half. No, yeah, that's definitely bait.
Nice ruse. Nice ruse, my dude. Impossible. Hilarious. Next one is anti-piracy on streaming
services. The next four are about streaming. Okay, whatever. Three, two, one. It's the same guy.
Probably. Three, two, one, go. So you also mentioned ripping a show from a streaming
service and then putting it on a torrent or pirate or whatever. I don't think it's possible to do
that anymore because they've done this thing where if you even just take a screenshot or a screen
record, the screen will turn black, at least for HBO Max. I don't know about other things.
I don't care. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. I'm not reading. I don't care,
but I'm skipping the next one too. Fuck it. We're moving on to Digibro's pretentious explanation.
Yes. Yes. Ready? Three, two, one, go. Let me explain to you the point of my previous voicemail.
You see, Digi, like six years ago or some shit made a video about the wind rises and it's like
quick analysis or whatever and it's like four or five minutes and like almost all of it is pretentious
bullshit. And then recently, separately in the PCP, he has like said that like people are stupid
on voicemails or whatever, but like, he's so pretentious, bro. What the fuck? That's the
theme. That's the point of the voicemail. You just didn't connect the dots. That sucked. Fuck you.
Fuck off, Digibro, is pretentious guy. You are a fucking mutant. Do you understand why I skip
voicemails now? Are you getting it? Oh my god. This is just so bad. It's the same voicemail again.
Shut the fuck up. It was entirely just as stupid as before, but I think you had a complete
garbage. I don't know. I feel like voice jail's too good for this fucking monster. No, no, no, no, no,
Voice jail has kind of become a meme. It's a badge of honor now. It's been undone.
Voice jail has become a mark of privilege. Yeah, oh god, fuck. Three square meals a day,
all your needs taken care of. I'd kill to be in voice jail right now. All right, voice bad credit,
how about that? Yeah, they'll never be able to churn as long as they would. Voice churnless
status churnless. Okay. Unchurnable. Okay, I've calmed down. I've calmed down. Next one is
remember the grinding religion? I do. Three, two, one, go. That one guy mentioned getting into
the PCP when he was 11. I just wanted to talk about how I got into the PCP. It was episode,
I think it's 107 religion. It was really great. And you might be wondering, what is the fucking
point of this voice? What is the point of voice? The point is grind jealousism. You got to grind,
and then that's the amount of time you get in the afterlife. That was the religion that you guys made
up for that episode. And you never brought it up again. And I want you to bring it back. Grind
jealousism is so base, bro. Grind jealousism. I don't remember this at all. Like a religion about
grinding as it is. Like on a skateboard? Yeah. No, like grinding, like getting worked on, I thought.
I choose to believe that it means the more time you spend grinding on rails on your fucking
skateboard is the more time you spend in heaven. You know what? That's even better. I'll tell you.
You got to get a streak go. It's a life as a Tony Hawk level, and there's a time limit,
and you've got to get a certain score to get into heaven. You got to be God's gift to grind.
You got to be chaining. Everywhere you go in life, you got to be chaining your moves,
you got to be aerialing, you got to be manualing from rail to rail. It's the only way.
It was the same guy that we were just saying the same thing.
It was the same guy, I guess. I think it was. Okay, it cancels out. No,
fuck it. Okay, okay. I feel like you're more entertained by your grinding explanation. You
are about the voicemail itself. Yeah, you're right. Okay. Okay.
All right, guys. Next voicemail. God, this is another, this is another sequel voicemail. It's
the guy that said like vocals are instrumentals. No, I don't care. Yes, of course they're
instrumental. Shut up. Yeah, thanks for your voicemail. Love you. Thanks for watching.
Thanks for the ad revenue. Fuck off. No more. Next one. Slime Caves background music from Ben's
Dream. Holy shit. I'm stoked for this one. I am fucking, I am ready. Are you ready?
It's zero seconds. Do we have to copy the link? Yeah, I'm gonna copy the link. All right, just
gonna do that. To vocaru. Oh, good old vocaru. Wait, I think he doesn't realize that the link
he sent does not link to his recording. Oh, no, it doesn't work. Bruh. This is just that I have
to press record and this is my own thing. This is not what he thinks it is. Oh,
Bruh, your LinkedIn work. Bruh, you gotta send it again. I gotta know the background music to
my slime cave dream. What if it's gone forever? Send it to Twitter? Oh, no. You must have saved
somewhere. Well, I mean, call again, call again, try again. I want to hear it. Next one. Digimon
God. Sounds sick. I'm in. Three, two, one, go. Digivices are Kino and the guy that recommended
them as a genius. I didn't know Wave 3 was out, but thanks dude for letting me know.
You all need to get a Digivice. You all need to go to Radcon 5 and start your Digivices at the same
time. You all get eggs at the same time. And then at the end of the week, whoever has the best
Digimon is king. Oh my God, this thing needs to happen. This needs to be one of the main events
of Radcon 5. I want to see a Digimon battle. The battle system is deep. It's not just, oh, it's
a little toy. No, there's vaccine, virus, data types. There's like fucking, there's an element
wheel. There's a fucking, how much you love your Digimon impacts its power. How much you feed your
Digimon impacts its power. It's true. There's so much fucking strategy. There's fucking tag
battles. There's fucking tag team 2v2 Digimon battles in this fucking little key chain toy.
Pokemon is shit. Digimon is Kino. Do Digimon for real. Don't let this idea fade away.
You know what? I'm totally, I'm totally with you. I'm totally down. Yes. I'm ready to go.
Really? Yeah. I have the first revision. I got it for my sister for Christmas and
December. We got to get, we got to get the newest, like for the next Radcon, for this tournament,
we got to get the new ones, right? Well, who knows what gen they'll be on by the time
Radcon 5 rolls around, but okay. It'll be pretty funny to like have in the background of like,
I don't know, you know, it was a live stream. We got the webcam and like four out of the five
people on screen are like clicking their little Digimon things. No, I got to have all of my
Kabuteremon just took a little poop and I got to clean it up. I'm sorry. I can't, I can't join you.
Yeah. I got to feed, I got to clean it up and then feed it back to him.
Fuck. Wasn't that a thing, wasn't that a thing you could do with the, could you like try and
like tell it to eat its own shit or something? Am I like crazy? You're definitely make a matter.
Could you like, or could you like, like point to it shit or something to like shame it or
something like that? I feel like there was something you could do, like when your Digimon
had shit, when you could like do something with the shit that like the Digimon would be like
sad. You might be thinking of like Digimon World, the PlayStation. I don't think that was on the
pets, on the V pets. Hmm. I don't think I ever played that. I don't know. Do you? I don't know.
I just want to play with Digimon shit. That's what I, that's what I want. I mean, it's pretty good.
It's good time. Next one. Genderbender. Three, two, one, go.
I thought I would change things up and actually ask a question with this, you know, voicemail.
So stupid. If you guys turned into a hot girl tomorrow, how much of a slut would you be?
Um, I would, uh, I mean, with girls, probably a lot. I would be, I would be a lesbian
and I would make out with girls. I would, I would, uh, uh, uh, yeah, I guess I would,
I'd have the same answer. I don't know. I would probably be quite a bit. Yeah,
I'd probably be quite a bit of a slut. I'd probably try and like find that balance where
you're not like too much of a slut, but you're still making money. Like I'd probably be this
Twitch streamer. Yeah, that's what I was going to say. No. No, you fools. That's not what the
question's about. All right. Well, if I was a woman, that's what I'd probably do. I'd probably
cash that check. He's okay. He's not asking how would you monetize it? He's asking like,
he's asking like, would you, he's asking like, would you, okay, he wants to know if you'd
fuck. He wants to know if you'd fuck. Well, what I'm trying to, yeah, yeah, yeah. I, like, if,
if it suddenly happened, I don't like, I would still be the same person underneath.
I don't know how to like immediately get laid. I would just be like, I don't know,
I'll stay inside instantaneous thing. But if you were, if you were a hot, if you were a hot girl,
it would be pretty easy. Well, I know it'd be pretty easy, but like, like, I don't know,
like what to do. The only thing I know to do is to be online. So I would start a Twitch stream
and see what happens. I mean, well, I mean, during COVID, yeah. I mean, if I were a hot girl,
it'd be hard for everybody at this point. Yeah. If I were a hot girl and I wanted to have some
lesbian sex, I mean, I don't know, I would just go to like a bar or something and just like be,
oh, but then guys would be hitting on me and I'd be close. You gotta, you gotta get on like
Tinder girls only and then just swipe and because you're attractive, you'll, you'll get all the
matches because it works. Yeah, maybe that would be, I mean, you're already a Tinder champion.
You can just use all your pro strats. This is, this is making me, this is making me understand
even just this, this easiest, simplest little thought experiment. I feel like I understand
the female experience a little bit better. Like, yeah, I wouldn't want to go, I wouldn't want to
go like out to like a club or something. Cause like, yeah, I'd be guys would be hitting on me
and I'm like, I'm not interested in them. Like I don't, I don't want them. Like they'd, like,
there's a chance that like a girl would hit on me, but probably not because girls are not used to
being like aggressive like that. So it would just, it would just be guys hitting. I would have to go
out and put in the effort. I would have to go out. God, it would be, it would be the same as being
a man. I just have to go out and hit on the girl. I'd have to take matters into my own hands and I
hate that. I don't want to do that. That's dumb. What, what's even the point? What's even the point
of being a girl? If I, if I have to go and fucking put the work in. Making lots of money from Beta
Man. That's literally the point. The point of being, the point of being a girl is that you don't
have to put the work in without that. It's worthless. That's why you got to start a Twitch stream,
keep all of them at state or more away from you and collect all of their money. I don't care
about money. Well, I mean, how much are we talking? Uh, hundreds of thousands of dollars, Ben, easily.
Okay. Hundreds of thousands. Yeah. In like a year? If not millions. Yes. A lot of these streamers
make hundreds of thousands of dollars a month, Ben. Look it up. It's really okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. But you can't just be any hot girl and make that much. Yes, you can. No, not any hot girl
can just make that much. Have you seen some of these people on Twitch? They have nothing going
for them. But it's not, okay. Personality wise or, or presentation wise. I, I, I understand that you
can be. They just sit there with a shirt unbuttoned and just read the chat. I understand. I understand
that you can be nothing but a hot girl and make that much money. Okay. But that's not to say that
literally any girl that is hot can just hop on Twitch. No, but make that and make that money.
You're already, you're already making money as a man, as an entertainer. You think you put some
tits on you and an attractive face. You're not going to like droople your income. Oh, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. You're not saying like start a new account or like start a new like face
with a new name. It's like start a new identity as a female titty streamer. You're saying, hey guys,
I'm still Tom Oliver, but now I've got tits and I want you to pay for me. No, no, no, no. I'm saying
you would start a new thing, but I'm saying because you're not, you're not just like an empty
husk of a human with some tits. You're still you and like your entire job is to be an entertainer.
So if you're an entertainer and you have all that experience being an entertainer, but now
you have the benefit of being an attractive woman on the internet, you're now playing with a stacked
deck. You have a huge advantage. I'm going to level with you, Tom. I don't feel like I have an
advantage. I feel like I would, I feel like I would in fact be starting over from zero.
You don't think that everything being equal, if you were a woman, you'd be making more money
than you are right now? That's not, I might. No, that's, that's, that might be true. That might
be true. That might be true. That is a fact. That is a fact. Okay. You might be right about that,
but that's not what I'm saying. That's not one zero at least to your patron. But that's not what
I'm saying. Yes, true. But that's not what I'm saying. What I'm saying is that if I were to
be a hot girl and, but start from scratch on like a new account with no preexisting clout,
I do not think that my experience as a podcaster or like online content creator or whatever,
I do not think that that would factor particularly heavily into like whether or not I make it in
like the Twitch titty streaming game, the only fans game. I think I don't think it translates.
I think it does. But I guess one of us is going to have to take the plunge and find out.
Okay. Yeah, that's true. Voice mail, just work your magic, gender bend one of us for science.
I guess we'll just have to find out the hard way. Yes, please and thank you.
Next one? Yep, I guess so. Okay. Next one is another one from Margar. More Margar please.
Three, two, one, go. Margar here. I'm on week two in voice jail. I'm fighting for my fucking life
in here. Ben St. I repeat Ben St. is sending swarms of fucking goons to my cell every hour
on the hour. I'm just barely cleaning on. Luckily, all of his goons are pretty weak.
So I'm being able to hold them off but the sheer mass of the bodies that Ben is sending
against me is getting on my nerves and I'm pretty fucked up right now. We need to abolish the
police state immediately. Please. Also congrats on getting the channel restored. Thanks. I don't
know. It kind of sounds like the police state's doing its job, which is to like go in droves after
his enemies and be defeated. Go in droves after his enemies who have already been locked up,
just to bully him a little, to rough him up. We already won but we want to give ourselves
an opportunity to lose again. He's in jail and I'm just sending like platoons of soldiers
into his cell where he is. Ben just feels so guilty. He has to send these cops in to get
abused so he can like feel better for supporting the police state. Yeah, you run like the police
but you make sure that they're badly trained and ill-equipped and you send them into war.
He's like the ultimate sleeper agent. He's like in the cell but he's like,
he still represents a threat to democracy. Like open fire. We can't let him get away.
He's just sitting there. I don't know. I don't know how it works. I'm not sure. But I like it.
Hey, Marguer. We're going to get you. We're going to get you one of these days.
All right. Next one. British people talking about African drums. That's me. Three, two, one, go.
Wait, is that a bongo in it? Quit sava and a bongo in it? That's not how we speak.
I didn't hear it too quick. I heard bongo. I got a bongo. One more time. Well, I don't have a bongo.
There's a bongo in my basement. It belongs to my neighbor. It's a pair of bongos.
They always come in pairs. I'm going to listen one more time.
I think he's saying, well, it's a bit of a bongo in it, which I don't know. That's what sounds like to
me too. Is it a bit of a bongo? I mean, I've never heard the phrase bongo to be used as any sort of
descriptive word. No, it just sounds like a silly, like, like a, like a little so random sort of thing.
I don't think that's a British thing. This guy's stupid. I think I don't even think this guy's
really British. Sad. Okay, next one. Sefirio creative shipping. Three, two, one, go.
All right. Favorite creative ship. So we've got like Digi Munch with stealing your dad as if it were
easy. I like that a lot of energy there. But like, what are your favorites? Best hypotheticals?
I know Tom and take the Gibbon take Tom Oliver combo on the PCP itself is just chef kiss.
But what are your opinions on best creative shipping? Okay, the challenge here is in which
one makes the funniest name. So fuck. I mean, nothing can top Digi Curious. It was the original.
It was the best. Like, it'll never be beaten. Yeah, true.
What about what about endless Nate? Pretty good, right? What about what about best St.
Ever really get some get some really good content? What about what about what about
mage chi chi mage chi like Munchie mage. Oh, mage chi. Yeah. What about
Gibbon? Tom, fuck, he already he already said that one, but reversed. What about Gibbon?
Naye. Gibbon a because digi name. What about what about the let's go through every possible
permutation. No, it's gonna make a make a spreadsheet. No, we have to go one down the list. Okay.
Voice jail voice jail voice jail everything can voice jail. I don't know. I don't think it's a
I think it's a judge jail. Yeah. Okay. Okay. All right. I'm sorry guys. Come up with good ship
names in in the comments. Yeah, put your best comments since we have agreed. Because I feel
like there probably are some funny ones, but I can't think about this right now. I'm working here.
Last one, friendly friend man Liam. Let's hear what he's got to say. Three, two, one, go.
Howdy there. Whoever may or may not be listening. It is I the mighty.
I'm fucking tired. Very, very exhaustive. Nobody probably apologies.
Can you wasted 20 seconds 20 seconds of our lives. I like what you are. You are a society living
clowns are doing here this podcast thing. I like it. It's cool. We're being trolled.
We're being trolled. Oh, God. Myself seems positive. Shit's bad.
Kippo's cool. Ben's pretty cool.
Munchie's pretty cool. You're all pretty cool. Voice jail voice jail. I don't know if Nate started
to shove yet, but Nate's pretty cool. Or yeah, now definitely.
You know, I can't feel my legs. Apologies. I've been up for like three days at this point.
Nerds have a wonderful, wonderful time. That was the worst voicemail I've ever heard.
It's as close as you can get to a drunk voicemail without him being drunk. I think he's just really
tired. You're sleep drunk at that point. Three days and no sleep. You're fucking gone.
I kind of like it. I kind of like there's you. I've got to remind all the listeners right now
that Ben gave us so much shit for skipping voicemails and then he insists on playing every
single one and they're half garbage. You never know. You never know when you're going to find
buried treasure. I don't know. I kind of like friendly friend manly. This is something really
funny about the title. Yeah. The man said nothing wrong. He was just like the PCP.
It's friendly friend man Liam, right? Yeah, I think it's Liam. He's friendly friend man Liam.
No, I just one word. Friendly friend manly. I mean, it's a positive note to go out on.
It's true. So I think remember to go to sleep every day. Remember to stay hydrated.
And remember to piss. Remember to say poggers. Remember to go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators
and give us your money. $5 a month gets you access to the bonus episodes. Oh,
we should talk about the newest bonus episode. What is it, Ben?
It's the tits cast where me and Gib discuss the age old question tits versus nothing
because there's no alternative. There's simply nothing compare. I can't think of what could
possibly compare to a set of big old mommy milkers. So, so cool. Listen to that.
Unironically based episode. It was very. I agree.
Unironically think it was cool and want people to hear it. $5 a month gets you access to that
episode and a bajillion other bonus episodes. $1 a month. You get access to the discord where
you can talk to us and other people as insane as you for supporting this podcast.
It's about community. It's really a great. It's great. It's 10 out of 10 fantastic in there.
And it's great. It's great. You know, you want to leave a voicemail,
speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail. That's the link for that. And on Twitter,
you want to keep up to date with all the shit, twitter.com slash tpcrastinators.
You know, who just posted on the Twitter or I retweeted neck oblivion fall.
He just made one of his PCP voicemail. Sorry. PCP dating sim songs. He ported it. He put it in
guitar hero or some kind of guitar hero game. And that's like a free download.
Oh, frets on fire for PC. Is that what that is? The free PC version of guitar hero.
I think it's called frets on fire. Cool. Yes. Well, I thought that was pretty fucking neat.
It's pretty good. Yeah. So all right. I think we've made it. We did it. We made it all the
way to the end. We survived. Let's fucking get out of here, shall we? Indeed. Yes. Disperse.
Oh, remember. Okay. Scatter. Scatter. Wait. And shout into the distance. Remember twitch.tv
slash give and take stream. Yes. Yes. Yes. Close it. Goodbye.