I'm going to bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
Man, I have no idea what I'm going to talk about. But whatever.
Well hey, isn't it AntonyLingland this weekend? Is that going on? Have you heard anything?
It is. Yeah, I've been there.
Oh, you were there?
I've been there a couple of times, yeah.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, Kazy Munchy and those guys have been there. I haven't been there the whole time.
I've been there a few hours each day, a little bit.
I mean, that's pretty good. How much time are you really going to spend there?
Yeah, well, I mean, they're there.
Dawn to dusk. Which is fine. I don't know. I couldn't be entertained for that long.
About six hours a day has been my limit. I did it in the evening on Friday and Saturday,
and then I went in the morning on Saturday because I wanted to go to a thing called a
pin trade thing because I had all my endless war slime pins and I was like,
I've got capital to trade, so I showed up and I arrayed all the RFCK pins on the table
and I sat down like a little merchant doing business. It sort of worked.
I got a couple of good trades, although it seemed like, I guess I didn't realize it was a thing.
Some people that I asked were like, I'm only looking for fursona trades.
I want to trade my fursona for someone else's fursona.
Yeah, I guess in hindsight kind of makes sense, but I wouldn't have expected that either.
I didn't know that it's a thing to get your sona as an enamel pin, but now that I think about it,
yeah, why not?
Yeah, I guess now you know how easy it is to get pins made, which maybe is before a seam donning.
It's really not that hard and I asked some people and there are some, you know,
some enterprising furries who will handle it for you if you're a soned individual
and you want to branch into that sort of thing.
There are people in the community that are connected and know how to do it.
If you find yourself bisoned, then you may be able to.
Yeah.
Oh, Kazzy drew me a, you know what?
I want to show you the tag they drew for me.
They drew me one of those, like a badge?
Yeah, a little badge.
Yeah, and that's classic furry contradiction.
You've got to have your cool artist friend draw you a badge to hang next to your con badge.
It's funny.
Everybody's got them.
Everyone's got them, absolutely.
Yeah, literally everybody has a laminated little, because you got your ticket or whatever,
your actual badge that you paid for that you got to show to get into the dealer's den or what have you.
But that's bullshit.
Right, nobody cares.
They want to see your character badge.
They want to know who you are, right?
Because obviously you're not what you look like at the fur con.
Precisely.
And even like 10 years ago when I was going to cons more often, I did have a friend who drew me a badge and it was great.
I've still got it.
Got a little crack badge.
I think, I guess the only, well I guess I went to Anthony New England.
What was it, three?
What was it, two years ago now?
Three years ago I had kidney stones, right?
That was terrible.
Three years ago, you went for like one day and on your way, you were there one day and then on your way home, you stopped at my house.
Yeah.
Stay hydrated, buddy.
You brought me like Gatorade or something.
I think I filled an Arizona jug with water for you or something.
Yeah.
I just carried you in a jug of water.
Don't die, buddy.
Wow, that was three years ago.
Jesus Christ.
And I've dodged that medical debt ever since.
Yeah, that all worked out, right?
You pretty much just didn't have to pay it.
They just stopped, they told me we're sending it to collections and then I just never heard another word from them and I'm pretty sure, based on some information that I dug up later,
I'm pretty sure that something called like a charity care clause kicked in wherein I was at the time too poor and they were not allowed not to treat me and therefore they couldn't like, they couldn't demand repayment.
Yeah, they try as they might.
Try as they might.
The law just was not on their side.
Yeah.
I think that's what happened.
Yeah, so then I think it was the next year.
I didn't buy a ticket.
I just walked in one day.
I just walked in and then I walked into the dance contest, the first suit dance contest.
It just in the middle of it and nobody checked my badge and I just got in.
Man, I don't know how they are these days, you know, corona times at this con, but usually those are pretty good.
When I went two years ago, it was fun.
I did enjoy it.
But then this year, I was gonna go to that same thing yesterday,
but I had gone there in the morning to do the pin trading thing and that was gonna be at like 6 p.m.
and it was like 4.30 and we were like, well, we got nothing to do.
We just kind of got to wait for the dance contest and that's gonna be an hour and a half and then the dance contest is gonna be two hours long.
Yeah.
And I was just like, I can't do it.
Listen, guys, it's about my bedtime.
Well, it was about my bedtime, except, but you saw, because you're in my patron discords,
you saw, I've been good use of that time yesterday.
I went home instead of going to some degenerate furry first suit dance contest,
I went home and I cranked out the last five panels before Phantom's Revenge.
Oh, and they're beautiful.
They're fucking gorgeous.
I'm happy with them.
It's so good.
They came out really good.
Okay, here's my, here's a little bit of my dysfunctional workflow.
I got home from, hold on, wait, wait, actually, I found the picture.
I'm gonna post it.
Yeah, post that before we get too far away from it.
I'm gonna post the picture because it's Kuhl, because it's Kuhl and I like it.
It's not the best quality photograph, but this is my tag.
Oh, yeah.
It's good, right?
It's great.
Oh, it's exactly what you need.
I know.
That's fucking beautiful.
Cassie made one for everyone and they even confided in me that they thought mine came out the best and I agree.
Yeah, I don't have the other ones for reference, but I can't imagine how much better they could be.
Oh, they're fine and all.
They're okay.
I'm sure they roughly communicate the idea, but this one.
I love this.
Oh, right.
So, right, so it was like five or so and I was like, all right, guys, I'm out.
And so I came home and I was home by like six and I sat down and I was like, all right, time to do some work.
And then around about like midnight, 1am, I kind of start and stop and do a little bit.
And then I get the first of those five panels done that I had already done, had half finished.
I get that done around 1am.
And then from like 1am to like 4am, I crank out the other four.
They take me like half an hour apiece.
Nice.
And they're all, and they all come out really good.
I'm just like, I'm just slapping colors down, just making them work.
The subtle little black outline on the green letters is so good.
I wish you were doing that sort of thing the whole time because it makes it so much more readable and it looks so much better.
Hold on.
The subtle little, let me go.
You're on the, there's one panel where it says bang bang and you've got this little black outline on the green letters.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I just said, I do that sometimes on, I do that sometimes for like onomatopoeia sounds.
Just for legibility.
If they had not, if they had not, just because like those green letters kind of on like the green, they're sort of adjacent to the green grass and like the light green on the white door background.
It was just not legible without a.
Yeah, I agree.
I think it's a huge improvement and I don't know.
I just wish you'd do that all the time, but it would probably take forever.
It's like, I don't know how you're doing it if you got to like line around all the other lines.
It doesn't, honestly, it doesn't take forever.
I mostly, I just don't bother unless I think like, I don't know, because like two, two panels before that I have phantom touching the tree and he goes tap tap.
And I didn't give those a little sound effect, but, but those are just a little bitch sounds.
Those are just a little tiny, little tiny noises.
They're not, they're not dramatic.
This bang bang is supposed to be like a reverberating bang bang.
Because, you know, the game starts, the game starts with two bangs and two bangs and a boom.
Absolutely.
These are the last two panels before phantom's revenge.
And the first thing you hear when you hit, when you hit play on the phantom's revenge menu screen is you hear.
As he, as he bangs twice on the door and then he explodes the door.
Spoilers for the first, for the very first instant.
For the very first second of the game.
Yeah.
So that said, is it, is it coming soon?
Is it coming out?
Yeah, I've got to.
So yeah, these ones that I posted yesterday, I have finished, it took me 42 panels, which is a little more than I expected.
I expected maybe 30 something.
It took me 42 panels to get it up to the game.
Post game, I think, definitely, I'm going to say 12.
I'm going to estimate 12 and it'll probably end up being more than I think.
It'll be 12, maybe 16.
Oh, so another comic after the game.
Yeah, after the game, there's a little, there's a little post.
There's, there's like, after the game, you got to see what happens right after.
And then after that, I have to think of like, okay.
And then what, what are the actual like last pages of the comic?
Like what's, what does like the V end look like?
And I don't know what that is yet.
I have no idea.
So do you think by the time people are hearing this, is the game going to be generally available?
Or is it going to be another week?
Sorry to ask you the tough questions.
I'm going to, I'm going to guess it could be out by the time this is out, but I'm going to guess probably not.
I'm going to say probably maybe more likely next week after, which, oh God, that's going to push into the next month.
Yeah, it's going to be March.
Gib, Gib's going to beat me.
Gib's secret project is going to come out before, before mine.
Yeah, I'm excited.
I didn't, I didn't realize how far along that was, but I was, I don't know anything specifically about it,
but I heard from some, some patrons of Gib that, that it's real cool.
So I'm excited.
You, did you not, did you not hear any, you didn't hear any specifics?
I don't know anything.
I don't know anything about it.
Really?
I know what it is.
Oh, that's nice.
And I won't, and I won't be, I won't get into specifics either, but it is real cool.
And I am really excited.
I am genuinely not, not even in like a, not even in like a happy for you sort of way, because I don't care about other people.
I'm excited.
Well documented fact.
I'm excited in like a, in like a, yeah, it's a cool thing.
It's a cool project.
And I'm excited just to see like what people will say about it and what the reaction will be.
It's a, it's not as good as Phantom's Revenge, obviously, but it's good.
I can't, I mean, I want to see what, what people have to say about it.
I think it's, it looks great.
I've seen a little bit.
I haven't seen that.
I know what it is.
I haven't seen much of it, but I've seen enough to get, to get the gist.
Yeah.
Good, good stuff.
She's going to beat me though.
I'm thinking probably.
It just probably will.
If, okay, okay, if, if I worked at the pace that I was working, not all last night, but just between the hours of midnight and like 5am last night, then I could get it done in a week.
I, historically, I can't maintain that sort of a frenetic activity.
Yeah.
If you need to do more than a page a day, I think it's safe to assume it's not going to happen, you know, on average.
Some days, some days I can crank out like eight pages, but it depends what the pages are.
Like, kind of the reason, like you would see my, even see my, my uploads because you're in that channel, the Patreon channel.
So you know that like.
Yeah.
Shout out patreon.com slash Ben saying give him $5 you can get in the channel.
Please.
Yeah.
So you know that like the eight pages before that took me like two weeks because I don't know.
They were just, I had a very specific, I had a very particular idea for what they ought to be and I had to make them, I had to make them meticulously match.
It's not even that they're like more complicated.
It's just that my, my mental image for them was very specific and I was like, I know exactly what they need to look like and I need to make them look like that.
Whereas these ones that I did yesterday, I was like, I basically know what they're going to look like and like as long as they generally get the idea across whatever.
And I just kind of like just started and I just kind of started throwing lines down and I just like to tap a tap a tap a with my stylist for like 45 minutes and then like whatever was there at the end of that.
I was like, yeah, that works.
Okay.
Next.
Good.
Go.
Yeah.
So it's sort of, it lets you do kind of whatever.
So it was just, it was just kind of like, I know it's going to be sort of in like the kind of dark looking woods.
So I'll just start throwing down some woodsy looking details.
Well, that was the first page.
The first page where I drew the whole background took me, I did that like half yesterday and then half, or half two days ago and half yesterday.
And, you know, I'll just, would it be a spoiler to post it?
I'll show it as a tree.
It's not that spoilery.
It's not that bad.
People know Phantom Horan's coming for his revenge.
He's coming for revenge.
I hope that's a spoiler.
Yeah.
So this scene with the tree, yeah, it took me a little bit to get the background, right?
It took me two days.
And then in the one, the post, the one after it, I just used the exact same background again, but I just kind of like reversed it and like zoomed in on one part of it and kind of like change the brightness, contrast, balance.
Just so it.
Oh, that's funny.
You know, I didn't even notice that it's exactly the same and you wouldn't write it.
Yeah.
It's fine.
That's totally fine.
I do that all the time.
I'll just like take, I'll just take a background that I used before and be like, well, if I, if I, if I flip it and I like just change the color balance a little bit, like you would never know.
You would never know that it's the exact same image.
And that's such a good trick to get that fake depth of field to just like, well, I'm just going to adjust the color a little bit.
You know, if it's desaturated a little people know, oh, that's the background.
And it works.
It works great.
It looks deep.
Exactly.
And then it's like, okay, well, do I want to, in this one, I think I made it, I desaturated it to make like, to make phantom pop a little bit in the front.
And then you can, you can make it, you can make it lighter.
You can make it lighter or you can make it darker.
If you want, do you want the carrot?
You want the character to be like a dark silhouette or do you want him to be sort of like a sort of a point of light focus focal point in like a dark area?
You can do whatever you can do.
I want everyone to do it.
I mean, that's just a theory though, you know, a color theory.
Yeah.
It's never, it's never been, it's never been tested.
Never been tested, never been proven.
Yeah.
As you're saying, I don't know why I put the Yig tree there.
It looks, it looks fine.
It looks like it fits.
It doesn't.
I think it's okay because if you didn't know what it was, it's like whatever.
It's just a weird looking tree.
And it's totally reasonable for a weird looking tree to be there.
Yeah.
Wouldn't you expect the thing that you're looking for to be in kind of a weird looking maybe artificial tree?
Yes.
So.
Makes sense.
In the, in the context of what this is and like what place this is and why that tree is there, if you do, I'm trying to think if you do know what the Yig tree is.
Like what is, what is the thematic connection? Like what is being said?
See, because great, great artists don't think about these things beforehand.
They just throw, they just throw shit together and then other people come up with what it means.
You hang up those blue drapes and it's up to the audience and, you know.
To infer.
To the reader.
That means I'm depressed.
Exactly.
So.
It means that.
Well, I mean, obviously it means that this is a place of villains.
I think, I think, I think that's the, that's, that's where my mind goes.
This is a place of villains.
There's a villain, there's a villainous connection.
This is a place.
This is not a place of honor.
Nothing, nothing esteemed.
No esteemed.
No great, no great deed is esteemed here.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what, that's what this tree says.
But it also, I mean, obviously, obviously it's a Y, but it also kind of looks like a V.
And it could be V for very bad things here.
Or it could be V for pointing down because it's down right here is the thing you're looking for.
You know, there's a lot of.
Well, I won't, I won't show it, but yeah, the V pointing down, the V pointing down, that's true.
And then also around the back of the roots form a GG.
And since this is a lead into the game, it's wishing, it's wishing you a good game when you, when you step through the precipice.
Yeah.
The thresholds.
It just works on so many levels.
Yeah, it's incredible.
It's incredible.
Very good.
Yeah.
Love the shoot.
It all comes, it all comes together.
This is, this is the real, the real artistry is not in throwing all this shit together.
It's in the sitting around and theorizing afterwards about how many layers of genius, of genius inference.
Can I, can I retroactively read into this juxtaposition of elements?
That's, that's, that's the real artistry right there.
Absolutely.
Absolutely true.
You know, all great art really is the summation of the references it can make.
All, all great art is made after the fact when you sit around trying to justify what it was you did.
Yeah.
You come up with excuses for it later.
Absolutely the case.
And that's what I'm going to be doing with Slime and Punishment for the rest of my life.
Hey Ben, why did you spend two years drawing like a Sonichu fan comic?
Uh, well.
It just seemed funny at the time, I guess.
And you know what?
It was.
What?
So, so that's, I'm trying to think if I did anything else this week.
Not really.
I've been working on these, I was working on these, not specifically these panels.
I was working on Slime and Punishment all week and then this weekend, uh,
Anthro New England has been taking up a little bit of my time.
And that's pretty much what I've been doing lately.
What, what are, what about you?
Man, well, first I want to plug very cool, uh, commission piece that I got.
I think you saw it already when I would post it, um, by, uh, by Liz,
aka Monochromatics on, on Twitter.
I did see this and I, I enjoyed, uh, looking around at the fine details.
I can't believe the amount of work they put into the, uh, the PDP 12 here in this picture.
Is that the, uh, the machine?
Yeah, this computer, it's a, it's a digital computer, digital equipment corporation.
So the old Massachusetts, uh, computer company.
Yeah.
Mainframes and mini computers.
Punch, punch cards.
Yeah, it's got that.
It's, it's got it all.
We got magnetic tape reel to reel.
We've got, uh, we've got punch tape, uh, like big, big strips of tape reader.
It's also got, I don't know if you could see in the bottom right there.
Those are a giant 14 inch, inch removable hard disks.
Uh, oh, the big, the big round things.
And you would slot those into those giant drives above it.
Like, like big flash drives.
Jesus Christ.
Each holding a whopping like two megabytes or something.
Like, like real service technology.
I, I was reflecting the other day on how, uh, on how I, like darn, I'm old, I'm old enough
that I actually used floppy disks.
That's a, I think at this point that's a real, that's a real real.
Like that, that's like my parents being like, yeah, we used eight tracks.
Lamal.
Yeah.
Man.
Now eight track is a terrible format.
That's.
I'm not sure I've ever even seen an eight track.
I don't know what it is.
They're awful.
So the thing about eight track, uh, not to get too diverted here, but like, you know,
with compact cassette, your regular cassettes, um, it's just, it goes from beginning to end.
And you can go forward or reverse.
You can flip it over.
Right.
It's two sided.
None of that with the eight track.
The eight track is a continuous loop of tape and you can only go in one direction.
So, so you can only play forward and you just have to loop it all the way through.
Yes.
Wow.
Loop it all the way through.
And they call it eight track because it's, um, eight stereo tracks.
So it's, there's four songs that are like simultaneously encoded left and right channels.
So you can pick which one you're listening to at any given time, but it's just like,
it's just in that part of the tape.
You know what I mean?
That's, that's weird.
Okay.
I did not know that.
Such a dumb ass format.
I did not know that about, uh, about those.
That's, that's fucked.
Yeah.
What it would usually be a lot of the times like track one would be one song followed
by another song and then track two simultaneous to track one is one song followed by another
song.
So you can get, so you can get eight.
Well, you get 16 songs because each track is two songs.
Uh, no.
So it's an eight track, but there's actually only four song for four tracks you can listen
to because they're stereo.
Oh yeah.
You could probably get eight songs on there.
I mean, they could put however much tape could fit inside the big cartridge.
Yeah.
It's a terrible format.
If it sucks.
Amazing.
You know, I never, never seen it.
You think a compact cassette like cassettes, like they're, they're kind of bad, but they're
so much better than eight tracks.
I did.
I did when I was like a little kid.
I think when I was a little kid, I did have cassettes.
I had like fucking baby.
When I was like a little baby, you know, I had the fucking little music cassettes on
a little, a little cassette player.
I think, I think by the time I was like actually listening to music cassettes were already obsolete.
Yeah.
Same.
Like I, I definitely have, you know, I've got a small collection of cassettes and stuff
and I listened to them when I was a kid a little bit, but it was, I definitely mostly
had CDs and then really mostly just downloaded music.
Yeah.
By the time I was in like high school MP, MP3 players and like a, you know, a lime, lime
wire and I kind of missed a nap.
I missed Napster, but like Kazaa and lime wire and it was like, just get a fucking MP3 player
dog.
I had a small CD collection.
I bought a bunch of CDs of bands that my friends liked so that I would feel worthy of their
love.
Yeah.
I need these, these totems so that they can, they can see the signals, right?
These shibboleths.
I needed my, I needed my God, my God smack and my incubus and my cradle, cradle of filth.
Incubus still, Incubus still a great band.
I still love Incubus.
No.
Do you?
Oh yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
They got, they got a couple of songs that are fine.
I'm not, I'm not, you know, I'm not well versed in the, I'm not well versed in the,
I'm only, I mean, I was never well versed.
I like, you know, a couple of their, a couple of their hits.
Yeah.
I still, I still.
I think the hits hold up.
Yeah.
Would also have, I don't know.
God, speaking of, speaking of this era.
Obviously, obviously I had hybrid theory, Linkin Park, obviously.
Oh, of course.
Of course.
Certified banger.
I was just listening to Good Charlotte's The Young and the Hopeless.
I love that album.
I still love that album, Front to Back.
It's great.
The first half of the album is just banger after banger after banger.
I'd recommend it.
You should listen to it right now.
Not right now, but you know, after this.
Right?
No, right now.
Eleazar.
Cut that.
Could you cut in the entire album?
I was, I was going to say cut out the next 45 minutes.
No.
I'm going to go give it a listen.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
I should listen to more, you know, I've said it before and I'll probably say it again.
I should listen to more music because one thing that I know, one thing that I historically
know for a fact improves my creativity or improves my productivity is when I'm listening to music
and I get in the zone with it.
I can just drawing.
When I'm listening to podcasts or YouTube videos, they, they are not, I do not get in
the zone.
They distract me.
And I, I mean, I can draw in spite of them.
I can just kind of ignore it.
Sometimes I can draw and get and just kind of let them, let them wash over me, but music
is more likely to do that.
So I should listen to more music.
If I, if I spent more time listening to music, I would probably be a more effective person,
I think.
Yeah.
And, you know, it would also sort of open your mind to new things you haven't thought
about.
You'll hear some new sounds and maybe that'll be reflected in your art, you know, so it's
always good.
Possibly.
Could, could happen, I guess.
I have a very, very limited, I have a very limited Sonic palette.
It's kind of cringe to say, but it's true.
It is true.
I didn't want to, I didn't want to call you out for it, but it's definitely true.
No, it's true.
It's true.
It's just, you know, finding music is hard.
Yeah, it is.
And I have historically often been like, eh, why bother?
Eh.
You know what's hard?
And listen to the old, just listen to the old favorites and eh, music's not that good
anyway.
The problem is making music is hard too.
So like my, my favorite band, Sad Baxter, have just like fallen off the face of the
planet.
They're not doing anything right now.
It's been years.
It's like, come on guys, let's, let's get together and do another EP.
Right.
What's it going to take?
Yeah.
I guess.
I mean, I guess that's, I was going to say most bands, but I mean, I guess that's the
fate of every band eventually is too.
I mean, yeah.
It's always a limited time thing.
Yeah.
Unless you're like, unless you're like, I don't know, some Boomer 80s band.
Unless you're Iron Maiden.
At which point you're just going to keep making another album every year for the, for the
for the foreseeable future until Bruce Dickinson and Steve Harris die.
Or, or failing that you just, you know, you eventually just have a reunion tour that lasts
the rest of your lives because like you're never going to do anything.
You know, you know, you're never going to, you're never going to, lightning's not going
to strike twice.
Yeah.
You know, you're not going to have a second hit.
The Rolling Stones bottle, right.
Is they just keep torn.
Yeah.
It's like, they're not going to write another, there's not going to be another.
I don't know, sticky fingers or whatever.
I don't know.
I can't even think of Rolling Stone albums, but I'm sure some were good.
That's sort of before our time even.
Yeah.
I mean, I've never listened to the Rolling Stones.
That's like my mom likes that.
You know.
Yeah.
I mean, Rolling Stone magazine.
I don't even, I don't, I could, I could, I consider Rolling Stones to be, I would consider them
more brethren to like the Beatles.
Yeah.
Same time period.
For sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
When I was, when I was a kid, people, people were listening.
My friends were listening to like Black Sabbath, but even that was like, that was like classic,
that was fairly old even at the time.
You know.
Sure.
I mean, that's like, by our standards.
It was like studying Mozart, for example.
You listen to the Sabbath to get the context for the genre.
Appreciating the great masters.
Yeah.
Right.
I was, you know, I definitely had a classic rock phase.
I think everybody has to if you're, you're growing up in that time.
Yeah.
But none of you really stuck with me.
I'm not that big a fan, except for, I always loved ACDC.
I think they're still pretty good.
One time, this is a very, I asked, my friends were going to Oz Fest and I wanted to go to
Oz Fest and I asked my dad if I could go to Oz Fest and he made fun of me for it.
Yeah, I would too.
But he made fun of me in a way that he, he kind of, I think it circled back around in
him because the way that he made fun of him is he started singing what he thought was
an Ozzy song at me, but it was an eighth.
He started singing dirty deeds, done dirt.
You know, you know, the classic Osborn digger.
So, so he was hoist.
He hoisted his own petard on that one.
That's funny.
Yeah.
And I didn't know, I wasn't that familiar.
So I didn't know at the time that like that's not an Ozzy song.
So I couldn't call him out.
I mean, it is an Ozzy song to be clear.
Pretty close.
I'm trying to think if maybe that's was what he was thinking, but like no.
No, I'm sure it's just a funny coincidence.
Yeah.
God, and speaking of this, you know, bands just coming and going, the chats down in
Australia were doing sort of a modern punk take on what ACDC was.
And the moment they, they taste a little bit of success, you know, they had this big
hit with Smoco.
They did one with a Dine and Dash song.
I can't think of the name of it off the top of my head.
The moment they taste that success, they fire their cool alcoholic fact guitarist.
They bring in some other guy and the band's ruined.
You know, you need the alcoholic fact guitarist.
We need pricey back.
I'm begging the chats, bring back Mr. Price.
I'm bringing pricey back.
You need, I don't know, you need something.
You need someone with someone's got to bring the sauce.
Who are you talking about?
Who is this person?
Do you know the chats?
I'll post one of their songs.
No.
It's Dine and Dash.
The chats, like the cats, like French?
No, it's, I thought that initially too the very first time I saw them, but it's, I guess
it's Aussie slang for like bad food or vomit.
The chats?
Yeah.
So if you, if you go to a crappy restaurant, they might give you a chat.
The food might be chatty.
Okay.
Whatever, whatever you say.
But this is great too.
I don't know if you ever saw that old clip of the guy who was a famous Dine and Dasher, right?
He's getting arrested, you know, and the cops are, are manhandling him.
He's saying like, oh, this is democracy manifest.
Oh yeah, that does ring a bell.
They got that guy and he's in the music video for Dine and Dash.
This is democracy manifest.
Yeah.
He's like, oh, I see you know your Judah well.
Oh yeah, yeah, he's like, who's an older guy?
He's an older guy.
He's very old in this video.
I see you.
I see you studied your Judah well, sir.
Right, right, right.
Crazy.
I forgot about that, but yes, yes, you've unlocked a memory for me.
Yeah.
And I think, you know, to everyone, to the viewers, please check out this song.
And you will also have that memory unlocked unless you're like under 20 years old at which
point you definitely have no idea what it is.
No, no, I don't even remember when I, was I in college?
When I saw that, maybe it was later than that.
Oh, I don't know.
I think that clip is from like 2000.
Oh, really?
Yeah, that's old.
Maybe.
Yeah, okay.
I guess it could have just been an old clip that I just happened to stumble upon.
Probably.
Yeah, I see.
Hmm.
What are we talking about?
How'd we get on?
You know, we're talking about this picture, this picture of the computer.
Oh, yeah.
We went down the storage, storage archive.
Right.
But anyway, the point I was making is it's a PDP, which is this one's not part of the
UNIX lineage, but the PDP 11 was another digital computer.
So the cool thing about all this is it's sort of like, oh, there's crack, learn a program,
learn to write C, you know, back when C was being invented on the UNIX operating system
that was being invented.
It's just kind of cool.
Man.
It's a very historical piece.
Making, I think I've complained about this same thing before, but I'll say it again.
Making Phantom's Revenge has made me feel so late to the party.
Like, learning GML, it's like, wow, okay, someone else, someone else who 30 years ago,
who actually knows how to code, decided what if I use my code to design like a baby code
for idiots to learn.
And that's what I'm dabbling in right now.
And I feel so patronized by these tools, by these tool sets that someone has laid out
for me.
Yeah.
And you know, you know where that started in like 1964, right?
They come out with the basic programming language, just called basic.
Is that like, is that like one step up from like assembly language?
No, basic is all nice mnemonic words, things like go to and print.
Yeah.
And they made it because obviously normal people could not just write assembly code.
It takes a certain kind of, you got to study it.
You got to understand what the instructions do.
So they come up with basic.
And it's very basic.
It's easy.
And basic is like a, I've never like tried it, but it's like a human readable sort of coding system.
Yeah, totally readable.
Like regular source code, no weird syntax usually, although the early ones had kind of weird
syntax because, you know, computers were junky.
Like you could fit like 40 characters of text on a line on your home computer.
So they had to be a little terse.
Yeah.
But like here's a, here's a picture of some Atari basic, which is very similar, like
a Commodore basic.
Oh, it's this.
Ola Wikipedia.
Okay.
10, 4, X1, 2.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
And in this type of basic, they have to number the lines.
And then if you were to do a go to, you would say go to that line.
But this one, this one happens to be doing a for loop, which is like, whoa, big, big
Mr. Programmer over here pulling out the for loop.
Oh, programming jokes.
Yeah.
But, you know, so, so since the very beginning, people have been like, oh, we got to make
a language so that more, we got to make it easier.
Yeah.
And there's basic, there's cobalt is another big one that, that's still incredibly still
used today.
This ancient terrible language.
Cobal.
Yeah.
C O B O L.
Absolutely awful.
Should have been dead 30 years ago and it's still going because they use it in like
insurance companies use this in like their, their mainframe computers that they haven't
changed since like 1970.
Sure.
So you got to keep the old language.
You got to keep it going.
You got to keep your cobalt going.
There's a bunch of these.
Common business oriented language.
There's a, there's mumps is one used in the medical billing and coding field.
It's another cancerous terrible language.
Yeah, I see.
And if you, if you look for programming jobs, sometimes you'll see still listings for like
we need, we need a mumps guy.
Those jobs are bad.
You don't want it.
You don't want that job.
Yeah.
No, seems weird, seems weird.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Massachusets general, that's not what I thought mumps was going to stand for.
Massachusets general hospital utility multi-programming system.
Okay.
All right.
Massachusets general hospitals all in one letter.
Okay.
I guess that makes sense.
Well, you know, it was really MGH utility multi-programming system, but they, they spelled
it out for, for the very basic among us.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
Or, or just M or just M for short.
And it's so funny.
If you can, yeah.
Well, it's so funny because all these languages are kind of a similar vintage.
Right.
And then we have, we have C that comes out like maybe five, 10 years after this.
Yeah.
And C is so actually good.
I saw, I saw your comment on the last episode in response to Gamer's Tavern.
Oh, he was talking about C sharp.
C sharp is a whole different animal.
Oh, okay.
Related only in letter.
I assumed it was like a, like a child language or like a, like a.
So, so with C sharp is sort of similar to Java.
The idea is to make this like a nice virtualized language that has like garbage collection
and automatic memory management and stuff.
It's sort of in the style of the C programming language.
So like the, the semantics are similar, but it's not actually like you wouldn't say it's
based on C, you know.
Okay.
All right.
But it looks cosmetically very similar and it's got like some other things.
Gotcha.
I think.
Okay.
So, same story as Java.
I also don't know much about Java.
I used a little Java on my website once.
I copied and pasted some Java.
What's JavaScript?
Oh, which unfortunately is very different.
What the fuck?
Okay.
C sharp.
Oh, yeah.
Nothing to do with C.
Yeah.
Unrelated.
Oh, JavaScript.
No, no, no.
This is not Java.
No, no.
This is JavaScript.
No, this is totally different.
Yeah.
You know, and the problem is like in the 90s, people just had Java on the brain.
You know, they come out with the Java programming language.
They're like, oh, we need a language for the web.
We need a language for the web.
JavaScript.
It's like they're barely connected.
The only connection really is, again, that they all sort of copy the C semantics and
styling, you know, the symbology of the two.
And it's not like, like the actual languages are not very similar.
Well, that sucks.
That blows.
Okay.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Right.
So you were saying C comes out five, 10 years later.
Yeah.
You know, sort of almost of the same era that maybe the next era of computer programming
to come out with C. And it's great.
It's the best thing that anyone's ever thought of.
We're still using it today and it still kicks ass.
Like there's just nothing wrong with it and it rolls.
I guess, I mean, I guess, I mean, I guess that's how it is with natural, with real languages
that you speak.
You figure it out and like, well, if it works, you know, let's just keep using it.
Makes sense.
You don't have to keep reinventing the wheel.
I guess.
You know, that's exactly it.
So the problem was people would make these languages.
You'd make your cobalt or your mumps and it would run on like this very specific computer.
The mumps runs on the mumps computer, whatever it is, like this one computer.
And when they come out with a new computer, somebody has to like reimplement the language
for that computer.
Or there's a new language for that computer and they got to rewrite all the tools for
the new language for the new computer.
But the reason C has so much staying power is they wrote UNIX, right?
And UNIX is this operating system that provides these API interfaces for the C language.
And then anything that's written for UNIX works on UNIX no matter what the computer is.
So you just port UNIX to the new computer and then everything, it's like a virtual machine
for all these programs.
All your programs just work.
You can build them on the new computer.
Hmm.
Yeah.
And that was, you know, that was so fundamental and so game changing that just like it embedded
C and UNIX forever.
Like they're just unstoppable juggernauts.
So is UNIX sort of like an operating system?
Yeah.
It's an operating system.
Okay.
And then later on, of course, in the nineties, the line of store vaults comes along and he
says, well, UNIX is kind of big.
It's kind of expensive.
People can't really get it.
I'm going to make my own kind of UNIX like thing for, for little normal people computers
instead of for, you know, the big mainframes of many computers at institutions and universities.
Oh, that's, that's line Linux UNIX line.
Yeah.
It's, it's cute.
Right.
Yeah.
Linus is like, I want to make my own little, you know, and the story goes that like his
CIS admin friend was making his home directory and mistyped his name Linus instead of, instead
of Linus, you know, who knows if that's true.
And he was like, Oh, no, that's good.
That's a cute, that's a cute story.
Like, like the story of like, like, oh, Toru Iwatana, he was eating a pizza and he looked
down and he took a slice out of the pizza and he looked down at the pizza with a slice
out of it and he said, Oh my God, I've got a new idea for the next legendary video game
character.
Yeah.
It comes to me in a flash.
It might even if it's not true.
Yeah.
That's okay.
It's better if we act like act as though it is.
You know, but, but so that's why, that's why C sharp and Java, they, they take this idea
that like, okay, we have this, this UNIX, this Linux operating system that is a virtual machine
for the actual computer.
Right.
And they say, what if we literally put on top of that another virtual machine layer that
abstracts the operating system?
You know, so now instead of writing your, your program for UNIX, you write it for Java.
And you build it for Java and the Java virtual machine just runs on, it runs on Linux and
it runs on Windows, right?
And it runs on Mac OS.
So you don't have to rebuild your Java code.
You just, you just deploy it and they've got a JVM that's already built for that operating
system.
But it turns out that sucks actually because in practice, like everyone just runs Linux
in their data center.
So you could just build it for Linux.
So there's no, you know, the whole value of Java and C sharp abstract in the operating
system.
It just doesn't exist in the enterprise space.
And like,
Will you say, or no, sorry.
We're going to, we're going to say something else.
Oh, I was just going to say also, so like the, in the enterprise space, everyone's just
running Linux and, you know, in the desktop space, everyone's just running Windows.
So it's like,
Yeah.
The value of, of doing it for Java specifically is like, why would you?
Right.
Okay.
Just build it for Windows, you know, or just Java.
So Java is meant to abstract the operating system as in like, okay, if you build a program
for Java, then Java will make it run on any operating.
Yeah.
You can pile it to bytecode for the Java virtual machine and then the virtual machine will
have been written for the specific computer and operating system that you're actually running.
So you just install one JVM or, you know, they call it a runtime environment on the computer.
And then it's like, oh, well now you've got this virtual computer that is the same as
everyone else's virtual computer.
I understand.
Yeah.
But, but in, but in practice, like everyone's, everyone's, everyone's running the same
operating system.
So why?
Right.
I get it.
If you're writing a game, right?
Like you just target Windows, realistically, and I say that even as someone who uses Linux
on the desktop every day all day a hundred percent of the time, like I just, I build
my games for Windows and then I run them in wine on my computer.
Like I, you know, wine is, isn't wine basically like a virtual Windows that runs on Linux?
Uh, sort of.
So what wine does is it provides like the API calls that Windows has.
It doesn't need to virtualize it because your computer is still the same CPU architecture.
Like the, the code that you built for Windows runs on this computer.
It just like, if it makes a library call out to like, uh, open a file dialogue or something,
like Windows provides that.
So wine provides a similar thing.
So it's not, it's not an emulator exactly.
And that's why wine is, it's an act.
It's like a nested acronym.
Wine is not an emulator is what wine stands for.
Wait, really?
Yeah.
Wine is not an emulator.
Oh my God.
Wow.
Well, that's, that's what it is.
So it just, it just provides these, these libraries that you don't have because you're
running.
I just, I just assumed that the W stood for Windows.
Yeah, it kind of does, right?
It's like Winnie, but it's also, you know, yeah, it's got layers and very clever people
over there.
This, this reminds, damn, they build, they make computers, they know, they know how to,
they do be making them computers.
They all be making, they making those computers bigger and better and smaller and better too.
This reminds me of, I showed you the weird, stupid dumb shit that happened to Slime, not
Slime and Punishment, to Phantom's Revenge when I tried exporting it for, for, for, uh,
Yeah.
For the web.
What was it?
Yeah.
On HTML three, eight, five, there, uh, yeah, just, just acted different for, weird shit
happened where like, did, did you see that, that the, like when I started the, the start
menu, the point was like looping through all the images, the arrow, the arrow icon, instead
of just displaying the icon, it looped through a bunch of similarly sized images as though
it, as though it knew that, okay, this image that I want to display is a certain size.
Let me find things that are a similar size and then randomly, not randomly and then sequentially
loop through a sequence of them.
It was, it was, it's like it knew something and, and then I tried to, I went in and I,
and I re-typed the code, I tried, I put in a new instruction to change that to make it
not do that and it didn't work quite right and then I undid the changes and then it worked.
I undid, I undid everything.
I went it all the way back, I reverted all my changes, but it worked now.
That's so weird.
I don't.
Yeah.
And you know, it's, it's all down to like, however, game makers compiling this stuff
and it's probably taking your art and like building new sprite sheets with like similar
sized pieces, you know?
Maybe.
And we, yeah.
It's just all invisible to us.
We don't know how it works.
It has, it has, um, it has automated a bunch of, yeah, stuff, stuff like making sprite
sheets.
Like you don't have to, you don't really have to fuck around with sheets in, in game
maker, but maybe in its own internal logic, it sort of does.
Yeah.
It probably, it's probably like arranging stuff onto a grid of images and it's like,
it's compressing your data in some way, right?
Like if you, if you were to look at the, the exe, it puts out, for example, like you won't
find your image, like literally in there, but it's in there somehow.
They've, they've compressed it and they've combined it with other things.
And I guess the, the HTML exporter just does some, some goofy stuff.
Yeah.
Very, it's, apparently it gets real goofy when left to its own devices.
I watched a video this past week that was called, um, it was explaining how JPEG compression
works.
Okay.
And I was like, well, it was real fucking needle.
Let me find, just to find the video.
Yeah.
So I, I'm trying to imagine myself how it might work, right?
Like obviously it's lossy compression.
So it's like somehow using maybe like some mathematical function that generates noise
to somehow compress the data, which is, I don't know, I don't know how that works.
It's cool.
Here it is.
The video is called the unreasonable effectiveness of JPEGs.
And there's, um, Oh, that's funny.
I, I remember seeing this.
This was recommended to me, but I didn't watch it.
It was recommended to me and I ended up watching it and, uh, a lot of good stuff in that video.
There, there's, okay.
Some of the stuff that it does is it basically just, it basically just loses color information.
It simplifies color information while retaining brightness information.
And like just that, just the fact that the human eye is more sensitive to brightness
than the color does like so much work.
Like you kind of don't even notice because your, your eye is more, it does like, um,
it does like color sampling, like it'll take like, you know, it'll like average out between
like four pixels.
Like it'll, it'll, it'll do like average color sampling for color, but not brightness on
a bunch of, bunch of different scales.
And that does a lot of the work.
And then it will, man, I mean, this is a long video.
So I can't explain it really.
I can't, I can't summarize it that much.
Dear, dear viewer, if you're interested, please watch this video.
You should just watch the video, but like it'll, it'll, um, there's a, yeah, there's,
there's like a dozen different things that does like, like the, the, the brightness signal,
it ends up, like it sort of, it takes the pixel because most J, because most images
are what it calls a low frequency, meaning that there was like, there tends to be relatively
little change in brightness just from like one pixel to the next, right?
Like two adjacent pixels are likely to be fairly similar.
Uh, and the fact that the images are low frequency means that if you plot, if you
plot the brightness data, the brightness values on a line and you associate a curve with
that, with that plot, you can then create a, you can sort of approximate a function of
that plot that you've just created by graphing the brightness data linearly as a
sum of cosine waves.
Oh, okay.
And yeah, so that's, that makes sense, right?
You sort of were expected to be something like that.
When you look at the noise, it's like, it's very particular the way JPEG noise looks like.
Hmm.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
I mean, I would, I mean, uh, it, it's, it's, it makes sense, like with enough data, it
sounds like bizarrely complicated, like that you have to turn like a sequence of data points
into this like weird sum of functions, but you know, with enough data, you know, if you
can, if you can, if you can do that, then I can, I can see like, yeah, you can definitely
store that sum of cosine waves in a smaller amount of data than just like, that is just
a sequence of values, right?
When you have like thousands of thousands of thousands of thousands of
Yeah, absolutely.
Because I mean, you think of like, you think of an image, like if you wanted to store a
literal bitmap, you know, that could be a, I don't know, three bytes per pixel, if it's
a 24 bit color image, and if there's alpha channels, not non JPEGs, but like in ping,
for example, you know, that's four bits, four bytes per pixel, that's up quick.
There's a lot of pixels, even in a small image.
It seems, I don't know, on face value, it seems ridiculous to suggest that you could
just, that you could just, that you could just take basically any sequence and approximate
it with the sum of cosine waves.
But, you know, well, you could, you can, you can make any cosine wave you want, and you
can add as many of them together as you want.
And you know, we're just, we're just approximating here.
We don't have to get it exactly right.
I mean, it's just like, you know, even in like a, in a Cartesian plane, like a 2D graph,
right, like if you have any set of points, you could construct some function that connects them.
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
So that, that the cosine wave thing, the sampling, it shows, it shows examples where
like, it takes an image, just a small image of just like eight by eight pixels, right?
And then it does like, like it retains the brightness in each pixel, but then it like,
you know, it like, it like averages out the color value, just, you know, it reduces it
down from eight by eight to, you know, two by two, right?
It combines, you know, sets of four pixels and losing the, losing the color value and
retaining the brightness value.
It's like, it's basically the same image.
Like it looks a little different, but like it, it's, it's basically the same.
Not in any way that matters, unless you're like printing it out.
Not in any way that matters.
Yes, exactly.
Unless you really, unless you need like pixel perfect accuracy, which you don't.
With any, like, you probably don't, right?
If it's a photograph, you probably don't.
Computers, funny.
I don't know.
I don't know if you've looked into compression in general at all, but it's kind of fun to
play with, like, you know, you could, you could write your own code to compress data,
for example, and do you were, you were doing, you were talking about this a while back.
Yeah.
Didn't you say that you wrote like a, I think you said that you tried to just kind of come
up with like a, like a sort of naive, like the most basic algorithm, the most naive, the
dumbest thing you could do if you wanted to compress data.
And the first thing to attack, I think, like, if you have a big is redundancy, right?
Combined redundancy.
Yeah.
So if you have a bunch of repeated bytes, you know, the same bite again and again and again.
What if you, you know, you just come up with some mnemonic to replace that with like the
number of how many of those there were.
So if you have like a hundred zero bytes next to each other, you know, just have something
that says, Oh, put a hundred of those in here, right?
And now you've saved 97 bytes or whatever, you know, because you still got to, you got
to put in your control sequence, but you don't have to print all those bytes.
And I did that.
So I went through and did that.
I made a program that does it.
And it was funny because for certain things, it was as good as like, Jesus, which is one
of the standards for zipping things.
It was like, it was pretty much as good.
It was the same.
What, what, what kind of data were you compressing with it?
I think, uh, MPEG video was compressing.
I mean, something, something like video.
Yeah, you're likely to have, oh gosh, I don't know in what form the data is encoded, but
I'm imagining like one, you know, like one pixel, you're at, like the data is like, you
know, what color display on this one pixel.
Well, see, it's likely to be repeated frame to frame.
It's just like the JPEG thing.
So an MPEG video, um, not only is it like a bunch of weird math to draw each frame, but
also they don't draw the whole frame every time.
Frames will be like just the Delta.
And every once in a while, there's a key frame where they have like the whole frame.
Yeah, so that, that's a whole, that's MPEG.
That's MPEG, MPEG.
Okay.
All right.
That's fucked up.
But you know, you could, you could expand on that compression idea and do like what zip
actually does, which I think is, uh, it'll go through the file and it'll look for like
repeated sequences of, of the same bytes, right?
Like it'll be like ABCD and it'll find that ABCD and put it into a dictionary and then
replace it with just like the number of the dictionary lookup, you know, you could build
this dictionary of all these common repeated sequences and just replace them.
And that saves you a bunch of data too.
Hmm.
Sort of a, sort of an extension of the, okay, well, what, we, well, we can, we can, we
can compress redundant data and then we can expand that to be like, okay, well, it doesn't
just have to be a single letter, one letter at a time in a sequence of them.
We can expand that to be, you know, a longer sequence that we find multiple times.
Yeah.
Instead of just the same one repeated byte, maybe it's like, it's some common sequence.
I got you.
Maybe you initialize all your values to one, right?
And so there's a bunch of these, these integers that are taking up four bytes each that are
actually just like zero, zero, zero, one in memory, you know, and you could replace that
sequence with one byte instead of four.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess if you, I guess you could.
I, hmm, is there like, I'm thinking like, okay, you take any arbitrary data that you,
you're looking at, you could probably come, you could probably come up with like an
infinite number of data saving tricks, right?
Yeah, absolutely.
So I guess is it, is it just a question of like, okay, at what point, at what point are
you going to be like, all right, we've compressed it enough.
We don't need any more.
Yeah.
You know, well, right.
And so that's, that's where lossiness comes in, right?
Like you look at a, you look at an MP3, for example, or, or an MPEG video or a JPEG, right?
It's like, we need this to be smaller.
So how do we do it?
You've got to start introducing loss.
And then, then it just becomes, when is it, when is it so distorted that it's no longer
acceptable?
And that's where you stop.
Yes.
And that's a, and that's a, that's a, that's a, I guess that's an, an artistic question
or that's an aesthetic question or not necessarily.
I guess it might be a technical, this is how, like, how much, I don't know,
probably depends on the use case or whatever.
But I mean, if you, if you look at like audio, for example, a wave file, which is not
compressed versus like an MP3 file, even, even a constant bit rate, 320 kilobit per
second MP3 file is much smaller than a wave file.
Yeah.
They've just cut out so much data that just does not matter.
You know, and with most things, it's like, they sound, they sound the same.
They sound the same.
You can get that like 10x reduction without losing almost anything.
Yeah.
Which is so crazy.
It is crazy.
You, like, yeah.
Naively, naively, you would think, I don't know, when, when I still conceive, I
still conceive of like an image file as being a piece of data that tells the computer, you
know, like what, what color to draw on each pixel.
Yeah.
It's funny what you said about MP, MP, MPG video, it only draws the Delta or whatever.
It's like, yeah, it makes sense.
Still, I'll probably always think of it as like, I don't know, a sequence of images, a
sequence of like, of bitmaps, pixel encoded images.
Yeah, and actually on the video, that's why sometimes you'll see like a video that gets
all destroyed, it looks like a mess, and then suddenly it like just pops back and looks
fine again.
Like, like it'll, it'll suddenly like stop and then it'll like turn all blocky and then
like some, some blob of cubes will start like smearing across the.
Yeah, yeah.
And it's because it lost the key frame, right?
It lost the key frame, so now it's building a Delta on something else.
It just doesn't, it doesn't work.
I see.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hmm.
I, I, yeah, I guess that explains it.
I guess that explains why video looks all fucked up sometimes.
That explains everything.
It's all, it's all come together.
Hmm.
How do we get on this?
Oh, yeah, I don't remember.
We're deep in the weeds.
Oh, we were talking about that.
We were talking about the commission.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Anyway, talking about datas, data languages in the it's cool.
Cracksa, learning rightsy on a computer.
It's nice.
I think I, I think I retweeted an endless war.
Yeah.
It had a, it do, it do have that little endless war guy in there.
I made sure to get that in there.
That's very, I was looking around.
I saw that I saw that it was green and I was like, is this an endless war thing?
Let me, and then I saw him on the screen.
I was like, hi, there, there he is.
I mean, it's gotta be, it's gotta be at this point.
There he is.
I feel like the characters become deeply entwined in, in endless war, sort of in
separate point.
Um, when I was, um, I was trying to trade pins, what I made a few trades.
The, the podrans, the podrans were pretty, a couple of people wanted the podrans pins.
One person liked the, uh, endless war night sky pin.
I traded that for, oh, I got one.
I got a trade that's like a black and white egg and it's, and the egg is
cracking and a little purple creature is looking out with like a green anime eye.
And I'm, and I'm like, that's me.
Yeah.
That's you, that, that egg, that's about that.
This egg is, this egg is me.
Sounds about right.
It's the smallest, it's the smallest pin that I got, but it's the best one.
It's my favorite.
I mean, I got some, I got some Sona pins, but like, you know, whatever.
I don't know who these people are.
I mean, if you don't know who they are, it's like, okay, I got their
Sona, but like, it's just a sparkle dog.
I don't know what this is.
Yeah.
Actually, I got one Sona and I asked them about it and they were like, yeah,
you know, I'm going to be suiting later.
And I was like, oh cool, keep my eye out.
And then lo and behold, when it was, you know, unfortunately, I didn't get to
say anything to them.
I didn't get to tell them at the time, but later on when they did the, um, the
first suit parade, when the everyone like walked through Boston Common.
Sure.
Yeah.
Like a few, like 10 or 15 feet in front of us was that, was that dragon, that
purple and green and teal, uh, dragon was, was very, was right there.
And I was like, oh, it's from the button, from the button.
I, I got him.
I got that guy.
I know that.
I got him.
Yeah.
Uh, and then it started snowing.
It started snowing like as we were walking around and I thought darn, that
can't be good.
I would say yesterday that was yesterday.
Yeah.
There were some crazy squalls here.
I don't know.
I don't know what it was like over there.
When I, I didn't see that much.
We were walking around the common and it just started to snow a little bit.
And I was like, okay, let's go inside.
And then five or so, I'm like, okay, I don't want to wait for the dance,
dance contest I'm leaving.
And then I got, I, I walked outside, it was fine.
And then I got on the green line and like a couple of stops down the green
line, all of a sudden it, it, it goes from light to dark in no time at all.
And then all of a sudden it's like a blizzard outside and not like a blizzard,
but, but suddenly it's wind and it's dark and it's snow.
Like I got on 10 minutes ago, I got on and it was light out and it was no snow.
And then now it's like it's dark and the, in the, in the street lights, I'm
seeing snow swirling and I'm like, Oh God, I'm going to have to walk in this.
But then no, it had stopped.
It had stopped or we had moved out of it by the time that I got off.
Yeah, it was the same thing here.
It was like a huge big storm rolls in and like 10, 15 minutes later, it was just gone.
I was, I was lucky that it, that it passed entirely while I was on the tee.
I didn't actually have to walk through it at all.
That could have been bad.
Yeah.
Lucky, also lucky that I wasn't in like a suit, a fursuit or anything.
I would hate, imagine if that had happened while they were all walking
around the common, everyone would have been, it would have been pandemonium.
Oh yeah, I got it.
I mean, well, I got to imagine you get that in your fur.
But yeah, but you don't want moisture in your fur, right?
It's got to be bad.
It's got to be bad to get wet.
Well, I think what'll happen, it'll end up causing it all to get tangled and
somebody will have to brush the whole suit out and that'll be a nightmare.
You always got to brush them a little bit.
But like, you know, if it's, if the whole thing's been wet, it's, it's bad.
I think, I think so.
Yeah, I would, I would, I would try to avoid it, I think.
But I mean, some people put them in like the washing machine.
I don't know.
I don't know how that goes.
I guess it depends what you made it out of.
Yeah.
Hmm.
No, I just spray it, just spray it with Axe Body Spray.
That's what people do.
They pretty much just usually like isopropyl alcohol.
They just spray it with and hope for the best.
Is that real?
Does that work?
Yeah.
Yeah, you just spray it and it kind of neutralizes the most offensive of the odors.
I guess.
Yeah.
I mean, if this infects, I suppose, so kill, kill whatever's growing on it.
Hmm.
Yeah, because you don't want to lose the musk of your, of your husky suit.
All right.
I mean, that's half the appeal.
That's half the appeal.
If you can't smell it.
It's like it's not even there.
Hold on.
And look at this guy.
I'm trying to remember if I did anything else.
What else did I do at Anthro-New England?
Not, not much.
Didn't really go to like, didn't go to any panels or anything.
Because, because, because what do I want to do?
What do I, what do I want a panel for?
Oh, okay.
I can't look at the schedule anymore.
All the previous days are gone.
They're all delisted.
Oh, that's very annoying.
I don't know why.
I guess she had to get the book.
Well, I have the book.
I have the book, but it doesn't have a schedule in it.
It doesn't have the schedule.
No, you have to look online for the schedule.
Because it, because the schedule is like at, at Bronycon, you know, there were so many rooms
and every room had its own schedule.
So there was like a whole like grid of like, you know, what room, what time, what's going on.
Yeah, yeah.
This is much smaller than that.
So it's basically just like one or two main rooms that have an event.
So the schedule is just a list and like at any given hour, it's like, OK, there's like,
you know, maybe, maybe one or two things happening.
So it's not that complicated.
So I don't know why they didn't just print it in the damn book that they give you.
No, you had to look online for it.
You know, they probably did something crazy, like printing the book months in advance.
And it's just they just don't have the data when they did it.
They don't know what the schedule was.
Oh, you know, that reminds me, speaking of printing a book, I I'm man, I'm thinking.
The printers that I use for various things, the local printer, it's called Fleming printing.
I use them for the Blu-ray jackets.
I use them for mostly for RotoradCon printing those.
I think they might suck a little bit.
Or maybe I just because I was very disappointed.
I asked them because I was, you know, because I want to do a book form of
slime and punishment and I asked them what would it cost me?
First of all, I'm just I'm just going to I'm just going to bitch about them for a second.
They won't just they this is something they've never they've never been willing to do it.
They won't just like tell me like how to figure out what something costs.
They they they adamantly will only tell me what something costs.
If I specifically asked them like how much would exactly one hundred copies
of this exact thing, this many pages, this type of paper, this coloration,
this type of binding, that's very many.
Yes, and they won't and they won't I've asked like, can you just give me the formula?
Right. Can you just give me the formula and they won't do it?
They're like, no, you got to ask.
So I have to be like, OK, please tell me how much a hundred would cost.
Please tell me how much two hundred would cost.
Please tell me how much three hundred costs, how much four hundred and how much
would five hundred and then she'll send me five quotes.
And it's like, OK, why are you why are you making this hard on both of us?
Yeah, like why waste their time?
Yeah, like just just fucking let me figure it out, dude.
Well, I asked.
I was asking I was sort of putting my feelers out and I asked them about
what a slime and punishment would be.
And I was like, OK, I kind of ballparked how big it would be.
I kind of ball looks like, OK, it needs to be full photo color.
It needs to be probably maybe about one hundred and fifty ish pages, something like that.
And she sends me back a quote.
I asked for a hundred because that seems like a good like minimum.
Like I would want to print it like no, no fewer than a hundred.
Yeah, I feel like you usually sell about that quantity or pretty much anything.
So I think, yeah, I would think I would expect to sell a hundred.
I think if I was doing it, probably more, hopefully more.
But but but she quoted the price she quoted me.
It was going to cost like fifty dollars a book, even even and I and I'm like.
And I I was I was taken aback and I asked her like, OK, this is pretty expensive.
Can you can you recommend me any ways that we could bring the cost down?
Like is there like a standard size that would be cheaper that's similar?
Maybe different papers. I don't know anything you can recommend.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
And then she sends me a reply that's like, sorry, here.
Sorry, here's the corrected.
Here's the guy made a mistake.
That was not the right price.
Here's the corrected price.
And this time it was like it was like twenty nine thirty ish dollars per copy.
And I and I'm like, OK, better.
That's still high.
That's still more than I think it should cost to do this.
So I just sent the I basically sent the similar.
I was like, OK, better. But still, can you recommend me any?
Like, is there a standard size that would be cheaper?
Is there like what how much would it cost if we reduce the size?
Like what? And she sends me back is like.
And again, she doesn't she doesn't give me any insight.
She's just like, here is the quote.
Here's the quote.
Here's how much it would cost if we printed it at the, you know, I said,
like what if we shrank it down to six by nine?
Like here's how much it would cost for a hundred and six by nine.
And she just sends me a number.
And I'm sick of it. I'm sick of this bullshit.
Yeah, that's terrible.
Just give me just just give me the I don't want to ask you
every specific fucking permutation of size and number of copies
and glossy or unglossy like I won't do it.
First of all, these prices you're quoting me are shit.
And second of all, you're being ridiculous.
Why are you making this so hard?
Why do you hate me so much?
And so I go on, I'm googling around for printing.
So and I found one just the first one I found was called Mixam.
And I'm typing in the specifications I'm looking for.
And Mixam is like is like half.
It's like 18. It's like, uh, 18,
$18 or less, depending on if I change format slightly for per copy.
And I'm like, OK, I kind of think Fleming is just maybe they just suck.
Maybe I shouldn't have used them for anything.
Maybe even printing Road to Radcon with them was a mistake.
Yeah, I mean, it sounds like they're just like, you know,
they'll make up whatever number they think I can get away with.
Like what is it? Oh, he made a mistake.
We'll cut we'll cut the price in half. What was the mistake?
You know, she said she said he like entered the wrong.
You know what? Oh, let me let me find it.
Let me find exactly what she said.
Like how do you accidentally like double the quote?
You know what? Her exact words. Here we go.
Uh, hi, Ben, I've attached a corrected print estimate for you.
Please accept my apologies as the estimator entered an incorrect number
in the production formula and didn't catch it before passing the final estimate along to me.
So there is a formula.
Yeah, it's like there is a formula.
Could you forward me the production formula?
Could you just tell me the fucking formula?
You know what? Yeah.
That's that's true.
And that's just more evidence to what I was already thinking, which is yeah,
they're just they're just telling me whatever they fucking want to tell me,
whatever thing they can get away with.
And that hurts me. That hurts me because I have I have used these guys.
I feel like I had some rapport with this lady.
I have I have done a bunch of different things with them.
I've printed a bunch of stuff with them.
I thought, you know, doesn't that mean something?
Am I not a valued? Am I not a valued customer?
I'm, you know, you're a valued, repeated customer, you would think.
And it's like, listen, you're running a business here.
You're trying to estimate your costs because you got to make money on this, right?
It's like, you can't just it's not it's not just a passion project
where like, you just got to get this printed like you're trying.
No, you're trying to produce a product that you're trying to produce a product.
And I'm trying to try the numbers matter and I got to keep the cost low.
And it's like, bro, surely surely you want me.
It's like it's like it's like the fact that they want to conceal information from me.
It's like, do you not do you not want me to be
if you don't like if you don't want to print like a less robust product,
like if you don't want the price to go down, then like, I don't know,
don't don't offer cheaper production methods, I guess.
It's like it's like she knows that I could bring the price down,
but she doesn't want me to know that.
Yeah, I mean, they're definitely they're treating you like an idiot and a customer
and not like a partner, you know, which is what they they probably shouldn't be treating you like.
I I wonder if it's like, honestly,
not I don't know what like their bread and butter is.
Maybe maybe they don't like me.
Maybe they're sick of me.
Maybe I'm like some small time guy whose whose orders are like,
you know, a couple hundred dollars here, a couple hundred dollars there.
And I'm and they're just like, oh, why do you even bother with this guy?
He's not worth the time.
He's a he's small potatoes.
He's a pipsqueak, small fry.
Yeah, you know, even if it's not the case,
that's definitely the impression they're given, right?
Yeah, so maybe.
Honestly, I mean, maybe maybe they don't care about my business
and I am and they're just sort of like doing it out of formality.
It's like, well, some guy came in and he wants to print, like, you know,
four hundred dollars worth of stuff.
God, I hate when that happened.
I don't know.
So I don't think I'm going to not.
I don't know. I'm going to look in the might look into it.
I'm probably will probably look into other options
for anything that I want to do in the future
before I before I use them again.
I'm a bit I'm just not disenfranchised.
I'm just I'm disenchanted with them.
Yeah. What were we talking about?
Oh, yeah, my stupid printer, my stupid printer in the, you know,
I wonder, damn, I wonder if I got a bad deal.
Makes me wonder if I got a bad deal on the road to Radcon.
How much did those cost me?
Those cost me like.
Two hundred and fifty bucks
or something for like.
Hundred and fifty. No, that's not right.
No, that's not right.
Hold on.
No, it was about five hundred dollars for like a hundred and fifty copies.
Which isn't that bad.
It's like a few dollars.
It was like a paperback comic.
Well, it was.
Printed text, but like I think functionally it was digital printing,
so it doesn't really matter if it was text or images.
So, yeah, like a paper, I mean, you know, staple staple bound.
Which is not not saddle stitched, but like that's fine.
That seems OK.
It doesn't it doesn't seem to.
But maybe I could have gotten.
I'm trying to think the Vapors was printing.
I mean, the Vapors books were bigger, slightly bigger dimension wise.
But they were.
And that that was like it was maybe like seventeen hundred dollars
for an order of like five hundred, but then it was plus shipping.
I think the shipping was a big deal.
I think shipping was a big deal.
I decided to order due with Fleming because I could just pick it up in person.
Yeah, I wouldn't have to pay like a hundred dollars for them to ship me.
Well, I mean, especially if you order five hundred books, right?
Like that's yeah.
Yeah, I'm sure the shipping cost is significant.
Yeah, it would be it would be maybe hundreds of dollars.
Well, maybe not hundreds.
But maybe a hundred dollars.
Yeah, maybe a hundred dollars.
Yeah, I don't know.
Seems pretty seems pretty obvious to me that like something like Mixam
or I have a few other services here that I have tabs open for.
It seems pretty obvious that if these are the prices they're quoting me,
I don't think I can I don't think I can go with Fleming for.
Well, I mean, if you're ready to quit Fleming,
like why don't you just take the Mixam quote and say, listen,
I found this other service.
It seems like they can do something pretty equivalent for much less.
Like, you know, you get in this ballpark.
You know, that's not a bad idea.
And it's probably because Mixam, what you're going to have to go get it shipped.
I will. I will have to get it shipped.
So, you know, there's there's some cost value there.
Like even if they quote you like two dollars more per book per book or whatever,
you know, it might still be worth it to get it done locally.
I should I should maybe order some samples.
What I'm going to do is I think I'm going to I'm going to throw together a book,
a book file, order like a sample copy for maybe a couple different.
A couple different different services, a single sample copy from Mixam,
though, is like seventy dollars.
The curve, the curve, the curve is brutal.
Yeah, like, I guess it scales well, but at low scale,
it's like shit, seventy fucking bucks.
Fleming was only going to charge me fifty for a like a test print.
But but what's the point of getting a test print done if then like it's
it's prohibitively expensive to print a full run?
Yeah, I mean, well, so you like the you like the print quality of Fleming,
right, like it seems fine.
Well, I haven't printed any color stuff with.
Well, I guess I did the Blu-ray jackets, which was was fine.
But that might be a different, you know, it's a it's a different product.
So I don't really know.
Yeah, it's they seem fine.
So maybe it's a tough situation.
Good luck.
It's a tough situation.
It's it's, you know, you know, give did the Red Man comics with the
the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter and she had the she had trouble with the green,
right, because I guess I guess printing green is hard or something.
Oh, it makes sense.
But so I think I mean, I think there are ways to do it.
Like, I think you you have to do like like digital.
I think like digital printing can do it.
It's it's when you're doing like ink printing like CMYK.
Yeah, yeah.
That producing that kind of green is is difficult to impossible.
So, you know, I think I'm going to have to go.
That I think that you know, because slime and punishment obviously has
some greens in there, so I can't I can't skimp on the greens.
So I have to.
Yeah, I'm going to go weird without it.
Yeah.
So I'm going to I'm going to have to spring for probably like the most
expensive like page coloring methods, which is unfortunate.
But it's just the nature of the beast.
So I will I will fucking glossy
prior to go like glossy pages or whatever.
I don't know.
I would like I would like to charge, I don't know.
I guess I was thinking maybe like 30 bucks or something for like a
for like a hundred and fifty page, you know,
eight, eight by or eight by eleven, eight by twelve,
maybe an eight by twelve horizontal print, perfect bound, soft cover book.
I don't know. That sounds nice.
That sounds about that was about the point I was thinking.
So, you know, when she's quoting me, oh, it's going to cost thirty dollars
to print each copy.
I'm like, well, it's like I was hoping to.
Yeah, I'm hoping to sell for thirty dollars.
That's not going to.
Why would I?
I just can't.
It's simply not going to work.
It's just it's just it's just not going to do it for me.
Yeah. Well, you know, they say you got to spend money to make money, right?
Like, maybe maybe you'll make it up in volume, sell them for thirty one.
They say you got to spend money to make money.
So the so if you can spend,
if you're spending all of the money that you're making, then
no, it's like a it's like it's like it's like a car.
No engine, right?
It's like the the the pressure and the volume
that you put the curve on the end.
You put it in and that's the money and then you squeeze it
and you create a combustion and that's the profit.
And then you'd see what I'm, you know, yeah.
And then and then through a through a process of isothermal compression.
That's there you you produce your margins, your margins
you create you create demand, a butter and guns.
Yeah. And so on.
I don't need to explain this fairly obvious analogy.
Yeah, it's simple, simple economics.
I'll be right back. Can you hold on?
You know what? I'm going to pee. I'll be right back.
Quick five here.
Yo.
Mm. Open my bathrobe on.
Cozy. Cozy.
Yeah.
So I think I think we're good.
I think we got a few topics just about time to start the podcast.
No, no, you know what?
Now, these topics suck.
Now, PZP's canceled this week.
Canceled, fuck it.
Yeah. No, thanks.
Nobody wants to hear this.
True.
Yeah, I don't know.
Not a highly eventful week for me.
We could start voicemails if you want.
Well, the only other thing I want to talk about.
Go on. Your favorite topic, cardio.
I've been I've been killing it lately.
It's been great. I picked up.
I picked up a road bicycle.
It's actually a gravel bike, which is a road bicycle like one to ride on the road.
Yeah, yeah, like, you know, your typical road bicycles,
like it's got drop handlebars that are like hoop shaped, you know,
and your skinny little tires so you can go fast.
Oh, as opposed to like a dirt bicycle.
Yeah, like a mountain bike or something.
Mountain bike was the word I was looking for.
Yeah. Yeah. So I picked I picked up a gravel bike,
which is a road bike, but it's got like slightly mountain bike like tires
so you can go off road a little bit.
I always I always a OK,
my my dad had like a street bike, a street bicycle,
and I had like a dirt bicycle as a kid.
I always I always associated that like big, big skinny wheel drop.
Yeah, hoop handlebar as just being like a grown up bike.
And I had, yeah, that's that's what I thought the difference.
It's the adult thing to do.
To switch to the drop handlebar.
And now now that I've grown up, I'm 30 years old,
it was it was time for me to forget flat handlebars and move on to the drops.
I mean, time to time to lose the tread on those tires.
You know, what?
Where are you going with that tread, kid? Come on.
What what mount what mountain specifically are you by?
Yeah.
Gotcha. But man, so I picked I picked it up and I've just been
I've been riding like a maniac.
I was out a couple of times on the road, even though it's winter
and it's cold, done like 25 miles on the road.
I picked up these rollers so you can just ride the bike in place
on like this, these like very belt rollers.
You just put it up on a device.
Yeah, there's not, you know, there's there's a couple of different ways
you can do it. There's some that like hold the bike up that are just like
it makes it into a stationary bike.
But what I got is the crazy person version of that, where it's just
there are just some rollers on the floor that you ride on that you can fall off
of at any time if you stop moving.
Naturally. Naturally.
And it's been great. I've been hitting them hard.
And I love it. It's the best the best cardio I've been doing.
I've got a treadmill, too.
It it kicks the crap out of the treadmill.
I'd absolutely recommend the rollers over the treadmill.
Hmm.
I mean, biking is like lower impact than like running on a treadmill.
It's low impact.
But what's great about the rollers is that you cannot stop pedaling, right?
Because as soon as you stop pedaling, the wheels stop immediately.
You don't have any actual momentum and you fall over.
So it's like if you're on there for 25 months, you're on there pedaling hard
for the whole time, the whole you cannot stop.
Wait. So it's like if you stop, if you like get tired and stop pedaling
what you just you just collapse, the device just implodes.
Well, you know, the only reason you stay up on a bicycle, right,
is the gyroscopic effect of the wheels turning, right?
Yes, like if you think about it, it's it's not moving through space.
It's that the wheels are turning.
Is that is that the whole reason?
Yeah, that's it.
It's the gyroscopic like angular momentum of the wheels.
Yeah, absolutely.
And their moment resisting, resisting, changing that axis
is all that keeps you up, right? That's it.
It's it's not like a it's not about like the fact that there's like two wheels
at once that is like providing like a like a stable like.
Well, that keeps you going like fulcrum, right?
Like that you have the two wheels.
But the reason that you don't like flop over left to right
is just that gyroscopic stabilization.
The wheel the the wheels just don't seem heavy enough.
The wheels just don't seem heavy enough to do that.
Like you're like your body weighs like your body weighs enough.
Like if you were just OK, I don't know to my
like if you can hold a bicycle wheel in your hand and spin it
and you can you can you can you can rotate it in your hand even when it's spinning.
Like the moment like the moment of inertia of a bicycle wheel is not that.
Well, you say that.
But have you ever sat in like a computer chair,
a chair that can turn and held a spinning bicycle wheel?
No, what you'll find.
We did this as a physics experiment when I was in when I was in high school.
Oh, does it does it does it like so if you make your chair turn?
Yeah, if you hold that wheel straight up and down like it would be on the road
and somebody spins it really fast.
If you tip that wheel a little bit, it'll turn the chair that you're sitting in.
Just just so I never did that.
It doesn't seem like the connection exists.
Like it could possibly do that, but it does.
That is crazy.
It's very cool to see.
Science rules.
I love science.
Oh, Neil, the grass Tyson.
You can only kiss yourself on the lips in a mirror.
But anyway, so because of that, right, because you have no momentum,
the wheels stop instantly because you're not, you know, you're not actually rolling.
The bike isn't isn't preserving that through physical space, right?
Wait, sorry, explain to me again, it's on.
You put the bike on a on a roller.
What does that mean?
So imagine a drum, right, like a cylindrical drum.
And you're just writing, you're writing on top of that.
So like you have there's two of them on either side of the back wheel
and it just sits between them.
And so when the wheel turns, it's right.
Oh, OK, OK, and then you have one out in front
that's sitting under your front wheel and it's belt driven from your back wheel.
So so as you spin those rear rollers, it also spins that front roller.
Are you are you directly spinning the roller with your pedaling
or is just like the the wheel is turning and it's spinning the tire is touching
the roller and it got so it turns the roller and then that drives the front roller
which drives your front wheel.
So you'll come to think of it.
I think I saw you post a video of you.
Yeah, I post a little video.
That's what I'm doing.
Mm hmm. And yeah.
So the moment you stop pedaling, the wheels stop turning
like almost immediately within a second or two.
And then very straight.
Well, as soon as you lose that stabilization, right, like you got to put your foot down.
Oh, so it's not like because when you're riding a bike,
you can just kind of coast sometimes. Exactly.
So that's what I'm saying.
You get some speed up and you can just coast down a hill
or just coast on a long stretch.
I see. Yeah. Yeah.
You can't you simply cannot.
You simply cannot do that.
So it ends up being this crazy cardio workout.
Oh, I think it's great.
It's really cool.
I have. Well, I have not been doing cardio, but I have been
counting calories very strictly.
And I think I've lost a little bit of weight and I feel pretty good about that.
I think I could could lose a little bit more, but I think I'm on track.
So that's that's good.
That's great. That's I mean, and as as we all know,
as everyone here knows, the only way to lose weight is a calorie deficit
and anything else is bullshit.
That's true.
Oh, but.
Oh, but I got this.
Oh, but I got this device that like puts a like a like a rubber belt around my midriff
and like vibrates my my my my torso flash.
And those definitely
those will stiffen you right up for sure.
They they move the fat to a more to a to a better region.
They move the fat into my biceps, where they look like big muscles.
Actually,
they squeeze, they squeeze the fat upwards into my upper back.
So it looks like I have big bulging deltoid or
I have big bulging lats on the sides when I when I flex.
Which is very cool.
Very cool.
You get the wings when you lift and you want those wings on stage.
Yes, you get those 10 out of 10s.
Oh, wonderful.
Very good. Yeah.
It's too cold to exercise.
Yeah, that's why that's why I did it.
That's why I got the rollers, because I want to be hitting this bike hard
like all summer.
You know, I want to go on some big like multiple days long, maybe bike rides.
Do a little do a little bike packing as they call it out there.
So I'm getting ready.
I'm amping up.
That's cool. Yeah, that's good.
You know, I have a new phone.
This is this is this is some bitch, baby shit.
But I have a new phone that actually works now and I downloaded Pokemon Go.
Wow, the last time I lost a bunch of weight,
part of the reason why was because I was I was calorie deficit.
I was keto and I was walking around playing Pokemon Go like every day.
That was my workout.
And, you know, it was it worked for what I was trying to do.
Yeah, I mean, it does not take very much to like get that that muscle activation,
you know, literally just walking around for a while is actually huge.
It actually would otherwise not be moving.
It's huge.
What? I lost like I lost like 40 pounds in like six months.
Yeah, I believe us. Yeah.
Yeah, I should I should do that at the very least.
For sure. No moving at all is is bad.
It was very bad.
I mean, if I were you, I would definitely be like jogging around the block.
You got a pretty decent area where you could be jogging.
Yeah, it could be jogging.
I could be jogging. I got a little loop.
That's a little tricky, though, because as soon as you start doing that,
it's like, well, now you're going to be producing a lot of sweaty laundry.
And like, if you don't have the right shoes, you're going to hurt your feet
and stuff and ends up being kind of somehow it ends up being expensive.
It's kind of hard.
I you're that's true.
And I I I hate running.
I've always hated running.
Uh, yeah, I'd rather just only there was some way to exercise
from the comfort of my own home.
Man, it's only yeah, I've got I've got this whole great
regiment that's been working out great for me.
I only do like four body weight strength exercises and I do my you've got those.
You've got those rings.
You've got those hanging rings.
I've got the rings and all I do with those.
All I do with them is what they call, I think, an Australian pull up,
which is where Australian is that when like you lean back on your heels?
Yeah, you lean back in your heels and you can do a pull up
and you adjust the rope length to to adjust the intensity.
And I've just got to set to where I can do like 20 of them to adjust like the angle, right?
So you're kind of on your heels, lean back and you're sort of pulling yourself
up and forward. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah. Yeah.
So I do those.
I'll do body weight squats.
I'll do push ups.
And then I also do a calf extension on stairs.
And those four things together, combined with like going for a run
or hitting the rollers on the bike is like crazy, great, full body workout.
And it doesn't even take that long, which is nice, too.
Well, I have not been lifting for I have not been lifting since New Year's,
which, oh, God, two months.
It's almost two months now, but it's a long time.
Yeah, it's pretty.
But I'm actually I'm actually for real going to start again soon.
I swear. I promise.
I swear, guys, I'm going to start soon.
Oh, really?
My games.
Do you know if, you know, if Kazi Munchie are lifting?
They are they're not.
They have they have also not been.
But I think I think we're all we're all on board of like,
let's we've got to stop fucking around.
Man, no excuse for them because, like, the stuff's there.
They got it. Yeah.
Just go downstairs, start lifting.
What's the problem? You know?
Yeah, true. Calling him out. Calling him out.
I'm the I'm the cheerleader.
Yeah, I keep the motivation going.
Without you, without you.
Keep everyone's spirits high.
The morale's too low.
Exactly. Exactly.
That's that's me. I'm a I'm a I'm a I'm a hype man.
You know, I'm a positive influence.
When you think of Ben St, you think positive attitude, hype.
Famously.
Yeah, the two those two things.
Positive attitude and I.
Put those on my tombstone.
Do you what do you think?
Voigt voicemail?
Can we start up a voicemail?
OK, let me let me check if we've gotten any last minute.
No. All right.
Let me grab the first one here.
Where did I put it?
OK, the first one of the day is called
Re folks with bad animation takes from pronouns at she dot her.
OK, sounds promising.
People, some bad bad animation takes folks with that animation takes.
There we go. All right.
Three, two, one, go.
I was listening to episode 300 when you're talking about people
who think lower frame rates inherently look bad.
And I have a theory as to why throughout its entire history,
animation is generally been looked down upon by the mainstream as something
that, well, perhaps good is always of less value and more disposable than live action,
something for kids or for cookie cutter sitcoms.
Beyond that, the masses don't see animation as a worthy art form in itself.
It's only valuable in the ways that can create a facsimile of reality.
In other words, people want to forget they're looking at a drawing as much as possible.
That's why Disney movies all used full animation, then went to 3D animation,
and they're now getting remade in live action.
Even though these are all equally valuable mediums, the stigma against
animation means most people see them in a hierarchy with most realistic at the top.
That's why Spider-Verse looks bad to these people.
For as well done as it can be, all of its stylistic flourishes are meant to remind
you that you're looking at a bunch of drawings as much as possible.
It's easy to misdiagnosis issue as people just not knowing enough about animation,
but that's just a side effect, not the cause.
You don't need to know the techniques to think Spider-Verse looks incredible.
But if you're the type of person who isn't interested in the unique artistic
merit of animation in the first place, you're just naturally not going to know
what you need to talk about when you try to critique it and end up sounding like an idiot.
Upsounding like an idiot.
So low frame rate draws attention to the artifice.
Yeah, I mean, there's definitely some truth to that.
If you're there and if you're there to appreciate the skill of that artifice,
it's like, hell, yeah, but if you're.
My dad, my dad is someone who is just like not interested in animation at all,
except he did think Toy Story was pretty great.
Like he thought that like, wow, they made a whole movie in a computer.
That's crazy.
A whole movie fit in a computer?
Jesus.
He thought that the 3D of Toy Story was pretty was pretty great.
But he's not interested in animation.
So I could see my dad being like shaking his head at a low frame rate
because it would draw attention to the artifice of it.
Yeah, well, I mean, what's a what's a low frame rate like 12?
You know, because I'm sure Toy Story was probably on 24, right?
Like, I doubt it was. Gosh, no idea.
It was probably 20 frames.
Well, have you have you seen Spider-Verse?
I have not seen it, but I know what it I'm really not into that sort of thing.
But I know what it looks like.
Yeah, yeah, it looks like a bunch of comic book type things
kind of glued together, different styles.
Yeah, it has it has sort of a sort of a jerky
sort of a low frame rate kind of like stop.
Well, it's got it's got sort of a mixed frame rate
appearance where like different things are are sort of different different
frame rates and you've got the low frame rate action pieces.
Yeah, you know, which is which school?
Cool aesthetic choice.
I think I think I think I think this person is is right.
Yeah, that probably is that probably is part of it.
OK, next one is called Sorry if I'm mean.
His videos are OK.
Three, two, one, go.
So you know how Ben doesn't like Saber Spark
or at least he doesn't like his voice.
Well, you know, I could listen to a Saber Spark video,
but my friend texting me about the new Lockston video.
I'm just like, you can listen to Lockston Lockston like that guy's voice.
If you if you haven't heard him, he makes a Pokemon videos,
but I give it a listen.
It's something else. Geez.
OK, I don't know who that is either.
OK, it's it's it's Lockston and Noggin, right?
Is the channel you tell me?
I don't know. I don't know anything about that.
I'm seeing it on the wiki tubia, though.
I don't know.
I've definitely seen a Lockston and Noggin video before.
OK, wait, this this is Noggin.
Oh, shit, I accidentally clicked on a Noggin when I was looking for a Lockston.
Stupid fool classic blunder.
We've all been there. There's Noggin, Noggin.
Wait.
I'm like, I'm confused.
They all say Noggin.
Maybe the ones that don't say Noggin.
Are Lockston.
Um, I think it's all the same guy, though, right?
I'm looking on wiki tubia here.
It just says Austin Lockwood is better known online as Lockston and Noggin.
I think it would be.
Why would he be Lockston and Noggin if it's one guy?
I think it's just one guy.
Well, I listen to like five seconds of him and he sounds like a you.
He sounds like a YouTuber.
Yeah, I don't know.
OK, sure. Yeah, yeah, sure.
He's annoying. Yeah, annoying.
But whatever. So is everybody.
I mean, that guy was very in the lead, though.
He's saying he likes listening to.
Saberspark. Saberspark videos.
I don't know. I don't personally.
I also don't.
I also don't personally, but that's OK.
I'm not his audience.
Absolutely.
As as definitionally proven by the fact that I don't watch his videos.
OK, next one is called.
Ben St is a grease puddle on the floor of a fast food.
OK, there it is. Three, two, one, go.
If I've done my calculations correctly,
then this will be going on to episode three hundred and two.
Good so far. Yeah.
Ben St, give and take. Hello.
You brought up in a conversation about smiling friends,
how there was a grease puddle.
I am whatever episode.
But you failed to mention because you probably didn't know.
But Psycho Pebbles, the guy who made that show.
Psycho Pebbles, not Psycho Pebbles.
Weston Chandler to do the voice of that grease pub.
We did mention that because, Chris, we know why.
We did mention that.
Harry Partridge to do an impression of Chris.
And if you watched the episode, Ben St.
Shut up. You probably, you know, hear that.
And you'd be like, oh, wow, I appreciate that.
Yeah, I'm sure that's how you would be.
You would be like, oh, I appreciate that.
Yeah, I'd be I'd be blown away to hear Harry Partridge's voice in a in a cartoon.
Such an irregular medium for the man.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Dude, we literally talked about that exact thing.
But OK, I'm sure that you did because I actually I listened to the last podcast and I heard that.
Yeah, exactly.
What a fool. What a fool.
Maybe maybe he well, he really he left this five days ago, so he must have left this.
Oh, yeah, maybe he left this before that episode.
So maybe that's explained.
That's all.
Yeah.
Next one is Revelations, the secret to good content.
Three, two, one, go.
I remembered Vic and Hope and I've been listening to them real good.
It's really good to hear somebody be talking about people that I like to think about,
I.e. Ben St.
Did they talk about talking about his gripes?
It's been saying really good stuff.
I could listen to people complaining about Ben St. for hours.
What did he say?
That's why I can go back and listen to old episodes of podcasts and just
not get tired of them.
What did he say?
Secret. Fuck you.
Yeah, secret to good content is if it's about people that I know who they are.
I like to hear my friends make fun of my other friends,
except none of them are my friends.
Listen, he did not he did not give any context
as to what what Vic and Hope conversation he is talking about.
So I'm just going to I'm just going to throw that in my mental trash can.
Yeah.
Unclear fever means like contemporaneous content or or historical.
Yeah. Like he knows if if if if I would be interested
if Vic if Vic is I doubt this.
This doesn't seem like something Vic would do.
But if Vic were like bitching about me and making fun of me or whatever
on Vic and Hope like these days, I would be interested to hear it.
Let me know if that's the case.
I'm going to assume it's not the case.
Yeah, I'd be surprised because I'd be surprised.
What would he have to say?
Nothing.
Well, he haven't done anything to him.
He commented on the documentary.
Just to say, like he said, like, oh, damn,
forgot I put like tons of work into this.
Sorry, I wasted my life on this.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, basically.
Next, Shade Shade was a replying to some tweets of mine recently.
I saw that.
So so I have to assume that I'm that I'm cool,
that I'm square with the Collins Brothers
because if one likes me than the other months, I mean,
I think you're doing fine.
I hope so. I like Vic.
So, you know, yeah, I agree.
Vic, if you hate me, we know.
Seems like a nice.
He seems handsome.
So it's going to be OK.
Hmm.
Next, next voicemail is called
Ben St.
Character Inconsistencies, parentheses, retcons.
Question mark three, two, one, go.
OK, so in the retcon two documentary commentary track,
the character of Ben St refers to the Digi Cat as a quote, good cat, unquote.
This is a complete contradiction.
No, earlier views where the character Ben St clearly despises the cat
exemplified in his sonic to one on one
lecture where he demands that the cat be removed from his premises
with pure malice in his eyes and hate in his demeanor and voice.
I forgot about that. Yeah, he's the Ben St.
I yelled at you.
Inconsistence.
Yeah, I forgot.
I yelled at somebody got fired for that one.
Lala was being Lala was very rarely annoying.
She just happened to want to sit in a very inconvenient spot that day.
It was unusual behavior for her that she she made me.
She she irritated me on this set.
This was somebody's actual cat.
Yeah, that was Trixie's cat.
And her or her parents.
Okay, Lala short for Key Lala after the the boomerang girl from Inuyasha.
That's embarrassing, but OK.
OK, her cat who would
who once who once caught a flying squirrel out of the air and left it torn in half
at our back door on the porch.
What a sweetie.
Lala was a Lala was a good cat and she was a good cat.
She was an outdoor cat and she would pretty much just leave you alone
most of the time.
Well, I think, you know,
if I were to characterize the Ben take on cats, I don't think you're a fan usually.
I'm OK with them, but like they
know, I like them, but I don't like when they're annoying.
I just I just don't like when they're annoying.
Sometimes they can be annoying.
I guess. So, you know, and there was right.
She wanted to be in a place where it was inconvenient.
And so, you know, it makes sense. Yeah, yeah.
So I so I had to so I had to verbally abuse the cat.
I saw in a public display of
Ranker, the next one is called
Ben St sings the PCP theme three to one go.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
That's right.
I want to drink.
Come on, I love.
Come on, and my name is Ben.
Just as I remember it, how do they how do they get this recording of me singing
that in to myself in private?
Yeah, sorry, you had to hear that, everypony.
Next voicemail is called Bibi three to one go.
OK, good. Good.
Yep. Next one is called What's up, YouTube three to one go.
What's up, guys?
Sorry, I haven't made a voicemail in a while.
We're going to get right into it, but don't forget to smash that like button.
Follow me on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Google, plus, Imgur and Mastodon.
All right. First things first, we're going to respond to the response to this voicemail.
Go.
It was a little short, a little short for a YouTube intro.
I met I met someone who used Mastodon
at Anne Annie.
We were talking about Psycholonials in line for registration
and someone behind us in line chimed in about it.
It was I was describing my my argument with Lady Emily and Sarah Zed
on Twitter about Psycholonials.
Did you see that? By the way, I don't think I did.
OK, I was just because you know who they are.
No. OK, well, Sarah, Sarah Zed is a YouTuber
and Lady Emily is also a YouTuber, but also is Sarah Zed's editor.
Oh, is Sarah like the the Lindsay Ellis type?
Sort of. Yeah, kind of. Yeah.
Yeah, I think I've seen I think I've seen her.
Well, she Lady Emily read Psycholonials and didn't like it.
I kind of replied to say I kind of liked it.
But I also agreed with some of the stuff she said.
And then Sarah Zed chimed in in response to me to say.
I'm I'm I'm going to paraphrase
because I don't want to go and like read the tweets all verbatim.
But I really think I'm not being unfair
when I characterize her complaints about Psycholonials as
the character does bad things, therefore, the story is bad.
She she basically she listed a bunch of things that.
The main character does that are bad
and says that she's not punished for them.
Actually, Ben, if you think about it,
a lot of people died as a result of her careless actions.
Like like literally, that's what she that's what she said.
She said like the character did bad things and and like
and there's no punishment in the story for her and it's bad.
And I was like, OK, well, those are all
like I'm pretty sure you're meant to know that those things she does are bad.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know.
And she said she said like her answer was like,
well, Hussie's real Andrew Hussie's real life friends
think that cyberbullying is good.
Therefore, it's it's weird that Hussie wrote a story
about someone who does bad things to people that harass them online.
And I'm like, look, I don't know what to say to that.
I don't know what Hussie's friends think.
I just I read this and I'm like, it's pretty clear
that what she's doing is bad, actually.
And I didn't need.
Like the fact like the fact that her friend.
OK, Sarah said that the only like the only like consequence
in the story that that Z faces is that it makes her friend Abby sad.
Yeah. And like, yes, that's true.
All the only bad, the only thing that affects
Z does terrible things.
And the only time she thinks, oh, this is bad
is because after enough bad things, Abby gets sad.
And I don't know.
To me, it's it's like, well, Abby's not good either.
Abby's also bad.
Abby is kind of like a freak for just kind of going along with it.
Yeah. I mean, the whole the whole story is they're like
in Florida. You've read it.
Yeah, I read the whole thing.
And it's like, OK, they're supposed to be kind of unlikable bad people.
That's the idea. Yeah, they're definitely not.
You're you're definitely not supposed to spoilers like, you know,
see her like send death squads after people that harass her online and be like,
oh, man, this is like Hussie's wish fulfillment.
Hussie thinks this is good, actually queen.
I'm glad someone's finally saying that we need.
We need death squads.
So I'll just I don't know.
I mean, and so you see, you see, you see it reflected in Abby, right?
That that what she is doing is bad.
That is the punishment. It makes sense.
It's like, yeah, we don't need her to literally go to jail or something.
That's so true.
Like Abby, yeah, like, like, what do you want?
Like, like, oh, yeah, she becomes a dictator and starts sending death squads out.
And then her best friend is like, wow, I hate what's happening here.
And and Z is like, oh, darn, I guess what I did was bad.
It's like, you know, what do you want?
She sees the consequences of her actions.
She sees the weight of everything.
And it's like, oh, now you're left with the moral choice.
And it's magnified to this like universally large scale.
But it's the same as any other story.
It's like, oh, I'm going to stop doing the bad thing.
And I'm going to choose love and friendship over over tyranny and power.
And it's like, OK, yeah, that same as every story.
I don't see I don't see what the specific complaint is.
It's just like, I'll be I'll be honest.
My my read of it is is basically just Sarah's Sarah, Sarah Zed.
And therefore, Emma, Lady Emily, because Sarah Zed thinks whatever
Emma, whatever Sarah Emily thinks, whatever Sarah.
Yeah, they just don't like Hussie.
And they read lots of bad and ill intent into the story of
Psycholonials because they think he's bad man.
Yeah. I mean, that's what it sounds like.
I feel like Hussie didn't even have really anything to say with Psycholonial seat.
He had he had the opportunity to say so much more.
It was just he chose not to and it was kind of meaningless.
I totally agree.
I completely I completely agree.
I think if there's anything to criticize, it's it's the lack of of of meaning.
Yeah, really, really, the criticism from my perspective is that it's exactly
what what Sarah Zed is wishing it was, which is a story where someone does bad
things, realizes they were wrong and and and watch it.
And it's just like, well, it shouldn't have done that.
Shouldn't have done that.
OK, I'll say there was another thing.
She sort of just mentioned this in one of her posts.
She said that like she mentioned that like it goes on.
You know, I'll just I'll just read this one, actually, because this this one
I this one is baffling to me.
What's her name? Mary Sue, writer.
Yes.
I'm going to find the exact one because because I don't want to misquote.
I don't want to I don't want to mischaracterize this.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
You tell me what you think when you when you hear this.
OK, there is zero mention of the fact that her group is mostly made up
of white people occupying indigenous land, save for one offhanded comment by her friend.
This is in the middle of a bunch of other statements, but this one stood out to me.
And not in a good way.
Yeah, I mean, it's made up of white people.
They're all wearing white clown makeup.
So first of all, I don't know.
How do you know that?
How do you know they're all they're all supposed to be white people?
I'm and second of all, I don't know, Nantucket indigenous land,
like maybe once upon a time.
Yeah, I'm sure that it was like a Wampanoag settlement.
At some point, but it's like.
But like today, it's like it's like white people.
Yeah. And really, I mean, what is the story?
If not a complaint that rich white people are on the island, you know,
that it's a waste of space and a stupid vacation destination.
To today, like that is the story is that it's terrible.
What we've done to it today.
Today, the ethnic makeup of Nantucket is eighty seven point four percent white non Hispanic,
three percent black or African American,
etc, etc, whatever, it's white people.
So like, I don't know, man, like,
Psychologials is definitely not the story of the of the Jew of Z's
Jew of Z's white jubilites coming and colonizing the the indigenous
Nantucket Island.
Like that's not what that's not what happens.
Like certainly, certainly that sucks that that happened.
But it's like what what the story is is like looking at the present
condition of Nantucket and why that sucks.
Right. Yeah. And I think that's totally valid.
You don't need to tell the other story to tell this story.
Hmm. What do you mean by the other story?
I mean, you don't have to include like, oh, it's bad that that white people
have colonized it like it's bad that rich people are there currently.
Like that is currently a problem.
I don't know, man.
That just doesn't even seem germane at all to the story of Psychologials.
That's just just to just seem like a bizarre thing to even bring up
in a discussion. Yeah.
So I guess I got to say, I'm not impressed with Emily and Sarah's
takes on Psychologials.
What it is is just that it's like, oh, sure.
Sure, he's making this message, but he could have done more.
And it's like, you could all you could always do more.
You could. Did you see if you read if you read Homestuck?
No. OK.
Well, you know who Jan Measley is?
No. Sorry. OK.
A guy, a YouTube guy who I'm fond of, he made of he had a patron reward
thing that he promised.
He promised to make a Homestuck video, and he recently did.
And I watched it and it was OK.
I was actually a little disappointed in it.
It wasn't a great video. It was all right.
He points out a bunch of things that suck about Homestuck, and he's totally
right that all of those things suck about Homestuck.
The.
There was there was one he again, he points out some things
that Homestuck doesn't do like it specifically doesn't make a point
about how like social hierarchies are artificial and arbitrary.
Like it specifically does not make that point because in troll society,
the blood hierarchy is extremely not arbitrary.
And there are extremely obvious like physiological differences
between the cast members, the members of the different cast, right?
So it's like it's it's he makes he says like it's setting.
It's set up almost as though it's going to make a point like that.
And then it just doesn't.
And like, I agree with what he's saying.
Like, yeah, it could have made that point.
But also.
I think it's I think it's a little petty to be like.
This like the story bad because it didn't make a point I wanted it to make.
Yeah, yeah, I it's really the same criticism criticism.
It's like, yeah, it could have done more.
You could definitely have done more.
But I don't know if they didn't want to do that.
So I mean, I don't want to I don't want to defend
Homestuck too hard because it definitely sucks.
A lot of it does.
So but that I don't know that.
Yeah, it's just like a point to something that's not there and be like,
why isn't that there?
And like, well, I don't know.
Yeah, man. Yeah.
And, you know, yeah, it's tough.
It's tough because maybe it should be.
But like, I don't know, not everything is going to be the perfect
enlightened criticism of of society that you'd want it to be.
Unfortunately, like, it's just you can't fit it all in to everything.
Like it's good.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
It's a shame.
Sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, sorry, Sarah.
Sorry, Emily, you're you're you're going in the trash.
I was I got I was a little annoyed.
I was I was a little bit annoyed with Sarah and Emily.
I thought they were being a little bit shitty about it.
I was trying to be they seemed a little bit mad.
They seemed a little bit annoyed at me for like defending it.
And I got I felt it felt like it was personal to them.
And I didn't really like it.
I didn't come away with a positive feeling about them after that interaction.
Yeah, but that's OK.
That's OK.
Next voicemail is called See you next week.
Three, two, one, go.
Well, that was a pretty cringe take.
But what else could we expect?
All right, let's get on to the next segment.
We got a voicemail coming in from Ben, Saint and Gibb and take go.
Should the voicemailers make it a lot of assumptions about the cast this week?
Well, there's well, there's another voicemail called See you next week.
So maybe I'll just go right into that one.
Three, two, one, go.
Well, I was not expecting that.
All right. Well, thanks for showing up, everyone.
We'll see you again next week.
Just smash that like button, subscribe, ring that bell.
Find me on socials, you know, the deal.
Don't little little bit of a swing and a miss with that second one.
Yeah, a little, little unfortunate, unfortunate timing.
You know, we've really got a wealth in the burgeoning genre
of just introductions and outros.
And I hope there's more voicemails
that are just the introduction and outro of videos.
I mean, when you boil down YouTube down to its core, right?
Like that's I mean, that is content, right?
Like the intro, the outro.
It's most of it, right?
You don't really need what's what's sandwiched in the middle.
I mean, I'm here for the bread.
I'm here for just absolutely.
Because I mean, what's I mean, I'm here to fill up on bread.
What is the meat really?
It'll be 10 seconds of interesting value.
But on the outside of that, we've got all this beautiful set dressing
that, you know, we need to appreciate.
I I couldn't have said it better myself.
All right. Next one is called I make them ponies talk
from horse at pussy.juice.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Rainbow Dash, remember when our good pal
Ben St. defended an alcoholic domestic abuser with his girlfriend's leg?
Butter shy. Damn right, I do.
That was epically based also like the part where Ben
then went on to call her soul fat.
That was peak sigma behavior.
We stand.
Thanks, ponies.
I'm glad you like my like the stuff that I do in here
on the procrastinator spot.
I love it. I love I love those little I love those little
love those little little candy colored marshmallow horses.
Always good to hear from them.
Next one is called petition to make the opening song
from episode 300 of the new three, two, one, go.
Well, do it.
Yeah, fair enough.
Which one was 300, do you remember?
Was that it was like the the Nate clips all crushed together?
Is that so it was?
You know what, let me let me find out.
The procrastinators.
Wait, didn't episode three started with.
It started with Nate and like mumke and Jeff, right?
I think so.
I think it was like all that stuff kind of crushed together
and then like layered on top of each other.
So like a a million Nates all at once, right?
Oh, PCP.
Yeah, but then it like fades into.
I don't know. I don't know if that's in every episode.
No.
You know, and I think if we really look at the psychology of this voicemail,
or I think what they're trying to say in a roundabout way is that they
appreciated the effort and the construction of that introduction song.
And they're just they're just trying to push.
They don't know how to genuinely express that feeling.
So instead, they're saying, oh, make it the one for every podcast.
That's not what they mean. We know that.
They're just showing their love for you.
Well, good.
Keep on doing it.
Show it at showyourloveatpatrion.com slash the procrastinators.
Get that commentary track.
Get the commentary track on that Radcom to documentary, baby.
I actually I I recommend the commentary track a lot.
Very good. Yeah, is it good?
Yeah, I mean, I think me and Gib had a lot to say.
We had a lot of we had a lot of stuff to say about like,
hey, you know, remember that thing?
What did? Well, let's talk about what that was.
What was actually going on with that stuff?
What did we actually what do we think about that in hindsight?
Yeah, we had a lot.
Yeah, I guess a lot has happened, right?
Like, yeah, the context of everything and and where you've ended up is really.
That's a lot. There's a lot there. There's a lot.
So, yeah, we we filled we filled the whole two hours
with in Trench and Insights and.
The
illuminating additional context.
Next voicemail is called Steven Girard.
There it is. Three, two, one, go.
Ben, can you take over or give uploading the podcast to Spotify and Apple
Podcasts because Tom obviously has lost interest
because he keeps forgetting and there's missing episodes.
Yeah, I asked Tom again the other day.
I added him in the server and I got no reply.
I don't know what he's doing.
He hasn't done it for a couple of weeks.
Yeah, I mean, I've seen people complain about it, too.
Like, people are clearly upset that the podcasts are not generally available.
Yeah, and I don't I don't know how to do it.
I don't I've never fucked with Apple Podcasts or Spotify or whatever.
So I like I would have to learn how to do it.
I guess I'm going to try and keep pestering him
and maybe I'll just catch him on a day where he's like, yeah, sure, I'll do it.
Yeah, I mean, even if you could just like just ask him to write you up some notes.
It's like, I mean, how hard could it be, right?
It's like, you got to log in somewhere and you got to post it like.
I thought he had I think he had some kind of like web hook that like did it for him.
Yeah, I mean, probably that's how, you know, like you see people put out
their their album on like 10 platforms and there's some kind of service that does that.
But yeah, I wish he yeah, I haven't heard from him in a while.
Uh, I'm going to I'm going to try and get it sorted out.
Yeah, you know, I was kind of I was hoping he'd be here because I saw he was
I guess now he's trying some stuff on like a Game Boy game maker.
Oh, right.
He I saw he like refurbished a Game Boy or something.
Yeah. At first, I so he's like taking the vertical slice demo that he had done before
and trans transliterating that over to this Game Boy Studio.
And at first I was like, well, that's kind of silly because oh, so it makes
like an imitation of a Game Boy game that you can play on a computer.
But it seems like it actually produces a playable Game Boy ROM.
So I'm assuming his plan is to like make the game there, you know,
make whatever tech demo and then play it physically on his Game Boy,
which sounds pretty cool. Sounds cool to me.
Is he wait, is he doing like Game Boy like game programming?
Is he making no way it's, you know, it's yet another drag and drop editor.
But yeah, it is like it produces a Game Boy game, which is kind of cool, but nifty.
Do what she was do what she was learning to code, though.
Tom, learn to code, please.
Is he what happened to killing code?
I don't know. Couldn't tell you.
Remember, remember killing code?
Vaguely. Munchy and, Munchy and Tom.
A distant memory of the deep dark past.
A distant memory, man.
Coding is easy. You just look up.
It kind of is.
You just look, you just, you just, you just look up.
You just fucking Google.
I mean, command you're looking for is.
Once you understand like logic and flow control, right?
Like if and for and stuff, and you understand the syntax,
you know, various curly brackets or whatever you need.
It's, it's, it's just about learning the syntax.
It's just about learning, you know, that.
And then you just look up the API, like you look up the functions
you're going to call and how you call them. Yeah. And like, that's it.
Right. That's it. That's it.
It's literally it, you know, like you're using Game Maker or whatever.
It deals with the whatever other bullshit.
It's just like you write your thing and that thing has some code
and it's got some, some variables and some functions, right?
Like you just use naturally.
That's it. Yeah. You just, they, they, they made them for you.
They made them for you. They laid them out for you to use.
It's just like, here you go.
You just take them, just take them and run with it.
What could be simpler?
So, yeah, I think I've said before that I found
I found the drag and drop Game Maker stuff to be
terrible, hated it.
Yeah. Yeah, it's tough because like, you know, I'm sure there are some
drag and drop tools that can get you pretty close to like some finished games.
But realistically, I feel like drag and drop is, is designed to get people
interested in it and not actually designed to complete a project.
And, you know, it's a fundamental trap.
Right. That's how it was. That's how it was for me.
Hey, speaking of before we move on of Killing Code,
how is, how is Munchie getting on?
Like, I know he's, he's sort of gone into computer science.
Is he, is he programming, do you know?
He, I don't really know that much about it,
but he is, he is doing some like web server stuff.
OK. With school, I think.
I think that's fine to say.
Yeah, he's doing some he's involved.
He's involved with some school server things.
And so he's, he's.
I couldn't, I couldn't really tell you much more than that.
This is what he mentioned once in a while.
Well, cool. I'm glad I'm glad he's still sticking with it.
He, yeah, he is, he is sticking with it.
He is, he just started another semester, I think.
That was his excuse.
That was his excuse for not lifting for a while.
It was a new semester, a busy school, a school is so hard.
I got to do my sorry.
I can't, sorry, I can't lift.
I got to do my homework.
Oh, I can't, I can't.
I have to write an essay for Mrs.
Terwilliger's history class.
I got to make a book.
Make a book report on the, on the, on the catch you in the Y.
Yeah, as one does in university.
I sure why not?
Why not? Why not?
OK, next voicemail is called.
Where was it?
It's called Boston with an exclamation point.
Three, two, one, go.
I did it, Ben.
I'm in Boston and I took the green line.
Yay, who lives in the suburbs.
It was freaking cool.
I'm in Boston now.
I'm coming for you, Ben.
Oh, wait.
But.
Sounds like a strapping young lad.
I'm glad he's found the virtue of public transit.
Take the B line green line.
B line, green line to get to to get to my my neighborhood in Austin, BG.
The old, the old BG, G, G, B, L, G, L, A, B, D, L.
D, D, L, G.
What was I talking about?
Next voicemail.
And moving on is is a four letter word used to indicate a valid statement.
Three, two, one.
What?
Is it just a gunshot?
I don't know what that is.
I think the word they're looking for is true, true.
OK, next voicemail is a image, I think.
I'll post, I'll post the link.
Oh, how nice.
Lovely.
This is from there is no you, but you're happy at purplevoid.com.
I guess this is a, this is a redone give with a little happy Kirby eyes.
Hmm.
Oh, cute.
Very nice.
Next one is called.
When will they notice three, two, one, go?
Ben, crack, munchy.
When is the YUM Corporation going to advertise endless war?
You literally have three of their main restaurants in your game.
Just imagine slightly Baja Blast in every pizza hut box has a link to the server.
Yeah, I think we got to we got to leverage that YUM brand's connection.
We, I mean, by putting YUM brands in the game
and featuring them so prominently, I think we've become effectively
board member shareholders.
I think that grants us some level of of intellectual property ownership.
I believe so. I agree.
I believe that's yeah.
I I think that's should that's how it should work.
And I'm going to operate as though it is.
Man, did you you remember when Star Wars
episode one came out a thousand years ago?
Right. Sure.
I must have been fucking a child.
Must have been a child.
Maybe ten, five or ten, somewhere around there, probably closer to five.
I don't know. OK. You're older than me.
I don't know how old you were.
But anyway, right.
KFC had this great tie in with like these little
like pogs of of Star Wars, like poggers, little paper, little paper things.
And it was this whole this whole thing.
Anyway, we got to do that.
We had to do that, but Slime.
You got to make Pogs.
We got to make Slime Pogs for a KFC.
Why you should be able to play Pogs in the Slime Casino.
I agree. I don't know.
You should know why it's missing.
You should actually someone should actually put Pogs.
I'll tell Stottle to just do that.
Tell Stottle to please add Pogs.
Honestly, it's a perfect fit.
Slime Pog.
We've we've got the Slime Pog emoji and brand tie ins, you know.
And when you're and when you're playing Pogs, right,
you have your your your KFC Pogs beat your Taco Bell Pogs
and your Taco Bell Pogs beat your Pizza Hut Pogs
and your Pizza Hut Pogs beat your KFC Pogs.
You know, it's a whole as a meta.
You know, there is that KFC near you guys.
What if you weren't engaged in a campaign of, say, targeted harassment,
wearing continually ad stickers, graffiti, posters
to just paint that KFC green?
Hmm, harassing a local business.
What about this? What about this?
Hmm, what about what about harassment, but we target it, right?
We're targeted with it, right?
We don't just do it willy nilly.
Hmm, it's not so much I misspoke.
It's not a targeted harassment. That sounds illegal.
It's more of a focused engagement, focused, focused, negative,
and pointedly negative engagement with an individual with an individual
or group of individuals.
Yet I'm down. I'm on board.
I see no downsides.
Next voicemail is Christian Cartoon fan, not Otaku, Twilight Four.
Three, two, one, go.
After destroying anime forever, I watched an American cartoon, Laurel Orrell.
This show is a masterpiece.
Starts with some edgy jokes about Christians, but pulls a Bojack horseman halfway through.
What show? I think that was Moral Orrell.
Moral Orrell. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, Moral Orrell.
Yeah, I wish it. I've heard that's good.
I think I have seen a little bit of it.
Harg's a big fan of that one, I think.
I caught I caught it on I caught it on Adult Swim once or a few times.
I guess I didn't really have a strong opinion about it.
Yeah, it seems fine. I'm not that into it. I'm not that into it.
Sorry. So OK.
Sorry, Twilight. Sorry, Twilight.
I wish I could say more about your favorite show.
I'm sorry, Twilight.
Sorry, Twilight.
Looks like you're going back to the glue factory.
Next one is an image.
Is this a draw your own graph or is it
suggesting that we have not let not yet left the cringe plateau?
No, this looks like these are the the axes are labeled.
Oh, you're supposed to draw a curve.
Like how based was every error?
Yeah, yeah, I think it's draw your own.
OK, let me. All right, well, let's let's do this.
Yeah, pop this open in the game.
I'm was it was episode episode 200.
Was that Radcon four?
Or Radcon three?
I think it was a 200 was a Radcon three.
Yeah, it would have to be. It was quite a while ago.
Sure. Yeah, here's here's my answer, I guess.
I'm going I'm going with it.
It's perfect. Oh, OK, OK.
See, I want to I feel like you had this start in the exact middle
on the left hand side, you know, because the podcast could be neither
based nor cringe at the start.
You just unless you're saying it's cringe to start a podcast,
which I guess I agree with, you're you're thinking, OK,
you're thinking that like how it started is like the baseline.
And like, well, yeah, and then have you have you moved more based
or more cringe from there?
That's I mean, that's how I would try it.
Not that it really matters.
I think this is a pretty good, pretty good representation here.
What's the so what's the giant Valley there?
That's probably the most significant thing.
I was the giant Valley, you know, I probably drew it a little too steep.
I would say the giant Valley, the Valley there is post
Radcon four when we were just we were just shedding people.
And we kind of didn't know what to do about it.
The it recovers from the Valley after we just decide
after after the tombstone rebrand, we decide like
we're just we're just going to.
Well, I guess it's the Ben and Gib show.
And sometimes Tom now.
Yeah. And, you know, it's funny.
I kind of did the same thing.
I don't know if my Valley's in the right spot, but that was my thinking.
I was like, OK, here's the big crash is everyone's leaving.
Right. You. OK.
And then generously I've I've said, oh, it's getting it's getting better.
And then I don't know.
Now I'm on this one, so it's kind of coming down a little bit.
You you put you put the Valley at Radcon, like at Radcon three.
Yeah. Right.
Because the episode two hundred is at Radcon three.
Yeah, surely after that, because that's like, you know, I'm not listening.
And then I'm assuming it's getting better while I'm not listening.
And then as soon as you start listening, that's when the worst.
Yeah, OK. All right, I respect it.
I had I gave it I gave it like I gave it wibbly wobbly
is around the episode between hundred and one hundred and one hundred and two.
Because like, who knows what was going on around then?
I assume some weird shit was happening.
People were joining. People were leaving.
It was a it was a fucked up fucked up situation.
Yeah, I like how at no point up until somewhere post episode 201
was the podcast ever really on the base side of the graph.
I in in in high in hindsight, I genuinely
I genuinely think so.
I genuinely look back at like I genuinely look back at some of the people
and some of the discussions and shake my head like.
Kind of stupid, kind of dumb.
Like, yeah, there's a lot of there's a lot of embarrassing stuff
in the back catalog question.
No, no doubt, no doubt.
And that's that's recorded in my in my in my curve here.
Yeah, there you go.
That that one in it.
But in right in the middle of one hundred and one to one hundred and two
when that one little little blob it spikes up, that was that was Jeff's
Jeff's brief appearance.
A bright spot in the dark, glad to see him back in the in the documentary.
You know, it's good to have more Jeff content.
More Jeff.
I'm just I'm hungry for Jeff content.
I don't know where to find it.
I've been waiting for more jet.
I've my favorite PCP character.
I've been waiting to see him again and he makes his glorious return.
Yeah. Yeah, it's unfortunate that he hasn't been like producing anything
in the meantime.
He just fell off.
He just fell off the map is low.
He kind of fell off as far as I'm aware.
He low.
He low key kind of fell off and L and ratio.
Yeah.
I think we might have talked about this last episode,
but I I didn't really talk to him like at all.
Yeah. I mean, what would you say to him?
I think I'm not sure if we talked about this on the
on the commentary or was it last episode?
But yeah, I'm pretty sure he was just there to talk to Digi Bro
because there was they were like, oh, we're YouTubers.
We're anime YouTubers.
We're here to collaborate.
You definitely did hit on that on the on the podcast.
And I can't really I can't really begrudge him that.
It makes sense.
It makes sense why he would like want to be involved in the PCP
and why he was there.
But yeah, then then very swiftly outgrew the necessity of that connection.
Pretty pretty much.
And probably the horror of the event was like, all right, I'm a head out.
Whatever, I I mean.
I remember us having a good time.
I remember him seeming to have a good time.
We all we all got we all got hyped together for for Mad Bull and all that,
you know, good good times were had.
Cici has posted a OK.
I think I can I think I can guess what
what's going on with this graph here.
Yeah, I think this is a graph of all the time Sims, he was on the podcast.
I think so.
We got we got to get that boy on here more often.
Yeah, for sure.
Well, what a lad.
All right, next next voicemail.
Oh, did I did I skip?
OK, no, I posted this one here.
This one is called GPU versus CPU three, two, one, go.
Hey, is this a quick voicemail?
I want to differentiate between a CPU and a GPU for you real quick.
GPU isn't just a CPU that is dedicated to processing.
A lot of design goes into the architecture
to make sure that those processors are able to do the mathematical
operations that we commonly use in graphics processing faster.
So there is a bit of a difference between the two.
The GPU is optimized for those mathematical operations.
CPU is kind of, you know, more general use.
Yeah. And, you know, when when all when all gamers tavern
was saying they're like fundamentally the same,
that that was a very strange comment to me when he said that.
Really? Like, I feel, you know, really,
the big difference is like your CPU, right?
You've got these like a handful of beefy cores and on your your GPU,
it's like many, many cores that just are are hyper focused on specific things.
You know, and cores like CPU cores, like processing units.
OK, OK, like your your normal desktop CPU will have like four
or eight, maybe quad 16.
Yeah, you'll have like you'll have some number like that.
But in a video card, you'll have maybe a hundred or something,
you know, like a big number.
What did you what did you make of?
Because this was this was about that that that crypto guy,
a crypto voicemailer, said that certain certain cryptos
are like mined in a GPU.
They're like mined on the GPU instead of the CPU.
Yeah. Yeah.
So so because of the design of some of GPUs,
because of that design, they're like good at very specific types of hashing
operations, they can do certain instructions that allow them to hash things quickly.
And so, you know, depending on the design of your crypto,
like that could be that could be a faster way to mine it.
And that's why GPU mining is so big because they use these GPUs
that do this very specific type of operation very fast, you know,
that you just can't you can't do it fast on a CPU.
But there are there are other cryptos
that like do things that that CPUs do well, you know.
So it's just like however you want to do it.
I mean, all right.
But you know, it's reasonable.
It's all pretty cringe. Don't don't mine crypto.
Don't I don't know I was coming around.
I was coming around on this.
Oh, well, if it's GP, oh, well, if it's GPU base, then I mean.
Oh, well, let's change this change is everything.
Next voicemail is called GPU versus CPU volume two.
Can you believe it?
Three, three, two, one, go.
And I just realized I should add the context
that the reason that GPUs are loved by bit miners
so specifically is because it turns out a lot of the mathematics
involved with graphics rendering happens to also be really useful for bitcoin mining.
This is what you said.
So, yeah, that's why they're coveted.
And why, you know, CVUs aren't equally as coveted for this specific use space.
Yeah. I mean, just just the one further bit of clarity.
I think what's going on is like you're trying to guess the result.
You know, like you have you have you have you have a result.
You're trying to guess the sequence of like cryptographic hashing
that would result in that result.
You know what I mean? Yes. Yes.
And so the GPU is just optimized to do that specific math
really quickly. And so you can make a lot of guesses versus on a CPU
where you couldn't make as many guesses as fast.
So it would take like exponentially longer.
Oh, OK.
Because because each different core can be like guessing independently.
Yeah. And there's something like that.
And like down like down to the the hardware level,
the the processing core is just arranged in such a way
that it can do this type of math quickly.
You know, like this mathematical operation, whatever it is.
Sure. I think I think I think I more or less get it.
Next. Oh, wait.
Next voicemail is called.
Read the foundation series.
OK, I'm done. Please don't berate me.
Three, two, one, go.
Gibbs right here.
You can't just kill Hitler.
That's not going to work.
What you have to do is print a whole bunch of currency
that's right for the time period and then distribute it in a way
that using psycho history, you can analyze how the society will interact.
And then prevent World War Two.
Like these are large societal movements with lots of people.
OK. Killing one person won't necessarily get rid of that.
Yeah, true, I guess. True.
True. But I don't know.
I mean, if you look in the in the modern era,
like if you if you just prevent Donald Trump from existing,
do we stop the rise of fascism in America?
Probably not. Probably not.
I I do think, OK, I think that probably
fascism would have come into vogue with or without Hitler.
But I mean, the specific ways that like World War Two shook out
like Hitler was a very idiosyncratic guy and he and he he made decisions, right?
He was he made executive level decisions that had impacts.
It does seem like, you know, replacing with almost anybody
and the situation would be better, right?
Like the man himself is definitely a net negative.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't know, maybe maybe someone else would have been more competent
at accomplishing similar goals.
OK. I get you.
Maybe you could maybe you could have a someone who's more effective
at doing the same stuff.
Yeah, like maybe somebody else wouldn't have gotten involved in a war
in Russia, for example. Right, right, right.
So something like that.
You know, it's not it's not like the rest of Western Europe
and America wouldn't tolerate terrible treatment of specific cultural or ethnic
groups, like clearly that's just part of the culture over here.
So maybe you would have gone away with it.
Yeah, this there's a that that that Henry Kissinger book
that I still occasionally read famously famously.
You crack that book open, crack that book on the toilet, right?
Because I don't know how to read properly, according to Jim or whoever
from from who are these podcasts?
There's a there's a what am I what am I trying to say?
What were we talking about, Hitler?
Well, what point was I going to make?
I don't know, ethnic cleansing war crimes.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know where you were going with it.
I don't know. He just he describes.
He describes Hitler, Hitler's like strategy.
He was very like he was a very like he had a he had a conniving sort of
like he used like cultural guilt in the aftermath of like the Treaty of Versailles
and like World War One.
He sort of he sort of did this whole shtick where he sort of sort of
pretended to be like an underdog who just wanted, oh, I just want to
I just want to restore Germany.
I just you guys were so mean to us before we just we just want
what everybody else has.
And then as soon and ever and the the international
like the international public opinion was like, oh, give Germany a chance.
Like, oh, they're just come on.
We've been so haven't suffered enough and then as soon as soon as he got
as far as he could get with that, he just suddenly like flip the script.
I was like, OK, we're on the FM. OK, we're going.
We're going get Poland, get Switzerland, get it, get it, get it, get it.
And everyone and like immediately public, the world was like, oh, OK.
Oh, shit. Oh, fuck. Oh, jeez.
Oh, boy. Oh, jeez.
Boy is our face red. Yeah.
Yeah.
But probably other people would have maybe played it similarly.
Because we can't argue with results next.
But just just on the on the point of their their title,
I've always been interested in maybe reading like the old the old Asimov stuff,
like foundations, the the Asimov series.
Asimov. I've read a few of them.
I've read some of his shorts, but I've never read foundation.
I just wonder if it I wonder if it's still good.
I wonder if it is. Is it a novel?
I think it's a quite significant series.
Oh. Yeah.
I've read I've read some short stories of Asimovs, and that's that's about it.
Yeah, I was sort of scared off because it looked like it was a lot to read.
And I'm I am busy little guy.
I think I should get I think I should get more into reading books.
I've said this before.
I think I wish I was more into reading books.
I just don't know what books I want to read.
I would like to be more.
I would like to be more awash in interest in ideas
and people's good ideas from the past.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah, to be ensconced in valuable thoughts.
Someone someone recommended I someone recommended I read Foucault.
And I was like, you know, a lot of people who whose opinions I like online
reference Foucault, so maybe I should read some Foucault.
I don't know.
Next voicemail is called.
Rants more like cants three, two, one, go.
You guys were talking about Trixie and the rats and stuff,
and made me remember something on Patreon.
You can limit the number of people who can like subscribe to a tier.
Yeah.
So that means like one or two things.
Either one, Trixie just didn't do that and let ramps pile up.
Because I remember them being like months behind at times.
Yeah. I mean, why would you expect her to like plan it out and like have a real
put a rational idea of like how much that could be done, which is stupid.
Thinking you can do infinite rants or two.
They put a limit on it and then still couldn't keep up with the limit
that they set for themselves, even with like an entire month to do it.
Yeah, I guarantee that.
And I thought about that.
What it is, is she just thought that rants are easy.
I can do unlimited number of rants.
I could do a rant so easily.
It doesn't even matter.
It takes no time.
So there was no limit on the number of rants and then just like she just didn't do them.
For sure.
For sure. Yeah, of course.
I agree.
There's there's no I cannot imagine her like looking at that option and being like,
you know, I think I can probably I think there's a there's a limit on how much of this I can do.
And I'm going to set the limit right here.
I'm going to be like, I'm going to moderate this.
It's just just not it would be very out of character.
Yeah, it would be out of character.
So it's definitely the former.
Next one is called half a wave dash three, two, one, go.
So wave dashing.
There's this great video by a dude called awesome sauce.
A S U M S A U S.
And it's just like a quirk of the game's physics engine.
That was discovered even during development.
Sakura had noticed it.
Yeah.
And mentioned it in like some smash for him back in the day.
And basically nobody.
I know vaguely that it would just take off and become the way it is.
So Melee is just a big, giant mess of weird jank.
But I guess that's kind of what makes it so fucked up and awesome at the same time.
Yeah, I know.
I know about Melee.
I know it's it'd be like that.
Next one is an image, you know, just just just to stop for a second.
I I just hate that nobody will explain what wave dashing is.
All it is, I think, is like you jump and then you dash down into the ground
like while you're in the air, causing you to slide on the ground, right?
And you just keep doing that.
Like why will nobody just say that that's what it is?
It's like a mobility option.
Yeah. Yeah.
So instead, instead of using your little air glide thing to to move laterally,
you can you can push it down and then you slide and it lets you do it again immediately.
Like that. So it's a fast way to move.
Yeah. So you can you can do that.
You do these little hops and you slam into the ground.
It makes a little wave shape and you dash across the ground.
Like that's a why is nobody saying it?
Why is it like, oh, Sakurai discovered this secret?
It's like, I don't know.
It doesn't have to be like that.
You could just you just say what it is.
Yeah.
There's so much mistresses and built up around it for no reason.
I think. Yeah.
I think you're right.
Well, now.
I guess I didn't.
That's not that's not exactly what I was picturing, but sure.
OK.
This this picture is Thai PCP.
Forget this stinking podcast.
The Thai PCP is where it's at.
Is that? It's delicious.
It looks delicious. I think so.
Is that? Oh, it's like it's like barbecue.
Oh, yeah.
Is that a gun that he's got?
He's got he's got to get he's got to get dinner.
Hmm.
Man, he's on like it's on a cool rug.
He's out there and out there in a wood.
Looks good.
Wait, I watched.
This like this past week, I actually I watched a bunch of.
Videos from that guy, you know, Nick, Nick Robinson.
Ever heard?
I knew a guy in high school named Nick Robinson,
but I don't know if it's the same guy, probably not.
Uh, Nick, Nick Robinson,
he's sort of like a lost media YouTube guy.
He he did, um, he he saved
he saved the the lost McDonald's
training video game on the Nintendo DS.
Thank God. Yeah.
I watched a video of him.
OK, he had done one about a sort of famously weird commercial
for a collaboration between Pizza Hut
and no, no, Domino's Pizza and Hatsune Miku in Japan.
OK, I had seen I had seen that video a long time ago.
And then recently I watched one where he he met the guy who was in that commercial.
The guy who turned out to be he's like he was like the CEO of like
he was like the Japanese.
He was an American guy, but he was the CEO of like Domino's Japan.
And he has a whole here.
Here's here's the video.
I'll just link it.
He interviews him and there turns out there's a whole history of this guy
appearing in like he was in like Chinese and I think Thai or maybe Vietnamese
like pizza commercials.
He was he. Oh, OK.
He's like the he's the Asian pizza commercial.
Yeah, like he like he used to have a mustache
and he he says in the interview that like, yeah,
there was a time when I was the sink.
I was like one of like I was like the single most recognized
Westerner like in in Vietnam.
That's like I couldn't like I couldn't walk down the streets of Vietnam
without people being like, oh, Pizza Hut guy, Pizza Hut, Pizza Hut.
That's so great.
I forget what the slogan was.
They had some they had some some slogan in Vietnamese.
And he says like, yeah, they would yell that slogan at me on the street.
I had to shave my mustache because everyone
so people wouldn't recognize me or something.
Hey, it's good to be king.
It's it's a heart it's a heartwarming.
It was a heartwarming story.
That's really funny. Yeah, it was great.
He he he he he's got a quest to find this guy.
And then the guy's son, the guy's son,
like reaches out through Instagram to be like, oh, yeah, that guy's my dad.
I can like do you want me to introduce like I watch your YouTube channel?
You want to I can try to like get him to talk to you if you want.
And then they do charming.
OK, next voicemail.
I was seeing seeing a food commercial
in an Asian language just reminded me of that.
Next one is called News.
Oh, great. News from Wong Chan.
Yeah, it's only three seconds.
Three, two, one, go.
Next week. Very big news.
OK. Oh, next week.
Coming up, coming up. Can't wait.
Yeah. All right.
Next one is called Ben finally owns someone.
Listen to find out who.
Listen to find out whom. OK.
Three, two, one, go.
I think I see tweets from a stereo every now and then.
A lot of what I see is just kind of like passive aggressive,
like look at this new really stupid thing.
Maddox is doing what he is.
He's just embarrassing myself.
That is funny, but it does start to be like
it's sort of been the same story for what, like a year and a half.
I just feel like.
I like Dick. OK.
These are old. These are old clips as an old clip.
Good to hear everybody on good terms back then.
The good old days. Damn.
I mean, and damn, here we are, you know, years later.
And it's still.
Dick is still Dick is still doing the same stupid shit.
Is he? He's still he's still milking
every time, anytime Maddox does anything.
He's like, we got to do an episode about it.
I feel like Maddox completely fell off online,
but maybe I'm just I'm just not paying attention when you say.
Well, if you mean like he you mean like he disappeared or like I thought so.
Is he like online?
Is he he is?
Yeah, he he he makes YouTube videos still, or at least Jesus.
I mean, I might I might be out of date.
I know as of a few like post Dick show,
he was still making YouTube videos.
I think he he streams now.
Like I think I've seen Dick making fun of him,
making fun of his streamer stick before.
OK, yeah, I see.
He posted a video last month.
I took a child development test and the results won't shock you.
He got an A plus and a child got an F in the thumbnail.
Cool, man. I'm glad you developed amazing.
I love astounding results.
All right, good for Maddox.
Glad he's doing whatever he's doing, but actually fuck him.
I hate these guys.
He's he's doing something.
He sure is.
So and hey, he's getting more views than Yig Studio.
So he's got that going for him.
Something. Hey, yeah, hey, yeah, you know, someone.
Another another another dunk, another slam dunk.
Next. All right.
Next next voicemail is a YouTube.
Link. OK, saying goodbye.
What a wonderful world.
Why? Why? It's just a it's a guy playing that one.
Who's that?
I see trees of green.
Yeah, Woody Guthrie.
No, I don't think that's right.
It's not right.
Now, you're thinking of Woody Allen.
No, I'm thinking of Lou Reed.
That's a Lou Reed song. Is it? Yeah, that's right.
That's correct.
I was going to say Lou Bega.
It's not Lou. It's not Lou Bega, for sure.
A little bit of Monica in my life.
OK, terrible, terrible.
Next one is called it's called Fuck Trixie.
Three, two, one, go.
So I watched the.
Thing, the documentary thing.
Yeah, I haven't listened to the.
Commentary track yet.
Yeah, it's good.
Is how bad was the house?
Like how fucking gross were the house?
This was fine.
I need to shame.
Fucking little man, children, in the past, you can see it.
You can see how it is and, you know, draw your own conclusions from that.
We actually did does mention in the commentary,
the kitchen did get kind of gross at some point, like people were leaving
there like like take out, you know, bags and like food containers out.
The kitchen did get kind of dirty and gross for a bit.
Other than that, it was fine. It was a nice house.
Yeah. Next voicemail is called Bob Disgaea for Voice Grail for Bravery.
Three, two, one, go.
This is a controversial thing, but I wanted to be known.
Kyle, I'm a funny man. Better than Cringus Bagus.
Is this the same guy as the last voicemail?
Uh, hard, maybe? Possibly?
I could see the argument. Yeah, I wouldn't take offense if you like Kyle and Funny Man better than Cringus Bagus.
I think that's valid. If each got their charms.
Comes down to what you want out of a voicemail, I guess.
Next voicemail is called 300 Hype, three, two, one, go.
Hello, comrades. Nicola, I congratulate you on 300 episodes.
Thank you.
Nicola, I congratulate you by sending vodka.
However, Nicola, I need credit card number, overdress, and any social and search number.
Oh, sure.
Thank you, comrades.
Please use my credit card number because I finished churning my American Express blue business cash.
As soon as I get my US Bank business credit, you can have that.
We can start the process.
Nicola, if you could just wait one moment for Ben to get the new credit card.
We got to get the maximum churn here.
Yeah, if I'm not churning, then I'm just leaving money on the table.
We need those benefits. We need that cash back.
It's money on the table.
And when there's money on the table, you got to grab it.
You got to grab it.
I mean, if, for example, $16 were to show up in your PayPal, you can't return that.
You need to hold on to that money.
That $16 turned out to have come from Bob Disgaea.
Oh, that's funny.
He gave me permission.
He did send it for a reason.
I forget what the reason was, but it's okay.
The conditions were met.
Next one is called B.
Three, two, one, go.
Do you hate Trixie because she changed or because your perspective on her changed?
No, I think, you know, Trixie just fell off.
I think Trixie did fall off.
I think she's been bad since she switched to anime, tell you the truth.
It was a funny goof in the pony days.
Not that like the content was good, but it was a funny goof.
Yeah, I see.
And like the sort of genuine, sincere transition to like analyzing anime is where it just falls apart for me.
You know what?
I get that.
That makes sense.
I think, I mean, I don't like her because of the way she treated me.
So, I mean, like that's the difference.
Like her, she always had faults.
I think she, I think she's worse now.
I think she's become worse, but mostly it's just that she changed from being, you know, mostly a friend to being terrible to me personally.
And that's what it comes down to.
Yeah, I mean, I think that's pretty valid.
Yeah.
That's what it mainly comes down to for me.
Next one is Gibbs Pick.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey Gibb and Take, what is your profile picture?
Is it a self portrait?
Is it a drawing or something else?
Is it just a random person?
What's the deal?
What is it?
It looks really aesthetically pleasing to my big blue eye, but what is it?
I need to know please, please fill up now.
I think it's pretty clearly a self portrait.
Which profile picture?
I'm assuming the one on the tombstone, so like the purple and green one, like the one that the guy redrew earlier.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I mean, that would, that would make sense.
What else would it be?
I think that's, yeah, I think it's a self portrait dog.
We got like, how many, how many more we got?
We got like, we got four more.
Oh, is that all?
I could do a hundred more.
Let's go.
I'm sick of it.
I'm sick of this garbage.
Next, next one is called Help.
Three, two, one, go.
God, I can't stop having dreams about the PCP.
Oh, poor guy.
Sorry.
I have never.
I'm trying to think, I'm trying to think I've ever had a dream about, about like someone who's like,
content I watch, I like listen to online.
Maybe, I could believe that maybe at some point I had a dream that in some form or another featured Gabe and Tycho from Penny Arcade.
But I don't, I don't remember any like, vivid ones that I was like, I don't know, mate, mate.
I feel like it was anyone, it would probably be those guys, if anyone, but I don't, nothing, nothing could jumps to mind.
This is slightly unrelated, but is there, is there anything that you do that you feel like makes you dream,
reliably or more often?
Yes.
Well, well, um, you know, I'm not really on a regular schedule.
Sometimes my sleep schedule gets fucked up and when I sleep in the day and when it's light, I can, I have, I can have very vivid dreams when I'm doing that.
Okay.
That makes sense.
You're probably not sleeping as deeply, probably.
It makes sense.
Probably.
Yeah, sleeping, sleeping during the day or when it's light in the room, it makes me dream vividly.
Kind of, I think kind of the same root thing, but I find if I like drink a can of Monster shortly before bed, if I get a lot of caffeine, I dream more.
I dream more vividly.
Just don't really know.
It helps me sleep faster, you know.
I'm all amped up.
I noticed that I, honestly, I drink caffeine willy-nilly and sometimes I don't even, like, I usually try to stop drinking caffeine like a few hours before bed.
Yeah.
Sometimes I don't.
Sometimes I just, and like, whatever, oops, I drank caffeine, well, I gotta go to bed.
And usually it doesn't really have a problem for me or affect much.
Yeah, it does really keep me up, for sure.
But I do notice that I tend to dream more.
I haven't noticed that.
But I could, again, yeah, I could see that, like, interrupting your sleep depth, your REM cycles or whatever, would make sense in my imagination.
So anyway, to the voicemailer, don't drink a monster before bed, sleep at night, if you can.
Yeah.
Try to keep those dreams away.
Take some melatonin.
Yeah.
I take melatonin.
Try chloroform, perhaps.
No more those pesky PCP dreams.
Anything to stop the horror.
Next one is called Oblivion Fall.
Three, two, one, go.
How do we know his name isn't Oblivion Fall?
Hmm?
What?
Okay.
Well, cool.
I don't know.
That is his name.
What?
I don't understand.
I mean, like, the season?
What if the fall means the season and not, like, when you go from a high place to a low place?
Boah!
Oh!
Oh, fuck!
Next, okay, next one is called Slime Times Weekend Update Number Two.
Ooh, looking forward to it.
Yeah, from Prince Isolation.
Three, two, one, go.
Telling you again, one and all.
Welcome to the second installment of the Slime Times Weekend Update.
This week was the week of Valentine's Day, and right on cue, I've come to you with some lovey-dovey news.
The stay dead, known as Duckhead, and the killer, Violet, have gotten married at Slimes and Clips.
In response to the union, rowdy Liam and Killer Dog went on to get divorced in the same location that fine day.
After filing the paperwork, Liam attempted to push Killer Dog off the cliff and into the sea,
but her big bones made her too heavy to even budge.
Liam called her a fat bitch, upon which Killer Dog threw him off the edge, killing him.
She finally capped off the event by committing suicide, jumping into the slimy abyss herself.
It goes to show that in Neil Milwaukee, love doesn't come without its sharper edges.
I hope to see you next time, and remember, the Slime Time is the best time.
It's a fine day for a green wedding!
Woo!
That's great. Glad Prince is doing that.
If I could offer a note, I feel like there was a better pun there about that unfortunate turn for all Killer Dog and Liam, but we'll never know.
A better pun?
I don't know. I mean, going on with the love as its sharper edges or whatever it was.
I don't know. They're all on these cliffs and stuff. I'm sure there was something else.
There was something good there.
Love is blind, just like when you fall off a cliff.
No, they say love is blind, love is deaf, fall off a cliff to your death.
We'll workshop it.
Incidentally, Ben St. asked me last week whether or not I am aware that there used to be a genuine paper titled The Slime Times.
I am well aware. However, these days, people no longer really like to read, especially off of paper surfaces.
And the director of the paper mill committed a grisly suicide and now lives in a suicide estate there.
So I decided to take over the matter and present these things in a new medium that is sure to be hip and cool. Radio.
Old time radio.
Thank you Prince.
Thank you.
I got a, okay, listen to this. I got some slime news. I got some Slime Times news myself. I don't know what to do about this.
I feel like this is fine to talk about.
Marron Pan sent me, this was two days ago, and I have not responded because I don't really know what to make of it.
Marron Pan sent me a document with a few written statements regarding the arrest of killer Ungin, because apparently Ungin was botting.
And this was...
Yeah, I am loosely aware of that situation.
I sort of didn't really read the details, but I guess people were upset about some botting shenanigans that Ungin was playing and they arrested Ungin.
Not botting, alting, I think.
Alting, sorry, yeah.
Yeah, so Ungin had an alt splat cat that was in the rowdies and they think that splat cat was a spy and allowed Ungin to make some big kills and people are real upset about it.
That's the situation.
I thought it would be fine to just like, okay, while it was funny, we'll ban splat cat, splat cat's gone.
And Ungin was speared or put in jail for like a week, but the people want more. They want blood.
They want blood.
They're coming to Pontius Pilate. Oh, the flogging. The 39 lashes are not enough.
To keep you vultures happy, I shall flog him.
Well, it was funny because initially you have a duty crucify him.
Initially.
Crucify him, crucify him.
Ungin was jailed for just three days and everyone said, no, that's not nearly enough.
We've jailed fraud for a month for such crimes. It's got to be at least a week.
They put him in jail for a week and now it's like, not enough. We need more.
Yeah, Marin sent me a document with some written statements by some victims or by some witnesses to the crime.
I think he wanted me to like, I don't know, I think he wanted me to like weigh in and like say what I think should happen.
But I kind of feel like, I kind of feel like the people who are more active in the game should be the ones that have an opinion about that.
Like, I don't know. Whatever they feel is appropriate.
Yeah, I kind of agree. I feel like just a week or two in jail was fine, but people are upset. So I don't know.
I don't know how to rectify that.
Community service.
Yeah.
Wait, no, we have a, not the channel community service.
Yeah, understood.
Community service hours, right?
Yeah.
He's got to pick up trash in the coast line.
That was the last voicemail. We're done. Nightmare is over.
I know I said I could do 100 more, but I was lying. I'm glad it's over.
I know. That's okay. I know. I know.
Nobody likes voicemails. We're here out of help.
A sacred duty.
Well, any final thoughts on episode 302 of the Procrastinators podcast crack?
Well, I think we got to wrap it up by doing an intro.
We never did the intro.
Wait, before we, before we end with an intro, I want to say thanks for joining me today and preventing the nightmare that would have been another solo, Ben Kass.
Yeah.
You came in the last minute. Last minute, I was like, please, someone save me.
Anybody.
I'll take anyone. Please don't let this happen.
I was thrilled. I was thrilled that instead of some refuse, instead of some ragtag ragamuffin, it was my friend crack that wanted to join me.
Oh, it's been nice. Glad I could hang out. Thanks for putting out the distress beacon.
It was such distress.
All right. All right, everyone. What's up?
This has been the Procrastinators podcast slash the like button.
Smash the bell. Ring the bell.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Patreon.com slash Ben St.
Listen to the bonus commentary documentary.
Leave a comment down below.
What would you leave a voicemail about if you were stupid enough to leave a voicemail?
Let us know in the comments down below.
Right. Please, please let us know in the comments.
Do not actually leave the voicemail.
No, no, please.
It's better for, it's better for engagement if you just type out your stupid voicemail instead of writing it instead of speaking it.
Yeah. All right.
That's going to do it.
Good, good, good.
Bye.