Hello everyone and welcome to Your Nightmare. It's The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm the
best guy ever. And today we're joined by Ben and Tom. Hey. We're just one person. We're
one weird amalgamation of internet hobo. We did the fusion dance before the show. Hey guys.
It's happening. I'm here. Bombsoliver. And I got a lot of personal problems. I got a
lot of emotional weight. I'm going to need you guys to shoulder for me, right? I'm going
to need you guys to do a lot of the emotional lifting for me, if you know what I'm saying.
That emotional lifting can most efficiently be done. I can't really support myself, you
know what I'm saying. I agree. I can't really, kind of a burden on others, you know, is what
I'm going to be. That's what I strive for. You need an emotional spotter, so to speak.
Yeah. Kind of an emotional vampire. Yeah, yeah. If you wear a burden most of your life, you
probably have huge thighs. They're very muscular and able to do so. Or is it like the opposite,
where they're just worn down over time? You start with a certain amount of hit points,
and they just get ground down over time. It's not a load like the load of iron that one
might lift to become strong. It's more of a load of like extra DNA in your bloodstream
that might make your blood cells spherical or some weird shit, right? Do you think that
people with Down syndrome weigh more than people with that, because they have the extra
chromosome in all their DNA? I don't know. You mean the weight of the chromosome itself?
Well, like every cell in their fucking body, he's going to have tons of DNA strands. They
must. Is this the least logical thing ever said? I don't think so. Here's my counter
argument. What do you think is the weight of chromosomal matter as compared to average
material of a human body? Do you think that a chromosome is more or less dense than the
rest of a human body on average? I'm going to bet that it's more. Well, if a chromosome
is like one one hundredth of a cell's weight, and we're all made up of cells, and all our
cells are made up of trillions of cells, we're getting like 1% heavier, right? No, I'm saying
though, it's not about, I don't think the chromosome adds overall weight. I think the
chromosome must add proportional weight, right? I think you're going to, it's like buoyancy
problem. You got to find the chromosome's density, you know, and then find the additional
or subtraction as opposed to a comparable volume of otherwise presumably average human
matter. Well, okay, you're talking about buoyancy and whatnot, and that makes sense. What if
we could do it in a vacuum and just, okay, maybe just mass based on total mass is the
average mass of an individual with Down syndrome more than someone without. I would guess it's
more for all of the things being equal. That's the same question, that's the exact same question.
Maybe I just don't understand. Ben has a physics degree, we can't even argue about this. That's
true. That's too powerful for us. It's not a biology degree though, maybe that's a factor.
I'm trying to be right. He's doing physics calculations right now. I'm trying to be
right about this. The problem though is that I cannot find, I cannot find how dense is a
chromosome. Google's not helping me. Yeah, well, it's like, it's, there's no article on Wikipedia,
so I just, I'll never know the answer, I guess. Well, let's see, a chromosome, massive a chromosome.
Oh, okay, the average human chromosome contains about one times 10, 108, I'm going to assume
that's one times 10 to the eighth BP of DNA. If each base pair has a mass of about 660 Dalton,
Dalton's, and there are about two G of protein plus histones plus non-histones per gram of DNA,
how much is a chromosome way? What's the end, don't ask me the question, I want the answer. Oh my
god, this is like a fucking quiz I have to take. They're still, they're still working on this. We're
still trying to hammer out this answer even now. What the fuck is a Dalton? I've never heard of
a Dalton before, although that is that guy from Chrono Trigger who steals the, the bird, the
Silbird from you? I'm shocked, isn't Dalton like a guy from One Piece, I thought you would say? That's
also a guy in One Piece who turns into an ox, yes. He's the guy from, from Cherry, not Cherry Island.
Chromosomes, Dalton's, all the Dalton's change into things or steal things. It was Drum Island,
now renamed the Sakura Kingdom. Actually, you know what, it probably still is Drum Island that
just houses the Sakura Kingdom that was previously the Waffle Kingdom. So I wasn't completely off base.
Yeah, he's the guy, he's the, the cool guy, he's the, the cool warrior man. Yeah, he's all right.
He became king. Down syndrome is cool, confirmed by fiction. Hey, Monarchy,
yay or nay, as an institution. Dude, the Diviner and the Kings do. I'm leading a hard yay right now.
Like the, the absolute consolidation of power, dude. Yeah, pretty good.
Dab, dab on. Cool, look, I'm the king, not cool if I'm not the king. What if you were the one with
the power though, Ben? What if it was you who was king? Then I would. Yay or nay? Dab on it.
I'm gonna dab on that throne, boys, for all to see. And the sword is just a simulation of the
divine right of kings, for Ben and Munchy. Hey, you know, if you go to patreon.com
slash PCP Minecraft and you join the Minecraft server, you can walk your hot little feet on
south and take a right towards Dabbington. And you can see what I would imagine would be
Ben St. Throne Room, which is those, those dabbing statues leading up to someone's house. I forget
whose house that is, but it is a real place in a fictional world that is the PCP Minecraft server.
More like, more like. The Minecraft server is more real than real life.
I prefer to spend my time in the PCP Minecraft server as opposed to real life.
Oh, that's right. We're not gonna do it again for the holidays.
Like, I don't want to do more. I want to do more Minecraft. Guys, did you know Minecraft is a video
game that's enjoyed by millions? No. That doesn't sound right to me. I can't be true.
How long have, how, people have been being entertained by this software for years and
nobody told me? That's why I wasn't I invited. It just happened that way. Hey,
speaking of, of tedium of life dragging you down bit by bit towards the shallow grave that's
inevitable for us all, I had a tragic experience this week in multiple ways as you will hear now,
which was just so I had purchased. Actually, okay, I won't start the story there. I will
circle back to reveal this information that will now be a secret until we get there in the narrative,
which is, so I'm taking Sessho out for a walk, right? He seemed maybe a little sluggish,
maybe a little sleepy that day. I don't know what was going on, but he seemed fine. So I take him
out all of a sudden. This can't end well. He's projectile shitting, like you wouldn't believe,
like a steady stream of liquid shit out his ass. He's like propelling himself on the ice with
the rocket. Basically, basically, yes. It was with the force of a thousand suns. It was an
incredible sight to behold. And it was something I'm imagining like a I'm just I'm just imagining
that that starts happening. You grab the leash to stop him. But of course, you're on the ice as
well. You're all behind the laws of physics. You end up going like down a hill really fast,
you know, propelled by dog shit. It was a Christmas miracle. So that's happening, whatever. He took a
horrible, nasty liquid shit. I got over that. And then I went inside and I was I was wondering,
I was like, Michelle, Sessho just took like the weirdest shit I've never seen before. What is
happening here? We didn't know he seemed generally fine besides that. Anyway, like the day goes on
and then all of a sudden I realized, guys, I had bought my parents for Christmas, a lovely box of
chocolates, just the nicest little box of chocolates from Godiva. It was wonderful. I just suddenly
noticed under the chair, there is a ripped up piece of this box. And I'm thinking about how did this
get what so up with this? And in case you guys don't know, chocolate is lethal to dogs. This is
when I'm this is what's reported. They're like, I've been in the past, such as like gotten little
bits of chocolate. And I've rushed to like is my dog dead.com for like the chocolate.
The answer is always resounding. Yes. It's always yes. Thank God I didn't buy the dark
chocolates or he'd be dead where he stands today was milk chocolate, I guess, probably.
Anyway, obviously Sessho had he this is insane. We had it in a bag on top of a table there. I
guess there was a chair kind of nearby. He must have done some crazy parkour shit to get up there.
But he pulled out like the box of chocolates he ripped it open. He ate every single chocolate
that were individually wrapped in the box except for one that I guess his fat little body couldn't
reach. And I mean, this this this is the reason why the shit was weird. So we deduced this he was a
terrible person. Hopefully he regrets it. But then he's just shitting in the worst possible ways
all over the place. And there's like a room that he goes to shit in if we don't walk him fast enough.
And you know, sometimes that happens, whatever, we try to walk as best we can. And then I walk in
and there's like half on like the pad, we put down these puppy pads, whatever they'll piss his
shit on so he doesn't do it on the rug. It's like half on half off. There's just a spray of liquid
shit all over the fucking rug and this pad. It's just a true nightmare. The point of the story is
he ate all the chocolate. It was a it was a Christmas gift for my mother. Sessho ate it
callously. He shit everywhere. He almost killed himself. He would have been dead. And now he's
currently in gay baby jail where we have put him, which is to say he's in like the the shelter,
not the fucking shelter. He's in fucking daycare until we come get him after after we get back
from visiting the folks. And I have to go replace the fucking chocolates with something else for my
asshole mother. This is why you don't let your dog you made it clear to him that he is being
punished. His abandonment is a punishment. Yes, I think I think that's very clear. He definitely
knows very clear. Yeah. And one other factor here is just that I so so as everyone knows,
we've been trying to work to lose Sessho. Wait, he he succeeded. He I mean, he weighed like 28
pounds. His goal is like 25. He reached 25. And the last measurement he was like 24 and a half or
something. So like he's doing great. He's at his target weight, whatever. But I think that because
we've been feeding him so little, I think it's actually draw driven him into the kind of a
Garfield-esque diet week madness where he's just been he's been particularly energetic. He's been
freaking out when we give him food. Dude, maybe he's got maybe he's got keto energy. Maybe he's
achieved clarity, mental clarity. That's probably it. That's what he's accessing energy centers that
he didn't know he had, I think. And so he's been like, for example, we had a pumpkin. It was just
a pumpkin that we had on the shelf, you know, since Christmas, it was doing fine. And it was in range
of him for months. And only now, only yesterday, did he decide it was time to rip into that pumpkin
and eat the precious seeds and gunk inside. So I think based on these conclusions, I think that
we are it's time to up his food a little bit. So he'll stop being a monster. But still fuck you,
Sessho, for eating those expensive chocolates, your piece of shit. So there you go. I hate my dog.
I'll end his life. And that's it. This story would be not a problem for me at all. If he just
hadn't shit on the carpet. That's the one thing I can't forgive. Because we yes, we have like this
liquid cleaner thing that you put stuff into to try to clean. I cannot get all the shit out of
that carpet. I just can't do it. It's soaked in there. It'll never be clean again.
Good job, Sessho. You did it. Yeah. Yeah. That's why you don't let your dog play near his edge.
Those are clearly transferable skills. And he got the parkour abilities. And now he's just all over
the place. You gave him energy and you gave him the means. You fool. It was a mistake. It was a
mistake. So there's your Sessho update for the week, everybody. He's the worst. And he's paying
for it. Fascinating. More proof that pets are a mistake. Never get them.
He's a burden. I guess I had a fucking wacky adventure this week. Yeah.
It probably will suck, but whatever. What else are you listeners fucking doing besides listening
to my stupid ass bullshit? I'm already at the bottom of the podcast barrel. I might as well just go full.
So I had a date with a girl. Wow, incredible. It was weird. Unforgivable.
All right. So this is... I'm getting on the bus, right? I'm getting on the bus to go hang out
with Munchy, Kazzy, Kazzy's friend Dusty, and Munchy's friend Leif, who's in town for the week.
Right? This is the setup. And I'm on the bus and it's cold outside, but when it's cold, they fucking
blat... Okay, time for a tangent, guys. I get so fucking mad in the winter because they blast
the heat on public transit. So I will get on the bus and I will immediately start sweating, right?
I will... And like, I'm the only one. I don't know what the fuck is wrong with these other freaks.
Like, I get on the bus. It's like 80 fucking degrees on this bus. I'm sitting here in my full
coat. I have to take all of it off. I have to strip down on my fucking t-shirt and I'm still
too hot and I'm still sweating and everyone else is on the bus and they're fucking, like,
woolen hats and, like, gloves and, like, full-on winter regalia. And I don't understand. I don't
understand what the fuck is wrong with them, okay? It's the uniform of the time. They can't take it
off. It's, well, why aren't they fucking sweating bullets? Like, I am and would definitely be...
They're not. I'm looking at their faces and they're not glistening. I'm glistening. I'm
fucking perspiring. I'm stopping. Anyway... I know what you're talking about, though. It sucks.
Such is my situation today. On that day, rather, I get on the bus, I sit down,
I start sweating and this girl on the bus is like, hey, hold out a fucking napkin at me.
It's like, hey, and I'm like, oh, god, is it that obvious? And she's like, yeah. And I'm like,
all right, cool. So I fucking mop my sweatbrow. And I don't know. At least how you talk about, like,
oh, yeah, where do you live? You live around here? Yeah, cool, cool, cool. And so I get off at Harvard
Square and she's like, the bus takes us a little too far. We both kind of miss where we're going.
We're like, okay, let's walk back to the station. So we walk back to the station, talk about shit.
She's like, okay, hey, what's your number? And I'm like, nice, epic, dab. So we exchange numbers,
right? So I go and I meet up with the guy. I meet up with the boys, right? We go, we're walking
around Boston, we're having a great time. I forget what we did. Oh, yeah, we got Chinese food.
Doesn't matter. Dumplings. So I like, I checked my phone, and this girl called me,
and she left me a message, and she's like, hey, do you want to hang out right now? And I'm like,
we had concluded our business. We were just kind of fucking around. I think we were going to go
back to Kaz's apartment and just fuck around some more. But I get this call and I'm like,
uh, should I go? And everyone's like, oh, Ben, you should go. Oh, you should.
True love only happens once in a lifetime, Ben. Yes, it's a once in a lifetime chance.
Like, oh, if you miss this, you'll always wonder, you'll always wonder what could have been. And
I'm like, oh, God, whatever. All right, fuck, fucking fine. Goodbye. So I leave. And I go,
and she's little did Ben know they just wanted him to leave. I think so. I always suspected.
But now it's confirmed. And she's saying she's at the Starbucks. It takes me forever. I'm on the
train and they tell and we get an announcement of the train. It's like, um, sorry, everyone,
some lovely customer decided to run onto the tracks. So we're going to have to resolve that
situation before we move the train again. So I'm like, I'm like half an hour late. And I'm like, well,
oh, well, but she's still there. She moved next door. Anyway, so anyway, she's a fucking,
she's a fucking crazy person, right? Because the moral of the story is she's fucking
crazy person, probably some straight and this is not an insult, probably some strain of autism,
like a certain, a certain, a certain disregard and an unawareness of like human social convention
definitely shown through. Surely that was what attracted her to you. All of her words and deeds.
We need examples. We need concrete examples.
We need social security numbers, Ben. We need, you know, what was the one thing that like broke
the camel's back and you're like, Oh, no, this, this is clearly a deadly situation.
I mean, it wasn't that bad. I was mostly just kind of amused. But she, well, okay. She, she was like,
she was like super forward about like sex questions. Like, she was really just like,
okay, we're sitting, we're sitting at the bar. Like, we, like we go to, we go to a bar in Harvard
and she's just, we sit down and she's basically just like, hmm, so what are you into? And I'm like,
what do you, and she's like, interpret that however you want. Like Minecraft? And I'm like,
yeah, I don't, I was like, you know, I declined it. I declined to answer. It's too early for that.
Yeah. And she, but she's like, and she just like, like the bartender that, and she's just like,
oh, hey, are you, are you straight? And I'm like, yeah. And she's like, ah, dang, darn, I hate fucking
straight guys or whatever. Like what, like, like what a disaster. You know, I'm looking for,
I'm looking for a quad and I'm like, I'm looking for, for people to fill out my quad. It's got to
be two guys and two girls. And I'm like, dude, she's a fucking troll. She's trying to fill out her
quadrants over here. And I'm like, impressive. And I'm like, what are you, I don't know what a
quad is. Can you, can you back away the fuck up and explain to me what a quad is? Turns out it's
really simple. It's a four way polyamory thing. And it's got to be, and it's got to have, you got
to have the X in the middle. You know what I'm saying? I don't. Is this four or five people?
I'm lost now with this X fact. Four people, but you can't just, it's not like it's everyone,
everyone's dating everyone. Right? Okay. Yeah. It's not like, you know, one person's dating two,
and one person's just dating one, and one's dating the other three. No. It's a mutual,
mutually shared pool. Yes. Each of the four is dating all the other three. This is a fully
realized quad. So while she may perhaps have been attracted to all of them individually,
this would be a no go over relationship if in fact those others were not attracted
to each other. That would just kill it for her. Okay. All right. Sure. Sure. And her,
and it's not necessary for a quad, but her quad that she desires is two guys, two girls.
So, so she's just like, she just says this in like a totally like normal tone of voice,
as though she were describing the weather. Like she, the way you said it before, it sounds like,
like with the barkeep or whatever, just as like also there probably. She's like,
she's talking to the bartender. Okay. We're there. We're on a date. She like, she asks
the bartender for his number, like later, like a couple hours, like before, like before we leave.
She says like she's never, at some point, she has maybe like three drinks. At some point,
she's like, yeah, I've never been drunk. Yeah. One time I drank like 18 drinks. I've never,
I'd never got drunk. Nope. Never. Like, you know, total, probably biologically impossible.
This person is starting to sound a little delusional. She says she's never been drunk.
She drinks like three, then like we get out, we start waiting. I'm kind of tipsy, right?
We leave the place, I've had like five or six, we leave, we're calling an Uber,
she fails to call an Uber three times, maybe it's not her fault, whatever. I finally managed to get
one, like after like an hour of waiting, we get in the, in the car, she starts talking about how
she's got like low blood sugar or whatever, and like she needs a, she needs her medication. She
like she pukes out the fucking passenger side. She pukes, she does. She does, she does. Not drunk,
never been drunk. This is a blood sugar thing. Always needs blood sugar. So, and then, and then
I don't, I don't think I lost her phone. I don't think it was me. I think I gave her phone back
to, I, I hailed the Uber with her phone because mine was dead. I'm like very sure I gave it back
to her, but one way or another, we go back to her house and her phone is gone and she's like,
but you know what? Honestly, she was a good sport about that. I felt bad about it, whatever.
She lives at her parents house. We go into her fucking parents fucking like boomerass house.
I just, I have to use the bathroom. It's not that far from where I live. So I'm like,
I'm like tiptoeing around, you know, she's got a nice cat. I pet the cat and I'm like,
hey, okay, I'm going to, you know, I walk home from here all the time. So I'm going to go and
she's like, okay, yeah, okay. So anyway, it was very weird, very strange. Yeah, that's it. That's
the, there's no moral to the story. That's what happened. And this was on, and this was on like
a Tuesday. Imagine, imagine all that happening on a fucking Tuesday. Yeah, you know, I think our
listeners would perhaps appreciate that when you just kind of go out in the world and do not in
fact spend all day just playing Minecraft, but just like occasionally talk to people. You can
have kind of mini adventures. We want our audience to play Minecraft. It's always a mistake. You
should subscribe to the PCP Minecraft Patreon server so you can avoid this sort of bullshit.
Keep your autism contained. Don't go out into the world. Keep it on Minecraft where it belongs
for a nominal fee. Anyway, I haven't told this to anyone. Like, Kazy messaged me earlier in the
week and was like, how to go with that girl? And I didn't respond because I'm like...
Did true love win, Ben? The truth is boring. The truth is like lame. I don't know. I don't want to say it.
People want a salacious story or something. So obviously it's an amusing anecdote, which I was
happy to hear, but... That's why you just have to respond bad. And that's it. Just let their
imagination fill in the rest. Then they want to know the fucking details. It wasn't even like a
terrible time or anything. Just kind of like... That's weird. The ambiguity of the statement,
though, it creates a bit of intrigue that you can't do by yourself. Of course. That's the
point. The goal is to create... Well, you know, I watched a favorite movie of mine. Keep them
guessing. Make them think they're the crazy one. Gas clay. That's the way. That's the way.
And the movie, The Prestige, is a very valuable lesson in it. It's a good movie, whatever. It's
not Christopher Nolan. It's... No, it is. The guy who made The Dark Knight, whatever. It's
obviously really edgy and cool. But the main thing I get away from it is that there's this
moral that if you're a magician, people will hound you for your secrets, but the second they give
it to you, you are worthless. You're not cool anymore, and you can fucking die. So always hold
on to your secrets, guys. It keeps you interesting. Don't be overly forward and honest like I can be,
and it makes you boring. It's important. I don't have any secrets.
That's your secret. You need to keep secret. You have to keep it a secret that you have no secrets.
That too. Literally true. Literally true. It's helpful in making you seem like a cool guy.
People always like to think. I mean, Ben lives a mysterious, degenerate life. That could mean
anything on any given day. Oh, the mystery, the intrigue. What are the details?
You just got to keep your statements vague. Let people's imagination fill in the gaps
with the best possible interpretation of what you say, so you become cooler to them just by
their own projection. I've been thinking about reading Sam Harris's book, Lying, specifically,
because I've long been a believer that lying is a very immoral thing to do, and I want to do as
little of it as possible for a number of reasons. But with subjects like that, that's not a lie.
You're not doing anything that's a lie, but I wonder about the world.
Some would consider that a lie by omission. Well, a lie by omission, or even
is it immoral to create an air of mystique around yourself to make you seem cooler than you actually
are? I would suppose it depends on the purpose of the mystique. Well, it serves you like a practical
purpose of like making, like upping your like, I don't know, social capital. But like, if that's a
lie, then you're kind of misleading people sort of into being more interested in you than you deserve
I don't know. I suppose you could play it off that you just want to keep your personal information
to yourself, and whatever conjectures people come to based on your vague statements is their
own issue and not yours? I mean, that's true. And I mean, there's another factor here that's like,
like, let's just say that you decide it's immoral to like, pretend to be cooler than you are,
like in any small way, that you insist on being an open book, like overly so. The thing is, that
makes you stand out in a weird way compared to every other person on the planet. And now,
so you just like totally sunk your social capital in a way that like no one else does.
You become the girl we just talked about. Yeah, sort of, sort of, which is
you become the autism arbiter, and we just don't want that. Nobody wants that.
It was a tough game. It's a tough game to play. It's to be
Socrates had it down. Golden mean, my dudes, don't be too autistic, but be a little autistic.
Keep them on the edge of their seat. Mm hmm. Agreed. That's what we've learned today.
Life lessons going into the next decade audience. Remember these words.
Oh, hey, speaking of decades, I just I noticed a random factoid is I was scrolling back.
I was just thinking today at the end of this decade and year and whatnot about how old the
PCP was the first episode of the PCP was released. Today's the December 22nd was released December
23rd, 2015. So tomorrow is the PCP's fourth birthday since the first episode was posted.
Isn't that interesting? Oh, no. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, boy. This is all we have to show for four
years of labor. Indeed. God damn it. I was just tweeting about how I miss the old days. Now
everything sucks now. Oh, yeah. I guess you've got to revive horse cast is what you're saying.
Yeah, just how back in the pony days, it felt like we were all going somewhere.
Look, we all got to hit it hard. When pony life drops, we all have to pick up, you know,
back in the saddle quite literally. Back in the saddle. We'll call it that. That'll be the new
podcast. Exactly. I mean, maybe we should do it. I mean, we did it for the movie, right? Didn't we?
I have no problem with like a one, I mean, just for example, like a one time episode of us watching
like season, would it be gen five, gen six? I do it. Oh, I agree. Get Dr. Wolf on for the
guests for that episode. It'll be a good time. Let's get, I love Kim Possible a lot for the
guests. Dude, yes. Dude, we, okay, we should, we need to have more guests. It's fine. I agree.
It's fucked up. It's fucked up. I mean, look at the people who showed up for today's episode.
It's clear we need guests. It's clear we need, yeah. There's three degenerates. This is just
not going to cut it last. You know what? On the guest thing, I think that the guest format is just,
is a little easier for me to think about if we have like some kind of like thing that we're going
to discuss with them, even if it's just like their project or something. We should have a prepared
topic if we're bringing a guest in. I think that maybe for those, it makes sense, even if it's
something soft. Absolutely. But yeah. Well, I mean, it should be something relevant to the
guest, right? I agree. We should, we should give them a bit of an advantage. We should, we should
just ask them to suggest something, yeah? Or, or maybe there's just something like we could just
suggest like, hey, you know, fucking, you made a new game, sir, or you are a really cool guy. Let's
discuss your work. No, no, no. No one who actually has accomplished anything would ever want to be
on our podcast. We're going to have to, we're going to have to softball him. Okay. We're going to,
we're going to have to make suggestions like, hey, what do you think about climate change?
What should we tell us? Sure. Sure. What a riveting topic.
This, this, this I think is the strategy. I think we can all agree that having like more diverse
different voices on the episode is always good. They're sick of our shit. And I don't know. And
also I think that having topics of some kind is generally a good focusing point for us to just
have something to bounce off of. So yeah, we're just going to like lean into the meme and just
become Digi's anime podcast that everyone thinks this actually is. We should embrace the meme.
Okay, wait, don't tell anyone, don't tell anyone this, maybe future bonus episode,
maybe just an episode. We just call it Digi's anime podcast as the name of that episode.
I feel like the only people that think that are the people who have never actually listened to
it, right? Agreed. I mean, I agree. I agree. And that's, and that's why it's funny. You can just
tell immediately who has never listened to the show. They know it's much worse than that if they
wouldn't. In the process of like capturing new viewers in any mechanism, in any way, like that
would not be by like, oh, I'm now suddenly interested in this podcast or these, it'll be like, oh,
there's something cool about this show that's presumably not anime or Digi podcast related
specifically, probably, you know, as part of it perhaps, but we have something else to bring.
If this is Digi's anime podcast, he's like the CEO just stays in his office and does nothing
while all of us, the workers, toil away. Absorbing our surplus labor value, god damn it. Oh,
it's infuriating. That's not really the case, though. Nate's the only one, Nate's the only one
who skims anything off the top. And I mean, Nate actually does like actual work. But he does earn
his keep. I would argue that I am underpaid for the amount of time I put in, but hey, that's,
that's life, baby. You actually do like sort of make it all run.
Yeah. I pull the gears and levers. I turn the wheels of the world as it is. I am a god.
I'm about to shrug, motherfucker. I know big way. Do we have a potential guest list?
You know, I think we had some list of like a couple of people who we were thinking of inviting.
That should be our resolution for the new year is more guests on the PCP.
Make the podcast not shit. What? Yes. Let's not go crazy.
Yeah, that's true. That's asking a lot. I'm sure we could think of some people who we'd want to
have on the show. I mean, and I frankly, I know quite a few people. Look, even if these people
aren't like, I don't know, super famous wouldn't give us like tons of new viewership, just having
a new voice. I know people who would be interested. We should get Vivzi on. We should get Vivzi Pop on
to ask what she thinks about the knot. We should get Vivzi's dog on to hear, you know,
he's kind of sorry about it. Get old Fido on the show. You can just see it in her eyes that
she's thinking about the knot. I'm sorry. She's thinking about it. We can call the episode the
knot or tying the knot, perhaps. Can you, can you not? Can you not?
Holy shit, that's a great name for a show. Oh, like a furry podcast? Can you not? That would be
incredible. Damn. Did you just discover our new revenue stream? Copyright Tom, you can't have that.
New side stream. That's another great bonus episode idea. New side stream. It's all just
punching down at furries and other furries. Well, they've thoroughly earned it, I would say. Can you
not? I'm also writing Digi's anime podcast. It's called Can You Not? Digi's anime podcast.
Endorsed by Digibro. Send all complaints to Twitter at Digibro.
I'm sure he would enjoy that. Let me say, let me say, what else am I going to bring up? I think
there was one or two other things. Oh, hey, hey, I was curious. Oh, I made another big batch of
curry yesterday, guys. It's large. It looks beautiful. Oh, it is. It is so good. And you know,
I think you guys would be proud. Maybe I'll get a picture of this later. But there's a, when I went
to the store this time, I was bereft of curry for a full, I don't know, like month, and it made me
want to kill myself. So this time I bought, you know how they have those like wooden, or sorry,
not wooden, like the cardboard, like things that like the product sit in on the shelves of any
individual product? Yes. I just bought the whole thing. An entire one of those. Damn.
It had a full like 12 boxes of curry. And it was the best purchase. So curry comes in like a box,
right? And it comes in a box of like cubes that you that you break up and put in the stew.
That's right. That's right. So how many boxes did you get? I bought 12 individual boxes and each
box is like one. I mean, I use two for my things, but like I use a big pot and make like a lot of
it at a time. So it's probably like double the normal amount or whatever. So like 12, you know,
12 boxes. And I'll buy more. Oh, it's so good. It's my favorite food, probably right now. I make
it myself. It's delicious. It's pork, carrots. And I got to tell you, you know, yesterday, when I was
making it, Michelle was like, Nate, you those sweet potatoes look so gross, because I was chopping
up these incredibly old sweet potatoes. Oh, they were, well, I'll tell you why it's the fact,
it's the fact they were old and moldy and oozing liquid. And I was like, no, no, no, Michelle,
these are the best part. We can cut around. Okay, okay. We can cut around the mold. Oosing
liquid is a little far. It's a little too far. I was so willing to put those in because they're
so good. They're the best thing in the curry, the sweet potatoes, the yams. Oh my God, I love them
so much. And that bitch, Michelle, she robbed me. She was like, I will not eat that. And I was like,
well, this is why God invented divorce, I guess, for this very purpose. You should have just been
like, you're lost, bitch, and just made them anyways. What were you thinking? I mean, I'm with
you. I don't know. Like, for instance, downstairs in my fruit bowl, there is an overripe avocado.
And I am angry at whoever left it there, whoever purchased that avocado and didn't eat it, right?
Sure, I understand. I consider it a crime that has been dealt to me personally.
I do hate, now that I buy all my own food and shit, I do hate wasting it. It is very
annoying to see any food go to waste. I have one of my roommates works at a deli, basically. And so
I think that food does not carry quite the same intrinsic moral weight to him because he just
got it all the time and probably has to throw tons of it out in the course of his job.
It's become a crime.
So he's just got all this, he'll cook food and leave half of it in the fridge and just let it
go bad. And I'm over here like, just let me eat it. Just let me eat it all. God damn it.
We have to find an answer to the food question sometime because I hate this fucking, we throw
out so much food and it annoys me to no end. I never throw out food unless absolutely necessary.
I'll eat it, whatever the fuck it is. I don't know. Sometimes things are in the fridge too long
and they get gross. And I guess the worst thing I do is I'll buy a bunch of vegetables and then I
just won't cook with it. And then it's too old to cook with and then I throw it away.
That's the only thing I do.
Somebody got heavy cream, like two very small, very small containers of heavy,
heavy cream, like one cup containers, like really little. And they were in the fridge
because we had other heavy creams, so nobody opened them. And like it finally comes down
to, oh, we're done with that, that carton time to open up the new one. Oh, we got these two
little ones. And they were like a month overdue or over ex expiration. And like their contents
was just like solid, like a paste. Yeah, like it didn't even didn't smell or anything. It just
had sort of turned into sort of a-
You just got to stir it around. That's still good. That's still good.
Honestly, honestly, it seemed like maybe if I had like sweetened it or something,
I could have eaten it as like a custard. Like it didn't seem-
Oh, dear.
It didn't seem that nasty. That's how they make yogurt, right?
To be perfectly honest.
But I mean, if you want to have the authentic Sessho experience, and yeah, you would just
eat that in a custard, I guess.
I mean, okay, what is cheese? Like what is yogurt, right?
Exactly. It had become some kind of cheese.
I feel like there's more artistry to cheese than that.
No, there's fucking none. I don't know.
It's just a sun net. It's just nature taking its course.
It's just a complete accident that happens every single time.
Oh. I mean, you could argue that like the yogurt industry was like originally made,
like on the back of like spoiled food that they found a way to market, which I think is true.
But now I'm pretty into it. It's pretty good. It's pretty good stuff.
I like a gogurt on occasion.
I'm a pretty energetic guy. I'm a kid on the go.
I don't have time to fuck with a spoon.
I hope we get to that point.
I need something to keep my lunch cold. I gotta freeze my fucking yogurt.
Freeze my yogurt. Yeah, it's good cold or room temperature.
Hot or cold, you know?
I mean, I was going to say that I can't wait for like businessmen to be eating yogurt.
Sweet or savory.
It's the optimal food. But then I think about, I actually,
I don't know, in animes, but occasionally in like Japanese stuff,
you'll see like businessmen eating those like, like,
they're kind of like baby food pouches that you can get at convenience stores in Japan and stuff.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Fruit mash or whatever.
Yeah, yeah. Which is, it's good. It's good. I've had a couple of them.
I had one. I liked it.
For men on a mission, you just don't have time to consume.
But just like all individually packaged foods, it's too expensive. It's horseshit.
Well, that's true. I would never purchase it at my own volition.
The struggle.
I just want, I just want the world to adopt, like,
forget like a universal currency. I just want a universal food.
We all just agree. We give up food and we just eat,
slop, optimally, like, nutrition, slop.
I know it's going to be a little different for everybody.
Wait, did you get the email? Did you get the email?
Are you on the Hewlett mailing list?
Yes, I am. Hewlett 3.0.
Did you see Hewlett 3.0?
New Hewlett bars, that's right.
But they also said that powders, they've revised the formula.
They now have Hewlett version 3. Oh.
And I'm curious to try it.
What a fucking minute.
I just bought a bunch more version 2, goddammit.
So Hewlett has moved into the solid food market?
Ah, yes, they have.
What a bunch of bullshit.
What a betrayal of all its principles.
No, it's not.
We know that Hewlett, Hewlett's like single serving, like,
drinks and the single, and like, these bars,
they're obviously just a cater to the norm modes, right?
You're like, optimally efficient.
I have to wonder why they even bothered with the liquid in the first place.
If you're as real hooligan as they call you in the email,
you only buy the powder because it's the best price to performance ratio.
You get it, it lasts forever.
For us, the consumer, absolutely.
But like with those products, they're clearly trying
to just get like normal people to consume you.
I bought the bottles and I felt like I betrayed my own values.
So I'm like, this is too convenient and too expensive.
They're so convenient and they're so delicious.
I mean, I love the chocolate ones.
I think they're absolutely fantastic.
It's just, but it's just a mistake.
Guys, no, it's about Questbars.
It's all about Questbars.
Questbars are fantastic.
The problem is I lived off Questbars for like three weeks once
and I couldn't shit for the rest of my life to this day.
I just can't.
They've got low net carbs.
They do.
They're fantastic.
They taste great.
They do.
They're like candy.
They're like my candy.
The texture is actually pretty pleasant.
I have tried like, there's okay, there's only like two flavors.
I looked up online to see if I've missed any.
And there's only like two flavors of Questbar that I've never tried.
And I, if I ever see them in a store, oh my God.
Ben, what you need to do.
I mean, try the donut sprinkle.
The donut sprinkle is very...
Ben, what you need to do is you need to go on eBay
and you have to buy a lot of Questbars.
They'll sell them like a box of 50 for cheap prices,
like half the price of what they are in the store.
So like $3 a bar, which is bullshit, too expensive.
I told my parents.
I told my parents, instead of candy in my stocking,
please just fill it with Questbar.
I passed that along.
I told mom.
So she shouldn't have...
What is it?
Hold on, hold on.
The one that I haven't tried.
Okay.
Fucking mint chocolate chip.
I have never seen mint chocolate chip,
but that, it sounds incredible.
There's like one other, whatever.
It doesn't fucking matter.
Unironically, last year for a while,
like when I was living in the car
and when I was first moving with Digi for a little while,
I had nothing but Questbars and Hewlett
was all I was eating because I had...
Weird, because I've never seen them.
I only started seeing them around like a month or two ago.
Really?
And now suddenly I see them everywhere.
Yeah.
I saw them in a Target.
I've had them for at least two years,
or been aware of them for at least two years.
They're around.
They've just been on the down low, I guess.
But I'm assuming it's because Keto's gotten bigger,
that they have expanded their business for obvious reasons.
They are very Keto friendly.
Maybe, yeah.
I mean, that's why I like...
Two years ago, Keto was not nearly as big of a deal.
It's like Ben found out about it
and then the whole world was like listening to the PCP.
Yeah, I spread the word.
Of course, yeah.
I, you know, the two Keto dudes podcast
spread the word to me
and then I spread the word to everyone else.
The reason...
It's the circle of life.
I found out them not because they were Keto,
but my sister told me she can't have gluten
and they are gluten-free.
And so she's like, these are great bars to have
if you have a gluten allergy like I do.
And they just happened to be Keto on top of it,
which was a good bonus.
Although, I mean, they're Keto,
but not if you eat like 12 of them, which is what I do.
No, that's a bad call.
They're so fucking good.
How do you shit?
Like, they literally just destroy you.
Um, I don't know.
No.
Fuck it.
I guess you're just so Keto-powered now.
Your body's adapted.
Yeah, although I'm off Keto for the holidays
because like, fuck it.
Yeah, it's...
What am I not gonna eat?
Mashed potatoes?
Hey, Ben, I've heard in the grapevine
that your weight loss may have hit its goal
and that it's time to perhaps relax and stop losing weight.
Who the fuck told you that?
Any feedback?
Oh, I'll never tell.
I'll never tell.
It never quite hit the goal I was looking for.
I wanted to get down to like one...
I wanted to get down to 150,
and I never got below like 154.
Damn.
Okay, that's pretty impressive.
It like got close and then kind of stalled out.
Well, that's not bad.
I mean, within four pounds after all that,
I mean, that's what I got to was 173, I think,
which was pretty good.
Hey, that's pretty...
Yeah, that's all gone now though, unfortunately.
I'm gonna have to start again after the holidays.
I've probably gained a few pounds.
I'm probably up in like the low 160s right now.
I had like two slices of pizza and sugar cookies yesterday
while I was holiday shopping.
I felt like a monster.
I also ate pizza yesterday.
I was like, it's that time of year.
Yeah, I suppose it is.
You know what?
I eat pizza and I feel sick immediately afterwards.
I don't know why I do it.
But I always forget.
I always forget.
Like every time I have pizza and an hour later,
I feel like garbage.
I'm like, why don't we go like shit?
I'm like, me and Michelle, me and Michelle were out.
And I just saw like, Michelle, I haven't had pizza in so long.
Like I want a piece of pizza.
Michelle's like, no, Nate, you don't want to eat that.
I'm like, I want a piece of pizza.
So I got a piece from Whole Foods
from their like delicious looking pizza.
That's where I got yesterday too.
I felt so horrible.
Why would you get pizza from Whole Foods?
I mean, it's...
Oh, because I was...
I went to see a movie and it was right next door.
And I was hungry.
I mean, we go to Whole Foods.
It's okay, I was right there.
I ordered, I ordered from fucking Domino's.
I got a $5.99 chicken bacon ranch sauce for dipping.
Classic American.
But I mean, I ate it and I just felt horrible.
It feels good while you're eating.
I mean, this is why we do it, obviously.
The salt and the grease and blah, blah, blah.
But I...
I thought I would feel that way, but I didn't.
I felt fine and I'm actually kind of in a pleasant way,
sort of looking forward to when I go back on keto.
Like when I start dieting again.
I'm looking forward to the sensation of like,
I can feel that I'm losing weight
and I can feel that I'm like, I'm not as heavy as I was.
Yeah, that initial like,
that initial couple pounds of weight loss...
I need to buy a scale because the scale is what keeps me going.
It's so important, Tom.
It's gonna feel good.
So important to have a scale.
You gotta get that.
That's a priority for weight loss.
Yeah, because like that's when you...
You're just afraid because I know I'm gonna step on it.
I'm gonna be like 25 pounds heavier than it was like last year.
And I'm like, well...
Wait, say it to Tom.
You're gonna get a scale.
You'll do it, right?
I will do it.
I will go get it before the end of the year resolution.
Did I mention that my roommate, same one that works at the deli,
he got a new scale because we had kind of an old craft.
When he got a new one, that was like, it had like,
it had a computer inside.
Oh, I think you told the story when like,
you used it without permission and like,
he got a notification on his phone or something.
I mean, that's not...
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I mean, it's not like he was like,
I mean, how much do you don't need permission
to fucking step on a scale?
But yeah, he would get like, he would get alerts on his phone
telling him how much I weighed because I looked like you used your scale.
It was like hooked to an app on his phone.
Dude, technology is too powerful now.
This is just, you don't...
There's some boundaries you just can't cross.
And like, the relationship between a man and his scale is just sacrosanct.
You can't do this.
Or can you?
I guess you can now.
But like, that's the whole point.
We've gone too far.
Yeah, well, we're making everything like, it's like in the,
like in Metal Gear Solid 4,
all weapons are like, like individually DNA tagged.
So like, every machine is like,
for use by a specific human ID and no one else.
Our scales, this is kind of similar to what's going on with the scale sort of.
I mean, it's plugged into like a system here
that's like expecting it to only be used by him.
Then we'll find a way to spoof DNA,
and then people get framed for crimes all the time.
And there'll be a whole other industry.
We're going to have to unravel.
Everything is shit.
And we do need to return to a mythologized past
wherein our people was, were great.
Do you have any,
do you have any sympathies for the anarcho-primitivist movement, Ben?
Absolutely disgusting.
Oh, really?
Absolutely vile and pitiful.
I couldn't agree more.
Pitiful weak cowards.
You know, because I remember a while ago,
I made fun of this guy who I'm actually quite fond of,
but he is a boomer.
And he has some silly opinions in my opinion.
This guy, ephemeral rift, ASMR guy on YouTube, whatever.
I like him a lot, but...
Is he the guy who did the mob boss ASMR?
That is based Tirar A. Duweyo, aka Lobster Boy.
No, that is a separate guy.
Both are heroes in very different ways.
Tirar is from Ohio though,
and maybe one day I'll meet up with that guy.
That'd be pretty sick.
But this is a different guy,
and ephemeral rift just...
He is a big anarcho-primitivist guy.
He's like, man, it's just fucked up.
We live in a society, man.
We should be living in the trees, man.
That's what humanity was supposed to be.
Man, that's fucking insane.
That is what a coward is crazy.
I mean, we know he's dumb.
Obviously, he's kind of like...
I know that most of humanity would die.
It's just...
I have sympathy that it feels like we're monkeys
in the wrong environment now,
which I mean, you know, kind of true.
Kind of true.
But you can't go back without killing everybody,
so I don't know what the plan is there.
I mean, that's fucking dumb.
Broader shoulder is not a lighter load, you coward.
Yes, I couldn't agree more.
I couldn't agree more.
Like...
I don't know.
I mean, so he doesn't actually think that we need to do it.
He's just kind of jerking himself off like,
boy, wouldn't it be great if we didn't have society?
I think he would agree with that largely, yeah.
As someone who creates ASMR content on YouTube,
I would assume he's not super sold on the whole idea.
I mean, he totally acknowledged...
He's done some vlogs where he's like,
yeah, I totally acknowledge I do stuff on YouTube.
I mean, he's one of these adult men
who started doing YouTube who has a job
and he does other things, so he doesn't need YouTube.
So that's a little different from our generation
of desperate e-whores trying to make it,
such as myself, you know?
Yeah, we're all guilty.
Too close to home, man.
In any case, very, very silly in my head.
Now, Lobster Boy, on the other hand,
is an anarcho-capitalist hero who will stop at nothing
to seize the means of control over the world and...
Lobster Boy.
Check out Lobster Boy ASMR, everybody,
if you want a bad time.
I watch a lot of Terrar.
I watch almost anything he makes.
Oh, Terrar, DeGuello.
It took me like a year to figure out how to pronounce his name,
but I did it eventually and...
Degeo?
It's Dewey-o.
Dewey-o.
Terrar A. Dewey-o, which is like...
The lore behind this guy is deep.
Like, that is...
All these older guys...
I follow a lot of older guys on YouTube.
And they all have very...
Kind of like, larping stories about themselves,
but it's still fun to hear and they're mostly true.
And he was given this nickname by a South American friend,
a woman of his.
What, Lobster Boy?
Well, I'm talking about the man who runs the channel,
Terrar A. Dewey.
Lobster Boy is, to clarify, a character,
a horrible character on his channel.
I mean, this is the man who was shouted out by PewDiePie
for doing Pickle Rick ASMR back in the day.
So, you know, he's really...
That's amazing.
He's really hitting the ground running here.
He's got a lot going on.
He's a cool guy, though.
I like him a lot.
But, in any case...
Hey, speaking of the ASMR grind,
you know, ASMR content creation is interesting
and it'll lead into what I was going to say,
which is that like, with those guys,
you can do ASMR on anything.
Like, find a new box to tap.
Boom.
You got your next content.
For your next hour-long video of ASMR,
put an ad at the beginning and the end,
not in the middle.
That is a sin in the ASMR world.
Never do it.
And boom.
And you just keep doing that for years
and it seems to just generally work out pretty well.
Obviously, it's a bit violent.
And the swore slime ASMR when?
I don't know about...
I mean, it generally work out pretty well.
I mean, for the like...
Yeah, you're right.
Dozen guys who are famous for it.
You are correct, Ben.
I am the human.
Dozen guys and thousands of women.
It's a, you know, I feel a certain sense of envy, I suppose,
with like...
A lot of those guys do write scripts.
They'll come up with like characters and do things.
Others do not.
They just kind of do whatever.
But, you know, as opposed to people who are making more
complicated content or whatever.
I'm not even trying to say I'm good or anything.
But here's what I was going to say.
I just...
I am envious of how some of those guys are able to just churn it out
without having to do too much.
But here's what I was going to say.
So I'm leaving tomorrow for like four days away
off the grid or whatever.
I'm still going to be working on some stuff all the way.
But it's, you know, it's like a little mini-vacation.
First kind of dedicated one I've taken in quite a few months.
Except when I visited Digi, to be fair,
that we did actually work while I was there.
Whatever, it doesn't matter.
I feel like I could have stayed at the folks place
for longer.
But I really didn't want to.
Because I just don't want to be away from my computer.
Because I want to be working on things.
Because I have so much desire to make shit.
Are you there now?
No, I'm still in my place.
I'm leaving tomorrow to go.
You're leaving tomorrow?
Okay.
I'll probably get there.
I'm probably going to get there, like,
early on the day of the Eve.
Okay, that's cool.
That's cool.
That's my plan at the moment, anyway.
Sounds good.
I mean, yeah, Michelle and I'll be settling in,
then probably, the day before.
So, like, I was wondering if you guys
feel a similar sense of, like, I suppose
it's not really a guilt.
I mean, we've talked about this for a long time.
I know Jesse's talked about this a lot.
About, like, the pressure to always be working,
that I like, and I don't really want
to not ever be working when I can.
But, I don't know, do you guys,
how do you feel about, like, taking vacations
from your online content creation?
To fill you with nerves?
I don't really feel...
It always feels like a sin.
I don't really feel like anything that I do is work, per se.
I only do things.
Well, with a couple exceptions,
I basically only do things that I feel like doing.
Fair enough.
Like, I don't, like, the poo videos felt like work.
That was me, like, starting a project to be like,
how's this going to pan out?
And I felt like work.
I chugged through it.
Didn't get any, didn't yield much.
It's worth trying.
Those are good.
I enjoyed them.
But, like, slime and punishments,
what I work on mostly now, at this point,
although not for the last couple days.
And that doesn't feel like work.
Yeah, that's cool.
That's cool.
So, I don't know.
I guess I don't feel the same way.
For me, everything is an uphill battle.
Like, left to my own devices, doing what feels good,
I would become 300 pounds and just play video games
and watch anime.
So, everything that it's not that is, like,
an active, like, brain-busting effort.
You know, the funny thing about that, for me,
is that, like, you know, for example,
maybe, I don't know, you guys probably relate to this.
It's like, or, you know, in some form or another.
Like, the weirdest thing is that, like,
I have kind of been having tough, tough time,
making time specifically to get to the gym
for the last couple of months.
Like, I've been going, you know, maybe, like,
once every week, once every two weeks sometimes,
which is not great.
Obviously, that's less than it should be.
But, like, you know, I'm finding time to squeeze it in.
But, like, I have trouble doing it.
I find that the times that I most exercise
is when I'm on vacation.
Because then I'm finally not,
I don't have this thing looming over my head of,
Nate, you could be working on your project right now.
Like, you need to blah, blah, blah, do that.
It's when I am, like, set free.
That's when I most, like, go running and do my lifts
and hit the gym and stuff.
When I've, like, got free time to do that stuff.
I don't know.
I mean, what I did for the gym is I just made it
the priority number one.
Like, as soon as I woke up three times a week,
Monday, Wednesday, Friday, I would go to the gym.
Like, it was more important than work,
it was more important than anything.
Like, that was, because it, for me,
I only went for, like, you know, 45 minutes to an hour.
So, it was not a huge time constraint.
So, like, getting it out of the way early
meant the rest of the day was open to do whatever I wanted.
I absolutely should do that.
But, like, the mental block I keep hitting with that,
I know that the first thing I should do
is wake up and go to the gym.
I feel bad doing that.
And, like, I feel guilty making it priority number one.
Look, I know that a lot of this is, like,
rationalization and it's me being stupid
and I should just do it.
Absolutely true.
And there's no excuse to not do it,
blah, blah, blah, all that stuff.
But, like, when I, the hurdle I encounter is just, like,
I want to get up and get straight to work
on, like, editing and videos and stuff.
And, like, to instead go to the gym,
I just feel such a guilt and, like, a fear
that I'm, like, pushing back, like,
two more hours into the day is when I start editing.
Here's how, because I had that feeling a lot of the time too,
especially at the beginning, before it became habitual.
Right.
The way I justified it was, like, if I get up,
like, I want to go to the gym
because I know it's the right thing to do.
If I don't and I start working,
my work will be tainted by my conflicted mind
going back and forth between, like,
should I go to the gym versus continuing to work?
Whereas if I just do it, I will have mental clarity
and the work will be better because I will no longer be
caught between two brain spaces.
Okay, I understand realizing that in principle,
but there's no fucking way that you actually act rationally,
right?
You're right, Ben.
You're right.
That's my, like, that's me, like, oh, don't you know,
what, just get your homework done early
so that then you won't be, you can relax afterwards
and you'll be happy.
Like, fuck no, I can't do that.
No, I'm gonna fucking want it all night,
but I don't want to fucking do it.
Well, that's mean, Tom.
Six months straight.
Yeah, I'm gonna ruin my whole day.
Once you get into the groove, and I'm not trying to diminish it,
because I was like this too, it, like, after,
let's just say, if you do it for three months,
if you're able to force yourself, then it's a habit.
And then, like, it's basically easy at that point on,
because you've made it just part of your routine.
So that's the place everybody should be aiming to get.
But I have, I have solutions.
A lot of the time these days, because I have this fear
of, like, not doing my work, so I don't go to the gym as much,
what I will do is I'll just say, okay, Michelle,
I know you don't give a shit, which she doesn't.
I'm gonna swear to you, Michelle,
that I will go to the gym tomorrow.
And she's like, I don't care, but okay.
And that's exactly what happens.
And then, once I have someone else involved,
like, holding me to a count, then I actually do it.
Yeah.
That's all it is.
She's really gonna hold your nose for the crying stuff.
It's not about her.
You just gotta tweet it.
You just gotta tweet the night before.
I'm going to the gym tomorrow.
And if you don't, all of your followers
will just blast you for the rest of your life.
If I had, like, a personal Nate account, I would do that.
Since I only basically-
You fucking do.
That's what Twitter is.
I mean, I don't really think of it.
Do you not read it like that?
I do retweet memes and stuff, but I don't know.
Like, I kind of make something of an effort
to make it, like, not particularly personal.
I don't know.
That's just my, how I've been handling it.
Like, maybe I will make, like, a personal Twitter
that's for, like, personal stuff.
Put it in your Discord server or something.
Have all the people who give you money
to know that you are a failure if you don't do it.
You know, I'm sympathetic to this,
and I get your point on it.
It's fair to have the people hold you to a count.
I feel a little bit weird getting, like,
my personal things involved with, like, the people at large.
But I'll tell you what I would do.
Perhaps either of you guys would want to enter
in some sort of illicit demonic pact right now
when it comes to, perhaps for just the first month
of the new year coming up, to swear to,
I mean, my goal, I want to work out three times a week.
And that's what I would hold my,
that's what I would want to hold myself to.
What do you think, Tom, you want to do that?
I mean, I can hold you to a count.
I can't do any working out,
but I will, like, try and hardcore get back on my diet,
and we can hold each other accountable for that.
Okay.
Check in and make sure you're not fucking up.
I will get, I will, I am willing to do that for a diet.
For diets?
Okay, okay.
Working out.
Me and, me and Kazy were working out all the time,
but now she's, like, busy with schools.
And I don't have a gym buddy anymore,
so now I can't bench.
I can't, I can't fucking squat by myself.
I'll fucking die.
You can squat by yourself.
I mean, benching seems more dangerous to me.
That I always worry about executing.
I'll fucking die.
You're trying to kill me.
You just shrug the bar off if you're squatting.
What's the danger there?
This is an assassination attempt.
I mean, I, I never benched with a buddy,
which I know is irresponsible,
and even when I'm alone in the gym,
I'm just willing to roll the dice,
because it's too embarrassing to, like,
use something else.
I'm just willing to die if it comes to it
to avoid any kind of social interaction.
Yeah, but, I mean, there's other people there, right?
Not every time,
because sometimes I work out really late,
and I'm the only person there.
Even if someone's not behind you
with their hands under the bar, like,
light weight, light weight, light weight, light weight,
ain't nothing but a peanut.
If the bar ain't bendin', you just pretendin'.
Even if you're not doing that,
like, as long as someone's there,
you won't die,
because they'll hear you going,
you know, that's the thing.
The bar on your throat.
I haven't thoroughly investigated it.
And they whip out their phones
and record your death instead of helping you.
I'm kind of banking on,
like, because it has happened to me before
that I've been benching back in the day
when I have gone for that extra rep,
and it has been a mistake.
And, well, I mean,
it wouldn't be a mistake if someone was spotting,
but I wasn't able to do it,
and thus I almost died.
But then there's people around who can, you know,
pull it off.
I'm just banking that I'll probably
be able to shrug it off,
or, you know, I don't know.
I'll probably survive, right?
I mean, nobody dies.
Your problem is, like, you're getting older,
and your body will start to break down,
and those gambits will not pay off anymore.
It just, I mean, it happens to everyone.
I mean, you're right.
You gotta pay the piper at some point.
I'm not even doing a thing about, like,
I'm strong enough.
You're livin' on borrowed time now.
I've already been in my life,
in positions where I easily could've died
while lifting.
If there wasn't people to save me.
But then again, like, I wasn't pushed
all the way to the limit, though.
Like, we're talking about situations
where I'm benching.
I don't know.
This is probably back in the day,
going for, like, a round two plate or so,
which was, like, my peak ever,
and I was trying to do it.
I'm below that now, whatever.
And I'm doin' a bench,
and I go for that last rep,
and you're lying on your back.
You got the bar hovering over your face,
and you go down.
You bring it down to, like, onto your chest,
and then you try to push up,
and it will not go,
because you just ran out of steam.
You can't do it.
So, what happens naturally
is it kind of sags back onto your chest,
and it'll naturally kind of roll,
it'll try to roll towards your neck.
And that's where it just will naturally go.
And if it gets there,
it'll crush your throat,
and you'll probably die.
But, like, maybe you could, like,
swing the bar to, like, the right,
and get the thing kind of pushed up.
If you just push,
you're pushing now, like, half the weight,
kind of to the side.
Hopefully it doesn't hit anyone.
I assume things like that will happen
if I'm in that situation.
I've never tried it,
because, obviously, it would be embarrassing.
And you might be out of strength at that point.
I might die.
I could die.
Who knows?
This sounds like a terrible plan.
It is a terrible plan.
I'm just throwing that out there.
But what's the alternative?
Socialize?
Ask for a spotter every time?
No, the plan is just don't
push yourself farther than you can.
That's a pussy plan, Tom.
Or just don't work out alone.
Just work out a place where someone could save you
if you were on lethal scenario.
The easy way around this is just,
I have a 24-hour gym,
but just work out when there's at least one person there,
because if you're going to die,
that person will save you.
And you'll probably make a friend.
So won't that be nice?
I look forward to it.
Indeed.
So speaking of Twitter.
Wait, so are we agreed?
Are we entering the Sacred Pact?
I'm done.
I'm entering the Pact.
I'm entering the Pact right now.
With regards to diet, yeah.
Okay, so you guys are agreeing to stick to your diet.
Let's just make this a time-bound thing
for the month of January.
A month is easy.
30 days, no problem.
Maybe starting now until the end of January.
Or so, I mean, I won't be able to work out.
New years, new years.
Okay, starting new years through the month of January.
We three warriors, we three kings are agreeing to this.
You guys stick to your diet.
I will work out three times a week.
This was my plan already was to get back to diet.
It's not only us.
We are now beholden for the entire PCP audience.
That's true.
That's able to hear this.
Goddamn.
And if we can make it through this month,
that's a long way to setting the routine,
which is exactly what I want to do.
If you can make it through a month,
it's basically, you're basically set.
You're on cruise control.
Yeah, absolutely.
So, hey folks, if you want to also,
perhaps post in the comments below,
something that you want other people
to hold you to account for.
Perhaps you'd find that useful.
I don't know, up to you.
It's not a bad idea.
There it is.
This is the healthy bro pact.
So it shall be, so it shall be.
Three times a week for me, as soon as possible.
So, I guess speaking of keeping yourself healthy,
I think I want to back off from Twitter.
I hate it.
I hate Twitter so much.
It's so bad and so terrible.
I agree.
I've said multiple times that Twitter
is a net negative for society.
This is why, I think Ben,
I think we probably feel similarly.
This is why I just made a conscious choice
to just make it like an anime girl image thing for me.
That's like all it is.
And also, my friends will tweet.
And even they fuck it up sometimes.
I don't know, it's like, it's the platform
that I have like the most, you know,
I got like 5k followers, almost 6k.
Yeah.
Making a tweet is not an effort
like making a video or something.
I just, you know, I want to talk,
I want to say stuff and have people hear it.
That's like, that's where I go.
I don't like it.
Fuck you, don't like it.
I was on there, I saw the fucking J.K. Rowling.
J.K. Rowling getting all turfy on Twitter.
And I was like, I'm fucking upset about this.
And I say so on Twitter and everyone hates me.
The long story short, everybody hates me.
Lose 20 people unsubscribed from me.
You're wading into tumultuous waters
every time you talk about those kinds of things.
And I'm not saying you shouldn't,
I'm just saying that kind of comes, unfortunately,
with the territory.
Is that when you plant your flag on something,
you're going to get blowback from people who destroy you.
That's what Twitter's for.
Is that not what I don't understand?
Well, all I'm saying is, all I'm saying is,
that's what Twitter's for.
I'm using it as intended.
The results are horrible and make me feel bad.
That's why Twitter, as intended, is a bad platform,
which is why I never make political tweets ever.
That's what I was, look, I just think that Twitter
and a lot of the things, I just think this,
it's not a fault of anyone.
This wasn't intended.
But I think it's just as a result
of the world that we're in now, the digital age,
just like the most contentious arguments
and people's biggest disagreements
are the things that get propagated.
And just as a result, it just makes everybody more mad
and more sad and stuff.
Even though, I think I was saying last time,
I think we all agree on most stuff,
but that's just not what gets discussed.
No, I don't think, I used to believe that.
I don't think so anymore.
Okay, maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I mean, that's what Twitter does, though.
It skews your perspective.
Like, what's that game or that video or whatever
that shows like the anger machine?
It's like a game where one person-
Is it a CGP gray video that's like the meme?
Like the anger meme?
I think I'm actually thinking of a video game
that was designed to simulate like how anger spreads
or something.
The one of like the crowds watching the news and like-
Yes, yes, exactly.
Yeah, I know the one you're-
I actually, I landed on that GameDev's Patreon page
the other day, like totally randomly.
Yeah.
Um, I don't know why.
Do you have a name or the name of the game or anything?
Oh, god.
I'm gonna Google it.
Oh, wait, it's-
Ignored you were talking about that.
She has another game called like Adventures in Anxiety, I think.
Oh, I know that game.
I think it's by the same person.
Really?
I didn't know they made anything else.
Yeah, yeah.
They had a, Nicky Case is the developer and the old game
that you're talking about is, uh, ooh, ah, ooh, what the fuck?
I'm looking at her, oh, uh, I'm scrolling down her page.
She's got a lot of cool games here, looking real good, but I don't-
Oh, uh, what we have, we become what we behold.
Here it is.
Yes, found it.
That's the one, that's the one.
Here, I will, I will link it in the show notes for everybody.
I think you can play it right here.
Yeah, yeah, you can.
It takes five minutes.
I love those games.
Yeah.
So, I mean, this, uh, yeah, it's pretty much,
this is the phenomenon that I think social media propagates to some degree.
And, uh, that's-
It's tough.
It does.
Tough.
It definitely does that.
I don't know.
I don't like it.
That's it?
I mean, yeah.
Man, I'm upset.
I'm, makes me upset and I don't want to do it anymore.
And, and you know, the other thing is, I think that-
And I guess it's just my good fortune that I've come to the point in slime and punishment
where I have to take a break to make the next big update.
So, I don't really have to post very much there anymore.
So, maybe I won't.
That's fair enough.
And, uh, it, it makes me think back to the curious case of the Spoony One.
How he just, I, I don't know his full story.
I don't know everything about it, but like, you can, and I feel this myself.
Like, you see, there's like a sliding scale about like someone starts off being like a YouTuber.
Then they start to stream.
Then they just start to tweet.
And like, like things devolve.
Like, they stop putting effort in and we see less and less good things from them.
And I feel that there's a pressure on almost everybody to do this.
Like, I've been streaming more.
I'm doing my Nuzlocke now.
It's fun.
But like, I, I think, I feel that people are here for me.
The only reason anybody follows me is for like videos of enjoyment.
Maybe they think I have an interesting perspective.
Fair enough.
But like, they're not following me for, I don't know, like anything outside that realm.
And so I just, I try to put that as my focus of what I, like that's always should be my top
priority, I think, for what I give to the world and some online space.
Yeah.
I mean, I thought that everyone followed me for comics, but now I've been like doing slime
and punishment and like, nobody gives a shit.
So I don't know.
I mean, maybe people just don't follow me for any reason.
It's a very, it's kind of punishment.
It's pretty niche, dude.
Like, you know.
Yeah, but it's a comic.
And I, I don't know.
I don't get it.
Well, I, I, I think.
I don't get why everyone isn't as excited about slime and punishment.
Slime and punishment is on Twitter and Twitter is a terrible place to host content.
It's not only on Twitter.
It comes out on Twitter first, but like it's on all the other fucking platforms that a
comic can be on.
Do people, do, do our like sphere of influence like frequent those sites?
It just seems like I've never been on the, on like webtoon ever.
I think this is part of the equation.
It's not a site in my rotation.
Do you, do you think that people would want to read it more if, if like when I get around
to putting it on stcomics.com?
Cause I would assume so.
I think so.
I do.
I mean, that is, that is the plan, like to eventually, once it's done, put it on
stcomics.com.
I mean, for now, okay, whatever.
For now it's readable exactly as it will be on stcomics.com on tapas and webtoon.
I mean, I guess if you don't like those platforms, whatever, I don't.
I mean, it's not about like, it's just about.
I don't see what's off putting about the way that it's presented.
I feel like tapas and webtoon are good for like expanding your audience.
Cause you know, those are discovery platforms.
You would think so, but no.
Well, that's my whole thing.
Cause I think, I think slime and punishment is like, it's, I guess like it, it's sort
of an insular work.
Like there's just so much like going into it, you need to like be aware of.
Otherwise it's just gibberish, you know?
So like, it's not going to do very well on a discovery platform.
I don't know that it is.
Cause like it explains itself perfectly well.
I don't know.
I feel like even if you'd never heard of endless war, you could read it and like,
you would still understand what's happening.
Maybe, I mean, possibly, I don't know.
It's hard for me to really even gauge just because I do know the context.
Honestly, I took pains.
I took pains to explain everything.
Cause like sort of, uh, I mean, at this point, maybe it's a little beyond that,
but especially for like the first couple chapters of it for the first while, like it's
Slam and Punishment is sort of designed to be an introduction to endless war.
And that's why you have like the humble juve.
It's like explaining how mining works and stuff like that.
It's sort of supposed to be a gateway.
Not a thing that is gated by entry.
I don't know.
Maybe there's just needs to be more.
If you can get them to, if you can get a human being to page one of Slam and Punishment to read
it, I mean, I'm obviously biased and I know the source, so I can't judge for everybody,
but I think they'll get a lot of it.
The art is good.
The story is fun.
That's what I think.
Honestly, that's the problem.
How do you get them there?
I mean, I just think that's the, that's the real issue, whatever that is.
Well, I mean, I have gotten some readers front on like fucking um, uh,
dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirty, dirt, on those platforms.
I have gotten some.
I was, you know, just not maybe like, maybe like a hundred, maybe like some,
probably less, maybe less than a hundred, which is like, I mean, that's cool.
I guess yeah, I think that slime and punishment even with it's like exposition is still a denser harder to penetrate work than the Vapors or the champion
It's more complicated. There's more that would be the case, but I mean I
Think it's just because like the Vapors and the champion are both self-contained works like designed to just be themselves
Whereas slime and punishment is a tie-in for endless war and Chris Chen which are both like you need to understand both of those
I think that there's in a wider context to fully appreciate what's going on in slime and punishment
I mean that's partially true and that definitely helps the understanding
But I think that there's like a slight
Like misunderstanding here because I think that what Tom's speaking to which I agree with is that like
Knowing the general idea of what slime and punishment is can be intimidating when you think like oh man
It's like a Chris and an rfck and a t-bap and a pony. Yeah
You don't need to know who Chris is or who nightstar is to like understand what like the premise which is that
But knowing who they are makes the comic much more appealing. I mean just consider for example. Why have just take one example
I assume this is true. Why hasn't Digi red slime and punishment because I don't think he has I
Can answer that it's because he's intimidated by those factors. I mean, you know Digi's a very easily intimidated man
Like it's cuz he doesn't he like he doesn't hear his lack of moral character
He doesn't like I mean he doesn't identify as someone who like understands rfck
So I think like just knowing it's that's involved makes him be turned off
Whereas like the vapors what do you need to know you need to know what like a human going to school is okay?
I think we all you know we get that and that's not easy to read
It's just that's a that's an aura around it of perhaps an intimidating, you know, just set like I imagine digi
Might be among that set of people who yeah, not gonna read it while it's still being made
But once I can I say like okay, so I'm the punishment's done. It's over. It's complete
Then he maybe he goes in because you know, that's that was basically me with them
Bail jpe was like I was aware of it as it was happening, but I didn't really sit down and read it until hippo was like it's done
I think that like the main thing when I hear like a comic like okay
If you already care about any of the things that are involved in there
You'll probably be interested for for many reasons
But like in order to get like a new audience the the thing that should probably lead is like here is an awesome comic
That's really cool with great art, etc. And also it's tied into these other things that are also cool if you which I think it is
I got a lot of enjoyment out of it. So yeah, yeah, that's exactly what it's that's exactly what it's meant to be
Yeah, that was the that was the goal. Mm-hmm. So I
I understand I get that like if you know if you know who if you're invested in
Chris Chan, yeah, and you know who nightstar is and you think that that's funny
Like I get that that would heighten the enjoyment of it for you
My hope is that it's not something that you cannot enjoy without
Knowing the context or same for like endless war, right? Yeah, I think you can it's just a harder sell at that point
A harder sell explain the slower and I don't really think it's about the quality of the comic
Like you are interested in endless war. I think it's a must read if you are interested
Yeah, I think it's a must read because Chris is like involved in its creation in a sort of
Semi and occasionally direct way indeed
And other than that, it's I think I don't know to me it's has got everything
It's got everything it needs to stand on its own. I don't know. That's just my opinion
I I still think this is a this is a marketing question as it is probably for most
Maybe not most but you know, ironically marketing is the most important skill in the world. Yeah, probably probably
Tragically, but I'm terrible at it. Unfortunately
Which explains pretty much everything since we're all competing for eyes in this cruel internet digital age arbitrage economy
On that side, we've got voicemails we could go to if you guys want to unless you want to talk about anything else
No, I think it's fine. I think I've said enough for a lifetime
Yeah, yeah, did you say anime podcast rolls right along with more hits?
Let's uh, all right, let's let's go to them. Let me see
We've got voicemails people you left them for us link down below to the speak pipe thing
Record them leaves the name etc etc
Okay, here we go. First one is
From will it hold up is our first one here and let's find out if it will go
Okay, so I'm probably way too early with this
But I recently listened to the pcp episode 100. You know, it was one of the greats
Right next besides the drug episode or the yellow episode or even the legendary virginity cast
It was fucking live on the couch. It was epic. What about fucking French? It was magic. I mean friendship
so
I've calculated and
The pcp episode number 200 will be on the
Will be released on the 28th of February. So how the fuck are you gonna hold up?
I mean red con 4
Probably isn't gonna be in February. So
What you're gonna do about it?
Shit, he's got the first thing this calls to mind for me is like how the fuck
Has it already been so long since episode 100?
when
Like which was at rad com 3 it just makes rad com 3 feel like an era ago like a like a
A million years kind of was dude. We're going into like two years since right
Yeah, like the last the Kickstarter launched in february of 2018
Yeah, so we're getting close to two years. We're going into 2020 dude march 2020 will be two years since
We kind of meant to do them once a year, didn't we did we fuck up pretty much?
Have we have we we missed this entire year, dude?
I mean there were extenuating circumstances, but yes, I mean, you know, it's uh, it's on us to a degree
I mean entirely 100 but uh, okay. So the answer is
I don't think our like I've been thinking about this too. I respect you doing the math figuring these things out
I also looked up this uh, this ahead of time
February is probably not a great time to do
Anything to get get together
So I doubt we will do any kind of in-person meeting, but uh, I don't know we should we'll we'll perhaps think
Wasn't it in the chat? When we talk about march?
Yeah, but that's not february. That'd be uh, that'd be a little late. This is this is the plan. All right
This is what we're gonna have to do
The week before episode 200 we'll do episode 199. Then we'll do episode 200 one
Yes, and we will just skip 200 until rad con four
Where the legendary missing episode 200 will search for 200. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah people will be so confused when they're looking through their feed
They're like, why is I missing an episode? What happened here?
Fuck the viewers played them
That pretty much sums it up
So I we will think about this. I'll uh, we'll keep you posted keep your eyes peeled around february rad con four temporally
confirmed
Rad con fourth dimension
We control time. All right. Let's uh, go to our next voicemail. This is uh
Keyblade spirit names a meme interpreter. Okay, right. Let's uh
Oh, don't we all these days take it away
Okay, pcp. I need your help
I found this spicy meme at the end of a dosion that I need your help interpreting
Oh, no
The text says this h-manga was translated by two cooked for you gang we
Okay more translations no virus act and then the url
And the picture is a picture of heath ledger's joker
and there's a an arrow
So
Pointing from the joker. Why are you asking us a red circle?
Around an arabic looking guy. I think it's just a stock photo and it's got some arabic words
at the top of that and then
Another meme inside of this meme
It's this guy with looking real surprised
Going
And then inside that meme there's another meme that says bra moment
And then there's a minecraft skin
of the arabic looking guy from before
And he's standing to the right of
naked thanos
What
That's he should have put a link to this so we could actually see what does this mean? Yeah, okay does it mean?
I'll uh, we should help me. I'm gonna I'm gonna reach out. I'm gonna see if he can
Yeah, this is too dense. We don't have visual. He did not provide one boomer for this
Unfortunately, you should have put the fucking link or something in uh, you're the name of your voicemail
Do you guys want to feel boomer today is december 22nd?
I saw a post on twitter today saying it is the 15th anniversary of like the first official youtube poop. Really fascinating dude
Undertale can vote now
Feel old yet feel old yet. Oh, there it is. Yeah. Yeah
Yes, I do but for a completely unrelated I can't interpret that meme
But I will ask you on twitter later to give us a link to that
So perhaps at least the people can can work it out for themselves what they're seeing
Uh, yeah, look in the comments for the answer. Let me see here. Uh next voicemail. Oh, uh, this one is a star wars question mark
Okay, let's uh take it away
Hey
Is any of you gonna see that new star wars film? No
I know I am I like star wars. Does anyone in the pcp make star wars?
You know
I already did see the movie. I saw it yesterday when I heard this voicemail
I was going to be like, I don't think any of us has seen the new movie
Or gives a shit. I certainly don't but then tom had actually happened to see it yesterday
What would you think tom tells the story? Uh
I mean
Do the story is that I had every intention of either watching it when it came out on like video or
Watching a cam whichever happened across my desk first
But then forgotten paladin in my patreon server is like here's 30 bucks
I want you to go see it and shit on it. I'm like
Uh, okay, it's a heavy burden. I bear but I I'll I'll carry this cross. I suppose
So I went to saw the movie and uh, it was pretty dumb. I was so sure
I didn't like it. Yeah, it's gonna be a totally
Non-controversial like just like give it a standard fucking ending just like do do empire again
You know just just uh soft to reboot it like they did with with force awakens
Just make it I don't think there was any like they had rocked the boat and like robbed it of all
I mean, look, I did not see the last one
I saw the force awakens and I thought it was okay
But like my understanding is that they fucked things up so that there was really no way to make it satisfying
To the public. I thought it was gonna be I mean the movie the movie does heavy damage control for last
Unsurprising like if I was gonna sum up like I did I did a 45 minute podcast that you can list to for a dollar a month at patreon.com
So it's called station 2 link in the description. Check it out. It's fucking sick
This was my contractual obligation to accepting this 30 dollars to see this movie was to make a podcast
But um, if I was gonna like sum up the disney trilogy is in a word
Uh, the force awakens would be uh inoffensive
Uh, last Jedi would be insulting and this movie would just be retarded
Uh, that that's really how like because the movie is like an almost all
Sequence of set pieces and when it's just like explosions and blasters and lightsabers. That's pretty cool
But every time I try and move the plot around along it just gets progressively stupider
And it's just like I can't believe this is happening and they thought this was okay
Like there's times where a character is just like I have a feeling we should do this and it's like plot integral
And there's no reason why it's just it's just the worst insult I can give it is simply that I lost interest after
You know the force awakens. I was like, yeah, I mean, you know, whatever sure
Enjoy. Yeah, I mean, I've never been a huge star wars fan
The trilogy is based I watched them back in the day
They were good, but it's not like I've never been like I'm gonna buy star wars merchandise
And I'm gonna like go see star wars opening day. I just like you know me and my buddy went to uh,
I think we missed the grand opening of the phantom menace, but we saw opening night the uh episode two and episode three
Because we were uh, we were way into it, but uh, I mean that was before
Like I just I just that was before my brain awoke
Uh, you know, like there was I I talked about this and there was an event like the first time I saw garen logon
And the first time I saw ghost nashel. I was still a young man
Then at some point in college my brain awoke and I realized actually I like I remember the last thing I saw
Before my brain awoke was my first watching of kill like kill
After that and I still I've been meaning to go back and watch that again
Then I watched garen logon again and I'm like, oh now I get it then I watched ghost nashel
And I'm like, oh this isn't shit. This is actually good and and et cetera, et cetera
Um, so uh, that all the star wars prequels I saw before that
But of course I seen red letter median all those things
Anyway, I don't think any of us really care about star wars. Uh, so
Just nope next question
Next question it is we've got uh, oh ben you're gonna be happy to hear this. We've got uh
Fido vizipops dog is calling in with a message for the progress
Get him out of here. That's disgusting. Let's uh fido
Take it away go
Bark bark. This is busy pops dog fido and I'm here with a message to ben saint. Yeah, but sadly to my knowledge. She does not
Fuck dogs. Yeah, that's what you want us to think and I'm sure you're uh, probably sad to hear that been saying, you know
You did a call right but hey man, think about how I feel
I was at the pound looking at this girl thinking man, this this one's definitely down
I'm looking look at the hair the general face for like the choker, but you know, I'm I mean, this is a little early
I've uh
Got a couple intense belly rubs if you know what I'm saying
But uh, if I do get laid, I'll be sure to let bent state. No asap. Yeah probably through speakpipes since I'm a dog and
Please they don't let us have twitter accounts
Bark bark, which is very speed. Yeah, make me the first. I want to be the first one to know. Um, I think he's lying
Um, I think he's just doesn't want us to I think he wants to spread the misinformation that this isn't going on
It's part of the jewish conspiracy to uh, to uh
Well dogs are loyal and why would you want your master? He just he just doesn't want us to build the wall between
America and the dog nation
He doesn't want to know that they're coming over they're coming over the border and stealing our jobs stealing our women yada yada yada
Y'all know it y'all know it. Mm-hmm sound off. We know
Sound off. We want a human only
All right next try to answer the dq
All right next voicemail is from uh, this is uh, harlock aznebel who if you don't remember folks
He's the one who uh got the um, the the gf from anime club his little brother
Got a gf an anime club and if you recall he made a bet between
I mean he made a bet saying if he kept the gf
He would give you tons of fun bucks on patreon and if he lost the gf
Oh, wait, no, no, if he lost he would give it to you if he kept it he would give it to me
He came up with this
But that's uh, that's what he did well. Do I recall?
Indeed indeed. You're up to speed viewers. Uh, let's hear uh, how things are going for him harlock. Take it away
So ben saint wins the bet
Yeah
Fuck
I don't have his money yet because uh, I thought this would at least last till past christmas
But it actually ended literally the second the semester of my college ended. So
Fuck was he right?
I mean, I guess he's always right. He's right. This is me to can presume when college everything
I suppose it makes sense that you wouldn't be wrong here either praise papa saint
Anyway, uh, I don't want people to get the wrong idea and think anime club gfs are a bad idea all around
Brothers
His girlfriend get along really well. So
It is possible. Yeah, we'll see about that. You know, don't don't rule it out entirely
Yeah, but but yeah, I didn't say when
Didn't last till February
Didn't even last till christmas
This is cause for celebration
Yeah, everybody wins the problem was entirely in the framing you should and you don't go to anime club looking for a gf
You go to anime club looking for a quick fuck. That's what you do
You fucking pervert you go to anime club looking for anime for fuck's sake
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
I go to mia.si if i'm looking for anime. Uh, there's um indeed indeed. There's um, what was I gonna say?
Something about oh, right. I mean, okay. Now that we're in where we're past relate. We're post relationship here
It's time for the period of reflection. I mean obviously we never met this girl
We didn't know the nature of the relationship the fact that you were so unceremoniously dropped at the end of the semester like
We that just reveals that this relationship was obviously
Nothing of substance. It was an it was an anime relationship. The worst time
Inherently unstable like a like a like a radioactive isotope
Exactly, although, you know, what what's his face the young brother harlock bronable is is keeping his life
So good for him, but uh as far as we know
So he left another message actually that uh, I'm over there playing but he was saying that like, you know
Like what should I do about like my next relationship? I mean, I think you should you should reflect
It sounded like this was his first relationship. Okay. I don't know
You're like, whatever. I mean, he was saying like don't don't do anything. It's fine
He was asking questions like like how long should I wait? Is it weird to move on? Okay, like what this is feeling? No, it's fine
Don't worry. Don't worry about anything
Harlock and there's no shame in it. It's all good. But like obviously you don't know what you're doing here
And that's fine. I forgive you for that
But you forgive him
Like yeah, he knew he obviously didn't understand the relationship
He just had if it was so flimsy all along and was so easy for it to dissolve
It sounds like you had much more emotional investment than she did if if you're like reflecting on like what do I do now?
I mean did this man sound like he was that emotionally invested when he was making bets online about how long
Maybe there's he's just beaming with pride. Um, who knows? Yeah, yeah, it's a mystery. Um, don't worry about it
Whatever. Yeah, I mean, there's nothing to worry about here dawg. It's fine. Just do it again
Yeah, you have come and go but anime club is absolutely right tom
Harlock, yeah, don't overthink it. Obviously this relationship wasn't that big a deal to her. Keep going to anime club
Yeah, don't let her win. Don't let her take anime club
Don't let them see
Anime club was always meant for me
That's right
You can meet your else out there. Oh, hey, have you guys seen frozen 2 or heard about it by any chance?
No, I saw big Joel's video about it
What what did he think? I'm curious. He I think he thought it was weird in a good way
Michelle saw it yesterday. I wasn't there. She saw it. I'm kind of regret not seeing it with her
I was just I'm a stream at the time or whatever
But like she said it was weird and michelle
She kind of loves frozen one and it was just like this was weird and like there was like superpowers and weird elemental things
And they give the mom a weird backstory that was obviously not intended from the start
Uh, a bunch of weird stuff seems like they took like the trailer blocking blockbuster ever
and they fucking uh
Went fucking weird weird bizarre place with it
It was so clearly not intended for a sequel and part of the charm of like a big temple disney movie
Is like like just for example, like I mean moana is a dope ass hawaii island movie
Like there's a whole culture. There's like a bunch of like, you know songs relevant to the period and whatnot
Obviously frozen was like, I don't know sweeten or whatever
It's like themed around that old land and just like making a sequel is like, okay
None so we don't get any new stuff like that
They're just like adding details to characters that we didn't care about in the first place
And they're trying to put together something that was never intended
Trying to give characters arcs that don't do it. I'm just I'm hearing this whole second hand from michelle
So I don't know what I'm talking about but like I mean line king two and a half one and a half
Now there was a sequel for the ages that filled out characters. We cared about that we had deep connection with
Uh, it did not fuck up the lore any in a serious way
Uh, I'm I'm lying but they say line king two is good. You said that tom, right? You're a fan
I thought I mean I watched it as a much younger
Child but I remember enjoying it at the time
You know, I'm still mad at those motherfuckers are trying to lie to us and pretend that that kid who's exactly looks like scar
Isn't scar's son. It's the most retarded ass thing they've ever tried to come up with
He's obviously scar's son
The weirdest thing is that they have a new television show called the lion guard
That entire movie never happened video about that
I did
You made it look like real tempting
Uh, yeah, you may I was on
I mean if you want to watch I there's apparently in like a later episode like the the character bongo
Who's that like farting guy made a fart joke. They have like a love scene with farting. I like farting. No
This I wish I was lying. I've been told second hand. I've not seen it, but this is what I've heard
That's that's somebody's fucking
Life's dream to see that brappers unite our people are being represented last like like wet dream
Realized beyond their wildest imagination
I mean sometimes right the animators fetishes leak through that's this is definitely an example of that
Indeed we're all richer disgusting
All right, that's one word for it. Uh, what do we got here? We got uh, uh nuzlocke deep lore
Kill hoot hoot is is is is said here. Let's how mysterious. Let's find out what that's about. Go wait
Tell me something is it true that team rocket has returned? Yeah
What you eat them
Quit lying. Are you serious? Let's see how good you are
There he is useless pokemon listen you you only won because my pokemon week
I hate the week pokemon trainers. It doesn't matter who or what I hate see them hanging around
That goes for that was neoliberal scum team ron
They think they're big and tough as long as they're in the root but get them alone and they're weak
They will be crushed by my venture capitalist fingers
I hate them all you say out of my way
You won't be an exception if you get in my way too juicy. Oh
That's it me. Uh, that's that's famous
Rival to me in the heart gold nuzlocke a voicemail god calling in
Uh neocapitalist monster trying to talk shit and get hit sounds like sounds like him
Uh sounds like silver or whatever his fucking canon name is
Uh, well watch I leave it as silver. Yeah
Watch out for him guys. He's around
He's a rough character. Don't cut yourself on that edge. I fucking love silver as a rival in in silver and gold is a
Is a great fucking boy. He's just so mad all the time. I'm waiting only the president of fucking, uh, uh,
Canto
Wait, which is the second one. He's in joe. If only if only the president we need the president of joe so to fucking sign a bill
Breaking up his monopoly
Yeah, that's that's what I would vote for
We uh, oh and also ben you should know
My I think I didn't mention this last time that people tried to get you to be the rival in the uh, in the thing
Yes, and fucking shan ruined it. That's right. Voice of god, and I remember I'm a hood hoot
And I said just keep just keep hypnosising with ben saint the hood hoot and do not switch him out under any circumstances
How did it go?
Uh, you know, we I did switch some things out
But uh, that that hypnosis has been extremely useful
Hell and even catching all kinds of great pokes
So ben saint the hood who's actually been putting in some good workforce over on the next lock
So nothing could make me happier other than other than a heroic death that lets me go god tier
That's inevitable. That's definitely inevitable. Don't let me fucking don't fucking let me die a cow like radaway and the cowards
PC box Ben, I gotta tell you the people are just calling for your death every moment of battle. They're just they're
Yeah, so am I let him die. I also thirst for blood
Uh, I'm sure I want my I want my blood to turn brown on the rocks of glory
It's it's certainly an only a matter of time
All right, so hey, hey folks, uh, I'm gonna be away for christmas eve
But next saturday, uh, come come stop by and take take a look at the nuz like it's a good time
All right. Anyway, anyway, um, we've got one final voicemail
Who could this one be from what what's what's this? This appears to be from, uh, ellie azar the editor of the pcb
How could this be true my god, um, two worlds one family
All right, let's uh, let's see what he's got for us
Go here's a christmas present for you guys
Somebody once told me that I could be a winner in the pcb editor contest
I was looking kind of dumb as a 17 year old with no future or plan of progress
Well the answer start coming at it don't stop coming everyone is shit except me and plushie flower
Also enters
He was really just doing a flexing you finally gets the job and I say screw it all
Hey now you're a loser without a pay
Hey now you're a loser get out of here
All that sweet money
Going to someone who is not me
I know that feel
ellie azar learned how to edit apparently for this contest and I'm just gonna tell you he was tied for number one
Yeah, ellie azar overrated green fleshy flowers
Time for me to get my top three overrated editor submissions
Everyone like you guys son shit
ellie azar bolden donasore get fucked
Someone please kill him before he kills you
You say I'm overrated
Well, I say that you are over-retarded
Yeah
He said yeah, he was too busy then I knew I had to act really quickly because I saw an opportunity
Well, I didn't they don't really saying that I'm still willing to work for them because it would be really thrilling if I
Say yes to me. Thank you very much bcp
I can't take the sincerity
For this opportunity
And I was just kidding a lot of there were a lot of great entries for the pcbator contest
I'm not saying even if you are the anti-christian person
Everyone serves love
And a happy new year
Thank you very much
Mary crimson very cringis everybody. I'm glad to have you glad you fucking like the job
He does he's very happy as far as I can tell which is he sounds pretty chuffed, which is uh
That makes me happy as well
What a nice what a nice what a nice little treat
We are not used to that level of sincerity here on the pcb. No, no, no fuck that guy. It's like uh
You know, uh, you know a wrinkle in time remember when uh, I don't know that was a complicated book
There's a lot of weird shit happening
But at the end the girl tries to like love a thing that like can't handle love or something and it like makes it die
That's how I feel right now. It's uh, don't remember that can handle it. All right. Just trust me. Okay. Yeah, it was fucked up
Okay
Well, thank you. Eleazar. It's a pleasure to have you places any to fucking call it after that love bomb
That's that. Yeah, that's the end. That's the end. That was our voice. Love you. Love you, bro
Yeah, I don't love anything. Say hi to Eleazar in the comments. Go give him go follow him on twitter
Yeah, thank Eleazar for his great work editing. Is Eleazar on twitter?
He is though. He's not particularly active, but he's out there Eleazar if you want to put your twitter or something feel feel free in the description or something
Um, yeah, but he's doing a great job. We couldn't be happier with him. I think he's uh, he does a bunch of extra work even beyond what we ask of him
Uh, uh, he's very happy with you buddy. Thanks. Uh, thanks for being such a great sport and great editor. All right, whoo
Leave your voicemails people speak pipe link down below
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators when you hear this in a couple days the new bonus episode will be dropping
Which I believe is episode 33
And you get all of those for just a low low five dollar pledge on patreon.com slash the procrastinators
Who boy what a deal um
You could also just pledge one dollar to get into the patron lounge if you are a cheap scape
And of course this patreon.com slash psb minecraft play minecraft with us all season long
We'll be doing another one of the streams except for the christmas season
Except for the christmas season when most of us will be away. We'll be back at it again in the new year
Indeed, but it is decked out for christmas right now. So you can go check it out like on the stream and uh design your house anywhere
Come come join us in cool guy village. That's right
You know, you could you could always use this downtime to get in on get in there to build your fucking homestead
Right and then when we get back in there, we'll see what kind of bullshit y'all made
We would love to take a tour of all the new things never we we check back in and see what's up
I was uh, just doing we'll go on we'll go on the new year the january pcp minecraft home invasion tour where we'll like
We'll we'll go we'll go in there and we'll claim our right to first night
For all of all our subjects
Indeed and of course follow us twitter at tp crassinators for updates and all that good shit
All right, that's it. Thanks for being here everybody. This is the last episode of this year
So we'll see you in 2019. Hey if you're doing any you want to do any join us on our quest to
Whatever fucking uh fitness or otherwise. Uh new year goals
Bullshit make it make a man goals are tough. Make it time-bound. Just do something for a month, man
Once you're there then see how you feel. Um, anyone can do anything for a month, right?
I empower you to take the challenge whatever it is you're trying to do make it reasonable michelle michelle said
I'm gonna read a hundred books next year. That's too high. Don't set it unrealistically. That's like two books a week
It is
Yeah, that's way too high like I mean she could do picture books or something small
So you got to do like a book a week is even even that's probably too many when you said it was her
I assume that's what she meant
I mean she she had this idea in her head that I argued against so she's like
But if I set the goal super duper high then like I'll get close and I'll still read tons of books
I'm like that's not how goals work. Once you will fail and give up once you break
Yeah, once you break the expectation of keeping the goal
Yeah, exactly
That's the thing. So don't do that folks time-bounded. There's a really good acronym that I forget
It's like time-bounded something something like attainable love a lot whatever
Whatever that is do that. It's like star or something. So, uh, all right. Anyway, we're done here folks
We'll see you in 2020, baby, and it's going to be a great time. Oh, yeah, 10 more years of pcp
All years in the movie, please 10d movie. All right. See you then. Bye