Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am your
host Tom Oliver, so far alone, sitting here 15 minutes, 20 minutes after the podcast is
supposed to start recording and no one has shown up. So, you know, I had some time and
I went out, I got a snack, I got a drink, I got, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm refreshed
and rehydrated and ready for battle and nobody, nobody seems to be here. I added everyone
and I just figured, you know what, the show must go on quite literally, even if no one
else is here. So, here we go. Solo Tomcast for the beginning of the podcast. I'm assuming
and I'm hoping that somebody will join me at some point during these proceedings, but
if not, this may be a short podcast because I'm not interesting enough to talk for two
hours about my life. That would be sad. We're approaching the new year. That's fucking fantastic.
2020, glad to leave it fucking behind, be gone with it, banish it to the shadow realm
for all time. 2021 gearing up to be interesting. I just saw on Twitter yesterday that there's
like a new strain. There's like a new hyperpowered like Super Saiyan strain of COVID-19 that
people are already kind of freaking out about because it's like going crazy in the UK. Too
bad it wasn't here. I could maybe poke a brain about it, but I guess Japan just closed down
all travel again to prevent it from fucking them up because I guess they got a case. There's
been some cases in Russia. One of the CEOs for the vaccine said that it'll like their
vaccine will work on this new strain. So maybe it'll be a nothing burger, but you know, you
know, 2021 gearing up to be to be a whole big fun thing. What have I been up to? What
have I been doing for the last month and change? They haven't really been on the podcast.
I've been playing a ton of video games. I talked about that briefly last week. I've
been working my VPN to the core, downloading a bunch of high definition movies and stuff.
In fact, my 4k rip of Godzilla, King of the Monsters just finished. So I'm going to stop
seeding that because I'm a bad torrentor. I bought it legally on Blu-ray. So as far
as I'm concerned, this is totally above the belt. So fuck you copyright law. I don't care.
Maybe I shouldn't admit that on the podcast, but whatever. Ben can talk about shoplifting
and be fine. I can piss off the MPAA or whoever the fuck is in charge of movies and shit. It's
fine. Started using Plex. Has anybody here used Plex? I had heard about Plex for like years,
but never bothered with it. I've just manually been managing my media on like multiple hard drives
and it's really annoying. And I tried using Plex I think like five years ago because I had an
account when I signed up for it a few days ago, but it's the fucking shit. And anybody who has
like a big media library that isn't just like if anyone is like me and hasn't completely succumbed
to streaming services and that convenience and still like tries to keep like digital files of
their media that they have complete autonomous offline control of and that's something you care
about, but you still kind of are tempted by the allure and the simplicity and the streamlined
clean aesthetic of something like Netflix. Plex is your answer, my friends. Okay. So it like
you run a client on your host PC, right? There's a Plex media server client and you run that and
then you hope you like point it at all of your media. You can like choose movies, TV shows,
music, all that kind of stuff. And it has like a bunch of databases it taps into and it's pretty
good at matching like jumbled bullshit, like internet downloaded names to the actual show
or movie or whatever that it is, populating all the metadata, bringing up like, you know, like,
like images and graphics and descriptions and episode titles and all that kind of stuff. And
it automatically populates your downloaded local stored media with all this really good
presentation. It has a really clean UI and this is like built into smart TVs. You can get it on
like it Amazon fire stick and all that kind of bullshit. And so you basically just have access
to all of your media that you have locally, freeware. So I'm just like keeping my desktop on
it's hosting all my media and anything with a web browser, I can go and log into like the user end
of Plex and just have access to all of this. And I guess there's a way to configure it so you can
even access it remotely over the internet. So if I'm like out of the house, and I'm like on my phone
and I'm bored and for some reason I want to watch an episode of Garo, I guess I can do that now.
So that's pretty fucking cool. There's a way to like manually override the automatic metadata
matching because some of the times it doesn't like pick up exactly what it is, especially when
you're like me, and your your library is full of like, you know, Garo gold storm and common
writer Kabuto and ultra seven X and shit, like weird Japanese Tokusatsu things, where like a lot
of these databases think that like, oh, common writer, that's one series with like 700 seasons
when each one is like its own distinct show. So it kind of has some trouble with that so you can
manually go in and like set some things up if you need to. But for the most part, for most like
normie core shit, like even anime, I haven't had any problem with any of my anime stuff, it's matched
all that up almost perfectly with the exception of Babylon, I thought it was some 2014 live action
show. But other than that, it's been pretty fucking good. And I don't I don't have much to
complain about the only thing I have to complain about is I've been starting to get into 4k,
right? Because I just talked about how I was got my 4k kick the monster, but I don't think it streams
any higher than 1080p on the free plan. Or if it does, I haven't been able to figure it out,
because it seems to be downscaling my four by couple 4k rips I have to 1080p, which still look
fine. But it's like, man, they're taking up 30 gigs of space. I want I want every last little pixel.
But what are you going to do? What are you going to do for free? I can't complain too much,
much, much better media experience than just sifting through hard drives and having to like
get a laptop and plug the hard drive in and bring it up and hook it up via HDMI to a TV.
Fuck that shit. Just load the Plex app and stream it. That's way better. So I highly recommend Plex,
if you haven't tried it out, if you're a media hoarder like I am, if you're like, you know,
a fucking hardcore doomer, and you're torrenting and line wiring before it was cool.
It's this is what you've been waiting for. This is a solution to get shit on all the screens
without having to like juggle cables and shit, because nothing is more annoying than having
to deal with motherfucking cables. Let me tell you. That's the end of my Plex story.
Let's see. Did I talk about Remnant last week? I don't think I did. I'm playing this game called
Remnant from the ashes. It's a I get tentatively call it a souls light game, but I feel that's
kind of dish and genious. I think it's an indie title or it's made by a smaller studio. It's not
like a triple A thing or anything, but it's like a randomly generated dungeon kind of crawler game
shooter souls light all kind of mixed into one. So you're like playing through these randomly
generated levels and depending on like the world seed, like the seed of like how it makes the
levels, like there are a bunch of bosses and some of them you won't even find on like a single
playthrough. So you have to play through it multiple times to experience everything. And
it's a shooting game. So instead of like fighting with swords and shit and armor sets like in like
souls, you're using guns. You have a melee weapon, but it's usually kind of like a last resort sort
of thing, but like you have a long gun and a sidearm. And so you can customize these and level
them up and they have like their version of tight night with just different kinds of iron.
And so you collect these iron resources and you can make your guns better and add different
like attachments and enchantments to them. And just like souls, every time you kill a boss,
you get like a unique item from them that you can go back and craft into a weapon if you have
enough materials. So like in that regard, it's pretty similar because you also have the same
kind of world progression. It has like an estus flask. And then like you have checkpoints throughout
these levels. And when you die, you go back to the checkpoint. From what I can tell, there's no
like souls that to lose if you die, because like you pick up scrap, which is your currency,
because you're doing a lot of like crafting or going back to like the girl who like crafts
your items, like you give her resources and she can craft you stuff and you can go to the armor,
like the Smithy and he'll upgrade your armor and things like that. So it kind of has like the,
I don't want to say it has a loot system like Diablo, because it doesn't it's much more reserved,
like like Dark Souls, you know, like where there's not like there's not like a hardcore loot game,
but there is like an item progression, you pick up items kind of as you go.
I'm not I'm of the two minds of the game, I guess this the shooting is really good,
which is what's kind of keeping me there, like firing like the hunting rifle
feels really good, like the gunplay feels great. And the controls are really nice. I'm playing on
controller, even though I have it on PC, just because like it's a super casual game. At least
I'm playing it casually, because you can play it offline by yourself. And that's where it kind of
feels more like a Souls game, because there's like a bunch of dudes against you. And they're
a fair bit more brain dead than then Souls enemies. And like, obviously, the back and
forth is different, because you're firing at range, and most enemies have range attacks too,
whereas in Souls, it's much more up close and melee and based more on positioning.
So this is like different in that regard, but the kind of like tepid like forward momentum,
where guys can like easily like kind of get the jump on you. So you can't just kind of like barrel
through the level, like a crazy man, you got to take it a little bit more calmly, that kind of
like moment to moment kind of like slow, paying attention to the environment kind of gameplay
is there, but it's not nearly as good, because all these environments are randomly generated.
So like the careful handcrafted attention to, you know, Lordran that Dark Souls has, it isn't
replicated here, because there's so many repeating tiles and stuff, which kind of makes a level
navigation kind of difficult. There's definitely not enough tiles in any of these environments,
because with multiple environments, you kind of like go through this like threadbare story
that I barely am paying attention to. And you'll see a lot of repeated tiles through your playthroughs,
like you a lot of the time I will start and end in the same, like the exact same room. So it feels
like I went in a circle when I actually did go through the entire level, you'll be referencing
your map a lot to make sure you're not going in circles, because there's so many repeated tiles,
which is pretty fucking annoying. But even to someone like me who doesn't usually pay attention
to level design or give a shit at all, I noticed a lot of this repeating shit. So that way, you
know, it's like kind of egregious. But they serve as like shooting galleries well enough. And
yeah, like you can play it solo, which getting back to what I was saying, you can play it solo,
that's kind of like the Dark Souls sort of thing, where you have that kind of like slow
forward momentum. But then you can also play it co-op, which I haven't done yet, you can play
up to three other people. And I'm assuming once you do that, like it scales up, like it adds more
enemies and stuff like that. But like these levels, unless they get bigger, they're definitely not
designed, I don't think, to really facilitate that like tense souls forward progression with
four people, I'm assuming at that point, it'll become much more of just like an open season
shooting gallery, because you'll just have so many, so many extra like firearms and like,
like options on your side that you'll just kind of turn the tides pretty easily. So I just feel
like it will become much more frantic if you're playing with friends and feel like a different
game, which is why I haven't decided to play multiplayer, because I kind of like the the
one person versus everybody more tense kind of atmosphere that the single player is providing.
So that's interesting. I got to the last level. The final boss is ridiculous, has like multiple
phases like a Dark Souls boss. The boss designs are pretty cheap, because again, all this feels more
like a co-op game that I'm playing single player rather than a single player game that can play
multiplayer. So like bosses will spawn tons of ads, they feel like the worst Dark Souls two bosses
at sometimes where it's just like, let's just throw more shit at you. Like one of the most
difficult and annoying, not even difficult, but just annoying bosses, like, you know, the butterfly
boss of Dark Souls one, they basically ape that boss fight, except you're still on a narrow bridge,
there's the butterfly that's like floating in the air, but there's two of them, there's one on each
side. And they're spawning like these like homing projectiles that have HP do tons of damage, you
can't dodge roll through them. So they're firing those firing missiles, like throwing down AoE poison
effects, and there's two of them. So you can never see the way the level is designed, you can never
see them both at the same time on the screen, you have to be facing either one or the other.
And this is where it feels like this is a multiplayer boss, right? Because if you have two
or three people on this bridge, you can kind of like, you know, have one person doing DPS on one,
one person doing DPS on another, and they have a third or four person kind of taking care of
like the homing projectiles and keeping you clear and doing like some secondary DPS in between
bursts. But when just one person, it's ridiculous. So the boss designs and the boss encounters
definitely seem like balanced more for having multiple people in the fray, because if you die
in multiplayer, someone could come and revive you. Whereas if you die single player, you get kicked
back to the bonfire or like the fucking, I don't know, some weird, they use a weird fucking like
red stones that are basically function as bonfires. They have the exact same thing.
It's good. It's not great. It's not great. It's good. It's fun. It's worth playing through it.
Like it survives really on just like the catharsis of the gunplay alone. Like if the gunplay didn't
feel so good, there really wouldn't be anything else super redeeming about the game. But that
carries it, at least for me, who just like plays games to like feel cool cathartic things like firing
a rifle and a magnum and like the black as the headshot goes off. That's pretty fun. And that's
all that's all I need to be happy when it comes to video games. So remnant from the ashes, I guess
there's a sequel coming out soon, I think, if it's not already out. This games, I think a couple years
old, but it's pretty fucking cool. I watch a skill up video on it. And that's what made me check it out.
And that was pretty dope. I was thinking of doing some more I am games podcasts or like like like
vlogs sort of style videos kind of similar to what I just did for remnant. Maybe I'll like cut this
out and put it on I am games because that was I was literally planning after this podcast to record
a bunch of stuff on some games I've played. I played Jedi Fallen Order, Ghost of Tsushima, Remnant, Halo
4. And what was the other one was another game I played recently. Dragon Age Origins, which don't
play Dragon Age Origins on PC. It keeps constantly crashing it deleted my save file. It does not run
on modern hardware very well. It is not a great PC port. Despite the name on Steam, it is not the
ultimate edition. Yeah, we'll see about that. God, no one is joined. No one is no one's here.
Gib says I'm about to eat dinner. I'll jump in later at some point or or not IDK sick,
all right. Well, damn, I'm floundering. I'm floundering. I thought I was I was fucking sure
that I was going to add somebody jump in and like immediately, Ben was going to be like I'm not
missing out on my Patreon money and was going to jump in and like be here and we'd have be having
a discussion right now. But no, no such no such luck. It's just it's 15 minutes and I'm running
out of steam already. Let's see what else what else can we talk about? Oh, I mentioned on Twitter
a couple days ago, like two days ago, yesterday. Oh my God, I don't even remember a couple days ago
that I was like really like reminiscing fondly on like the DS and like its graphical style. The
DS is like such a cool aesthetic. I was trying to like kind of figure out what I like so much about
the DS. I mean, I've always like really like the PS one blocky like non texture filtered graphics.
But the problem with the PS one, in my opinion, aesthetically is that it's almost too simplistic
at sometimes like a lot of games really work well on the PS one, like the cartoony style games,
like you look at medieval, you look at Spyro, you look at Crash, like those are such like
cartoony style characters that even on the PS one, they have tons of emotion and tons of expressiveness
to them. And they just look really good. But you look like Metal Gear Solid one. On the whole,
the game looks awesome, right? Shadow Moses is a gorgeous looking environment. They did so much
with the PS one, but like the character models themselves kind of break down when solid snakes
faces like seven pixels, you know, that has no room for emoting. Like, I appreciate it aesthetically,
but in terms like something I would want to reproduce in my work, the PS one has always
felt a little too limiting as someone who'd want to do not necessarily just games, but like if I
wanted to make like a multimedia project, you know, like, I think like the biggest barrier to
getting into Metal Gear Solid one for like a zoomer would be taking the cut scene seriously,
because solid snake has seven pixels and when he talks his head just kind of shakes like he's
having a seizure. And like, if you're an old fuck like me, like that, you're totally immersed in
that because that's just what games were at the time. But I feel like anybody experiencing that
kind of thing now with the PS five existing would be like, what is this? How am I supposed to take
this seriously? So I've been hesitant to work in that style some because I feel like
like I would love to make a game in the PS one aesthetic like something you just play,
but in terms of like a more multimedia narrative driven experience, which is stuff I do as well.
PS one seems like would be almost antithetical to the emotions you're trying to invoke would hit
that nostalgia nerve. But like, I feel like anybody who was disconnected from playing games back in
the late 90s, mid 90s, would not kind of resonate with whatever kind of emotion was trying to be
conveyed. Maybe I'm overthinking it, but that's just kind of been my kind of hesitance. Also,
I do when it's hard to envision a complete PS model, while you're working on it, right? Because
when you're building a model, initially, you're doing the modeling. So there's no textures and
on that sheet, you're just seeing the geometry. And when you're working as low resolution as a PS
one is, you have to kind of imagine the detail because the majority of the detail all comes out
in the texture work. So a lot of the times I like put too much detail into the modeling part,
because I'm not envisioning it with a texture, I'm just envisioning it as a shape and the shape
needs more detail in order to be defined. And then by the time I get to texturing, I'm like,
this is way higher poly count than a PS one model would be anyways. So it's a it's a balancing act,
it's like juggling and like really optimizing. And like, if I was going to do this style,
effectively, I would probably do more studying and like ripping more models from like VG resource
and like seeing how they put them all together and how they work. But the nice thing about the DS
is that it has that texture filtered, like that non texture filtered look that the PS one has,
but the poly counts are just a little bit higher. They're closer to like, you know,
something like an N64 or like really low level Dreamcast that sometimes they're kind of like
in this middle ground somewhere, like the DS, I feel to my eye, and I haven't like fattened,
you know, looked up anything, but I feel like it's got a little bit more is able to push a
few more polys than the PlayStation is. Or it's just because it's so much later,
uh, time wise, like it came out like over a decade later than the PlayStation, like in that time,
artists just got better at like doing 3D. So like they've just able to use those same polygons
more effectively. I don't really know. I just find the 3D on the DS to be more detailed and
more representative of the objects in question than what the PlayStation could produce. And
that combined with the really low resolution screen, it's like half the resolution of the
PlayStation. The PlayStation is QVGA 320 by 240. And then the DS is like 160 by 144, I think,
something like that, something low, something low, like actually 160 by 144 is Game Boy Color.
It's a little bit higher than that. It's like 240 by 160. It doesn't matter. It's lower than the
PlayStation. So that lower pixel count actually kind of helps further obscure the lack of detail
in the PlayStation and like the DS's models. So like the low fidelity of the models combined
with the low resolution of the display kind of like tricks your eye into thinking there's more
detail there than there actually is and carries the art style even further. It's really fucking
interesting looking back at like DS stuff. And I'm thinking like Final Fantasy III,
Dragon Quest Monsters Joker. There was a Dragon Ball game that looked really good. Of course,
the one I mentioned on Twitter was Final Fantasy Fables Chocobo Tales. Like a lot of these games
that like used cartoonish, anime inspired aesthetic combined with this low resolution display,
these low resolution textures and these very low polygon models all coalesced into this really
evocative and like kind of semi nostalgic art style that also felt like this is kind of more
like how I remember it than what it actually is because you go back and play like Siphon
Filter 1, you're like, oh my god, this is a fucking technical mess. You know, there's just like,
there's a lot of just jank that the PlayStation one had to deal with like the
the way the texture is kind of a blur and distort because they're kind of being projected to the
camera and things like that. Like that looks weird, but the DS doesn't do that. So it kind of like
presents the PS1 as you remember it being more so than what it actually was, which was like a series
of technical concessions. So I don't know, coming back to the DS and like playing Final Fantasy
Fables again a little bit was like, oh, this is like really cool. This is like really fucking cool.
And I would love to work in the style. And I kind of just tweeted that out saying like, oh man,
this stuff was great. So maybe I'm making a zoomy game in the style of a DS. That would be weird.
That would take a lot of extra work that I would not know how to do. So I still don't know anything
about 3d game dev. But I found this really cool guy sickly wizard who does a bunch of tutorials
and blender on how to do like PS1 kind of stuff. And a lot of the stuff I've watched so far is pretty
basic. It's just like this is how you unwrap a model. It's like I've been there done that.
His stuff's really designed for like total beginners. But like if you're interested in 3d,
and you're like, man, I have no idea where to start this shit's really fucking complicated. PS1
is so easy. It's I mean, I don't want to say 3d is easy, right? But like in terms of like levels
of complexity, you take like sculpting a high poly model and baking normals down to like a mid
poly geometry and like retopology versus just like PS1 where it's like the arm is a square.
Like it's the barrier of entry there is so much lower. So if you were ever like interested in
3d and wanted a place to start, check out sickly wizard, follow along with some of his videos.
Like you'll have PlayStation one graphics by the end in like an hour and you'll be like,
well, like there it is, it's real, it's done and it looks cool. And I don't know the I guess it's
like watching his streams like the efficiency, right? Because like doing a PlayStation 2 style
model is significantly more work requires much more finesse in the weight painting. You can't
get away on the PS2 style with like segmented limbs and stuff which makes again rigging a lot
easier to make them like animate and deform easier when you have segmented limbs, you don't have to
worry about like how am I going to get the shoulder deformation right because there is no
shoulder the arm just moves in a socket essentially. So like I'm just thinking of it in terms of like
aesthetically, I really like the DS and then practically making props and characters and
like tons of like game assets at this resolution is way simpler because I was looking at the wiki
for Chocobo Tales. They made that entire game with 2006 tech, which is not a lot compared to what we
have now at least they made that with 20 people in like a year. And it's like that was that's a
way more complicated game that anything I would make for Izumi. So like scaling that down to like
one or two people, you could probably turn around a decent game in a similar maybe a little bit
longer timeframe. Like if I was going to do like a basic 3d Izumi game that just had some basic
systems of just me and like someone doing sound. Maybe I could turn it around like 18 months like
I don't fucking know. It's just another idea. It's another it's another idea to think about
because I don't have enough ideas. God fucking damn. But that's that's cool. That's that's nice.
Now we're at 25 minutes. And now I'm like really tapped. What else do I got going on?
Okay, let's see. This was this was a bad call. This was a bad call. I rolled the dice thinking I
was just going to have like a cheeky little intro. And it did not work. What else have I been doing?
Oh, fuck Vizio. Okay, so another thing I mentioned, this is going to be my Twitter
escapades, I guess. Twitter, I mentioned a few weeks ago, I ran a poll saying should I buy an
HDTV, like a big 4k TV with my my cashback, my credit card cashback awards and everyone
overwhelmed me said no, fuck you, I did it anyways. My cashback on my credit card is not
actually cashback. It's like here's some gift cards. And I'm like, that's
literally not cash. In fact, on the back of a gift card, it says this is not redeemable for cash.
So saying this is a cashback rewards card is like straight up lies. And I feel like I have
legal grounds. But I probably don't because I probably said yes to something in some terms
of conditions that the cashback rewards card from Santander Bank is not actually cashback
rewards. We lied. It just sounds nice. So I had a bunch of gift cards, and I had nothing to do with
them. The GTX, the RTX 3070 is not in stock, you know, and I already got my overpriced 3060 Ti.
PS4 and Xboxes are never going to be in stock. And I don't want to buy one until the new ones come
out with at least like, you know, a terabyte or two terabytes of storage, because like the PlayStation
5 having 600 gigs of storage is a non starter for me, my dude. My PS4 came with more storage,
and these games are way bigger, especially with a backwards compatible library. So that's skew,
in my opinion, is out of the question. I want two terabytes of flash storage, or at least some
fucking like SSDs on the market to up the storage, because right now you can't even officially upgrade
your storage on your PS5 because they haven't rolled out the firmware update. So I don't want to buy
that. I want it in matte black, fuck you. The white and black looks terrible. And ideally,
I'd like it to be smaller. Like I have the PS4 slim, it's so much nicer than the base PS4,
like the original. So if they do like a PS5 slim, that's where I'm going to jump in.
Because I don't care about Demon's Souls enough to drop a million dollars. So like,
what else am I going to get at fucking Best Buy? If the consoles aren't on the table right now,
the cashback expires eventually. And I already have the graphics card. Well, I have a shitty TV
that's like from 10 years ago, it has terrible pixel refresh rate, it goes all the time. So
whenever you play a PlayStation game on it, it's all blurry, not in a good way. So I'm like, well,
here, let's just do this. So I'm like, fuck it. I order like a mid tier, big ass 70 inch TV,
which was stupid. But I didn't know what else to do with my cashback. And it's Christmas.
And I'm in consumer mode because corporate programming works. So I got this big ass TV.
And it's pretty cool. But I immediately have concerns. And my concerns are thus,
I did a ton of research getting this TV and I got the Vizio M Q7 series, which is like
their middle of the road. Like I don't need 120 FPS, I'm only going to be playing consoles and
watching movies on this, I'm going to play high frame, I'm going to play on PC. So that's not a
big deal. It just needs to do 60 4k 60, which it does. And it's big, it's a nice big display,
I got a nice soundbar with it. I've never had like a big TV, I've never had a 4k display,
I've never had a soundbar with really good audio. So this is like, you know, watching like movie
trailers on this, because I'm just like kind of digging through it. Like this is fucking great.
I'm going through all the settings, you know, turning off the fucking like soap,
proper effect garbage and all the preloaded terrible settings I have on these things,
turning all that off, whatever, getting it dialed in, but I'm a nerd. So I go through
all the settings and look at all the little things. And then I realized copyright 2019
Vizio, I'm like, wait a minute, wait a minute. This is a 2020 TV. This is the M Q7. This came out
like a couple months ago. This should not have a 2019 copyright on the firmware because it's new,
it came out this year. Like, what does that mean? That's strange. So I decided to start digging.
And this is when I realized I got fucked. Okay, because this TV is not the M Q7,
even though it's labeled M Q7. They rebadged their low end entry level 70 inch TV by adding like one
extra like quantum dot feature to the display, and then marketed it as the mid range. So this
is an entry level. It doesn't have any of the stuff that the mid range thing did, which I
actually wanted like really good HDR 10 brightness. It didn't have local dimming zones. It didn't have
it didn't have enough HDMI ports. The panel was not nearly as good quality because it was like
the V series panel at the M series panel. So like it was a lie. It was a fucking lie. It was not
actually the series it was it was saying it was it was like a lower tier garbage TV
that they wanted to sell to like dummies like me buying near Black Friday. So they tricked me.
Those motherfuckers. So I was pissed off about that. So it's sitting next to me right now. I'm
looking at it with disdain, but there's a really good return policy on Best Buy. So I'm swapping
it out with an actual M Q7. It's 65 inches out of a 70 inch, but this is like the actual one
with all the good tech that'll have a good picture and all that shit. So I can watch my Plex
and fucking god tier HDR can watch Thunderbolt fantasy in the best possible way with like booming
sound and a really good screen with HDR. Actually, I don't know if my torrents have HDR. If not,
maybe I'll find something to do. But Thunderbolt fantasy is cool to watch Thunderbolt fantasy.
It's it's like Thunderbirds are go on crack. It's by Urubuchi again. Music by
Hiryuki Sawano. Attack on Titan dude. And it's it's like puppets. It's like puppets,
but like the most ridiculous, over designed, like well choreographed puppets you've ever seen.
Oh my god. Tom. It's been saying I can't believe I slept until 350 p.m. You fucking idiot.
I got really drunk last night at because it was friend's mess. It was friend's mess dinner.
Baby friend. My friend cooked a goose and I ate it.
Good morning. Sunday morning. Yeah, it's definitely morning. Good afternoon. Sunday afternoon.
What I want to give you shit, but I didn't I didn't drink anything and I still woke up at
like 2 30. So I don't know. I can't I can't throw any shade because you're still doing
better than me. All things considered. Oh, how long you been going? A little over half an hour.
Okay. All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. What's what's up? What's on the docket?
What's on the what you what you been? What's what are you? What's going on, buddy? Not much.
I've just been talking about bullshit like video games and TV because that's that's all
my life's been for the last month. The worst the worst things. Yeah, just being a good old consumer.
How was your how was your holiday? Dumb. Nice. Yeah, it was pretty nice holidays around here
and never anything to pay attention to. So I forgot it even happened until you mentioned it.
I see. I did a I did a I hung out with my parents and my parents house and it was literally just me
and my mom and dad hanging out at their house for like two days.
It was fine. It wasn't it. It was it was okay. It was all right. Me and my dad got really drunk
also. I see a pattern for you. True. True.
Did you get your dad twisted? I guess I guess so. Yeah. Excellent. We watched we watched flushed away.
Which was which was really good actually believe it or not. I thought it was really good. Yeah.
That's my mom. My mom didn't like it. She thought the characters were ugly.
Oh, well, that's unfortunate. And then and then and then we and then we tried to watch
Escape from New York, but I think we got too drunk and we stopped in the middle.
I haven't seen that. I haven't I have tried to watch it once before
and and I didn't make it all the way through that time either. I don't know why.
Well, I was talking earlier about how I'm doing nothing but like abusing my VPN and stealing movies.
So I'm going to get escaped. Oh, good. I mean in a video game, this isn't happening for real in
Minecraft. Yeah. Yeah. Oh my god, I'm sweating. I'm having hangover sweats. I think is what's
going on with me. Ben, why do you never learn? Why do you keep doing this to yourself? Is it worth it?
This is life, Tom. Life is about making the same mistakes over and over again.
Oh my god. I'm so sweaty. Why? Why? Please help. Did you have water?
No. Oh, you fool. I have an open water bottle here, but it's like it's not drank at all. So I
probably just didn't drink it. What are we going to do with you, Ben?
Oh, refreshing.
You ever had goose? I've never had goose. One of my roommates procured a goose
and cooked it. The long story short is it almost tastes like beef. It tastes very beefy.
Really? Yeah, extremely greasy, extremely beefy.
So what he did was he roasted it in the oven, gave it like a Christmas herb rub,
things like cinnamon and allspice and nutmeg and things, and then he let the grease all
drip down onto trays of potatoes and cooked the potatoes in the grease. It was so good.
I ate so much. Yes. And then there was a... Fat Ben strikes again.
Oh god, I was going to mention, I was going to bring this up, that Fat Ben is officially back
and it's the worst thing. I weighed myself before I got in the car to go to my parents.
It was bad. I have gained back all the weight that I lost doing keto.
Oh, all of it. Yeah. Dude, this year's really bad. I started doing keto again like three weeks ago,
like the end of November. And then of course I had to break it for Christmas, which made me angry.
I told her, I'm keto, I'm dieting, I don't want to have anything like here's pumpkin pie
and ice cream and all this shit. I'm like, I hate you, die. So now I'm back on keto again.
And I feel a little bit better than I did in November, but November was the worst. I was
eating like shit for like four weeks straight. It was bad. You just feel worse. You feel
yourself becoming less human as you gain weight. It's the worst. Agreed. Yeah. Well, it's time for
me to get back on it. It's time for me to get serious, quit fucking around. But I have all
the leftovers. All the leftovers I have from the holidays are turkey and beef and goose.
And so that's all good. That's all good keto shit right there.
I'm thinking I'm going to combine keto with intermittent fasting to like double you. Yeah,
that's how you do it. You gotta really do it, right? Gotta do those speed heads, you know.
You like only eat during like an eight hour window or whatever. Yeah. Yeah. I like tried that a
little bit before. I had never got, I never was super serious about it, but they say it works
good. Oh, I just, you should just combine it with regular fasting and not eat for a week.
Yeah. Give it a shot. I was saying on my bonus podcast a couple of weeks back,
I was watching this video on like breatharians. Do you know what that is?
Yeah, I saw there was a video. Oh, was there like an H bomber guy video about it or
Sarah Zed or someone I watched the video on it. That's really interesting.
And the only thing I took away from that is that if you don't eat for two weeks,
you lose 40 pounds. I was like, that's a really good time investment ratio as far as I'm concerned.
No, it's all going to come from your, it's all going to come from your muscles and
your vital organs, and then you're going to die. That sounds like a bonus to me.
Hey, if you fast for one week, you lose 20 pounds. That's still a good deal in my book.
And if you fast for two weeks, you lose 40 pounds. And if you fast for three weeks,
you lose all the pounds. Right. You lose your life.
As you, as you shuffle off this mortal coil, as you end the nightmare of your own corporeal
existence, as you, as you move on, this is like a great ultimate abstract.
Exactly. Exactly. So sacrifices have to be made for the greater good. Can't have fat people.
No, it's unacceptable. And by fat people, I mean just me. I have no problem with fat people
unless the fat person is me, in which case I hate them. I same about you.
Yeah, yeah, I agree. Totally, totally fair.
No, man. Okay, my hangover sweating has, has subsided. I feel a little more normal.
I think I got, I like, I rolled, I rolled out of bed.
I rolled out of bed and I stood up and I sat down at my chair and I think the
action of moving made me a little nauseous. I got, I only got, I would have kept sleeping,
but I, my, my computer is just making a horrible squeaking noise, or it was. I don't hear it.
Yeah. I think the fan was going like,
and I didn't like it. So I, so I got up to click, kick it and make it stop.
It seems to have stopped on its own though. So good, good for it.
My computer is on all the time too. Like one of the fans is loose or something,
and you just have to like beat the shit out of it sometimes. I'm just like, I spent like
$70 on ultra quiet fans and I'm still dealing with this garbage. What a waste.
Every, every once in a while, it'll make a weird noise and then, and then I don't know.
And I think, what am I doing with my life? What's the, what's even the point?
There's no point, Ben. No, it's true. It's true.
Hey man, 2020 is over. By the time this comes out, it's going to be 2021.
Holy shit. You're right. I didn't even think about that.
Pretty fucked up, right? Actually, no, this is coming out on New Year's Eve, or on New Year's rather.
They have the last ones on Christmas.
Amazing. Hit Christmas and New Year's.
Last ones on Christmas. This one's New Year's. Happy New Year, listener. Happy. Welcome to,
welcome to the fresh hell that is 2021. What new horrors do they have in store for us?
I was saying earlier, I hope the, the Super Saiyan COVID doesn't come in and like fucking destroy us.
Oh, the UK one. Yeah. I was saying about that yesterday. I'm just like, oh no, not again.
I haven't read about it. I have, I've heard a little, heard that there's a new one.
Of course it would come from the Brits. Of course it would come from those fucking bongers.
Give me to get on so we can flog her for being a piece of shit.
Killer. Just fucking murder. Yeah, for sure.
Just dissing.
You have a good old fashioned lynching here on the PC.
Bring in the new year with the sacrificial lynching to kind of appease the COVID.
If only. If only. Yeah, okay. Yeah, I didn't, didn't think,
my sleeping, my sleep patterns have been really weird lately when I have,
when I have gone to bed at like a reasonable hour, I wake up like two hours later.
Like when I go to sleep at like midnight, I wake up at like three.
And then when I say, okay, well, time to just, time to sleep like during the day,
that doesn't happen. I sleep for like 12 hours. And that's what I did today.
And that's why it's 4pm and I'm, and I'm just up now. It's fucked up.
I wish it would just cooperate. I wish my circadian rhythm would just get on my fucking
level already, but it won't. Never will. Never does. I've never, I've never had a normal sleep
cycle. It sounds glorious, but I wouldn't know. Waking up in the middle of the day kills you.
It just feels, it feels like the day is already over. You just want to go back to bed. I'll just
start over tomorrow. Fuck it. It's already getting dark outside. It's already kind of dim.
Damn. Why did I even bother getting up? Right?
Oh no. You ever just wake, you ever, you ever rise back into consciousness and think, oh god,
I'm a, I'm a corporeal entity. Oh god, I'm a conscious being in a, in a universe that I,
that exists beyond myself and that I have, have no control over and, and, and I, and I,
and soon I will die. That's, that's just my life. You know, it's just like,
you just wake up, like someday I'm just not going to, someday that's just going to be forever.
That's it. That's it. Yeah. God damn it. Makes you think, really, really gets the noggin' job.
Yeah. Yeah. Maybe I should just get COVID and die. Maybe it's better. It's better that way.
No, you won't, you won't die. You'll just, you'll just permanently lose your sense of smell and taste.
And, and, dude, think how easy it would be to lose weight at that point if like food no longer
had power for you. Dude. Maybe getting COVID is a good thing. Hell yeah. It's like, yeah,
I'll have broccoli. It tastes exactly the same as anything else. I don't give a shit.
Perfect weight loss strategy. All right. COVID. We're starting the COVID-19 diet.
It's going to be called, you're going to lose the COVID-19. By getting COVID, you lose 19 pounds.
That's, that's the COVID-19. That's why we call it that. Exactly. We cracked the code, finally.
So, were you talking about, were you talking about like models or rigging puppets or something?
Some of that bullshit? I was talking about all sorts of things. Talking about games I was playing,
movies I was watching, TVs that I hate. All sorts of things. It's been a, it's been all,
it's been the best podcast. Best is in quotes. Yeah. I've been working on something,
but I can't say what it is. It's a mystery. You don't even know. I would,
we don't even know viewers. I would like, I would like very much, I would like very much to elaborate
but I won't because I have, I have things I could complain about. I have things I could say
about it. I have things, I have things to talk about with regards to it and things I've noticed
during the process, but I won't, I won't get into it. I won't get into it until it's done.
You're just building the intrigue. Building intrigue. That's right. That's right.
It's called, it's called hype. It's called marketing. I hope, I hope, well anyway,
I won't say any more about it. Lamal. So, Tom, do I hear wedding bells?
I don't think so. My uncle, my uncle called my dad while I was home and he's like talking on
the phone. They're talking about like, oh, how you been? Oh, I had, I had sinus surgery. Like,
oh, that's terrible. And my dad's like, oh, Ben's here and my uncle's like, oh, hey, Ben,
do I hear wedding bells? I'm like, what are you fucking talking about?
What are you fucking talking about, you weirdo? What is that even mean?
I don't know. I literally think he was merely inquiring, like, when the fuck are you getting
married, Ben? You useless prick. Like, what are you doing? That phrase is usually used after,
like, you've said that you, like, love someone, right? And they're like, like, it's too implied.
You love them so much, you must be getting married soon.
And even when my dad asked, like, uh, like, no, like, what do you mean?
It's not like my uncle, like, thought like I had a new girlfriend or something.
He just, he just didn't elaborate on why he asked that question.
That's so bizarre. It was very bizarre. It was almost as bizarre as when I did it to you.
Just a minute. Yeah, I'm glad that we were able to first like experience what you're talking
about first hand, you know, help with the immersion. Now you know. I empathize with the
story a lot more now that I've experienced it myself. Exactly. Exactly. Uh, my,
Nate, Nate, uh, made fun of me for, because I said we shouldn't do a Thanksgiving get-together
because COVID, but I nevertheless went to see my parents for Christmas.
But let me defend myself. My, my explanation is that the Thanksgiving thing is everyone
who's going to be traveling across the country, like Nate and Michelle would have been flying
in from Virginia. My, my sister or sister would have been traveling in from Kentucky,
you know, and then I also would have been there. And I think that it's, it's the traveling,
the dangerous part. I thought it was fine for me to go and see them just because like they would
just come to my house, I would just get in the car and it would be, and that would be it in terms of
like exposure to the outside world. And I'm extremely safe. I don't ever leave my house.
I think, I think I'm a very low risk individual. So that was my thinking there. I'm not a hypocrite.
Damn it.
The very least you change significantly.
Yes, definitely. So that's my excuse.
Sick. Have you been getting text messages from, from the Massachusetts government saying like,
don't go out for a Christmas this year. COVID is at risk in half of Massachusetts.
I'm just like, you're not my mom. Shut up.
No, no, I don't think I have been getting those, but I know, I already know.
The numbers are, the COVID numbers are insane. We thought, we thought they were bad early in
the year, but no, there's so much worse now in terms of like new, new cases.
Yeah, but it's all fake anyway.
Post Thanksgiving, the, yeah, it's all hoax. The post Thanksgiving spike is like,
it's funny. I saw like a graph, I saw a graph a few months ago that was like,
it showed like the Spanish flu, I think, and how it had like an initial wave and then sort of a
secondary wave. And then it's like, we are here. And then there's like a huge third wave that dwarf
the other two. And I was like, oh, haha. Nah, that's just like funny. That's just like a joke.
So that's like, that's probably how they actually, there's no reason to think that would actually
happen again. Super COVID coming in right on schedule. Super COVID though.
Oh my God.
So, you know, that's where we are. My dad's getting vaccinated pretty soon.
It's a lot lucky him. I guess I will as soon as I get the chance.
Then you just go out and be like, fuck you guys. I'm better than you.
Fuck you guys. I will put it in my tin. I'll go, I'll go on Tinder and put it in my bio. It's like,
hey, vaccinated. Like put that at the top of the top of things you'll like about me. Number one,
vaccinated. Number two, house trained. You got all my shots.
But you won't mention you have AIDS and that's how you get them.
No, no, no. Of course not. You can just assume that everybody on Tinder has AIDS.
That's true. Why else would you be there?
Yeah, it's your last resort.
I just got spooked. I just got spooked by a thumbnail. It was creepy. It had a face on it.
Yeah, on YouTube because I'm looking at YouTube. What are you doing on YouTube?
Wow, we're recording the podcast. I just had it open. I just had it open. I think I was
watching the new best of the worst last night. I think that was what I was doing
before I went to bed. Oh, the Christmas one. Yeah. I guess I only got 17 minutes and 30 seconds.
You don't? I like those. They're pretty hit or miss. They're hit or miss.
Like sometimes the tapes are just not interesting and you're just like, okay.
There was one really good tape in that one though, like the gun one. That was pretty fun.
Sometimes the movies they watch on the non-black spine ones are not very interesting.
Yeah. It feels like those ones are curated a little bit more.
All right, buddy. We're allowed to agree to disagree. Black spine versus no black spine,
COVID hoax versus real. These are things we can agree to disagree on.
These are things that need to be discussed in the free marketplace of ideas.
I like, I don't know. The black spine one had the octopuff, which I thought was very memorable.
Octopuff was pretty good. There's some hidden gems in the black spines,
but you got to wade through a lot of boring shit sometimes. I don't know.
It's, I don't know. I like just, the other ones, they're all like movies.
You know what a movie is and you know why a movie exists, but then the black spine ones,
they'll find things that are like instructional videos or like the Don Beverage seminar or whatever.
Well, let me clarify. Why does this even exist?
I like Wheel of the Worse, where they spin the wheel and there's a bunch of dumb movies,
but the black spine ones are the ones where you can just get a lot of the same kind of
low tier thing in a row because nobody knows what's on the tapes. Whereas even on Wheel of
the Worse, like they're slightly curated, so there's like a diverse mix of like weird looking
shit. I guess that's fair. Yeah, I just like it when they watch the really weird things that
make you go like, who bought this? Like why did anyone make this and put this on shelves?
The journey of how that tape got to where it is, got into their hands. Like who created it,
who thought it was good to purchase it? You know, what a mystery.
Oh, I got my new tablet. I got my new tablet and then I, because I, did I complain about my
stylus situation about how, okay, okay, well, I ordered the new stylus and I got it. It was here
waiting for me when I got back from Christmas and you know what? It worked. It works perfectly. I
had to fuck around with like the, I had to fuck around with settings and I had to fuck around with
drivers and stuff to get it to like actually recognize the pen, but it did eventually. So,
beautiful. Now I can, now I can, now I can draw again.
I can do art. The worst. Stupid, pointless. Working, making things. God, we're all going
to die anyways. It's even the point. It's true. It's true. Damn, you know, you know, that's true.
You know, maybe, maybe I should just watch TV all day like all the normies. Maybe they had it
right all along. Why should I make entertainment when people can entertain me? That's, that's
compelling. And you know, maybe I should just kill myself instead. You know, that, that would
save like, think of all the time you would save. Speedrunning, speedrunning life, baby.
Life any percent. Life any percent.
Now nobody, nobody runs life any percent because it's like, like the record, the record has been
cut. There's, there's all these hacks that have been found. The record has been cut down to like
zero, zero minutes and zero seconds. Yeah. Yeah. And the any, any percent run is just boring.
You got to try and make the run as long as possible. That's, that's the real,
that's the real end game for life. Speedrun. Slowly. What's, what's the name for like the,
there's like the category of speedrun. Is there like a,
there's like a minimum percent category, right? In some games. And it's like, I'm not a big speedrun
I think there's a channel called lowest percent. And it's like, a lot of its videos are explaining
like, like lowest percent categories for some games. And it's like, I watch speedrunning videos
all the time. I watch like speed docs and, and, and stuff like that. And, oh, what a,
Bismuth, I just, I started watching the Bismuth channel this week. And that's
like a, like summoning salt as videos explaining like the history of a speedrun. Bismuth will do
videos explaining like, what is the, what is the tech that's being used in like, you know,
the world record run of, you know, whatever game. Yeah, lowest percent is like, lowest percent is
like, yeah, you want to do it faster. You want to do the fastest you can. But if you can beat the game
by doing less of it, if you can, if you can cut out even more of the game, even if it's slower,
then it's still a better run. Cause the main goal is to do, do as little, and some, some games,
it makes sense in, in most games it doesn't. Yeah. Cause cutting out, sometimes cutting out
stuff is not faster, right? Some, sometimes it's faster to just do the game, but that's for nerds.
Gross. Who'd want to be a nerd? Imagine. No.
Shameful. Disgusting. Hell, yeah.
What else is, what else is going on? What else is going on in the world today?
I need to share this. I shared it on Twitter. Nobody cared.
I'm going to, I'm going to tell you, do you know, do you know Linus Sebastian, Linus Tech Tips,
the guy who talks about tech on YouTube and he's like, obnoxious. He's like a Canadian guy.
Linus Sebastian. No, I don't.
Well, viewers, if you, if you, because I was, I was up late last night, this is why I didn't
get up until like two 30 and I was testing out my Plex server, which I talked about earlier.
And I was watching this movie, this Tokusatsu movie called zero black blood. It's like a,
it's like a Japanese, like, you know, common writer kind of movie, but it's a spin off a series
called Garo. And the main villain is a white guy and it's just Linus Sebastian. Like it is him.
Is it literally him or does it just look exactly like him?
It's not, it's not literally him, but it looks exactly like him. He plays like an evil demon
and it was the funniest shit in the world. And I, it's, it's not, I did, I added him in the,
you should add him on, yeah, okay. You should add him on Twitter and get him to retweet you
saying you are the monster in this fucking Tokusatsu movie.
He won't do it, but still, the people need to know that if you want to watch Linus be an
evil womanizer demon that turns into a giant feathered CGI monstrosity by the end of the
movie. You can watch Zero Black Blood. He's in it and it's incredible.
Zero Black Blood. Let me see. I'm, I'm trying, I'm, oh, I think, I think I see him. Is he this
guy in the white tuxedo? Yeah, yeah, I linked it in the chat. Oh, okay. Whoops. Where am I? Where the
fuck am I? Yep, there he is. Well, good for him. You know, I'm glad he's, I'm glad he's getting
work. Living, living his best life. In between tech tips, fighting fucking Tokusatsu guys. That's
cool. Man, I was surprised. I really liked Flushed Away. It was really, it was a really good flick.
It was a very, I mean, it's your, it's your very normal, like, hero's journey, three act structure,
you know, rising tension, the hero's lowest point, followed by a, followed by a, the ah-ha moment,
and then the denowment or whatever. But you know, it was very, it was very charming. Little, little
film. I thought the jokes were pretty good. I liked the protagonists. I would recommend it. I used to,
I used to really like them. Or my dad was a really big fan of Ardman stuff while he, he loved Wallace
and Gromit when I was a kid. And then I, I filmed an episode of Pokemon over one, one time. I think,
I think like we were going to, we were going on vacation or something. And I think it was like
the, the Indigo Plateau arc was happening, was going to be airing on TV. And I didn't want to
miss it. So like I set the VCR to record the episode while we were gone. And I think I accidentally put
like the wrong trousers or something in the, in the VCR and filmed over it. And I think my dad was
pissed. And you know what? And you know what? Ash didn't even fucking win. So fuck. What was it all for?
Nothing. Nobody cares about Richie. Yeah. That was the beginning of a series of disappointments
with the Pokemon show is Ash got cucked. He never, he never won. He never won the fucking, it seems.
I think he does eventually like way the fuck later, like, like only like a year or two ago,
he actually finally won something. I heard that like he never, I heard that he never did. I heard
that, didn't, didn't Digi do a video or maybe it was a vlog or something talking about how like
the Pokemon got like, like the, like the, the show got like more and more, like the stakes of
the battles got like more and more epic in X and Y or not X and Y. It was, it was in black.
Or was it, was it an X and Y? I don't know. I don't know. But, but it just never, it never,
and it seemed like it was the perfect time to finally have Ash win the fucking, the fucking
Indigo Plateau League or whatever. And they just don't do it. I don't know. That's what I heard
anyway. Imagine, imagine caring about Pokemon in 2020. Pretty cringe. I, I just think, I just
think a little boy me would be satisfied to know that eventually Ash did become the very best.
Some closure. Yeah. But oh well. But oh well. And then they like really like rebooted it for
Sun and Moon, I think. Like rebooted it with like a new Ash, right? I don't think it's a new Ash.
I think it just went to, they like changed the art style significantly and all that kind of shit.
I, I thought that like, I thought that they like changed the, it was like a new continuity or something.
Did they really? That's what I thought. That'd be wild if so.
I don't know. Viewers, let us know if you've been, if you can enlighten us.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh, thank god you're here. We're floundering. We're floundering.
We're so desperate for content. We're talking about Pokemon of all things. Oh god.
Yeah. Hey, hey, when, is this 2021 right now?
Yeah, this will be, this will be out on the day. Wow. Wow. The nightmare's over. Everyone,
COVID's over. It was a hoax all along. Everyone go out and spit in your neighbor's mouth.
Oh, I can't wait. I've been, I've been dreaming about this my day for the whole year.
We've all been dreaming about this day since the last day of Radcon 4. We all found out
shit was bad and it had arrived and we were worried that we were going to be able to get home.
Let's, let's just take, let's just take a stroll down memory lane about how like COVID
became like serious at Radcon 4 and that we all,
After we had made a bunch of jokes and all of our shit making fun of coronavirus
and they're all going to age terribly when they all come out.
No, no. Can you imagine, just from, I just, you know, you know exactly what I'm talking about.
I know exactly what you're talking about. I can't wait. I can't fucking wait for that
shit to come out and be like so weird in hindsight. So tone deaf. It's like so bad.
Well, whatever, coronavirus, probably nothing. It's going to be great. It's going to be great.
And remember how like, like the last day of Radcon, we all, we all had a big meet up. We all had a
big meet up with everybody and we all, we all went out and played fucking laser tag and we're
all like running around and sweating in a room together and like picking up this, like all
these plastic shit that like kids have been like, scrubbing their hands on. We did. We did. It was
like the worst thing you could possibly do. I feel like at the time, it really was like early
enough that that wouldn't have been a problem because I don't think anyone had it after that,
after that exchange. I mean, you never know. Maybe one of them did.
You know, I mean, it doesn't seem, it doesn't seem like anybody got it, but
but like easily, easily we could have been spreading it at the time.
Yeah, we could have had the first super spreader event.
It's just really funny how like what we were doing was like the worst thing to possibly do,
like three days after we did it, you know, like that shit would have been not allowed.
And it's just like, God. And then like, we're all like waiting with baited breath. Like,
are they going to close down the flights? Is Gabe going to be able to get home? Like, we don't know.
Oh, yeah, laser tag arena for a little while. They burned they burned down that laser tag arena
afterwards today. I mean, that's because we're super spreading. Oh, because it was super
spreading is the last known place where the PCP were just burn any place where the PCP are.
Any place we've been. We're in. Yeah, they burned they burned the Radcon 4 house.
Shame. Oh, man. Yeah. Hey, it was a nice house. Radcon 4 was fun.
Can we just reminisce about how fun Radcon 4 was? It was fun. It definitely like as fun as it was.
Every time I think about it, I think nothing happened, though. It was so quick. It was like
a slap in the in the face. Yeah, I think Radcon 5 longer. I think that's the lesson we've learned.
I agree. I don't know so much. It needs to be longer and it needs and it needs to be less
tightly scheduled. Well, it was it was only so I mean, you remember Radcon 2?
Or even yeah, right on to a right on three. I think right on three more more. So we had about
the same amount of time staying there as it as in Radcon 4. And even then, people were showing up
a few days into Radcon 3. I think Ben, you were like a few days late or something. Yeah. And yeah.
So we couldn't do any of the lectures, any of the group projects until everyone was here.
And it's like somehow that feels like we did so much more stuff.
And it didn't feel like anything. It's very strange time. And like, I don't exactly know why.
I think it might be really just those two days where we were all there on Radcon 4,
filming the OVA and and other such things that we needed sunlight. And there wasn't going to be a
lot of that weather wise, weather forecast. So we had to get a lot of filming done immediately.
And it took up two full days of like extreme filming. And we were in costume and it was a lot of
sweat, a lot of falling over. A lot of work. Yeah. A lot of work. Yeah. It was definitely more packed
with stuff Radcon 4 was. And then after that, there was a lot of downtime. After that, it was like
everybody was like, oh, shit, I don't know any how I don't have any notes for my lecture. I got to
do all of them right now. And that was the Radcon 4. That's what it feels like.
Maybe we were also probably could have made it feel. Yeah. You know, we made a lot of money on
those streams, actually. We got a lot of donations. It got really drunk also. Yeah, it was bad.
But it was very fun. As much as I harp on like how quick it was, it's only because I wish it was
longer, because I wanted to do more stuff. I wanted to be there and on the beach. It was so fun.
It was cool. I got like, I mean, we could I got mad. I got like actually high for the first time
with Digi. It was really funny. We could have just streamed saying stupid shit.
If it had been a week longer, we could have just streamed more. Like we wouldn't have had to like
do any any more stuff. We could have done the same amount of stuff, plus a bunch of streams and a
bunch of other bullshit. And I don't know, let's plays and stuff. It would have had to be in a
week earlier rather than the like the like the game. Let's play from Radcon 2.
Yes, right. On 2. One. Yeah, that was a that was a really good one. But I'm just realizing. Yeah.
It could not have been a week longer because Munchie had he only had those two weeks off from
school. And so that was what we were well setting it. Well, Munchie Munchie just needs to drop out
of school, obviously. Yeah, whatever. But like, I feel so bad for Munchie about the whole school
situation. Yeah. Have we have we talked about on here about how we were all totally right
that Munchie shouldn't have gone to school? I feel like you can't even do a victory lap on that,
just because like none of us knew this was going to happen.
Yes, kind of. I mean, we didn't know how we didn't even know how right we were going to be.
But covid has made it like even more. Munchie would be getting what he wanted out of the
experience if this wasn't happening. Woody, though. I mean, in his mind, I don't I don't I
can't tell you if like he would have been satisfied, but like he would be getting what he said out to
go get, which is like a personal hands on experience and making connections with people,
which is what he said he wanted out of it. That's all it's such a scam. School is such a
fucking scam. The youth have to learn these harsh lessons even their own. No, that's no,
that's so dumb. They don't have to learn the harsh lessons. They can just learn. They don't have
to learn the hard way. But like, nobody wants to agree with an adult. That's the thing.
Fucking adults are always stupid. Yeah. That is that's fair. That's fair. I don't know. You know,
it's like why why do you know if if something like this, right, if something like covid can show up
and just like ruin your school experience, right, can just take away all the stuff that like is good
about it. It's like, oh, it's not the education. It's the it's the connections. It's the hands
on experience or whatever. Then like, oh, okay. So what you're telling me is that it's it's pointless
and it's and it's fake and it's a scam is what you're saying. And covid has merely has merely
highlighted that fact. It hasn't it hasn't made it into some like fake. It was it was fake all along.
In my opinion, I mean, in my opinion, this merely this merely exposes what was already true.
The education has always been a joke in a post internet world. You can learn everything you
can learn in school online for free. Yes. That's indisputable. Yeah. But if you're going there
to meet people and make connections, then you can't really do that online to the same degree.
I think the thing is that sure that you can't do that online. But the the cost of that experience
is like very antiquated with what the internet can get you.
What what a disaster. What a disaster of pounds.
Yeah. What what a disaster that like that's that the only way like like there is no there's no like
alternate way to do that, right? Right? There's no there's no it's like, oh, well, I want to,
you know, make connections with people and, you know, have a fucking experience or whatever.
But I don't want to pay a million fucking dollars and and live in a dorm and attend classes. Like
I don't want to do those very specific things, but I want that other experience and there's no
alternative. And and and why? Why is that? I guess the alternative is just like go
capitalism is in the world. You just have to like go out into the world and just talk to people
and just like be outgoing. You just need to be sure. Sure. But the weird cool guy nearby the
university who just hangs out with all the students. He doesn't actually go. You need to be that.
That's a creep. You're describing a weird creepo. Whoever went. No, no, he's cool. You don't
understand. I said he's cool. He's not cool. He's just being cool. That's not cool. You know,
who did that? Oh, Steve Jobs. Steve Jobs dropped out of school, but like sat in on a bunch of classes
anyway, learned about typography and all this cool shit. And then he made the Mac dope. He just
like stole that. I feel like if I just hung out near a school, I would be arrested.
Somebody would find some reason to arrest me because you're your fat Ben right now. Once
you're not fat Ben anymore. Oh, that's true. Yeah, that's true. Okay. All right. Now I really
got to lose that weight. How bad is fat Ben right now? How? How? What is the percentage like
overtaken of him? Fat Ben is. Fat Ben is about. Are we at a game back?
Uh, right. You mean Radcon? Was it three that I was fat? Radcon three was what made you start
keto? Yeah, I think I weigh about as much as I did at Radcon three. So, you know, it's bad.
I don't, okay, I don't think I look as fat. I don't feel like I look as fat as I did then,
but I weighed myself the other day and I weighed about as much. Do you still have the beard right
now? No, I have no beard. Oh, no. Some of it might be illusory. Like some of it might be water weight
or I might like I was weighing myself with clothes on. So like actually if I like started
dieting, I might be down to like, I might be down another like five or 10 pounds than what I
think I weigh. So I might not quite be that level, but it's pretty close. Yeah, I've gained like,
yeah, I lost like the difference between fat Ben and skinny Ben. It's like about 50 pounds.
And actually there is no skinny Ben, just fat Ben and normal Ben. It's like about 50,
it's like about 50 pounds. And so I'm up, I'm up almost that 50, at least 40. It's fucked up.
Yeah, it's fucked up. Dude, COVID fucked everything up, man.
I mean, you were doing well under COVID with keeping on keto and not being fat Ben.
I kept on keto, but yeah, I gained, I did gain a little weight. I gained like maybe 20 pounds back
over during quarantine, but while I was still doing keto. And then I think when I went off keto,
I gained another, I've gained like another 20 or so since then. I was like, I was like slowly
putting weight back on while I was still keto. And then it, and I was just like, I kind of wanted
to lose it again, but it wasn't urgent. But now I feel urgent. I'd like to get it off by, I'd like
to be back down to normal Ben weight by like April or so. I think I could do that. If I'm,
if I do like the keto intermittent fasting thing, it should be doable. It should be pretty good.
Yeah. Hey, it's going to be, it's going to be hype. Yeah.
What happened over Christmas Day? Did you talk about that already?
No. Yeah, I said, I was talking about that. I went and hung out with my parents.
Uh, and I, then we had friends giving here at my apartment and my friend cooked a goose
and I carved it. Uh, and it was delicious. And there was a dessert he made. Let me tell you about
this dessert he made. He made like a, like a, I don't know what you call it was like a chocolate,
like sort of roll of like a roll of like sponge cake and some kind of like chocolate ganache.
And it was rolled up into a log, like a yule log. Yeah. It was, yes, it was,
it was rolled up into a yule and it even like, it was even textured to look like bark.
It was very nice. There's a fun classic. I'd never seen something like that before,
but it was cool. Yep. So eight goose and a log. What'd you do?
Um, fucking, we ate a turkey and I was, I can't, I don't know. There's nothing really to say.
I guess I get, I could talk about the, the presence I got. I was thinking about, uh, like
fucking AVG and DVDs. I got those. I saw you tweeted the picture of those.
What did I get? I didn't, I didn't like get anything because I, oh, my, my mom got me more,
um, got me more, uh, Copic markers because she always, she always buys me a bunch of Copic markers
every holiday and she asked me what I needed, what colors I needed. And because I had finally
used my Copic markers this year to do all the like drawings in people's, uh, Vapors copies.
I actually, I actually was like, oh wow, I finally got some use out of these. And this,
and this time I knew I was like, oh, I don't have nearly enough like light blues and light
purples and light greens. I was, I, I have only like medium shades. I need pastels and she got
me a bunch of like light blue, light purple, light greens and it's very, very good, very good. Uh,
very exciting. Yeah, I don't, I don't know why, but I can't remember anything. Like am I brains
gone? Like my mind is addled for some reason. Christmas was just, I know why I can't remember
anything. Oh, we walked the dog and then we came back and we had breakfast and then we stopped
having breakfast and then later we had Christmas dinner and presents were involved at some point.
Do you open presents in the afternoon? We open them after breakfast or like early because it's...
Oh, okay. Yeah. Okay. You gotta open them in the morning. Um, I know why I don't remember
anything and it's because I was plastered. Uh, I don't remember what happened last night
when I went to sleep. I think I was watching Best of the Worst Christmas 2020. I think
that's what I was doing, but I don't know and hopefully I never will.
Who's more dangerous to drink than a fat Ben?
Fortunately, we don't have to choose. We can have, we can have both and that's what we did.
That's what, that's what, literally that's what happened last night and it was a real,
a real nightmare and it was really the worst of both worlds.
Oh boy. I'm probably, I'm going to go and I'm going to eat some of those leftover goose fat
potatoes and that'll be like the last non keto meal I ever have.
Damn. It was good. It was fun while it lasted. It was nice, but now it's gone.
It was fun, but look what it cost.
Look what, yes. At what, at what cost? Look what, look what it's wrought.
Looks down at body. Ugh. Disgusting.
Adios. Here's, here's what's good. I learned this Christmas that I like champagne.
I drink it and I'm like, yeah, you know what? It's, it's not as bad as I thought it was
because I've never really been much for wine. Everyone would make fun. Yeah, wine's gross.
I hate wine. Actually, I was drinking it last night, lol, but I still don't like it.
Everyone would make fun of me because I would go to the liquor store and I would buy two bottles
of sparkling, of sparkling, brute cuve and then drink them alone in my room.
And that was, that was one of my favorite, that's been one of my favorite quarantine
activities this year. And everyone, and everyone's thinks it's funny because it's,
because it's a girl drink, but you know what? It's tasty.
There's no such thing as girls drink.
You just, there's no such things as girls. You just drink whatever is you want.
Yeah. Wine is, wine is gross and the fact that it's not carbonated, I think,
can make you like drink it too fast. The worst hangovers I've ever had have been wine hangovers.
They're horrible. Yeah, they just sort of have, I don't know, it's like, oh, it's sort of similar
to fruit juice, but like not good taste, but you know what? It's got a hint of some sort of fruit,
so I guess, you know, I'll drink it like a, like a normal drink. Just guzzle it, just chug it down.
Because like sipping it, I don't want to have this taste in my mouth that long, I just gotta chug
it down, like blip, blip, blip, blip, blip, and then you're done. Then you're fucking toast.
And then they say, hmm, some more, and I'm like, no, no, no. No, no, please, no, please.
Oh, we didn't make, you know what, you know what was missing from my holiday was, was eggnog.
We, we did, my parents did have some pumpkin eggnog that I had like a little paper
shot glass of, because I just wanted a taste of it, because that's, that stuff's good, but you
don't, you're just, no. Most holidays, we make like, we make like hard cider in a crock pot,
or we make like, or do like rum eggnog and a thing, and you're, and everyone drinks it out
from a ladle, everyone ladles it, but we didn't do like a party this year. So I guess nobody did that.
And now that I remember that we didn't have that, I feel it's absence. That's a holiday tradition
that I like, and it's gone. It's gone. COVID took everything from me. They took my eggnog.
Fucking egg frog. I've never had eggnog in my life. What the fuck? Yeah. What the fuck? I heard
someone describe it recently as cold cum, and now I do not want to try it ever. What the fuck?
It's no. It's not like that at all. It's not even. I think I've asked this question before,
and I keep forgetting because it's so, I don't care. So I guess I won't ask again what it is.
It's, it's like a, it's like a, I guess it's got egg in it. It's like a, it's like a cream. It's
like you drink an egg. It's like a, it's like a milkshake. It's like a milkshake, but it's
flavored with like, with like nutmeg, I think is the, is the flavor. And it's good. I don't know.
It's just a good milkshake and it's great. I love eggnog. It's the best. I don't think it's keto
best. Oh, you know, I'll bet you could make a keto variant. I bet if you just, yeah, if you just
left the sugar out and you just replaced it with like stevia, you could absolutely make keto eggnog
because it's made of like cream and eggs. There you go. No problem. Is, is egg keto? Hell yeah.
Yeah. Eggs are keto. Yeah. Egg is, egg is keto. Okay. Milk, milk is not keto, but I bet if you
just use more cream and less milk, you could make like a, you could make a version that's low enough
sugar that you could, that you could have some and it would still be keto. I think it would be totally
doable. I mean, I used to just chug. When I was, when I was really hardcore keto, I would just chug
a heavy cream out of the bottle or out of the carton. So, you know, I could just make it with
all cream and it'd be fine. That's, that's the kind of person I wouldn't want to let on my
college campus. Someone who's just sitting on the side drinking heavy cream right out of the carton.
Those, those are the days I have to, funnily enough, that was like the least fat Ben was the,
was the like just chugging heavy cream out of the carton Ben. So I have to go back to that.
I have to like reclaim my lost animal nature. It sounds disgusting, but scientifically, if you're
burning ketones, that's just, that's just you're not, you're not getting any fatter. It's, it can't
argue with it. I can't wait. I can't wait to piss on the keto strip and have it turn purple again.
I'm going to feel so superior to all of you. That is the closest thing to a fucking glucose.
The closest thing to ascending to Godhood is doing that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Ben's saying
it's like a, it's like a real Scott Pilgrim character.
Like I'm imagining sitting, sitting on the side drinking heavy cream in front of a university
trying to be cool. Not that you actually do that. And yeah. And you're with your shirt.
I'm just being cool shirt. Link in the description. I should,
I should act, I should actually get that shirt. You're, you're, you're making me actually want
that shirt. The shirt is really, I got, I finally, I went back, I went back to reality.
Oops, there goes gravity. And I bought the, I bought the T-faps. Let's do the slime war again
shirt. I don't know why I just wanted it. Like I wanted to get one back when it was like relevant
back during the old RFCK hiatus that the, that caused it to exist. But I just thought about
and I was like, I really wanted that shirt back then, but I never got it. I'll get it now.
And I did. And now I have it and, and I'm too fat for it. So I better lose some weight so I can
wear it. Yeah. Fat Ben has taken everything from me. Fat Ben has ruined my life.
When I was like hardcore keto, I was actually able to finally like get into like medium shirts
comfortably. I was always like either large or extra large. And it felt, it literally felt like
ascending to a higher level of Christ consciousness. It was, it was so good. I let it all slip away.
There's nothing worse. There's nothing worse now than like putting on a shirt that I know
fit me when I was lighter and it doesn't, and it's not comfortable. And I just, I just, the
self-loathing is just unbearable. Putting on a pair of pants that you needed a belt for and you
don't need a belt for it anymore. It's like, you want to just use that belt and just hang
yourself with it. Cause it's just like, what's even the point of being alive?
It's, it's a nightmare. Well, I'd like to say that I cannot relate at all to that.
Yeah. I know. Fuck you. I know. I hate you. I hate you so much. Fuck you. Get the fuck out of here.
Get the fuck out of here. Go on. Get. No. Go on. No, I'm, I'm, I'm dodging the broom.
You're trying to brush me out. Are you trying to like, are you trying to like gain weight?
Are you trying to like put on? Who would ever want to do that? I need to.
Put on, put on girl fat. Kind of. Is that, is that the plan? Yeah. A little bit, a little bit.
I heard, I saw, I think it was, oh, who was it? I saw someone on Twitter who was saying they were
trying to gain weight to get, to get the girl fat. I think it was, I think it was Izzy from,
the, from the, from the pizza party podcast, who, which doesn't, which I don't know,
where's the podcast? I don't know. I think she was saying like she wanted to like,
she was trying to gain, gain girl fat. And I thought that was funny.
I mean, you don't need to gain necessarily. It's just like under HRT, fat redistributes
to the hips and stuff. So if you have a, you know, depends on your genetics, I guess,
what, where it goes exactly, but that'll happen. Lamal. Lamal. So if you want huge
tits you need to eat, I guess, I don't know how that works. Gross.
Being a stick figure is my ideal body type. I can't do it because I'm not built that way,
but it doesn't change the fact that I want to just be like 2D. Just, just nothing. I just
want to seize existing. I just want to, I just want to look like Goku.
I'm too, I'm way too lazy. I want to be like Luffy, like pre time skip.
Well, like with a fucking eight pack.
When he was, no, before when he was just a little twig man, that's what I want to be.
We just a little bit of a strong, strong the whole time.
Maybe, maybe he wasn't drawn like that. I can't remember.
I mean, he has like stick arms, but he has like, I think he's like a little bit of a define,
define chest. I could do that, but I just don't, he has like,
aesthetically, I would be totally fine looking like that, but I have no illusions that I have the
discipline to like actually work out to that degree. It just isn't going to happen.
That's really, it's really funny. It's really funny that that's your ideal body type.
It's like a stick. I just want to disappear. No, no definition whatsoever.
Yeah, yeah. You just hold out your hand and it just keeps going.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's, that's the, that's the bonus.
It's got to be, it's got to be powerful. You got to have that, you got to have that,
that masculine V shape. You got to have the, the, the broad, the broad shoulder look.
The thing longer. You got to have the, you got to have that big dick.
Yeah. That's my ideal body type. My ideal body type, big penis, please.
My ideal body type. Everything else is negotiable.
Can I have three legs?
Thank you. Yeah. Thank you very much. Oh God. There's a, there's a, there's a,
there's a thermos here on my desk of a mysterious substance and I'm pretty sure that it's probably
sea ice and coke. Should I drink it? No. You don't know what it is. Oh God. It's come.
Okay. It's, it's sea ice and coke. It's sea ice and coke. Oh God. Fat Ben wins again.
Oh, it's, oh, it's flat. Oh, it's flat and it's gross. Fat Ben is just, what did you gain from
that? What did you gain from that? Nothing except more weight. What if I just, what if I just drank
all of it right now and just got drunk here on the procrastinator's podcast? What if I just did
that, huh? Good night, good night everybody. Ben, it's fat Ben speaking now. You have to,
you have to resist. What would you do? You can't stop me. You can't stop me. Ben, you were just
saying how, how you want to be powerful. You want to be powerful Keto God and now you're just
immediately caving to pressure at the first possible opportunity. Pressure that no one is
really putting on you. Alcohol's Keto. Alcohol's Keto. That's cute. Sort of, technically.
If I drink it first enough and then pee it out, it's not, it's Keto. It's like it never happened.
It's, it's, it's, it's, it's, there's a science to it. There's a, there's an art. There's a
technique. It's, if you actually, if you, if you chew your food properly, you can, you can make
things more or less Keto. You can control their Keto levels through, through breathing exercises.
I prefer breathing exercises. It's strange, but it's true.
Mmm. Yes. Excellent. Mmm. Yes. Delicious.
Did anybody see my fucking Game of the Decade video I made?
Game of the Decade? I saw it, but I saw that you posted it, but I haven't watched it.
It's an hour and 30. It's an hour. Oh my God. I think it was because I saw,
I think of you, Tom, on the IM Games Twitter talking about Game of the Decade or something.
I thought, hmm, that was a good idea. That was a tweet from last year. Oh, well, that's,
I think that's probably like, I made a mistake, but I did, I didn't do it last year, I don't think.
So this year I talked about games that came out, um, in the decade. I don't, I get the decade
wrong. So, but it's 2010 to 2020. Fuck yeah. I, yeah. So it's a long rambling. You did a Game of the
Decade video and you got the decade wrong. Yeah, but, um, I could just do it next year as well.
I'll just keep doing it. 2011 to 2021. That would be pretty funny, actually.
They'll have the same, they'll be like the same games.
Some of them. They probably have the same winner. Yeah. Can I ask what the Game of the Decade was,
or would that be spoiling it? Um, I mean, it's a long video. If you go listen to it,
if you want to hear, basically it's like a tournament bracket thing where I have the,
I pit the games randomly against each other. And then I deliberate to myself, hmm,
is Fallout New Vegas better or worse? The Dark Souls? Hmm. What are the Bennett pros and cons?
Like you can't compare games like that. It's stupid, which is why I thought it would be funny.
And so I did that for all of them. And I think, uh, I can spoil the winner was Minecraft, because,
you know, because, you know, wait, that doesn't come out this decade.
The, the, the, um, came out officially in 2010.
It technically, the, the Alpha was in 2009.
Okay. I'm pretty sure. I looked at the thing. Wow.
Um, I believe it. I guess, I guess it just feels so much older than that. It feels ancient.
Yeah. It feels like it's always been there. If Minecraft doesn't count,
then the second place winner was Pokemon Go.
Really? Yep. That's shocking. That is, that is a shocking pick. I think you'll make a lot of
people upset with it. Yeah. Um, so go watch the video. I mean,
I can't wait to go dislike this video right now. The video is like very like stupid and like ill
thought, ill prepared, ill thought out. I was just like game of decade. Hmm. What do I think?
I guess nobody would care to know. So I won't put any effort into making the video about it,
but I want to make a video about it. And it was just like all of the games I have played
and enjoyed, uh, those were the only ones in the running. If I played a game and I didn't
care for it, it's not on there. So there's a lot of games that just have never been,
were not on in the running.
Indeed. Indeed. I'm looking at these games. I played
like two or three of them that's on here. Maybe four.
Criminal. Let me, let me see here. Let me, let me just take a, let me just take a quick look.
I'm judging your game. Just choose. Please do. The best, the best game on here is
what the fuck is from dust? What the fuck is Trover saves the universe? That's, that's Justin
Roiland's VR game where you're, he's Justin Roiland and he says, ah, ah, geez, you gotta,
you gotta save the universe. And I'm like, okay, it's very funny. Oh, it's the best game.
Lisa, Lisa, the joyful on here, I think Lisa wins. Lisa, the painful got very close, got to fourth
place, I think. Wait, you put, you put Lisa and Lisa, the painful and Lisa, the joyful as
separate entries. No, the first Lisa, I didn't put on there because I didn't feel it was as good of
the others as the other two. Okay, I, I just, I disagree. I disagree with this
because I think Lisa, the painful Lisa, Lisa, the joyful is DLC for Lisa, the painful. So really,
they should be one entry and they should win. Yeah, as I said, takes the video really poorly
planned stupid video. Like the longer, the longer I think about what it is, the more cracks and like
complete inaccuracies and flubs and like, this is just wrong. Why would you do it like this?
I didn't have the bracket like, have like a loser's bracket so that we could figure out
of the losers who wins. Just some people get eliminated too early. Single elimination.
Yep. This is like everything that could have been like, like not, not quite correct about it is,
is the case. Nice. Cool. But if you like listening to me ramble on about stuff,
then there's that.
You know what? I do. That's why I'm here listening to the procrastinator's podcast.
The best podcast. Actually, the best podcast on the internet.
Ted interwebs. Best game of the decade was Slime Ranch. The best game of the decade was Endless War,
a free MMO playable entirely within Discord server.
Uh, you know, I would have put that on there, but I didn't like it. It sucks. Game sucks.
Fuck. No, fuck. No, fuck. No.
Too hard. It killed me.
No, I'll, no, I'll kill you.
No, you're gonna die.
I rage quit so hard that I destroyed all Slime.
Hell yeah.
No, you didn't. You didn't do that. You can't.
Oh, god.
It's impossible.
Do we have anything else left to say? We're floundering right now.
We are floundering. I'm, I feel kind of sick from drinking that, from drinking that,
that, that's, that's soda water.
Really? That was a bad idea and you shouldn't have done it. Wow.
No, no, it was good. It was a good idea. It was great. I'm glad I did it.
But I am ill now. I am feeling terrible. So, you know, whatever.
I mean, it's not really much to talk about other than like, I guess I've been continuing to clean
up my room and I got to these boxes that have like toys in them that I was like, I don't want to
throw these away. They're funny. And it was basically just a lot of like rubbery, floppy
dinosaurs that you can squeeze and, and like weird fish and snakes and spiders. And I was like,
I don't ever take these out. Why do I keep them? So I've been
packing them up in a box. I'm going to toy story them over to a charity shop or whatever.
That's what you call.
I'm going to toy story three though. I'm going to fucking toy story three those bitches.
As in like throw them into a fucking furnace.
No. No, no, no.
I found, I found all my old Yu-Gi-Oh cards. I was like, ha ha. Look at them sitting there.
Oh, my, my mom, my mom, she's always, she's always trying to like sell our old stuff,
like our old, like baseball cards and stuff, which I like had, I guess, for some reason.
And I think they're all worthless. I don't think that any of them are ever worth anything.
I think, I think she's tried to sell our old Pokemon card collection and, you know,
that's all worth nothing. Even, even though I have a Charizard,
even though I have a Charizard, it turns out it's not actually worth that much.
It's not actually that rare. Just everyone just wanted it because it could do 100 damage.
And everyone thought it was cool.
It does.
First edition.
No shortage of them.
CGC rated.
No.
You're worth money.
CGC rated? What's that?
It's like when you like send them in to get them like rated so they can be like, oh,
like, like a professional like card thing, like Riggs, how good the condition is,
and like make some more valuable or some shit. I don't know.
I see. I see. No, it's not first edition. It's just normal.
It's just normal.
Friends.
Just normal Charizard.
Imagine.
Piece of shit. Yeah. I don't, I don't know.
My family threw out all my Pokemon cards and they refused to admit it to this day,
even though they don't exist anymore.
Why?
I had so much shit.
Why would they do that?
Because I don't know.
Why would they do such a thing?
I don't know. I don't know if it was on purpose or it was an accident.
They deny it, but they don't exist anymore.
So it's a travesty.
Tragic.
It really is.
Maybe there's a hidden memory of you having a poke and meltdown.
Maybe you just let them all on fire.
Yeah.
I did fire spin for 100 damage to all my cards.
How could you?
That's fucking criminal.
That's terrible.
Should we do voicemails?
We should do voicemails.
All right.
Okay.
Let's, let's, let's, let's go.
Let's go.
Are we ready?
I see that.
I think the first one we got is the jungle man.
I believe so.
Are you ready?
Nope.
Hang on.
Faster.
Okay.
Speakpipe.com slash, well, there's not many of them.
Oh, you're right.
It's a small miracle.
There's, there's like a, there's like a normal number.
If you can even believe it.
Okay.
Wait, hold on.
Why is my computer taking so long?
Just to download.
Thanks.
Not even, these are not even.
Your internet.
Good.
These voicemails aren't even good.
You don't need to download them.
I'm on the site.
We can listen like.
Okay.
All right.
I guess you'll have to download them at some point, but yeah.
First one is called the jungle man.
Also, I haven't forgotten when Ben said rule of thumb.
Okay.
Thanks.
Three, two, one, go.
You guys talked about The Simpsons last episode,
and I just wanted to recommend Jonas Chakas previously known as
Cuck Philosophy's video called The Simpsons and the Death of Parody.
Ben would come on this shit.
It goes into how capitalism inevitably leads to shows like The Simpsons
and how it creates ironic entertainment,
which is similar to awareness of exploitation,
yet still doing actions that support exploitations.
But since you know it's exploitation, it's fine.
Or creating things that make fun of capitalism or of anti-establishment views,
but still make a boatload for their owners, shareholders,
and the word pastiche, which was coined by Jameson,
Dude Fox, which basically means parody without jokes.
Simpsons went from social commentary through parody
to just referencing reality and that being the joke.
It leaves off it's high from a generation ago as a zombie.
You can also see the zombification and a lot of other things
like superhero movies, picture play games,
the Assassin's Creed, Cod, etc.
Go watch it.
I am the jungle man.
I literally watched
Okay, cool.
Thanks jungle man.
I watched that video
on Christmas Eve.
I went to bed.
No, no, it was the day after.
I watched the video last night,
or no, two nights ago in bed, and it was really good.
Cuck Philosophy is a really good channel.
I think he's changed the name to like CCK philosophy.
I don't know why.
I wish they didn't, but they did.
You too probably.
Was it because people were calling him a cuck?
And it was like, no, you don't get it.
You don't understand.
I'm not a cuck.
It's the name.
Perhaps.
Also, I'm noticing that I have like a burn on my hand,
and I didn't know, and it looks painful,
but it doesn't feel like anything.
So I guess it's fine.
A short subburn.
Ben, stop.
I don't know what it is.
You have to stop this.
Is it a bruise?
Or it kind of looks like a burn,
but it doesn't feel like anything.
God, but you really shouldn't have drunk that, whatever it was.
I think it's destroying you from the inside.
God, I hope so.
I hope you're right.
Next, next voicemail is called The Quest for Cold Corona Episode One,
Bat Dong.
Three, two, one, go.
And I got some city warehouse.
The middle is up to his evil ways.
What's the valuables in the truck, boys?
Grammatically crushing just about silly like a boss.
Well, it's Batman and his Bat Dong.
Stop saying I'm a Bat Penis, brother.
So I have cry-fighting zone, but I can kill my right-out of function.
Never mind that.
Minions, attack.
Batteries, I choose you.
Go.
Ow, my eye, my leg, my penis.
Your cry-fat bone predicts the fight.
Brother, you can go to Ogham without a penis.
The choice is yours.
No thanks, Bat Dodo.
I plan on ruling the world.
And I rule the world.
You need a penis?
True, but I'm still taking you down.
Wait, Bat Dodo, I have a hostage.
A PCP member hostage.
Impossible.
I say no, PCP members.
And this is very happy with her new Android dong slash plus.
You say it all but one.
Look at my ass, Batman.
Who's been here the whole time in the furnace room?
You know what it means?
Yes, Batman.
I'll save you.
Who could really possibly have it in his clutches?
Batman's kind of in the lagoid.
Who's the identity?
Did you, Whippiesle?
Who would Batman save next time?
Save your next time to find out.
Same PCP time.
Same PCP channel.
Thank you for watching this episode of Riddle My Ass, Batman.
Go to riddlemyassbabman slash patreon.com
for more great content to support me.
Okay.
Same PCP time.
Same PCP channel.
I could only barely understand what he was saying.
I got enough of it.
I got enough of it to last a lifetime.
The commitment to one take.
Is truly, truly inspiring.
I'm going to go right now to riddle my ass, Batman.
Was it backwards?
Was it supposed to be?
Is it the other way around?
Like, I don't even know.
Is it real?
I don't know.
Hold on.
Wait.
Okay.
No, no, no.
I would be more impressed if it was.
There was an actual website.
Unfortunately, tragically, riddlemyassbabman.patreon.com
does not exist.
No.
Surely it must.
I've been misdirected.
Damn.
Okay.
I googled and I'm reminded of the P.C.P,
the ultimate fanfic quest for cold corona.
That fanfic.
P.C.P.
Oh my god.
The riddlemyassbabman fanfic.
Yeah.
I haven't.
Did I read that?
Did I read that on the show?
No, on the show.
It's quite a long thing, isn't it?
I think we had an X.
It's kind of long.
Yeah, I think that's right.
Oh my god.
The show's been going on for a long time.
The show's been going on for too long.
It needs to be put down before it hurts someone.
But we can't.
We can't stop.
We're running on pure momentum now.
There ain't no getting off of this train we're on.
Next voicemail is from Janess.
Originally it was Janess, but I have a new name now.
It's spelled differently.
A new vowel.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, P.C.P. Happy 2021.
Can't believe it's been more than five years
and a couple of years of me listening to your podcast weekly.
My favorite thing this year was finally getting around to
listening to all the horse cast episodes.
You were just as good back then as you are now.
So I want to wish you good luck and don't blame yourself if you feel like
you're not going to be able to be on the podcast regularly.
I understand.
I'm going to be doing a re-listening to all the podcast episodes myself sometime in 2021
and figure out which episodes are my favorite.
Who knows?
Maybe it's not actually going to be the yellow episode.
It will be.
I like the idea that we're just as good back then as we are now.
Okay.
We have not improved once, like even slightly.
I think saying we're just as good now as we were back then is an indictment of how bad
it was back then than it is to say it's good now.
I just always exactly the same.
Janice, I appreciate the kindness, but it was absolutely 100% was Ben's fault.
He was late to the podcast today.
100%.
That's on me.
It was also Ben's fault that I was late to the podcast.
Agreed.
Just a throw out of the bus a little bit.
I take full responsibility.
I don't know if we talked about it when he was on the show.
Tectonic Improv made like a big, I think he might have mentioned that he made a big
ranked list of PCP episodes at one point.
Yeah, the big image.
Right, right, right.
Okay, we talked.
I think we linked it in the description.
We did.
Maybe we showed it on screen.
Okay, you should contest that one.
People should argue about placement.
People should be angry about the decisions made and that and not angry at us.
It's not a proper audience if they aren't arguing with each other about pointless ranking.
Absolutely.
Ab, so Lutely.
Next one is called PCP Makes You Trans.
Three, two, one, go.
Confirmed.
The PCP makes you epically trans.
Did you give Andavu?
Come on, Ben.
Then it will be your turn to become a cute anime girl.
I would love it very much.
Yeah, yeah.
And many people are saying this.
It's definitely a statistical anomaly.
I wonder why.
It's statistically based is what it is.
Statistically, I would say it's pretty epic.
We're pulling our weight for social progressivism over here.
What are you guys doing?
Davu's not even on the PCP anymore.
Davu's dead.
Davu is fucking dead.
No.
She's, I don't even know who that is.
It's not even real.
Next one is called SUCK.
Wait, you missed Kyosano.
Did I?
Oh, right.
I didn't realize the next one was called SUCK.
I thought you just didn't want to attempt pronouncing that and just said SUCK.
No, the one after is called SUCK.
Ah, I see.
Okay, Kyosano Ure.
Three, two, one, go.
Me, what you filthy capitalists call virtual YouTuber.
You fight for love, justice, and the revolution of the world.
You can find me in secret underground bunker where CIA can't hear.
And I destroy western culture with fact and logic.
Come join me in struggle for glorious future and always remember the east is red.
Was that like Russian?
What was that?
Like either someone explain.
It's foreign.
That's all I know.
I don't, I don't, well, okay.
Sorry.
They say yes.
So it's like that.
There is a lot of things happening.
I think they were speaking Japanese with a Russian, with a Russian accent.
I think that's what was going on there.
They said the east is red.
And all I can think of is G Gundam.
The east is burning red.
The school of the undefeated of the east, which is the greatest show of all time.
So they have my support.
Yeah.
Good luck.
Good luck destroying capitalism, you know, rooting for you.
Okay.
Next one is called, um, sec.
Why won't it play?
But wait, mind fucking, mind like don't start for a while.
I have to like start mine early, wait like 10 seconds, and then, and then.
Okay, whatever.
It's fine.
Next one's called, three, two, one.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben, you absolute lazy fucktard.
Where the hell is Son of True 102?
If you don't give it to me soon, you lazy fucking cunt.
I swear to God, I will break into your house and suck you off in your sleep.
Well, I explained why you didn't wake up for so long.
You're just so exhausted.
You better not make the thing then.
If you want to get sucked off.
I'd better not.
Oh, I certainly wouldn't want anyone to suck my God.
That would be, that would just be terrible.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, suck, but you missed your window of opportunity.
Ben just got his new tablet in, so now he has no excuse to not be drawing.
In fact, I will, I will say, um, on the other hand, though, maybe you'll want to procrastinate on
drawing now that you have the ability to do it and you'll start editing.
The Son of True lecture.
The thing, the thing that I'm working on now, my secret project is, um,
this is the last thing that I want to do.
And as soon as I'm done with it, the next thing on my list is to finish,
finish the, uh, the, the Son of True 102 lecture.
I could have done it at any point, but you know what?
I fucking didn't.
So get fucked.
You just went to get your dick sucked.
Played the long game.
It's about to pay off.
Fuck you, audience.
Die.
Um, uh, okay.
Next one is called Tale of Sand slash the in call.
Wait.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Somebody asked for more comic book recommendations.
So here is more recommendations.
Tale of Sand is a script by Jim Henson.
They never got made.
So they turn it into a comic are very fully illustrated comic with a,
really like a bare bones story.
I started, I could take place in someone's subconscious, maybe,
but it's, it's a fast read and it's delightful.
And, uh, I don't know, take a cup of coffee and, and, and chug this one down.
Uh, the in call, it's a sci-fi epic and it's illustrated by Moebius,
one of the best illustrators of all time.
He's French, uh, and Joe Dorovsky, who is, who makes movies,
these weird spiritual movies.
So, um, it really bleeds into the in call, the spiritualism.
Um, and it's weird and it's funny.
And it came before Star Wars, despite being also a sci-fi adventure tale with weird characters.
It's so slowing down.
These need to be like one ch-ch-ch-ch-chow to you also.
I'm looking at Tale of Sand, um, and it looks pretty cool, actually.
And yeah, I see it's The Lost Greenplay by Jim Henson and Jerry, Jerry Jewel.
Um, looks nice.
Isn't Jim Henson the Muppet Man?
Yeah.
Yeah, Jim Henson the Muppet Man.
Who lives on Drury Lane.
They were like, they were like, uh, they were like, hey Jims, thanks for this script,
but we're not gonna make a fucking movie about it.
So, uh, get fucked.
It's just too cool.
We'll give it to some idiot.
We'll give it to some sucker and he'll draw it instead.
You nerd.
That's what I would do.
And, uh, I don't know, fucking thanks for the comic recommendations, I guess.
Next one is called Captain Max Nezbit to the care of CaptainPatrion.comS
Oh, wait a minute.
What is happening?
Didn't, did this guy, okay, never mind.
This guy made a shitty voicemail last, last week.
Let's see, let's see if he can redeem himself.
Three, two, one, go.
Yeah.
Ha ha ha ha.
Patreon.com slash Ben Saint.
You've done me a great disunner by shunning my voicemail on a previous episode of the
Die Max Nezbit, you fuck.
Ask a better question next time.
You will never hear the tale of how I became a more interesting character or how I came to pirate
a frigate of tea guys and tea boys.
You'll also never know the secret to eternal heterosexuality or how we came to acquire it
at the bottom of the ocean.
You'll never find the treasure.
Fire.
Ben Saint, this is my message to you.
Your heart tightly fit to a captainship you've got.
By happenstance, if you've ship crossed your path, you'd be killed.
Hold.
There's no ship's diligence, but in the hippo girl, she's old in rickety ship and she's
limp led to nautical miles.
I'd hate to see her go down to the poor sailing.
I like the idea to crowdsource half your content with no checks of a quality.
So ship up Ben Saint or else my transship will transfer some cannons into the side of your
YouTube channel and bring her to the bottom of the sea.
That would be terrible.
Yeah.
You know, say what you like about Max Nesbitt, but he really does bring the enthusiasm.
I like how crazy he is.
Reminds me of Spongebob's Pirates a little bit.
He's damn and that's, I love Spongebob.
You know, as a millennial, I love Spongebob in my opinion.
It's a good program.
And we can, and that's something we can all agree on.
Okay.
Sorry, I'll never get to hear the tale of whatever you were just talking about.
Next one is called the actual best Pokemon game.
Give me a second here.
Please start play.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
You guys are sleeping on the actual best Pokemon game, HeartGold and SoulsFilver.
Like for one, you know, Pokemon Diamond and Pearl had HP bars made of platinum.
They sped up the HP so it actually goes down pretty fast.
Like in Ruby and Sapphire, you can have your Pokemon follow you around and it's right,
you know, just walls behind you as you run around the area.
I don't even use the bike in that game just so I can have my Pokemon run around.
And to compliment that they can toggle running shoes on and off so that you didn't have to hold
the B button to run all the time.
And some features that just didn't make it back in later games like that.
It's fucking red and you guys need to check it out.
I'm a little bit baffled that he thinks we don't know about HeartGold and SoulsFilver.
I mean, he's right.
It is one of my favorite games.
Yeah, even I, a person who hates Pokemon, have heard that that is like really good.
It's because Gen2 was the best gen.
So when they remade it, it just got better.
You know, I've, Pokemon Challenges has redpilled me recently that Gen2 is actually not,
it's not that good.
Gen2 is not as good as everyone says it is.
It's hard to disagree.
HeartGold and SoulsFilver is a good remake.
I think HeartGold and SoulsFilver is probably the best remake in the series.
Black and White 2 is still the, is still the best game.
It's the best in the series.
But everybody loved in Black and White, or not in Black, in HeartGold and SoulsFilver,
the following Pokemon that you could have them follow you around.
Everybody loved that.
And that's one thing they just put in that one remake and never put in any other game ever again.
Just to mock us, I assume.
Game Freak.
Just because they hate us.
They're a bunch of freaks.
They put in their name.
They're, they're demons.
They're monsters and I hate them.
I mean, yeah, it's got that and everyone likes it.
And it's the only game you can do that in for some reason.
So, you know, that's pretty cool.
That really is stupid.
I've always like, in the sun and moon where it's like, oh, you could write Pokemon,
but I don't have these specific ones.
No, you can't just have your Pokemon there.
It's not like they have 3D models or anything.
Everybody, yeah, it's not, it's not, it's definitely not like they have like 3D
models of these Pokemon running.
They fucking, everybody, everybody defended ride Pokemon in sun and moon.
And I hate it.
It's, it's terrible.
It's so shit that you, you don't even ride your own fucking Pokemon around.
You ride some other tourists that you're like renting so bad.
Cringe.
Is it like that in some sort?
Is it like that in Sword and Shield?
Yeah, you just have like a taxi service with the, uh...
The crow?
Corvik Knight and stuff.
Ravencroft.
Corvik.
Corvik Knight is a good, is a great Pokemon.
Corvik Knight is incredible.
But it really sucks.
That really sucks so fucking bad.
I hate it and it sucks and it's bad and it's terrible.
At least, you know, but it's so, like in fucking Pokemon, in Let's Go Pikachu and Eevee,
they give you, they let you, they actually let you ride your Pokemon around.
And then you, and then they take that away again in Sword and Shield.
It's almost like-
Why do they just give you something good?
There's no idea what they're doing over there.
And then they just, they just take, no, they do, they do, that's the thing.
They do know what they're doing though.
They do this on purpose.
They literally, they literally add features that people want in one game and then take them away.
So that like old games never become obsolete by the new ones.
I think that's why.
It's cause it's like, oh, if you want a game where you can ride your Pokemon around,
you have to play Let's Go Eevee and Let's Go Pikachu.
If they, if they just kept all the good features in every game,
then the new games would just be objectively better than the old ones.
And people would only play the new ones.
I don't know.
Maybe that's crazy, but I can't think of any other reason why they would do it like this.
There really isn't any other reason.
I think it's, but I, it feels strange that they would even think about that.
Like games are made, like they always know.
The reason they make new games all the time is because they know that the old games stop selling.
It's like, why would they try to future proof a game for sale that is like,
that they'd know it's not going to sell anyway, because there's new ones to make.
Yeah, yeah, um, I, it's kind of, yeah, it's true.
No, maybe that doesn't make any sense.
Cause like the new, they make, like they make all their money on like the sales of the new games.
It's not like they're making bank selling old games.
So maybe that's like a stupid theory.
But like, if it's, if not for that reason, then I genuinely don't understand why it seems like
they deliberately just like put good features in and then, and then just ruin them and take them out.
And forget about them.
To be a Japanese fly on the wall in those board meetings.
They put the fucking, they put like the ability to ride any Pokemon in, let's go.
And then they just took it away.
And why?
Why can't I just ride a, you can have a Pokemon follow you, right?
But only on like the Isle of Armor, I think.
And why?
Why is it like that?
Maybe they're, they're stringing people along on the off chance, on the hope that eventually
a really good Pokemon game will come out that has all the good features that people like.
And you know, they get them to buy it based on that.
But they'll never actually, but they'll never actually make that game
because they just, they throw features away.
Even ones people like, everybody likes that in HeartGold SoulSilver, you could have your,
you could have your Pokemon follow you.
And then they kind of put it in Sword and Shield, but only in the DLC.
Is it just because Sword and Shield was rushed?
Is that why?
I think they just know they don't have to try.
Because like they made a bajillion, zillion dollars anyway.
So like, why do you do anything?
Yeah, I would attribute it more to like, just not thinking like the people at the top,
making the decisions are like, I don't know if I can put Pokemon in there or something.
It can't, it can't be that they don't know what they're doing.
It can't be.
I feel like they have to just not care.
I feel it.
Well, Pokemon's just a gargantuan like media property, but like a lot of it is,
is not the games so much.
So I feel like whoever's developing the games might not have enough of a say to like,
make a good Pokemon game.
Well, but like, all right.
There might be people in the company who want to do this stuff, but like,
they can't do it for some reason.
And it's stupid.
The guys in suits are the ones that like decide, that like produce the game,
but like they're not personally in charge of like designing it.
Like they, they have like people that are working on the game that presumably like,
know what they're doing to some extent.
I would think that even if the executives are not like,
smoking their cigar and being like, hmm, yeah, see, we got to keep this,
this next Pokemon game is going to be, we really, we really care about quality.
Hmm.
Keep all these features in that everybody likes.
So yeah, we want, like they, like they don't care.
But like you would think that the people who are actually making the game would be like,
okay, people liked that you could do this in another game.
So we should let you keep being able to do that.
Do you think that like someone in the, in the chain of command,
I really don't want to think that be responsible for this.
I guess it really just could be that they're just incompetent and stupid, the people making it.
I don't want to believe that because I don't know.
And it feels like mean because I don't, I don't, I don't believe it.
I don't believe that it could be by accident.
Yeah.
Like it must, it's, it's either just that it simply doesn't matter to them
or they are doing it deliberately with some sort of agenda because it's, it's, it's,
there's like such a consistent pattern there.
Okay, what was that game that came out that was or it was in early access?
I don't know.
The, the Pokemon ish similar game that had stuff in it that was pretty good.
Oh, Temtem?
Temtem.
Yeah.
I never, I never played it.
It looked cool.
It wasn't, it was an MMO, right?
You could like.
Yeah, it was on the line.
You could see other people and fight them.
God, that looks, that looks cool.
That's a cool idea.
Yeah, I don't know.
I had friends that were playing it in like early access or whatever.
Looked, looked pretty neat.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called is cross desktop wallpapers.
Three, two, one, go.
What is the backstory to your current desktop wallpaper?
I just watched Akira for the first time.
So I got a cool moving desktop wallpaper of Shotaro Kaneda.
He's sitting on his throne.
He's looking all cool, like he's got a bunch of energy around him.
Some cool thunder and electricity and stuff.
Looks awesome.
What about you guys?
My desktop wallpaper is an RFCK wallpaper.
It's, it's, it's cop, it says cop killers and it has the original,
it has the original version of the cop killer logo as it was drawn by Slimes who created it.
And it's got a drawing of me next to it also by Slimes.
And I just think it looks really cool and aesthetic and I have,
this has been my wallpaper like for like a year and a half, I think it's nice.
It's nice and it's black.
So it's easy to see stuff on it.
And I think that's good.
Tom just left the call.
Tom was so bored by my explanation of my desktop wallpaper.
He left the call.
Yeah.
Well, I got, I got a desktop wallpaper for you.
It's, it's something I commissioned from Kazi and it's Riska and there she is.
She's Riska in the old web.
Oh, that's pretty, that's pretty good, I guess.
That's a pretty good thing you got there.
Good job.
I like buying commissions.
It's pretty fun to get, to get a little something.
I don't know why.
Well, I do know why, but I always ask the artists to like put some sort of a
reference into something I've in, you know, some sort of me reference.
So that there's no, there's no way people can free boot it and just think it's just
Riska because it's just, it's Riska, but she's got punk there as well.
Yeah.
So it's tied to me forever.
Damn it, how do I, I want to like, I want to post my desktop, but I like,
I don't know where the file is saved that it's like referencing.
I guess I'll have to find it and I'll post it so Eleazar can, can show it.
Man, Kazi's so good.
Look at that.
Look at that sky and shit.
I don't know.
What a, what a fucking, what a fucking masterpiece.
Yeah.
Fuck yeah.
Where did Tom go?
The Tom.
I hope he's computed.
I hope he didn't die and lose all his audio.
That would be pretty fucking tragic.
Oh, and he started the episode.
Can you imagine though, like, can you imagine if that happened?
I guess I can imagine.
He did, he was, it was the, it was the solo Tom cast for a while until I bombed
it and ruined everything.
Okay. Well, we got one more voicemail to go and it's called,
and it's called, wait, funny joke two.
Yes. It's called funny joke two.
Sorry.
It's doing the thing again.
We're please, please, please just play the fucking voicemail.
I don't know what's wrong with my computer today.
It's like particularly shit.
All right.
I'm ready.
Funny joke two, three, two, one, go.
Fanti fa, more like fa.
You see, cause they say they're against fascism, but actually.
Cool. Nice. Got them.
Well, we did it.
They're the real fascists because they don't,
because they'll punch people for being racist.
Well, I said five.
That's the joke.
Like B, like A Tifa and B Tifa, C Tifa.
What?
Never mind.
I know.
I got it wrong because I heard it wrong.
I didn't get it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm, I'm developmentally challenged.
I'm like stupid or whatever.
That's true.
True enough.
I can't believe everything is crumbling around us.
I can't believe Tom is dead too.
And now I'm, now I'm wondering if maybe he didn't,
like his computer died and his audio is lost.
And this episode will never see the light of day.
How fucking tragic would that be?
Well, post in the comments how tragic that would be.
If you're, if you're hearing this episode now,
then, then I suppose that probably didn't happen.
But so fingers crossed that you do in fact,
listen, hear this on, on January 1st, 2021.
Happy 2021, every, every pony.
We made it.
Hey, what's your new year's resolution?
Me?
Yeah.
You're gonna kill fat Ben.
Oh, good one.
I'm gonna kill myself.
What about you?
Uh, I don't know.
I'm gonna kill myself.
Nice, nice.
Hey everyone, I'm sorry about this episode.
I'm sorry about this show.
I'm sorry about me.
I'm sorry for who I am and the things that I do.
I can't believe fat Ben is such an apologist.
Yeah, he's a fat Ben is a fat Ben apologist.
And that's the worst thing about him is that he thinks it's okay.
Oh, I see.
He thinks what he's doing is fine.
I see Tom going online.
Is he back?
Oh my God, Tom, Tom.
Yeah.
What happened?
My whole, Tom, what happened?
My whole, my whole computer crashed.
Really?
Yeah.
The whole thing just besotted and died.
But I was, what about your audio?
I was able to recover the audio.
Thank God.
Oh my God.
Yes.
Yes, Tom, you're a genius, Tom.
It's a, it's a January 1st miracle.
It's a, it's, it's a fucking PCP 2021 miracle.
This year is looking up, baby.
Oh my God, what a fucking nightmare.
Everything was at the bottom and now we're here.
We've ascended to the top of that peak.
Hell, yes.
Hey, we, we already listened to the last voicemail, a spoiler alert.
It sucked.
So, you know.
Whoa, big, big surprise there.
So don't even worry about it.
It's all good.
So, Tom, I don't know.
Real quick, what's your new year resolution?
4k.
No, but try, try and just make more shit.
Make, make more shit, make more shit consistent.
That's pretty good.
If you chew your food, you'll make more consistent shit.
Are you sure?
I'll give it a try, I'll give it a try and get back to you.
I'm, I'm about halfway through this horrible, horrible sea ice and coke.
Why, why did you continue to do it?
Why are you, I don't know, I started, I started doing a thing.
So I have to finish it.
That's just, that's called having honor.
Ben, you two wouldn't know anything about that.
You don't, you don't finish anything.
You two wouldn't, what the fuck are you talking about?
You know, I finish everything eventually.
You finish that drink faster than you finished any project in the last 100 years.
Um, you're gonna, you're gonna eat those words because the thing,
my secret project is going to be done before you even know it,
and everyone will be in awe of its perfection and its majesty.
Yeah, so suck it.
Dumbass.
Okay, uh, are we done?
I guess.
Are we, are we finished?
Are we finished here?
Have we set our piece?
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators, if we haven't already said that.
Give us money.
Oh yes, bonus episode.
Is there a bonus episode?
Do we already, do we record a bonus episode this month?
We did, right?
I think we did.
We did, I think, with Game is Tavern.
Yes, we did another.
Right, we did another commentary track.
We had Gamer's Tavern on to record a commentary retrospective on Gamer's Tavern's original
cameo for some reason.
We did, we did it.
We really did, uh, based, um, yeah, Patreon.
And send us a voicemail at speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail.
Your New Year's resolution should be to make voicemails that don't suck.
That's right.
That's right, it really should.
But I know you won't do it.
You won't.
I, you, you, you don't, you don't have the courage.
It'll be like going to the gym.
There'll be a bunch of good stuff in January than the rest of them the year.
Just be terrible again.
There'll be one week, one week of quality voicemails before everything just degenerates
back to its natural state.
You, you, you know the thing, the CGP gray thing where he's like, don't have a New
Year's resolution and have a theme for the year.
You know that?
Yeah.
I've thought really hard about it and I've watched that video multiple times and I
don't get how you're supposed to do it.
I don't get it.
It's about, I think it's about like having a system instead of a goal.
Like a goal is a tangible finite thing that it's like a binary like win or fail state
where a system is like a structure that continues to go on in perpetuity.
So you're always working towards it.
I just can't decide what the theme is because I don't know what I want to be doing.
Get your New Year's resolution.
If your New Year's resolution was to make a good voicemail and you made a bad voicemail,
you failed.
But if your theme is make good voicemails, then you might make one voicemail that's
bad, but then you just got to try again.
Exactly.
It's about the next one can be good.
It's a goal is a finite game.
A system is an infinite game.
I just don't know what I'm supposed to be doing.
Well, let your theme of this year be discovery and figuring out what it is you actually want to do.
Like that discovery.
That Duff Punk album.
Yeah, the theme of this, the theme of my year is courage.
And honor.
And integrity.
And justice.
And return scroll.
No, no, definitely not.
Returning the scroll is the one thing I won't be doing.
Ben's using the scroll as his coaster for his drink he's nursing right now.
For my terrible, terrible drink that I hate.
Almost as much as I hate the scroll, yet I won't let it go.
Mmm.
Oh, horrible.
All right, is that it?
That's it.
We're done.
We're done here, everybody.
Goodbye.
Thanks for listening.
Happy 2020.
See you next week.
See you in fucking hell, bitches.
Bye.
You