Welcome to the PCP. Here we are on the Pro Crastinators Podcast. You all know what we're
doing here. It's me, of course, Munchy, and we have Nate here as well.
I am metrosexual.
Uh, nothing new there. We have Mage.
It is I, here again, to ruin your day.
We might have been. I don't know if he's secured that deal yet. I don't know if he's signed that contract yet.
I am contractually obligated not to affirm or deny that I am here. Continue as you were, gentlemen.
On our news site, we posted an extremely ugly story about how Hippocrit here actually turned out to be a transsexual.
Would you care to elaborate on that?
Uh, it's all true. The rumors, Avery, and all rumors, even ones that don't make sense, that's the truth.
Post-op, non-op, coin-op, give us all the deeds.
Uh, my trainer code is 182797624568 for my, uh, my trans-go-game-community-video-game-gamer.
What are the, what are the three numbers in the back, and what did, what did datas expire on?
Um...
Alright, speak, speak, speak.
Uh, uh, hello. I, I, I am here.
Enough. Ditty.
Okay, goodbye.
No.
Moshi moshi.
Uh, watashi umai umai suika.
Watashi wa.
Umai umai suika.
Umai umai.
What?
Prosecut, uh, okay, okay, I must, okay, we're on the PCP.
You know, you know, you, you heard, you guys all heard, you're all serial viewers, and you all heard two episodes ago when there was that big old funny fucking farce that we had where you're talking about, oh, topics aren't cool.
Well, here we are.
There was that formless cast, Digi, and Davoo, and Tom did, and now we're trying it out here on the actual show itself.
We're gonna try and just kick it back in now.
So it's just gonna be laid back, we're gonna do an old, an old formless cast.
I've, I've pulled up the, uh, urban dictionary definition of top list.
No!
No, I wouldn't hear it.
Let's do it.
I didn't actually.
Aw.
That was a joke.
Thank God.
A medical joke.
I, I do not like the slant eyes.
I do not like the slant eyes, Digi arc.
I think we're gonna have to take that back out.
Uh, I, I, I have multiple things that I've written down here to talk about.
Does anyone want to go first?
I, I want to, I want to hear about Tom.
Did you, am I, am I, am I crazier or did you start playing Pokemon Go this week?
Uh, I restarted playing Pokemon Go.
I did play it, uh, back, back in the day.
I got to like level 18.
I did my shit.
Oh, okay.
You're not as much of a noob as I thought.
No, no, no, no, no.
I just, the reason is like back when I was playing, they didn't have like raids.
They didn't have like the appraisals and like IVs and shit.
They didn't, and like battles like were fucked up.
The game was trash.
It was, it was broken at launch.
No, it was better at launch because they had the, because they had the footprint system.
The footprint tracking system was the most fun.
That was super dope.
And it will never come back.
And the fact that it's gone is of travesty to me.
I want to let you know by virtue of you trying to act cool, you've actually made yourself
out to be a noob because you thinking that 18 is not a noob makes you a noob.
No, no, no.
I thought that Tom was, because he was saying like, how do, I thought he said, how do I
get rid of my Pokemon?
I felt like he didn't even know how to transfer.
So I thought he was like level one.
I thought he was like just started.
And that was like,
Can we talk about the fact that Tom just this week, finally at long last, actually started
living in his car.
And the most thing you were excited about, about what's going on with him is that he's
playing Pokemon going.
That is the most important thing ever in the group.
Like I fucking dominoes are tumbling to the Pokemon Go influence.
How, how credit personally.
I bet, I bet you can hit like so many fucking Pokestops living in a car dude.
I was going to say his lifestyle is perfectly calibrated for optimizing Pokemon Go.
I bet you can, I bet you can hit 10 raids a day.
What I've been doing.
Car charger too.
It'll be perfect.
Well, well, yeah, it's, it's, it's, it's pretty silly.
So like I'm at home right now because I have a bunch of eBay stuff that like is, needs to
be shipped out.
So that's what I'm doing today.
But the last couple of days, it's just like, oh, everything's closing at 11.
So I'm just going to go do Midnight Pokemon Go for like two hours.
Yeah.
That's just what I do.
Same.
Oh, being homeless is so fucking productive.
It's so, it's so romantic.
I mean, I know you're around Boston, but like Boston's a city that kind of shuts down kind
of early, but maybe there's sections of it that are like open later or something like
stuff.
I mean, I think I was going to be living in my garage before very long.
Well, that's true.
That's true.
Hey, my, my topic is actually directly related to Pokemon Go.
So it might be a good time to, to get into it.
Does anyone mind?
Yeah.
I mind.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I would rather elaborate on all the Pokemon that I caught this week.
Let me see here.
I got, I got a low tad.
I got, I got a sir skit.
Yeah.
I did not get a low tad.
I got a lowland, a lowland geodude.
I still think back with you.
Didn't you have a lowland bullpicks?
No.
No, but I would love one.
I dreamt that I hatched in a lowland bullpicks, but I'm so sad.
Only in your dreams, Mage.
Only in your dreams.
What are you going to say?
So, so my title was everybody's getting back into Pokemon Go here.
I certainly am.
I've been playing it a ton.
I'm loving it.
Some fucking cuck, instinct piece of shit just took back my gym.
Oh yes.
Fucking bitch.
Praise yellow.
Yeah.
Me and Michelle are pretty pissed about it.
But what, what I want to talk about was all this talk about Pokemon Go and whatnot.
I want to talk about gamification of the human condition and how I think it's the only
way that we're going to survive longterm.
I think it is, it is a great idea.
It's not happening like everything.
It's so powerful.
It's really happening to like all aspects of society.
But everyone complained when they did that in China.
Was it, was it China?
Did they?
Some con, some Asian country instituted this like social gamification where like you
get scored based on, I don't know, like how well you follow the laws and like some
other stuff.
Like if you associate with other people that have low scores, your score will go down.
I'm into that.
That's a really, I think it's a system I can get behind.
With gamification, there's a real danger in the fact that like you have to make sure
you're gamifying the right things, you know, like gamify, like if we gamified like eating
nutritionally and like going for jogs and like, you know, things that will actually
make people's life better.
That's a good idea.
Like if we're just like, if we're just gamifying like the numbers at work, it's like, you
know, that's, I feel like that will do worse for people because you're turning yourself
into just numbers, you know, and that's like the opposite of what we want.
I hear what you're saying, but like every time Nate says, I hear what you're saying,
what he really says is, well, that was fucking retarded.
Let me correct.
I do say it a lot, don't I?
No, no, those are all things that I agree with.
But it's like, when I think about it, I think about how like, like human beings are hardware.
The hardware of a human being is really old and dated and it's calibrated for a completely
different game than what we're playing right now.
And I see absolutely no way outside of like cyborgification of ourselves to like literally
fix ourselves so we can handle it.
So I think what we need to do, what is so broken, I mean, for example, look at me, everything's
broken about me.
I would argue that like social media use is making people like more and more timid and
like not like social creatures, which we are predicated to being and that's creating a
lot of depression and people.
You know, the funny thing about that, I've been thinking about this a lot.
Like why I think social media existed and like what it's been for all this time, especially
YouTube has been for like people who don't think they have a place trying to find one.
But the problem is that people get on Twitter and instead of like realizing, oh, I'm a human
being, I should participate in the world.
They realize, oh, I'm like a this whatever the specific gender slash sexuality category
is and I'm going to hang out with exclusively those people on Twitter and assume that everyone
else is an evil monster who wants me dead.
And it's like it just I think it has the opposite of intended effect in a way where like, yeah,
people do find a sense of community and that's great and they start talking to people, but
they they talk to their little bubble and then they hate everyone else even more.
I mean, that's like that's regressive, you know, I've been weirded out by that because
like clearly a lot of these groups are formed by like superficial things that don't actually
make you a different sort of person.
It's just like a label that anybody could say that they're part of this group.
And I I've always wondered whether or not the people in the group like everyone else
in the group or whether they because like clearly there's lots of different types of
people like incompatible types of people that would be in a group and like be like, yes,
we're on this side, but they like why do they not fight?
I've never really understood how that they can stay together.
Oh, that's true.
That's true.
Well, it's just like in person, in person.
I mean, this has been said a million times, but in person, no one is as rude as they are,
like in a comment section or just online on Twitter.
I don't know about that.
Way nicer.
And like, like, like, give a saying, like, I could choose to hang out with only my little
bubble of fellow transracial Japanese people.
But like, you know, I recognize that there are people who are not the superior Eastern
bloodline, such as myself, that, you know, have things to contribute as well.
And it's like, yeah, the forming of bubbles is one of the major issues that goes along
with this. I mean, you say I mean, I think the forming is inevitable.
I don't think you can not.
I mean, well, this is how do you avoid being in your bubble?
Because like, you're going to be you're going to be seeing the people that like you have
you have chosen to follow the system and so on.
Yeah, I think it's OK to form bubbles in small communities.
The problem comes from when they just reject all the things outside the bubble.
Like, it's one thing. Yeah, it's one thing to live in your neighborhood and be like,
this is what's good for my neighborhood.
But like, we also have open trade with that neighborhood over there.
We can exchange ideas and and and products.
But when you just close yourself off and you're like, no,
fuck everyone else because they're not us.
It's like that's the same.
It's every ism.
You're doing the same thing as all those guys.
By the way, nobody nobody laughed at my transracial joke.
I thought it was funny.
OK, didn't want to interrupt you by laughing.
I got you.
Sorry. Too late.
I've spent it spent.
I'm just I'm dead because I didn't get to hear you.
Well, get used to it, sister, because I'm coming in hot.
My joke was it's all fun games when the violin pilots are fighting
the in the Indigo infidels.
Yeah, the Indigo infidels, you know, the Indigo incels.
The fucking scourge.
I think the trait that makes you most likely to be either insane
or a common Twitter user is the idea or just the feeling
not so much a victim complex, but just the idea that people
are intentionally trying to make you upset, that people are intentionally
like making bad decisions in the world to make it a worse place.
So there's some sort of super villain out there that's in charge of all the things
that you don't like. It's called Donald Trump. Exactly.
And like, yeah, you can talk about your dad, it's fine.
There's like a super villain in charge of, like, you know, I don't know,
big GMO or like the Republican Party or just any of these social issues.
There's someone trying to make you upset, like, and that's not how it is ever.
It's always reasonable people doing reasonable things that they think is a good idea.
Yeah. But you know, I won't say always, I will say that with those corporations
and like I will say that there are some pretty evil like big corporations
who are who are a lot, like, especially in the like the food industry,
who are just lying about what is nutrition to fucking, you know, like the food pyramid
is cancer and that shit was made up by companies who want us to eat more grains,
you know, and it's not good.
You shouldn't eat that many grains.
Cereal was a famous thing because like they just said, well, why not part of a
well balanced breakfast? Why not make people eat breakfast with this stuff?
And it worked. Kellogg's killed the whole world.
But I love Kellogg's cornflakes and I eat them every day, so I don't even mind.
I mean, so like these are fine points and it's true, like,
but what we're talking about is kind of like one facet of like social media
is something that human beings were not built to handle.
And but I think like the way that we fix it and I don't have as usual,
I don't have an actual solution or anything here.
But like like gamification at large is just like we like this is how we adapt
for our lagging software.
We we we test, we figure out some way to like make things fun that we don't want to do.
Like like everyone in America is a fat piece of shit.
For example, here's how you fix it.
Like a lot of people have done this and they've been effective,
like these running apps where you can like compete with your friends
and like go for high scores. Oh, yeah.
And and like all this stuff is good for that.
Is that is that a joke? Is that true?
No, no, no, I'm serious for a video.
No, yeah, they have these things like the the Apple Watch has these things
called rings and like the thing is you have to close the rings.
You have to do enough like exercise and stuff to close your ring.
And as you look at your watch, you can see them shrinking as it goes on.
And so like it keeps track of you and all your contacts that you accept.
So like you can challenge people and like, oh, like Nate's closing his ring
faster than me today, that fuck, I got to get back at him.
Well, I can think of when I hear rapidly right now.
All I can think of when I hear closing rings is
prostate and anus. And that's exactly what I was thinking.
I've never thought of that before.
And now it's ruined. I will never buy an Apple Watch.
Whenever, whenever anyone says the word Apple Watch,
everyone immediately braces for some sort of ironic joke.
Like there's no way that is true.
Preface with an Apple Watch.
I just think Pokemon Go is such a great thing.
It like that's it makes me feel hopeful that, like, yes,
human beings are weak, foolish creatures, but we could theoretically come up with
systems that trick our shitty hardware.
I am so much more active as a person.
Exactly. Now that I'm playing Pokemon Go again.
But see, the only thing I actually leave my house and do the only problem
with doing it with with doing it that way is that, like,
you all stopped playing Pokemon Go for a long while when, like, it was shitty.
And when there wasn't any updates and, like, I think that no,
it's because where I lived was shitty.
That's the only reason. All right, all right, same.
But I well, I mean, and that's a consequence for a lot of people.
Like if I mean, from the time the game first came out,
the biggest problem has always been if you don't live in a big city,
it's a far worse game. You know, so it's true.
We need to like Pokemon Go is a good first step,
but we need something that actually works for everyone, you know.
And like, I don't think the people who live in big cities are the ones
who were the most worried about not walking enough because they probably walk
way more. What they should do is they should make polling stations
at Pokestops so that when you Pokemon Go to the polls,
a special Pokestops. No, because when you go to Pokemon Go to the polls
and you vote for the correct candidate as sanctioned by the government,
the government pays Niantic and you get like a shiny dragonite for free.
And then the Niantic helps people take over the world.
And then it would be very far. Here's what I'm going to do, though.
As an evil corporate chill, I'm going to only put the shiny dragonite
in the Republican booth. So you have to go vote Republican.
Oh, that is the point. Oh, OK.
Yeah, that's that's how Niantic will make loads of money.
Oh, I see. And that is my modus operandi for some reason.
I'm really excited for all sorts of like, even though I all I all joke
about Jurassic World Live because it's a Jurassic World Live.
And I actually actually played a little bit of it.
The way you capture the dinosaurs is you have to like control
a drone that shoots arrows.
It's fucking crazy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yeah, I know. Munchy, munchy, munchy.
That's that's cool and all.
But but but Jurassic World Live is old hat. All right.
It's old hat. It's it's the old walking dead.
The walking dead, dude. That's the new one.
What about the Harry Potter wizards?
What about the walking dead?
There's a walking dead Pokemon.
Glamon. Yeah.
OK, literally, what do you catch?
What do you catch?
I you catch a virus that turns into a zombie.
What if what if you were walking around with like your VR camera on it?
And you know how you can catch Pokemon like with the real world background?
You know, it sucks like we do at that legendary time.
Yeah, like you could you do that.
But you see zombies and you tap on your screen and you're like you're
shooting you're shooting zombies like in your field of view.
You know, and you like maybe you're standing on like the sidewalk
and you move in your camera and like there's so you have to go find zombies
so you can kill them.
Like, yeah, yeah, why not?
The whole point of the show that you avoid zombies
at all costs and stay in one place and don't wander around.
Well, you have a small issue, though, guys.
I have a small issue, though, like how can I play Pokemon Go
and the walking dead go at the same time?
Two phones, two phones, two phones, two phones.
Can't afford like a drug dealer.
My fucking phone is literally unbelievably
the most amazing thing I've ever seen.
It like I can I can minimize my like Google Maps thing
and to get a little preview of where to go
while having the big Pokemon Go app open at the same time.
So I can do a screen.
It's on. It's like like I can look in the little finder thing.
It can tell me where the Pokestop is with the Pokemon I'm looking for.
I put that in Google Maps.
I like make that a small window on my screen while Pokemon Go is open.
I'm on my way to getting that rare Alolan executor
while I fucking him, you know, just guide it.
It's amazing, so that you can sort of track where was within Pokemon Go.
Like, you just you got a shiny puzzle yesterday.
Feeling pretty good. Oh, my God, you and hippos.
Shiny Minin got a fucking fuck or something. Yeah.
I got a little hippo that's what I said.
I thought you got a puzzle
and you said you would look boring and a shiny Minin would look great.
But yeah, today, today, I got I got three shiny Minin.
I went to London and I went fucking ham and it was too hot and I died.
There must be like way more Pokemon in the city because I find
like maybe like 20 Pokemon a day, if I'm walking.
Hmm. I was at Pokemon Go,
the procrastinator's podcast episode one hundred and twelve.
OK, well, I wanted I wanted to I was saying that with all these clones,
I'm excited for the day where one day it won't be a clone
and there will just be more games that are set in this air environment.
I retreat this other day when I am tick is going fucking crazy,
advancing air technology.
OK, by the way,
that's literally what the Sword Art Online movies about.
OK, it's about them like building an air like overlay on the world.
Well, Apple has this whole technology right now.
They've been working on for a couple of years called air kit.
And it's designed to like have really like fucking dope air.
And like they demo it every year that they're making progress on it.
And the rumor right now is that because like they have like this demonstration
where like it just builds, you can like point your phone camera at a table
and just builds an entire like battlefield on the table.
And like it just sticks to the table so you can like do stuff
and move troops around or whatever.
And like that's like they're demoing it.
And the rumor right now is that they're developing this air stuff
because their next like big release they want to do is like a pair of glasses.
That's just air glasses.
Literally, they're making the Sword Art Online movie real.
That's literally what the movie is.
It's like I'm just I'm just excited for that
because we can finally game world.
We can finally have the Yu-Gi-Oh game.
We've all wanted since we were like, oh, shit, you're I will actually get into that.
If they actually make Yu-Gi-Oh with the fucking with the dual disc system or whatever,
you'll see me finally get into a new set of Yu-Gi-Oh cars with QR codes.
You just look at them, then they appear.
Exactly. I only want this if they rebuild it.
Like if they restructure the card game from the ground up
so we don't have to play with like the modern Yu-Gi-Oh cars,
we have to read like a fucking paragraph on every card.
And then read your whole deck to even understand what any of it means.
I retreated the other day.
But but but but Niantic made updates to AR.
I think it's just called Niantic AR because they're narcissistic.
And here's the fucking thing.
Pokemon, you know how it would just like like the AR was is just that it would be
a Pokemon that was overlaid on top of like, you know, a picture of what you're looking at.
Pokemon can pass behind objects in the real world now.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Check out this shit.
Check out this fucking shit.
Niantic real world platform.
Pokemon can like pass behind flowerpots.
So you've got some guy standing right in front of you.
A Pokemon can pass behind him in the real world.
You can like detect where all this video it's it's like the end, I believe.
Oh, yeah, this is fucking sick.
This is the cutest thing I've ever seen.
Whoa. Yeah.
It's like a minute 30. Oh, damn.
That's dope. Nice.
Lincoln show notes.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'll just put it on the screen right here.
Hey, did did did Shadman's Twitter get deleted?
No, he got suspended, I think.
Oh, again. Huh?
Again.
Why do you know anything about Shadman?
Well, I'll tell you why, because just the other just the other day on V,
somebody posted a screen cap that was and I couldn't be more in favor of what he said.
He said, guys, this is this is Shadman saying this, guys,
there are actually people in the real world
that believe that fictional illustrated characters have human rights.
These people are trying to fuck with me in what I do, despite, you know,
he claims he's not into Lollie.
He's not into any of the Gurosha he just likes to draw because it's funny and provocative.
And that's fine. You know, whatever he says, so I believe him.
But like who even gives a fuck about whether he likes it or not.
Yeah, it does not matter.
It's just utterly like I mean, he is saying and I'm just believing him
that there are people out there.
And I believe these people exist who claim that the fictional characters
he's drawing have human rights.
It's the only way that they can they can judge.
Like they just want that to be a law.
If they want to say that then literally every time you've ever drawn someone
getting killed, you're a fucking murderer or like people in that very thread
was being like, no, he like, for example, like he, you know, draws like lolly stuff.
Yep, he's a fucking pedophile.
And then other people were applying aptly so like, oh, just like how you're a murderer
for killing people in video games. Sounds right. Yeah.
Sounds about right.
Well, here's the thing, Nate.
Like not only is there people that think that in Massachusetts,
lolly is illegal and it is considered pedophilia and you will go to prison.
Man, what the fuck?
You will go to prison if you don't know how to defend yourself.
I will gladly step up to the play.
I guess all I can say is I'm glad that's not my thing.
Listen, Chad Base is in every.
Chad Base is Chad based, man.
He has every single right in the book.
Yeah. But Chad Base is the worst artist of all time.
I don't even particularly like his art, but he's just such a he's just such an institution.
Yeah, like I think I'd be sad if he were gone.
I wouldn't be able to tell Shad's art if I used to show it to me.
I have no idea who he is.
I know he's quite well known around.
I've heard the name a thousand times, but I've never fucking discussed it.
It makes you a little bit.
It makes you want to throw up.
Is he the guy who draws those like those gumball animations?
No, that's salty, salty something.
Salty ice cream. I'm so glad I don't think I've seen any of his stuff.
Salty ice cream is awesome.
Salty ice cream rules.
Salty ice cream is a legend.
Yeah, well, anyway, I just I'm fully in support of all of Shad Base.
I don't think the salty ice cream and our fans will actually thank us for that.
Yeah, they probably will just go watch Shad Base
and then cleanse your palate with some salty ice cream.
Nate, you wanted to talk about Hawaii.
I mean, I want to stop here.
The guy who drew the the the the the violet fucking her mom porn.
Yes, that's him. Yeah, that's him. That's that's the one that I see.
Nate, Nate, I want to talk about my vacation I had recently, too.
So you go first so I can see him like I'm like I'm the same as you.
OK, did you already go to Hawaii, too?
Did you already go and come back?
No, no, I'm OK.
I'm going to many things, but I'm going to talk about an expo when you're OK.
Cool. So yeah, like so I just went to Hawaii recently.
You know, my my girlfriend's family lives there and we just took a trip to go
visit them and it was like a great time and like among the amazing things there.
OK, so like let me just say I was telling the guys before I didn't I didn't
finish my point, but the great thing about Hawaii is that it's it's it's a
full state in these United States.
So it's it's got all the great convenience of America.
I had an internet connection the entire time I was on this fucking island
and I was on Oahu, which is the most developed island.
But but still, like it was like Party Central in Honolulu.
It was like there was like the incredible, beautiful beach
like the most beautiful place I've ever seen in my life with the fucking internet
connections, the videos you posted, yeah, like look like, you know, travel videos.
Like exactly. It was just like random shit.
You busted out on your phone on Instagram.
It looks like a fucking travel movie.
It was so beautiful.
And the water was like it's got like the low humidity with the sea breeze.
So like, even though it's like 80 degrees, it feels completely comfortable.
But anyway, like the great thing about it is it's like it's like got nature's beauty.
It's got the convenience of America because it is America.
And it's like 75 percent Japan, which is just great, which is just great.
Because they've got this is what I'm going to tourists.
Tourists, right? Yeah.
Like the Japanese, like they swarmed that place.
They they love. So so Ragon for Hawaii.
Is that is that what we're talking about right now?
Hawaii. Well, we literally should.
I got to say just the prospect that people live there
and the idea that just for some amount of worthless currency,
I could also just live there.
It just seems like the only logical thing to do with one's life.
But but the biggest thing that I like miss
ties into my time in Tokyo years ago, and it's the food and like the smells
and like just having like takoyaki stands and and being able to go to like ramen places.
You mean like not even like it's like Asians, right?
Like it just is Japanese food.
That yeah, it just straight up like is Japan a lot of the island.
It's so. Oh, my God. Yeah.
I mean, honestly, where I live in Boston,
there's like it's probably like 80 percent Asians here.
And sometimes it does feel like I'm just in like not not in any specific Asian country,
just in all of Asia, like one little microcosm because you know,
they're all the same. They start to blend together.
Well, Michelle, no, because like we were just at an Asian grocery store
that literally is in a plaza that has like a Thai place, a Japanese place,
a Korean place, a Chinese place and a Vietnamese place.
Like I don't know if I said that already.
All surrounding an Asian grocery store.
And that is the entire. So it's just like you go there and it's like,
here's all of Asia in one fucking.
Like I'm not only useful parts of the Asian country.
Yeah, I'm not a true.
I'm not a true weed.
But the more time I spend around Asian shit,
the more we've I become because it's just better.
It's just better. It's just infections.
It gets under your skin.
It's right. It's right.
You fucking redpilled me so hard in Boston.
Last time we were together, you reckoned me so hard.
Having actual ramen.
Oh, God.
It blew my mind to have like I still haven't experienced this yet.
You guys got to go.
Do you know, I have been to some ramen places.
I have been to some ramen places that, frankly, suck dick.
And maybe I have to actually like ramen is like really hit and miss.
But when you get ramen, it's fucking unbelievable.
It's unbelievable.
You get that real Naruto shit, my dude.
It's just you got to get that little that little Naruto Maki in there.
The little spirally fish cake.
Yeah, dog shout out to local business.
Tajie East Village ramen over here in San Diego.
Fucking go there if you're in the area. It's so cool.
Actually, last time I was there, I think I said about this in chat.
I was I eavesdropped on two people who were eating behind me.
And they were two people who were like the marketing agents of like a mobile game.
And they talked about how easy it was to manipulate
YouTubers to advertising their mobile game for no money.
Hell, yeah, they were for Naruto online.
Probably do. Oh my god.
Eating fucking just stuffing their face.
They were doing they were doing field.
Oh my god. They were doing field research.
Holy shit. That's all we want to sell Naruto.
We got to think like Naruto.
You guys saw the images I posted last year in in Philly from the like
we went to a ramen shop that literally was like full of Naruto iconography.
Hell, yes. Hell, yes.
It's so happen to be in Chinatown in Philly.
There's a keep a look out for a place that has like a what a Luffy drawn on a sign.
One time I went.
Actually, why did you specifically mention Naruto online?
Did they like try to give you a bad deal?
Did they they they literally have worked with like every anime?
Yeah, they have. And most of them I never got a deal.
I mean, you get like it's a they give you like four grand.
It's not a bad deal.
But like I don't want to fucking show Naruto online.
The dead game is so shitty, though.
Yeah, well, tell that to Jeff do who made a whole video about how it's kind of OK, guys.
Naruto online is not terrible.
I played it for one hour and would never play it again.
But it's not terrible.
Will you buy it so I could make more grand?
The guys who I was addressing are not even malicious.
They're just like, yeah, like I can't believe how easy it is.
Like they'll just do any guy.
You know what? Let's talk about this.
Let's talk about and you guys are part of this problem.
Let's talk about how the millennial generation
has the lowest idea of what their standard of life should be ideally
of like any generation in history.
No, no, well, well, I better take Ben for example.
My my standard of living is lower even than that.
I don't I don't I don't think Ben has any problems with understanding that.
I think it's just that Ben legit doesn't give a fuck.
Like Ben is right because most most millennials are like sad about being.
Yeah, or like Ben is not.
He was like, oh, I can not work and live off of peanuts.
That sounds like I have a room that I can live in.
I'm I'm set. I'm done.
Let's talk about that.
That's that's about just we don't have to get into it too deep.
But a Gretzko, I was really thinking about a Gretzko reason
because I watched a bunch of episodes.
I'm going to finish it soon.
But like a Gretzko is the perfect picture of like a millennial,
even in America, because what she is is she is like she she chooses
to work this white collar job that she hates.
Like she's she's kind of punk in that she, you know,
like rebels that she hates the system and all that, but she is still 100 percent
complicit, a true like 80s or 70s punk would just not work there and like be poor.
But she willingly goes back day in day to suffer and to punish herself in this life.
I just got to get my my poker coins.
Well, I think the big part of it is that like most of these young people,
they just think that they have no options because they just they just go down
the list of like what jobs are in the area and they sign up for like whatever.
But like you got to be just too many people are too picky about what jobs they'll take.
It's like you can just go do road work or go farm or something.
Like those jobs pay decently and they have openings.
Nobody wants to do them.
But like guess what?
No matter what job you get, it's going to fucking suck.
And if you get a job at like Target or something,
they're just going to overwork you to death and they're not going to care about you.
They're going to fire you as soon as you don't pull numbers.
And it's like, yeah, you need to just don't worry about what the job is.
Just do the job that pays decently and will like pick the one that is physical labor
because it'll put you in better health.
You know, like, that's true.
Don't get a fucking white collar job working for pieces of shit
because you're just going to hate yourself become another average
obese American and hate your life and just be unhappy in all kinds of ways.
Physical labor actually makes you less depressed.
It really does.
Oh, I believe labor is is like it's like a cheat code
that people are sort of shied away from.
And I don't know why that's what I do every time.
Every time like my dad's a drummer and every so often he has a gig
and he's got a big old drum set and he needs help carrying it
from wherever it's stored into his car and, you know, guitar amps and stuff.
He does gigs.
So like I sometimes help us like a roadie picking up heavy things
and moving them around.
And it's like, yeah, this is this is really fun.
This is really I feel I feel so helpful right now.
I love doing this.
In spite of what I just said about Target, the one thing I did
like when I worked there was that I was on the flow team,
which is basically just move boxes around.
And like I gained a lot of muscle mass doing that.
And as a result, I was yeah, I was just stronger and fitter
just from doing like this incredibly basic and granted.
Like that's not the best way to get that fitness.
But like it made me appreciate the idea of like, man, having a physical
element to your job is just going to make your life better.
It's like doing chores around the house.
Like I love chores that demand a great amount of physical strength
and an endurance.
What sort of demands that?
Well, like my mom would need help digging stuff in the garden.
She she does gardening sometimes.
So I'm like, OK, there's a there's a tree stump.
Can you help dig it out?
Sure, I'll get the sledgehammer.
I'll get the pickaxe.
I'll get the fucking everything.
I'll smash that.
But if I have to like wash dishes, that's less as fun because you're just,
you know, they're not it's not very hard to move dishes.
And dusting, I've hated ever since like I was a little boy that was like,
you know, little baby kids chores that little baby kids can do.
And it was always like polishing and dusting.
And they were the fucking worst because you you have to be very delicate
to move in your little duster around.
I fucking hate it. Does anyone do any of you actually dust?
And no, no, no, no.
Does anybody ever do that?
It's just I only does my entire room around.
I have to I have to dust.
I don't do it too often.
But my boyfriend's allergic to dust and pollen and stuff like that.
So that's fair enough.
You know, I worked at at Pier One, doing like building furniture and stuff.
And that was a pretty physical job.
The only downside about it is like, like this was when I was starting
Best Guy Ever and like I was working on the the girl in login videos.
And it was this girl in login part one at that time.
Like I would I would do that.
I would go to work all day.
I like a couple of days a week I had school and then I would like come home
and try to work on like the videos and stuff.
And it's like it really does tax you physically a lot.
And so like I mean, that's a lot on the side.
It's tough. Yeah.
And I will I will say that that that with the target job, too,
because I was that was when I first started my YouTube channel
and I was doing two videos a week.
And it was some days I'd come home and it doesn't help.
I worked from like 4 a.m. to 12 was my hours.
So like I'd come home and just fucking crash and be like,
I can't even do a video because like how am I supposed to think my body is done?
You know, but you just got to overcome.
Just cheat your body with caffeine and beef to work or quit.
I had one summer I had a I had a job doing physical labor.
It was working with these.
It was like a temporary job with these guys with a truck were up from Alabama.
And their business was going to nursing homes and loading boxes,
mostly of like documents and loading boxes into their truck
and taking them to storage facilities.
So it was just a lot of lifting boxes and putting it into the truck.
Now, the job itself was pretty all right.
But the people that I had to do it with were very disturbing.
All right, the old folks, right?
They did not work at an old folks home.
They were just they work with all people that will destroy.
No, no, no, they don't.
No, no, no, that wasn't it.
They these guys were just being contracted by the nursing homes
for this one job of shipping shit.
It was a it was like an old maybe 50 something guy
and his son-in-law or his prospective son-in-law.
The guy was marrying the guy's daughter
and he was like marrying into this fucking own a truck business, basically.
So the older guy was grooming him and they were these two racist ass
Alabama. Oh, yeah, no, listen, they would just casually throw out
fucking slurs like at people like it within our field.
Alabama is like that's a scary.
I think that we drive by a black person
and they'd like say some shit about it.
And I'd be like, is this is this is this real?
Well, I have to ask Ben, these guys are white, right?
They they are. Oh, yeah, of course.
OK, just check. Just check.
So and I was like, and I think they could tell
that I was really uncomfortable with it and I thought that was really funny.
They were like, they were like the month.
Yeah, true.
And so the other I think they just kind of like,
you know, they just like said more shit and like kind of chuckled
because I was like, do something about a pussy.
Defend the the the Negro race.
Why don't you already?
I won't. I won't.
And the other two guys that I worked with, they were they were younger guys.
They were cousins of each other and they were like these two, you know,
they were like lower class like white dudes and like one of them.
I don't know, they were just they were like one was like fat and like
and kind of just kind of looked a bit like an ogre.
And the other was like skinny and like had like a fucking dome.
He had a big old dome head.
Are you sure it wasn't Ben and Munchy is what I mean?
And they and they and they were just saying, I don't know,
they just say funny shit like I was like one.
OK, the the the the the guy with the dome head.
One time he's like, hey, you're a scientist, right?
Like you do science because I was and I was like, oh, yeah.
So he like he tilts his head down and he points it like a rash on his head.
And he's like, I spilled some chemicals on my head.
And as you can see, and as you can, and as you can see,
my fucking skin is flaking off and my hair is falling out.
Do you think that's permanent?
And I was like, I don't do that kind of science, my dog.
Ben, I have to make a recommendation for you chemicals from you with your magic.
Ben, I recommend you read this book called
it's a manga called Disappearance Diary by Hideo Azuma,
who was like a famous lolly con manga artist in the 70s.
And then he he had basically this book is a autobiography
about two times that he just decided to be homeless,
to run away from his family, that he his family as in his kids and wife.
Oh, oh, no, run away to go be homeless for like a month at a time.
And then a third time where he ran off to go get a job
working for like like plumbing services or something like that.
So they're like they're on a bio.
Yeah, it's just his.
But it's presented as very cheerful and like upbeat
because his the tone of it is he says, I want to present the story,
but without the dark parts.
So it's just like him being like, oh, yeah, I'm homeless.
And like, oh, I found some stuff.
But like, it's very clear that this is really fucked
that like the situation is it is very, very fucked.
Because it's the first time he just like lives in the park and eats scraps.
The second time he gets a job for like this company.
And then he lives with like like they put a roof over his head.
But eventually he gets brought back to society by
who are brought back to his wife and kids,
because the police finally find him after the missing persons report.
And then the third part of them becoming like a real deep level alcoholic.
And let me tell you, I never actually understood what alcoholism really is
until I read this book.
Like you hallucinate shit and stuff like you're just like in the streets,
throwing up and seeing visions and shit like that.
Like it's fucked.
And then he goes to rehab and that's like the last part.
But it's it's really interesting to just like watch the not only this guy,
but especially in the plumbing chapter, the people he works with
like sound exactly like the people you're describing right now.
Like just kind of weird off kilter people who like are clearly in this job
because it's, you know, like this is the job weirdos end up in.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a it was I think you'd like the book a lot is why I recommend it.
I it sounds like I would be great friends with this fellow.
Yeah.
It's a pretty similar alternative lifestyle to Ben here.
Yeah, yeah, pretty much pretty much.
Yeah, he's considered the father of Lollicon by many people.
You can tell that they started off with a strong candidate as you can see.
Real real good how curious, how curious, how curious.
Incidentally, him and his wife like did like they they worked to get
like she was like his colorist or whatever like for his old Lolli shit.
And most of it was not even really sexual, but like kind of more of a punk
aesthetic thing, like they were doing it to be rebels, like to say, fuck,
you were drawing like shed man.
Yeah, a little bit like better art than shed.
That's cool.
Is that even possible?
That's I don't know, man.
I don't know.
I have a topic that I've been thinking about.
It's it's it's come on along after like the The New Gorillaz album came out
and I listened to the single with the animation and then I went back
and re listened to Plastic Beach and I got way into it and I love Plastic Beach.
Welcome to the world of the Plastic Beach.
So good.
And and there's this other guy on YouTube, Lewis Cole, who I've found,
who is like, I would describe him as like a funkier, more
musician-y Bill Wirtz, who does like a lot of weird, but incredibly
tight, musically, instrumentally music stuff.
And I've just been like looking at all that and I'm like, I just got to be a musician.
I just want to make music all the time.
And I just don't I don't get it.
I don't know how to do it.
It's kind of annoying.
It's kind of annoying how I have some talent, but I can't
turn it into a song that can be listened to.
You got to take my approach, which is open up FL Studio and just
fuck around for like an hour and then publish it.
It's not a bad idea.
I I tried FL Studio, but it's bad.
You got to try it out, I guess, I don't know.
Well, it's it's not as easy to like record live instruments into it.
The thing that sort of leads into like the talking about physical labor,
because I was thinking I have like trouble, like my brain is a bit
different from the way that I have been using it.
I work so much better with like physical things and with my hands,
like in art school, in, you know, school art class.
I was always like the sculpture kid, like I would make the most elaborate,
incredible sculptures, which would take a really long time
because they required like repetitive tests of like sticking things together
and twisting wire around things and stuff.
And I love that.
I love the whole process of like making a 3D thing with my hands
for a very, very long time with repetitive motions, which is why I was thinking
maybe I'd like and every time there's like physical.
I like using my hands for repetitive motions, too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I mean, the sculpture in my head just is a dick.
That's what I'm. Yeah, yeah.
All right. Well, if you must, if you must know, my one of my pieces was like
an entire man made out of tape, like I molded after my own body.
Dude, we we used to have we used to have a tape man
that was made out of Victor's body and then like a mannequin head.
And we used him in all the old project
awesomeness videos, like anytime we someone was getting killed,
like you'd see a sword about to hit somebody and then it would just swap
out to the tape man getting killed.
Actually, we beat it up so bad that we had to throw it away.
Rest in peace.
But my point with that is like I I don't like computers,
despite using them for so many things.
I'm so much more of a physical guy in terms of like,
I just prefer doing things physically.
Looking at the studio makes makes me a spiritual guy looking at
FL Studio and clicking on on clicking on all the like different keypads
to make melodies just makes me die.
Makes me puke. It makes me.
I don't ever do that.
I like it is just like shit myself.
And I just want to go to the keyboard, which is much more physical.
You just tap the thing and it makes the sound.
And I'm like, boop, boop, boop, boop.
And I'm not very good at playing the keyboard, but like the drums in there is
like it's it's great.
But when I go to like click record and try to line tracks up, I fall apart.
I just don't I don't care anymore.
I need a recording monkey.
I need I need a digital boy.
Let me let me tell you, you know, I'm on your side here
because I just I started writing a book.
I'm writing a new book.
It's called fixed that for you.
And it's going to be my my my just fix for everything in the world.
And I'm writing it by hand.
I like I bought a notebook just to write by hand because I'm able to just
formulate sentences better because it takes so much longer than typing that
like in the time it takes me to write one sentence.
I've thought of how to say the next one much more cleverly.
So like it reads like just a wall of aphorisms and funny shit.
And I love it.
And yeah, I think I'm just going to any any time I want to write something
more personal from now on, I think I'm just going to do it by hand.
Hey, that's a that's a far more interesting story than what I'm about to say.
But I just want to say that the the Galaxy Note 8 available at retailers
near you now sponsored by Samsung sponsored by Samsung like has this feature
that I thought was going to be bullshit, but just is the best thing ever.
And it's that like it's just so there's a little pen thing that you click out
and pull out. That's the reason why it's called the note and all.
And when you do that, it instantly pops up.
It goes. I don't even have to click anything.
It goes straight to these right memo on screen.
I then just write whatever I'm thinking of with zero delay or having to fuck around.
Click save and boom.
I have like stored this information that was in my brain.
It is so much better than what I used to do of going into this bullshit
like memo app I had and then like type me on the fucking pussy keyboard.
Just scribbling it down with my actual words.
It's just so much.
It's a life upgrade of the highest caliber.
Incidentally, Samsung asked that we read their slogan.
Yeah, this ad so Samsung Galaxy 8 get one niggers.
They're talking to the urban market.
Yeah, that's exactly what I was going to say.
I got to say, I, you know, I personally don't necessarily support everything
that our sponsors say, you know, this is not necessarily
represent representative of our opinions.
Emotionally paid a lot of money like you all understand.
We were just talking about how much millennials need money.
Like it paid us a lot to say that like intellectually.
How can I disagree with that sentiment?
But emotionally, emotionally, so if you have a problem,
so if you have a problem with the slogan, take it up with fucking Benjamin
Franklin, he says, just offering Samsung,
Frank proffering a hundred dollar bill was the joke there.
I could point to my dollar bills.
Yeah, it didn't.
That was a visual.
But no, it was a visual joke.
I got to take it up with George Washington.
Yeah, but he's dead.
Yeah, you're dead.
He's really, I recall they first his head, the Disney Castle,
and he's going to come back any one of these days now.
George Washington.
Yeah, yeah, Walt Disney and George Washington, great contemporary.
Dude, do you think George Washington and George Lopez are related?
George Washington was George of the jungle.
I hope my fucking mom almost stayed.
George Lopez, and that's not a fucking joke.
She was just about to go on a date with him, but my fucking on cock blocked
with who?
George Lopez.
Oh, I thought you said George Lucas.
No, I would have been way better.
I mean, you should get all the Georgia's together.
He got cut by C3PO.
George Lucas.
No, sorry.
George Lopez used to do like, like, you know, before he was big,
he just used to do comedy clubs around LA.
He used to just fuck sluts, you know, just used to fuck sluts.
And, you know, my mom was around.
Yeah, my aunt knew him, like personally, my aunt, like, was his friend,
like, for real.
And George was like, you know, like, I want to date your sister.
And she was like, oh, no, my sister wouldn't be interested.
So my fucking aunt cock blocked my mom.
Even though my mom would have dated George Lopez.
Dude, that's what happened.
Was this was this is this like George Lopez would have been your dad?
Is what you're saying?
Yes, he could have been my dad.
He mad.
I was afraid it would have been before or after you were alive before.
Yeah, yeah.
His seed could have made me.
Well, I mean, yes, it could have been.
Don't take this from me.
All right.
Well, enjoy.
Who else has got a thing going on?
And I'm an expo.
Oh, yeah, if you would give me the floor for a moment.
And expo, along with like all conventions and all vacations,
basically any time I'm away from the house for more than like three days,
I have like a like a like a life crisis of varying quantities
and my entire perception on life changes.
And I'm now I'm happy to announce
Macraman, I'm exo officially a socialist now.
I just am a socialist and I now have no sympathy for capitalism
or any hierarchies of any kind that I'm now communist.
But you were last anime expo.
It was due to our capitalist connections
that we were able to get into that Illuminati party.
Fucking exactly, Nate.
That's exactly what I'm fucking talking about.
All right, flashback flashback to last year.
I'm with Digi and Nate.
I'm part of the fucking bourgeoisie.
I'm getting into all the spirit cooking parties.
I'm getting to all the fucking secret Illuminati Suarez.
I'm getting to all the crazy one rooftop.
I got to go to all the fucking breakfast.
Breakfast every day.
I got to go to all the fucking anime expo.
Orders and crabs at the Wahoo.
I got fucking so many aids.
I can't see straight from all the Illuminati Suarez.
I went to an anime expo.
Why don't you just do and blow off of anime hookers?
Yeah, those maids were basically anime hookers.
Wearing one of those masks, those French funny masks.
What are they called?
Oh, Guy Fox.
No, no, no.
You know, when you go to like a secret Illuminati club meeting.
And they have like a Tom Cruise mask from Eyes Wide Shut.
One of those like sex masks.
You mean like a Richard Nixon mask?
You mean like the mask from the mask?
It's super long nose, the fucking, the old doctor masks
with the long ass nose.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Like the late night.
I walked into an anime expo wearing the mask from the mask.
I got so much fucking pussy.
You wouldn't even be that different
if you were wearing the Jim Caron mask.
That'd be an acceptable costume.
Why didn't the mask just fucking rule?
Actually, like, munchy acting normal.
Like, if you just put on the mask, you'd be like,
that man's been possessed by the mask.
It's like, no, it's just munchy.
That's true.
In any fucking way.
Last year at an expo, I was a big shot.
Everyone fucking knew my name.
Jeff, it was like, I'm kind of being
in your fucking arm retrieval videos.
I was like, maybe I'll put you on the wait list.
Anyway.
Yeah.
Arm retrieval.
Oh my god.
OK.
That's how you know you made it.
Yeah.
Anyway, this year's fucking smash cut.
Fucking, like, no transition.
Do not fade out any audio or video.
Like, just cut the scene mid-transition.
Here we are at this year.
I'm with my fucking bullshit friends
who haven't made a fucking YouTube video.
Fuck you, Ethan.
You suck dick.
Fucking Ethan.
Fucking Leif.
They don't know shit about being a fucking god like I do.
They don't even know the rituals.
So we're fucking walking.
We have to wait in lines.
We have to fucking do our taxes.
We have to fucking, we have to keep our heads,
like, firmly looking at the sidewalk at all times.
We can't look up unless we be fucking shackled
and fucking lashed.
It's an awful experience.
Like, we can't do any of the bourgeoisie spirit cooking.
We just have to sit in line like everyone else.
We have to, like, we have to fucking bear
the brute force of the sun.
Guys, guys, this anime expo was so fucking hot at nighttime.
At nighttime.
It was pitch black at 10 fucking PM to 11 PM.
It was over 100, and the wind was blowing,
and there was not a cool breeze.
It was not a cool breeze.
It's like a fiery hell storm.
It was like every time, it was like a fucking fat guy blowing
spit into your fucking face, and the spit was lava.
That's what it was fucking like going to anime expo.
It was a fucking nightmare.
It was a nightmare.
So we couldn't go, you know, I don't know if you guys
remember this specifically, but there's like this, like,
anime expo last year, Naden, did you?
Yeah, I am.
There was like this part where special select industry
people could take an escalator up to a higher level.
Yeah, of course, of course.
You know, like a speedway was like Rainbow Road.
That shit, of course, that's locked fucking off.
Oh, I forgot about that.
That would have been completely cucked getting around the place.
I mean, for what it's worth, I thought anime expo sucked
balls and cock, like, in spite of us having all those,
like, I hate it when it's like for the normos,
like, munchy here, you know?
I know, I'm a fucking proletaire.
That's the entire point of that.
So I realized, I realized what it's like to be on the fucking
bottom and it's not worth it.
I, it's not fucking fair that these digital influencers
get to have all the fucking, they have a monopoly on space
and air.
It's not fucking fair.
I mean, that rhymes.
I would say, for what it's worth, I would say that a lot of it,
a lot of last year, it was not really the capitalism
that allowed you all that.
It was my libertarianism that allowed that,
because you were not even a guest.
I just snuck you into everything because I don't give a fuck
about the rules.
Only I had like a password.
It's superfluous.
The rich rid the rich and the poor gay.
That's my saying and I'll stick into it.
Anyway, I will not, I would not rest.
This was like day fucking one that I realized
that I needed to destroy anime expo,
like the entire debate and like topple the government.
And I needed to fucking raise the tricolor
of the four day passes and I needed to declare influencers
no longer.
I needed to fucking shoot up every single YouTuber
that I saw.
And so I went through this like character arc of like,
I tried to like infiltrate this like parliamentary debate
otaku debate so I could spread the world.
And if you see, I believe Ethan posted them on IGTV
the other day, I need to tweet them out myself.
But the second round that I was in.
Whoa, Ethan has an IGTV account?
Yeah, yeah.
What's his name on there?
I have no fucking clue.
Dick Sucker, one, two, three, four, I believe.
On Twitter, I retweeted the first round of the debate
sorry and where I got stomped.
But on the second and third one, I fucking killed it.
Because all I did was just say popular shit.
All I said was like, more people have seen Naruto
so it's better, vote for me because you have seen Naruto.
I fucking guarantee you've seen Naruto, vote for me.
Even though the question wasn't even about Naruto.
And so I just fucking slammed that shit.
It's the people want what the people want.
And that's all the power, they all want power.
And that's how it became a fucking revolutionary God.
And it was great.
So I'm literally a socialist now.
I'm literally a fucking socialist.
That's literally true.
Like a true socialist.
I don't believe being a populist and being a socialist
are necessarily the same.
Well, I mean, with Munchie here, in true socialist fashion,
it is simply the fact that other people have things
that he doesn't have that makes him decide
that this whole apple cart needs to be fully turned upside down.
Like cabbages.
It was fucking, oh, on a tangentially related note,
this made me think about my foreign policy.
This made me think about my foreign policy hard.
My foreign policy is fucking neutered.
Related, this is like the social factor.
This is the social question.
I was talking about the political question.
Sure, I could bypass lines and everyone bowed down
to me last year.
But the real thing that was important
was that fucking people knew who I was.
That there were people like super eye patch wolf.
So I just met with Digi and by the end of it,
he knew my name.
He knew who I was.
I don't even fucking know that guy, but he knew my name.
And this year, it was eye opening
because here's the thing.
It's not like I was cast to the shadows
and no one knew who I was.
Because weirdly, bizarrely, unbelievably, in fact,
I was stopped by fans constantly.
Oh, no way.
Every hour or more, I would run into them a new fan.
And that's not a fucking exaggeration.
It was unbelievably constant.
And the fucking basement and the entertainment hall, it was.
I was just walking by a booth and just some fucking wage
cock was like, oh my god, are you Munchie?
I love the PCP.
I used to watch on time and I was like, oh, why'd you stop?
And he was like, oh, the drama got too much.
I was like, oh, hello.
And then I walked away.
Sick.
He should have said pussy.
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, I just was getting stopped and non-stop.
So it's like, I have the power.
I have the power.
But for some reason, I've just been so neutered lately.
Between last AMX show and this, I've
been so neutered where I don't fucking try and reach out
and tackle people who are above me anymore.
Like the entire reason why I'm here
is that I tackled DigiBrownie and I
got him to fucking submit to my will.
I don't do that anymore.
I don't talk to anyone anymore.
Well, is there anyone who you're impressed enough with
to feel that you want to tackle them?
Yeah, a lot of people, a lot of them.
Well, go tackle those motherfuckers.
I very clearly could, who are small enough and important
enough to me that I very easily could do it.
And it just hasn't really been in my thought process.
But it is now.
It is now.
I'm thinking about it a lot, really.
Well, that's good.
I mean, the thing is that every time you make a new friend,
you complicate your life that much more.
It's like, if you want to have any really meaningful
connection with this person beyond like, I mean,
some people are easy.
It's like, my art and your art are similar enough
that we could easily collaborate and then never talk again.
And that's fine.
But if you want to be seriously involved,
it's like, I have to now know another person.
And then all of their entire social circle
is now on your shoulders too, because they have all the shit
they're worried about.
If you want to talk about meaningful connection,
let's talk about the one that I established yesterday.
I was just on tour.
With Munchie's mom.
Hi, fucking fucker.
No, no.
I mean, I told this on my live stream yesterday,
but whatever, I mean, I'm happy to tell it again.
I saw that my boy, lobster boy, Tyrar A. Deweyo,
the ASMR legend and god, he just hit 100,000 subscribers
recently.
And got his silver play button.
And he made a video where he just says the usual stuff of,
like, I never gave up so hard.
I make content people likes, blah, blah, blah.
And I like that guy overall, even though we disagree
on some stuff.
I just unsolicited.
Just tweet out that video with the thing.
Hey, just want to give a shout out to this guy who I know
I'm a weirdo who likes ASMR.
ASMR is cool.
Fuck you.
Tyrar is great.
Congrats, dude.
You're the best.
I know we disagree on a lot of stuff, but you rule.
And like I tweeted that out, we added him.
And he responded, and we just had a whole conversation
about how we're both Ohio boys, and he's cool,
and he likes me, he subscribed to my fucking channel.
He watched the fucking, whatever it is, the fucking,
right, the Thanos video.
He had made a bunch of ASMR Thanos videos himself.
And he told me, he commented on that video,
do a video about no country for old men, which I'm seriously
considering doing based on that recommendation.
And it was just out of, I respect this guy?
What was his name did you ask?
Have you seen the movie before?
Yes, I have, yes I have.
I quite like it, quite fond of it.
And I was actually just watching some analysis videos
on it the other day, so I'm kind of up to speed.
But anyway, so good things happen when you just
at people in a non-obnoxious and generally positive way
on Twitter or elsewhere.
It was great.
I'm constantly surprised on how true that is.
It's like so many people who just like at famous people
and then get a reply in like a semi nice way.
People do it to me.
It's like famous people are human or something.
It's like Flattery will get you everywhere.
It's insane.
I think that's what Maryweather,
do you guys know Maryweather?
Post Pavilion?
No, I don't know her.
I don't know her.
No, he's this comic guy.
He has a bunch of popular series like Winter Moon
and Steam Dragon Express and stuff.
Oh, you were telling me about this guy.
I don't know.
He knows everyone.
Like he knows, oh god, who are, he was named.
Casey Neistat.
Like he's personally in touch with the Zontan guy.
He asked me to write.
No, he probably knows Shadbass.
Oh shit, there's more.
God, I'm blanking on names.
But I think he just fucking ats people.
I mean, you guys remember DJ Calcos, right?
From the Brony days.
Where Calcos was just a guy who just got the contact
of like every Brony famous person.
So they all knew who he was and he didn't really do anything.
Like he had a, he had like a third string radio show
on Celestia Radio with like 10 listeners, you know?
Like Nino's the same.
Nino's the same kind of guy.
Yeah, Nino's very similar.
Nino got himself onto Pantaku and everything
and he actually does make decent videos and raps and shit.
But like, he knew, he like writes for Gigguk
because he talked to him.
You know, like just messaged him.
I almost, I mean, oh he knows Christian with Gigguk
just by adding him in a critical way at one point.
Mary, Mary knows Christian.
He even got Chris to, Chris even made fan art
of his characters just because he, I don't know.
He's just like, yeah, this is what he does.
He just talks to people.
It's not hard.
I mean, again, the only reason I avoid it is that
like you can have lots of frivolous connections
but having a meaningful connection
just is a lot of work.
That's why I try to keep it to the PCP
because like it's easy to keep track of all you guys
because we're all kind of doing the same thing
and we mostly work with each other.
And like, I don't really have to worry about,
like none of us have such complicated home lives
that it's like, you know, that I have to worry
about everything else going on with you.
It's like, mostly we just talk to each other.
But like, it's because some of the other people I know
who have like their own communities
that they're a part of, like those communities hate me.
And it's like, those friends of mine have to like
constantly like justify being friends with me
to their communities.
And it's just like, this is a load of horse shit.
Like, I don't want to have to worry about all your bullshit
just to be friends with you, you know?
Didgy, I don't know if I said this on record or not
but one of my real life friends,
well, more like one of my real life acquaintances
has stopped talking to me because you're a pedophile.
Oh, what?
I'm not even a fucking pedophile.
That's fucked up.
No, what do you mean?
Question mark?
What do you mean?
That you're not a pedophile?
What?
No, I'm not a pedophile.
No, not, didgy, not real.
Well, he's joking.
He's joking.
Oh, okay.
But wait, wait, wait, but this friend is real, right?
Yes, this friend is real.
Yes, someone's, someone.
Okay, okay.
And they're not talking to you.
I mean, how much do you value this friend?
Were you like, oh, good riddance?
No, no, no, no, no, this is not,
all I'm saying is that this is really funny.
That's, that's, that's, that's okay.
No, it is funny.
I'm just wondering if like it was a,
like, was it like a good friend you lost or anything?
I don't know for sure that they top talked to me
because of this, but like, they stopped talking to me
and I then found out that they were really upset
that you were a pedophile.
Oh, well, I mean, fair enough.
Supposed, allegedly.
Oh, yeah, allegedly.
They haven't, they haven't caught me yet.
Man, that's fucked up.
It's really fucking funny.
I mean, there's a, I have like some of my friends
who were like, told me that they like unfollowed me
on Twitter because I was like defending Lolliport
and I was like, can we have a conversation about that?
Because the fact that you did that means
that I think you're a piece of shit.
Like, if you think it's wrong for me to defend this stuff,
please come out and say so to my face
so I know that we're, that we are now in conflict.
Because this is not something I want you to write off
and be like, oh, that's digi bro off.
No, fuck you.
Like, come say it to my face.
Let's have a conversation.
Cause if you're not willing to accept this,
then I think you're a bad person.
You know, like if you are actively against,
like any kind of art expression, fuck you.
That's just my statement.
That's a pretty informative statement
on how they view like what people should
and shouldn't be, it baffles me to this day.
The number of people who consider themselves
like libertarian-esque and yet are opposed
to like Lollicon art.
I think they just are not sincere in their beliefs.
And you really, when you beat him over that,
like, I'll tell you man, Dick Masterson,
when I went on his show, he was a great example.
Yeah, and he said that was one of his favorite calls
because like it really made him confront it
and be like, if I'm supposed to be a libertarian,
I have to like, you know, like if you're,
if you're gonna go around calling yourself libertarian,
you can't be against Lolliport.
Like it is literally, that is, you know,
it's in, what's the word I'm looking for, incongruent?
That's not right.
Yes, it's incongruent with the belief system of-
Incongruent.
Yeah, that's a better word.
Well, I mean, you can be a libertarian
and still be against some things, right?
If you wanna go out there with a whole nine yards
and be like, no, no, no, I'm an egalitarian
or I'm a libertarian, but like I do believe
that this thing like actively hurts people
so like we should do something to like discourage it,
you know, in whatever way.
Dude, the part that pisses me off the most
is like the SJWs and shit who,
because SJWs are very anti-Lolliport,
which is fucking bizarre to me
because they're all about having acceptance
for the shit they like and then they-
There's like two camps there, isn't there?
Like some is kind of really, weirdly pro it.
I have no idea.
I've only seen like the anti people
and it really fucking pisses me off.
Fair enough.
Fuck you guys.
Well, hey, I mean, totally, totally tangent.
Fair it out.
I was going back to like the subject
that got us two here and just wanted to say
on the subject of like people like communicating
with people and like adding them and stuff,
I'm not trying to encourage legions of people
to at me and just say hi or what's up.
No, no, no, not at all.
Make sure it's a meaningful connection.
Bring something to the table to offer,
like something good that I'll care about.
That's the whole thing.
If you wanna like make connections to people,
like you have to offer value.
Of course.
Yeah.
Well, that's part of the reason
where I don't think I would be like a good person
to go to a con to have people meet me.
Like the time we went to BronyCon,
people around, they were talking to everyone.
And I was there and some of them were like,
well, okay, you're here too.
I may as well get a signature.
And I felt really bad.
Not like I wasn't cool enough for them,
but I felt like just bad in general.
Like they didn't think much of me.
And I was like, well, I'd rather you didn't ask
for a signature if you don't actually give a shit.
I mean, that's fair.
That's fair.
I can understand that.
Incredibly variable experiences with people at cons
because they're definitely the ones who come up to you
and they want the signature.
And then they just kind of stand next to you expectantly.
Like, okay, like, I'm here to do the thing.
And I'm just like, I don't know what you want me to do
because I don't know you
and I don't know what your connection to me is.
I don't know what videos of mine you've seen.
They got the signature.
But it's time to get working on this best friendship now.
Let's get going.
But there are a lot of people I've met at cons
who I have had interesting conversations with,
you know, where like they come around
and they come up and they're like, hey, Digi,
I'm a big fan, let's talk about your stance on this show.
You know, a lot of the times it's just like
some misunderstanding that's cleared up in two seconds
and they feel stupid to walk away.
But like other times we get into some heavy,
you know, some heavy discussions
and it's like, you know, there's a lot of people
who send me the message like,
hey, you and I see eye to eye on lots of things.
I think we'd make good friends.
And I'm always just like, yeah, of course.
Like if you watch my videos consistently,
it's most likely that you're someone who's,
who would be good friends with me.
But the thing is that for you, it's like, wow,
I'm seeing this Digi Bro guy,
the first person I've ever heard
like have the same opinions as me.
I want to be his friend.
And I'm like, dude, look,
do you see that I have 350,000 subscribers?
Go talk to any of those guys.
They're all just like you.
All my fans are exactly like each other.
They'll look the same.
They'll act the same.
They're the same age.
They go to the same places.
They like the same shows.
Just talk to each other.
There's only one of me.
I don't have time.
You're totally right about that.
But you know what's changed the game on that front?
Our Discord's.
Because seeing our Discord's,
like bring people together to act,
like there's a book club that's begun both in the potty cast
and in my personal, like best guy ever Discord server,
which warms my fucking heart
that these people are getting together.
On my Discord server,
there's guys who play D&D together,
that they came together through this.
Yeah, all kinds of stuff.
I love that.
My Discord formed like a, sorry.
Mine just like early on when it was pretty active,
like most of the people from mine
who were like pretty active in there
just went off and made their own other.
Cause I basically told people like,
look, I want this Discord to be accessible to new fans.
So like, I don't want new people to come in here
and feel like they're not a part of the clique.
So like, if you guys want to be clickish,
go make another Discord.
We don't want a rowdy fucking.
It was a super successful.
God, how could you not?
A bunch of people in my Discord server
have like started podcasts with each other.
Oh yeah, that happened in mine too.
Yeah.
I encourage that.
Cause I made a podcasting like,
I made a podcasting channel when I created the Discord,
like just in case people wanted to do that.
Oh, that's cool.
There was for a while the Digi Boys channel,
which had one podcast that was just for like
group watching anime and another podcast
that was two of the like,
like the main guys who were doing
weekly analysis of my content as a podcast.
It lasted a couple of months,
but yeah, again, those guys have gone on.
Like a lot of people make connections in our fan groups.
I love that.
And I know most of us are dating fans
who we met that way as well.
You ain't wrong.
Gross.
So I also, and tell me what you think about this.
I made the roles.
I made the roles in my Discord server,
like based on what kind of art people do,
like there's like a role for draw people
and a role for video editors
and a role for writers and musicians.
And like my idea was that if I did this,
that maybe they could like collaborate with each other.
That's a good idea.
And even us, what was the lowly video hacks,
such as myself?
The lowest tier is the video hack,
which Nate sadly inhabits.
That's right.
Yeah.
I'm gonna, I set up a board on my Discord server.
The second highest tier is the ultimate art form,
the drawsman.
Above that, even that is where I reside
at the coveted role of Ideas Man.
Yeah, that's been all right.
That's the best guy.
In my Discord, I created a Flash Pros board,
but it very immediately became just meme cancer.
That's all it is.
People just posting like horse shit.
Yeah, yeah.
Turns out my fans are not really Flash Pros writers
for the world.
Imagine that, imagine that.
Hey, while we're talking about just cool things
about our Discord, I just wanna give a shout out
to the vibrant community of the Poddy cast
that me and Gib have.
Is that true?
I did not even know that.
Do you not have its own Discord?
Yeah, we've got our own Discord.
It's part of the Patreon rewards.
And more than that, I don't know,
man, this is a great tabic actually,
but like we have instituted an intense cast hierarchy
between the pledge rolls.
There's a literal race war.
Yeah, that's right.
All at all times.
The lowly, because you can get into the server for free
and you can get into the main chat,
but you are a disgusting lowly pathetic white.
We have to hashtag kill all whites.
They are a disgrace.
They have access to the general voice chat,
but if you pledge even $1, anything above that,
you are a colored and you are a supreme God in the server.
And at that point, you get excellent emotions.
It doesn't matter what color you are,
you just have to be a baby color.
So you'd be a POC or a patron of color.
That's exact, a POC.
Oh, oh my God.
You, I mean, yeah, there is some disagreement
or there's some ranking between the colors,
but most important is colored versus non-colored.
I mean, my favorite thing about like the way
that sort of spiraled is like the main chat is,
it started off slow because it was a small discord,
but as the putty cuss became more popular,
lots of normal fags jumped in there
and they started having stupid discussions.
Is the putty cuss like popular?
What is going on?
Dude, it's getting popular.
We've had videos with like 10,000 views,
which is like, you know, for that show, it's great.
I think our biggest is like 20,000.
One of these days, I'll catch up on one piece.
Shout out to the leader of the whitey army sigh.
You will be dispatched along with your low league.
It's not that size, CY size, a different size.
I see, you had like one chapter got like 19K views recently.
That's right.
That seems to be like the,
there's a few of these that blew up,
but it seems like I'm guessing really big chapters.
That's exactly right.
That we get out.
Once again, the highest grossing arm retrieval
is the one that you guys were on.
Oh, really?
Oh, great.
You got that potty cast bomb.
What do you mean by grossing?
Like just view counts or like how?
Yeah, yeah, view.
Yeah, there's no money, no money's here.
You should, the way it's sort of spiraled out of control
is like people in the blue tier, like it's like the $1.
That's the $1.
The cabin boys.
They started saying, oh man, all these whites are so annoying.
They have such bad ideas.
We patrons are smarter because there are less of them.
But then like every color up, every like higher tier patron
sort of like copies that idea and then like,
those stupid blues, those fucking idiots,
they would have arguments in there
and like the very top chat is just me and Nate
and we laugh at everyone.
Well, the top is the commander's lounge
where the commanders and the edgy cool guys
or the cool edgy mysterious guys,
that's the one below commander.
They're allowed in there too.
Cause they're,
Would Luffy's entire crew be classified as that?
Like, cool edgy mysterious guys?
Yeah.
If you were like to build these lounges around like character,
like what characters in one piece
would actually live in these lounges?
Would it just be like Luffy and his whole crew
are all like a captain and cool edgy mysterious guy?
I mean, basically, yeah.
Yeah.
They all, I mean, they're more of a family.
We are a regimented capitalist enterprise
on the body cast crew as they all know.
And it's great.
It's great.
It funds money to the top.
They have their own book club.
They have a lot of their own like little things they do
and they're constantly chatting in all the chats.
Very active, very cool.
It's great.
I love that service.
It's one of my favorites.
My discord's fucking sick.
There's like almost all the people who patron me
are all art boys and do like creative stuff in some way.
So I made like a chat for them to just like show off
their shit so like we can easily share what everyone's doing.
And then they started doing a,
like sort of an accountability thing.
Like every like two weeks they're like,
this is what I did.
This is what I worked on.
So they're doing like a little micro art.
What is art apologies with each other?
Yeah.
Basically it's fucking,
they beat us to the punch on art apology.
It's kind of embarrassing, but it's also kind of rad.
So yeah, it's fucking dope.
We'd have to apologize about that.
Yeah, yeah, well, you should for sure.
Apologize to the audience for doing that.
Shout out to the Golden Shell Foundry,
the best fan slash friend discord ever made.
It's everything about it.
Didn't it die?
I thought it was dead.
No, no.
Dude, what are you talking about?
It's fucking a lie as well.
I guess I've just never been,
I've never been cool enough to come in, I guess.
Nah, you've never been invited.
This is an invite level only discord
and there are regular purges.
We're all the cool...
Well, hang on, Munchy,
how good can this discord server be
if it doesn't even generate revenue for you?
How, I don't understand, like how...
I don't know if this is a good business's decision
to make this discord actually.
I don't know, I think we might be wasting our time
inputting resources into this.
This one we're doing right now.
Pull out, pull out.
Yeah.
Yeah, shout out, shout out.
I love, by the way, who else loves the awesome one?
My discord is the best discord by the way.
Oh yeah?
I bet it sucks.
I bet it's gay.
I'm not even going to pretend
like anything interesting happens in my discord at all.
Well, to be fair, mine is really quiet,
but I kind of like it because it's so chill
and there's like regulars and I like,
hi people, I know who you are.
Let's cry.
I often to the mage discord every so often
to just look at the not-safe-for-work chat
and then run away.
Dude, Michelle has told me
about your not-safe-for-work chat, Gib.
In tones, in words that would terrify
a less powerful man than myself,
it sounds like the most debauched server of all time.
And by the way, this is why I want DeVoo
to make his own server as well.
Cause just imagine what his not-safe-for-work.
I actually have no idea what's in my NSFW one
cause I just made it as a containment board
cause a lot of people post porn everywhere if I did.
I mean, I did the same thing.
But I've never actually looked at it right now.
It's like a fortune I had to make the pony board
cause we had to contain the pony scourge, you know,
on the, on the, on V and whatnot.
Occasionally I will post like, you know,
a hundred images of Riska in my not-safe-for-work chat
at a time.
It'll just be like a little, little party for everybody.
Can you drag and drop a hundred images into Discord?
Do you have to do them individually?
Probably not.
I think I did it in bunches.
Damn, okay, okay.
This is what I posted in my not-safe-for-work chat.
Oh God, what is it?
Oh no.
I want to wiggle my pee pee.
That's extremely sexual.
It was, it was a screenshot from a video I watched
and laughed so hard I had to share with people.
That's explicit.
I don't know if I would just do that.
How would you do that NSFW?
I don't know.
Would you have that as your desktop background?
That's, that's the joke.
Yeah, good idea.
I'll put that in my.
We have, behind the scenes,
pull the curtains back a little bit, people.
We have, we have a, we have a,
we have a topics list here that we,
everyone just casually will put in stuff
that they want to talk about so everyone's on the same page.
Yeah.
And on here, you know, in the show notes type of thing,
I see your note is Boyga,
a big juicy one in parentheses.
That's right.
Yeah, I'm curious.
I'm curious about that.
Yeah.
What do you.
Consider my interest.
Is this just in the regular PCP topics doc?
Is that a different one?
Yeah, I put Boyga.
It's a Boyga.
A big juicy Boyga.
Burger.
Hamburger.
Yeah.
Well, a full disclosure.
This was Michelle's best tweet of all time.
Was simply the word Boyga with a,
with a hamburger emoji and like a bunch
of New York emojis next.
And she was very proud and she laughed for hours.
And I agreed.
How many, how many likes?
How many likes?
For her, I mean, for her pathetic baby Twitter,
probably like five, lol.
Sad.
We give her Twitter.
May gets like a few hundred likes on some shit.
Well, she is the greatest anime analyst of all time.
So of course she does, you know?
I mean, that's just a fact.
So do we want to move on to questions?
Are we done with, is that, was that in for the Boyga?
Like, yeah.
Was that why it was on the list?
The reason I put it there was as a joke.
And I mean, like, that's the story.
Michelle said it and it was funny.
There's nothing else to it.
All right.
Do we want to move on to question six?
We've been going for almost a hour and a half.
Wait, what about Mages?
What about Mages' topic?
She's got one here.
Oh, bitching?
No, no, no, no, no.
Let's not talk about that topic.
Mages, I'm calling you out.
Why?
I'm calling you out about this topic.
Which is.
No, it's because we're gonna just go back
to talking about Shadmin' again.
And I don't want to talk about Shadmin' again.
No, we aren't.
Why don't you guide the discussion, Mages?
Well, I mean, she doesn't want to.
I don't want to do it.
Let's not do it.
Here's our first question.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, did you, did you?
We've got things to do before we get to the question.
Now, this is, there's been updates.
I don't know what the format is anymore.
Okay, it seems to be different every time we want to.
There's good news.
Preferably no format.
There is good news here, everybody.
Today is, in fact, the last time
we're ever doing the fan art section.
Wait, wait, Nate.
I have to tell you, I've stolen more of your goods.
What do you mean?
I stole more of your shit from our parents.
Oh my God.
What did you take?
Because, you know, because I had to go there
because they're moving, so I had to help them pack.
I just remember going back to your house,
you just had to take another thing from Nate's place.
Yeah, I mean, I just had to take,
yeah, this was willful theft this time, okay?
This one, there's no excuse for it.
What the hell was it?
I'll tell, I'm holding the hostage.
I have, Nate, I have your electric globe
that shoots the lightning bolts
that you touch your hands on.
No, I love that thing.
Yes, no, it's mine now.
I spent like $100 on that when I was like 10.
And now I have it next to,
you're gonna have to come get it in person.
I'm gonna steal my shoes back, Ben,
and stomp in your fucking skull to take back my like home.
It's gone from Ben vehemently denying
that he's done anything wrong,
and there has been no benefit to the thing.
Ben has completely and rapidly seated
all moral high ground completely.
Let's just say, oh, let's just say I'm borrowing it.
I mean, parents needed to clear out space.
I'm just holding it for you.
Oh, he's a nice guy.
He's doing your parents a favor, Nate.
I'm doing you and them a favor.
I really appreciate that.
You're welcome.
Well, you know what?
You know what I'll say?
Consider it, we'll consider it alone,
and I'm actually glad that thing's getting used
because it is cool, and I do like it.
It's way cool.
It warms my heart.
So like any good capitalist,
you're gonna be charging like 15% interest.
Well, of course.
I just need more furniture to actually put it on.
Yeah, once you make it to Boston,
you can take all this fucking shit back from them.
That's, yeah, that's true.
That's true.
Just like I'll take back those shoes.
Guys, it's a sad day.
It's a sad day, but we desire we're not gonna do it anymore
because it's kind of weird and awkward,
as you can see right now,
to put this visual stuff in an audio podcast.
We'll retweet stuff.
We love your fan.
We'll be a little bit like it.
Keep retweeting.
We will, you know, PCP is the biggest brand in the universe.
You know, we'll retweet it.
You'll get your five minutes of fame.
So we encourage it heavily,
but this is the last time it's gonna be featured
in an episode unless we figure out some of the format,
but we'll worry about that.
Someone in the comments suggested to just like have
show a couple of them, like as the episode ends,
because there's like that 30 second kind of like block
when you put like a-
Like a slide show.
And just like cycle through a couple of them.
That's not a bad idea.
I kind of like that.
That's not a bad idea,
but I don't think it's a replacement
for the like discussion of them.
Well, sure, sure.
It's not, but it would be a nice way to just have them,
like give them more visual.
Like frankly, I just want to keep encouraging people
to make fan art because I love it so much.
So anything you can find to encourage that.
I mean, I do want it to get seen.
You know what?
Let's talk about that.
We'll get back to you on that.
Well, I'm just putting that one on the table.
Thanks to whoever left that in the comment
on the last episode.
It was a good idea.
It's not a terrible idea.
That sick, the never paint sick ass fucking drawing
of Mage with swords.
He's going back for round two.
This is a very like a 90s anime look.
I dig it.
Digi, you should scroll up a little bit in the chat
because he made one before that we talked about last time
or maybe the time before.
What the fuck is it?
Well, it's here somewhere.
It's a bit, it's a bit above you.
It's somebody like, I can't find it, but it's noticeable.
This one is.
It's up on June 24th.
Okay, there you go.
Thank you.
Jesus Christ.
Something about the picture that shows the markers
around the drawing is so aesthetic about this area.
It's like a very tiny drawing as well.
It's incredible how tiny they are.
That's true.
Such detail.
Oh God, it's so, it's such a small drawing.
I kind of like, I remember like drawing on paper
back in the old days.
And I always felt like drawing small is way easier.
Oh yeah?
I just actually draw small.
Like I draw really tiny just cause it's the most tiny.
Cause you have so much more control over your tiny pen.
I do as well.
The pros.
Well the pros they draw big.
They are called Micron pens, so you know,
they must be micro.
Yeah, but look at that.
Marker tip.
Like the marker tip is so big compared to like the Marks maze.
You just do a little dab, little, little, little, little.
Well that's the, that's just the color pen.
Oh, I'm dabbing.
I think the Microns are what he like did.
Yeah, those are smaller I think.
Well whatever.
I mean, I don't get how it works.
I don't understand these art things, but this looks great.
Love the city in the background on this purple bullshit.
It's cool.
Is that a purple smoke rising from the, from the wreckage?
It sure is.
The funny thing is there's like one building
sort of like towering.
And in my city there is a church that towers just like that.
Damn.
Yeah, I mean that looks, looks about right.
But my experience in the region.
I like the little bird.
I like the little bird near your leg and the cat on the shed.
Oh, I didn't notice them.
Yeah.
Oh, they look cool.
I noticed the bird.
I wonder if it's related to my feud with the crows recently.
The guy, I hope so.
All right.
Well, the next one we've got is from King Salmon.
You have to really get to the max resolution on this
to understand.
Yeah.
I still can't.
Like it's very light.
It's very light.
You got to really open that shit up in a new tab.
That's what I did.
It's a fucking massive image, but it's awesome.
It's got all of our faces fucking being,
it's just really expressive face work.
Kind of reminds me of like the movie Wings of Honey Mies,
like old, very old Gainax like facial style, especially
DeVoo.
Yeah.
Nate's got this awesome.
I love that pose.
I just noticed that's an awesome face.
I'm not entirely sure because, OK, we've got me, DeVoo, Nate,
Ben, Mage, Hippo, Tom.
Those are all obvious and they're all colored in.
And Jess.
Jess has got to be the bottom right, the part.
Is that?
Jess isn't yet.
Why is he wearing?
Is that supposed to be like Asuka's hairband?
I think it's a pirate.
That's a pirate hat.
It's a pirate hat.
Yeah, it's a pirate hat.
OK, that makes sense.
Who the fuck is the lizard?
Well, the lizard.
I think it's supposed to be me.
It's got to be Munchie by process.
Well, they lose who's Donkey Kong, then.
It's Munchie, probably.
That's definitely Munchie for sure.
Yeah, I think the guy said in the Discord
that this was drawn a long time ago.
Oh, OK.
I mean, he just hadn't submitted it.
I do actually love this like monkey in a car
shooting two-sew machine guns.
It is presumably doing a in-cell drive-by,
is where my mind goes.
Why is fucking Munchie a lizard?
I have no idea.
Yeah, that one I don't.
He has this big jaw for maximum munching, obviously.
That's true.
Makes sense to me.
His tongue is like a made form.
Maybe this was drawn near the beginning
of when Munchie and Munchie joined.
And I guess he had a better understanding of who
Munchie was and not Munchie.
I guess so, I guess.
Yeah, because it seems like he's not.
I like the Tom.
Tom's like a lizard guy.
Tom's like scary, like foo-man-choo.
Tom looks like a Voldemort.
Very Dracula lizard guy.
I love it.
If I could look like this in real life,
I'd do it in an instant.
It's pretty cute.
Alongside Tom being a communist,
which everyone just believed because we believe it.
For no reason, yeah.
There's also a general design trend
that I, myself, partake in and has been illustrated here,
where Tom is a vampire.
We draw him as an evil vampire.
He kind of looks like that, though.
He's a lizard person.
He does have a little luminon in his mustache,
and he's like a tall, skinny, dark.
He's always wearing black.
He's like Dracula.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Hey, yeah.
Snake dragon look.
No comment, guys.
Guys, think about it.
Have you ever seen Tom and a vampire in the same place
at the same time?
Damn, that's, he's right.
He's right here.
He's close.
I like the little mage, not found.
Yeah, I know.
It's great.
So I'm trying to think of who I look like,
because it reminds me of a cloud.
A cloud.
I mean, no, no, no, like, like a specific character.
Yeah, it reminds me of something, too.
Do you look at the man in the mood?
Because you're a big mood change.
It might be Dumbledore a little bit.
Yeah, something about, like, the way your expression.
Guys, what if Dumbledore and Hagrid put on the Potara
earrings and fused into a more powerful being?
That's what this guy, that's me.
What if Dumbledore read one piece?
Whoa, which is what I was referencing just now.
Definitely.
What if Dumbledore ate the...
Can we move on to the next fan art?
Yeah, let's go.
Tadpo drew some of what I would describe as us as in that one
world in Psychonauts, where it's like the Mexican level.
The black velvet paintings.
Yeah, there's actually, there's backstory for this.
Oh.
There's a story going on.
I wonder about this.
The backstory is, this is actually in the
Radifugures Copulars universe.
And one time on some stream, we alluded to some nefarious force
known as the PCP, and this is around suspicion.
Because no one had known, or no one knows what the PCP is
in the Radifugures Copulars universe.
Because, and he only presumes some evil Illuminati,
spirit cooking, bourgeoisie-esque league.
Canonically, Deben and Munchin, are they actually members
of the PCP?
Well, I don't even know what the PCP is.
I mean, I think that these other shadowy members are probably,
they're probably ruling over some other scary SS cities,
somewhere else in this post-apocalyptic slime world.
All right, all right.
But you know, we occasionally get together and go bowling.
You shoot the craps, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, next, we actually get back to these Gabriel Starrmangs,
sir ones, a Starrman senior.
Starrmang senior, whatever.
You got Action Giraffe and the PCB guy, look great.
I love the PCB guy one.
I love the GIFs.
Click on them, make sure you click on them,
because Action Giraffe's got flashing aides and sunglasses.
Aides, aides, aides, aides.
PCP guy's got this cool static background,
I like that a lot.
PCP guy looks fucking sick.
He looks dope.
It's like something from off.
Yeah, it's really, it's nail-less.
I'm just gonna drop this.
I think it looks like something that would be
in the Space Ghost OP.
Sure, something like that.
I hear that OP in my head when I look at it.
Like, d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d.
I do.
I love the fact that his eyes are also, you know,
just cropped down.
It reminds me of Church of the Subgenius,
who I watched a bunch of videos
about the Church of the Subgenius recently.
The sub, whatever.
No.
It's this like post-modern, like 80s, like pseudo cult,
but it's like a joke cult, basically.
But it was kind of serious, like they were actually,
they actually did have churches.
Gabriel, I like that you wanted to do
the funny manga slash flip note studio effect,
where it was like, instead of just doing all black,
you did a bunch of dots together
to make it look like it was gray.
But instead of like just doing that,
you like Google searched that and they got an image of that
and then upscaled it and didn't put on nearest neighbors
that looks really blurry and it's really funny.
Is that what happened?
I don't think that's what happened.
I think this is the spray tool.
If it were a screen tone, the dots would be uniform.
Are they not?
No, no, no, that's what I, no, no, no, no, Ben,
I'm saying his hair, his hair.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, the hair, the hair.
Yep, that's a screen tone.
I like it.
That's a screen tone.
All right.
We got, I just assumed it was the actual drawing,
but they're not at it, that's obviously not true.
No, no, it's been redone.
You guys, we've heard that,
we know that people want the PCB guy
and we've heard those cries
and hopefully we can alleviate those fears soon.
We'll get back to you.
Can we?
Maybe.
I don't know.
My interest is peaked.
Well, we'll just have to see now, won't we?
I don't believe it.
Believe it, we'll be done.
Next we got from Hale on Twitter.
All of us being in the DeVue collective.
Yeah.
Cleverly placing mages back to the camera
because nobody knows what her face is.
How intelligent.
I like the color fading out from each of us.
I like that.
You have to have a pretty high IQ.
What is up with Munchie's neck?
What is the double neck?
He's fucking buff.
He's fucking buff and he has a thick neck.
Thick with two seams.
All right, thank you for this image,
but riddle me this viewers.
Why is the DeVue collective still a thing
and Ben stealing Nate's shoes not a funny fucking meme?
That is the best thing and funniest thing
to happen in the PCB today
where you're still on fucking DeVue.
But it never happened because it was not theft.
The funniest thing about that was Nate commenting
on the video where Ben was in my backyard wearing the shoes.
That was what made it fucking hilarious to me.
That was great.
I was like, Ben,
why do you have to flaunt them like this, Ben?
Why? Just tell me why.
You gave them up and now they're mine
to do with what I please.
No, this is not right.
You abandoned them.
This is not right.
I'm saying this.
And I saved them.
There's a ton of meme potential in the new episode.
You guys don't realize it.
I agree.
The shoes are a gold mine.
We have to elaborate on that.
That well will never run back.
Never, never.
This will never be a return.
The arc will never end.
I gotta hope so.
Once you're famous, sell those shoes
for like millions and millions.
Do we already finish the theme contest last week?
No, no, no.
It's going until the 31st of this month.
So we've got like two or maybe three more episodes.
Yeah, technically three more episodes including this one.
We've got like five to listen to.
Well, let me see real quick.
We do have more.
We've got one, two.
We've got four to listen to.
Four to listen to here.
So let's just not waste any fucking time
and get right into it, shall we?
Yeah, please do.
Here we go.
First one of the year.
First one of my dad's biggles.
Well, isn't this his third entry?
I think it is.
Man, it's a monster.
This is called China.
I like his, wait, hold on.
Before you say anything.
I like his fucking Steve Banner on Twitter.
I like his Steve Banner.
He has a Steve Banner.
I don't know who this person is,
but I mean they just have Steve as their fucking banner.
Like in what capacity?
As the, oh, well yeah, okay.
And then some anime bullshit.
No, no, no, there's anime bullshit
and then there's Steve on the left hand, the bird.
The bird.
Maybe he drew that art.
The anime bullshit, we mean a picture of Luluko
and also Mario.
Right.
That's right.
Alright, here we go.
Let's play it.
This song is called Chop Every Onion by Das Biggles.
Here we go.
I love it.
Well, this would be good in the PCP video game.
True.
Very true.
I'm not really sure what this conveys.
Yeah.
I mean, it sounds kind of...
Spacey, I guess.
Yeah, it's alright.
It sounds like a cave to me.
I liked it.
I don't really see how it would be a PCP theme song, but...
It sounds like Splunkin'.
That's what it sounds to me like you're going into a cave.
Yeah, I'd rather...
Or, like, I just picture, like, Mega Man's start screen
like, where he's like, against the black sky, you know?
Sure, sure.
Kind of imagery.
Again, not really PCP.
When we make the PCP shitty mobile game,
we'll use this as the main theme.
That'll be good.
Alright, here's our next one.
This is from...
Let me see.
At Robert Floyd TV, I think.
It's called PCP Theme.
It's name on SoundCloud is Pope Jesus.
Alright, here we go.
And... go.
Well, that was pretty hype.
Yes.
I don't know if that was on time for you guys, but...
I heard it.
I got the gist.
Alright.
Wait.
Wait, was that you?
Was that not part of the song?
That was just me rapping just now.
I was just doing that.
Oh, yeah.
Well, that's disappointing.
If we used me, like...
Well, I wouldn't...
You could tell it was my voice, right?
I don't know.
I thought maybe you'd said that at some point.
Well, that was just me rapping.
Okay, well, if we used that one, like, fucking rap,
put that in and rap over it.
And then it'll be my favorite.
I would just use a better beat than that one.
Well, sure.
I mean...
That sounded like a football match.
That sounded like one of the commercials, like, you know,
the robot, the stupid fucking football robot.
Yeah.
I love those, incidentally.
I'm a big fan of those football robots.
I always have been.
I've just never had a platform to say so, so I'm saying it now.
But anyway.
There you go.
Next up.
I don't know what that is.
One time I got Rick Royal at the football stadium.
Really?
Is that true?
Yeah.
Damn.
Did they just blur it over the loudspeakers?
Yeah.
They blurred that and then hard and smashed cut to the hamster dance.
And then smashed cut to Caramel Donson.
Hell yeah.
And then smashed cut to me bleeding out.
Let's just make Caramel Donson the opening theme.
All right.
The smash cut to the next fucking song.
Right.
Here we go.
This one's from Slam Rarn.
This is called Four Fun Crastinator.
Oh.
It's fucking Sixten.
Yeah.
Oh.
Right.
Here we go.
Boom.
Impress me.
That was not me.
That was the actual song.
Incidentally.
Oh, the word impress me?
Yeah.
That was fun.
Oh wait.
I did.
I mean, that was a great song to hear.
Memento.
I love the music.
There's kind of funny music.
I really don't like ASMR.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
Do you know it.
I consider it.
That's the song.
I'm really confused about what's real and what's fake
OK.
I forgot.
This was already entered, but we did a meme last episode,
where we just said, play PCP.
We're like put words over the song because we like it,
but it needs words.
So he literally took those clips and put them over the sun
Guess what it fucking is great?
The guitar playing was really sloppy and hippo could do better
Well, yeah, but he didn't so fuck
Apply for the contest I have no rights. That's true. He's got no rights
Okay
Wrongs we got we got one more. We got one more today. This is from sick Rick
It's called faggots. Hey, it's called faggots. Whoa name of the song. I got high hopes 37 seconds. Here we go
Faggots
To faggots
It sounds like sick Rick just wants to do a sequel to his album that he did for Jesse. Yeah
The one person who is not even on the podcast that he was the only one featured at the theme song apparently
Yeah, I'm not sure that which I mean is true. Anyways, this is Jesse's world. We're just living it
Sam you're right. You're right. I love the album
I'm wondering if he used my faggot compilation. That was what I thought that's what I assumed
I bet he did. I like the the like really bit crushed guitar tone sound, you know, it sounded pretty good
I kind of want to animate that kind of remind me of the song underground from a green lagoon the ending theme
Yeah, it does sound like that. It was grimy. I think I think I think totally it was right on point
Yeah, right on point my humble opinion. It was pretty good. Yeah. I liked it. Yeah, I really needed
I'm just gonna make a bunch myself and submit them. I'm just gonna submit my own do it, dude
I'll just be in the contest with everybody else
Do it so I can downvote you to hell. I can't wait. I can't wait
Uh, well, that's that's that we're all done with that shit. So okay, so we got I just I just realized there's seven of us in here
It's what I said, you would have the full house true. That's what I said. Oh my god beforehand
But you can also get fucked. Uh, well, we guys you guys got two more chances
There's there's two more pcb episodes where we're taking submissions
So that's it. You got two two weeks left basically. So good luck
Then we can put this to fuck kind of and then we'll put it to rest
I mean, I've been loving this personally, but uh, you know, I get it
Do you remember that we record pcb episodes a week before you hear them? So, you know, oh, no, we'll now known wait
Oh, fuck. That's right. No, okay. Well the fact remains that by the time you're hearing this
Uh, we will have two more things to record. So when you hear this, you will have like eight days
I love like eight days to get it in when you hear this
Uh, so there you go. There you go
All right. Well, that's done. Let's get to the fucking questions. It's time to go. It's time to go
So far I've only found one that I even made sense as a question and it was uh,
Who else do you want to have as a guest on the pcb?
I I wouldn't mind having zen huckstable on sometime if he was interested because he's real cool and I like him a lot
Sure. No idea who that is. Yes. I know that lad. He's a boston boy. He's he's an anime youtuber who is
Who we we hung out with uh, he was he was in he's really I like him a lot
Was he in the in the six and eggs video?
He was like off camera. No, he was not I don't think he was at he was not there because he was there the night before
He was not at our house at the time that was recorded, but uh
But yeah, no, um, I hung out with them all day that day. It was cool. He uh, I'm a patron. So a word, you know
Check your stuff out. He does his videos are really interesting because they're not they're they're
He doesn't bother like editing them
Like he doesn't bother trying to make them like amazing and I don't mean not editing
But like he'll have blank screen and he'll just put images
And it's like he doesn't give that much of a fuck but the videos work anyways
And it kind of opened my eyes to the fact that like
You know, it really isn't about how much effort you put in it's about that's what what images you put in
You know, yeah, I've taken some influence from that, but uh, anyway, he's definitely
There's a question directed at me
Okay, all right, so what question from age
From king salman and do you relate to slav memes and how close uh to slavs are lafianians? Well, like
historically
or like, um
Genetically, I'm not too sure because like lafianians are bolts
And slavs are slavs and like russians and polish people. I think are slavs. So like we're not the same thing
However, like the fienia is inhabited or you know
It has been inhabited by a lot of russians and polish people and stuff like that
So like we're neighbors as well countries
So I sort of relate to the whole slav memes in a way because I have seen people like that around
And it's I found I find them funny
Here's here's one. I actually am interested in answering
Eric c bass asks if the content of your podcast slash channels didn't exist. Would you ever consider running for political office?
Yes, I think about this all the time. Uh, I I would love to run for political office
I think it'd be really cool, uh, and it would be great and I would love to do the reason that I
Who the fuck would want the reason I don't want to do that is because to run for political office
You are going to have to like
You have to participate in the system as it is and I would rather influence people to want the system to be different
So like I think I think I have a lot more
I just think that there's a lot more potential for me to affect the system by just changing people's minds in a broad sense
As opposed to
Trying to be
Even slightly clean, you know to try to like be a guy like like hunter thompson who is my idol
He ran for sheriff of his town
He almost won except that the the other two parties last minute colluded together to to prevent it like they realized that they were in
Shit and so they they fucking you know blocked him out
Using lots of dirty tactics that you can only have by having shit loads of money by being
In the bed, you know of of the lobbyists and everything the the political machine and like
There's no real way for that much of an outsider voice to break in because they are going to shut you out
So rather I just run from I just go from the sidelines and make people
Want the system to be different and that is how I'll overthrow
I completely understand all the corruption that there is in government and all the stuff like that and and and it would be
It would be for the most part just paperwork and boring
But I just have a romantic idea of speeches and just and just like the american government as a whole
Just just go into washington getting things done being being a patriot. I think I think it's cool. I mean, maybe when we're older
Maybe when we're in like, you know, no we're barred forever actually
Please drop munch boy goes to washington. I want to see him all dressed up on the campaign trail
I want to see him in a cute and kind, the pop culture
If the world changed to be the kind of world that we are wanting it to be that we're pushing for it to be
There's a chance you would still be a political candidate in your later years
I I think about running for office even now with everything exactly as it is
Now, I'll probably never do it for many of the reasons that digi brought up
But I I mean i'm agnostic as to whether or not my youtube career has made that an impossibility
I mean you have said nigger a lot
I think that like let's just say 10 years pass. I think if I just say oh, it was a crazy kid
I think that excuse holds some I don't know. I don't know if that works
I mean, please please do me a favor future future political opponents
Do not use this clip as a way to prove that I am in fact totally
Insincere about the thing that I just said and do not regret anything
Please do me a favor. Do not cite this very clip to use that against me in my 2050 political run. Thank you
uh
Yeah, munchie was
Referring to a video that I made about there was this game show in
It's called i'm celebrity get me out of here
Which is like a bunch of celebrities go in the jungle and they have to do tasks and it's like big brother
But in the jungle and um, it's all fun and games and there was this one for this the first time
A youtube celebrity instead of like a regular normal television celebrity was on the show and it was a big deal
um, but people
Because he's like new media and they didn't like the fact that he was getting
You know, he's got millions of followers and they didn't want him to get any more
Or you know, I don't know who it was
But like people sifted through his twitter to get something that he said when he was 17
He said somebody was a bitch when he was 17 and that was enough to get him like in trouble
And he decided to leave the show to like defend himself with his lawyers and stuff
And it was really
It was really like
Because he said they dug that right up like this was like the beginning of twitter. He was really young
Was it for swearing or was it because misogyny?
I don't I don't really realize it doesn't matter all that matters is that the media created a circus about it
And you know, you know the corporations will fire you because it doesn't even matter if people if like actual people give a fuck
All that matters is that someone said something and the easiest way for us to cover our hassles to fire somebody
You know what's interesting about this
I've actually been kind of keeping eye on like sargon of akkad specifically is doing a thing right now
Where he's like getting actually involved in politics in britain
And like he's a guy who said a lot of bullshit online
And i'm just very interested to see how it goes for him if he's like able to go badly
A lot of people think that he has no chance like like uh, mr.
Medeker has has been on a lot of live streams talking like he has said like he's called people white niggers
He's like blah blah blah said all this bullshit like there's no way famously he he did this tweet to jess philips like his
A p.m. Or something he said, uh, I wouldn't even say grab him by the pussy and that
I mean, I would argue that grab him by the pussy is totally not sargon is no sargon is no trump
You know, he has he does not have these are gone actually running for office
I know he joined u-kit party. No, no, i'm not saying he's running for office. I'm saying he's getting involved in politics
Well, he's been he's been scurred in that line for a while now. I guess you could say that sargon that yeah
Like if trump could get elected anyone can even someone who who's no i didn't mean to say but sargon's just not famous
I didn't mean to say that anyone could get elected. I just meant that he you can say fucked things
You just have to be you have to be trump. You have to be donald fucking trump like, you know
If he didn't win like it's not just that he won in spite of that he won because he's he's donald trump
He's way bigger than that statement
You know, of course like sargon is someone who you could just easily bury under the dumb shit
He said because it's innumerable. I hear what you're saying. I am just simply interested to see how it goes
We'll see we'll see. All right. We got to wrap this up. So I got a poop
So happy d says something related to me specifically. Okay. Why is munchies so angry these days?
Did something happen in his personal life? Is he with a child?
Am I
Uh, maybe he's referring to your your much discussed hatred of the pcp, you know just in general
Oh, maybe I don't know. Maybe that's what it's about. I don't know. That's not that's not hatred. That's that's that's that's
Fucking revolutionary fever. That's that's fucking that that that's fucking i'm lying. I'm lying the candle that will explode
Because we're surrounded by methane at all times. Well, that's what I'm that's not anger
Fair enough
I see a question here by kajuro bit of thorn, which is a very interesting question that i'm surprised hasn't been asked yet
Okay, uh, how much time does it take to edit these podcast episodes? And what are the best and worst parts of doing it?
Oh, well, we have an answer for this for sure
Yeah, because a lot of us have edited the podcast and um
Well, I have I have not edited the podcast since the new since like the new
Format yeah, we've been introducing lots of new
Styles and rules and like it really depends on who you ask like if you're talking about like
Deveu editing or me with the uh, the ghibli cast we've been like
Literally like editing every fucking second of the audio to make it clean, but like pcp editing normally
Half an hour, I don't know
Digi that's hilarious. You think editing a pcp takes half back in my day
It's a cat when I when I was doing it would it would take an hour tops
Okay, well, here's the thing now that we have to do this stupid after effects glowy thing
Just rendering that out takes about six hours and then you have to re-rendering
Is not editing a rendering doesn't count
I mean rendering always took a fucking eternity because it's a long-ass podcast
I would say just what quality are you rendering it in because I've always done podcast exclusively in 480p because
I've had fans literally tell me like don't render it above 480 because it's audio only and like
It's just a bigger load on my phone
That makes sense. It's a fair fair point
Like it's a bigger load on the uh, I don't know. I don't know
I mean most most phone plans now at least in the us if you're on um, if you're on cell service
They automatically downgrade everything to 480p to save the carrier on data. So yeah, why would you look at youtube on data?
That's insane
Uh, that's insane because because here in america. I haven't unlimited data. Yeah, I've got unlimited data too
Well, that's uh
I hate that
Carrots over there. I still didn't want the carrots over there in brun
Huh, I still didn't know you're still dealing with the carrots over there carrots
Yeah, yeah, the the raisin minutes the the carrots minutes the fun for raisin the carrots
I have no idea what you're talking about. The fuck you saying anyway next week on the pc. Bye
Before we go everybody remember patreon.com slash the procrastinators do us a favor give us a dollar get in our server
Wait, I didn't even get to answer the question. Oh, oh, okay
The worst part about editing is when one person has
audio problems
with such as noise
Where like
Usually you listen to it and you you make sure it's okay
But if somebody has like a big noise thing that you can't really get rid of
I have to like go through and like chop out every instance that whether or not talking to get rid of it
For me, it was always just like trying to get the levels all equal like I would just impossible
It like never works all the way through it's it's impossible because not everybody
compresses their audio before they sense it
And it's kind of a hassle to open it in audacity and then compress it and then put it back in
Yeah, I have done that before. Yeah, it isn't knowing we this is why we need pcphq
So we can all record in a controlled environment. We're all using the same equipment and this wouldn't be a big of a deal anymore
Well, it's coming soon. I haven't patreon.com slash make it real
Yeah, by the way everybody we
Just just for the record
We did go five hundred dollars over budget on the Kickstarter. So I didn't get paid. Oh, so just saying well actually technically
You actually did get a little money back. Uh, oh, I did. Yeah, as it worked out. You got a little bit of money
Um, and many of us I made a cool three dollars indeed, but you know, you know, that's the negative side
Here's the here's the positive side guys. Well, we got to do rad rad come through
Happen. Yeah content is unbelievable. It's mostly is that a real figure three dollars. Yeah, he really got paid that much
Although none of the biggest stuff is out yet. So keep your hype levels up other than the rad shot
We still have a lot of like really huge ones the good and I mean people fucking got their merch now
So they've got the items that I see people talking about them and loving the shirts and thank god
Thank god that that all made it. I was very afraid that like people weren't gonna get shit or something
Like if anybody like give give it like at least another week, but if you should have gotten your shit and haven't
Uh dm me or message me on twitter and I'll look into it
But uh, yeah, I'll make tom help me to figure out how to
Actually make all the stuff you are still owed for the plea for the weave kick starter
You know not what you're putting on yourself, did you the fucking
The money is sorted though. I did my job podcast three
Uh rad con four one of these days rad. What does it know our rad con forever?
Red con forever like the pokemon movie. Oh, yeah, that's right. That's a good one
By the way, where's I just want to let you know on happy arm shows
And we're so honored that you put arm retrieval con three and the background was about of the belting part podcast
We're so honored. Did you what the belting part podcast, you know that you did? Oh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, I just threw random like literally whatever was the latest thing for the worst video. I could find just threw it in
All right guys that the procrastinators. No wait, no
patreon.com slash the procrastinators five dollars for our fucking bonus episodes
Uh, I forget what the last one was but we got more coming. You know, you know us
All right. Thanks for being here forgot. We do bonus episode. We need to do another one soon
I gotta be on the next one same bitch. All right. We'll see you guys next time
Yeah
I'm supposed to be working right now. I'm supposed to be working right now
But I'm not working