Hey guys, welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. Today we have a really funny thing to do for
you guys. So here we go. Here's the high octane action and lovable cast members that you've
all become accustomed to on this glorious podcast of ours, on this podcast that spans
C to Shining C. We have Hippocrit. Hey, it's me. Tom. Hey, it's me. So this is what we're
going to do. We're going to talk like this, which is our normal voice, and then every
once in a while, when we want to make a funny joke, then we'll just scream really loud.
And then that translates into us being happy and slash or energetic. And that will mean
that the show is better because energetic is better. It's not about having interesting
things to say. And when you're naturally passionate about a topic, then you will just get loud
because you have a lot of things to say. The raw volume is what determines the interest,
not the energy behind that volume. So just crank up your gain, and that's how you make
a good podcast. Speaking of which, today's topic is podcasts. That's what we're talking
about. Speaking of podcasts, last week, my intro was Topic Sky Committee, Rhymes with
Chitty. And that's my new topic here again. Nate's not here. Nate's not here. You may
have noticed Nate's not here. And when Nate's not here, everything falls apart. Everyone,
like their mind control ceases, like their eyes are turned normal from their all black
and red state. And they start looking around and they start to unbuckle their chance. And
they think, what the fuck am I doing here? So we're doing podcasts. A topic none of us
have any passion for or even know how to tackle. What can we talk about podcasts? Podcasts
that we like? Just go to like a list of podcasts that we like. Oh, that's really fucking funny.
Here, I'm going to do that for you. Revolutions. Hello, Internet. There you go. Those are the
two podcasts I listened to.
Fucking Cox and Crendoor. You know, podcasts, they're bad. And I don't like them. And this
is also a bad one. And you know why this is also a bad one? It's because, and I actually
remember like the very first podcast, like the procrastinators podcast discussion of
like what it should be. We were discussing this at the very, very, very beginning.
Oh, that's history. It is a history fucking cool. Because Ben was like pushing for the
podcast to have a topic like a theme, like a thing that we would do. And every week we
would do a thing. And Nate was like, no, it's okay, we can just turn our like conversations
that we have all the time in the chat into a topic, we just talk about any topic. And
that eventually won. And so the procrastinators podcast became topics of any type that we
were talking about. And that has been like the curse. If only if only we'd listen to Ben, if
only we'd listen to Ben and made the show something that you could, you could, you know, it
could stay fresh by having like a structure to it. Right, right. And a structure that was
flexible and not just completely dictated by weird ass segments that we tap on the very end. So
here's what the structure of the PCP is right now. You got the intro, you got the Urban Dictionary
reading every single time. You got that every single time. Then you got the top the actual
topic for an hour. And then at the end, just shit that I assume everyone turns out like tunes
out for because I tune out for it because because what is it? It's just being like, Oh, wow, look
at this fan art. It's really good. Thank you. Look at these things. They're like, I like the fan
interaction. I like building the community. That's always good. I mean, dude, some of the
fan art has been fucking sick. Like the main stuff has been dope as fuck. It has been like
as as as as an audio pod. Yeah, as a segment in a podcast, it's sort of like, I don't know, feels
I mean, it is obligatory. Like I would react nicely to it normally, but like to have to voice
it in a podcast makes it sort of weird to me anyway.
To have to come up with something just like like for the sake of coming up for something on for
the segment, then it just means Oh, autumn, like automatically, it means that we're forcing
ourselves to say something like like for a lot of like fan art, I'd like it a whole bunch. I'm
glad that it exists. But it's not like we need to have an entire hour long segment dedicated. This
is why are we doing this right now? Okay, we podcast. Do we have anything to say about podcasts?
Well, I mean, I guess the interesting thing about podcasts is like podcasts started way back in
like 2003, like the early 2000s, they started doing podcasts just because it was an efficient way
with like internet speeds and stuff of the time to do long form content. This was like pre
YouTube pre like being able to do long format video. So like podcasts were just an efficient way
of like going through iTunes and going through RSS and stuff of getting like radio style content on
demand through the internet, you know, it was definitely it was a medium that was defined by
like technical limitations at the time, you know, like iPods back then, because that's what the
name podcast came from was putting them on your iPod is like a broadcast on your iPod, whatever,
was because they only did audio, you couldn't watch a video on an iPod, you didn't have internet
connection at the time on your iPod, it was like, it was a different time back in 2002, people. But
um, obviously, as technology evolved and shit, like podcasts kind of became sort of antiquated,
you know, now we just like we throw a video up on YouTube that you can or cannot watch, you know,
depending on how artistic you are. And it still functions as the same thing, because that's just
what the format is. But like, the the the limitation no longer has to be there, people do our long
video podcasts, you can stream and watch or whatever. But the interesting thing is like, we're
kind of sweet, like there's a bunch of people I watch, like there's a podcast, Gary Vee's podcast,
which I watch a lot, and listen to, I suppose. And he's talking about and I think it makes a lot
of sense that like audio is making a big comeback now, because like, there's so much shit online
right now, and there's and people are just like super busy, that like podcasts now, even though
they're not, it's not a technical constraint anymore, people value time and the ability to
multitask. And like, we talk about this all the time, like we put on a podcast in the background
while we're doing something else, you know, that's something you can't do with a video. So
what started as like a technical limits limitation is now like a convenience thing, because like
we're so bombarded with media, and like, I want to play this video game while doing this while
doing that. Well, now podcasts allow you to do I felt like that for a while. But I feel like
that's like a trap mindset, like if you're you're trapped at work, like, and you're doing a nine
to five, you know, when you have to leave, then it's probably okay. But like, if you're a person
who can like, like, so I feel like this, this is a sort of thing, like if you put on a video of
any length, you feel like you want to watch it to the end. And you're like, okay, I'm, I need a
break. I need a lunch break. So I'm going to go get some lunch. And I'm going to watch a video. And
it's like 20 minutes long, you finish eating after like six minutes. And and then you're watching a
video for like 14 minutes longer than you wouldn't you wanted to have a break for. And I feel like
podcasts for me, for a long time was just like, Well, I'm watching it. I haven't got to the end of
it yet. I got to finish it before I can do anything else to do with audio. And that's that
it's terrible. It's the worst thing that I've ever I've cut out most podcasts out of my life,
because of this reason. It's like a time it's like a multitasking thing, but only for people who do
the most menial of tasks. I resonate with that a lot. But I feel like I have more space in my
heart for podcasts for stuff like videos where it's like, I mean, the most common example is did
you or did you would always talk about how monkeys podcast was perfect or podcast? Nuzlocke was
perfect for lunches because he could eat a sandwich in the meantime while he watched it. And I was
like, Yeah, that makes sense. But actually doing it for like any video above like 20 minutes, I've
actually been doing this a lot funnily enough with digi videos, where I've turned on one of the
Bloodborne Let's Places doing with May, and then I'll either Chipotle, and I'll either do it really
slowly so I can trick myself into thinking that I'm maximizing my time by like finishing the
burrito like a couple minutes before it ends, or just eat like normal. And then and then just be
like, Well, I've already started this video. It has 16 more minutes, but but you know, I've already
started. So I just want to continue. But like podcasts, I think are great, because I don't
really video edit a lot. Certainly have anything to work with with audio a lot of the time. So I
can just draw and put it on a podcast and it is of little effect to me. Yeah, it's good for
some people who don't have to to work with audio. So there's things or something to say about how
my brain has been permanently altered and I am a new type. And my brain does not function the same
way that I think you guys might, where it just due to the fact that I've always grown up on the
internet and there's always been a thousand things to do at once. I feel like I'm like
constantly if I'm not doing two things at once, my life is being wasted. And I know that that's a
complete like that's not true at all. And in fact, you should just be focused on one thing at all.
But it's just it's just like a social thing that's been hammered into me and my brain can no longer
work. And like right now, I'm just rocking back and forth, looking at my audacity. And I'm also
like strolling through Twitter right out at the same time, because I'm fucking broken. And I'm
I'm a media creation. That is not a new type thing. That is something everybody I think deals
with at some point. If they if they get used to being able to do two things at once kind of
like, like, I know a lot of us who are like in the PCP have just talked about like being unable
to play a game without listening to a podcast. Like if there's not a new podcast, I'm not playing
any more Dark Souls, I need something to listen to. I've heard Digi say that I've kind of felt
like that sometimes. But I don't like it because I don't know, it's just it's it feels like it's
fake. It's like cheating. It's like not real podcasts, and let's plays and like video content
where you're listening to other people. If they're not like incredibly interesting, it's usually just
like a surrogate friendship chat, like, like, you know, I'm just hanging out with my friends,
they're speaking, they're making funny noises, and I'm going hey, and I'm playing video games.
I'm just like in the room with them playing video games. And I'm like, it's it's like a
it's not a fix for actual human interaction and like relationship building. It's sort of like a
what do you call it, like a quick get rich quick on friendship high. Yeah, like a high. And it's
I feel like the ideal is to never listen to anything like that. If you can avoid it, but
people sort of sink into that sort of lifestyle and they can't help like listen to and watch millions
of hours of people talking about stuff. And I don't think it's healthy. I don't think it's a good
thing you can you should do because if you do it too much, you think that's all you need because
it's the highest the fix if it sort of prevents you from realizing that you have a lack of like,
you know, if you do actually have a lack of like human interaction in your life,
you sort of dull that sense by by listening to all this stuff. And then occasionally you'll
remember oh yeah, I'm really lonely and you'll explode. There's just so many problems inherent
to the idea of a personality driven show. From the point of the producer to the voice actor
to the consumer, there is just it's just a riddle of like a medium riddled with problems
where okay, I listen to a lot of podcasts admittedly, but they're only podcasts that I feel like
have a point and enrich my life in a number of ways. I named drop to the beginning,
Revolutions, which is a history podcast, which has no personality really, the guy will occasionally
crack a joke, but it's mainly just hit him, you know, reciting history lessons, which I enjoy
greatly. And then there's Hello Internet, which is a show admittedly built upon personalities.
But the reason I care about the personalities is because they constantly have interesting
conversation that is that are integral to my enjoyment of them as people. I would not really
care about CGP Grey or Brady if they were just two, you know, comedy hosts, so they're just there
for chuckles and laughs. But the fact that they have genuine enriching conversations about technology
and science and stuff is the reason why I tune into that. And just like having personalities
parade around in podcasts or let's plays or whatever will like, okay, on the part of the
creator, it will get old fast for them to do, they will not have a direction, so they'll mostly
have to flounder. And it's not sustainable anyway, because you only have so many like stories and
relatable points to mine from the cold pit that is your soul to parade around to the point where
after you've done like a year or two of that content, you'll be all tapped out on, well,
I've already told this story, I've already showed this part of my personality, I've already done
this gimmick for them. So you just have to flip out, you know, retarded shit that you don't actually
care about, but you just want to phone in, you know, sort of like a podcast topic, something like
that, you know, some sort of like meta commentary such as that. And then on the point of the consumer,
again, like what you said, a hippo, it's just, you know, arbitrarily filling in the space of a real
friend. I don't know how many times I've, you know, like, like, my let's plays to hanging out with
real friends ratio is horribly skewed. And I never, I've never gotten the same amount of amusement
or joy I've gotten out of listening to let's play, as opposed to just inviting my friends over and
playing smash. Those memories that I have with my actual real friends are greater than any enjoyment
I've ever gotten out of let's play in my entire fucking life. So why do I do it? Because it's easy,
because I because, you know, because sometimes I don't want to deal with having people or sometimes
I don't want to clean up my room. I just want to sit around in the darkness. I want to watch a let's
play. It's disgusting. It's horrible. It gives me nothing. The personalities on display in most
let's plays are not inherently interesting. Game for us was good because they occasionally had
really in depth conversation and it might not be, you know, like the most high of mind conversation,
but with conversation that you cared about the Nickelodeon gut stuff is not just funny because
it's John and Aaron making goofy noises. It's funny because it's relatable and you've had those
experiences before in your life. And it's interesting to hear, you know, people get mad at one another.
It's interesting because of the thing that the personalities are talking about not just because
the personalities are speaking inherently, which is what we're doing right now. Where's where's
washed up personalities who were funny and who were cool and people liked listening to because
they watch old PCP topics and they're like, oh man, I love this funny fucking one. They keep
referencing the Wake Me Up song by whatever that band is or like this one where they talk about all
the memes that need design and almost all of them are not memes. That's what the really fucked up
weird editing style. I like all of those things because they were interesting topics. Those were
interesting things that people wanted to hear about. Those were things that people were like,
oh yeah, I like these personalities because they're talking about this topic and this topic is integral
to their work, their social life and something they've talked about before. So they have a lot
of interesting things to say. But nowadays, it's just like, oh, what do we do? What do we do? We're
gonna pull up document. Oh, wow. Look at all these topics. They're all one noun and this one noun
we have to talk about for an entire hour and one hour specifically. Even if you're, you know,
you've somehow gotten lucky one and you want to go over one hour or if you it's something that
you've actually want to talk about, but no one else has approached the topic from the same angle
as you. So you've just been waiting itching to say your actual point between the entire thing.
Oh, oh, no, one hour. Alright, everyone stop. You know, it's one hour. You know, we gotta turn
the thing in. It's baked. It's good. It's done. Just push it out. It's over. It's a podcast topic.
Yeah, it's really fucking funny. What do they say about podcasts? I've said all that. Yep. What else?
What else? You've said all the things. Do you remember the fucking horse cuss? Do you remember
the good old days when the pony boys would jump into a call and talk about nothing?
That was fun. It's so the horse cuss. I've actually re-listened to all of the
horse cuss recently for my own nefarious purposes. Type in YouTube ham n o i z. Type in
that to YouTube and you'll find a secret item hidden behind the wall. But anyway,
I've re-listened to all of the podcast, the horse cuss recently, and it's kind of jarring
not only to see how everyone's personality has changed, but also to hear them make like
allusions to like friendship and like, you know, playing video games or like watching anime or like,
you know, speaking. Yeah, it's it's so much more clinical now back then. It was like,
we'd I we don't we didn't have conversations in person. Those were like the first times we
were talking audibly to each other. And that it was just you could it's so weird. It's so weird.
I don't like how where we are right now. It's just it's a product of our own design. It's
it's of our own design that this is the case. Because there's no reason why we have to have
one noun topics. It's not even like we had one noun topics throughout the entirety of this show.
There were there were some things that were just like, like, like broad topics that we just,
you know, switch in and out of back in the early days. People liked that we went off topic and we
branched out from one topic to another. Because you know, that's how conversations work. That's
how real life interaction works is you talk about one thing. And then you talk about for as long or
as little as you want, because there's no reason to pad out time or to reduce the amount of time to
make a concise YouTube video. You just talk about for as long as you want to. And you know what?
Tugging for things as long as you want to usually interesting, because usually you know when things
aren't interesting. And you don't want to talk about bullshit for longer than you need to because
you're not you don't have you don't have time for that. Because you're not because you're pretty busy
and just want to say what you want to. And what you want to say is usually cool, because you're
saying it and you're a cool person. There's no reason to talk about things for an hour specifically.
That just that just was the case for all topics as we're talking from, you know, like around an hour
and hour and a half. We'll just make that the normal. We'll just make that we'll just make that
every single episode because that makes sense. Because because guarantee you guarantee you we
can talk about podcasts for an hour. Something we jumped into this medium. I've never even
the progress podcast was like the first podcast I ever really listened to.
I guess the horse cast technically. But you guys were the only podcast I had listened to.
And up until like a year ago, maybe even like nine months ago, I brightened out the other stuff,
revolution to low internet, other shit like that. You guys were the first. So like, like,
I don't it's not even to have a history podcast. And like, oh, well, my childhood, I used to watch
over the bum fuck podcast all the time. No, you guys, you guys were the podcast.
If we're doing an episode about podcasts, let's talk about you guys, because you guys are the
only podcasts that I listened to. And what has happened? Why? Why is it like this? I was a fan.
I was a fan of the PCP. And I loved it with all my heart. I was in the fan chat. I prowled out
every single day. And now I'm here. And why have you bespurched me in this way? I wanted to be
like the horse. That's why I'm fucking here. He was like, Oh, I love these guys. Oh, I love
the gym. They're so interesting. I've never seen I've never heard these opinions before in my life.
Here's why it's because due to various, you know, happenings of life, we talked about so much stuff
in the discord or the Skype rather. We talked for so long about so many things. And we started
to have podcast things where we would elaborate on what we were saying in the chat. And we did
that so much that we stopped having things to say to each other that weren't like fresh news,
like new things that were going on. We knew each other so well through what we had said,
that there was nothing new to talk about. And now every week, we have to shuffle on into this
little this this this gross little gray room. And the topic list and be like, do you have
anything to say about that? I've never heard any of you talk about this topic, but maybe everyone
will have something to say. Yeah. No, no. I think it's because like now that it's it's like expected
to come out every week that there's like money involved. And it's like, Oh, we got to make a
podcast. We got to have a product to make as opposed to like, I mean, I was never on the
horsecast, but like the horsecast was more spontaneous. There was no schedule for the
horsecast. It just kind of happened. You know, all right, let me let me blow your fucking brains,
friends. PCP obviously comes out once week, because you know, not to make it sound too cynical,
like we're like, we're trying to pull a fast one on you or like we don't give a shit about
anything. But that's what's good for business. So that's what makes sense and is concise and
good for algorithm comes out once a week. And people just like regular people just like having
things come out on a regular time because it brings you know, familiarity to their life.
And just as an overall, you know, good thing to do if you want the podcast to grow, which
you wouldn't want the podcast to go. You want to build your business. And also you want to meet
more people with the content that you create. But here's the thing. It doesn't have to be that way.
That's not the way that things have to be. And you may think, Oh, but but of course,
having a regular schedule will of course make the podcast successful. Well, here's the thing.
The Hello Internet podcast is notorious for never coming out on time. And it has like
unbelievably diverse like windows of release. Sometimes it'll come out two in a single week.
Sometimes we'll be like an entire month before one release. And you may think,
ah, well, just because the fact that they have interesting conversation and they wait
to have recordings podcast and they have something to say and they make everything,
you know, actually interesting and they wait until they have points to discuss.
Just because they do that doesn't mean it'll be successful because, you know,
they aren't doing it right. They aren't releasing every week. They're making $4,000 per episode.
$4,000 $4,000 and $62. Sorry. Hello Internet is is a masterful show because it is clearly
it does the same thing that we used to do, which is we were talking about something in the chat
and be like, let's do a podcast about this. Let's hash it out in more in depth and record it.
And that was the initial idea. And they do that. But they do it, you know, whenever they actually
have anything to say. And it's it works so well, because those those guys have such chemistry
through like their interactions. It's just two guys. It's the fucking it's the best.
It's so great. And the thing to actually like talk about the podcast topic a little bit here,
just just a tiny little bit to satiate. Yeah. The reason I like Hello Internet,
which is interesting to me is that there's no cursing on Hello Internet.
There's no apparent jokes. There's no real wet comedy. It's just like two people
who are nice, upstanding, like normal citizens, just speaking to one another about their experiences
who they are content creators. They speak about some of the same stuff that we talked about a
long time ago, but they just do it without cursing or making themselves weird targets of drama
or like weird social pariahs. They don't curse. They don't do weird shit. They just talk like
normal. And they have interesting points about like technology and the state of humanity,
space travel. These are just upstanding citizens. And they're living the high life. They go on
trips all the time. And they turn their and you know, they have interesting things to say about
the trips. It's all perfect. CGP Cray is literally my ideal life, but I literally, I literally cannot
live the CGP gray life anymore. I cannot. I didn't think of this a lot recently. I cannot run for
president. I don't want to run for president, but I could not. I cannot have any political office
because I've done this show and I've said the n-word a lot. I cannot do that anymore. My life
is so limited by my own design. This is what I wanted. This is what I wanted my life to be. And
now that it's, now that it's here, I realize, oh, I don't have to scream. Oh, I don't have to make
jokes. Oh, I don't have to curse. I don't have to be edgy. I don't have to do any of those things.
But this is what I wanted. And this is the life that I have now. It's like growing up, dude,
like you fucking realize that like, oh, I don't have to like put on airs and shit. I can just be
who I want to be. My life would be better for it. The thing that like I've noticed about, I guess,
our dynamic and shit is like, the topics are very forced because like we have this list, we have to
do one topic. I always felt that the PCP is in this interesting like middle ground of like the two
extremes that I think are six or make for a more successful podcast. Like the podcast that I like
the most are either podcasts that are a single topic. And it's exploring that topic in depth in
each episode. So like, I listened to like a podcast called pro blogger. And like most of the podcasts
I listened to are just like to get information. But like pro blogger is about blogging. Every
episode is about blogging. And it just explores a different aspect of that. So like, there's always
a singular kind of like cohesive concept behind the entire show. So you go in knowing exactly
what you're going to get. And the people who do the show have a direction every episode, they always
know like, Okay, there's one big meta topic that that drives this entire production. So there's
all there's never any like doubt or confusion as to what are we going to talk about this week,
it's like, blogging, obviously, but how, right? And then the other end of the spectrum is like
when it's personality driven, it's just like whatever the people are passionate about and like
not trying to like, have it be focused on one, like topic for that episode, we're in the middle
where we have one topic, but it's there's no cohesion behind it. Like we don't just dissect
like a big meta topic. It's just like, it's like the worst of both sides kind of like, and that's
what we're doing on once on the other side is like something like the Dick show where it initially
was like, he had like a gimmick where he was trying to find a cohost. But then it turns,
it's like morphed into just occasionally talking about Maddox drama and then Dick being mad about
stuff that happened throughout the week. And there's always something to be mad about. So he has
like an endless well that he can pull from to make big rants. And then he has people on it's just
like, it's a show about him and it's a show about how mad he gets at the world. And that's all it
needs to be. There's never a topic on anything. And then yeah, on the other side, there's
the stuff like the fucking, the fucking podcast, chibi barkers, the Ghibli cast, the pony cast,
arm retrieval, all those are way better than the procrastinators podcast because they have points.
They have a reason to exist. Because they're talking about things. Exactly.
Because every episode you're like, Oh, what are they good? What's the weird topic? They are real
at this time. Oh, they're just going to continue with the talking about because they have more
stuff to say on it. They're just going through a show. They're going through a webcomic. They
want to talk. Oh, oh, it has a point. Oh, it has a reason to exist. The PCP is ostensibly a show
about us, right? It's about the hosts. Like no one comes here. No, not a single soul has clicked
on this episode thinking, Oh, wow, I really like podcasts. I can't wait to see these people talking
about podcasts. Oh, I'm really excited for this kind of guys. No, they all come here because they're
like, I remember Ben saying, I remember Jesus. You nearly said Jesse. I nearly said Jesse. Oh,
no. And then I was like, Oh, I swear, I can't say that. And then I did. But anyway, the point is,
is that we, like, we like, to make the show make sense, it would be Hello Internet. It would be
the life and times of an internet creator and the stuff we go through working day and
out, you know, the steps we've taken in our careers and in our personal lives. Okay, what's
like to be an internet person? Here's the problem taking this weird awful topic system and make
no sense. Here's the thing. And this is the second thing I was going to bring up like,
because we're talking about like, Oh, like the old PCP in the horse cast would be continuations
of what we talk about in the chat. Like, I don't read the chat anymore, because every time I look
at the chat, it's always cynical, negative bullshit. And I don't feel like reading it. Like,
every time someone posts something, it's complaining about a YouTuber or complaining
about something or shitting on something. And I don't want to hear about that. I don't care.
I completely agree with you, Tom. Every time that I tune in here, it's just like a wall of tech.
It's just like message upon message of like, Oh, the YouTube industry fucking sucks. Oh,
everyone's just here to make a buckle. It makes no sense. Oh, it's all just a bunch of shit.
And I don't want to hear about that, because I love the internet. Right. I like making internet
content. I like being here. Sure. There's reasons to get grumpy. In the horse cast, everyone
talked about like, Oh, all the way doing the chases make fun of YouTubers. But that was kind of fun,
because they were all making content themselves. And they all referenced the contents they made
themselves. And it was just a fun, a fun time. And that's part of life in times of the content
creators talking about the other creators in your space or made sense. But now it's just
nonstop cynicalness. It's just nonstop. Oh, everyone sucks but us, even though what are we doing?
What is this right now? Oh, is this really a paragon of what YouTube should be? Is this
what's happening right now? I'm going to kick off the podcast. I'm literally going to get picked
to kick off the podcast. This episode is going to air and I'm literally going to be kicked off.
Do you, do you not, do you not like me, Munchie? No, no. What are you saying?
I'm saying this, but I don't know if you know, I don't know if you've realized
you've been caught in a catch, a catch. This is not the podcast, this episode.
This is the disillusionment with the PCP episode. Oh my God, yes. Thank God. I'm so glad I didn't
miss it. Yeah. Right now we're talking about how the topic system makes no sense and how
we're ostensibly a personality driven show, but we pick topics that do not accentuate our
personalities whatsoever. And there's no sense for us to cynically pick topics that none of us
have an interest in like podcasts. Well, what do, what do personality driven shows talk about?
Stuff like, stuff like Hello Internet, where they're talking about the stuff that's happened,
you know, in their lives, anecdotes, stuff that's been on their mind, stuff that might not cleanly
fit into a one hour window, stuff that just might, you know, be casual conversations that the others
can build upon. You know what? I mean, do we even have that much happening in our real lives?
Yeah. And yeah, yeah, Ben, and you know where we, you know where me, you talk about that,
is Ryfurg's cop killers? The YouTube videos are constant non, like, like wall to wall
shit that has happened in our lives. And it's all fucking interesting because we pick our
topics carefully and they all don't have to fit into a sensible time period. It is, it is peak
content. You know what? I mean, sometimes, sometimes the topic system yields good results.
Sometimes, but not right now.
Okay, I fucked up and slept through the PCP today. So I mean, you guys have been, you know,
I'm here to save the show because you guys have been floundering with only three guys,
but I'm here, I'm here, I'm a breath of fresh air. I'm here, I'm here with my rude to and my,
and my, you know, and my, my, my radical leftism. Just, just to spice things up a little bit. Did
you guys hear about that? That there, there's, there's 10, 10 genders now and they're all male.
Yeah, yeah, that's a meme. Hey, whoa, ha ha, patreon.com.
I'm sorry, I'll see myself out. It's been a pleasure, everyone.
Let's just do a horse cast. Let's just stop doing this. Let's just do a horse cast where we just
talk about things that we care about. And that's happened before in our lives in the past week.
Yeah, because there's a lot of things that happened to me that I don't talk about on
podcasts, but I talk about on my patreon people thing. I mean, there's, there's, there's adventures
that have, that are being had. Ben, you've moved, you've moved, you're in a completely different
city now. Oh God, I bet, look, that's all bound up in some shit that I don't want to talk about ever.
Well, fine. I, well, I mean, about the moving, I mean, I mean,
my house, I mean, I'm in a sick house. It's pretty great. Where are you? I'm real happy to be back
in Boston. Are you back, are you back in the monkey house? Yeah, oh yeah, I am in monkey
house, although we don't, okay. Actually, this is interesting and frustrating to me. I come back
to monkey house only for them to tell me that they don't call it monkey house anymore. And I'm
like, yeah. And I'm like, okay, so just last night, I finally, I finally popped the question. I finally
was like, all right guys, when did it, when did it stop being monkey? Apparently now for a while,
it was Beijing house. And now it's, now it's wheelhouse, which dude, I don't know. I'll never,
I'll never, why was it called monkey house in the first place? Well, it was because
when we, when my friend found a shit, I shouldn't use people's real names, when he found the house
and like, got a bunch of people that wanted to move into it. We made a Facebook chat group to
like, you know, discuss the move. And someone sent someone set the the automatic like button,
someone changed the like button so that it was a monkey face. And so we became monkey.
And then like, and then dad, who is a print maker, he brought over this, he brought over this like
this little print of six different monkeys. And he like, and he took out like a fucking power drill
and use these giant bolts and like bolted this tiny thing into the wall. And they and there were
six of us. So we were six monkeys, hands monkey hat. But anyway, a lot of shit went down while I
was gone. Like there were a lot of like, kind of weird and or somewhat scary people lived here.
Because while I was gone, there was an empty, scary. I mean, at least one of them was a drug dealer.
I can't remember if someone, okay, the place got trash, one of our former roommates,
and possibly his girlfriend, who, weirdly enough, I matched with that girl on Tinder
the other day. And it was a very awkward exchange because because she recognized me. Well, she
she asked me, do we know each other? And I was like, do we. And then I realized because she
has a butterfly tattoo on her leg. And I remembered it. And I was like, you, you trashed our house.
Yeah. So that was weird. And she said, I mean, should I talk about what she said? Because it was
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. All right. Did she deny this statement? She not at first. Like, she was like,
okay, you like who I was like, Oh, yeah, you trashed her house. And she was like,
what? And I was like, monkey house. And she was like, Oh, great. And I was like, yeah.
She didn't disconnect. She was like, Oh, great. Like here it comes. Yeah. Yeah. She didn't. She
did not disconnect at that point. I don't know what happened next. You know, I could probably
just get it up on my phone. But shit, my battery is dead. The point is, so we were talking about
this guy, this ex got roommate that used to live with us. He had come back and trashed her house.
Apparently he had put dish soap in the dog bowl. Yeah, like, yeah. So like poison ostensibly to
poison a dog. And so I mentioned that to Oh my God, we should fucking should we cut her name out?
You mentioned three names so far. Well, this is whatever first names don't matter.
So, so, so I mentioned that to and she's like, Oh, a vegan putting dish soap in the dog. Well,
yeah, right. I'm like, okay, whatever. So she doesn't she doesn't come out and say it. Eventually,
I asked her like, are you saying that you didn't do it and that or that he made you do it or something?
And she is like, No, I didn't do it. And then she starts like, she's like, I hope,
I hope you never I hope you never date someone who who like tries to choke you while you're
driving them to work. And I'm like, Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry about that. And then she's like, Listen,
he was he was the love of my life. And I'll never get over this. And I was like, God,
leave me alone. Listen, I was just I was just here.
Looking to make some friends and you and you sir have soured the mood. Yeah,
I was just looking to invite people to my fucking bounce house moon party on Saturday. And you're
and you're really bringing me down. Eventually, she was like, you, you people are all still haunting
me from this situation. I'll never get over this. Leave me alone. And I was like, I was like, fine.
I was like, Okay, you're like a ghost of Christmas past. But I was like, haunting her.
Guli over her head. I mean, I felt bad because she was clearly upset about all this. But also,
I don't care. Even a little bit. And that's my story. Well, she destroyed your house.
Maybe. I mean, she might she said she didn't. But it's like, she didn't seem to like push that
angle, which seems like the angle to push. If you got it. I don't know. Anyway, about monkey house.
It turns out that like, you know, all this shit had happened, the house getting trashed, people
coming in and out and like, you know, people, people changing the cast of characters here
changing. And finally, I guess it was around like last September, when weirdly enough, it was when
one of the original guys who had been there for monkey house moved back in. And yet for some
reason, this like around this time, everyone decided, you know what, this is the end of monkey
house, monkey house is over. So they had a party that was the end of monkey house,
like the end of Ava and forever after it was the end of monkey house, even though like four out of
the six original cast is still here. Weird. So I don't know. So what was the whole saga happened
while you were gone? Like nothing, like, like nothing, nothing was the end. Like at some point
after a bunch of stuff happened and or change, they were like, I think it's time, I think we
should stop calling it monkey house. And then they just did. And then I come back, it's like,
hey, I'm going to be back in monkey house. I'm four out of four out of six original cast.
Don't you know, don't you know about the wars? Yeah, we're not, we're not,
we're not real anymore. Now we're now we're wheelhouse, because it's a pun, get it? Because like,
oh, that's totally in my wheelhouse. And I'm like, what a fucking disappointment.
It doesn't good to be, does it feel good to be back in the area at least? Yes. Yes, it's
fucking great. And I missed it. I know, dude. I know, bro. I missed it so much. Dude, going to
Boston has been an absolute delight every single time I've gone. It's been so, so great. It is
a delight. And yet, let me, let me tell you, on the drive back to Boston, we passed through New York.
And it was a little bit, it was a little bit like, what's a good analogy? Like you finally,
like you want something and you finally get it. But at the same time, you see something else,
you know, like we drove through Manhattan and we stopped in Manhattan and we hung out there for
a while at this, at this manga store. And I can only assume the econ was with you. Yes. Okay,
okay. All right. All right. He insisted on, on this manga store and he spent like hundreds of
dollars on manga, which was funny. But he, so we, so we stopped at this manga store. And anyway,
the point is that New York was fucking great. And I have thought like, man, Boston's the best. But
then right before we get there, I'm like, wait a minute, New York's pretty good, though. Shit.
Um, New York's really expensive, though. I mean, Boston's really expensive too. But I don't live
downtown. I live, I live a great thing about Boston is you can live on the outskirts. You
could live on the outskirts and still be connected. Like I live in Medford, which is like pretty far
north. And yet I'm like a quick bus ride from like the inner Boston area. And then it's like a very
quick subway trip to the actual like center central downtown. Everything is like, like,
you can get every fucking which way in Boston, even the brief time that I've been there,
I've been at like easily like almost every sub that's like not on the blue line or like the
orange thing. I mean, every stop. Yeah. If you're, I mean, if you're on the, if you're on the tee,
like if you're near the tee, you can go anywhere. Yeah. Like, like, like nothing will stop you.
Especially since like in almost like every stop, you can just like change trains. It doesn't cost
you more money to get back. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You get on and then you make as many fucking changes
as well. Usually only need to change trains once. But yeah, you can go entirely from like,
you can ride like two entire subway or lines, but they're full, full distance for like $2.50.
You guys sound adorable talking about the trains being like that. When when in London,
it's like, it's like that times 10 in every aspect. Oh, Pshh. Oh, Pshh. You would love,
you would fucking love to see King's Cross St. Pancras. It is fucking, it's like an airport,
how big it is. There's like 70 different fucking train stations in one train station.
There should definitely be a hippo, munchy power hour, pow wow someday. I definitely,
I very much intend to go to England one day, whether you're alive or not,
which, which, you know, fingers crossed in London. It's called the tube, right?
Yeah, the underground, the tube. Okay. Okay. All right. I see. No, I see it. I see it. It's
okay. I'm looking at a map of it right now. I wouldn't say that it puts the tea to shame
per se, but, you know,
the tea has made me aware of the greatest luxury in life, which is good public transportation.
It changes everything about your life irreplically going to Boston and I mean, like, oh, I can just
like go downtown and then hang out and just like get back home and it won't cost me like $20 to go
there. Good public transportation is fucking amazing. The bus in San Diego fucking sucks.
The way like, like it only has like scenic routes, which means you're going to like,
spend like $5 to get downtown in like 40 minutes to an hour if you're lucky and there's no traffic.
It's fucking horrendous. Okay. So in, so in Atlanta, there is, there's like, all right,
I never really spent much time in Atlanta proper, but apparently there is like a road
that circles Atlanta and inside this perimeter, you are ITP and outside this perimeter, you are
outside the perimeter, you are OTP and like, there's like, yeah, yeah, yeah. So there's a,
so there's like a, there's like a difference in kind in terms of like how easy it is to get around
to like whether anyone wants to hang out with you. Okay. Yeah, whether you're ITP or OTP. You're
on the outskirts of reality. And I was, I was OTP, which was, was not great. There was a bus,
there was a bus that would go into Atlanta, but it would only go in the mornings. You could only
catch it a couple times in the mornings. And it was really, it was long and bad.
Yeah. You sure were in the OTP, but you sure weren't in AOTP. Am I right? High five me. High
five, high five. I, that's, I'm extremely uncomfortable right now. We'll delete that,
we'll delete that. No, it's, no, you're right. High five, high five. All right, okay, all right,
okay, let's simmer down. So, um, so, I was going to ask Tom, because like, I just got to, I just
got to talk about the Atlanta subway because it's just a cross that runs up and down and left and
right. And it's not, it's not great. I mean, it's okay. It helps. And like Atlanta is not,
it's, it's less sprawling than Boston, I think. So like, I think for Atlanta, it works pretty
okay. You can get anywhere. There's just not as many places to get. Um, but the bus system is,
is kind of, kind of bad and, and confusing. And Boston has like Boston has very good buses. They
go all over the fucking place and they run all the fucking time. It's really good.
Yeah. All right. That's it. That's all I have to say about that.
Yeah. So, so speaking of like moving around, uh, Tom. Yeah. Yes. What, what's, what's the deal
with you? Are you still in, going to be living in a car? Is that still a thing that's gonna heal?
Uh, yes, yes, that is happening. Great. Probably within the next week or so. I think I'm gonna
like stay here for the fourth and then I've been, this has been like coming, like I've been hearing
about this eventuality for like a long time, like over a year. It's about damn time, Tom.
It's about, I kind of agree. No, the thing is, is that like I keep, there keeps, there's a lot of
like family conflicts going on and I'm not going to get too deep into it, but just know that it's
been threatened multiple times that the house will be sold by X date. And then I go into a panic
trying to get everything set up and ready to go. And then the date comes and nothing has happened
and, and, and, and was like, okay, well, I guess I just like lost a decade off my life for no reason
then. And then like a few months after that, a new date will be presented and, and I'll have to
like redo the whole thing over and over again, but this time it's really gonna be real. And,
Is it? Yeah. So I bought, I bought my car. I got my shit packed up and it's gonna be an adventure.
So I plan on first going where Digi is, we're just going to hang out for a bit and just shoot
the shit and like be bros for real. And that'll be interesting. I guess I'll be seeing you soon.
Yeah, dude, like I'm going to be around in the area. So we should all, you want to come for,
you want to come for the fireworks on the fourth? Maybe. I don't know if I'm, I know I'm like
grilling some of my dad on the fourth. I'm hanging out with Munchy. Can I say, can I say,
can I say someone's name? Okay. Kazi? Yes. Okay. I didn't know who he was saying.
Yeah. I'm not, I'm not in control of who speaks her name and who doesn't.
Oh wait, Nate, wait, Nate, Nate talks about Michelle on here. Okay. Yeah. Sorry. I got nervous
because I fucked up and said real names before. Yeah. Yeah. Kazi's coming and, and you know,
Kazi, which is, which is her real name, of course. That's, that's right. Shut up.
Wait, yeah, I know her real name. I don't even know your real name, Munchy.
Everyone knows my real name. I actually, I don't know what that's supposed to say about that later.
Yeah. Anyway, we're going to, I saw the fireworks on the Charles Bridge a couple years ago and it
was really great and we're going to do it again. It's going to be fun. And hopefully this time,
the smoke from the fireworks won't blow right over her faces and choke us and make us gag.
That sounds unpleasant, but I will try and make it. Yeah, that would be fun. I'm so,
I'm so fucking jealous. I would love to do that. Also, what I'm also envious of is Ben, you are going
to be able to play Pokemon Go for real this time. You're going to be able to go to fucking
Boston Common and play on Community Day. Do you understand the magnitude of people playing
in the area with real people? Yeah, that's going to be way sick. That's going to be way
fucking sick, dude. I was not prepared for the community of Boston because the community of
San Diego is there's like a few people, some of them raid, basically no one raids. And even when
you do raid, no one talks to another. They're all just huddled. They're all looking at their phones.
No one's looking up. No one's saying hello. But in Boston, people, okay, first of all,
you meet unbelievable caricatures. And then also everyone, even like the normal people,
are just talking to everyone. Everyone's super friendly. Everyone's having a good time. They're
just becoming big groups that go on raiding adventures for the entire day together. It's
great. I feel like I've missed out on quality PCP lore bonding by dropping off the Pokemon Go
bandwagon. I feel like I need to get back on that. I have to. The only times I have really
Pokemon Go is when, I mean, I did a little bit here and there, but for the most part, I only did
at Radcon and Armortreeblecon. It's pronounced Pokemon Went in that.
I went for a bit, but now I'm not going anymore. Tom, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Are you not in
the separate chat we made for Pokemon Go, the separate Discord server that we've been talking
in? Wait, I clearly know. Wait, send me the fucking link. No, not really, you fucking idiots.
Oh, god, shit. We should fucking make like a chat. I'm doing that right now. I'm literally in
the process of doing it right now. Because I have also been getting into Pokemon. It's really just
like the update that added trading and friends lists, and now it's like great that I can see
people playing the game in some sort of way and be like, yeah, I'm gonna download it right now.
I'm getting it. Dude, I'm about to post my frame code in chat right fucking now. There's nothing
you can do to stop me. All you fucking babies and I'm just like, oh, oh, munchies playing Pokemon
Go. Oh, I'll jump on the bandwagon when I'm the pioneer. Motherfucker. To ever click on Pokemon.
I was there. I fucking downloaded Pokemon Go illegally before it was out in the UK because
I wanted to play it so much. How did you do that? I googled it. There was a way to download it
onto like a USB and then download it into your phone from the computer and then activate it in
a secret way, but then it became the real game anyway. I don't know how it works, but I still
have that. Did your account transfer over? It did. So I was managing, I was like the only person,
well, not the only person, there's clearly a few other people who were playing, but like
for a few weeks, I was the only person I could see playing Pokemon Go and I was always looking out
for like, who else has done the cheat? Who else has done the secret cheat to get this game before
anyone else? And I don't think anyone else I met was. After, like after, like after some time,
we can like hang out. We can play Pokemon Go together. Maybe we can get a group together
and then we should do fucking Pokemon Go as the topic. Oh, of course. We were actually thinking
about doing that today, but you're like, um, well, it was originally just going to be me,
Tom and Hippo and Tom hasn't really played a lot of Pokemon Go and me and Hippo have said a lot
about Pokemon Go already, but I would love to do Pokemon Go episode someday. I think that would
be, because I have a lot to say about that. It's kind of weird how, uh, disharmonious our
Pokemon Go has been, because we all started at the same time when the game first came out.
Then you, Ben, uh, and Hippo kept playing for like a couple extra months, like like a pretty
long time after everyone else stopped playing. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. I would go on Pokemon Go walks for
like a long time after. I never stopped and I never really stopped until I went all the way
through like that first really cold December. Like I was still going out even in the middle of the
night, like really cold. Like I just, I want to, I just want to catch Pokemon still. And you guys,
you guys were going strong and I had dropped off. And then everyone stopped playing because,
you know, it was like when Jota was out for a little bit or maybe even a little bit before that
and everyone's like, okay, enough of this game. It sucks. And then I picked up again right around
when, like, like a day or two before Rick Waze came back or when Rick Waze first came out rather.
You mean the third impact? Yeah, the third impact. And I turned the game and like there are these
things called raids and there's a ton of like new social features. I think it's completely
different. And the game is like really, really fun now. You know, there's hardly ever any glitches
or any like retarded shit like that. There's a few now that friends are out and friends doesn't
work as well as it should. But you know, whatever, whatever, it's mostly fine. And there's barely
any like game breaking glitches. And there's so many features that incentivize you meeting new
people in real life. It's fucking great. I absolutely adore it. Too bad San Diego kind of
sucks for the game. And it's not very funny. Here was no one talks to one another, but in
Boston, that should great. Oh, wait, teams, teams, hashtag team yellow, hashtag team yellow,
instinct instinct. Team mystic. Yeah, I was a mistake. Of course, of course, you're a mystic.
Yeah, Tom mystic. Yeah, we should have a fucking war. I mean, what can I say? Articuno is the best
bird. That's not even true. It is true. The other ones look like shit. And you know it. No, Articuno
has a long tall head and Zapdos is funny. He's a funny boy. Zapdos is a fucking big bird ass
mother fucker. Exactly. That's why I love him. That's what he is. And Moltres is a rubber chicken
that's on fire. Moltres does suck. I think I've told you before, but I routinely listen to your
Pokemon Go miniscule review just like regularly, just like every other week or so. I love that.
Yeah, I also I have watched rewatched it because you've said that and you said like Ethan really
likes it as well. And I've rewatched it and I agree. Like it has something like undeniably great
that I don't do anymore. I don't know how to recapture that gold. I don't know if you got it.
I don't know if you heard Ben, but because due to shiagans are too long to discuss, but basically
the entire world wide community of Pokemon Go has completed a set of like challenge ARG
challenges that Niantic has presented for us. And Ergo, we have unlocked a special bonus in the
game and next weekend shiny articuno will be out in raids. What color is shiny? Is he the yellow?
No, no, he's like he's like icy blue. He's like more light blue. He looks cool. Okay. Okay,
that's pretty cool. I did not have any legendaries. I've never caught a legendary. I got two articunos
from last week. I have three. I'm a fucking big boy. I think I think I'm the the what level are
you guys? I'm 32. I'm like 2026. I think I'm probably like 26 to get fucked. Oh, I'm not. Yeah,
well, get fucked yourself. That's all I have to say. I the annoying thing about like where I live
is there's this one park, and there's like five Pokestops. And if I want to do anything, I need
to like take the train into the center of London, where it's like unbelievable amounts of Pokestops
and there's too much stuff. But like it's still a day trip in and it's it's expensive and I don't
want to do it every day, but I want to do it every day because there's so many Pokestops.
So it's like I could even play normally just having a nice walk and not take it too seriously,
or I could take it incredibly seriously and take the train every day, which I kind of want to do,
but I can't because it's too much time investment. Look, you got to be the best like no one ever was.
So get your bitch ass. Oh, you're right. I will do it now.
That's why that you know what this this ties back to what we were saying before.
The reason why Boston's so good for Pokemon Go is that you can just ride everywhere you want
because that's good public transport. When you go and public transport are inherently linked.
Speaking of Pokemon, I hope you're all excited for the first ever Muck League tournament,
the first ever New Los Angeles City, aka New Milwaukee Muck League tournament. Are you guys
fucking pumped for it? I know I know basically nothing about it and I'm in it. So I can that
shows you how professional I look. I am a Muck master. I am deeply involved in the meta. I know
all the subtle the subtle nuances of raising, breeding and training mucks and battling. Did
I mention battling? The subtleties of the Muck trade are not to be trifled with. You are not to
oh you are not to underestimate the nuance that goes into training these blobs of gas and goo.
The Muck meta is subtle and nuanced. It is it is like it's a minute to learn a lifetime to master
is how I would describe. Graham is disallowed. I guess not. But why would you use one? You use
it just uh well they have like secret specials different moves. No there's no the Muck League
is all mucks. That's that's the Muck League rule. There's no little Muck League little cup though.
I mean sure I guess. The Grimy Cup. The Grimy Cup that's it that's cannon. All right well yeah
sure why not why not but but uh yeah the tournament it's on the it's on the 12th and we're uh we're
going to be commentating it on the rowdy fuckers twitch uh and I'm gonna win spoilers I fucking
crush it. I will probably lose but that's okay that's that's fine this is not a slime fest I have no
slime on the line. Guys me and Ben are about to require right first cop players after this.
Go watch right first cop players do that now do do that now. Oh god I forgot about that.
Oh are you not prepared? No I'm not prepared but I will explain why later and we'll probably
just have to do it anyway. Okay cool great yeah uh this is gonna sound like a basic big question
but it's not do you have do you guys have anything planned for this summer because I have an entire
theme this summer is themed for me this this summer this summer is is a is a new
type of experience it's the summer of pain because my mom my mom has recently retired
at least she's retired she's got a retirement bonus and and do and due to her poor money to
money management skills and also her extreme generosity she's offered to take the family
on several trips and these trips are numerous but also I I have many things I need to get done
this summer I have many a thing the projects they have they have had they have deadlines in my
brain for and so I have to manage my time between absolute decadency and pinging out on vacations
in various foreign countries such as Hawaii and Italy uh so I'm going there but but whenever
I'm not there I have to work harder than I've ever worked before in my entire life and the
and I've just been resulting and me waking up typing things in google docs and like and like
drawing little character designs and then passing out after like 15 hours of just trading like doing
nothing else other than that and it's been it's been a great experience it's a summer of pain
where I where I balance I balance the excruciating work agony that puts myself every single day and
and then the absolute decadence of like being on vacation and and seeing my friends and going
weird places that's my sorry tumour is my plan for the summer is to enter a kind of zen like state
where time passes without me even noticing uh during during with quality during which during
which art gets made um while I fucking don't even know about it uh yesterday I fucking yesterday
I fucking hopped on on twitch on the saint comic switch and I fucking banged out I banged out the
first I banged out the first new vapors page in a while uh threw that up in my fucking patreon
and I'm like yes I'm back I'm fucking back it's it's happening again um I'm I have a similar
vapors three soon vapors three is coming did I say dream I said uh plan uh plan for the summer
I have like big plans at the moment I have a whiteboard in my room and I haven't shown anybody
this uh like in a in an image or a video because it has like I've written down the entire end of
bail japan exactly what happens in what order and I'm currently going through and when I've done
like drawn a panel or like an an event I am I rub it off the board so as soon it will be clear and
then I can fill it with like a whole other thing that I'm doing but like I want to finish bail
jpe I want to I want to I want to get some hypocrite videos pumping out uh doing all doing all that
stuff I'm organizing my life I'm getting I'm getting used to using calendars for the first
time in my entire life by actually like setting reminders like everybody says all the phone apps
and the things baps and the they say set reminders and notifications and I'm like uh no thanks but
this time I'm doing it I'm doing it and I'm doing it like properly and I'm smart and I'm a good boy
and I'm a big boy and I'm not gonna shit around for a whole other summer and I'm not gonna play
world of warcraft I'm not gonna do that I'm gonna work I'm gonna work hard uninstall world of warcraft
never again never return I uninstalled it like every year I also have to get used to calendars
where I've actually like like funnily enough someone actually gifted me the homestuck calendar this
like like like last christmas I'm like oh thank you thank you uh and it's just been you know
wasting away but I've actually broken it out for the summer of pain so I can see how many days I
have to work with uh and and it's kind of weird being aware of your surrounding it's like bizarre
knowing what's happening in your life whereas before I would just have to guess like oh yeah I'm
recording something in like two days I think at like three but no I can just I just write it down
and it will be there and I'm like oh I'm doing something tomorrow I know my life is in my own
hands I'm not I'm not a passive passenger yeah I'm actually doing things in my life it feels it
feels good to to have even just a little bit of a plan of like yes during this day I will do this
vague thing like even that is nice to just know all right because like I've mapped out my days at
the moment I'm doing like YouTube stuff and then also like writing stuff like writing for for secret
projects that I don't know that I don't really kind of talk about but like uh for for like other
real big boy things such as uh scripts for tv and film lol sick so I'm sorry like I've mapped out my
days like okay Monday Wednesday Friday I will do this and then Tuesday Thursday I will do the other
thing and by switching to and fro I will keep things fresh but also be making progress every day
and not be doing the same thing for days on end you know like every time I get stuck on something
the next day I'm going to be doing something else anyway so like it's not a problem
and it's and it's been working pretty well so far the beauty of having multiple projects I don't
I do not space my time like you do I probably should that's probably the best but it's kind of
for me it just I know I have to work for this certain amount of hours every single day because
this is how much I've calculated is a good idea uh and so I'll do this uh for like you know like
like 10 hours or something or whatever it's just not you however many hours but the beauty of having
multiple projects is that a lot of the time in in my youth I would start something and then I would
have everything open and I would be working and then I would hit like like a stump or some sort of
block and I would be like I don't want to do this like this is really hard and like I nothing's
coming to me right now and I can't I can't get the juices flowing and then I would just sit there
twiddling my clip thinking about how hard it is for like an hour or something wasting time
but now I just realized when okay shit's not happening right now I'm I don't want to waste
my time I'm just gonna do my other project while I wait for my brain to refuel so I can do the other
thing so I never have moments where I'm just like ooh I don't want to do this it's always I'm
constantly making things and I can and I and I'm not afraid to switch off of something and do something
else in the meantime I will I recharge my spirit I mean the way I do it is like it's easier to to
swap after a night of sleep because like if I try to swap during the day I'm constantly thinking
maybe I shouldn't have swapped maybe if I waited for another couple of hours I would have figured
it out what I was trying to do and I'm still the previous project I was doing in the morning
is still in my mind as I'm trying to switch to a different project in the afternoon so like I like
to even if I can't get anything done that day because I was a bad day I I instead uh you know
I I try my best and then if I can't get anything done that's that that day is it's done but at
least I tried next day I know that I'm flipping I know that I'm doing something else and by the
time it comes to the day after that it's usually like oh yeah yeah I can do this and then because
I don't I don't like leaving like niggling thoughts in the back of my head of like oh maybe this or
maybe that I want to have a good old sleep for just like slice the slice my time in half slice
slice slice moments of life with sleep days I think they're called I would do that but going to
like like laying down in bed is always the worst experience of my entire life it's the scariest
thing I have to deal with a day in day out because every time I lay down in bed I'm like
did I do did I do enough today did I spend my time wisely am I am I on track am I not on track
what am I doing wrong how should I kill myself and I just have thoughts like that like like
routinely just over and over again until I like somehow fall asleep so I don't ever want to sleep
if I don't have to dude when I feel like that which is often I go outside and I have a midnight
walk and I catch a Pokemon or two on the way I I would like to do that I don't think my area is
very good I live in a little bit of a shanty town a little bit I live in the outskirts of society
would you get stabbed I would get maybe a rape or two one or two when I get when I get done
recording shit today I might I might go out for a little Pokemon little Pokemon John just catch a
couple because I know that there you can catch some around my house like around the corners they
appear they appear in your nightmares of the corner of your eye you can't feel in the periphery of my
consciousness uh uh shit I was gonna say something else uh oh yeah about sleep uh yeah I hate going
to okay I hate going to sleep because going to sleep is like admitting that I'm done for the day
and then I know oh yeah and it's never it's never enough I've never done enough um but you know
what uh so the other earlier this week I was uh revamping my website to make it easier to edit
in the future and also to add um Bscapades which is there now Bscapades or what what is done of it
is on stcomics.com baby anyway yeah yeah well it took me so fucking long like it took me way
longer than I thought it would um partially for like technical reasons partially just because
there was like just that much that needed to be changed um for it but also so yeah I was trying
to do it because I went into this project thinking there'd be maybe like two three four maybe five
hours to get this all done uh so and then like I'm doing it for like 10 hours straight yeah and then
it's like you know it's really late in the night and it's like 3 a.m and I'm like way past my bedtime
and like I've been awake for like 24 hours straight and I'm like hmm but I'm not done yet so I just
keep going and I just don't sleep and I work like and I work all through that night and like all the
next day and you know it ends up taking me three full days to do it and partially that's just now
you might say well I stayed up all night so I got eight hours to work on it but I didn't get
but I was going real slow by the end there I was like you know I was getting easily distracted I was
like losing my focus forgetting what I was doing I don't think that I saved time get this good news
flash guys incredible fucking hot take from Ben St um sleepy is good for you and if you don't sleep
you will be unfocused and unable to do things that's peak efficiency yeah that that is just like
hashtag just team thing who you've just said to me that is like the most relatable thing I've
ever felt because whenever I'm sleeping I've been working for a really long time and it's always
like I've gotten to the point where it's where I start to feel the experience that I've been that
I explained before where it's like oh I'm stuck I'm stuck here there's a there's a creative problem
here that I'm not thinking of the solution because it's been like 10 hours since I started working
on this exact one project and now I'm all burned out and then after a while I just have to admit like
listen it's like 3 a.m. I have to go to bed I'm not I'm not getting anything done yeah yeah yeah
yeah you're not getting anything done and there's no reason to be awake but that's the worst that's
the worst feeling is when it is you walk away it feels bad but it's what you gotta do it's it's
like like when when you like when you're on a streak and like overwatch or something like you're
you're doing a lot of commuter like competitive games over and over again you're on a high streak
and then you lose one and you're like well I guess I have I guess I should go to bed
yeah but I lost one so so I feel like I'm an asshole and like I've like I've lost my entire life
the worst I to to get over this sort of exact feeling I've just accepted that when I'm mad
and I'm done uh rage quitting is okay and should be done like regularly like if you if you feel the
need to rage quit do it don't be worried about like people calling you a little baby my problem
with rage quit people who don't even know what you're doing right now and that's no way to judge
you yeah well I understand that then I do I'm just saying it's you know it's funny it's funny
that our brains think that when I rage quit like art the problem is I just keep thinking about it
even after I've raged like I get it out but then it's still there and then I'll just go back and
keep working on it like I can't stop I have this I mean this is like it has to be fixed there's
definitely a balance for like if you you're thinking like I'm so close but I think the the main
thing is like if you're tired um just go to bed like if you can't keep your eyes open then start
I'm pretty good at sleeping I hate it but it feels good so that usually over rules I don't really go
to bed until I'm like having trouble keeping my eyes open and maybe that's I mean I don't really go
to bed late I just sort of I'm sleepy a lot of the time but like um I don't go to bed at like
my bedtime I just go to bed when I feel done for the day so I don't really have all these problems
I used to I definitely used to have all of these problems I don't know why or how it changed
but I just sort of like okay I'm tired well I'll figure it out I'll figure it out rage quit life
I I definitely I definitely like like especially nowadays in the summer of pain I've definitely come
to the cushion like you know when it hits like specifically around like 11 to 12 30 I that that's
definitely like like the graveyard of like of like my my productivity for that day that's definitely
when I'm when I start to do my worst and you know I start to feel like rage quitty so I definitely
like now where I want to maximize all the time the sooner you go to bed the sooner you can wake up
so around there yeah at my hard bedtime yeah you got you got it you got to just accept you just got
to accept that it's what has to happen you don't be it don't be a coward get some sleep it's a
harsh thing you can do but you gotta do it yeah yeah um beautiful do anything else this is pretty
good this this felt pretty good this felt like refreshing this felt like I was engaging in a
conversation that was not blind me but like you know blowing me by this felt like I like I was
actually participating in an evolving conversation that mattered if I was there not and like it
wasn't just completely dependent on a few like members steam rolling things and all approaching
a topic from various different angles yeah it was great um we'll send you we'll send you your
court summons tomorrow smash cut to me being kicked from the pcp next week oh no hey uh nothing
like I wanted to talk about dogs because I've got a dog I don't there's nothing to do with anything
like um he's a puppy and he's a very funny puppy boy and he likes rolling upside down on his back
and like uh I grab his paws and he does a funny little like puppy movement and he's really cute
and he's adorable and I love him and um I feel like I was wondering about like crazy cat ladies
and why it's always crazy cat ladies not crazy dog ladies oh and it's because and it's because
dogs force you to be real people it's it's like dogs train you to be like uh like a parent but
without having to have a kid you have to take care of it and it loves you but you have to you know
you have to go outside you have to do things it can't it can't work on its own isn't it's not a
it's not a person it's not a cat a cat is like another person cats cats are like passive ownership
they take care of like 99 percent of their own cats cats are like roommates you know you give them
a little bit of food and then you can stroke them and that's their their rent money and and you
you know and but dogs they just they're fucking stupid idiots but they're adorable and they're great
um and I I like him I don't like either one I think that I think that dogs are just like you
have to fucking micromanage a dog it's it's ridiculous like in hindsight like I owned a dog
I owned dogs as a kid and it's like it wasn't so bad because there were five people in my family
so we split like walking duties but like you gotta like take your dog out to shit like multiple
times a day are you fucking kidding me no never um and cats are just well I don't I don't I don't
see the appeal I they're cute I guess I think like dogs definitely it's easier when there's multiple
people in the house like I don't own a dog it is the family dog and it's like I've never picked up
the poopy and put it in the bag yet I I've avoided that um by just not taking him on walks when
he's likely to be doing that and I've got I've gotten away with it mum usually has has the poopy
bags I'm like yeah very very very good you do it and not me and as soon as I have to do that I'll
be like fucking dogs suck I fucking hate dogs I'll come in I'll just shit all over my hands
I have numerous dogs my I mean you know my family has uh and I hate them I hate them I hate them
well they fuck a lot I I fucking hate I hate I hate pets I just I hate pets and I never okay okay
I I like pets I like animals but my dogs specifically are are demons not of their own
ill will not not they have done nothing wrong the problem with my dogs is that primarily my mom
has trained them and no ill wish on my mom but she's one of the people that's like
squirting dogs with water is abuse and like that's too harsh yeah so obviously predictably the
dogs are not trained at all like they have no training they have no sense of like you tell them
no they won't stop because they aren't trained to know that no means no they they are rapist by design
yeah yeah my my dog's my dog uh it it was starting off like that like it would chew on
everything and my mom was like um trying to like she she heard somewhere that if you treat it if you
give it a treat when it's doing the right thing then it will do the right thing you don't have to
punish it and I continually saw him being a cunt like deliberately being a little shit
and knowing that he could get away with things and I I was like the first one to punish him
I picked him up and I put him in his little dog cage and I locked it and I didn't let him out
even when he whined and and when he calmed down then I let him out and he immediately after that
like things have been like as as soon as that was like established as a thing like
if he tries to jump up on the table and take out plates of food you put him in the cage
and he feels and he's like wow I'm I want your food I want it I'm I entitled to that food uh it
smells nice and no and he's been he's been getting good he's a good boy now here's the thing about
fucking dogs is that they love it they love being trained they love having discipline that's what
dogs were bred for was to have like they're like they're like Pokemon yeah exactly they need a human
to mat to dominate them so they can reach their full potential yeah I give him some dog candies I
power him up and then I take him to the gym yeah it's it's actually true so there's no reason to
be like oh you can't punish dogs and that's what they've been they've evolved to do that they've
evolved to take punishment and learn from their mistakes if they didn't take punishment you
tell them no and they fucking bite your hand off yeah like dogs don't do that they are like oh I'm
sure I I didn't know but they knew whenever you meet a bad dog just know that the owner has
fucked up and they don't want to train it right and they're doing like weird bizarre practices
where they're trying to hype the dog up and then they have weird power dynamics it's just retarded
dogs are all great if you just know how to train them if you're patient and you and you know
you're a good leader a lot of people don't they either like dogs because they're cute and they're
like yeah I could use dog right now and they just get one flippantly and they're like well hello dog
welcome to the house I don't want to train you yeah I want to treat animals like stuffed animals
are the worst like no it's not here to to be a comfort item yeah that's what I was that's why
I was thinking about like crazy cat ladies because the cats are stuffed animals that you just have
to feed occasionally yeah and and like if somebody owns a cat I'm like okay well let's see let's see
where this goes but if they own a dog then I'm like okay this person's cool this person clearly
knows something unless the dog is like crazy and rabid like if the dog is just like a normal dog
then I'm like okay I can trust this human being because they know what they're doing
they have some semblance of like like discipline and order in order to discipline the dog
my cousin in Denver who's a stoner uh that that right that rival is digi and he's high 24 seven
and he has us he he quote unquote draws but I've seen his sketchbook and it literally not a joke
this is not funny it literally just is a lot of like naked girls with poor anatomy and the middle
school s drawn over and over again that's pretty funny yeah uh he has like three big dogs he's like
a pit bull and like a german shepherd and some other one but it's funnily enough he actually
has trained them really well and they're actually really well behaved and they don't fuck around
with anything and they don't jump up on anything and and you know there's you know he can tell
him to do things and then listen to him so even a stoner can do it you have no excuse you have no
excuse you fucking cucks who don't want to raise a hand to a dog they need it they love it they
want to serve you let them be your slave they desperately want it
oh you don't think it's dogs no no interest no interest in pets of any kind they're just too
much effort I respect my time too much to waste it uh uh training an animal
yeah I don't mind people who who like don't have the time but like implicitly like in my brain if
I see somebody with a dog I respect them just a little bit more than like a random person who
doesn't have a dog or it's not me a cat or something wait walking the cat I see that and I'm
like don't you have anything better to do it's not that I it's not that I don't have the time it's
that I don't want to spend any time because I don't see what I get out of it uh you get a cute dog
that you can waggle his face great he's got fluffy ears and you can move the fluffy ears around and
then you can pick them up and you can you can that's not gonna get me any subscribers I I might
enjoy petting a dog maybe once a month this random person on the street will not benefit my subscriber
base in any way I see I see no reason to vlog at aka you know recognize it as reality there's no
reason to engage with this person if I can't blog it's not about engaging with no no it's
about owning I'm talking about owning a dog like owning a dog I would get I would get to pet the
dog what am I gonna pet the dog every day fucking I'll get bored I'm gonna get bored of that shit
I think I think I'll just be petting this dog I'll be petting this hypothetical dog it'll just be
like uh again and like the same as yesterday lap dogs have been so cupped from every aspect of
their fucking life they've been evolved to be these shitty little things and pugs can sneeze
their eyeballs out and they've been deformed and all their spines are fucked up and they're and
they've just been made small and smaller so they're cuter and cuter and their bodies function less
and less and on top of that the people who buy lap dogs are always the ones who don't want to punish
dogs so there's just these shitty little barking assholes they just roam around sneezing their
eyeballs out and barking at strangers from across the door and I hate it it's just a sign it's just
a sign that the person who's done this is a jerk and a meaning I don't like them because they're
they're supporting uh pugs sneezing eyeballs out and also they probably have no backbone or
marble fiber uh I do think pugs are pretty cute but but you're right their eyeballs at the pugs are
like they like a real life meme face that people like bread to look like that like they they they
he was the original rage face he was the original reaction image before they invented before they
invented tablets people's canvas was their dog's DNA give it a for it give it a couple decades people
would have like bred nyan cats to be like real oh my oh my oh my word how devilish my my lord you
guys uh I think that's I think that's all I have to say on this episode of procrastiners podcast
wasn't this refreshing wasn't this nice this this was nice and it was just it just talking
what do we want do we want to look at fan art or fan songs oh fuck it's okay I was just on
twitter and I think there's only like a couple no dude oh my god I was so happy I was like wow
this is really our game like like wow this was really nice and refreshing and it was a real
breeze and it was real nice to hang out with my friends and actually you know connect with them
I know your real level and you see what they're doing in their lives this is really refreshing
oh we have to do the we have to do the sake oh shut your pie hole it's great it's gonna be
fucking great here all right well I'm gonna start I'm gonna start posting shit I'm gonna start posting
shit in the I'm just what yeah before before we get onto this I will say uh we need to make
our apologies real we have yes we really do oh god our apologies apologies will be like the pcp but
without the stupid stuff at the end not that it's stupid but like you know we've been softcore
waiting for you to be all settled in and you seem to be all settled in now so we knew that oh yeah
I totally I yeah I totally can do it now that's right we were gonna do it like a long time ago
and then happened and you and you were at you were trapped econ's jail
yeah it was it was what a what a fucking mess the last month was dude this month has been
really funny was it funny I guess it was pretty funny um yeah but I'm back I'm settled now it's
all good oh so we have some fan art uh one of them is from trip wiseman it's uh mage's tiger
oh is that what that is the next one is munchie what I know you hate fan art no no no speak no
speak go what do you have to say no I don't have any no no no guys it was the floor all right
settle down settle down guys settle down if it has the floor he's a spotlight come on
I really like fan elite like the the mage thing with the tiger it's good yes I have nothing to say
I like how two weeks on the the meme still lives it's it's got some vitality to it uh they may have
a whole bunch that are all going to be put up on screen uh by Gabriel the star man he's
the one of every single uh member so far uh wait wait has he has he done everyone yes
uh where where I see okay I see he's a hippo mage nate I guess I just assume that people
will take the initiative and and just go to his I I've been off twitter for a very long time I haven't
been looking at anything well it's all all right which ones have you not look at those yeah yeah
just I don't want to fucking post all these individuals just go to his fucking twitter yeah
yes uh mine is really great and someone posted it in my discord and I was very pleased and then I
looked and I saw that there was a whole series and I was like damn dude damn Daniel do you mean
damn as in like oh I'm not the special one he was just doing everybody yeah I was really
mad that's okay he didn't do me so so everyone got one oh that's right I knew I knew he didn't do
I see how it is uh I see how it is Gabriel the special thing about this is that this guy also
made this sort of same sort of thing for arm retrieval and it was and those ones were really
great he did one where where is all of the arm retrieval that was taken down various villains
of homes like and that was great so I remember that I remember oh yeah was yeah he was that guy um
probably not probably not I don't remember I don't think so I'm checking all of his images
uh you've done good Gabriel you've done good yeah I like he's what we've got by slam ran is this
Sixten is this is this like the Sixten yeah yeah yeah this is Sixten hey Sixten Sixten
the the the famous rowdy musician yeah yeah a creator of a creator of such such memorable tracks
as hunt the night miners and uh extra cheese please the hip hop page behind available now on the on
the rowdy fuckers cop killers bandcamp page oh is that the the not a single Mexican shell purse
yes walmart that was funny wasn't it funny when we thought to Mexicans weren't people
munchie I don't even I don't even remember what this is referenced to yes it was I think we were
talking about like uh we were talking about how walmart walmart walmart not allowing giving
mexican stuff to mexico be there where we had it was even on that episode I don't think I don't
think you were you know lol we were too scared to say it in front of you yeah yeah uh then there
then there's this piece where it's Nate as an egg this is hard boiled oh that's because I said
that one thing yep we did talk about that cool that's a pretty nice egg easy I actually kind of
like the lines on it it reads it reads like both Nate's face and an egg at the same time it works
I thought he just had a big chin yes it's a very it's a very tall egg yeah from a from a long bird
then we have uh by smirks hidden fairs for some mage there's a cat there and then it's mage and
there's some Japanese shit I assume it says watch chibi bakas on the pro grass dairy channel
I assume that's what it says yeah yeah for sure wait wait where is that scroll down just keeps
going down uh are you looking on twitter is it in the fan fan art chat
uh what what what what what it's near the bottom it's not that hard yeah it's the second the last
one sorry I scrolled way I scrolled way the fuck up I said down no the last thing here is a link to
Gabriel the star what's right above right above it oh all right well I saw that before why did you
waste my time that's all that's all the I have to announce that we're doing questions in the in the
questions bar wait wait wait what about what about fan songs what about themes pcp I know we're doing
it we're doing we're doing it wait wait wait wait wait what about it
he's asking the questions and then we're gonna do themes while they send questions and then we'll
do hold on hold on give me a minute I'm gonna get a minute where are you going I need I need some
energy I just need some no no no you don't I'm really thirsty uh guys guys in the comments please
please tell us if you enjoyed the way the podcast was going until the segments please tell us if the
segments was ruined your mood because we want to destroy them as much as you do but if you like them
then I guess we're trapped I don't mind we're gonna die here we're gonna we're gonna play the first
one without Ben because I don't know why he just left in the middle of a fucking segment I don't
know why he thought that that was a good idea uh we have no sympathy on the on the progression channel
this is the this is the you guys are my business partners you guys are my business partners we are
not friends we are business associates and we clock in under nine to five when we phone it in so here
we go here's my bald deep 69 uh fuck it I'll do I'll do this later
I that yeah that was pretty what was that what was that at the end there it's he said fuck it I'll
do this later okay he had all this music and he was like oh yeah but like that it's funny
because procrastinate it's like haha didn't finish it until the end I it was like it doesn't sound
specific to us enough but it does have that at the end here I was it was really good it was
called deep 69 it was it was a song all right I like the the snare drum it sounded like you were
slapping a sandal to another sandal it was like bap it was a bit of generic rock I you know like it
felt like a quake game sort of thing but they made this sweet little video explaining you know who
did what and who played what instrument and they sent a tweet to us and I I would like it if you
whoever's doing the show notes maybe me maybe not could link to this tweet because it's quite nice
and then they're like hey we like the procrastiners podcast here's the song we made and that's like
whoa yeah where is it where can I find it oh here I will link in chat right now
fucking awesome yeah here here you go oh okay
oh dude it's like people and stuff they play instruments dudes it's like they're dudes or something
it I it actually is like that it's almost like they're real humans it okay at arm travel con
three since when did our audience get so fucking punk heavy metal I like I like it
at arm travel con three there are these two people I'm sorry I forgot your games I'm really sorry
from Virginia and they were talking to me and I'm like and they were like yeah like I love the
pcp I love this one from the pcp like that's really funny you guys did a good job and I'm like
what there there are like humans I can meet in like the real world that have seen the podcast
like like I usually don't think about it but like there are a lot of humans that watch this show
like like people with like hearts and souls yes yeah all right here's here's a fun thing
send us a selfie of you as a human being yeah yeah I want to see some faces I want to see your
I want to see the face of the pcp fans yeah yeah like how about like hashtag uh what's a good
hashtag hashtag pcp selfies simple enough we are the pcp fans no hashtag me too hashtag me too as
in I also watch the pcb yeah hashtag me too as in I also watch the pcb that's the official
hashtag hashtag me too as in I watch the pcb no that's confusing no no no it's decided but it's
it's decided here's here's the next uh just send it to the twitter just in case wait one more time
one more time me too as in I watch the pcp as well right that will work okay there we go uh here's
by wings of strife pcb intro main entry come on everyone sit down with me you know i'm supposed
to be working but instead I'm watching pcb whoa okay okay it sounded that has a lot going on it sounded
real that that was really short it was sounds like a radio jingle yeah I like that one podcast
dilly dilly d pcp ding and here we are um that works I I really like that one I think that might be
top that might be top of the list for me yeah I don't have a top of the list I do like it though
I I like I like the concept of it the execution could be a little bit better okay just just I like
how short it is I'm reading I like how I'm reading the tweet here it says I also provided three other
versions for your convenience and utility you'll find them linked in the descriptions of the main entry
wait like huh okay hold on let me let me investigate this
there oh so there's an instrumental then there is instrumental then words one loop each then there
is an instrumental with three loops exactly so I guess it's just it's just in case we need to be
a looping thing that is handy that is that that's actually really nice I think this is the first
I think this is the person that that's realized the sort of like like like like what we're looking
for yeah for what we're looking for in the sense that we want how we want an intro to be
the yeah okay I mean first like a real intro intro this is the first um I mean it's 15
seconds long uh which is like I mean I think the ideal intro is like five seconds but this is like
you know most are the entries we get are like a minute long two minutes or whatever which is great
and everything I'm remembering that one from last time where it was like built made up of like
news reports of people saying the word PCP and stuff yes and I'd like I'd like that like
feeling if that was like 15 seconds it's good if if if only if only we had something else
this is basically what I'm saying uh then we have this by by by famous uh person Ben Smeals
Ben Smeals is here I quite like wait wait Ben Smeals is a real person yeah and and and I quite
like the I thought he was just a cruel joke at my expense no no he's real
this picture
this is a sonic level it's curvy level bro oh no I failed it in the game
I don't I don't know if that's a PCP intro but that's definitely I'm definitely saving that
using that for my own devices I definitely love that uh make sure not to give credit to Ben Smeals
because he's a slur against look at that look at that cover look at that cover pretty yeah it's
it's gorgeous show what it show notes guy show the cover editor show the cover or something
whatever delicious uh it didn't really have a whole wait wait is this Ben Smeals by Doon
Coon or is this Doon Coon by Ben Smeals oh wait oh you nerd Ben yeah Ben Smeals is the name of the
song wait why why wait why is that the name of the song because I apparently Smeal well okay
that's Ben Smeals daily uh what Ben Smeals is Doon Coon
Doon Coon Ben Smeals is is merely a statement of fact okay okay uh well I liked it I liked it I did
like I did like it but I don't know about it as an intro then we have I mean I would put it in
the pc I would use it in stuff anyway we have this by Alex Siebel it's it's it's it's Alex
I reckon I don't watch the videos well it says PCP I've never seen anything this beautiful
I wonder what happens if I touch
if I keep fucking around I'll never make anything decent for the contest
here's what you do Alex you take the stems of that song keep everything
exactly the same in that song but you change the words PCP to RFCK and then
you send that to the RFCK yeah you'll be on album number two wait Alex you wrote
a song and I think it is not on the discord you wrote a song and I did it
did not make it on to the first Rowdy fuckers fan album but I want it I want
it on there you know I don't know why I'm asking you this publicly on the PCP I
could just fucking send you a discord message but I find this to be a more
fun and interesting way of going about back shady back room dealings in the
most public way possible yeah yeah yeah exactly those are the themes we have so
far I think the best one of this batch was probably 15 second one follow
closely by the I am quesadilla which one was iron quesadilla the fucking the one
with the three cabieros oh yeah I iron quesadilla not I am quesadilla no I am
quesadilla iron iron iron quesadilla where are you getting iron from I that's
what you're saying you're saying iron quesadilla I don't know I don't know
what you're going on about but I will not stand for it whatsoever alright yeah
I'm gonna yeah wings wings of strife wings of strife is on the fucking like
that's the kind of thing that I want and that like that's the kind of thing I
mean look we're getting all these really great things like like like Alex's
thing Alex's song and the bench meals like these are all really great and I
would use them but not as an intro unless maybe like we cut out like a chunk
of them guys I've had like an amazing idea yeah what we should do we get all
these themes and then when the deadline for themes is ended we would we have to
like choose one or like you know we'll put pit them against each other we should
assign them to like a Smash Brothers tournament computer people and and see
which theme is is the better yeah but I'm just you know like they they get
that one day of like the PCP theme Royal Rumble so yeah but like a Smash
Brothers tournament we make we make wrestling characters based on the
track art free song and we see who wins and then that person like becomes that
becomes like the theme for the next episode but not like forever that's
like the the funny little prize or we alternatively we do nothing here's a
new section and by a new section I mean what I originally wanted the feedback
the feedback section to be aka not a hardly defined section and just a thing
that I was thinking about that relate to the fan reaction the last episode that I
would bring up because I care about and not because I'm obligated to do it because
it's now a new section on the show so Dane I recently I was doing like an
overhaul of the PCP Patreon lounge because it was kind of languishing and
getting dusty and don't really talking in it because it wasn't really that
entertaining and there wasn't really a whole lot of room for discussion so I
added both an off-topics chat as well as the suggestions of offer feedback and
we actually got I did the suggestions chat in the RFCK discord but due to the
nature of the RFCK it was all just suggestions for the game of endless
war and a whole lot of memes suggestions really what were they supposed to be
suggestions for just for like actually the show like like like you know the ways
to improve the show and slash or the discord itself okay but I did this in
the patient lounge and that sort of thing actually did happen so there was a
lot of interesting well-thought-out points regarding the show in various
different ways one of which by Dane good friend of mine I'm going to read this
one specifically because it's related to the section of the theme so quote from
Dane as you're probably aware the current PCP theme is iconic there's a
direct correlation between everyone making correlation everyone makes
between those notes and the procrastinators as a brand I think that
keeping the old melody as a light motif would be a great way to ensure that you
don't have to start over in the process of rebuilding a deep association with
the brand as well as avoiding alienating fans with changes that aren't 100%
necessary this would also allow experimentation for known interesting
ways to set the mood for the show or situation may also be a good idea to use
it in either the intro or outro theme or if there must be completely new one also
you may want to oh they was just in like fucking retarded shit but yeah I said
that I just didn't use the word like motif when I said it but yeah well that
was you that was your biggest mistake yes that's where you put that so I did
but yeah I agree with that yes I do as well Dane he's on the right I don't
think it's necessary I don't think it's necessary for a theme but I think that
it is not it would it would help the decision if it's like oh yeah it's the
PCP theme but it sounds like this I didn't I didn't initially think about
this but I but I'll probably want to read a few of these suggestions pretty
on the show because they've actually been really insightful surprisingly like
right off the bat there's been a few that have been like a couple paragraphs
longs by various different people by various different aspects of the show
and all of them were insightful in some way or another and it was really actually
kind of great to see so I'm extremely happy about that and I'll probably read
some that I think are interested in or that I think it should be passed along
to the guys in episodes so look forward to that oh another one for me what's
this don't go into every section on every episode
but how are we going to community build
I mean I mean the PCB themes one is like kind of because it's like finite it will end
forever and we will have done I don't know at this rate like at this rate
well we already have a deadline for when it stops wait yeah I forget when it is
the end of this month we got a whole month to go but like four more episodes and then we're there
we're done so that one we should continue doing until it's over but like others we don't always
have to do the fan art section if there's not a lot of fan art or like you know we should just
allude to it should be like we got some good fan art we saw it all there's this piece in
in particular that I think is interesting that we should bring up and if not there's no reason
to bring it up there's no reason to have that segment if there's nothing interesting to say
about it if we're just saying this was good this was good this was good yeah uh the questions new
segment new new old segment let's just do like like like one let's just fucking do one can we even
find a good one no I mean let's look let's look yeah I'm looking we look for a pity question on
the twitter are you looking on twitter should I look on twitter I didn't even ask on twitter
they're usually not that good so I just asked in the patreon lounge what's the hashtag pcp questions
yeah or ask ask the pcp I think I think ask pcp yeah oh or is it ask pcp here's a really great one
by by uh arrows and how much how much would munch could munchy munch if munchy could munch munchies
that's really great thank you for typing that thank you for your time
uh
yeah questions much I got a question what do we ask what do we ask for questions isn't that the
question uh beyond sorry dude there's there's this one guy in the patreon that's literally
asking us if we would be a cuck for money that's really funny that's he that's actually the question
he's asking if you're doing it is it is it still cuckled or if you're doing it for money I don't
know okay well I don't I don't want to give me uh I mean you know that that's the kind of thing I
think about on the daily yeah yeah I mean that that's an interesting like hypothetical suck my
suck my big pp asks prostate massage yes or no yes definitely I feel like we already got that
question before too and wait really oh well my my eyes just went right to it so well that says a lot
does the okay does the ends justify the means from chaotic slaw in all circumstances just
blanket statement yes of course there's no way that question of course yes yes capital yes
doombox two asks dad it's me it's me son it's me I'm here now
god go to your fucking room I'm here and come up with better questions here on here on patreon.com
yes because all children patron their fathers I mean that's that's how that's how you get
money out of them why why have a kid if not to make them a patron uh see Katie asks if you had to plot
the convoluted murder of another pcp member at radcon for would you how who would you kill and how
would you do it who would be the easy to kill you probably the easiest to kill it bro I don't know
I don't think so away I can crawl away up the walls and and on the fences okay I have an answer
to this but it's pretty I think it'll be pretty boring like duh did you would be the easiest
to kill because you'd be high on weed bro you just replace this weed with crack weed we just put
some fucking yeah we just we just put we just swap out his weed with some poison weed or it's
failing that we just wait until he's high and then we sneak up on him and stab him when his reflexes
are I think all this would be easier to kill I don't think any of us really put up that much of
fight I mean I mean no that's true we're also like vulnerable and squishy if someone just like
like if someone just got the jump on us we'd be dead instantaneously just from fear alone
yeah I mean all of our organs and that's that's why that's why we can never ever release we can
never release the the location of radcon four because if anyone decided to attack us like we
would just drop we would fall like dominoes we're not prepared for attacks of any kind
assault or other we we have no fortifications we are laid bare on the land
it's sad really uh yeah really fun did you or hippo neg would probably be the hardest
Nate or me probably uh dude who would win a fight Nate or Monchi um Nate's uh Nate's strong
but he's also a bitch Nate can't squat for shit Nate would follow Nate just tips over
in the slightest breeze he's all he's all show I think Nate would probably win I think that makes
the most sense we need to have like a real cage fight I don't know I mean I mean a royal rumble
in real life kill each other like the winner is the the the last one alive the arena was real
have you the royal rumble in real life Monchi have you like ever like been in a fight yeah I I've
been multiple did I tell you did I tell you guys on air or off air yeah I told I told you on air
about how uh one time a high school junior was bullying me and I was in fourth grade and I beat
the shit out of them no oh wait wait yes you did yeah I do remember that that's right that's right
um I mean I think I mean you know what like the fact of life yeah Nate works out and everything
but like the fact of life is that just like fucking momentum like fucking just fucking like
just like a height and weight advantage it's like overwhelming like it kind of doesn't matter if
you work out I honestly I think just from size alone I could see you winning you just need to swing
a big tree log like Whom whack him and like also Nate's never been in a fight which you know
neither have I so you know I'm not not judging or anything but that's just that's just the
cold hard facts that actually I don't know if that's true but I'm pretty sure it's I think I've
only been in one or two like real fights and then I've been I've been in a dozen or so fake
playfights but I still beat the shit out of whoever challenged me now I'm just imagining like like
the same like like Radcon 3 arena with the go pros but instead we're like picking up random
objects like smashing bottles and like like going around the house like trying to kill each other
dude like that it's such a vivid sight in my head like seeing that like with the GoPro footage
everyone just like like the stakes are so much higher in round three wrestling is honestly the
funnest thing in the entire fucking world the funnest thing to do as a kid when I was in like
you know elementary school was I would bring out I would bring over some friends and we would just
all wrestle a hardcore we would get on my bed and we would all just like wrestle as hard as we
fucking could we would push each other against the walls we the optimal strat would always to
be able to like like lay on your back and like get your legs up and you would be able to kick
as hard as you could and then and then we'd kiss a little bit yeah and then there'd be some you
know it just just just for a laugh just just to make up just just to make up for the you know the
trauma that we've been you know inflicting on one another we take our shirts off well because
that we get too hot we live we live in Coronado so you know you would you would just you know
take your shirt off you know we get kind of sweaty so we'd like we'd wipe each other down you know
we get in the shower together afterwards you know good good times in kindergarten
nothing nothing wrong with being gay there's nothing there's nothing wrong with being gay
oh the pause there's no more there's no more questions there's nothing more to say
uh except uh go to patreon.com slash oh my god uh the pcp i don't even know pro crass
sounds as the procrastinators i think uh go to the red bubble go to the blue bubble go to all
the different bubbles we have many bubbles in those description click on all the bubbles
they're funny they they're rainbow colored click on all those funny bubbles and uh goodbye go to
rfck.buru.org
bandcamp.asticallycopkillers.com or whatever
watch chippy bakers watch the podty puffstart
just in my
argent
paypal money to
Barry
I'm
supposed to be working right now
I'm supposed to be working right now
But I'm not working, I'm doing nothing
Why did come through here?