You appear to have caught me by surprise, hello I'm Dan Huxable and I'm taking over this
channel. Unfortunately the first 20 minutes of my audio was lost because although many
things are very good, nothing is perfect. My new laptop for some reason wasn't recording
the audio. So I'm going to improvise as I'm often known to do. Enjoy the show.
I don't think illustrious is the apt word to describe him. I'm more of a shadowy, shrouded
in a fog. A mist shroud. The barely perceptible Ben Saint. Just the way I like it honestly.
We're talking about Pokemon this episode. New Pokemon, absolute garbage. Let's talk
about communism. There's no new Pokemon. They're all gone. All Pokemon are gone. There's no
more for anyone. It's a Poppers Pokemon thing. Who cares? I was in London today. I met with
LeMantart who is a person you may know from RFCK and General Discord stuff. He's going
to be there at RFCKCon London. Let's talk about that a little bit. Why did you meet
him? What were you guys just saying? He just landed this morning. Yeah, I was just to say
hi. So he actually flew in for this? He's from Spain. I met him in Madrid when I went
to Madrid. He's in London for a work thing. It's perfect timing for him to be at RFCKCon.
Assuming he can get that one day, that day off. I just met up with him and it was nice.
London is really big. Oh, that's great. That makes me happy. I understand this might be
like a cliche and make sound like something that I say and it's fake and meant to get
your eyeballs on to me and rub your juices all over my sinful, sinful corpse. But genuinely,
I actually like meeting fans because kind of inexplicably is the newest Pokemon that
was just announced. You know what? That's a great name. Anyway, they're all like cool.
RFCKCon is like only people who I genuinely like and would genuinely consider my friend.
AJ Shoop and Connor and Paradox Crux. People like that literally just like them. Here's
why. Because in order to be into RFCK at all, there's a certain threshold of general personhood
competence you have to rise above as well as commitment to the organization of RFCK.
That is a perfect segue. I should just say that Potat was also there. I didn't mention him
because RFCK people may not know Potat. I know Potat from the PPP, the PPKP. Yes, we talked
about that a little. Oh, wait, who is it? I don't remember. The Potat PAPES Kevin podcast.
Oh, okay. Yeah, yeah. I know Potat from sounding vaguely similar to Tadpo. Anyway,
I was going to say, actually, it sounds more like Lotat, who we all famously met at that one
RFCK meetup. Stop talking about Pokemon. Stop even trying. Lotat tweeted at us. No,
no, Nate's actually the real fan in the scenario because I can't believe you would remember that
occasion at RFCK. It was a legendary moment. Lotat was so honored that we would acknowledge his
existence. Wait, it was great. Anyway, I want to talk about how I- You mean the Lotat? Yes,
the Lotat Twitter. In the flesh? In the flesh. Obviously, I wanted to get more people going
to specifically the London meetup because I feel it's like a PCP London meetup, a PCP
adjacent meetup. That doesn't happen a lot in Europe. That's a rare beast. I feel like it would
get people a little bit mad that they did not know this was happening. I thought it would just
be a nice gesture to post on the PCP that that was happening, the London comm was happening.
And so I decided to denounce the other ones as well, Baltimore and San Diego. And so I do that.
And then income flooding the PCP heads into the RFCK meetup. And I knew this would happen,
but the rate and the ferocity that which it did was simply like, I can't describe it in another
way than disgusting. Let me describe literally every single PCP fan to you. They're an anime avatar,
they're smug, and they think it's okay to be mean for no reason and just like just viciously bizarre.
So they're just coming here with no personality and no tact and no just like willpower. They are
pure leaders, not followers and their role play skills infantile, frankly. When you see
a PCP fan next to an RFCK fan, the PCP fan with their just some random anime bitch, no personality,
versus the level 100 boss, literally, yes. And then you and then you look just one thing over
to a frame, the paragon of RFCK culture with his completely original art avatar made for his
character, depicting a moment in RFCK in the game that happened in real life. It's not,
it's not a lifestyle, a noteworthy person as opposed to, you know, just an average RFCK,
you know. It's imbued with spirit. This has so much lore and context and history and culture
just imbued into this one aspect of his avatar where the PCP fans have literally never known
culture or history in their entire lives. It's because there's, there actually, there is a
barrier of entry to PCP stuff, but it is far lower than RFCK stuff. And that's why it doesn't
weed out the chat. Well, it's because PCP fans are all named DigiHeads, aka like I can't imagine
it in words fate. That's funny because PCP is like there's, it's so niche. It's so niche already.
It is. It is. RFCK is like niche within that. But you need to go even niche here. That's the way
to the, to heaven. Yeah. Anyway, I'm trying to pacify them and civilize them at the same time.
I'm just like continuously spamming the invite link to the main server in this meetup side
server that I created for the meetups. And so I'm going to try and save them. I mean,
I think it's a long shot. I think, I think they're going to reject it. I think they're going to be
like, what's the text command? It's way too hard. What's reading? Oh God, it's way, there's way too
much personality here. Please take me back. You sound like an actual cult leader. The only way to
save these people is to get them into RFCK and civilize them. Literally, yes. That's what I believe,
Nate. That's what I believe. Please just read my text. Read my Bible. It's way better than the
real Bible because it's got a little bit of a slimy touch to it. Just a little bit. We should
actually write one. We should actually just write one. There's a newspaper, right? But maybe those
people could be reappropriated to write an actual one. Or maybe the PCP should write one. You know,
I was reading, my friend John lent me this book called the, The Chapo Guide to Revolution
by the Chapo Trap House, which is another sort of podcasty collective, not entirely
dissimilar from us, but vastly more successful. Impossible. You can call getting into politics
success. Nate, you of all people cannot say that, die. Would you call making money success?
No. Okay, well, I guess. Who are you and what have you done to Nate? Yeah, yeah, yeah, Tom.
Nate said lying through his teeth. Yeah, yeah.
Nice. That's all I have to say about that, I guess. Did you read it? Did you like it?
I am reading it now. So far, it is a little bit too world history-y for me to get it. I'm a little
too dumb. You stabbed me. You stabbed me. I'm not, I'm not, Ben's no history buddy. I'm saying,
I'm saying this as a like, I am ashamed of myself. You know what, you know, that's fine. You know,
you know how it's like funny and like quirky to say online, like, oh, I'm so like bad at math,
or at least it was in like early 2010s. Yeah, no, I'm not trying to be like, I don't know any
this world history. It's like, oh man, like now I wish I knew more about world history so I could
laugh at these jokes. Yeah, I feel that. You know what? It's wasted on, it's pearls before swine.
It's, it's just anime. Absolutely true. It's just anime. I've said this a long time, but it's just
anime. I mean, I know what the war on terror is in theory. But do I experience it day to day? Do I
participate? Did I live it? Do I facilitate? Do I facilitate it? Yes. Do I continue to vote? Absolutely.
But if you walk outside, you saw Modica Magica anime girl right there and like in the flesh.
It's like that. Hey, you're ready for a hard left turn. Here's a hard left turn. So I bear the singular
distinction of being the first PCP individual to acquire the legendary silver play button,
which I now have. You've got it. I have it. Yeah, it was in my, I showed it off in my,
my last video of me a math of a two. Digi should have rightfully gotten his, but just years and
years ago. Absolutely. But, but the thing is Digi is so incompetent at life and such a hack
fraud at basic organizational skills that he has not put his two brain cells have not collided
to produce in the production and speaking to the, uh, actually, you know who helped me out. I
didn't know how to get it. I talked to, um, uh, the gaming Brit and he was just like, yeah,
just message these guys. And I was like, Oh, okay. I did instantly solved and they got it rolling
immediately. Sounds, sounds, sounds about right. I'm all, I'm all for trophies and knickknacks and
just things to put around your house and just have clutter to just, you know, seize up your brain
and make you unable to function whatsoever. I'm going to hang out next to my diploma from school.
I mean, the diploma is far more impressive, but, you know,
I'm down for stuff like that. Oh, yeah. Do you like it? Do you like it?
Anybody can get a fucking diploma. Anybody can get a diploma. It takes work to get a hundred
thousand subscribers. You know, that's actually an interesting one's one's an accomplished more
impressive because like, I mean, just for example, look at the case of the, of the, the furtive Si.
Si is not, you know, he actually was pretty successful on YouTube for a while. But like,
but the question is like, what did it turn into long term? Because it wasn't like sustainable,
but he did get the play button. So as opposed to like a degree, a degree is something tangible
that you can have forever and used to to apply for jobs. Are you talking about Si all the time on
this show? This is something that if your diploma is something that if all goes according to plan,
you will never need again. Well, that is true. That is true. Then we can't hear you if you're
talking right now, if you're saying something. Yeah, you're dead. I don't hear a thing from Zen.
Having some audio. Maybe try rejoining or something. Oh, no. I don't know. No, no.
We have not even the last couple of minutes, at least for the past 10 minutes. I don't know.
Try restarting Discord, dude. Try. Doesn't make any sense. He introduced the episode and then
died. Is it just your mic? Is it recording into audacity correctly or something?
I don't know.
Is that dance text status or that damn voice status?
I guess restart your computer. I don't know. That's all I got. Delete your computer. Delete
your account. Discord complications. Delete system 32.
We're all docked up and ready to go. Hey, here's here's a fun fact. What's up,
Tony? The PCP has been getting just so fucked with demonetization recently,
that it simply was not the case up until very recently. But now I'm used to every episode.
Add Pocalypse too, baby. I mean, maybe. I'm used to every episode initially
getting said it's going to be demonetized. And then I do an appeal and they say, oh,
that's actually, you know, now it's fine. We understand. Like, sure, you guys were a little
bit silly, but you've been demonetized. Every fucking piece, literally every PCP episode
until late, like late April has been demonetized. And I don't think they were at the time. I think
they've been changed since then. And these have all been confirmed by manual review. YouTube changed
their their policy. And then they just, I don't know, man. They said no low quality podcast allowed.
Well, no, it's because of the fucking swearing. Yeah.
Yeah, because I've been seeing a lot of people complain about getting demonetized.
Carlos Mazzo started a whole fucking thing with Vox and they came down on YouTube hard.
I mean, sure. But like, we are in no way, I mean, people could be offended by what we say,
but we're not like in any way attacking people. We just swear. No, it has nothing to do with that.
They just they just doubled down on everything. And there's like hundreds of channels.
Just for the sake of clarification, the Vox thing was completely coincidental,
like the timing with at which YouTube changed the terms of service.
You think so? That was actually the case, because like they had it
like a while in the making. And like, you know,
well, regardless of the cause, it's fucking bullshit because there's nothing
unfamily friendly about this podcast. And they should be begging us to line up to serve ads on
our podcast. I was going to say that it's about time they finally caught up to our shenanigans.
They finally caught up with the times, demonetized the menace that is the procrastinators podcast.
I mean, I get it. If you got like a family friendly company, you probably wouldn't want to be on a
rather crass podcast, which is this one, I guess. It doesn't make sense to me because of the fact
that you can target ads to people based on the data you get from their computer or whatever.
So give us the fucking big titty enhancement surgery ads or whatever, you know?
People who are not children also spend money. Like there's lots of people who
adverts are going to be useful to for them to see.
Like fucking like Dick's Razor sponsors, you know, like they themselves sponsor fucking,
what's his name? Harry's Razor.
Maddox X co-host, Dick Show, Dick Show. Okay, I understand those guys,
I don't think they have like ads on YouTube, but like people like those are obviously showing
that like they're perfectly happy to be on like rude, crass stuff.
So where's the why not why not have a category for that kind of stuff?
Yeah, we've got YouTube kids. What about YouTube? Not kids.
I don't know. Maybe maybe like YouTube dark red YouTube.
After dark YouTube after dark the whole site.
It's just in dark mode.
Dark mode has to be enabled always.
It's mandatory.
I don't know. Maybe it's like a kind of worms that they don't want to open for some reason.
You know, yeah, that's probably true. And I get that like YouTube,
you know, a lot of people will find it really easy to shit on YouTube.
I'm actually pretty sympathetic to a lot of these things that they're being forced to do with.
No.
Because these are questions that like no one in the world has been had to like sort out the
exact nitty-gritty of YouTube now.
Except for fucking television.
How come you're not sympathetic?
I want to know.
To YouTube?
Yeah.
Because like, I don't know. I mean, it's not even something that's like super like based in logic
to be fair.
It's just like, yeah, just like an emotional reaction.
Like, like we have, we have TV and we have radio.
These other mediums that existed forever.
And like they've sorted all this shit out.
It's not that difficult.
Right. But like the sheer amount of content that YouTube has as opposed to those other mediums.
It's just like.
I think it was.
What does that have to do with setting policy changes?
You know, like a policy.
Whether there's five channels or five million, your policy affects them all the same.
Right.
Yeah.
I think that the manual review thing, that's kind of bullshit.
The fact that you guys got the monetized form.
I don't think there even should need to be manual review.
There should just be simple policy that affects everything.
And it's like, okay, if you are, if you, if we detect swearing or whatever in your fucking thing,
we'll have, we have something for when you're an advertiser and you get on YouTube.
It's like, do you want your stuff in front of adult content?
Yes or no?
They check.
Yes.
You just go on whatever.
They check.
No.
If the system scans and figures out anything.
I mean, I would love that.
You just aren't put on those videos.
So that's why I have no mercy.
No, but like the thing about that is like, it's such an easy solution that like,
I, I, I can't help but think that they actually have a good reason for not doing it.
You know, because they probably make more money with the convoluted system they have right now.
I guess.
Well, I mean, maybe.
I mean, it seems to me.
But has money always been like the motor's operandi for YouTube?
I thought that the thing that they value most is like the advertiser information,
as opposed to like making, because like, aren't they always in the red?
Yeah, they never, they've never been profit.
From what I understand, hosting the videos puts them in the red,
but I'm sure the data that they're skimming now lets the rest of their business,
such as search and ad words, make way more fucking money.
I don't know how it all balances out.
Like the, so of course they're not going to make that data public because they don't want you to.
The idea that you had.
So everything speculation at the end of the day.
The idea that you had, Tom, about like advertisers checking if they want things,
like that would be great.
But I think the reason YouTube doesn't do that is not because YouTube like is good.
Like none of this is like, oh, YouTube's, you know, I'm not like
saying that any of these things means that I respect and trust YouTube,
because ultimately they do stuff that I don't like.
And even if they can't help but do it, I don't like it.
But it's probably just because big advertisers, because of various news things with like PewDiePie,
have this idea that YouTube can be like a really horrible place.
And so YouTube has to like double down on getting rid of adult content,
even if it's like not that bad, even if it's just a fuck word every so often.
They have to like, they have to be seen to be pushing that so hard
so that they can get the biggest advertisers back.
Don't you think it's stupid, right?
That YouTube costs, like the Carlos Mazda thing is like the newest like example of this,
but like YouTube has a history of doing this where the legacy media will like
write hit pieces about YouTube and they'll capitulate,
even though the legacy media is their competitor and they're just like allowing their
competition that's already like basically dead already.
Like YouTube won, like it is a bigger, more powerful platform.
But all these small sites are just like,
well, if we just keep writing hit pieces and we still have this like
image of power or whatever our influence, we can force this company to do what we want
to put us in a better position.
It's just like insanity to me.
Like there's a really interesting video series by PSACich talking about the last adpocalypse
and how it was all like, like purposely designed in order to
I saw that video.
It was fucking great.
Or one of them anyway.
There's like two of them, I think.
Wasn't there one that you were talking about with like Rupert Murdoch
being sort of like the market value?
That's the one, dude.
It's fucking fascinating.
You're like, he's behind it all.
And it sounds like you're in a beautiful mind room.
But at the same time, it sort of makes sense.
Right.
It's like one of those crackpot conspiracy theories that it's like,
yeah, but like the pieces really do kind of fall into place.
Like it's pretty compelling.
Well, I mean, when it comes to YouTube's action specifically,
like I it's your world.
We could all sit here all day and talk about like the things that we think are a better
policy for them.
It's just that like I feel that I don't want to be ungrateful.
Really is what it comes down to great.
And I have lots of sympathy for how like I was saying before,
like how complicated some of these questions really are about like,
like advertisers have expectations.
And then I think it's true like the media class will kind of try to swoop in on things
if it doesn't just have good optics.
So they have to like take that into consideration and like think,
OK, well, we can't.
Because the only reason advertisers are on YouTube is because they realize it's more
effective than traditional media platforms to get bigger reach for less money.
That's like the whole thing.
So if they don't want to play by the rules of being like,
yeah, new media is all about crazy fucking uncensored, insane content.
And you don't want to be a part of that.
Then just don't advertise on YouTube.
Like YouTube had all the power here because they were the ones.
They are the second biggest search engine on the Internet.
They are the single biggest website in existence.
They have all the eyeballs.
They had the power.
They could have said, you know what?
This is how the game is going to be played.
If you don't like it, have fun.
Advertising and like People Magazine are reaching seven people,
but they didn't do that.
They let themselves get co-opted by interests that are counter to their platform functioning
properly.
I would not give YouTube a free pass for like doing stupid shit on the regular
because of how stupid it is.
But I will say that there is some sort of like,
there's an element of like entitlement to being paid on the Internet.
Like this was not a thing that could be done like a decade ago,
or maybe two decades ago at this point.
So like I won't give YouTube a pass for being stupid,
but I will praise YouTube for at least existing as a free video
uploading site that has a large amount of people to see.
I'm not going to say here that like, oh,
YouTube like sucks and is the worst thing ever.
I just think YouTube is making shitty bad decisions in terms of running.
Perfectly fine.
Perfectly fine point.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know.
I mean, if they keep on capitulating, what is why then?
You know, is it because like they want the image of being like a legitimate source?
Because I mean, there's a lot of a lot of just evidence of Google and YouTube
wanting to be seen as in a certain political light.
Political might not even be the right word for it,
but just like social light like they want.
Yeah, like friendly stuff.
The quote unquote right side of history or whatever.
Like that's just like the zeitgeist, the cultural zeitgeist right now.
And because they're like a company that's like affects everybody,
they kind of have to like try and ride that wave just to be like, I guess safe.
I'm not really sure.
But like, but like, you know, it just seems that I mean,
I'm obviously biased in my assessment of this because I'm not like into the whole
politically correct thing.
So like when you capitulate to those ideas,
it just inherently pisses me off because I think they're bad ideas.
So I can't sit here and like be the objective arbiter of what YouTube is doing
and what Google is doing.
So my opinion obviously isn't the greatest in this sense,
but it just seems to me that like this site was built on the backs of people
doing weird fucking shit you wouldn't see on TV.
And in response, because TV is getting fucked and all these legacy
medias are getting fucked, they're trying to turn YouTube into a platform that
supports that kind of content at the expense of everyone who made the site
what it is today.
Without fucking crazy weird people, you wouldn't have this platform
to even get ruined like this in the first place.
And it's like you like YouTube should be in my opinion.
And I think most people would agree to me not TV.
It should be something else.
If you want to get a TV experience, you should go get a cable subscription.
If you want to see people in profitable and YouTube isn't.
Well, is it not profitable?
YouTube isn't profitable in terms of like hosting all the video, right?
So Google's responsible.
The question is why does Google continue to subsidize YouTube at all
if it's so unprofitable?
Well, I mean, I think there are many reasons why.
Yeah, I mean the data they're getting from it must be insane.
But like here's another thing.
Instead of like trying to like court advertisers and change what the product is,
like we have a small site like BitShoot, which is built on peer to peer
instead of having servers.
And they're drastically undercutting the cost of hosting video
because they're not hosting any videos really.
They're hosting the the torrent files.
So like it's not if like a bunch of people who are pissed off with YouTube
can make a quote unquote more efficient system.
I don't see why a massive multi-billion dollar company like Alphabet couldn't be like,
hey, maybe we should try and change the way that YouTube's underpinnings work
to make it more profitable for us short term.
Well, there's always going to be cultural inertia at the company
and a desire to change as little as possible.
Like like in order to do that, they might need to like go even further down the fuck
the common people and, you know, suck up to the big companies that can pay them to have.
I mean, but here's the thing, it's like you can suck up to the big companies all you want.
But are any of us going to say that Google is smaller than like the New York Times?
Like Google is the biggest company?
Well, what I mean by that is like investors, like an individual human being who makes a
YouTube channel and can make it big is more than it just being really nice as an idea.
It is kind of a marketing thing.
They want to keep that alive.
And I think if they need to make money short term, they're going to have to like
cut a lot of the people who are trying and like hogging up a lot of the, you know,
the data on the servers by not being that good.
They're going to need to like cut because it really is not profitable to have all these people
a free platform.
And like to keep, they have to keep that going because that's the gimmick.
But, you know, how do they do this is like it could be considered defeatist.
At the same time, I call it pragmatic.
It's just like, I'm not going to get mad at a business for being a business and trying
to attain more capital.
It's like, yeah, that's what it's always been like, whether it's social or monetary.
It's like, yeah, this is what I expected from the get go.
And like people getting mad at it.
It's like, well, you're just fighting like a, a, a Sisyphean struggle and not even that.
It's just like, you're not going to get to, you're not going to appeal to the morality,
you know?
Sure, of course.
Like, like I can be righteously indignated all I want, but I'm not going to expect YouTube
to make better decisions.
They clearly have their agenda.
You've got guys like Carlos Mazza making an explicitly moral case for changes to the contrary.
And it's not like he had a ton of influence, but at least the one thing that was done in
response to that was, you know, like Steven Crowder being demonetized, which I mean, I
didn't, I don't know the exact details, but I think that they said first, he hadn't violated
any rules, but they changed it.
Violate rules?
No, no.
It's so weird.
They said that they didn't violate any rules.
It just goes to show, like, how, it's like, how, how, you know, the way that they do it
is so case by case, they don't even follow their own guidelines.
Like if they had, well, that's why I want to follow, they just be like, okay, yeah,
he either did do it or didn't do it, but then they like flipped on the decision.
Right.
Like what do they do?
Because of the public outcry.
They're just trying to protect the room to be able to take whatever position is the
most convenient at the time.
That's why they don't want to convict, could like commit to either being a publisher
or a like a free, you know, open platform for everybody because they want to be able
to take whichever position works for them.
Well, all of social media has that problem.
It's not just a, and I get it.
I want to do the same thing too.
If I was them, it's the most interesting thing with Carlos Mazza.
How I had nothing to do with that in the first place.
And they were just using that as a leverage to fuck over Fox to get more money because
there was a huge strike going on at Fox.
And anyway, that, that, that's true.
And they're trying to hurt YouTube as a platform because that's how Fox makes their
money, but they don't care how fuck YouTube is because Fox pays them.
It is a coincidence.
I'm, I'm a pretty anti-conspiratorial guy though, which is sometimes I probably miss
things because I'm so like not.
I really don't want to be that guy, but like there may legitimately be some connection
between the fact this attack came at that time and Fox was trying to negotiate.
Or like Carlos Mazza was talking about how fuck Fox is and how they need to change their
shit and then does this.
It's just like, I mean, I'm not in his head.
I can't, I can't say for sure that that was what happened, but it just, you know, looking
at the evidence, it's like there is a case to be made there and who the fuck knows.
All I know is that YouTube is going to do what it does.
I don't expect it to ever get better.
I only expect it to get worse because that's been the trend for the last 10 years.
I don't see it changing.
And so I'm just waiting.
You can't even remember a time when we weren't talking about how YouTube is fucking up and
making terrible decisions and ruining everything.
I mean, back in like 2007, like it was pretty dope.
Well, no, I think people always complained, but the complaints they had were like, oh,
why did they change the layout?
Right.
It was really very smooth.
People like to complain.
It's just like, we didn't know how good we had it.
Yeah.
All we had to worry about was shit.
I don't know where my buttons went.
You know, it hasn't been until the last like five plus years that any of us were even on
this side of the fence.
Yeah.
That's true.
So I didn't give a shit about monetization back when I wasn't even thinking about it.
You know, right.
And I'm sure this would be a more common case if because like what site is there like YouTube
where it's this big and there are this many people making money from it.
You know, Uber, Uber, Uber, I'm talking about like a YouTube, YouTube is video Uber.
Maybe like Instagram only Instagram doesn't pay its people.
Instead of taking you from point A to point B, you're taking them on like an like an emotional
like video journey.
Like I'll let me teach you about like precisely something like hey guys, we we we the company
will pay you some like piddling amount of like what your what your what your videos are worth.
But like, you know, you can just but the sky's the limit.
Like it's you know, it's like a fuck it.
I don't know.
I can't I can't wait.
We'll give you the tools to make content for us.
It's like they do that with like the music catalog that they make available.
And you know, of course, all the tools to just uploading and premiering and
super chats and that kind of stuff.
Yeah, which of course they benefit from.
I can't wait to get into my Uber.
I can't wait to get into my Uber and the guy to look at me and be like,
hey, Tom, sorry, I haven't driven you anywhere in a while.
Oh, yes.
Oh, now I want that.
Now I want now I want an Uber driver to be like vlogging while Uber driving.
Now that's doubling up on content.
That's just smart.
That's just the way to do it, man.
Hey guys, I got some freaks in the back right now.
I'm just trying to make a YouTube channel about being an Uber driver.
And you just it's like Uber is like playing Russian roulette.
But instead of dying, if you get the bull, you actually just have an extremely euphoric
experience of talking to some bizarre absolute freak.
For instance, most of the time, let's get like a nothing burger, just absolute like,
oh, guy with glasses or guy with hair.
But then if you're out on the prowl late at night like I am, you know,
scrounging for trash on Newberry Street and you call your guy at like 2am, then he'll come
and he'll be fully dressed and drag literally in dominatrix gear, dominatrix gear, not a joke
and offer you candy, which you will of course accept with a whole open hand.
You will just get poured candy candy from this man.
And it will be a great time and you'll talk to him about his ex wives.
Literally just the best experience I've ever had.
Uber drivers are the weird Uber drivers specifically are a treat to the world.
Truly.
I haven't had many experiences like that.
People just talk about crazy taxidrivers and stuff.
But I don't know.
Mostly they're just like quiet, older guys who clearly do not want to be doing this.
But I don't know if they've fallen on hard times, their their corporate job got,
you know, shipped off to China.
And so now they had one Uber driver who was really into his car and he was just like,
hey, check this out and just kind of a little bit.
Imagine if he does that with every single passenger.
Dude, check out how I can rev with fucking engine, bro.
Look at my car, how fast it can go.
Just a little bit.
Just a little bit, just enough to make me uncomfortable.
My favorite thing about Uber drivers though, they are the exact archetype of character
that I enjoy, which is to say people who are really like enthused about bizarre things that
don't matter at all.
For instance, there was one Uber driver I was in the car with who just was,
just completely hung up about Hangover Part 2.
And he just loved the Hangover Part 2 specifically.
And the entire time he was just talking to me about how, you know,
oh, it's kind of dangerous on the street, you know, like in Hangover Part 2,
they got into a lot of trouble back out of there.
And I just think we got to be real careful nowadays, you know.
You know about the combat zone back in Boston, there used to be a combat zone.
People would be, they'd shave your back for a nickel and put the Hangover Part 2.
They wouldn't do that if you gave them a $5 bill.
I'm like, oh, God, let me out.
I think you remember too much of that.
I think you're destined to become an Uber driver.
You know what?
Maybe so.
And if I am, I accept that Disney with open arms.
Because I love it.
Could you imagine having Munchie as an Uber driver?
Oh, God.
Munchie is famously post job, along with his whole generation.
Being an Uber driver is definitely post job.
Oh, 100%.
Buckle your seat belts!
We're going on a bumpy ride!
Goes two miles an hour because I'm scared of driving.
Just be a Boston Uber driver and not respond to any locations in the real world,
but simply use, you know, slime city locations.
Are they going to say not respond to people when they talk to me?
Just like open the door and just like if they try to speak to me.
Just like say, oh no, I can't do that.
You know what that reminds me of though?
When I was in Japan, there were these restaurants that you, before you enter,
it's like a vending machine on the outside where you select the food you want.
And you put it in and you put your money in, like a vending machine.
It gives you a ticket and it also prints it on the inside.
You just go sit down and the guy behind the counter, like he got the ticket on his side
and he just like, you know, brings it where you need to be.
There should be, actually now that I think about this is exactly how Uber works
because they are given the location that you're going to ahead of time.
And so they know beforehand before they even pick you up
if they want to drive you there or not.
So the future is now, I guess.
We did it in Japan.
Truly.
I missed those restaurants though.
They were the best.
I didn't have to talk to anyone.
Oh, that's the way.
Do you think this is the way to de-populate Japan?
I don't want to be presumptuous in assuming that you all have,
you've all had the experience of having a bad computer or laptop.
Is that true?
Of course.
I mean, I think it exists without having that experience.
So that means you can truly appreciate that I recently, yesterday,
got a beautiful 28 gig RAM, 512 SSD, 512 gig SSD laptop yesterday.
Oh, it's beautiful.
It runs.
I bet Minecraft runs like a dream.
It runs like a dream.
You have no idea.
I love it so much.
And that's exactly the reason.
I got that feeling the other day.
Or like a couple of months ago, I got my new desktop.
Oh, this will feel like, dude, when you can open up Firefox
doesn't take literally like two and a half minutes to load.
Dude, it's fucking beautiful.
It's like the contrast between like the old laptop that you had the day before and like this one.
Oh, oh, yeah.
Beautiful.
Oh, yeah.
And it's like, that's exactly why I offered to edit this episode because of that.
Oh, just for the sheer joy of doing the end of the process.
Oh, seeing the render off.
That render bar fill up like way faster.
And just like, oh, my pet peeve with my old laptop was the fact that when I was rendering,
I couldn't do anything else with the laptop because I took up all of the RAM.
So literally, I uploaded a video that was like four minutes yesterday,
and it took an hour and a half to render.
All right.
That's insane.
Absolutely.
I rendered a video today about the same time.
Took a minute.
Beautiful.
Took one minute.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's insane.
You know, I don't know if this is just me, but I feel like, I mean,
this definitely happened with my old computer.
I've got a relatively new one.
It's pretty great.
Tom helped me build it and stuff, or help me pick out the parts.
And I moved stuff Tom as well when I made my computer, so.
Indeed.
God bless, Tom.
I feel like it's taking longer and longer for renders to happen.
And I'm just wondering, like, what processes can I do to clean this up so it stays pristine?
Oh, yeah.
I've been wondering about that as well because I've noticed my computer is like taking like
five minutes to boot up now.
It's a long time.
I think I need to like defragment or something or like clean up some stuff.
Because it was, I hadn't really added that much more things.
I don't think.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I just, I assume it's just like adding junk to, I mean, I don't know,
when you install stuff, sometimes there's just like, not installers, but like run,
like it was start up processes, just start up, and then they just eat up.
Yeah, I got, I went to settings to like turn off the things that happen on startup,
but it wasn't even that many things.
And it's still taking a little longer than I would like.
I just assumed that it's like, it's like a big bag.
My computer is like a big cloth bag.
And I just throw software in there and they all got piled up.
And then it's like on Christmas day, when you're at Timmy's house and you got to give
him his present and you're reaching around.
Oh, there's so much.
I can't find it.
Why is the fucking, why are you at Timmy's house on Christmas?
Because I am Santa Claus.
Your parents kick you out.
Okay.
There you go.
I am Santa.
And it's very unfortunate.
This is how I imagine computers work.
I actually do know how they work.
I did, in fact, go to school for this, but none of that.
No, computers are like magic, dudes.
You know, you put a weasel in a box and he makes it go, wha!
Exactly.
True or anything, exactly.
I built an OS once in college.
I mean, it was very simple OS, but it worked.
Oh, temple OS?
Oh, best OS ever.
I know about allocating RAM and shit.
Is it, was it, was it you call it best OS ever?
I, oh, actually what it was was, it was a, no, I did not, but it's an OS that the,
like they give you like, here are the specs.
Make this in Python.
At least I think we use Python.
And just like have it run with exactly these parameters.
So it's not like we let like come up with like an original OS.
They gave us one to make and it was like,
everybody's is going to work pretty much the same.
Oh, so you were a sheep.
You didn't, you didn't make it yourself.
You know, you were just following orders.
Well, that wasn't the assignment.
Now was it, Munchy?
I'm not Jim.
I'm not here to learn.
I'm here to do.
I am Nate does his homework best man.
That's me.
Can we all just talk about how great Jim Microsoft is?
I love that guy.
He's really done good work.
I like Jim Microsoft, but I hate when I go to the Jim Microsoft
and he starts beating the shit out of me just because I entered his domain.
Wait, I go to the Microsoft gym and I push computers to gain muscle mass.
That's the right thing.
I like Microsoft penis.
I, my penis, yes.
We can all agree on that one.
When you're running on fumes and your bryos start to shut down,
I have experienced that multiple times throughout this past week.
Throughout this call.
It's wax and wane.
I like, you know, I would start curing, becoming disheveled.
Then I would like wake up a little bit, you know,
someone would say something.
Then I would just recede back into the annals of just
docking foreskin and other man's penis.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, yeah, exactly.
But for the past like week, I have been creating and have released
and it's already all done in a series of updates for endless war
that have involved an ARG.
And there's this out of cash.
This is oh, see guys, sorry.
So don't worry about that.
There's no way this is going to top the Japanese juggalo.
I'm just putting that out there right now.
We've nothing, nothing can.
Nothing can in society, like not just like the Japanese juggalo ARG,
but just like, you know, in general, the Japanese juggalo.
We've hit peak culture.
I remember, I remember when I first met Econ,
we first met Econ at Anime Expo like 2017, I think.
I don't like, like, like the first thing that we said to him
is just that he was asking, you know, like what we did.
And you said that you had a YouTube channel.
I was like, oh, yeah, I did anime videos too.
Then I put on the Japanese juggalo form.
He didn't know what he was in for.
Anyway, so I did a, I hosted a successful, I'll say, ARG.
In, in this war.
And it was a great experience.
And like, legitimately, like it's a really like
enchanted magical feeling.
When you have constructed this puzzle for people
and you hit the sweet spot of not too hard, not too easy.
And you can hear them do like their, their brains rattling off.
Like, you know, like their CPUs overheating,
trying to figure out the puzzles that you said,
but they are exhilarated by it.
They're not just absolutely defeated by it.
And you can see them like work through and like just discover
and like soak up all the lore that even viewed into each image.
And that was incredible.
The payoff of it was great.
And I'm extremely, I'm just happy with how it turned out.
However, the preceding hours of my life,
I can only describe as just literally the Majora's Mask commercial from 2000,
where it is a faux radio announcer saying the world's ending
and that he is pressuring this kid who's playing Majora's Mask
to win or else the entire world will die.
And then there's spliced an interview of various people in real life
saying that they missed their parents.
That was literally what my life was.
I don't know how to say this kid, but there's not a lot of time left.
Play hard, will ya?
So literally for the, like previous to me releasing that,
I had been awake for several days and unironically,
just going fucking ham.
The amount of things that I had written in that time
were akin to maybe 500 clay slash stone tablets,
depending on the mining quality that I could possibly achieve at the same time.
And etching those runes into that stone was a difficult process.
And I'm going to spare you the details
because I'm not here to suck my own dick or take up the show for any longer.
But I just want to say that to set up for my real anecdote here,
just know that I, this is our, I believe, 27.
I'm almost done.
I've written mountains and mountains of work.
I'm almost, the end is in sight, mere hours.
Literally two hours before it's set to go live.
And I have a hard day.
I released a video on the PCP you might have seen
in coming Slamtorp Transmission.
There's a hard date set on there for an in-game event
that would be happening to set out.
So yeah, I had a hard date that I,
or rather a hard time in that date that I had to achieve.
Or else things would go fucking south.
So, two hours until that time.
Almost done.
Make it, you know, make it, make it a good time.
I mean, I'm feeling good.
Make it count.
You know, you know, I-
So that's by the time people hear this.
It will have been several days.
Oh, oh yes.
No, yeah.
Yeah, of course.
The time thing always fucked me.
Okay, I'm with you.
I'm with you.
Say it.
Um, and so, you know, I'm doing good,
but I can't take any more breaks, you know.
I've had my mandatory one hour every 12 hours where I go to eat.
I've already had that.
I can't do anymore.
But I'm on track, and then I get a phone call.
I answer.
It's my mom.
She says the following words to me.
Hello.
The cable band's here.
He needs to see the modem
so that he can install a camera on the front door.
Okay.
And then she hangs up.
And then, like, I just slow pan out to my room,
which is a disheveled tornado mess.
Literally corpses in here, as far as I can tell.
There's just blood and shit smeared on every single surface.
And the amount of quake energy cans that are just crumpled up near me
could, like, just recycling.
Done.
The moment that I turn these cans in.
We don't need to do it anymore because I've done it enough.
Metal is saved.
Renewable resource found.
And so I haven't showered.
I'm just a complete mess full of wax and brimstone.
And I have to just open the door for this cable man who, of course,
I did not know this person was coming.
Of course, there was no, you know, hey, hey, Anthony, there's a dude coming, by the way,
most important day of your life.
The most important day of your entire social experience online.
All this guy coming to ruin it.
So I had to open my door.
I just had this man violate my personal space.
Violate my room.
Just fuck around with my modem.
You know, just drill a hole into it.
Stick his dick and come in and say, oh, this is fine, right?
No, it's not fine.
It's not.
And I get to work up into a tizia.
Just walk downstairs.
I allow him to do his work in my room.
I come downstairs and I say, hey, I say, hey, what's going on?
What's this about a camera on the front door?
And they're like, oh, actually, we misheard him.
We don't even want him to do this.
Like, we just got a bundle.
So we had to let him do it.
But we don't even want the features in time.
But he's installing smart lights.
So we'll get an app on our phone where you can dim the light smart phone.
Well, with that being neat.
An hour goes by.
An hour of time lost.
I do not have this time to spare.
I do not.
I just walk out to my farm and I want to plow the field.
I do not want to plow the seeds of the ocean.
I don't know if I get against the waves of the world.
And yet I am fucked.
I do so.
And I go and I and I and I must have the words flow from my finger at this point.
I have exiled cable man and it's coming down to the fucking wire.
I release the video like mere like minutes before it's set to go off.
Basically, no one knows what's happening.
But the fact remains that I did it technically correct.
I'm seething and I'm panting.
And I and I log in to my alternate account that the character,
you know, blah, blah, blah character, ARG stuff.
And I do it like within 10 minutes from the event happening.
But I do it.
But I do it and it's glorious.
And I just wanted to share that little story with you because I hate cable man
and I hate modems and I hate smart lights.
And I hate all of you.
If you're listening to this, play hard kid, win this one, will you?
I appreciate that.
I will say in my dad demeanor that one really should never find themselves ever
if it can be avoided in a position where an hour of distraction will make or break
some great enterprise.
It should be ready significantly ahead of time
so that you don't have to be in a crunch time like that.
But I'm not one to talk having literally failed me a math of a two.
Now am I?
So, you know, I will say a point, Nate.
There's something oddly like I find like perversely erotic about crunch time.
And I know it's bad.
And I know that everyone's gonna cancel me on Twitter.
I know everyone's gonna-
I know what those game devs are complaining about.
I'd be jacking my at full mass the entire time while boss man whips me into submission
as I crank out that last, you know, animation on the bull testicles
in Red Dev Redemption 2.
I know like five minutes after release this episode,
Super Bonnie Hopkins in a release of Angry Video that has me as the subject.
But like I'm just saying that like crunch time,
looking it ruins my body.
It like it literally like makes me like ill and like I felt sick for like a day or two
afterward.
And it wasn't cool.
I was a very unhealthy man during me a math of a two.
Just just in general as a lifestyle thing for sure.
But like there's something about like dude, I'm getting shit done.
Like I'm achieving goals right now.
Literally like I see a goal and I'm running towards it.
Like it feels good in that way.
Obviously there's a lot of downsides, but it feels good just-
It's the classic Shonen trope in which the MC obtains a retarded power that gives him
extra strength, but at the extremely nebulous cost of like quote,
some of his lifespan or quote, it's shortening his life.
It's just the most, you never have to worry about that while the series is going on.
It's a total like Deus Ex Machina piece of shit answer to give a false cost to whatever
the characters are doing, but it's pretty sick.
I kind of literally agree that like okay, I've recently come to the conclusion that like
basically no bodily harm is that bad.
Like you know you can treat your body poorly and like you know it's not good,
but like you know like it's it'll be fine.
Like I've taken it just not eating.
We may reevaluate that.
I've taken it just not eating because like you know like whatever, like you don't eat it.
Whatever dude.
What's the worst that could happen?
Yeah, you know literally.
Die.
That is the worst.
Munchy, I have like not necessarily for like the like I know exactly that feeling,
but like not exactly for because um because the the the prospect of like producing stuff
still like or doing good work because sometimes I just feel like shit
like everything is going wrong and I am so ragged like run ragged like I smell like shit.
I feel like shit like I've got both legs broken like blood everywhere piss everywhere
like nobody knows how bad I've got it um and I'm just like I'm standing there like with all my
skin like falling off like I'm I'm dead like I'm a zombie from from Dark Souls and I have like
one arm that can work and I'm looking at like a sheer cliff face and there's like
there's you know I could just sit down but there's there's something there's something really cool
about like just continuing like even though every bone in my body aches and like I'm just
not feeling it and I feel like shit and it's terrible and everything sucks I'm I'm just climbing
that mountain I'm climbing and I like nobody will know that the like there's something like
um uh there's there's a way to describe it but it's like
like the the the feeling that even though I'm not going to boast about having done this I know I've
done it right and and like I I I like the fact that nobody will uh like care that I done it
you you like the fact that I don't care I don't know why it's like it's some some sort of weird
dad thing like dad's like just doesn't matter dad's like complaining about like things not being fair
and things being fucked up and like everything sucks um but they don't really do anything to
make it better they just like to complain well I think just inherently like like everyone in the
entire world can agree that doing something that's dumb but doing something that's hard sexy as hell
that's so cool well true America loves winners the whole world does really uh yeah yeah I don't
know like I don't know whether other people understand this like the lack of recognition
because I'm I don't I don't usually bag a bragging boast um no no no I I totally understand where
you're coming from and this is sort of tangential but it applies so uh I was I was leasing a place
for a couple years and uh it came to the point where uh my roommates were uh starting to get a
little messy little messy you know and uh you know I I decided to become the house mom I did all
the dishes I uh I cleaned the tables I uh sweep the kitchen you know what it is and you know what
I never asked for gratitude I was like yeah this is what the house mom does and I just felt good
knowing that they see they see the kitchen next time and uh something that they left on the table
is no more there because I cleaned it up and they could have done it but I did it
because I'm the house mom you got you got taken advantage of my friends that's unpaid labor right
there my it is it is you got a demand compensation you know my compensation is feeling good about
job well done what a worthless currency if ever there was one the way I would explain the feeling
is like if I'm like really tired after doing a lot of work and stuff and then somebody says
hey we're going out to this thing and I'm like not in the mood at all but there's this there's this
you know it's good to be social like it's a good idea even if I'm not really feeling it I may as
well so I go to this thing um and nothing good comes of it and I come home no and it's like
at least I tried I guess that's the somewhat of the feeling sure yeah absolutely like doing
doing stuff even though you're not in the best of places it just feels good rather than than
than appeasing your base instinct to sit and do nothing and watch anime and play video games or
whatever it is yes yes which by the way this reminds me of I so I mentioned it before about my
quote-unquote failing me a math of a two I mean you know I can I can see why people consider that
because I did not succeed at getting one video out every day but uh there's one interesting
thing about it um so I heard a bunch of people shitting on like the last episode of me a math
of a two for one you know uh being a piece of shit begging for money uh you know bragging about my
vast internet success by showing my play button uh doing a terrible tier list section and then
playing a terrible cover of a uh boring hacky song wait Nate hold on it's all champion super
okay can we please smash cut to me earlier today scrolling through the comments of that video
specifically saying like Nate your singing voice is amazing ha ha wow even though I can't give money
you're an inspiration me Nate tee he well okay it's all about the human tendency to focus on the
negative absolutely absolutely true absolutely true but but I'm not even I'm not even saying that I
particularly think it was an overly negative reception but I'm just saying that there were
some voices that were critical there was a dude that had the same avatar focusing on it oh yeah I
appreciate that thanks a lot um but okay but my point was I what I what I felt was that like I had
made some very specific mistakes that led people to being uh critical of that and it was like by the
thing about me a math of a is just that it was set up to be one day one video so that even people who
hate me a math of a which I'm sure there are some or you know people who find my more I don't know my
less heavily edited content which I've been doing the last couple years is like less interesting than
like a best anime ever like they want smash videos they want that stuff where is it Nate so I totally
get why those people would like not be interested want to tune out any of that stuff and but the
thing is the the conceit on the ground is that you're getting 30 days of a 31 days of like a video a
day and after that you're free and after that you your debt is paid to society viewer subscriber
and you don't have to sit through any more of this the problem is by me getting off my schedule
one I'm pissing off those people who are like can we just be done with this um two by taking longer
to make videos it inherently raises expectations for what those videos are going to be so people
like with that last they were like wow like we waited three days this was the last episode of me
in MAFA not everybody said that but you know some people did and then finally the other problem and
this is the biggest one that ties into Gibbs Gibbs thing is that I personally like feel bad about all
this and I the thought comes into your mind of like can I like just not release anymore because I
don't think anybody like there's diminishing returns on me in MAFA too uh like this was evident
from the start um but like I owed it to like the promise of the of the of the program I guess
to get all the videos out but once you're past the deadline by like 20 days and you know people are
getting a little ornery and they want you to get back to your other stuff it's like what's the use
in continuing this and I mean I had to do it but it was like it was like a weird self-doubt
position I found myself in of like I know people just want me to move on to other stuff but I
promised I would do this and you know for all these reasons there are these negative consequences
that are going to come no matter what so so the answer simply is you know maybe I'll do a me in
MAFA again in the future but I I have there is no choice but to stick to the schedule for all
those reasons and uh I don't know and like because the original conceit is just to motivate me to
make content to to exactly feel what you were talking about kid to like feel like I'm doing
something as opposed to nothing like I because the original me in MAFA was maybe I can actually
make a fucking video or maybe I'll actually make a fucking video like me doing something as opposed
to nothing not these six month long projects um but now people know I can make a fucking video
so there's not a lot to prove um I don't know I don't know I was just reflecting on this and
I thought the whole the idea of like how it getting off schedule had a myriad of negative
effects both for me and for the people watching um it was it was a good learning experience if
nothing else um but I but I don't know I don't know it ties into all this stuff I realize I hadn't
watched your final episode all the way through I go over to it and I'm I'm seven minutes in
and I like the first seven minutes but then you start doing a tierless and I guess I just
was like oh lol who cares and I start joke but it is like a 15 minute long segment so that's I
get why some people are not a joke yeah well but okay it's a joke but it's also substantive
because it is a reflection on the entire me in MAFA two experience so you know sure there's an
I actually haven't watched it yet because uh my subscription feed is just it's so weird well it's
it's completely normal but the way that I interact with it is weird like I just well as that tier
list will tell you oh yeah sorry but as that tier list will tell you not every video is a gem so
don't feel you know any burning need to fucking sit through it all uh but some are but some are
the the fairy tale is dead featuring Zach Rittner oh no I've watched me a man for a
I just haven't watched the last one you know this is a this is another weird thing do you ever
okay this is just a general thing with all of us people we all make content we all make videos
isn't it kind of a weird thing when like you're talking to your buddies or whatever who like
know you make a content of some kind and it's gonna make you make it a content yeah like like I'm
talking about this thing like I I never feel this I really don't well okay I suppose in a little bit
I do but like I never feel like anyone needs to watch my content or owes me watching my content
or anything like that but you can tell when the conversation goes that way there's like a you
know there's like uh oh of course I've like seen some of your stuff I'm not even trying to show
and use then I just mean like I've noticed this over the years many times right and it's uh I don't
know like like right now I'm just like I have not watched Zen stuff in a while and I really like it so
I I should but like you know I it's almost kind of like a guilt thing I'm so sorry sir I please
forgive me a real a real fan would have watched uh insert fucking video name here yeah you don't
even know right exactly that's the thing shameful and it's like that's the thing about my content too
because it's literally whatever I want and that's true yeah I'm sort of uncapitalating in that sense
and you know that's probably not best in the business sense but uh it's a gratification on
what I'm making I love it it's a it's a grand old time I literally just release like two covers of
songs just cuz you know I have a second channel where I could have put it but the way I uh you
know choose what content to put on what channel is literally just a gut feeling I just look at the
video for three for three seconds and I'm like okay this channel or this channel and like there
there's no real distinction between the quality between the channels just like okay yeah uh I
just feel like it goes this way or this way it's like I love it you know it's like and I feel that
people subscribe for that experience just like oh it's a random grab bag what am I gonna get next
I went to I did a live stream where I just went to the museum of fine arts I was like okay hey
yeah that's all very good course stuff I think people who like who have stayed subs do you I mean
I don't know how uh how big you are now but you you're getting a pretty sizable following now yeah
and um it's uh I think those people definitely are on board for like the the eclectic zen experience
at this point so yeah so you you I think you've seemed to have really broken through any kind of
barrier like if there's people like a couple hundred subs and they upload like random stuff yeah I mean
I could certainly understand them thinking like uh geez if they've been doing it for a long time
what do I need to change but you I mean you seem well past that now so yeah I'm gonna make a I'm
gonna make a video on the world fair the 1964 world fair why that one I would I like I like I mean
that's I like that tell me tell me you tell me about that well I mean later yeah in the video
I don't want to follow too much because it ruined the incentive to come to the video but yeah yeah
okay yeah it doesn't to my knowledge it doesn't happen annually and um
um that's the one that uh come uh I caught wind of I don't know why exactly that one's important
but uh hey that's what research is for and that's what I'm going to do if we're calling like Disney
dates correctly that is relevant to Epcot I don't oh yeah that's it that's correct yes yes
did they like build Epcot for that or something well Epcot's well sort of kind of a little bit
in a roundabout way yes Epcot currently is sort of like a permanent world sphere because Walt was
always fascinated by them as a kid and and yeah okay so on and so forth I could go on all day about
Disney it doesn't matter here's a here's a slight left turn but not quite it's that uh hey Vapors
3 is out and I have read it oh my god sure why would you do that I I did it I did it and I mean
I don't know how much uh you would want to talk about I mean I would certainly encourage everyone
to go read it uh it's very in keeping with uh the Vapors style and uh a lot of great artwork
interested in magda focus story this time which is a magda chapter uh here's the thing about um
whenever I make anything I'm embarrassed about it instantly I put it out there I put it out there
and all I can think is like why did I do this you know I totally know what you mean it's like
it doesn't serve my own interest because I know that the thing to do is get out there and like start
talking about it and promoting it and pushing it but my instinct is to recoil away from it
as though in horror uh you know what I mean I totally get you and I think the problem is like
with somebody like me I have the advantage of my content being like a video thing that YouTube
just kind of helps me I don't have to go out and chill it really it just kind of you know
out there which is very convenient yours is a little bit different because you gotta
pound the pavement more and you gotta do something is magda just like rule 63 ben
they both are not entirely both Vincent and magda are both rule 63 ben ben I was very
think about it think about it I was I was really thinking about um uh Vapors in general after
reading that I was doing some reflection and I of course uh Vapors has always had a fairly um I'm
I'm not trying to say negative but like a fairly dark tone to it yeah I mean yeah everything about
like a desperation of their lives and I don't know things of that nature yeah yeah you could uh
you could say that I def I when I was reading this one I not only felt that that was the strongest
in uh in chapter three here uh and I I know was played for laughs but I felt a deep profound
like concern for magda's well-being yeah based on the events of this chapter and and you know what
like they're they're absolutely would have been a way for like these same events to be written in
the exact same way but to it to feel more light-hearted and like not serious but that really is not
what it's just not that's not what happens it felt deeply concerning about her state of mind
I've been all the things she went I've been thinking about this a bunch and I think yeah maybe
one way to describe the Vapors is like the opposite of a superhero story and that it is
stories about people of exceptionally low capacity just like people who are capable of the least
possible a super zero story yeah of course I could never tell you what to what to do with
the stories or anything but like the super relatable story yeah they are certainly relatable
although the thing magda goes into like almost it she's superhero level of incompetent at life
kind of and it is it is a sight to behold I think the fact that the entire chapter was like silent
like there was no dialogue really helped with the atmosphere that's kind of I mean um one and two are
largely like that as well the dialogue is really minimal there's there's no text maybe I mean I
I guess that's true but I mean I'm reading it now Mike magda always felt like like the sort of person
who like thinks in her head but it's like mostly nothing and then like there's nothing that she
thinks to say all the time she's a real cloudy head if you know what I'm saying look at her look at
her hair just like if somebody asked her a question she'd be like uh do I have to do I have an answer
to this I don't know doesn't seem to have a lot of self-confidence that's true um though you know
at the end of chapter two there's that moment and actually even at the end of chapter one
my my Nate senses gets so amped up to fucking 11 I get rock hard my veins bulged from my neck
when like for example at the end of chapter one Vincent goes to this event has a terrible time
but but he signed the form so he will be notified of future events I'm like yes a redemption is
he did it this character yes that's what I like to see motherfucker yeah I mean what's he gonna do
and maybe sign it he's fucking defeated he has no he's not defeated there's hope and then and then
chapter two he throws the book in the trash he has this horrible social experience because he's
got no competency but at the end he's reading the book again yes he didn't give up he can
got it he got it out he got it out of the trash he did that I'm like those moments of hope think
about it that's that's what I really I mean I love seeing the being such terrible pieces of shit
I love how he keeps on saying think about it think about it well that's just think about yeah well I
mean that's it that's all I want just think about it okay fair I but but in chapter three I'm glad
like I'm that is a super amped that you do think about that's all I want that's why I want people
to read it and just think about it think about it yeah but the difference with the end of three
it was good and I guess I won't go people should absolutely go read it but like it ends there's
there's no exactly the same kind of moment of like possible hope there although it does feel
like just kind of silly at the end which is good I'm glad the tone lightens a little at the end
so it gives me a similar kind of slight upbeat note at the end and I don't know the fact that magda
kind of overcame all the stuff in here that was kind of hopeful like wow this bitch can really walk
she can really walk she she really she really did it um I respect that uh well you know I mean
what choice did she have very well she you know when when faced with the possibility of like well
do I walk home or do I die in the streets she overcame she overcame I'll tell you what I'm
looking for Ben yeah I want to see in the future when it comes to the vapors I want to see more
magda not even necessarily like like winning at life but I want to see her strengths I want to
know what is going on in her head yeah because mostly it's been like she of course did drawing
stuff in in chapter one which I appreciated but like I want to know more about her her thoughts on
life aside from just her kind of general disposition um yeah that's well you know what I have what I
have to do now is I have to write a bunch of short um a bunch of short uh vaporette stories for uh
guest artists to draw for uh Kickstarter to for book two and I don't know what those are going to be
at all um uh they've got they've got parents I could have them like talk to their parents or
something I've been thinking about I don't know what they would say I don't know what the content
of that would be but that's like an aspect that's an interesting idea I haven't been really listening
but I have the mysteriousness of just these oh yeah I go on I just finished reading it uh I almost
did this exact thing in real life yeah yeah wait tell Elizabeth what do you mean tell me more uh
well it was yeah which thing it was like uh the the walking around aimlessly not knowing what to do
and then just walking all the way back home I was hoping I meant lying inert on the grass
not that stuff I mean I think I've done something like that before but like walk outside before and
like done things before and then walk no no no like walking to the point of like I've gone places
man I don't know what I'm doing I uh uh and then like yeah like yeah you know like uh same I get
that I get that like like you could maybe ask someone for directions or help but you're just
like no I don't want to interact with anyone I'm just uh well it's not even just that it's not even
just that I didn't know where I was going it was just that I had no direction in life literally
and I would walk oh I went I walked for a really long time and it was cold and it was terrible I
literally I literally guys I literally can't even um but I literally can't even uh like look at it
or think about it without feeling embarrassed or something yes it is nothing to pain for me to
constantly you know I think Ben all the things that I have done and made it's a small small point
but it's you know Ben I people always talk about how you know much they like my like
login reviews and stuff the fact of the matter is I have done like what five of my like big
staple videos like total in my entire video making thing yeah and frankly the ideas of making more
is extremely intimidating that I won't be able to like live up to it or that and releasing those
was always terrifying yeah and I remember when when Galco first came out um like I knew it was
like a less substantive overall video it and like people were like not I remember you these people
in this very call were not impressed with it I absolutely hated the Galco video yeah yeah and
and that's fine that's totally fine yeah but I just I have that same fear about like important
stuff I make and I think with it with both of us the more we make I think the more comfortable
will be just like well with it hasn't improved it hasn't gotten any better for me but that's my
point you haven't made that many maybe you if you get like five there's there was someone once said
that fear points true north and I thought that was an interesting fear points true north when it
comes to when it comes to creativity the thing you're most afraid of doing is definitely points
to our insecurities that's for sure I wait to elaborate on that I don't really I tell me if
this is right I think what you mean is that like um I mean I've heard this before that like if you're
afraid of something then like the thing to do that like that means you should do it like to grow as a
person or whatever yeah that was like the general idea of the quote that in the context they were
talking about like creativity and stuff is that like if you're afraid of doing something uh it's
it's the one like you're the most the most afraid of fucking it up because it's the one you're most
passionate about yeah hey give it I'll tell you I'll tell you what uh I actually do that that thing
where I just walk around aimlessly and I actually do it to my benefit because uh I'm I'm very much a
homebody so sometimes I'll just leave the house walk in any direction till I get lost right dude
it's fun I like that idea it's very fun I like that idea but like the time I was talking about is
right it was a bad time right it was a bad time in my life uh like uh bad like before even like
pony youtube this is like early early life like oh what do I do I'm gonna die I'm saying like do it
in a more neutral context it's great you get to see more of the city places you've never even seen
yeah I mean I I generally I generally I generally default to play pokemon go bro just play pokemon
go just literally just play pokemon go I mean I generally default to walking around rather than
getting transport because I don't like spending money and I think like my legs like could use the
exercises and it's free like it's better and for free so I'll walk it's an it's an hour's walk but
you know what I'll walk I'll have to walk back but that's fine I haven't talked to you in a while
and I just want to say that you stood me up you you you stood us up no I was broke and I'm here to
be funny I think I literally had two dollars in my bank account at that time there's no more embarrassing
excuse that I'm poor I hear people say this all the time just buy some money
mine's some crypto I don't understand the problem just mine some slime
yeah I don't have the diamond payback so I can I say me me Ben and Cassie we're on the prowl we were
gonna get happy lamb hot pot and we invited you we extended our we extended our hand to you and and
you first laughed away and you stabbed us in and and and you berated us you said why would ever
want to come out to have hot pot I hate Japan I remember that I did say that verbatim yeah
and I don't regret it actually yeah well you were you were right because that particular hot pot
was a shit show no no Ben no don't okay okay okay all right stop being an apology stop being an
apologist for happy lamb all right no no no no you must understand okay kaze was the shit hot pot
happy lamb is the good hot pot uh well whatever well whatever the first one the first one okay
me and ben went to a hot pot place it it sucked and the entire time ben was like oh I hate this hey
waitress hey toots come over here let me grab your ass I fucking hate you and and and she was like yes
sir yes sir I'm sorry sir and she was like oh fuck you and then he started pounding his desk saying
baby what bop bop baby went bop bop hey hey and and then and then he like he like jumped up on the
table he started banging his chest he leaped over to the next table ever he said hey eat the smallest
eat this muscle eat this $12 muscles marinara hey what a good deal let's go to Whole Foods next
let's get a good deal on some nuts yeah it was pearls before swine really oh was it Ben Ben Ben
it was terrible scallop was the one that scallop was the one good thing yeah that's why I meant the
scallop he was he was trying to use the forest and people to eat scallops against their will left
scallops right just like this is like how ben did the 180 uh when I came up like what like three weeks
ago when you specifically told told ben that it was an hour earlier to meet up than we actually
were going to assuming he was going to be late and then he woke up right when we were supposed
to be there and didn't even come to the uh to fire nice for you because munchie told me that you
guys were like already leaving I said that I was already I was like I was like I was like a little
bit late and I was like a little bit late yeah like that's like less than an hour and I was like hey
should you get should I still come and you were like nah we're already eating we're basically done
and then like four hours later you get to my house we did we did well wait this is not the
story how I was told munchie told me that he said to you we're meeting at 11 yes and that's yeah
no no I was I was like but we were actually but I could have still come the thing is we were actually
meeting at 12 he told you an hour earlier assuming you were going to be late no exactly that just
makes it worse because then it was like 12 and I was like should I come and he was like no it's
like two hours away from you I didn't think that you would want to do that you hung out for like
four more hours before you got to my house you told me this is vastly inaccurate most of that was
uber time because we got stuck in traffic in uber oh you're a fucker but but but you didn't
why am I a fucker because you lied to me what did I lie about you betrayed me well I did like you
saying to get there earlier than you were supposed to yeah and you didn't accomplish that I did I
know what what's the point of telling me to come an hour early and then so when I'm an hour late
and therefore on time you're like nah it's too late don't show up that's technically not on time if
the idea is to me yes at that time yes that's not on time at all you know but the point was that you
were just rolling out of bed and you were rolling out of bed an hour after you were like you thought
the time was supposed to be listen that's all fine that's that happened whatever I was at that point
at that point there was a choice at that point there was a choice to be made do I still come
and the right answer was yes but you told me no you did not care about your facts yeah that's
right I was I was going to say though that Ben Ben turned the day around because he was making
keto donuts and they were made those keto donuts and they were meat flavor and they were protein
flavored yeah okay I'm sourd forever a happy ending the black the blackberry ones were an experiment
and it failed and I and I and I copped to that I respect the effort though yes by the way I'm
enjoying this image that zen posted in the chat that I'm assuming your dad sense no I don't know
who that is no you don't know who it is no no I know Steve I don't know who sent me the
picture oh okay so wait Steve Aoki isn't your dad I'm confused now I'm getting lost in the story
put that where's where's the other people which chatter is in general general general yes
well when it comes to art block I mean yeah the the only thing I have is whenever I oh actually
we're talking about this before but it's like whenever I am stuck and I don't know what to do
I simply try to to find the smallest possible atomic version like step forward on whatever
the project is and I find that once I am in the mode where I do that one thing that's super easy
the next thing just is much easier in general so that's that's my yes I mean there's there's all
this sort of like just do it a sort of helpful advice that I that I hear um but you know all of
it horse shit all of it horse shit I think my point is a little more nuanced well no here's here's
the thing I was thinking about though um I I was getting on like from this from this uh
annoyance that I can't be bothered to like work as hard as I would like to I was getting on like
oh depression and then also um thinking about like uh what I want to do with my life maybe I
don't even like comics maybe I don't even like drawing maybe blah blah blah this like all stupid
shit that has no actual basis and it's just me being frustrated um that's a real and it is real
shit but I was thinking like the the the way that motivation like comes about is as a result of
something going well like you do something and you don't think much of it and if it goes well
then you're motivated by that to continue doing it and I guess I just feel like comics bail jpeh
it was good but for some reason it doesn't feel like it was a good like idea to I mean it was nice
that I finished it you know I know what you mean that scathing review I gave you last pcp where I
said it wasn't the best comic in the world and he said he he he's his hand quit around his
stylus and cracked in an ass so sorry so sorry tablet but like I mean it was mostly my own
thoughts about it and then it was I was asking people in my discord uh or rather like they
read the watch the pcp and heard that I wanted more criticism and they gave me criticism I was
like yes I agree with all these things and that's true and I was thinking like yeah that's good and
the fact that the the punk Kickstarter is like I know it's an inexpensive plush and not everybody
has the money but if it was popular it would just work it would just you know there would be
more fans if it was more I suppose like more marketable or I was better at spreading the word
or just it was if it was like from the beginning if it was like nicer to look at because the first
few panels are like complete shit and it doesn't seem to be going anywhere it's like that was the
nature of its creation that I didn't care about it initially and then it it sort of grew from
you know a very small thing but it's certainly got more impressive in it makes it difficult to
get into it I think punk is great but I mean I have put my money down on a plush I want everyone
go give money to the same fucking make it it it would start to be over by the time this comes out
or with the I think it will be over I don't know maybe maybe like a day just go check just go check
it I think there's like a day I think there'll be like a day or two left when this comes out
but um give not to be pessimistic but if it doesn't work out is it possible to do one
like of a smaller scale that would also make the plush real because I still want the damn plush
no matter what happens um I have been thinking about that the the possibility like what was
what's the cost now is it like it's like 50 right like six grand or something is that including
delivery uh well I just know that your kickstarter asks for something oh no no like
individually like what what the like 40 bucks 40 to 50 I think something like that like 50 something
if I scaled it back to like I don't know 50 plushes because there's like 50 people already
that want them or at least 50 backers so like potentially I could get 50 people again but
that would mean the plush would be like a hundred and something dollars plus shipping oh which would
which would like reduce the amount of people and then I won't probably won't even get 50
and then it would just be the same thing again I'm not sure okay okay but nonetheless people
go fucking pledge please help me get my plush yeah I put my money down god damn it I deserve a plush
do it for me do it for Nate Nate deserves his pump plush that's what I want beautiful but guys
it is just sort of a thing like seeing it not succeed sort of confirms my suspicions that it's
not that big I mean obviously I knew that it wasn't huge but it doesn't feel like it doesn't
motivate me to continue making comics not that I'm gonna stop but it's difficult now to like
I thought it wouldn't affect me the Kickstarter not working I thought I had like in my head
oh you know maybe it works maybe it doesn't doesn't matter I'll keep working and then I suddenly
find myself that I don't want to work and I thought it might be related to Kickstarter when
you started on this topic but when the when the PCP Kickstarter was going and you guys know I mean
we were all heavily invested in that I was worked a lot on getting that going I was terrified
dude we all were I was fucking worried I was just like I was like oh my god if this fail like
I'm just gonna feel like such a failure and feel so bad but the reality is like even if it hadn't
say I mean it vastly like doubled what we wanted to get you know due to the stretch goals and stuff
and that was great but even if it had failed I mean it's always scary because like you have a
vague idea of like how big your audience is and how much they're invested but like you never have
the exact amount or otherwise you you wouldn't be scared so it's like every time you go into
that venture of starting to kickstart it's like what's gonna happen but but you know like your
Kickstarter and Kickstarter is in general like obviously it's not like oh it's either you succeed
and you win or you fail and like now you're shit and everything you've done is bad yeah I mean it
shows you the real life the real situation that like you know there's currently a little bit less
people willing to put down money on it and that's just a good reality to be aware of
and like I mean I was just thinking I was thinking of this before like I was thinking that like
maybe this is one of your like ms paint adventures now deleted and homestuck.com but like maybe this
is like your I don't know what was the thing before before problem sleuth barred quest jail
and jail or whatever and I just I mean I I've been filled with hope and like Gibb's really done
cool comic stuff here I can't wait to see what he's gonna do next time I bet it'll be even better
and even cooler it is so if I may have the floor for a moment hippo I know you're a smart guy and I
sure you've thought about this before so I speak now purely for the audience's sake but you say
at the beginning of the conversation that you're making you know you're writing you're doing character
layouts is not the point of bail jpeg just that you were supposed to fly by the sea of your handle
by the by the by the seat of your pants by the pants of your pants not very but very marketable I
suppose I mean that's that's very slapdash and not very uh but possibly you know impressive
but that was the point that you were supposed to you know just kind of get it done and I just
want to say that you may want to you know increase the marketability may want to increase the overall
popularity of it for purely like a non you know oh great you are bad optic scenarios just you know
you want people to enjoy the art you create and you want people to be happy with the stuff that
you make and I think those are noble and fine but I just there's no reason to make a comic unless
you want to make a comic you do not have to rely on jail babe for your for your patreon you don't
have to rely on those comics to be to have a house over your head they are just purely nice and maybe
you want to make a career out of it and that's a different story but if you are having such a hard
time making a comic then we will probably see that in the result and I don't know if that's
necessarily something that just needs to happen you know well it's it's it's it's I don't know
whether it's that I don't want to work on it it's just that I find myself not you know I wake up
and then I watch youtube videos for a really long time and I just don't give myself a time
like um I mean I'm always like this even with things that I do like this is when schedules come
in handy because I actually also make comics and uh you know I also spend a lot of time on youtube
and I cut down by making schedules and adhering to it and punishing myself if I don't physically I
know Zen's a big schedule guy right like like with the cat and I entails no I hit myself I I think
yeah well no I mean I it's not I'm not Jesus Christ you by yourself yeah I just cut myself
with a claymore you cut yourself into pieces it's your last resort I decided to hang a literal
sort of Damocles above my head no but but seriously it's like night and day when you
apply a schedule and actually adhere to it and like make the effort to you know
follow the it's so hard for me to upstick to schedules though because no one's enforcing it
but me and I'm a oh yeah that's the thing tell us you I want to hear about zen's like enforcement
measures and what what how does that work for you what do you do with that what do I do well yeah
like if you fuck up what do you do okay so uh one is like the I do physical repercussions right
and then second of all uh there are things that I like right like um there are four can relate
they're like foods that I like or sometimes I'll I'll often go to the store to get candy and like
if I don't do something if I if I don't stop within like if I go like 20 minutes over right
right like I'm watching YouTube like two hours or something but I go two hours and 20 minutes
instead well I won't go to the store to buy the candy or I won't make myself that pizza you know
because it's like stuff like that that's and it's like the trouble the trouble there but yeah the
trouble there is you know finding something that you care about to the point that you know it's like
this is actually it'll actually motivate you to do yeah exactly what what I find I mean this could
just be maybe a lack of discipline on my part but I find that like actively trying to like just like
destroy yourself doesn't motivate me in the same way that it might for you I feel like everyone
gets motivated differently and and punishments don't work for me but what does work for me
is just removing as many options as possible so instead of punishing myself for doing something
bad I just will set up my life in a way where I can't do bad things and so it's not a question of
will or I want I and if I do something bad then I have to punish myself it's it's a matter of oh
there is no option here because either the easiest option is to do something that's beneficial to
me and productive or it's not the most easiest solution but it's the only solution that is
available to me for instance a perfect example right now I was fiddling around with my schedule
and and and my and my auto blocker that blocks various application on my computer and I messed
up so right now I'm recording my laptop right now and not on my desktop like I would because I
literally locked myself out of my desktop and I cannot access it anymore because I misclicked
and I literally like that's one of the functions I employ every single day as my computer will
auto turn off at various points in the day okay right it's like whenever I'm doing something like
essay or something like that I'll just turn off the wi-fi on my computer yeah man I tried that once
one time I tried like shutting my my internet off and it worked really well for getting me to do
stuff it yeah I mean it works really well until until you realize I mean when I'm drawing stuff
I'm like oh I need a reference I gotta turn it back on and then I forget to turn it off
oh it's always just a fucking nightmare like I I mean I tried the youtube challenge
the hashtag youtube challenge of like not watching youtube ever ever again and I completely failed
but you know and I'm back on I'm back on you know look at watching like multi hour videos every day
and I mean they're fun videos and they're sort of background videos and I can play a game at the
same time but I'm not working at like it's it's really just I'm wondering if that that whole thing
just ultimately doesn't work but what does work is you know a good thing that I'm doing is like
going along like getting getting the motivation like I was saying it it comes from a success it
doesn't even need to be like I put it out and people like it it's that I drew something good
and it's good so I'm motivated to to continue working on the thing getting started on anything new
is so difficult because you have to make the initial good thing like if I do a sketch or like
or if I think of like a really cool way of the story could go then it won't matter how much many
distractions are in front of me I will want to be doing the thing because it's so cool in my in my
head and I'm like I gotta do this at the moment though it's just sort of like I've got lots of
ideas that could be good but I don't know whether any of them are going to be good and I'm just
sort of like avoiding starting the only way to know is to try though which I'm sure you know
so like I've just been feeling stupid for a few days and I'm usually a few days is all it takes
for me to like finally be like no no more video games and then I try and it it works for me it
so often it just like it always it always gets preceded by me feeling like a depressed idiot for
a few you know I must have said this on the podcast before so please stop me if I if I repeat this
exact same line before but making a schedule is creating the perfect harness for yourself that
is not it does not cut too close to your skin you want to shear the sheep not to skin it so you
want to make it you want to make a harness around yourself that you know enables you to be productive
and direct you towards a path but also isn't too heavy that it makes you pissed off and want to
die and piss and shit that's true that's very true it's called it's all part of the setting
appropriate goals or setting realistic goals for yourself and if you say like just for example if
you are a new youtuber and you say uh just like you've never done it before I want to hit a million
subs by the end of the year like that goal is is purely unhelpful now it's so stupid because there
can be some things about that and people have done this before but you're setting your sights in the
wrong way you need to be way more specific and way more I don't know have a plan and I so I linked
a video setting fitness goals by my hero scooby 1961 he's got a whole okay this guy is my favorite
person in the world he taught me everything about fitness that I know but beyond that he is a he was
he is a successful retired engineer who is let's just say extremely financially secure
and uh he uh he retired at age like 50 or 60 or something just so he could he was doing his online
youtube stuff yeah he's this guy is he is one of my favorite people on the planet uh he's a hero
and by the way all yeah all his fitness tools he so he has made he like I said he's a software engineer
he makes many fitness tools he releases them for free to the public to be used by anyone
surely because he wants everyone to be able to benefit the way he has from fitness uh and to be
able to like you know work on their goals and stuff it like to anybody who follows this guy you
know what I'm talking about okay but specifically this video is part two of his of his series on
setting good fitness goals but it applies to any goal at all so everybody you should watch it
and the rest of the series because like setting goals in appropriately it's it's not just like I
was saying before there are many ways to gauge if a goal is good or bad there's an acronym I cannot
remember what it is right now it's like there's like four criteria and it's like measurable uh time
bounded uh like not doing too much there's like words for it but like all those should be frankly
if everyone's at work like optimally you should have those goals for like basically
everything you're doing in life absolutely no no I'm totally with you yeah like the word of the
day for me all the time is compartmentalization it's like yeah break it up into smaller more
consumable chunks for you to understand and then the ostensibly daunting task just becomes a cake
well not a cakewalk but you know you know something plausible that can actually be done by you
absolutely during during me a math of a two I had a big backlog excuse me building up of
things that I needed to do I simply couldn't do uh because I was too busy doing videos and stuff
and now now that it's done I've been going through them one by one checking them off I've got a I've
got a huge list of individual small tasks and I gotta say I don't know if everybody else feels
the same way it feels so fucking good to one by one put my big done sign next to each of those
tasks and soon I'm gonna have a big fucking list with nothing but guns and I'm gonna be an
accomplished heroic individual and I can't wait it's so exciting this is the not this is the
number one arc in my life that's giving me excitement and I can't wait to be done but
go back to your to your new comic and stuff like that again I would just say I mean I don't know
I don't even know if anyone else feels this way but again comics aren't what define you they aren't
they don't have to be you're like a new thing oh god hey everyone the hey everyone in the village
come over hippo crits doing comics now this is what he does now ha hey new comic please ha hippo
please new comic that's not what's happening right now you don't have to be be held into really
any standards I am in me and you are somewhat similar though you have a uh a different uh history
but like our incomes are not online really uh or yours you you have like a writing job that
assumably is like a job that sustains you correct uh yeah pretty much so you don't have to do anything
you don't have I know I I was thinking about this it nobody has to do anything nobody has to
die with with money that's not what I mean you can just you can just homestead your whole life
you can just go live in the woods the thing is I don't like I don't really care about um making
comics a career I would just like to have a few because I have some in my head well that's a great
reason to do it that's a great reason and I'm not saying don't do it I'm just saying like I know
what how it is to have people expect things from you and when it's your career you know you got to
do it but yeah like when you literally promise a comic four years you know that's you know it
could happen you can find yourself in that situation I mean I mean yeah I've done that exact same thing
and I mean I I haven't talked about explicitly for literal years because I I have not I've not
once brought it up in like a very very very long time because I'm not doing it duh I mean how could
you think I possibly still would be after all these years you'd have to be insane yikes well now they
know that they already mean now they know that's not a revelation yeah well I mean that's true anyway
I decided that I mean I don't have any want to do comics really the the thing that was animations
pathetic like I feel this this you know some sort of like kicking the butt of my of my own self
to get started on it rather than to just wait until I feel like it because that never really comes is
is just because I think it's nice to have something going on like it's it's nice to have a project
that I'm working on if I wasn't thinking of writing a new comic I would be doing nothing really
and aside from like the the writing thing which is like it's not insubstantial amount of work
and I do enjoy that as well but it feels very separate from like internet online things and I
know I don't have to make a comic I don't even think people are that interested in the next
comic I make maybe a few people are well you got to get us interested of course you know yeah I mean
I've got to get me interested in it that's that's indeed I don't say what I say to promote laziness
or to say like oh you know like don't worry about just you know you just don't try and do anything
that's obviously not what I'm trying to say yeah you are you know that's what I'm saying that's what
I'm telling you mom position uh which is fine which is a totally appropriate one but I'm advocating
the dad position uh human beings are beasts of burden and I very much believe that we do better
when we have tasks assigned to us so well it's totally it's totally well he has but but as he's
saying he's not that's not enough he's not satisfied if he didn't want to do it anymore
that's totally fine but I mean I would absolutely advocate that like you shouldn't just always I mean
I'm not saying Gibb thinks this but just in general like uh one shouldn't always like feel that when
there are things that you know raise obstacles and I know Mudgey isn't saying this either but
but just to state the general point when when obstacles arise and you feel uncomfortable
the answer isn't necessarily to shy away sometimes it can be to rise and overcome that fear we'd all
agree on points true north right we talked about that pretty much pretty much so uh so yeah so like
sometimes in Gibb's situation I based on what he said it seems like he does have at least a interest
in making comics so I would say you know whatever like try things power through etc find the solution
all that bullshit you know you know yeah so if you have ideas for a comic I would be more than
happy to see because because I like your so even if the idea is to make a comic like you did before
where it's just like you know just literally make it up as you go I because that's great that's that's
just like my problem is not uh no you go ahead I was gonna say if um if you have a couple ideas
and you don't know which one you want to do like you can always just start doing them and not post
them like if you want to just do like the first couple pages of each idea privately and be like
if this isn't clicking for me then you don't have to like risk starting it putting it out there and
then my my my brain is like not set on any of this exactly I bring it up because the the problem
at the moment is that I feel like I have no direction and no motivation and no passion for
anything and so the to try and make one of these things that I have ideas for will hopefully give
me a purpose and then I will continue doing that but but you know though Gibb it's it's interesting
because this is actually exactly I mean it sounds to me like you're a little bit down about the
Kickstarter which is totally understandable one of the things that Scooby says I mean you know
this is a very well said just this is where I heard it is like well like when you set yourself
with expectations that are too high and like frankly like you asked for more money for your
a pump Kickstarter uh and of course they get a more tangible thing of like the the thing
than like we even did with Radcon and I mean just doing the math that's like uh like with all of us
involved who are at Radcon we we were able to drum up a lot of money all our combined efforts
and for you to do it on your own to ask for I mean we made like 9,000 I'm not saying that's a
tall order I already be demoralizing if you don't reach a goal yeah you know I I did know going
into it that it would be a quite a big ask and I wasn't expecting it to do well obviously not
trying to be amazing I mean it's it's it's just the reality of like how much the thing costs to
make yeah like like you said on the thing like you're not out you're not trying to make money
like those just this is what it's this is what it's gonna cost to turn this thing into a physical
product which uh yeah I mean I was making t-shirts it would be easy but t-shirts aren't as cool
can I can I ask uh like what's like like how do you want to talk about like how you arrived at
the number like what's the arithmetic behind it uh I detail that in the Kickstarter description
uh okay yeah there's the there's the there's the base cost of like manufacturing the things and then
them sending it to me so it's delivery cost and manufacturing costs then uh it is uh the customs
import tax that I will be charged with once I receive it and then uh what else is it oh yeah
and then there's five percent Kickstarter fee on top of whatever the big number is right right and
shipping really fucked us with ride con three that was like a big expense I mean on on the Kickstarter
like you you input the thing and then you say where you're from and then that uh the amount that is
delivery cost I calculated how much it would cost to send something that that size and that
weight and uh it's about ten dollars for america so that's yeah ten ten bucks plus on top of however
much it is divided by 150 uh and then that's how I came to the thing so it's like uh yeah I could
I could like I was thinking like I know this is not like literally allowed in Kickstarter
but I was like thinking if it gets pretty close but it's like a couple hundred uh just off you know
off the mark I was considering just like paying through some account for the rest of it yeah
yeah you can do that well what what is Kickstarter gonna gonna get mad that you contributed more
money to the campaign that they skim off the top of no yeah I don't know but um yeah I don't know
if there's a rule I'm not I'm not really down for like putting like more than half which is where it
is at the moment yeah yeah for sure for sure that's a big chunk of change I I I just want to say
just at the end here just say the reason I say all that I say is simply that to say don't make
shit art just because you feel like you have to because I don't want to read bad things so don't
make a bad thing they don't want to oh no I feel that and there yeah okay it's just like you were
saying I you don't really feel motivation and a lot of time I don't feel motivation too until like
it's a really an opportune time to have motivation because I can't write down the idea and I forget
it like you know when I'm I'm in bed or in a shower so I always have a notepad next to me you
know so it's like I can write it down and this isn't necessarily to you because this might not
be the case to you but so I'm just talking in general so it's like yeah I just always have
something that you can write something down on even if you're sleepy and it's like you have to
you sort of have to um what's what's the word not domesticate uh you have to uh uh discipline
yourself to to do it you have to be really tired you'll be like uh it's a good idea but I don't
want to write it out you have to do it you just have to do it I have definitely ruined my sleep
when I had sort of a cool idea and I was like I gotta I gotta write that down I turned my phone on
the light blinds me and then I have no eyeballs but then I type it down in like a google doc
that's literally how I made my first youtube video yeah it was like it was like 12 o'clock
in the morning and I stayed up for seven hours because I never edited before and I made a video
okay this is this is how much joy in the square feels me with every single day of my life this is
how much like creative juices are flowing when I work on that shit because every single day I'll
code a little bit and then I'll write a little bit and then I'll get into bed and then I'll think
myself oh dude what if like just to myself over and over again like dude what if just like just
constantly thinking of ideas and then it gets a brilliant point where I think I gotta write all
this down and I just I just get on like a google doc for like five hours make a ton of shit yeah
feels so good feels great that's great you know what felt that I had like a big like typing of a
type storm the other day did you made his video like why I play games and I was like oh dude I love
thinking about that I love like um thinking about why I like things and so I try to figure out why I
like playing games and I typed in a notepad document like for like 20 minutes straight like
as in like that my my fingers were not leaving the keyboard to think I was just like so much
info is like getting like put to paper and it felt great uh but it was like spelling errors and
like really disorganizes like good thing I'm not a youtuber anymore because this would be a nightmare
to like go through and make into something presentable there there are days where writing
feels so fucking hard for me but then the days just like spontaneously having words just words
flow from your fingers ah oh yeah that was me last night I started writing a script like in bed on
my phone for a video and it was like three pages worth of stuff just on a tiny little phone screen
and like why am I still going I should be sleeping right now it's weird when it just like hits you
hey hey hey ben I've got a request for you what I got a request that I've been thinking about like
for like like a month now sorry I was I was just I was just thinking about the shiny teeth song
from fairly odd parents and I was and I and I almost started crying uh but go on
just like a christmas tree uh chip skylark just like the stars in space do you know that he was
voiced by one of the members of in sync I'm really uh yeah yeah that doesn't shock me joey
something I think joey trubion joey salads yeah that sounds right is that a real person yeah yeah
yeah he's a youtuber well he's a youtuber okay so not his real name is uh joey saladino but uh
joey salads i like salads i like salads youtubers aren't real people but anyway what munchie what I
I've been thinking about this I want you to make a shirt ben I want you to make a shirt
of wanting to make a vapor shirt hey I can do that all right here's what I want it's you know
there was a vapor there was a vapor shirt it was available through print all over me and it was
a disaster really all over me is a nightmare yeah it was like the it was the cover like the entire
shirt was an all over print of the cover of the first one but print all over me just fucked it up
and like I saw one I saw one that was made there were like like three people bought them and I saw
one in real life and I was like I regret it so bad I feel so sorry for everyone who bought one
he just thought of the shirts and he almost cried I I want you it's very specific I want you okay
okay I want you to take the it's vapor you churl that panel put it on t-shirt but specifically
remove the white from it so it's just the black outline so we're gonna put on an off white like
beige t-shirt and then I'll buy it that sounds awful no it sounds great does it not not like
like like oh like oh like oh like a cardboard a little bit of a cardboard color hey benny boy
want to make yourself what like 750 yeah literally I get to edit it I would love 750
okay well I'll get on it thanks right after we're right after we make that um
pokemon podcast side channel we you oh yes wait you haven't made it yet who's we
no I haven't made it yet I said last week I was gonna make it and I didn't yeah well
you know well I like I started I started thinking about the shiny teeth song and
shall we head to voicemailings that's how I think it's time I think it's time all right
ladies and gentlemen speak pipe link below leave us some voicemail messages and we they're good
we will play them so let's see we all they all they all know that they can be bad and still get
played they all know it Nate no no no no no no no that's a rumor there's no evidence
before we start voicemails I want to I want to point out something funny about the voicemails
in a medicine I went to speak pipe the website a couple days ago because I wanted to start a
speak pipe to help with the community show that I want to do for my patreon the free plan doesn't
exist anymore I have no idea how we're out paying for the money wait what doesn't exist anymore the
free plan for speak pipe doesn't exist anymore it's only on the wire lads so I have no idea how
they're not charging us for this yet but uh there you go yeah you know the weird thing is when with
speak pipe there is a limit to the number of voices I think it was like like 50 or something
it's like 50 a month and we do way past that and they've never charged us yeah we haven't
been charged is there is there someone is there someone else is getting charged and they just
don't know what's going on I hope so we're by the way I know exactly what number we're up to or
okay we like the messages we're up to we're up to we've had over 1068 before this meeting we had
exactly 1068 messages that was the last one before I started uh get the voicemails this time
fascinating fascinating 999 and uh the shit ones that were not played ever no no no okay look guys
this whole meme of lack of quality it's it's a lie and I'm gonna prove it to you right now
we've got a voicemail from my hero he's called you know you know it's fucking true let's let's let's
give him a chance to clear the floor here we go is this quality women back back at it again
no not yet let's let's go go hey um do you ever feel like straight guys who haven't at least
tried to suck a cock are um just fucking cowards
that's the whole voicemail I tell you that's the whole voicemail the fact that you are the only
person laughing it's true they are cowards it is absolutely cowardice I'm so with this guy
it's cowardice I've tried to suck my own sexuality's on a spectrum it's try to suck your own in the
abstract like like legitimately like sucking dick like isn't like actually the worst thing that could
happen to someone like in the abstract like sucking a cock I could probably do it it wouldn't be that
bad honestly sure uh well I mean that's true it wouldn't be like a painful experience might be
unpleasant I would rather I would rather enjoy a delicious meal with friends well I mean it's the
rest of it for me the only reason the only reason I wouldn't suck a dick is because I wouldn't want
to give the person the satisfaction sure like if it was just a floating dick with no person attached
like yeah sure why not yeah okay who won't tell who tell tales of your of your back room antics
you know I want a little privacy in my interaction I don't know I really don't have to be convinced it
genuinely does not strike me is like that bad like yeah like whatever I just suck a dick it's not
into the world sure that's fucking gay yes it is I guess it's like I guess the implication is like
oh what do you do with your with yourself and like your sexual identity after that are you gay now
but not yeah yeah it's just someone's like finger but it has a dick on it why would you put someone's
finger you know I feel like that's even worse uh I'm gonna give everyone look I think look we give
women a pass for like messing around with other women like in college that's like a meme I'm I'm
officially going on the record I'm giving guys one gay sex pass if you want to try it out to see how
it goes and then afterward you say that like it wasn't for me you're very you're very pro this
position am I if I want to assume you've already used your one slot is that why I'm just really
glad that the arbiter of gay experiences has given us one gay pass thank you Nick thank you
I have had no gay experiences we've got to lay down the law we've got to set down many raise an eyebrow
at my devout love of the male form and that's on them that's not on me um but okay let's let's go to
our next one this one's called uh I miss I miss quality women I want quality women don't work
no no no don't work yes choice words for me specifically if you're listening okay hopefully
Nate has picked that voicemail to play you better we can say but right now we've got a message from
holy shit banjo kazoo okay I wonder what this may be about let's let's go hello it's me the average
switch owner a 15 to 22 year old young adult who uh really likes the switch and can take it anywhere
wow breath of the wild was such a great game fire on them is for gay weaboos
his voicemails just get worse and worse we need to have a conversation about this
I love how everybody's just so unimpressed
we get piano playing every single episode it gets old there's always someone with a grandmaster
piano trying to show us that he's cool you're not nobody's always a grandmaster pianist trying to
impress us with his voicemail you're a fucking grandmaster pianist oh there you go hey thanks for
that buddy next okay next I do appreciate the piano stuff but there's not there's not much to say
about it other than it was cool that's the thing I'm always impressed by you know decent even decent
level music uh playing oh yeah how about this that's the good shit at easily decent next voicemail
I can't quite not make it the name uh it's uh quality women returns here you go play and go I love him
what's up guys it's your boy quality women here back at it again the voice grail contestant
voicemail can I get a one in the chef quality women no can I get a one in the job no no okay so
I'm calling back just uh okay just a little update here set to explain myself so uh my highly
controversial voicemail yeah I'm saying that only eight out of ten and above women are uh okay that
was that was bullshit that was a stupid thing I think what I what I meant what I really meant
to say which is actually could be even more offensive and uh oh oh oh munchie oh munchie
you're gonna get offended you're gonna whitenight me a little bitch here we go okay so I think what I
meant what I meant to say what I really was feeling inside is uh I I can I can fucking
tolerate an eight out of ten or above I can tolerate your craziness more because it's like
oh because you're it's like you're fucking hotter you know it's like why should bitch I'm not going
to tolerate your craziness if you're below eight dog just walked in you know I'm saying like if
you're an eight and below like your dog why would I tolerate your fucking craziness if you're a 10
you know you could tolerate a 10 out of 10s craziness more because they're fucking wicked hot
you know so I think uh I think that's what I really know is this more we're not fucking anymore
she uh he kind of hates me now she said she was thinking of never talking to me again good yeah
she's seeing a therapist now and uh yeah we're just kind of we haven't fucked in like two or three weeks
so well great oh let's hear it let's hear it wait is is this the guy who was like uh he was
breaking up but he was still seeing this person yeah he was so dumb so dumb okay okay incredible
let's talk let's talk about this yeah please well I I do understand I understand the eight out of 10
thing I don't agree with it sure but it makes a little more sense to me comment on this been king
of fives that was that was a time in history he's learned and grown yeah okay five out of five
right I like the end of the story being punctuated by like oh yeah this person like hates me she's
gonna go see therapy for what I've done to her like he didn't say from what he's done oh okay okay
fair that's definitely mixed grappling but it's funny to assume that so I will do it anyway
that's smart that's wise that's wise uh I mean frankly it doesn't sound like our boy has learned
to say the least it does seem that things are despite his best efforts improving because he's
not with this person anymore and it's going to be phased out so that's good I'm glad to hear that
proud of him oh proud of work on proud of your boy that is not more controversial than this last
statement come on no all right the saga the saga concludes okay yeah so thanks for that quality
women here is a little voicemail from uh Jerry uh late honest love him love Jerry my favorite hey guys
so I know that whole Nate's girl is retarded thing is really funny yeah but I think that guy who
left the voicemail was onto something he was trying to expose a secret darker side of the man who
refers to himself as the best guy ever and I have some damning evidence spoken from his own mouth oh no
this is a clip from pcp episode 47 at one hour 51 minutes and 41 seconds he's got receipts take a listen
so why don't they why doesn't society allow me to play with retarded people yes I want to have
sexual retarded people I think that this is enough the show is clearly one of Nate's many
it's been nice knowing you he got you oh all right dude my last exactly to finish out this podcast
before I go to it the police are outside you are right now they ban you your last wish it's okay
though I believe I they've got your last meal it's a bottle of fuel I like to imagine like you know
there's always like the dignified deaths in tv shows where it's like an assassin's come and it's
just like grant me one last wish and the assassin's like of course and yours is just like let me finish
this episode of the pcp let me record one more podcast there's a gun pressed against my head
right now they're just waiting for the end to pull the trigger so well you know I thank you
officer you're doing a great job it's Michelle holding the gun against you she's trying to get
it might be Michelle dressed up um yeah well okay all right that's that's very damning uh I admit
to everything you've heard is true everything everything even the lines those are true too
all right here's uh the biggest virgin ever uh how exciting here you go it's your parallel
hey pcp in one episode it was said that oneitis is the deadliest disease known to man
I was wondering if I could get some advice on how to deal with my oneitis I'm going to call this
girl Karen I asked Karen out in high school she said she just wanted to be friends and I accepted
this and moved on I started a thing with another girl and that fell through really hard Karen helped
me recover because she is my friend and we started hanging out a lot but I ended up becoming obsessed
with Karen I think that this has caused me to no no longer see other girls as attractive or
interesting I recognize I had a problem in college and tried separating entirely from Karen twice
the both times even if you're not communicating for months the first time and years the second time
she tried to get back into my life and I allowed it because I figured I could handle it but I still
can't help but think about her every single day unfortunately trying to separate again is not an
option for me anymore because she joined a discord server that is pretty much all of my friends in
it oh he's he's locked in now boys he can't escape she's in the discord server anyway I communicate
with my friends if I were to try and fuck out of here dude that would mean leaving the server and
losing contact with that entire group of people which I am not willing to message them I feel that I
really need to get over this make another discord actually been dating this one guy since we graduated
high school so about five years I've never met him but I heard he was in his late 30s so his biological
clock is going to tell him to get married soon and I just don't think I can handle hearing that she
is getting married so that's my confusion okay I'm a 23 year old virgin with oneitis and I need
some advice on how to do I have thank you girl I know exactly well from what you know you know what
you know you know what I was kind of on board with it I was like yes oh well you can't help how you
feel I guess until you got to the part about how like she came back into his life and then I was
like this this girl is a fuck this is that's like some that's a little manipulative I think that's a
little bit well wait well hang on I mean I mean tell me if you think I'm wrong but my take is that
maybe that's true but he also might just be framing it that way like sure did she really
armrest her her way into his life despite I guess I guess we don't know yeah I mean it's it's the
fault I don't know if it's a fault of hers because if she if this if he's being her friend and she
misses her friend then I guess that's like not a bad thing on her part I think maybe she should be
more sensitive the fact that she knows there's more feelings there on his end but it's not this
really I just realized something I think I've just realized that we can only take this from his
perspective and if we actually want to understand like the best way forward for either of these people
we would need to get her perspective as well but since we don't have that anything we speculate
maybe completely off the mark and that's why we're not you know this isn't marriage that's why we
can't actually tell you how to do it it's just fun fun hypotheticals to to chew on so like if someone
does find themselves in the situation in which we happen to talk about they know the correct answer
because we're always right I suppose that's right that's right for this particular person like what
we say may not be the right thing okay okay that is true here's the thing I don't know okay maybe
this is cruel but I don't know if I can even have pity anymore if you've been jonesen for this girl
who's been with another guy for five years five years yeah are you fucking kidding me
look look okay I don't want to be like overly mean to this guy or anything but but okay frankly I'm
sensing a bunch of issues one I'm sensing generally low self-esteem and that's fine it's not like a
problem but like obviously if you could have got honestly guys maybe I'm crazy but like I really think
99.9% of guys issue with women is that there's one girl and they like that and they can't see
themselves being successful with any other woman like do you think Genghis Khan ever had
fucking one night is for anyone woman would he had you know like thousands available to him at any
time the answer is no the answer is if a man has a if a man has two women that would make themselves
available and one says I'm you know I'm not gonna do it he will say buh-bye and immediately plow into
the other one like light speed he'll be in there it's an impregnation um and so where is the light
where's the light I mean I want to be nice to this guy because I like to give helpful advice
dude I think your problem I mean that you yeah yeah you want to say something if you just cut in
I don't know how many how how many different ways can you say it's fucking get over it
like it's obviously not doing anything it's not even get over it you have to you have to cut
this person out of your life and keep it that yeah I want to put it in terms of actually
guys it's pretty it's pretty simple he's he's he's a coward because he hasn't tried sucking dick before
so consider consider it wrong you ain't wrong you know it's not gay yeah you know what you know
what just go to the guy that she's with and suck his dick and then make him gay and then oh my god
oh then she'll be available and then you can go any think about it yeah but then he'll be gay too
so he won't want her anymore no you can buy buy you can you can you can do that no that's a myth
you okay I mean yeah like Ben was saying obviously the the solution here is you got look
five years dude like what has it been like a relationship we're like oh my god they've been
on and off again these two like oh maybe there's a chance for me everything there's not a step in
this equation is you limiting yourself and being un like un healthily fixated on one woman every man
in the world is better off if you just accept the reality that like there are more than one
okay so this guy was saying like it's affected his ability to even be into other women okay here's
here's your here's your prescription this is dr. Nate's prescription I demand that you go and in some
capacity some social capacity whatever you just do an exercise doesn't involve it's just in your own
head think about the women around you and like are there any redeeming quality about what any of the
women around you chopped up in pieces in your refrigerator like yeah I'm just just a thought
experiment just a thought it's possible that anything decent could theoretically come from
like a dating or just fucking or whatever like relationship with any other woman and I the
answer you'll inevitably arrive at is yes you know what there are actually other girls that are nice
and might you know bring something nice to my life I'm sure I'm sure on some level he understands
that right and like of course yeah so like there seems to be some sort of mental block that's going
out so I think that what he needs to do is literally just pound a pavement go in there and
actually meet the women and see it firsthand this man needs a hardcore dose of of pickup
artistry he needs to go out literally talk to this is the cure for most men's low self-esteem
go out and talk to 100 girls just go do it have a checklist check off 100 and by the time you're
done you will no longer give a shit because the thing is 99% of men give up before they reach
that number if you do it you will you won't care anymore and you'll be over it now you'll probably
meet a girl who's nice no I agree the guy just the guy just you know you you're a guy you get like
this you get in the you just lack perspective you just gotta shake himself out of it that's the
problem the thing is he was asking about like what do I do about my discord friends oh I forgot
about that like join me make another one right I don't think you know I don't think you have to
do anything like the problem is not the discord the problem is that you lack the perspective
the fact that you see this girl in the discord server still like it fucks you up to the extent
that you have to fucking ask us for what to do about it well that that's true that that's true but
on all right well maybe maybe then you leave the discord and in that time use that lack of
distraction to try and sort yourself out and then you can go back and then you won't care I mean
because this like that's like this is where you totally lose me dude you're like crying about how
you need this discord server it's like the only revenue yeah like I get it I guess that your friends
are there I get that you like these people and this man has a lack of creative lack of creative
thinking because there are other ways you can be in contact like no no no no other social media
other social media I think it download Skype or whatever I don't think you're an idiot if we
did that none of us would talk if we still if I got downloaded Skype right now I would never talk
to any of you again okay what okay Skype Skype wasn't a joke but like I don't know like Twitter
your friends are on there no I don't know make another discord like what's it just make another
okay that's the real answer make another yeah yeah make another discord okay well I don't think it's
that crazy to say that like oh well this is where all my people are at like like that's a thing like
yeah you if you might okay I mean like limit your interaction with them if you I mean that
take up another venue the only problem to that problem no but the thing is I understand the
solution I think the solution is that you gotta fucking get over your shit so that the presence
of this person isn't like ruining your life long term that's absolutely correct but like I at the
very least I want to get look I'm sorry I'm not really trying to be mean to this guy I don't even
really find it funny or really want to but it's like to give him a tangible I want to give him
small steps because ultimately like yes you shouldn't care like long term yes that's the
place to be but in the meantime I understand that this does bug you and obviously he says like
ah if they get married I'll be really really upset like okay that's fine I believe you what if they
get married it'll be the same I mean he should he should already be as upset as he needs to get
you know what I mean they've been together five years exactly exactly there's no like that would
just be the status quo continues okay you just okay look can we all agree look five I have a
little discord server with like four people in it and they're my best buddies from college
like is it really that crazy an idea to just make a server like even if you like I understand
if you're trying to make a parallel server it'll be weird because like oh now they have to like
pick a side like which server are they gonna be like in mainly don't don't even make it that
complicated just bring in like the people who you really got to talk to like what is there like
50 of those people no you probably got like five maybe like 10 maybe less I don't know make a server
just with those people and talk to them through that and leave the server with everybody or if
you don't want to leave it whatever like mute it check it rarely like avoid the girl you should
probably leave it though you can come back later if you know I understand the only thing I could
have I wish that he had the mental capacity to just get over and not have to like completely
remove this person from his life because they were friends originally well of course so that's
this is the nature of the beast some relationship dude just do something but respect her agency
it's been five years dude well yeah but she's been such a tease she came back into her life you see
she came back into his life how could she yeah like again not trying to show any dude but like
come on but listen to that you sound a little bit a little silly because you're yeah you're
fucking okay anyway quick fucking up speaking of fucking up our next voicemail is from a hero
named simply insertion let's see what he's got right here should I hope go anime is a Japanese
colloquialism about smoking dang wait I got him by my calculations I should be sent to the boys
jail but with his fucking mongoloids don't understand this how much shit I have shoved up
my ass I got fucking cigarettes razor blades his plastic spoons dildos works I got so much
shit in there I can't fucking see straight man everyone in the voice jail I'm coming for you
you know you know I would go right into his trap mind you I would send him to the voice
jail but he did say a funny munchie meme from the donation lecture where I said I'm gonna
I'm gonna shove my dick so far up your ass you won't be able to even see anymore so I you know
what voice voice grail for me no voice grail if it's not much if voicemail is shit it doesn't
matter if it's like deliberately shit it's still shit into the jail agree I say yeah he'll make a
mince but you know it's no skin off our back he's got he's got all the illicit materials he'll be
selling to a little let me see who's in the jail the Japanese man Utah and oopsie bobo see the
thing is he thinks he's going to a jail where he can you know use his tools in his ass to break
out but what he doesn't know is that the door you open the door and then you fall straight into a pit
of like fiery snakes and they will eat you and you will be dead instantly and you can't wait a minute
is the pcb jail canonically in the same location as bail jpe perhaps there's fiery snakes around
oh you know it's true you know it dog damn that's some rich ass lore
I mean that is a jail that it like that is yeah it's a jail I you know what I let's make a canon
canon he did it you did the canon that's that's what it takes you slap the table it's can
we'll have to figure out where the voicemail grail is get a pump plush everybody and have a part of
pcp history yeah indeed if you fucking dare if you go in the voice gel you have to buy like 10 plushes
indeed okay well or maybe that's the cost to buy your weight by your freedom is to buy like 10
plushes we should make like a pcp city it's like washington dc where it has like monuments to all
of us and there will be endless war which would be the actual mon Washington monument yeah Nate
you're gonna have Washington DCP you're gonna you're gonna have like a like a like a Lincoln
monument or something Nate you know guys let's watch something out did you did you and I were
getting really hyped up on city planning a while back like like like eight eight months ago let's
bring it permission let's make it let's make pcp city and then we can have all these occasions have
like warp like trans like trans portalizers so you can go to like the gib and take area you
know if you insert a secret code into the text channel is this like in real life in real life
the secret codes yeah okay okay that sounds good we'll buy a floating island of the coast of
Bangladesh or whatever well there's like free farmland in Oklahoma so we should just go there
and then like set up like like like like a disney world-esque functioning city
that sounds okay all right all right green light up yeah think think about it green light it
uh let's we'll launch the Kickstarter short link link below uh okay next voicemail is from
Annie Fred uh okay go no this guy no did you I wanted to ask you your opinions on Nate's recent
comments about you um frankly I was disgusted oh yeah um and it's pretty shocking I mean
how are you guys gonna sew up your relationship I mean surely it's over at this point I mean
Nate I mean I got receipts from the outside line um you owe digi an apology frankly
I owe that man nothing he owes me everything okay okay okay let me get a low den I mean
in your words did you all right oh god he's still going oh what oh god okay that's the last part
yeah I did too I don't I don't know I don't know what he said okay okay okay Annie Fred is the
antithesis as I think he said fuck digi I believe is what he said he's the antithesis of me of me
aka the average pcp fan so Annie Fred like is emblematic like if you were to take every pcp fan
and put them into like a big like like melting vat and just stirred them all together you would get
Annie Fred he is the literal embodiment of what it means to be a pcp fan he comes in to the rck
discord meetup he comes in with his anime avatar I make fun of his avatar and and and then and then
he changes it facetiously to a shit avatar to make fun of me when really he should be the one
that's made fun of for his shit anime avatar listen I'm not gonna forgive you just goes you oh right
the wrong facetiously I'll kill you I'll kill you Annie Fred you're dead statistically well what was
this yeah what was the drama that's being discussed is in the um uh the mea math of a two
film festival uh one person uh in their video did they made some like a criticism of digi uh
and in my in my feedback in the notes I just put a haha yeah hashtag fuck digi and I stand by it to
this day and I do not apologize and I do not backtrack uh and I'd say it to his face if he was here
fuck you digi hi it's me digi bro oh man I know I take it back I have nothing bad to say about
you buddy uh hey hey we can't find the my plot to go all across the sands hey
it's me digi bro dude I thought that was digi bro yeah you know what you know what me too dude I
okay I become like the digi head defender I've become like the ultimate digi head yeah listen I
was saying that I was saying that all PCB fans are dumb digi head head defender no one goes to
back literally has made heads like are like vile they're all debauchers they're all impotent
welps I fucking hate them all every native head is sin every native head is lepers every native
head would crucify christ if they had the chance literally all of them
say we need ironically all of them have anime avatars all of all of them say jokes oh I hate them
all oh god how could they it's a good 90 percent I gotta say all right but we gotta we gotta brace
ourselves uh for a real a real special caller next up because we've got the wacky wavy inflatable
two band with his message a hashtag all voicemails matter no okay strap in let's let's let's go
keep
I see how it is I could I could see that voicemail I could see the waveform in my eyes
I'm sorry I'm laughing I'm sorry I'm sorry people love my goofy jokes
we shouldn't we shouldn't encourage this they respect me they appreciate my eclectic taste
in voicemail comedy god damn it and I'm standing by what the people want I'm with the wacky
wavy inflatable arm flailing two man you know what wacky wavy inflatable two man you know what I
I should be cursing you, but you know what I had to preach you know a master's
represent masters and you know what I that's right God look my my my my
experience with that was completely binary I was like this is garbage
that was the best voicemail today God you know all right there's some there was
something about like the extent to which that effect was applied like it was a
little way too much which made it sort of kind of good exactly exactly I mean I
don't know if we heard some more of the saga of the wacky it was it was it was
PCB bonus episode ASMR core that was what I liked about is just that like it was so
like the visualization of it is just this man like it's so extreme that I
could not possibly imagine like what this man were to look like and how he would
be recording to a microphone like it like you'd be moving away so fast it
would be like a single frame he's on screen than a single frame he's not just
over and over again oh what a hero thank you so much if you there's more into
this song that honor there's always space on the grail for a man such as well
okay all right well let's not go that far let's not go that far this guy this guy
is going to jail okay he's going straight to jail
we've got one time not just like South America or something yeah basically the
same thing but we got one final message and this is from of course our old buddy
the I'll die corporation voicemail bot today on true
oppression no more no more soccer for us this dumb these now this is good this
let's hear what he has to say about oppression okay go booting up I'll die
corporation voicemail bot okay I'm ready through an objective analysis of all
social issues spanning the entirety of the globe I have rightfully calculated
that the most depressed minority in the world is foot fetishists the most common
through line in all discourse is the insistence on such a fetish being the
lowest of flow could it be because of the sweaty odor calculation saying while
the foot can often be sweaty few areas of the body perspired more than the
genitals which are nearly universally acclaimed as areas of high sexual value
how about it's association with unclean substances such as dirt again this is
found wanting genitals are most strongly associated with producing human waste
product oh my god that is far from being described as clean perhaps it could be a
fear of transmitting disease alas it cannot be so virtually all forms of
physical sex are prone to promoting the transmission of disease yet this does
not deter humans from performing such actions in conclusion my calculations
have assessed that the reason foot fetishists are so looked down upon must
be a jealous explain to anybody involved with its creation especially the
moderator of the aisle die corporation voicemail bot alright this no the facts
are in game I know the fact is you're a degenerate foot they framed it shit this
voicemail bot framed it in the wrong way people don't look down on foot
fetishes because you it's stinky they look down on it because they don't get
it I mean they like because they literally look down on it I don't think
foot fetishes are like that maligned because people like as a joke will just
put their feet like yeah sure look at it like because they don't feel anything
they don't feel like they're being slutty by showing but on the other end
people will be like oh feet like it's it's just sort of like like I don't I
don't I don't buy the the foot fetishists are maligned I don't see that all the
time yeah there's there's definitely a good people don't get beat up for
liking foot feet so oppressed they can't even be public about their love of
feet it's it's a damn okay but like horrible that's like the case for a lot
of kinks like most of them yeah I feel like feet feet are like like that's the
more on the vanilla scale more on the vanilla side of like fetishes that you
can't say that you have well okay did you see that famous king of the hill
episode where Peggy with her famously massive feet was contracted to be a quote
unquote model and then they had her doing some very odd foot positioning and
it turns out it was for a foot fetish website and when she found this out she
was deeply disturbed and you know that people would be a quacking it to her
old big old knockers of the foot variety and I get it I get it would you get it
what point did you even make with that I agree that I did it fetish people
to be put on a pedestal the exact reverse of everything that's happening now
they should be completely like a pedestal like on a on a gallows before you pull
the switch and they all you know fall through but I just agree with the
statement that they are the most for I think my friend George Washington tune
fetishist we'll have a problem with that as he is of the variety that tune
fetishists are the most marginalized group in society so what's a tune fetishist
somebody likes the Simpsons no yeah well exactly someone like like who likes
over stylized like overly cartoony like no anatomy no representation of the
human anatomy whatsoever like like you know like just pure like bending for
example just pure undultrated lines on a page that don't represent humans but
think they have like so they're adults can't help but like them yeah that's it
that's all I think you I think you George Washington tune fetishist will be
good friends yeah that's my that's my new friend I talked about I checked out
on a really long time ago people will know good man all right well that's it
that's our last question was steeped in comedy I was trying to be serious and I
couldn't I couldn't tell if anyone else was serious I was being serious I was
being serious on the fact that's like why why why foot fetish like that's not
the worst fetish okay okay being completely serious but it's not that
it's the worst fetish it's that the people who have it are the most they're
numerous they're numerous and like you never see him coming and like they're
sneaky and they're weird no okay I don't I don't get I speak seriously there's a
lot of people who like make fun of foot fetish like that's a go-to make fun of
for a lot of right guys how can you think it's not a joke it's not a joke it's
not it's not it's not obviously the they're not the most oppressed minority
god damn it but that's what the voicemail if you fucking shut the fuck up
and die I mean you're changing the topic to be the most oppressed fetish okay
fine no why are you fucking listen why don't you we're we're having a
conversation keep up think about it I'll put shoes on my feet and I will keep
up I'll keep all the fetishes away I don't want them looking at all the same
way I feel about like people saying that ginger people are like really oppressed
XD nobody have no souls it's just like I don't know it's not even that funny
that's why it's a noisy so much because it's not even that funny to say all
these things that aren't even that particularly true making fun of people
who have diaper fetishes now that's funny because that's clearly very strange
and haha clearly I guess so I mean I have no substantive argument to make
against foot fetishists I suppose other than yeah I mean the bot pretty much
I've got no ammo in the chamber fetishes are all by their nature just really weird so
like you know keep it in the bedroom you're not hurting anybody cool cool
beans indeed my knee trick reaction will be to make fun of them but like the
knee trick reaction isn't always the best reaction so it's like you're not
allowed to show your feet on twitch under any circumstances because yeah
because okay I mean I've heard this from multiple sources I could have been lied
to by multiple I heard you're not allowed to show your feet on twitch
because it is porn to do that I mean that that you know a slightly different
example but like just like now these days you are not allowed YouTube changes
policy you're not allowed to comment on perfectly innocuous videos of minors a
lot of the time because some people like perceive them you know like sexually or
whatever and yeah that's pretty weird that's a odd stance to take I mean I
get it I think we're kind of throwing out the baby with the bathwater
saying oh yeah I love videos of babies being thrown out with
that's my go-to epic that epic baby and bathwater prank 2019
gone sexual gone sexual all right that's it everybody no more fun fun's over for
the day that was the last one that was the last one
oh my give us your voicemails people keep them coming these are all good do more
stuff be be like my hero the wacky wavy inflatable tube man he's really the MVP
of these voicemails in my humble opinion hashtag all right patreon.com
slash the pot no wait no $5 people 26 bonus episodes and I think by the time
you hear this if I remember correctly I think the next you know in three days
there will be of another bonus episode that'll be the 27th and won't that be a
fun surprise so give us your money now so you'll be ready for it when it comes
out what else you got join the discord for $1 and you'll be in our patron
discord lots of fun times had and actually get the very excellent TPC feed
that only exists currently in the fucking discord it's this wonderful feed
that just shows all of our releases whenever they come out it's actually a
an undervalued but really great feature of the discord that was made by Dane I
think that's Jack that's right thanks buddy coders oh that's right that's
right he changed his name yes syy of relief covert ops here he comes all right
well thanks for being here everybody we'll see you next week more voicemails
more money more fun that's the PC yeah we'll see you next week everybody all
right
you