Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. We're here to talk about all the cool things that you like. I'm the best guy ever. Jesse Wood is here.
Hey, hey, everypony.
Digibro is also here.
Uh, sup medic, fuck my ass.
Ben Saint's there.
Patreon.com slash BenSaintSaintComics.com. It's a meme now.
It's a meme. Everyone give him money. Hippocrit's over there.
It's, um, I sure am.
Tommy Oliver's in the his house.
Yeah.
And Davoo is nice as a mouse.
Square of disease? What square of disease?
Yo, I got 500 houses. I got 500 houses and 500 mouses.
And today's topic is, and everybody join in, those fucking normies.
Reeeee!
All right, we're gonna talk about how much we hate fucking normies now. They all need to fucking burn in Auschwitz
We need to reopen Auschwitz and rename it normie Auschwitz, so they all fucking
Get out it all belong in the norm switch
Call it norm schwitz. Yeah, let's define what we mean by a normie. Okay. Hang on. They're gonna urban dictionary
I'm bringing this back
After I just made the greatest pun of all time and you deliberately ignored it until you can make your worst pun guy
I I just make it again. I said call it get out schwitz
That's a good one
I'm gonna get out of this
Urban dictionary right now because you've offended me greatly. Well, we'll be sorry to miss you. Yo, my infuror
I give that a nine out of ten
Okay, I don't even know what that means. Normie, a person who does not have a mental illness such as bipolar disorder
Schizophrenia mood disorders PTSD depression or any other similar mental disability wait
Wait, wait a reference to those who are a part of the mainstream culture the 97% of the population who doesn't have a mental illness
Okay, fuck urban dictionary. That's really a fucking normie. I didn't know what that was about. That's a normie definition if ever there was one
That's exactly right. This is a normative definition of normie and I don't appreciate the
Demonstricizing those fucking colonists fucking assholes because we don't identify with their their fucking identity politics over here on this fucking website
Fuck them there. They're they're on my shit list. Urban dictionary is dead. Let me let me make a let me make a thing here
My one of my favorite mangas ever Watamote. I mean, I forget what the word they use in Japanese
But the the main character in the English translation is always railing against normal fags
She has normal fags. Yes, because yeah, you know what the Japanese word is guy
There's a specific Japanese word for a person who lives a normal life. I mean no guys. It's just a foreigner
I don't know because white people are normal
And I'm gonna Google this I'm gonna come I'm gonna you guys continue the conversation
I'm gonna button and completely disrupt the flow and I find out what that's fine
But we can talk about what a motive cuz what a motive is the perfect example of what we're talking about because because fuck
I forget her name. What's her name?
Koko Riko no Tomoko Tomoko, right Tomoko is is is the greatest human being who's ever lived
Right, you just have to read her story to understand why everyone else is a fucking piece of shit
Who doesn't deserve to be in her companionship and all these all these psychosis psychotic breaks from reality
Are just her escaping to a higher plane which she has the ability to do because she's superior to everybody else
Okay, okay, I googled it and it looks like the phrase is Ria Jew which means people whose real life is fulfilled
Jew means Ria Jew. Okay, Jew. I think it's like an ending. It's like a prefix. It's a suffix that means person
I believe that would be gene. Oh, yeah, he's right. He's right. I don't know man. Whatever. It's the same shit
Whatever the point is there's a Japanese word for a people whose real life is fulfilled and she rails against the concept of them
And she's right because I mean there's people whose real life is fulfilled
And then there's the rest of us that turn to fucking anime and 2d and and and and all that and all that bullshit
Yeah, to fill the hole
To fill the hole that that that real life has left in our hearts
Yeah, that character that Tomoko character and then did you made a video about that Tomoko character and watching that video
Got me thinking about my life and I asked myself
Why did I always say weird stuff that made everyone mad or annoyed mostly?
And I think like fuck the blacks whites are the supreme race
It was for everyone would have agreed
Not really anyway the point is I really looked back on myself and I realized that it was just because I was bored
Everywhere I went I didn't have anything to say to these people
I could have had a normal social life with all of these people if I had been like all of them because you know
It starts off like this. Hey, hi. I'm David. Hi, and that's
David I just met you, but you're a fucking normie. So go now. Fuck you. Yes
I went down like you know what I just realized everyone will sit down and be like fucking topic that we hey
Would you what you know?
Oh, yeah, you know, I had a sandwich yesterday. Oh, yeah, I had a sandwich yesterday, too
That's normal life. That's real people right there sitting down at a table. They're like
But I'm sitting here
So now I'm sitting there at the table being like I don't care what sandwich you made
I try to get into interesting stuff like what's your favorite movie or what's your favorite something?
What are your thoughts on life all these interesting things and they don't answer respond to any of it
They're not receptive to any of it. Hey, bitch, let's fuck and she's like, you know, it's like fuck you, dude
You don't know me. What's up with that?
Let me stop you right there. Let me respond to the view in a more meaningful way
Okay, I can totally appreciate your your your desire to just say things that just upset people out of boredom, right?
People I was trying to get I was just trying to have something happen
Yeah, well, you're just trying to entertain
I don't know if I was if I was eating a meal with someone and they started spouting off some like what's your philosophy and what do you believe?
Shit, I'd be like shut up. I only have a go man. Yeah, Jesse
I'm with you. I mean, I mean much better much more carefully selected when I was younger
I had I wanted to like dive into deep concepts and like talk about meaningful shit all the time
But now that I'm a little bit older and a little bit wiser
I really think that all that stuff is just a bunch of bullshit
Not I didn't ask but I was just had to come up with an example geez I didn't ever ask what your philosophy
All right, well, that's what you said dude. That's what you fucking said and nor me right now
Right. Well, the point is I'm trying to have something interesting happen
Nothing happened that was ever interesting. It was boring and I hated it
And I'm now a socially normal person because I don't make myself go out and hang out with people who were boring for five
I'd like to quickly redefine normie as anyone that I dislike. Yeah, that's yeah, you know
Yeah, that's basically what it comes down. I mean, we're all here to rail against normies the concept of but really I mean
I have a normie story
It was not much but I was in the library the other day doing
the thing I do, you know Jack in my dick and
There's a guy behind me and I heard he was talking about video games
I was like, oh, that's cool. He's a video game guy, you know, because usually people are talking about normal bullshit
Yeah, and I was just sort of eavesdropping on him and then he was talking about yeah, I don't know about crash
You've seen that the naughty dogs you blah blah blah the last of us is really good
It's my favorite game ever and the new on-charted is amazing because it feels like you're playing a movie and I'm like
Truly get video games the highest they can aspire to is to be as good as a movie
What I was impressed just by the fact that he knew crash. I was gonna say yeah, that's kind of
I mean, how old was this guy? It was about my it's the library at my university. So it was about my age
I remember one episode of your let's play where you're talking about how like when you were a kid
Everyone was into Pokemon
But then one year later everyone got out of Pokemon and then in college
Everyone pretends to have not still loved Pokemon secretly where they'll go remember Pokemon
Remember back when we were kids who liked Pokemon. Yeah
But now we're the day when liking Pokemon is totally normalized so that people who don't even really give a shit about it
We'll say that they love Pokemon just so you know
It makes a complex situation being a normie, you know, they would be like tough. Yeah, this what were they called?
Pokeballs. I think that's what they were called. I don't
I don't care people as that as that nerds are just ahead of the curve man, you know
Yeah, I gotta I gotta get into this. All right. Okay. We got to figure out what the fuck what the fuck makes a normie
Yeah, I we're still like way
far away from
So look, okay, I think this is the difference. I think that I think the normal people I
Think that normal is is sort of something that that is performed and that people try to
Try to chase after it. I think most people look at what everyone else is doing and they sort of make themselves that
They listen to people like let's say you're overhearing a conversation where someone's like, haha
That guy's wearing cargo pants. What a nerd and then everyone goes, okay
Well mental note never wear cargo pants because it makes me a nerd. Yeah
But then there's people who are the the not normies who hear that and go what the fuck
But I like cargo pants and they keep wearing it anyway, and that's where you go off the beaten path and become the not normie
Yeah, I think that's something that that sort of happens as a result of either not understanding
What or why the normal people are doing what they're doing or not just not wanting to do it wait a minute like for me
I kind of just didn't get what the well where where those people were coming from, you know
Everyone was like what the fuck are you doing? You're wearing Pokemon shirts, and I'm like, yeah, Pokemon's cool, you know
Yeah, I mean at the end of the day that really is it like there's nothing like if you're wearing like a death note shirt
Okay, which I did death note is awesome death note is a really good serious
Especially if you're like yeah, and the thing is that though the people who everyone else around you the reason they're not wearing that shirt
Is that everyone else thinks it's not okay? Yeah, you know everyone else is like hey death
You're wearing a gay shirt, and you're like, you know
It's your kind of inability to process the idea that you need to change to be like everybody else
Everyone else I don't think that a normie is something like it's not something you can rigidly define like if you do this and this and this
You are a normie. I think that it comes in like aspects like everybody has normally things about them
Like normie is like porn. There's no definition, but you know it when you see it. That's true
Well, that's true what I'm getting is that like everyone is a normie in some ways like
Like my fucking like my friend Dylan who's been like my friends in high school
I know for a fact. He's a fucking freak. He used to fucking he used to like like stand around on the farm naked and fucking
Two tribal dances and shit and fucking swim out into into the middle of a puddle in like a fucking box like a canoe
In the middle of a puddle, okay, yeah, he's a fucking he's a fucking freak man
But but he also has like a normal you're referring to Lake Erie when you say a puddle. Yeah, yeah, okay
Just check him so like so in some ways, you know
He's just as big of a fucking weirdo and a nerd as me
But in other ways he has a normal job and stuff and kind of a normal life
He lives in an apartment with his girlfriend. So in that way, they're filthy degenerate. Yeah
Yeah, there's sometimes is like a wedge between me and the rest of the world
I mean, I gotta try to I gotta make what the hell is wrong with you
I'm talking up. I'm wearing my heart on my sleeve here. I'm sorry, Jesse. I'm trying to understand
I'm picking up what you're throwing down. Jesse. I want to fight just can't wait to get in there with something
Jesse, I'm gonna ask you a fucking question. All right
Let's hear it Jesse. I want to spice up this conversation by asking you and everyone else eventually
Do you feel sometimes that you are either to normie or not normie enough?
Well, that's what I was just fucking getting to but yeah, well, I wanted to make it a topic
So I knew you were going there go for it
I'll don't be a bitch
Flustered and flung I have a counter question. I do I do feel like no tofu fuck you Jesse has to answer my question first
Do you feel sometimes that you're either to normie or not normie enough in everyday life
Nobody answer this as if you're talking about your prior self talk about right now
Yes, okay as I was saying before did you ruined it for like a 20 minute train wreck just then
Because of what I do
My norminess has gone so drastically down
To the point where there's a like an even greater wedge between me and the rest of humanity than there ever was before
But like I remember in the years right after high school. Yes, where I was doing good
I would wagger around I talked to girls and stuff
I was young and hot and but then I started doing this YouTube shit
And then I just turned into this mutant that you see before you today
And now it's like like the thing about this job is that you can't relate to anyone in the world because if you work in customer service
And you complain about it. Everybody is with you because everybody's worked in customer service. I cannot
Even talk about my job because nobody understands anything about what I do
It's so weird and the worst is when people pretend that they do understand. That's pretty fucking annoying
Yeah, just if if you're a youtuber try explaining to someone else like what a copyright strike is and they're just like oh man
Like they're just like are you in trouble? Is that like it's like just fucking forget about it. Like I'll tell you like and I like I like
Like sometimes like I'll catch myself being not normie enough like I'll
Like sometimes I'll just be sitting don't want to go down into that place
I'll be minding my own business and suddenly like
Like it'll all hit me that the stuff that I usually ignore about how fucked up my life is that I just don't notice because I'm not a normie like I
Don't have a car right now. I don't have a phone. I haven't had a phone for six months. My life is in shambles
No, I haven't had a phone for like six months
I I live in a fucking dump and it's like I don't even notice these things because my life is
Creativity, it's what I do for my job and it's what I do for my hobby. So when I get distracted from my job
I'm still doing my fucking job. I it's all I do is just I make weird stuff
I'm living this weird artist lifestyle. That's the quintessential non-normie lifestyle
And I feel like a fucking normie
It's a spectrum my friend it's a spectrum because of that
I don't have a reason to usually go anywhere
I don't have a reason to call anyone because I hate people anyways. I don't like going out. I fucking I hate everything in the world
So but then like I'll catch myself like hey, wait a minute. Isn't it weird that I don't have a car?
Isn't it weird that I don't have a phone? Yeah, I guess it kind of is pretty fucked up
How did I get to this point, you know, Jesse brief
Yeah, I know what you sometimes I feel like a normie, but then I just look over at my Nico Robin statue and I'm just like
Both Ben and Jesse were saying like cuz I brought this up because I was interested to know
Dude, I can look up her dress right now
Jesse Jesse was saying that he mostly worries about being not normie enough
I have concerns about being too normie sometimes and it's mostly when I hang out like with Jesse because Jesse is
So
Unhinged and doesn't care and in ways that like well like when I'm in
When I'm in public especially like I I guess because I grew up very like rigidly following the rules
You know, I was never something like not the social rules
But like the rules of like the law kind of you always go pretty normie when you're out and about doing shit
Yeah, well, I just haven't I'm like very afraid of like breaking laws
Like I was just raised in a way to like I you know, I'm extremely conscious about that kind of stuff even in like minor circumstances
so like if we're at brony con or something and
We're on you know on top of the the building up there. Yeah, and Jesse's like going over the railing and I'm like
Come back
It's really not a big deal and if anything I wish I was the one over there doing that
Leaning over a railing Jesse's fucking unhinged
Well, you
Well see that's what I'm talking about Jesse you don't care about those things that means nothing to you in my mind
All these alarm bells go off because I'm like that's where the rules are that's like that's the law mark that line in the sand
You know that arbitrary marker is where the law ends and begins and in my brain
It's like we are now breaking the law. Maybe we should take a step back, you know, but I wish I was the one going over that
I don't think that rules are for cowards, right?
And that applies socially as well. I do too, which is why I feel too normie when I follow the rules that strictly, right?
And Jesse is why I like being drunk in public because then I don't care anymore. That's that's definitely true
Gibbon was saying just the other day
I don't even remember this but he was saying that when we all met up at Brony con like one of the first things
I did was that I just when we laid in our when we went to our hotel
I just started humping him, which I have no memory
Thing because it just devolved it just dissolved the tension and I'm always thinking that I wish I would do more of that shit
That's what I'm talking about. Well, that's yeah, that's the thing like every time Jesse talks about him and his friends all like showing each other
Like I I feel I feel wrong that I'm not doing that
Yeah, like that I would be so prudish as to like when we all shared a hotel room
Yeah, you know, I avoid if Jesse was in the shower
I made sure I didn't go into the bathroom even though I might have had to piss because there was like the bath the fucking tub
Is right next to a shower. I mean, this is why I love stories like the d-club story so much
It's like yeah, these guys are so free. I have a genuine
Of right, you know, yeah, I was just thinking I was like we all need to get it
We all need to get together and do some cock handshakes. Yes, it's like a handshake, but you grab each other's dick
You know, I hadn't thought of it like that until you said something you know, that's the danger
It's just a cock handshake
Don't get hard I'm gonna tell my therapist in 10 years. Yeah, it was just a cock handshake doctor
Martinovic and 10 years later you're you're
Ideally a cock handshake should be the length of a normal handshake
It shouldn't go on for like some handshakes. Well, it's pretty long and be pretty satisfying. But all right
All right, so on the subject on back on topic. Yeah, it should be like one of those like like like like secret handshakes
Like where it's really complicated
Some handshakes got to involve the mouth a little bit, you know
All right, what do you back on topic? I want to say that in I don't really consider myself
That normie but like you said before guy. It's on a spectrum right like in a lot of ways
I am normie like you know, I kind of have sex with girls, you know
Ultimate normie act you can commit it is a shame other than marrying them
Marrying them is the normiest thing you can do, you know
Like I I meet girls and stuff and like I go and like I talk to people and like absolutely shameful
I behave like a generally
Functional member of society on the other hand like I don't have a regular job and like a lot of my income comes from like
Creativity and stuff and like my room my roommates see me as this totally weird
Out there, you know kind of goofy character. Yeah
Oh, so you're that guy to them, huh? I don't I don't see myself as like a crazy wacky person
But they see me as just this like impossible
Confluence of like weird that's cool trades. Yeah, like they're really fascinated by my and they're like, oh, didn't you?
Didn't you make money by making pony videos?
What the fuck
Com we don't make videos anymore
And
Everybody pledged to the t-bat patreon on patreon.com slash endless Jess so like so like compared so like compared to my roommates
I'm a complete like they're so normie next to me, but like compared to Jesse. I feel like a total normie
I know like I still have have a phone and like
That's another one of those awareness moment for me because when you say it like that
It really doesn't sound like I've become an insane hermit. I mean, I have functional kidneys
I'm living the normal life the normal lifestyle right now. You know, I I sleep on a bed. That's made out of a bed and not garbage
My bed's not in a bed frame like a like a true normie sleeps in a bed in a bed frame
But at least it's a bed and not like a pile of dish right
The frame because I went fuck that yeah, mine also is not in the frame
You know, I can't help but wonder if if it makes it like even less normie that I have like a Casper mattress
That I bought because it's like a podcast recommended it to me like
Does but on the spectrum it's it's it's less weird than having no bed and sleeping on trash as Jesse
Yeah, I don't know. It's funny. I I feel I I kind of a similar status with my friends where I'm like the weird guy
But a lot of them were at least as weird as me until after like they got jobs and like became more
Yeah, yeah, like to to make to make a living in a normal way. You kind of have to become a normie
Yeah, I can get I mean I work a nine-to-five every day of the week
I must super normie and I like no challenging that notion right and then again
By the way, I I really hope that this podcast comes across as like funny and self-aware and not like the most
Autistic thing that's ever happened, but I hope we'll have to we've got a
Let it let it be known that we we understand that
Awareness of normie is like it's totally relative. Yeah
Definitely like the term normie is almost a misnomer because I feel like I'm the only normal fucking person on this planet
I know right when you see those YouTube comments, but yeah, like you know
Like among my friends man like one of my best friends is a dude who when I met him was a
Full-on Hikikomri who hadn't left his room in like years
He was like pissing in bottles and shit because of paranoia and stuff like that
Clarissa
Thousands of anime like he's seen he's seen way more than I ever have and that's saying something
Yeah, I'm known to be a man who's watched a lot of anime, you know
He he had this because he had something called cluster headaches were like every morning at like 6 a.m
He'd get an intense migraine that lasts like a couple hours and as a result
He couldn't come to school most of the time
And the only times he came was like on the first couple days of the year and it just so happens that one day
He was reading like a lucky star book at school
Yeah, yeah, there was a show that no one had heard of at the time if you weren't like well
2006 or 7 or something 2007 yeah, so I started talking to him based on that and like got his
You know his instant messenger handle right before he left school entirely. Yeah, the last day
He was there so me and him became friends and like you know
This is a guy who is about as as weird as it gets right? He's locked himself in his room all he does is watch anime
He's got like Daki Makura pillows everywhere on his fucking walls
He was like he's always slept on the floor just cuz he's a big fat guy and like
He's got like that's he has like bad snoring that like you can hear for like like like yards and
Like you can hear it forever
Yeah, he won't sleep over at people's houses because his snoring is so loud that he'll keep you up like
He's just got a lot of odd traits
But then over time he you know and he would he was like a terrified of talking to people
We'd go out to like fast food and I'd have to order for him, you know
Oh, I couldn't talk to people like that
But over time this dude has gotten to be so normal because like he started working out losing weight doing diets and stuff
He started talking to people he got a normal job
You know, he's been for almost two years now. He's been like moving cars working for my dad and like now
He's like a completely normal guy all he does is like talk about cars and fucking
Oh, I didn't know this was the guy who one of your friends who started working for your dad. That's awesome
I'm glad he's doing that. Yeah, he he's yeah
He's got a complete he went to college for a couple years on like, you know scholarships and stuff because he's like
He's like yeah, but like now he's like so normie that like I try to talk to him about weird stuff
And he's kind of like he can barely, you know, like he's the only one of my friends who can still like get to that place
And be like yeah, I get where you're coming from
And this is the fundamental difference between even most weird people and those of us in this chat right now
Yeah, right if I it's not just what situation you're in
It's the core of what you want out of reality out of your life
And where does it bring you because I think all of us
Yeah, all of us are gonna either like live off our art or die in a gutter something like that
I don't know. We're all people well Jesse
Shamefully for me. I'm living the plan B lifestyle right now fine
Which is which makes me ashamed of myself, but I'm doing it, you know, I like to I like to have a house
I'd like to go back to have a part-time job if he needed it for food
But he hasn't had a part-time job in a while
So I don't trust I mean frankly frankly my job
I've got is so good and I'm expecting like a promotion in a couple months like the amount of work the amount of money
I'll need to make to like equal or even come close to like achieving what I'm doing now
It's good is like puts the level of like my patron. I'll need to get you to go full-time at like so high
It's probably making it harder for me to break away. Yeah. Well anyway, yeah
In response to my my
Willingness to go back to work like yeah, if I did go back
It would always be with the idea that I'm going to get out again, right?
Yeah, I got a job the first time under the impression that I was gonna work until I could afford I think it's safe to say that all of us have
Found a legitimate passion in our lives that we're looking to pursue, you know, right?
I mean phrase is better. I didn't phrase it bad. I now want to phrase it better
Most people who are in some sort of weird situation like being locked in their room
We're having a huge medical problem. They are fundamentally drawn to being normal some day and maybe they'll succeed
Maybe most of them succeed, but but for me personally
No matter how normal of a situation. I'm in I am drawn away from it
Like I could right now be like that's true
We can attest to to DeVu not being into having a job whatsoever. He's I well
I gotta I gotta address the guy who's been quiet here Tom who?
Flew just just got back from having flown from like Boston to Vancouver
Yeah, and stayed there for a month and a half with his internet girlfriend
How normally do you feel Tom good question?
Um, I honestly I've been so silent because I don't think about any of this like my social standings or how normally you're on
Normie I'm doing my I don't buy that for one fucking second. I don't know I know you're judging everybody
Don't you don't you take the same perverse pride that we all do
I mean
I know for me that like I can't hold a job like I've told like
Everyone like it's my my family's like because I live with my family still and I make like pittance
I make pennies on the dollar that I used to like right years ago on the internet and they're like pony days, man
You need to get a job, but I'm just like no and they're like why is like because I will probably kill myself
Well, I have a question for you. It's probably the most not normie question ever
Do you feel blame? Are you mad?
Do you feel like who's kebab rath rannage your franage pooch-gooch-booch-google your rammage jiggy-jiggy
Google
What's being said
Even more like to do the what the in the have more like to do if that's not how it goes, you know
Tom
Have you ever been want to do more look like that's the one well Tom brought up killing himself and really isn't that the way to?
Not be a normie truly
Living is so fucking normal
Dude that was a guy it was like this Jewish guy at MIT. He wrote like a thousand page. He wrote his PhD thesis
It was a thousand page manifesto on like Jewish mysticism and like I'm like the subject of life as like an abstract concept
Yeah, and his final conclusion was that life and death are both fundamentally equivalent to each other
I then like the next day
He went out in public and like put on a tuxedo and just like shot himself in the head
I have someone in front of like in front of like a tour group at MIT and you know
Work that guy was too normie for his own good
You know speak of normie
I mean this this very this very channel you're watching this video on right now
I made sure that I was the one who made it and would be financially
Responsible for it in the instance. They were ever to take off and be successful. So just so you know
I'm always thinking about the shit Machiavellian style in case one of these one of these things is to take off
I want to be the guy who's gonna make the most because I'm here to sabotage it from within well my goal
To make sure none of these guys ever become normies and surpass me in life
I did that with teabag and I made sure I to do it again with with the procrastinator
Tom reminded me because he mentioned work living at home like that the hardest thing for me about trying like if I even
Wanted to try to be normie. It's impossible because my living environment is so fucking bizarre
That like it can't happen like I mean aside for the fact that my room itself is giant and covered in posters on every inch
Which I can't I can't escape it now like I've put so much like you said you were going to only over my bed
And there's a bunch of sexy anime girls over my bed
And so now even if I want to like think about something else
I look at my ceiling and I'm just like I guess I'm jacking off the anime girls tonight
You surround yourself with the ideal and I want but uh, that's not a good point
is
How even if we like made an effort to be normie how normie could any of us
Is something that you can wheel yourself to do a suit and got like a normal job and live the normal life
I would still essentially be the same guy who fucking punches teenagers in the movie theater
And that's right family is alcoholics, you know when addicts of all of us
Yes, I think you're the least willing to hold on. Let me finish ready. Okay, my story
Cuz like you guys have seen what the inside of my house looks like right that
My living room is literally a castle. I know but in fight I saw it in that monopoly money music video
Yeah, yeah, it's been in a few videos there. The entire living room is a castle my
Like you can't you can't just like live in there and think like this is a house
It's impossible like you go in there and you're like what the fuck do I live in this is madness, you know
And my my brother Victor because Victor is like the guy who's trying to escape and become the normie guy, right?
Right, he's like a you know like in the in the boys in the hood
In boys in the hood where there was the one kid who wanted to go to college and escape the gangster life
Yeah, yeah, that's Victor. He's trying to get out of here go to LA
He's just too gangster, right well, but it's funny though because like
Compared like we all always say like oh Victor's going to become the most normie guy of all because he does work that deals with other people
And it's like a job that already exists
But filmmaking is the most not normie job before we existed like up until the existence of you of YouTube and people making up their
Own jobs out of thin air like we did like nothing was less normie than going off to Hollywood to become an artist
But like from our perspective it's like oh Victor's gonna go be the normie one
But he's always talking about like how for him
it's hard to like get into the mindset of being an adult because of the fact that he lives at home in a home that is so like
It's so massive and so like
Over-decorated and designed where like you know my mom's office is nothing but toys because she's like a toy collector
You know our living rooms a fucking castle my room is full of posters
You can't go anywhere in this house and just feel like a normal guy. It's impossible
You know my parents aren't really that like my dad is super normie, but my mom is not very
Normie, you know, so yeah, so you can't escape it. It's and even though my dad is super normie
He's also the guy who made it a fucking castle, so he's not that he's still got his own
He's guilty of conspiracy to commit and apparently he has like a huge
Exhaustive memory of movies because he just remembers all the movies he watches. Yeah, that's pretty not mine between
I don't know. I think that's more normie than you think I think I think a lot of people can
Movies are very normie these days
I think the line between normie and not normie is really thin and I think it's getting even thinner right
And I think even today like I think even in the past everyone had sort of like this pop cultural
Sensibility about the most everyone was to some degree tuned into like you know movies and music and like art stuff
That is not exactly no
It's not it's not normie like going to work nine to five is normie
Yeah, and you know like drinking in bars is normie, but it's not it's not I think the internet is slowly blowing the doors off
Yeah, and yeah, that's the thing and I mean now it is stuff like us is accessible to people to stuff
Right who aren't yeah culture is more accessible to everyone
So everyone's more exposed to it and just the whole the whole thing about like nerd culture like the whole nerd pride thing
And how being a nerd is cool now like I think today
The normiest thing you can be is like a little bit not normie, you know
Not
It's niche to be just a straightforward like corporate guy now, that's it's only square
Like normie get less and less normie until the point where like we're normie
The internet is causing like every group that exists was a kind of kind of existed in its own little circle
But the internet's allowing people to form smaller and smaller communities of like many people like us that
People even more to bring it out to like a broader perspective, you know like we all grew up on
Cartoons that would show high school or or even TV shows that would show high school is like this very like
Fragmented like here's the jocks. Here's the the the nerds
Here's the Goths, you know, like that's how you should always be presented and for a lot of places in America
Especially in middle America
It's still like very much like that where people still get beat up for being gay or get beat up for this and that you know
like for being nerds and stuff, but like
At the high school I went to all the clicks had kind of bled together like everybody knew someone in another
Click like we had we had a bunch of skater kids who stood around and a bunch of goth kids who stood around
But they weren't like enemies. They kind of knew each other and yeah, that's true
Clicks weren't that code they really weren't they really and it was largely because like Facebook had made it so everybody
Knows what's going on with everybody else anyways, so I don't know
There was Facebook so much as they didn't really exist that much in the reality
Facebook only became a thing like after we got to call like like right when we were going to college and it was like college
Well, you say Nate that it wasn't a thing ever, but I don't know cuz like
Tropes that were
Not a lot of people on forums who have told who like are from the Midwest who have made it sound like they're high school like super was
Okay, well me and then we're on we're in Massachusetts, so I mean
There's and we're from big cities, so like it's a little more small town, but nonetheless east coast. Yeah, but yeah
I think this coast is a little bit because we have like I guess the best way to put it is we have a lot of black people and
Like I think the fact that we're not racist has a lot to do with you
That's true of you me and Ben went to a pro almost entirely white school
They were like a couple Asians couple black people here and now you hate
And yeah, now we're super racist as a result, of course
But the the the thing about that is that like it's true
We do I mean I mean I mean I knew from like I
Knew culture like culturally. I was told that racism was bad. I just didn't get very much
Let's just talk about clicks, you know, we're talking about you know being an army and like at our school
Like I remember pretty much everyone. I went to school very well
And there really was like at the very like there were opportunities to join whichever click you wanted to the thing
Is that when you're a high schooler you're super retarded and you don't know what the fuck you're doing with your life
If you wanted to join a click it would be super easy
You just need to put in a tiny amount of effort to like express interest in whatever they're doing and show that you're not a
Complete fuck-up, but I mean those high schools are not capable of that
I felt like a fucking insane person in high school because I I looked at all the clicks and I didn't get it like I didn't get well
I hung out with the goth kids, but they all actually looked like
Goth kids. They actually wore the makeup. They actually
Was a kid I hung out with the goth kids, too. I was the least gothie of the goth
Yeah, that was I was in with I was the guy real goths. I mean I had I had bondage pants from hot topic
Did you hang on Ben did at one point write a letter to game informer explaining why goth culture was legit
That's not what my letter to game informer was about my letter to game informer was about that
I really liked the Wheel of Time series and I really wanted them to fucking
Whether there were any video game tie-ins coming out since you hung out with that click
Did you ever read Johnny the homicidal maniac? No, I was not I was not aware of that and so
this was hilarious to me right because I
In high school I hung out with that goth click and it was all all kids, you know who dressed the part they
They had my my chemical romance. They had the all-black. Yeah, they had the my chemical romance shirts
They have the you know
They listened to those bands and went to those shows and stuff like that
They were all fucking potheds to at least half of them
And I was the one who was like I was I was over there
You know with those guys hanging out with like the nerdier ones because there was a lot of overlap between nerds and goths in my school
You know, yeah, like so I was at the nerdy goth kids and I just dressed like a fucking freak
I had like my my super long hair that went down to my ass
I had the scraggly ass horrible beard the fucking like random anime t-shirts and shit dirty ass clothes
And I smelled like farts, but ripped apart leaking. So I had to plug it
So one of those goth kids one time gave me
One of those goth kids let me read Johnny the homicidal maniac
And it was really funny because the whole thing is a criticism of like click culture
It's all about how much Joan and Vazquez hates God
Yeah, like all of the goth kids absolutely love Johnny the homicidal maniac because they all think they're the good ones
I'm like, how did the person who loaned me this not understand they are exactly what this is about
We are self-aware in this chat right and almost no one else is in the universe
It's like no one else knows what we know we're the smartest people in the world
We're fucking geniuses. Listen, listen, there's a pair. There's a parallel. There's a there's an idea forming idea eating in my neurons
It's like we here talking about this are like Joan and Vazquez
Pointing out that we everyone including ourselves is all just pretending and we're all and by you know the goth sit around talking about the
Preps and how and how foolish they are, but they don't realize how foolish they look not realizing that they themselves
The goths and the vampires and the emos were all calling one another posers and so they
They got the ghost of Edgar Allen Poe. Yeah reanimated and he called all of them posers
He would he would he's the biggest record. I don't think I think we have shown that there is a level on which we admire
Norminess and yeah, true and like we're more we're not so much saying that being
respect for normies
Like I mean I I would never completely reject norminess. I mean
I think we're distinguishing ourselves without saying that we're necessarily better for being I see I see normies
And I see like something that I could never be but that like it's like a normal person looking at like Superman or something, right?
Normies are truly superior. Yeah, I think that maybe I think maybe there's no such thing as a true normie
I think that normie nest absolutely correct is like it's like a platonic ideal
Yes, and there is some like hypothetical theoretical perfect normie archetype
But no one right when we recognize traits of norminess and people we can call them a normie
I've come to realize I
Think I just understood why I can't be normie was that I think that if I tried I would always come back to
Because if you try we'd reject you if you ever have you ever read the book The Stranger
absolutely by Camus of course yeah, or
Alternatively seen the play waiting for God. Oh that the stranger was about a guy who was the biggest
Non-normie of all so hard that he had to murder everyone the guy's way think about he only killed one
He only think about the guy for the stranger is that from his perspective
Nothing he did was that weird, you know, he was just like I went to my mother's funeral
I didn't really feel like crying so he didn't cry
Yeah, and then later on he just kind of ends up killing a guy
And then they use the fact that he didn't cry at his mom's funeral against the sense him
Yeah, and then like he's you know getting executed at the end and he kind of has like this breakdown where he's like
I don't understand like I don't get what has happened here, and he's just like I feel you know distant from it
The play waiting for God. Oh meanwhile is about these two guys waiting for a good dough waiting for good
Oh
They go out they go out to this bench every day, and they're waiting for God. Oh, and they
Can't say that good. Oh, it's easy
It's fucking
Talking about how they're gonna kill themselves or about how they're gonna do this and that or about how this whatever's gonna happen
But the point is they just go out every day and nothing fucking up waiting for gay dough
It's there always just waiting around guy, which is like I feel like whatever I don't ever think of like
But if I think of the idea of becoming
Enormy like all those like absurdist ideas flood into my head, and I'm just like what is the meaning of anything like why?
Like I could die tomorrow, and none of this will matter like putting effort into being anything is is like meaningless
Putting it oh that ties right into our last podcast where we talked about this very topic
Yeah, the idea of trying to create a self-identity is so strange to me like like nothing that I am right is like something
I went after being that guy
Wasted effort come objective
The way I keep my hair and beard is because I'm too lazy to get it cut and then when I cut it
It just all goes you know it's like there's no there's no sense of like crafting a self
It's myself is like the untethered expression of what interests me at the time
It just so happens I've been into cartoons since I was a kid, and I love writing about them
So that's why I write about anime. It's not like I'm trying to create this this idea of myself as the the anime guy
It's just like that's what I am the anime man has that in the market cornered
You know no challenge that guy um
But yeah like to me like if I try if I think about like what if I tried to create a self-image and like become this person
And then it's like you could spend like a year doing that and like getting towards this this eventuality
And then get hit by a truck and die and then like the universe is meaningless
Why are you trying to do anything just like live by your?
By your instinct you know yeah like I want to like live on my own
I want to like have a relationship
I want to have a car and I want to have
Disposed I want to have a relationship those things with standards because those things are desirable. I want them
Yeah, like I wouldn't I would not mind having all those things
But I I and I and I also think if you're working towards it
That's not the same thing as being normie is just being goal-driven, you know
I think yeah, I think the more normie attitude would be the the the girl who like gets knocked up and then keeps the baby
And marries the guy even though they have no love for each other because it's just
Yeah, I just sort of consider that to be like one of the most like one of the most intense expressions of norminess
Like because like I have older cousins who get married like they're all female they get like two of them
Like right I feel you on this fuck them well like
Yeah, I have these two older cousins who've gotten like who are like in their 30s now
And they've gotten like oh, I would definitely have sex with them or married like a
Bunch load of times. It's always just like to some generic guy with like tattoos. I'm like this looks like
And with tattoos
It just seems like that seems like the most normie thing like one of the most intense expressions
The quintessential focus point of being normie is to not be self-critical not be self analytical
Is that what we talk about the saddest outcome that I think most like normies have
This is what happened to like
Everyone on my mom's side of family like all my all my aunts and uncles like they they started off like living
The normie life right like they got made they had kids and then at some point everything went horribly wrong
But they stuck with them. They know that here's the thing in their minds
They're still like a part of that like that that's still who they are. They're still like normal
Yeah, but they're totally not at all like there are a bunch of fucking weirdos like you know my aunt like
Went crazy and just like now all she does is smoke weed constantly and like and
Weird diet, but like in her mind
She is a normal person who is like trying to get you know like oh my life is gonna be back on track soon
You know, it's like it's never happening. You're you've lost your mind somewhere along the line
You don't get that. Yeah, I think that's what happens to a lot of like
I don't know maybe it's just in my family
But like I know a lot of people who are like in their 50s and have it
The other shoe hasn't dropped and they haven't realized that their life is totally not normal
They still think that they're working towards like getting stability back, but it's never coming back
Yeah, I think of all these like failed relationships as a super normie expression is because it's like they're doing it because
I mean, I understand if you have specific reasons like a pregnancy happened
But if you're doing it just for like just to do it it really shows this weird conformity of yeah
Oh, I'm kind of like doing that because like that's what's socially accepted like I'd even say happen like not having an abortion
Even when it's obviously the thing to do in your particular circumstance is just is a very normie thing to do
You know
See it sounds like you're like a thousand feet from the microphone suddenly what
Sounds like you're all the way across the room
Well, I don't know the stats on that I I mean I could have been told either way getting an abortion
I'm just saying that like to do things without
Like when I was like that's what being a normie is when I was seven
I had learned the statistic that half of marriages end in divorce and I know right
Well, then clearly I'm only going to do it when I'm like at least 98 percent sure that it's gonna work out
But so right we'll just go into it. It's like didn't you see the stat? What else would you do that had a 50%?
That you have to that you have to do this thing because it's expected of you
Intense norminess right just just the other day. I was lying on the floor in a depressed stupor
Regretting every decision. I made in my life up to that point and I just thought to myself
You know what you were pulling a naps to blue. That's right at that moment
I thought to myself you know what you know what I could get married
I could give myself to someone just you know and be done with it, but then as soon as I stopped doing that
I realized that's a terrible idea. I think that's where it comes from
Normies have no hope and nothing to live for and that's exactly depressed because they're why I mean
So I mean we all we all we hear all live for our art right true
We all we all live for our creative outlets and for the purpose of creating something that you know will impact people and
Maybe you know stand the test of time and and and and continue on. Yeah
I'm all that and pussy on my face. You know what I'm fucking saying guys
But yeah pussy just no no no shut up shut up fuckers
And fucking the the point is most people don't have that yeah, that's true
And I read I think that I think that I don't think that the difference between normie and not normie is that well-defined
But I think that if there is one yeah, I think that's probably
Cuz to look at for example like our own parents which is our probably like our role models in this sense
I look at like our dad and I think my dad my dad right now has like his job is
Causes him a bunch of angst because he has to do a lot of shit for it
And he his happiest moments are on the weekends when he can go sailing and he really love
He really really loves sailing because he can just cut loose and do that shit and not be beholden to anybody
That's what he said is happiest and you know
It just makes you wonder if if he chose and not that he made any mistakes
But that if he chose the optimal way to live his life
Just because you know, I mean, I'm glad I exist because he married my mom that that worked out well for me
But perhaps it worked out better for him if you'd make a different path that let him pursue this kind of pleasurable activities more
You know if having a normal job had any merit at all then why do normies take vacations?
You know, I'm gonna counter-argument that a little bit. I think
Okay, I think that happiness
Not straight
Happiness happiness kind of balances itself out right like like the more miserable your job makes you yeah
Like the happier you are in comparison to it when you can get on the weekend and do what you want to do to a certain point
Yeah, I think that in the long run that kind of like net happiness tends to balance out for people
You know, that's true because humans aren't built to be happy all the time
It doesn't work out when you're given everything like like it would if you think if you think like if if dad's job was to be
I don't know a professional sailor whatever that would even mean right
He would be just static all the time while doing it. Absolutely. No, right. You're you that's so you're entirely right
You're entirely right about that. I don't know
I mean is the optimal life for like everyone to be an artist doing whatever they want like if we were living in
Star Trek and like everyone had everything they need like what would everybody do to obtain like their perfect life?
Would they all just like pursue their artistic endeavors or would they just like play video games?
I would do exactly what I'm doing me too
And I think that's the mark of of like that you're on the right path that that's the case for you
And I think most of us here, which I think is what unites us is that we agree that we are doing that in one way or another
Which means that all six of us are the normies and everyone else to get on our level
Everyone else is a failure and a weirdo you need to be like us
The real question is there's seven of us, so we're the main six plus spike. Which of us is the spike not it not it not it
It's digi digi's not here. It's digi
Digi's off eating ass like spike would be like spike it loves to do
admittedly, okay, so
Do we feel like we've covered this topic in general because before we leave I have one final challenge for us
Let's well should we wait I want us to wait for digi to get back
I don't think he's coming back anytime soon. Okay, let's hear it if he comes back in the middle of it fine
But before we finish this podcast
I really think we should all rank ourselves in terms of who's the most to least agreed agreed
I think and I'm gonna vote that
I'm gonna vote guy for no
Because you have a fucking job
Okay, all right, I don't mean to be critical, but I think Tommy might be a little more normie than me
I don't think so. I don't think so. That's not that's not an insult. I'm just like for example. He has a girlfriend
That's pretty normie. He went to visitor for a while, you know having a girlfriend is pretty fucking
That's right. That's right
I mean I sit here raging all the time that I don't have a girlfriend right now
So say that again. My girlfriend is like a continent away right now
But you have but you have one
I mean, it's pretty normie to to establish a kind of relationship that you would be willing to maintain over a long distance, you know
Well, I've got like some I think there's some merit to what you say guy
Thank you, but I'm still gonna give you
I mean if that's how the consensus will vote then I'll accept it
I do have a nine-to-five job that I work every single week
Making each other's norminess
We're gonna rank ourselves. We're gonna rank the whole portion
I'll just give you mine right now. I guess if that's what it's gonna be. It's gonna be me then I'd say Tom then
Hippocrates cuz he's going to school then maybe then maybe
DeVoo then digi then
Jesse oh no, I forgot Ben Ben's in there somewhere
Jesse's the least normie though is the I
Well, we're talking like lifestyle here
I think I think he is probably
Second least normie second least you think hmm. Yeah, I think so
Possibly I put you up there though pretty high
Well, I take being at last as as the greatest compliment of all but did you just you're the only one who aspires to be normie more than any of us
You know, I'm a complicated guy. I'm a complicated. I'm a man of many contradictions
Just like to say that for the past
I don't know how long we've been doing this like 40 minutes. Yeah, but I've been in a quarter
I've been twisting the ends of my hair into hook shapes
And trying and using those hooks to try and pick my glasses off
Well
Okay, that might be like the nail in the coffin of me ever being considered normie anyways
But this is this is about you beating up children again. It's gonna be the one where you peed on that girl
Okay, well those are two good ones. Yeah
Go on this is an example of how like normie us can come down to perspective
Because you can look at this story one way and it seems like I'm a cool guy who's got it all together
But then you look at it from the truth
I
Was that a Cody LaRue Halloween party three years ago. That's a five-star event. Yeah, so so basically
The normie account of what happened
Is that I went to a party and I hooked up with a girl who I had never even met before
Normie
But what really happened is that I ended up rape he raped her
Very not normie well done. No, I want to hear the truth. I think pedophiles and war mainstreamed and youtubers
Well, what really happened is that I set is that I was getting a blowjob from a very obese woman
in an alleyway in Flint, Michigan nice and
You say it like that
Did that really happen? Yes, he bet your ass it happened
Well, like so like so many of my stories that I think like could almost pass for normie and then I remember like where I live
Yeah, that's true
Yeah, that's not a fact. We haven't considered his geography here. Yeah, I I always think that like from my perspective
By the way, who always seems less normal just because he's from the Midwest and like all of his Midwestern isms are inherently very strange to me
Yeah, I'm a middlest of the Midwest. I'm in the Kansas I'm so proud of the fact
I'm so proud of the fact that a city where I hang out all the time is now in the news and widely
Regarded as not the shithole of America. Yeah. Yeah
It feels me with the bizarre sense of pride and tranquility. It's that's a very non normie thing to be the worst place in America
You know, that's well done
I
Got to give you props for that
Just the fact that I hooked up with a fat chick in my car and you know, you know
I'm like the worst city in America
I I hooked up with a sort of fat Asian girl one time, but not you know, she wasn't full fat, which is great shame
No, no
The Lord of fives so perhaps wait the Lord of fives
Toby Toby and John both both have described you as the no the king of five. I can't wait. Yeah
Um, um guy, have you seen Toby's girlfriend? But he likes fat girls. He's into fat girls. So to him to him
That's yeah, so to him. So to him the skinny girls that I was hooking up with were only five
Oh, you're right. That was Toby who told me that maybe all along. He was leading me. Okay, I need to reevaluate the whole more like king of king
More like ends more like king of the nines as in that thing that black people do where they insult each other creatively back and forth
They call that a nine. Yeah, the nine you play in that's what Hitler played when he burned all the Jews
He was like nine. It was like nine. Hilarious. Get it guys. Very good joke night. Very good. Thank you. Let's wrap this up. Goodbye
Wait, wait, wait. No guys. Where do I fall? Where do I fall on the normie scale?
Then I think you're right about the fucking abnormal. I think you're very non normally
I think it depends on like again, which which normie or not normie things we're talking about, right?
Like is it more normie to live at home with your parents and just basically
Do whatever these days. That's very normie, right? Yeah
like Ben
If we're talking about like right now me and Ben might be like, you know, I don't know closer to toe and toe
Maybe I'm less normie than him
But if we're talking about the Ben that lived bummed around California for a year
Oh, I think that was a little bit
Yeah, that Ben like I could never do that
I think Ben is one in non-norminess. I mean Jesse what we say I forgot to mention the best part of my story
Not only was I getting a blowjob from a fat disgusting pig girl that I've never met in a car in an alleyway in Flint, Michigan
But I was also dressed up as Winnie the Pooh
I
Did she pretend she was Christopher Robin? No, that would happen. I don't think she got the reference
Now that's normie behavior that we can all
He heard this but I'm positive
Knowing how drunk I was I'm positive that I did the voice at some point
No, I'm imagining him in a fursuit and like a Winnie the Pooh fucking
It's not a fursuit
Holy shit in reality Jesse's a Pooh bear costume was just the I'm a bear t-shirt
Or at the altered beast it was legit. I had I got a red shirt. I wrote Pooh on it
I fucking I had the ears. I had that's that basically all you need and my pants were off, too
So the costume was even more accurate
Really I had to go with that girl take my pants off in order for the costume to work
It was he who was loyal to the characters the last that's I like to think that's exactly what Winnie the Pooh would have done
he's
He's the least normie of us all we keep trying to rank ourselves based on our
On our lifestyles, but what about just our personalities like how we would
Difference like I don't know how I think we're all relatively similar. That's why we've all kind of
Yeah
That's how we all met yeah similar interests and similar like goals
I guess I mean what divu would you change the ranking in any significant way based on our personalities?
I don't know Jesse not still be the most
Abnormie
That's the word like I don't know like he's um
Like he has the weirdest things that he doesn't tell anyone about except on the internet
But in terms of just like a person out and you just see them and say hi
You know how weird would each of us right?
I mean our parents yell that through car windows with at an alarming rate when I go out
Which is why part of the reason I don't go out that's because of those those flint brains are added with all that lead
You know, who knows what's going on? I don't know man
I think I think the fact that I crave
Right now. I'm craving to hear how abnormie I am and I really think that speaks to the fact that being a non
Normie is like a pretty normie thing now. It is. It is. It's
Cool, it's edgy. I keep forgetting that my room flooded with poop poopy water and I fucking
I
Made a video
Instead of making steps to clean it
The first thing I did you know
I showed that video to a lot of people now and all of them would say the same thing
I can't believe he'd do his toys in there and I was like
Yeah, I tried to picture myself in the same scenario and I think I definitely would have thrown my toys in there
Like I don't think I would have had much hesitation in doing that
Unless it was like how I know I'm more normie because I would just be freaking out if my water was leaking
I mean, I would have freaked out considerably first and I'm sure Jesse has in the past
But he's just he wakes up one day sees it. There's poop water his house is like, all right
I honestly don't freak out because stuff like that happens to me so often
Yeah, I've acquired a zenness about it. I can definitely talk about his room flooding for years
So I can definitely see digi without the aid of even making a video just deciding cuz he's drunk
I have too much self-restraint
Oh, we were talking about this on a digi bros the other day
How like I used to get like I would get really mad and I'd like want to thrash my room
But then I would look at all the stuff in my room and think about how expensive it all is
And I would just push over a fan like I've done I have literally dropped kicked a fan several times
Just because it was the only thing that wouldn't break if I attacked it
Oh, the closest I've ever come to like real damage was after watching Bojack Horseman
Because I spent the entire time I was watching it getting drunk
Like I didn't stop drinking wine the whole time
I was watching the show and I was like oh like unbelievably beyond wasted by the end of it
and then I put on death grips and I went into my fucking bathroom the first song on on the new out on their latest album was
I break mirrors at my face in the United States and I'm like screaming it into the mirror at myself
And I'm just thinking like I got to do it
I got to break this mirror with my face in the United States
I have to and like I'm like leaning over the over the sink like and I'm thinking about it and I'm like
Do I because I my justification in my mind was I make enough money now that I can replace this mirror
So I was like I could do it. I could break this mirror with my face
I can replace you like Charles Foster Kane just trashing his own room because he has all the money
But then the conclusion or Tommy was Tommy was about to kill himself
But I was just staring at the mirror and then I thought about it and I was like all right first of all
I don't know how badly I'm gonna cut myself up doing this
Maybe I'll end up in the hospital and I don't want to pay those bills and then I thought about it
And I was like I don't know how much these mirrors actually cost. What if this is a $200 mirror
I don't want to spend that because I just wanted to break something with my face
So in spite of how being outrageously drunk and really wanting to break that mirror
I ended up not doing it and
Going back to throw over my desk chair because it you know wouldn't break
The best thing that I ever did was I punched my laptop in the screen and shattered it
because
It was pretty sweet
But it was pretty normie honestly because it was because I was like having a fight with my college girlfriend
You know because I was home for vacation and like we got mad at each other and I was so upset that I broke my laptop
Yeah, but
Walls where my dad had like gotten mad in a fight and just like punched holes through the wall like
Ben's done that Ben's the hole in the wall. I did I did kick a hole through our basement wall
Oh, it's my friend John who punched a hole in the wall. Yeah, okay different. Yeah, I kicked I kicked our wall in
Just a little bit
Because my friend who is a violent maniac who if we if he was here I do have one friend who might be less normie than me
In the sense that he is absolutely violently insane
And we'll like fight people for no reason and that kind of thing
That's like the clinical kind of non-norminess. Yeah
Yeah, there's so there's so many
Absorb his abnorminess. It's like jet me in the one. That's how it works. That's right
There's so many different axes upon which can be one can be normie or non-normie
Anime of all-time dimension w in which there are several axes in which
It's a big fan of yours too. What's that did you the friend of mine who's like super crazy
He's a big yeah, yes, he as well
But yeah, he put a hole in my uh in my in my bathroom door just by because he opened it with his elbow one time
Like just like slammed it with his elbow and broke it and I was like you're too strong
Because he's like a huge monster man like a giant fucking
Yeah, he's a Hulk dude
Is he one of these actually strong guys or did he no he worked out
He was like he was like a skinny little twink in high school
And then he like beefed the fuck up and became a monster. That's my now
He's like a psycho like vegan crazy man. Oh vegan too impressive. Okay. What the hell is this podcast about?
It's about fuck you
Hippo I was I was waiting for a chance for like a pause in the conversation to be like well
I think we've really said a lot on the subject of
Like
General I mean I
Think we've gotten the surprising like we've made it less cringy than it first seemed like it was I don't think it's
I just think it's silly because like we have that
Google doc of all the potential topics and like some of them are like actual topics and then in the middle of it
It just says fucking normies
I mean I mean I think we occasionally touched on some somewhat relevant subject matter
But for the most part we came to no conclusions. We don't understand
I
Stay together and find a place worth fighting for
I'm on the road
to normie city