But something happened on the way to the 20th century.
The profound, the inspiring, and the beautiful
were replaced by the new, the different, and the ugly.
Today, the silly, the pointless, and the purely offensive
are held up as the best of modern art.
It is they who champion graffiti and call it genius,
promote the scatological and call it meaningful.
It is they who, in reality, are the naked emperors of art,
for who else would spend ten million dollars on a rock
than think it is art?
Hello everyone, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I am the best guy ever.
Uh, I am French.
Uh, today we're joined by, uh, Lethal Aurora Mage.
I'm pushed again, but this time I'm the best.
First to the worst.
No, that's-
Oh wait, I said that last time.
Yes.
Oh, well, okay, debunked.
Uh, The Davoo is here.
This podcast emanates rich textures of aura, of satisfaction of the authority.
Ah.
Bzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzzz
All right, my name is Chris.
Tom Oliver.
Criticism.
Tom.
Oliver.
I just got flashbacks to my art history courses,
and I wanted to vomit all over my excessive microphone.
Disgusting.
You would have made art.
Yeah, clearly.
Oh, it would look like a- like a Pollock.
Uh, Ben Sates.
I'm I'm back with a vengeance
Indeed I missed one episode and I wanted and it ruined my whole life
My streak is broken
And muchy topics by committee rhymes with shitty
As you as you might be able to tell let's get right down to it our topic for today is
Monsters to everybody
It's the big one. It's the big one that no that was a joke that was art in itself postmodern art
It was meant to highlight how ignorant and stupid you the masses are for loving that so much
It's it's postmodernism modern art, but mostly postmodern art. That's what it is and to get down to the heart of the matter
What do you got for us?
Urban dictionary before we read from the Urban Dictionary. I'd like to read from Urban Dictionary occult edition
At at forum dot become a living God calm
Slash Urban Dictionary dash occult dash edition slash three four oh nine six
However, I cannot because there are only two entries one is for Yahweh and the other is for God
Okay, sure. Let's see what we got as our backup here. Okay Urban Dictionary
Postmodernism a term that you keep on hearing about in college and have to look up on Wikipedia
Basically says fuck it to the search for any intellectual conclusions. Oh my god. Yeah, more complete definition than I thought
I that's actually not terrible. That makes that's so that's the worst thing. I've ever had read to me. Well, all right
That was okay. That was definition to here's the top definition
Postmodernism is the ultimate lubricant
Invented by social sciences in order to fuck every concept and structure that humans ever came up with at the same time
It is used as a means for social sciences to penetrate one another
What dislike modern or what kind of person you have to be you have to be some sort of conservative God or or uncocked
Well, we I think it extends beyond just hard. It's like a whole
Mindset and philosophy that article that article sounds like it was written by maybe like an ex-professor
But who had like a drug problem or something and completely fried
But he's like he's like completely he's like completely burned out after he lost his tenure and he's like a shell of his former self
And he can barely string a sense together. He's definitely never lifted a pencil in their life
Definitely watched a lot of Jordan Peterson. That's that sounds like the guy that I think I think you're right
Listen, okay, but it behooves us because postmodernism and postmodern art exists as a response to modern arts saying like fuck that shit
Dude doesn't even it's not even real. So let me just read the definition of modern art as well
All right, Urban dictionary modern art a synonym
for bullshit
All right, it's actually nothing useful for modern art and urban dictionaries
Let me actually just read like the first sentence on the Wikipedia page. That's actually much much more helpful
So modern art includes artistic work produced during the period extended from blah blah blah the six that 1860s the 70s
1970s and denotes the style and philosophy of the art produced from that era
The term is usually associated with art in which the traditions of the past have been thrown aside in the spirit of
experimentation and it shows like some van Gogh starry night type stuff, which is very right
So part of what I intended to talk about is those scribble paintings like we were referencing Jackson Pollock if you
Don't know what we're talking about Google image search that and also. Oh, what's his name?
Yeah, oh, yeah, also the painter guy who paints just like painterly squares of various colors
Who's name always escapes me just search like wasn't in the velvet underground. What's his name?
Not that are you talking about Andy Warhol?
No, no, are you talking about that painting that's like it's like white and it has a bunch of black lines forming squares
And some of the squares are like red and summer. That's what that's what I did on my best appearance in the drawcast
Yeah, I drew modern art. Yeah, yeah, yeah
That guy so that's kind of the heart of what we're gonna talk about and the reaction to it
Now I'm just gonna like come right out with what I think is the crux of the problem
Which is the criticism and analysis of modern art remaining so
rigid traditionalist and
Classical see it's the reason why people often don't take it seriously when a professor comes up and tells you about how such
And such painting subverts the idea of
Art and subverts the idea of the establishment and authority
The reason why people don't take that seriously is it's coming from a professor a guy who went to college has tenure works in
The system and talks like the system and this is where modern art breaks down for me is when that because like I
Was like in a waiting room recently that had a bunch of modern art books
And I would always pick them up and think the images look cool
And then I want to read some analysis of it
So I go over to the paragraphs and I started reading and this is where my eyes start rolling like a fucking tumble dryer
Because it's trying to describe
Like post-modern art it's trying to describe subversiveness. It's trying to describe
Like like this escape from the traditionalist structures by very traditionally
Explaining it in a very literary way and it doesn't work when you try to employ this sort of
Tangible literary analysis to non tangible inspired art you end up with a bunch of vague sentences
Like what triggered Tom at the beginning of me introducing myself where they try to be like
Oh, it has this texture that implies this feeling of this idea, right?
Like we're it's like you're trying to analyze modern art the same way we analyze classical art where a lot of paintings were of like
Actual things and and paintings were inspired by Bible or other ideologies very explicitly
So so you could actually describe what the paintings actually are very like factually and
Then we get all these paintings that aren't supposed to mean anything technically and yet the analysts and the critics think they're still supposed to
Describe them in these tangible words and it just becomes really stupid and misses the point and makes the average consumer
Miss the point of the whole goddamn movement. I
Got one response to all that
Davoo is where are the fucking memes? Where are they where there wasn't well any means in there
I was looking for some means. I was browsing the the become a living god.com forums as I often do
So
So I'm searching for modern art and I can't find any topics about modern art
So I brought in my search to just art and unfortunately poor results the best thing I could find is this top is this
Thread on the topic of is it possible to learn martial arts from a demon?
The journey the jury
The jury's out on it. So I'm afraid that the become a living god.com has failed for the first time in history
Well, that sucks wait wait actually I have something to say that's relevant also
There is a great good. There is a great video. It is by the art assignment
You guys have ever seen the art assignment
Yeah, no, I have not okay. It's a YouTube series. It's like I think it I think it might be John Green's wife
Or something or someone that John Green knows I think it might be by PBS digital studios
Yeah, but it's it's the video called I could do that. Yeah. Yeah, I could do that. That's the right, okay
That's right. Okay. I haven't I haven't I haven't watched don't co-op my topic
I haven't watched it for a while
But it's about she's talking about how people say that like, you know
You look at a Jackson Pollock or a fucking drawing of squares or a toilet in a museum and you're like
I could do that anyone could do that and
You know the answer is like well sure you could but you didn't like and like it doesn't matter
Like whether you could replicate it. I said this just the other day and like a completely different kind
We were talking about business and entrepreneurs and I guess it's the same for art
It doesn't fucking matter if you could replicate the exact product that someone has made
Which you probably couldn't if you think so but even if you could it doesn't matter
Because the point is that you didn't and the point of this art was that it was made in this context and the context
Is what makes art meaningful even if you did it perfectly and you did in fact just recreate it
Well, then that's good. How does that make the art not good?
The artist does not claim that he is a god for making this piece of art
He wants to communicate an idea or yeah, right and you would just like something similar like like take for example like
Photography like photography is generally considered an art, right?
and at least you know, I guess it depends but like I
Mean for example, like I just watched Digi's new video on Fooley Cooley a little while ago and that was fine
But like there like there's a moment in there where Mamimi of course is this photographer and just at the at the last episode
There's a there's a moment where like now to in like all these crazy events that have happened now
It's does his iconic standing on the rubble holding Haruko's base. Oh, great takes the picture from behind great. He does it again
He does what no, no, this isn't the new Fooley Cooley. This is the he's talking about the original okay
I haven't seen the new. Yeah. No, he just does. I was saying that I just did it again
No, no, this is about the original even though the new ones are out which I should we should watch those at some point
Oh, yeah, but anyway, I mean just I guess I guess I guess I guess I have no choice. Yeah. Why not? Why not?
Yeah, okay
The point I was getting at was like, okay
So so Mamimi takes that picture and like no Mamimi did not like craft the entire situation to like
Generate all the artistry that's in that picture of like this ruined city of like a boy standing
Hopefully on this hill looking at his lost love and holding her base and what not remembering her
But like she did capture that moment in her art. Okay. Yeah. Yeah
The like the important thing there is that is that it was the image is curated, right?
Like the image is like what to what to include in the like Mamimi probably took like a thousand pictures
And she chose to show this one. Yeah, cuz it's the best most like that people when people talk about writing like writing is the same
Like like the act of writing
I think I think this might be a mr. B tongue quote
But he's not the only one who said it's like it's like the act of writing is the act of like creative exclusion
Yeah, selective exclusion to separate signal from noise
You have yeah separate signal from noise because you have a character and you have you know in your mind
If you know if you're most if most authors probably have like if not a full idea
But at least some idea of this character is like entire life story, right?
And this character has theoretically lived an entire life full of shit that could be remarked upon
But you as the author you are like selecting like where do I begin the story there by cutting off everything beforehand?
You know, what do I show or what do I describe? What do I choose not to describe?
And that's what you build your story out of and like photography is the same
You're you're you might yeah, you might not have created it
But you are still doing this the selective exclusion of like I won't take pictures of these things
I will take pictures of this because like my aesthetic sense tells me that this is a well-composed image and it and you know
It means what such-and-such part of it. I think
behind this mindset is
Like human jealousy in a way because when people say oh, I could have done that and you know
I would have been successful. I would have earned the money like I'm not saying like
People are bad for being jealous. It's natural people are just naturally jealous of things like they even did like a test
I think with kids like
Hold on it's not very relevant. It's a long story
Basically people prefer to
Rather than have someone else have more things to that both of them not have at all like, you know
Yeah, that's a thing. That's a thing. Yeah, so it's people are very sensitive to inequality, you know
Justified or not it makes them make some yeah, and like because this idea existed like oh
I had I possess the skill level that this person does but they're earning like they're banking off of it
The seal a lot more than I could ever, you know
I have I never thought about doing well and this it feels like
Like injustice in a way. Yeah, and you know, I think that's yeah, that's definitely a thing
It's like reputation is where the value in art comes from which is another video by the art assignment
They bring up that like yeah
Yeah, the the reputation of specific artists right is what actually drives the prices
But here's the thing that is also the case in other mediums such as live performance music
It costs like six hundred dollars for a ticket to the Rolling Stones or Paul McCartney or other such baby boomer era
Fucking bands that have been around for 40 years because their baby boomer fucking fan base is sitting on tens of thousands of savings
They need to spend in a couple of years before the diagnosis start rolling in
The dreaded diagnosis right
Like they're just able to pump themselves full of fucking money and just pump all that money out of their fans because everyone
I mean, I have to go see the Rolling Stones right you have to so and it's not like some other band where the tickets are say 60 bucks
Let's not like the Rolling Stones in anybody's opinion could have like core progression and lyrical depth that is 10 times greater
It has to do with reputation
Okay, okay, so yeah, it has to do with reputation and
Alright, so I guess someone who doesn't agree with modern art or whatever as like a concept would probably not agree with this statement either
But to me this is like core and I think and I
To me this is obvious, but you know, whatever and that is that like skill like it's it's sad to say
But skill really doesn't matter like in terms of like what art is meaningful and like what people respond to yeah
I mean, it's not that it doesn't matter because you have you need skill
Sometimes you need skill to execute an idea but not always and if you execute something that means something to people and affects people
Then it doesn't matter how quote-unquote skilled you are to two artists can be equally quote-unquote skilled
And it makes no difference if one of them use that skill to make something that people responded to and the other one didn't the reason
Why skill matters is because skill can help better
You know a communicate to the audience what the idea is so it doesn't really matter
How good your skill is as long as you can communicate the same ideas or statement within your art
Yeah, and the skills will just help you do that
So if you want to say, you know, like communicate the idea well aren't humans beautiful isn't the human form beautiful
So much should be good to have a lot of skills specifically the male
Yes, I quickly want to say I just quickly it's like the state as the saying like
Don't work hard work smart. Yeah. Yeah, it also applies to art
My three case studies for what Ben was talking about about it's more about what you're expressing than your skill, right?
First of all, there's fucking
M. Night Shyamalan, right who happened to make his first movie played at his strengths, right?
It's a movie where it seemed like his limited filmography
Which one is that the sixth sense like that that's where it seemed like it seemed like it was a stylistic choice to make the camera
So fucking slow
Which it was but then come last airbender it turns out Shyamalan is just bad at shot composition and moving a camera, right?
Other good example is George Lucas who like happened to have this
He has a great creative core that just has to be
Roped in to but by producers. So once he was allowed to do whatever he want that didn't work, right?
So he has good ideas. He had something really great to express. He just isn't very skilled
So my counter example is zoom someone who cannot fucking draw but
Can aesthetic more than not familiar with zoom. He makes the Toho games, right? Yeah
Like lots of video games espouse the idea that sheer graphical horsepower is how you make a game look good
Where is in other games that are all about art design say no good art is good
And then Toho basically says good art isn't good aesthetic is good
So he's someone who plays to his strengths brilliantly like he let's
I don't fucking are you sure that it's more that people I mean
Who would argue that it's like it's good that the art of zoom of being bad is like better
It's not good necessarily the point is that he he leverages what skills he does have to his favor to great effect
I don't need to do is communicate the idea those skill
Yeah, yeah those skills are not in the artwork itself
But like the art that he does make
Communicates these ideas that are built right through like the the gameplay and the dialogue and the music and whatever else has has for
Instance zoom is trying to communicate that
Or at least I assume I've not played me no to home games
But the art I've seen is cute girls are cute and he's not having a lot of you know artistic skill
But he can't communicate that with his limited skill now could he now couldn't ask so now could he do this better with even greater skill?
Of course he could make a really cute girl in actuality and you would be more convinced of that
But it doesn't mean that just because he does not have the skill
He is not communicated the idea that you girls are cute. I was gonna say isn't toho just like a lot of wifes
The whole point of toho is that if you've it has anyone played it
I have played I have played like one or two toho's
Okay, I've been playing toho. It's just that you go through like you play as like a rainbow or a Marissa
Whatever it is you play is just like a character with very little English damn it
Okay, whatever you're just like some girl with little personality
But you're like have a kind of cute design and you just encounter girls that say very little
But they say enough to get a hint towards their personality and my theory is this is given
I this is I know everyone believes I think it's that just like having so little presented about the characters
I mean just a couple hints about the personality and then you fight them in a cool boss fight
And they have a cute design that gave everyone such a blank check to fill in as much as they wanted for like
Oh, that this is why that character is Moe lol
She's such a one of my favorite youtubers back in the day Digibroni MLP compared the toho fandom to the fandom of the pony
MLP background characters at least circa seasons one two and three yeah four seasons five
But but but okay, okay, it's not enough. It's not enough to just give a blank check cuz like
Nothing like saying nothing would be giving a blank. Well, they give you enough. Yeah
So like there's definitely there's something here that makes people want to like fill the back well like here's a thing
Here's there's a character. There's a character whose name I forget. I'm gonna see if I can find it
It's it's one of the toho girls and the only thing I know about this toho girl
Is that she?
Canonically is is actually tiny like the size of a mouse she wears a sake cup as a big ol hat
And she fights with a needle that is some like legendary needle sword of like this diminutive race
Is she is she hollow night?
She I mean it sent she was hollow night before hollow night was cool. I forget her name someone please it's like haku-jaku
Her name is actually hold hold on
I'm fucking googly to see if I can find it. Oh, it is. Okay, Sukuna
Shin myo Mario Sukuna Shin yo Mario. That's her name and she is adorable
I'm like a fucking picture of her look at her so it's just and my point is just by her design being cute and these basic facts
About her being a cutie and being diminutive and from this weird. She's like a princess or something look at her
Like this was enough to make me like this is not my favorite toho character just because of these basic facts
She's she's cool. That's and I think that's what's happened. I think that's what happened like everybody
Why is she also the games are fun? Why is there a hammer? Why is there a hammer sized for a mouse? Ben?
Do you remember Secret of Mana?
Yeah, remember that item you could get the flammie drum the flammie drum, right? That's right
That's right. Yeah, or no, there's like a mini mallet or something that turns you big or small
Yeah, there's like a there's a Japanese folklore thing. It's like a hammer that resizes you and I think that's what that is
That is a fucking
funny thing
Folklore
Luigi games too, right with the hammer up to squish fucking it is definitely a thing that I have seen in other games
But I specifically I remember it from Secret of Mana, right? Okay. Well, so guys, this is okay
I think we've made our point that like art does not require
Like the artist to be the most skilled person so to that end. Let's get back to like
I mean, wait, wait, wait case and point fucking
Tails gets trolled. Well, yeah, don't watch my fucking lecture idiots. Well, I just want to plug his legs
He's the he's the least he's the least talented. Well, that's not true, but you know, he's clearly laserbot. Please come on our show
He's not the least talented, but you know, he's like there are better artists out there
But yet the story that he makes is compelling as fuck and it doesn't matter
Is it if it were drawn better quote unquote better? Would it be a better comic? No, so there you go
Well, and in fact the low quality of it enhances the majority of it and the comedy and I mean you get to see him improve
Which is always interesting like I mean for me seeing an artist improve over the course of their long-form work is like
Oh, it's fucking me. Mm-hmm. Okay, so I have a question
I've been listening for the last 25 minutes and and I just my my question is I rage building
No, no, no
Because my problem is that like I just as much as I want to say that like modern art is gay
I just need it like that's just the end of the story. I just hate it. I just hate it
Because I and it I'm glad we have a contrarian. I'm glad we have someone with the opposite of modern art
Oh post-modern art, which are we talking about? I'm gonna say I'm not gonna be so obtuse as to blanket statement in a tire
Genre it's just like that kind of art the kind of art we're talking about I understand it gets trolled
I know not tails get trolled but like like in a gallery setting and stuff. I
Okay, I just I don't find it appealing to me personally and I you know as much as I'd like to make a more intellectual case
I really don't have one but my question is is that for the last 25 minutes
We have you've all come to the conclusion that you skill doesn't really matter at the end of the day
And it's just you know people like what they like or whatever
So how do we reconcile that fact with the fact that we shit on awful youtubers?
I got it. I know how Tom. I know how Tom because we distinguish between
Art that is itself valuable and meaningful and it does not matter how that art came into existence
Whereas when we're viewing the artist when we're talking about who the artist is it does matter how they achieve the thing
They're trying to make which is why even though the room for example is what?
Yeah, I was just thinking of all time
I would never say that I think that Tommy Wiseau is one of the greatest filmmakers of all time
I think that's the important distinction here the artist separate, okay, but the problem is when we're talking about
Modern and post-modern art the people and the culture they do say that yes
Jackson Pollock is one of the greatest artists of all time. Hi. Well, he has made a lot of those it is repeatable
What he's done? Well, here's okay
I'd like to like make it clear exactly where I'm coming from on this and this it comes from something
I believe it was a year and a half ago when uh
We in the PCP chat talked about that art assignment video called I can do that because we were watching it because we had just come off
the coals of watching this Paul Joseph Anderson video where he's just like
Look at all these stupid paintings. This one's just a square. This one is just a bunch of scribbles
It's so stupid these people shouldn't be so famous and we're kind of like rolling our eyes like yeah
Yeah, we get it we get it, but then the moment where it goes from and that's uh is when he goes
This is why we need
Objective standards and art to make sure people like this can be stopped and it's like oh hold on there, buddy
Paul Joseph Anderson, that's the video game guy, right?
Paul Joseph Watson Watson. Oh shit. I'm getting my Paul Joseph
I'm not sure you said what Watson at least that I don't know am I crazy am I crazy? Okay?
I don't know the audience will judge anyway. Yeah, the YouTube guy who has the big fucking chipmunk face that he puts in the middle
Of the camera all the time. I feel like he used the fish island or he has the world's most bulbous face that guy
That's what yeah, um he uh
Yeah, so like he made the case that we need objective standards to stop these people and that's where it's like, okay
This is no longer an opinion thing. This is now a fucking good like socio-political thing
We have to maintain objective standards of quality and talent in order to discern the value of anything and
Munchie you just got done watching the clap the modern classic
Why is modern art so bad video by Prager University, which I just did a 40 minute rebuttal video to on my main channel
But now I'm here in this podcast a shit on me even more like it's from this guy
Who's like probably a Christian very like an old funny that he conservative type guy and he's a painter
Probably Christian right and like I went to his I went to his website
All right, Munchie over here
I went to this guy's website to look at his art and you can tell that he's like into classic style art
But he's not that good at it it ends up looking more like sci-fi pulp novel covers
But you can tell he's a classicist and in this video he makes the case for classic art being better than modern art
Which is fine at all except he then shits on the idea of
Beauty is in the eye of the beholder and that like shit is subjective
And that we need to bring back objective standards in order to stop these people the great art historian
Jacob Rosenberg wrote that quality and art is not merely a matter of personal opinion
But to a high degree objectively traceable without aesthetic standards
We have no way to determine quality or inferiority as if it's somehow like a drag on you
That scribble paintings and square paintings are popular like like you don't need to
Right, you don't need to kick out art
You don't like to make room for yourself like make art that you think is good
And make it good enough to get your own fucking attention
I I I think what he's responding to is the the the culture that has come to embrace this thing that he finds to be, you know
Unvaluable and well
I I literally do not understand what you're saying. So you're saying why do we think why why do we shit on bad youtubers
When we praise modern art, uh, I mean not so it's it's just that if you're saying that the skill doesn't matter
Right. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. And the execution matters. I'll tell you why
Because it's not a matter of the skill being bad that makes youtubers bad
It's that the art they make is terrible
But we do not like the art that they produce and and that that statement that you're saying implies implicitly
That that modern art is bad that we do not like it and we're just saying
Oh, you don't need skill to in you and making bad art is okay
When we're saying that you don't need a skill to make art that we like and resonate with we like marinara or at least I do
I like my art so I can explain away why the skill doesn't matter and I can explain and make an intellectual point about it
I'm not saying that
modern art is bad and therefore
The skill does not matter because you can make bad art and it doesn't matter the point of the matter is
Simply I like modern art and I don't like youtuber. Uh, you know shitty youtube reviews
And that's fine. You don't have to like you don't have to like modern art or anything
Okay, I think I want to say like I
Quite dislike modern art. I will say but I will but I you know
I I recognize why I dislike it
I recognize why I dislike it and I'm fine with people creating it. I you know
I'm free to dislike it and they're free to create it
There's no issue here between me and the people who create modern art
Well mage that is the you have cowardice in your convictions
You should demand that the world conform to your expectations. Therefore you're you you're either a coward or lying
Which is it mage? Which is it?
Anything less is a kid
Okay
Nate
Yes, I'll just bring this up and I don't know if we'll have anything interesting to say about it, but whatever
Come on. It's me. Of course. I will do you know
Did you know you probably did know that we have a
Like a second cousin or a cousin once removed or whatever that is a like a
Supposedly a pretty successful like somewhat famous abstract painter. I believe is his name winston. His name is winston
That's right. Yep. I mean should we like link him or should we say like his website or something?
Is it winston saint or winston bestman? I'm gonna lean towards no
That's a good question. I mean towards no and then maybe we'll add in the description or something. Okay, whatever
It it doesn't matter. Uh, yeah in winston. It's winston the girl picture him
I went to i'm at his i'm at his website and i'm just looking at his art and I gotta say you know kind of like with jackson paul like
I don't really get it
Although okay, sometimes I find I'm looking at these and some of the aesthetics are good and I'll be like, oh, that's a nice like collection of colors
That's a nice thing for the most part. I'm like
I don't like it
Okay, but but maybe maybe the point maybe the point is just you know
You you combine colors and whatever and like
You know like most of them will not appeal to most people
But some of them will appeal to some people and you sometimes sometimes you just get lucky and find your audience of someone
Who is like, oh that looks neat and then they buy it and I don't know
We're behind modern art as I understand it was a rejection of these styles and forms that had been used in classical art
Up to that point. Whereas that guy in that video that prager you video was talking about how like no like
Images used to like capture beauty and convey grandiose messages and use technical skill and these are the things we celebrate
But but like our boy our boy w here is like
The big w. Uh, he's he's like he's just attempting to like
Throw images out there and I guess like see what sticks and I'm sure you made like a lot of art
I think that's probably what painters do. I think that's probably what
I quickly want to say about the you know, the whole skill doesn't matter thing now
The thing is like skill definitely helps
In many ways and in many in many times
However, it's not like it's it's not mandatory because sometimes people who are very good at
Executing things can just catch lightning in a bottle. So to speak and
That's I was actually going to ask that is it possible. Is it possible that skill?
Holds you back from experimentation and that you're and that it that no human's ability could ever rival like the kind of
Electric
Stumble into if you're just if you're just trying random shit hold on no
So one of the things that keep in mind is that one of the things I've by the way just for fun
I posted the links to winston stuff in the chat and I checked out we will decide we will decide if we're gonna post
We will judge winston
This has obvious skill and intent in it. You think something good. Yeah. Yeah a lot of it
There is skill there not saying. Oh, yeah, this is really nice. I like these colors
I like how the colors are mixed some of them
I do like there are definitely ones here that are the first paint to get the very beginning has this like cool
Like fucking like circle in the middle. Yeah. Yeah, that's the one talk about potential images that won't be in the
video
No, let's what we'll show this first one because it's not now. Let's edit this in we'll edit this in yeah, so
So I had a comment
That was me stretching by the way not me being frustrated by ed people
So I had a comment say I grew up
Hating Rothko mark Rothko until I saw one of his paintings in a museum
Like eye to eye in person, right?
Mark Rothko is the guy who paints just like squares, right? And it's like what the what the I remember
Paul joseph watzkerson
Specifically calling out Rothko. He's just he just drew a red square. What the fuck right thing is when people like analyze mark
Rothko when you read up on him apparently what he does is he layers his painting his paint over and over
And over again
It gives it a sense of depth that cannot be captured in photography and then transmitted on to a digital screen
You have to see it in person and when you do
People say the images feel like they they become like three dimensional the images feel like they're floating in space because they're so
richly textured, right
there is something that he is doing there and
uh
Interesting thing about both Rothko and Pollock is when you research their histories
They both started off doing actual painting like that where their technical skill is obviously much more clear where they're drawing people or stuff
Like they both started out, you know pretty post-modernist
They weren't like classicists
But they both started drawing stuff that you obviously could not imitate right
They both started off with sketches and drawing things and then devolved their
complexity more and more and more as they continued to experiment and basically just got to the very heart of why they really wanted to paint
Right, they just went to down to the bread and butter of what they actually had been wanting to express and took 10 years
Of stylistic development in order to get there
And what did they want to express right?
Well, then when you try to explain that when you hear what other people explain
This goes back to my problem at the beginning where they try to explain it using these very tangible
almost objective terminology
Like, you know, it's supposed to express your the human condition of the feeling of the thought of the feeling of the whatever, right?
uh, I think
Yeah, um, and another thing is that it is definitely true like okay
I had someone I had another comment saying, you know, if someone told me they're an artist and then they showed me Pollock
I wouldn't take them seriously
Right like he doesn't take he doesn't regard Pollock as real art. He's like, yeah, you know
Most are you know, you have to actually consider what you're doing and have a point in a theme and skill and effort, right?
So what I said was okay go to ms paint pick whichever tools you like
Select four colors that you think are good
And then use whatever tools you want on ms paint to make a pattern with those colors
The pattern cannot be symmetrical. It has to be like it has to look chaotic
But the colors have to be evenly distributed. There can't be too much red on this corner
There can't be too little blue in the middle
There it has to be evenly distributed while also being chaotic and he he came up with an image that was you know
Shitty looking but it did fulfill what I requested and he's like, okay. That was kind of interesting, right?
And I'm like, there you go, right? This isn't something you can do effortlessly the the video. Uh, why is modern art so bad?
This fucking funny duddy said he would go up to his art students because I guess he's a professor
and he would show them a picture of a
A Jackson Pollock painting and he said analyze this Jackson. Yeah analyze this Jackson Pollock painting
And explain why it is good
And then they would say oh, it's deep. It's bold and then he'd be like it's actually a close-up of my studio apron
It's just a bunch of smears. You've been duped
Uptrolled
Right now. First of all, we'll just over
Congratulation people have found art within your studio. Yeah, good job. You should sell that for money, right?
So we'll just I'll just like sort of pass anything the fact that he presented with them a false question
I think I think that what that says is not anything about Pollock
I mean, it just it's just that hold on. Hold on. I think I think can be aesthetically pleasing even if there's no
Like there's so many things wrong with it though. I've been pouring over it for a fucking week in my mind
First of all, he specifically phrases it as analyze this Jackson Pollock painting
And explain why it is good
He's sure he said it was a Jackson Pollock. Are you sure about that? He said that he tricks them. He lies
Listen to the video. He did lie. So he did lie. Okay, and he specifically says explain
Why it is good. He doesn't say tell me what you think of it, right? Yeah
Now
Right, that is a bit loaded. That is when he presents when he presented the video when I first watched it, right?
He didn't explain it to the audience of the of the video that it was going to be a trick
I see the Jackson Pollock painting and I'm like, oh, I don't care for it. It looks stupid. I don't I don't get it, right?
It's dull. Oh, yes. It's kind of wise devout wise devout knew better. Yes. Thank god
Here's the thing, right? I didn't fall for the trick because I
I don't have a fucking art professor telling me the objective standard should be a fucking thing
Right. Exactly. I don't let people tell me what the fucking thing
This guy fucking lies. This guy fucks dude. This guy fucks
Yeah, he he is from a position of authority and telling them what you say exactly he didn't ask them to express themselves
He told them to say why it's good for people. So the people there, you know, they're trying to come up with reasons why it's good
They might not necessarily like it, but they're trying to fulfill
Right, that's the big problem with that whole thing is because he's in a position of authority
And this is this is like, but this is this this touches on something that I think
Because like I'm not a huge fan of post modern modern art whatever but like people can make it
I don't give a shit. It doesn't bother me. What I don't like
Is the culture
Around it because I think there's there's a lot of like the problem that I had in my experience because like
I went to museums during art school and shit and I looked at all this stuff
And that was like fine. Like I wasn't super engaged in it. That was fine
What I hated was the students and the teachers that liked it because there was this culture of of of of
I'm going to project why this is so good
And then everyone is going to like the public
Kind of looks up to these people authority like the people in the galleries and stuff and they're like, oh
They know better than me. So I'm going to try and like pull the meaning out of it
Even though I don't I'm going to lie to myself
To conform to social standards
Everything everything that I have heard about the I'm no expert but everything that I have heard about the modern like fine art
painting community
Suggest to me that what it pretty much is is just a bunch of rich people
Are bored and decide that such and such is the new thing
And then it becomes really and then it becomes really expensive
So they can all so they can all spend their money on it and then talk about why that culture is probably really fucked
But so again, I want to reiterate my platform here is to shoot down people who who want to elect the god
The great leader of objective standards to overthrow this culture
It's basically like finding the great communist leader to overthrow the capitalist system. It's a very very ill-conceived idea
Well when divu earlier mentioned about how he rolled his eyes when he read about people trying to describe or explain the paintings and stuff like that
I think like for me personally
I know why that would hurt me a lot because like whenever I you know do art and stuff and
I I would try to like I try to imagine people trying to analyze my art on that level
It would it just so would annoy me because they're probably going to get it wrong because there's not that much thought put into paintings
It's usually like in art. It's usually a lot of emotions and not a lot of reason
I could be wrong. There could be a lot of people who touchfully put every single dot or whatever, but well major
I'm glad to say that
I wanted to I wanted to raise a counter argument to some of this because okay guys
Uh, we've been we've been shitting a lot on modern art and postmodern art. You know general not everybody, but no, we have
No, we haven't we've been defending it
Tom, I mean tom has okay fair enough. I haven't done anything. I just said I didn't like it
I specifically opened with I don't like it. Okay, you know what I'll say to those people out there who who find it
Invaluable or in what not? Here's what I'm saying. Invaluable means it's valuable kind of like inflammable means it's flammable
God damn it. I can't catch a break today. All right. Uh, listen
Imagine that you are jackson pollock and you're in your studio and I'm saying this I'm looked at
I looked up pictures of jackson jackson pollock when he's working on his shit
Imagine you are out there every day working for like eight hours, which I'm projecting. I'm assuming he does this
You know, he's dead now, but whatever and you're in your studio and every day you spend all day throwing paint on a canvas
And trying new techniques to achieve more interesting effects
And you do this and your art your art gallery is filled with like things that you have
Tested these new techniques on that you have been slaving a way to try to make this thing happen
And then you pick the best of the best that you think are the most evocative convey the most
Just you can't even describe what it conveys. It just is interesting to look at and then and and yes
And you sell for a tons of money because they're popular and then you have people say well, I could have done that
Well, I could have done that, you know, what after like a lifetime spent honing this craft of experiment
I'm sure there's interviews of him talking about it because it's not like this was something that like came up as a criticism
After the fact this is sort of like what got him popular was people huddling around being like is this even like is this
It's funny that we use pollock as an example though because jackson pollock became famous not even because people liked his art
It was because he was from new york and he looked like an all-american kind of guy and like at that
No, seriously at that time the uh, like the whatever art movement he was a part of it
It was like big in like france in europe and people like in new york
They wanted it to be american so there was a photo of jackson pollock wearing a cowboy hat and it looked stereotypically american
So they specifically chose him to make him popular and pull that movement back to america
So he was the k-pop star of his era basically that tom that tom that is really really really depressing
Um
Guys who the fuck
Thought it was an okay idea to change the topic on the day of recording gib you weren't even here
Why would we have to worry about what you think you're not even here piss?
This is the topic. This is the thing I have the most to say about and the topic was changed an hour late
And you didn't show up on time. Well, you're here now. What can we do?
He didn't think that this would be the topic. So he didn't have a reason to show up. He didn't have a reason to show
Yeah, that's fair. That's no, that's fair. Yeah, but yeah, so now that you're here. Are you recording?
Oh, oh, oh, you're oh, this is a topic you want to talk about. Oh, absolutely. Yeah, youtube alternatives was a piece of shit topic
I didn't want to do it
Agreed and this is the the most
I'm so mad. I don't this should never ever happen. Well, why why you're here now
I'm angry that it has happened and I'm gonna clip the mic right now. That's what I'm doing
To for brevity's sake, I'll just say my general top like stance on modern art. It's good
Jackson Pollock is shit and I don't like him
But that's where did you hear what we were saying about Jackson?
I jumped in and you were talking about him and he always gets brought up because
He rides the line some say
The the way I view art
Modern art or otherwise is that if it's good, I like it and if it's not it sucks
And the fact that it's modern doesn't have anything to do with us
Yeah, I think Jackson Pollock is probably much better seen in person than uh, you know, fia fucking digital
Yeah, media whatever
There's a painting downstairs in my in like a little book nook
Near our porch and it is I mean, it's just a bunch of fucking colors
Maybe I'll take a picture of it and like upload it and it can go on the screen
Yeah, that's just it's just a bunch of colors and like there's some like blotches of like silver paint on it in like squares
And like, you know, it's whatever it doesn't it doesn't mean anything
But but the colors are deep and rich and it's like these beautiful jewel tones like kind of coming out of like a kind of black
sort of general black
Area and there's these just the silver the silver
Square is just kind of like cut through there and they kind of like fade at some of the corners
And it's like it's like the thing has been stamped with like a spiral like stamp or something
So it has this like this weird like like tactile like ridges to it
And I love this fucking painting because it's got like it's really just textural and like beautiful in those colors
I know that we've been exposing our ignorance by by just fucking mentioning like Pollock constantly
But he's just the one that I happened to like get treated about him. I'm super ignorant
He's well Pollock is emblematic like okay. I don't I don't know that much
I couldn't name that many like painters of this style honestly
But Pollock is emblematic as someone who is like basically all you know all aesthetic and no like no concrete like like
Subject matter right right now
That's one of the things that people brought up as one of the painting's strengths
Is that there are no like centerpieces in his paintings where your eyes are definitively drawn to which is actually
A lot harder than you think so this guy in my comment section who I I challenged to do something sort of like a Pollock
What he ended up doing was he made a whole bunch of very definitive shapes that he himself expressed
Uh, dislike with because they drove him nuts right the thing about Pollock is that they're so
Interwoven and all the shapes are so minimal and they're in themselves that there's just no beginning or end to his painting
I'm gonna I'm gonna contest that because most of his paintings are on canvas which have edges
So there's going to be a middle point
How like like if you if you want to take it to to a degree where it's like
Where does the art begin and end? He should just take like get a paint like bomb grenade and throw it into a room
Yeah
So the last thing I'll mention about Pollock. I swear to god is is yeah the the guy who did the the fucking apron meme
prank bro
Someone in my comments also mentioned that that fucking apron does not in any way look like a Jackson Pollock painting
His apron is a bunch of fucking smudges
And the smudges are of way too many colors all turning into a big brownie mess
And they're mostly cornered in the upper left corner, right Jackson Pollock's paintings are
splatter paintings
Not smudges with very limited well considered colors and are very evenly distributed
I so like it's not just random. I knew that it was not a painting. It was something like some sort of goading
I I I had something to say about that because I I saw you that what you linked it before debut
And I watched it and I'm like, yeah, this guy this guy's a fucking silly billy
But the thing he has about like art students
Faking that they're smart about things is definitely something that happens and a lot of people in the art world
Just sort of nobody knows what art is or what is like
Correct
But people there's this general idea that there is something correct
So people have to you know pretend constantly and they get wrapped up in their own like weakness like oh, yes
It's it's inspiring. It's this and that but they don't actually know what they're saying. I want to contest that
I I have uh, okay
This is we we've been we've frankly wasted a ton of our viewers in our time here because these are the facts of the matter
All right classical art modern art post modern art
They have one thing in common and it's that they're all equally worthless. All right, the best art
The best art is that that which uh, uh, achieves some
Real world impact and that is why the greatest the greatest artwork that was ever made was literally the uncle sam
I want you for the us army poster. That is the greatest piece of artwork
Could we just have one episode where you don't devolve into retardation one episode? No
I refuse that call. This is what about Aaron and me. What about gran lugen?
Well, okay, there is something to be said for inspirational stuff that that uh, that that conveys some larger truth
Uh, it adjoys more people point up and point for what?
My favorite thing is not about
like
Practical effect like like art is why not. Why what's wrong with art that it's not about that is my question
my ganda
Yeah, like you're like, no, that's okay. That was effective as propaganda, but that doesn't mean that it succeeds as art
I mean, maybe it does. The thing about that is that the art was not responsible for people joining them the the military
That that uncle sam was extremely it was provocative extremely. Yeah, but the thing is that's not the sole reason people join the military
That's not the sole. I mean like the flat the american flag is more in the context
American flag is more of a thing and then also like
Just advertising and like pushing like yeah people talking about it and you know speeches that the president said
Those are all equally going towards the same goal. You can't say that that poster is the art that made it all happen
Probably most of the classical art is the most classical art. I believe is propaganda for christianity, right?
Yeah, that's that's right. It depends like a majestic and inspiring. No, generally to celebrate
Well, well, how do you apply propaganda to that? I mean, you know
Well propaganda is it's made with us with the intent of you know, fucking
I don't know doing something. Well, I guess if you're like a really religious person and you make an art just because you love
Jesus so much that isn't immediately propaganda like I think the intent
Yeah, but with this fucking commissioned by the church for you to paint in their fucking buildings
It's obviously like trying to make the building more inviting
I I mean, I guess you could argue that that is their building that like where that I mean they are already down with Jesus
So like they're not trying to convince. No, they're trying. Well, no, they bring fucking people
That's how Christianity works. That's literally how the Catholic church writes. What's monkey's favorite thing about Nate?
I want to hear
My my favorite my favorite thing about Nate is that his two modes are completely memeing and no sincerity and then
Trying to have philosophical
Debates those two go together so well, dude. I gotta tell you they really
And then and then when he breaks out the insightful ideas on the podcast he says them in the most
Obviously outrageous and me me way that no one could ever possibly leave them
But then just keeps presenting them over and over again like that and then everyone has to slowly
Stop chuckling and be like well, Nate. That's retarded. And then I don't what are you talking about?
What are you saying post modern art? All right, like what post modern art specifically is is like look at this toilet
I'm calling it art. I submit like ooh gotcha
You are celebrating this thing because I got you all mixed up in your fucking head to be like, oh, that's art
But secretly I knew that it's just a fucking toilet. It's nothing you you fools
I tricked you like so it's basically it's just saying that like art is bullshit
But but my question is what is more valuable about classical art that like guys like that guy in that video are like celebrating
I agree. Okay. I think okay. Here's here's my theory. Tell me if I'm wrong and if there's a tangent final stop
But it's like I feel like what guys like this guy are saying is
He thinks that like a world where classical art is celebrated and made more
Is like better because we've got like expectations for like what beauty is and like what the world is and I can understand
Is the point someone like that is trying to really he just likes them
Yeah, yeah classical art
If you wanted if you wanted to do something like Michelangelo or da Vinci that requires
years of study
And which obviously he respects obviously he can not imitate. I looked at his paintings. They're not that good
Right. So like I think I think and like there's while you can't argue objective standards
There is no arguing that objectively it takes more time study and effort
To be a Michelangelo than it is to put a signature on a used toilet and put it in a gallery
And I think people if you stop looking at it at that level
Then I think a lot of people that's where they stop the analyzation. It's just like, yeah, this takes more effort
Therefore, it's better for a great another great counter example. There's this one guy
I don't remember what he's called or what his his comic was called, but he has this youtube video called
Oh, shit
The main title is something like how to not waste time on your art but the subtitle that you oh
Is the guy who's like he he's making a video how it took like 10 years to make his comic because he kept putting like
Insane line arts in his background. He did the comic about his trip to Japan, right?
Yeah, the subtitle of this video is from a guy who spent 13 years drawing a comic where yeah, he he used like
He's yeah 13 years drawing a three volume comic
So it's like four or five years per volume right and he explained and if you look at it
It's not that impressive like it's just it's just black and white like cartoony art
It's not like he like recreated some high-level mangaka or anything
It's just a guy's name. The guy's name is lars martinson. Uh, if anyone wants to look him up
It's a good video
Yeah, yeah, because because basically he explained that it took so long
Because he decided to use like he wanted it to look like certain styles
So he used like certain tools and pens and like inks that are like a pain in the fucking ass
and he also
He made all shadows hatching for yeah cross hatching decided to make that
Which takes super long and he drew every background
He never reused a background and sometimes he would have a very busy image
Even when it didn't need to be in the context of the story
So there you go
That's a good example of like putting effort and that you don't get your money's worth from it
Right kids remember this do not be precious about your projects
Get it done and get the next one rolling and you will you will get better art in the end than you would have
Just be precious forever to change be open to failure be open to failure. Yeah. Yeah, and yeah, you know
It's important. It's important. So like um
Oh people like Pollack fucking and other people like Rothko, right?
It is true that it didn't take as much work because like what had to go into it for consideration is a lot quicker
Right and you can see like Pollack in his studio that they have documentaries of him
He's obviously focusing pretty fucking hard like he's not just being random
But the point is he did make hundreds of those styles of paintings in the span of a decade and so did Rothko
I believe and so it's like, okay, clearly. This isn't as difficult to make right the thing is though
They made hundreds of paintings like the prolificity does count for some those like the paintings are not an accident
Like even even if an individual like okay, it's kind of like photography like you're you're you might be capturing a moment
That just happened to happen. Okay. Yeah, do you know there's like there's like a grand total like don't interrupt me. I will destroy you
You're making hundreds and hundreds of these splatter paintings or whatever
And then you know, you're finding your techniques and and you know, you're you're you're ending up with all these products
And you know, sometimes you have you might have a happy accident and something looks really good
And then maybe a hundred other times it looks like crap and then you take the good ones and you're like like this one
Looks really good. It's got some visually is interesting going on
So, you know, I'm gonna present this one to my fucking fans or whatever
You know, it's selective exclusion
Curation helpful in this curation is the ultimate art form perhaps perhaps so
You could argue that everything is curation, I guess, but but it's like
What I have found is very helpful in this process is sometimes when I'm recording a video
I'll do a bunch of takes. I do this with we got it wasn't just everything. I'll do a bunch of takes of a line
I'll do like a motion several times and like I find more often than not and I'm expand this in a second
But it's like more often than not
It's not one that I expected to be the good one that when I've got it in the editing bay
And it's time to to make this part of the final product
I look through the clips and I I pick one of them and it's not like in that one moment where I did it
I had some brilliant insight necessarily, you know, maybe I did something different
But it's just that like oh that one happened to go better
And so I pick that one and by doing that for like every take throughout the video
You get the best of the best of the best for the whole thing
And you know, like that is the process by which you produce something that's really good
And I mean, yes, you can be precious with everything and do takes to get them perfect
And you're like that was the one but like this is another
Another curation form of makes it good. What are you just saying not to worry about it and just get it out there?
And I was saying you do everything five times and no, no, no
No, listen what I'm saying is what I'm saying is I there's nothing wrong
If you if you're not sure if something's coming out good or bad
Don't just accept that it's bad like there's a level of degrees here. You need to accept doing five takes of something
Uh, if like for example, if I'm doing like an intro to we Agua like they're they're very random and chaotic
And I just make whatever the fuck up off the top of my head
But I will do it several times because I'll know that like I probably won't get it like looking perfect one time
But if I have five to work with it's it takes like, you know five minutes as opposed to one minute to record
And I give myself that much more likelihood of having the material I need to work with to make it acceptable in the end
So, you know, did you know that Stanley Kubrick when filming
Dr. Strange Love or how I learned to stop worrying and love the bomb
How that movie is famous because everyone acts like a goofball in it
None of the actors knew that that was how the movie was going to be
During the entire process of filming Kubrick said, oh, yeah. Well, let's have some
Improvised takes on the script here
So I'm just gonna film like sort of us doing the script
But goofy just to kind of you know, like like grease the wheels loosen up a bit and don't worry guys
All of you Hollywood actors you take yourself very seriously
We will then film the serious version
Don't worry and literally told none of them
They had to show up to the fucking premiere to find out that he used all the goofy takes
Similarly to how he actually swapped out the soundtrack for 2001 a space Odyssey near the end and didn't tell the guy who made the original version
That that's great
And that adds to my point because it's entirely possible that Kubrick didn't realize he was going to do that until the editing process
Uh, I'm pretty sure he did no Kubrick is evil. Kubrick was an evil evil man who deceived everyone for the sake of his movies
Maybe he did maybe he did that's fine
But okay, I'm gonna pretend that he didn't do it on purpose and that he did in the editing bay because here's my point
And and what I'm saying is like a lot of the times when I've got when I when I'm just like
Ah, fuck it. I just need to get this thing done and I film the materials and I put it in the editing bay
That's when I'm able to be honestly like my most creative and
Giving yourself the tools to proceed and get something done. Just it allows you to play with a more
Narrow down
palette that you can experiment with and do stuff with and that
Is honestly a very helpful thing to to get something finally done it out the door and make it and and that is not something
That you can really plan out ahead of time. You can but I'd argue it's inefficient or at least that it doesn't work for me personally
So, uh, yeah, that's what I'm saying. Do you have more things to say? I hope I hope you don't feel stifled in this topic
Because if you say it's your ultimate topic, I have to hear it. Well, I don't have anything to say about film
I I most of what I have in like my brain is like
People hate modern art for stupid reasons and I hate them
But I don't know what you've already like discussed or whether you've gone over that or not
Just feel free to like risk repeating shit. Go ahead
I don't know
Art's good. What do you think about post-modern art though? What do you mean like the toilet on the pedestal?
What do you think about that? I think I think what do you think about toilets? You want to get shit?
Oh
For my shit you fat slut
Um post-modern art. I mean, it's the same thing
For me if it's good, then I like it. So like, um
Something doesn't necessarily need a lot of effort to be put into it
But if it's like they and you know a toilet is like a terrible
It's a piece of shit, you know lull
um
The worst post-modern artist or like artist I've ever seen in my life and I hate her is tracy emin
She got famous for doing like a piece where it was her bed. She had a bed with like, um
You know wrappers and and dust and and grime and certain of dirty duvet
And it was just all like in on the middle of the floor
This is what it's like for me to wake up in the morning and it was all grungy and horrible and everyone was
Trey tracy emin
Yeah
Really don't like her face
I've seen her also on like a few like tv shows about like
Where she's like a judge of like post-modern artist, uh, like contestant things is awful awful person
I not an awful person, but awful art. I hate her
But like um, you know her art looks like she looks like to kind of like like people who do like little four panel comics of
What it's like being a neurotic girl and your periods are getting all over the place and you get like 20 000 retweets
It's just it's just like nothing but more squiggly
Well, yeah, um
That some post-modern art can be really funny
You know, it just depends on what statement they're making and whether I agree with it basically
Um one time in in college, uh, this is this is gonna get me in trouble. Maybe
Uh, I I did a funny post-modern thing. I got like a stuff. I got a like a stuffed little little monkey
And I got some black cloth and I made it a little burqa
And and that was my project and the teacher was like, uh, okay. Why and I explained why and it was all about like
shock value being like, um, you know
It's all in the person's head. It's not a burqa. It's not like I'm saying anything. It's just like it's cute
Isn't it it's a cute little monkey and it's just so happens to be a muslim woman
Like what's so what's so wrong about that and they they they were okay with it
And I wrote an essay like explaining my my thought process and that was I mean in in art college
That's what you have to do is you have to explain it in a way that the teachers can understand
If you just say it's uh, it I was inspired by x and I did the same thing that I was inspired by
Can I have a mark that's high please? It's like no, that's not how it works
You gotta be smart the number one thing I learned in art school was to bullshit like that's yeah
One thing I really hate now
I did say that like people are free to express themselves on something and I'm free to dislike it and what I really really dislike
I hate to even bring it up is like a lot of this feminist quote-unquote art
Because a lot of it has to do with like
Periods and like they're literally plopping plopping fucking like eggs out of a vagina on a canvas to like like it publicly
Yeah, yeah hitting my oldie position fetish dog
Yeah art and then like
Painting with period blood or like putting wool in your vagina and pulling it out and making a sweater or something out of it
People have painted with shit their own shit before why I know and that's disgusting too
But like why does feminists aren't always have to do with periods of vaginas?
That's great
I always does
Is it is it an idea of like is it the fact that we find it gross what they're trying to like fix with that?
You know, yeah, I think the thing is like they're celebrating it. You know, they're celebrating their womanhood, but also it's it's beautiful
Yeah, I mean, michelle. I don't I said michelle. I meant mage
Oh
You always do that you all you view all women is the same
Yeah, one of these days I'm gonna ruin the podcast Nate yet again. Oh, please call me mom. Oh
Yeah, you'd like that wouldn't you uh, uh, I don't know what you're saying mage, but all I'm hearing is a whole lot of internalized massaging
That's all it's definitely a lot of
It would be a more it would be a more effective
Thing to do like for shock value if it hadn't become a cliche
Yes, well at this point. That's true. Can we criticize the people who led up to the point where it became cliche though?
Like because they were you know, they were doing something new, right?
You know what on the same subject my my
My postmodern art like act would be to go to high schools and middle schools
And hand out cards to all the boys and the cards just has plain text saying
The reason why girls don't want to have sex with you despite being just as wired for sex as you
Is that they're very very insecure about their vaginas and how they smell
Scratch this spot to get a vagina smell accustom yourself to it and make yourself comfortable with it and you will have sex
What the fuck?
What the fuck's wrong with you? What the fuck is wrong with you?
How could you get a
We gotta keep the body in population up if we want to have fucking health care, right?
I hear yes. Okay. Yay
It all comes back to health
It's all about the health care
Scratch and sniff vagina smell
Yeah, that's
This is a okay. This is a loaded ones
I don't really want to get into the political issue of it
but like for like mattress girl if you remember mattress girl and
We can put put aside whether or not everything she said was true or like anything about it
But the fact that the art piece was her carrying around a mattress
Around her school and this was the art piece like okay to be fair
I understand that like yes, this will get people talking at her school
They will say what's the deal with the fucking mattress. Um
You know, I guess I don't know anything more to say about it. I've seen I've seen an artist
Which I don't want to do who had a giant block of eyes very insightful point
And he would go to me
He went to New York with a giant block of ice and he would just push the ice all down the street
And he had a guy following him like like a block
Like a big block of ice that you would like
Contain like a fishing fish and whatever in the market
And he would just push it until it melted and the the point of the art piece was to
To show how such a strange thing was happening
But nobody would ever pay attention and nobody did
Nobody even looked up at all at him
That reminds me of this uh, there's this one like tv show
This is one like low budget tv show on one of those low budget channels about human psychology
One of those like hey, it's like a human psychology show for 11 year olds, right?
But they go to a mall and they get some uh, you know, like the fluffy like theater railing you use to make queuing lines
Right, they put it in the middle of the of the mall and they put a sign that says get in this line
Like for no particular reason. He doesn't say for no reason
But it doesn't say what the reason is right and they do they put the queuing line there and it leads to nothing
And oh, yeah, yeah, the sign just says the line starts here not explaining what the line is for and they film this from above
And the line goes for hours and no one gets in so they send in one of their guys
An actor to go into the line to stand there, right?
So he stands there looking confident like he's ready for the fucking line, right? He stands there for a full half an hour
When finally this one guy who seems kind of bored. He's like, huh?
So he gets in the line and the moment that there are two people in the line the line suddenly explodes
So it was a test in human psychology if no one's in the line. No one's getting one guy. That's good stuff
There's one guy in the line
Some outliers will try it and once there's two people in the line the line fills up like crazy
And so then they just sort of like had the first guy who was an actor
He just started walking and everyone just started following him, right?
And they they led them all throughout the mall eventually jumping over like stupid obstacles
Like jumping over like a little stick or whatever or going in a circle doing jumping jacks and everyone fucking participated
Yeah, but okay at some point the people in the line must have been like what the fuck's happened
Like like I'm sure I think some point it changed from like I'm just bored and gonna wait in this line
Just like it must have been amusing to them on some level, right?
When it got increasing things increasingly bizarre
Within every human's mind, I think is this two competing things of like independent free thought basically and like are just kind of
Relaxing ourselves into just like going with what the crowd is doing. I think those are like two
Primal forces that kind of jump. I heard the saying that like
An individual is intelligent a crowd is dumb something like that
Sure
What interested me about what divu said there was like he was explaining that and he said it was like
A study in psychology rather than an art piece and I think that at some point the line blur is there like what what?
What is a study of psychology? What is that? Can we define this?
Well, why don't we head over to our friends on urbandictionary.com?
Why don't we head over to forum.becomealivinggod.com?
Let me just read by the way for fun
Did you make?
Um, I'm chillin for it. I'm chillin for it. Let me just read the definition of psychology on urbandictionary
It's the practice of taking things we already know about people
And weighing it down with jargon until only the other people who understand it are psychologists
Art to me, you know, you know this guy hates
Jordan Pete very funny
Uh guys, I'm done. I'm spent. I've yeah. Well, I have one more thing to say
So, okay the the guy in the fucking ragu university video
He's all fucking like where did the centuries long quest for beauty and artistic and skillful perfection
Like go away like what happened to it, right?
He said it didn't just die out. It was pushed out
You know by the by the fucking like hipsters and shit in the early 20th century, right? Here's the thing now
That's yet another thing about that video that's fucking retarded
It wasn't like one day some dudes decided to change the face of art and it was all their fucking fall
And they could have shown up in the 19th century or the 15th century or the 29th century
The fact that they showed up in the 20th century
Means a whole lot in the late 19th century because that's when film was taking off and photography was taking off
It was fucking inevitably going to become like static art
Paintings and sculpting was always going to become a bunch of hipster bullshit because of film because film is where we put
Our highest priority of beauty the most effort the most skill and often that is highly diluted like when we think of hollywood movies
It's you know, it's a mass produced
You know machine, but when you think when you think about the directors out there whose films are extremely artful
It's like this is the height of our quest for beauty and overt obvious depth
Now right like animation and film and video games even are like the mediums where we're putting our emphasis there
So painting and sculpting they're sort of like left behind as like mediums that cannot touch people as
Deeply in nine times out of ten because there's not as many mediums. So that's why they become so weird
I don't think it's necessarily that I think the fact that
You can now watch movies at home, but arts you still have to go to a gallery
That you used to have to go to a cinema to see a film
And now you don't need to so now it's like less of an art form in the sense that you go out to see it
Like a theater or a play or whatever and and more that you can it's a it's a consumable product that people
you know go through in their own time wherever and whenever they like and
I think
I think the the the art is like um, you know in galleries and sculptures and paintings are still like
The same a level of like
You know artistic fulfillment you can get from it. It's just you have to go to the place where it is
And for a lot of people that just isn't worth the time
But the thing that it evokes is like the feeling of going to a place
Like you go to a nice countryside and you take in the environment
You see the nice blue sky and the trees and the stuff and it sounds and feels really nice and that
You cut I wouldn't say it's art because that's stupid
No one should say that but like that's the feeling that a painting of a beautiful landscape is supposed to invoke in use
To remind you of what it feels like to see and be in a place like that. Oh, yeah
I remember one time in the chat we were talking about what are our favorite aesthetics and you were like
I remember you hit bill you were like, oh my favorite aesthetics is this and this or like uh
Some the point is you listed a bunch of like regular aesthetics and then you one of your aesthetics was
Being in an abandoned 12th century castle. Yes. I love that. I love castles that they're my favorite art piece
By mankind. They're better than propaganda. I prefer nature. Yeah, you can definitely argue that. Well, uh, here's what I want to say about
Davoo's point
So so to what that guy was saying about how like it was intentionally made so that we're deviating from these objective standards of beauty and stuff
So I am agnostic about if there is some grand marxist conspiracy to like destroy the west
I I do not know, uh, whether that's true or not. So I'm putting that aside
But what I will say is to to his point to his point of how we are in fact deviating from these beauty standards
Um, I want to give him as much credit as possible. He may or may not have intended this but like I'm reading this into it. Anyway, it's like
We definitely are
Getting further away on in the art scene at the very least from objective standards
And as Davoo was saying it may in fact have been inevitable
But just because it's inevitable it may also be inevitably
Destructive to the human race that that's happening that is like it's possible that christianity for example
Despite being not true would just be a useful thing to keep humans in line so that we don't kill ourselves
It's possible. Hold on. I think we I think this is a promo for an upcoming episode
I think me and you Nate would be most wanting to do
Which would be called wake of phobia, which is what some right wing
writers throughout the decades have
It basically it basically means fear of the familiar fear of the home
But some right wing writers have co-opted that term to mean the opposite of xenophobia
Sort of like whenever someone hears about a law that exists in the uk and they're like
We should have that law in america too, but america's too stupid to have it
Like how american feminists like uh are totally okay with like women being enslaved in saudi arabia
Well, they're not okay with it, but like the fact that they're their priorities
Yeah, like i mean i remember one time being in the car with like this girl
This chick who was just like constantly be like oh man america sure sucks for this reason
Oh, they're you could just passively mention something different about some other country and they're like, oh, that's so much better than is in america
Yeah, right and i think i think it's a natural
A natural result of becoming
The the most powerful opulent nation that it starts to destroy itself from within by people who felt like they didn't do
Anything to earn this opulence feel guilty about it and take it out in this manner. So yeah, this should be a
I'll add wake of phobia to the topics list. We'll do this some other time
Okay, and we will title that episode we hate white people
That's what i am beautiful
I feel like like um
with like youtube videos and and and and uh like media that we consume at home or wherever
Even music to a degree, but music still has festivals which are big and live performances
but like getting out of the house and going to see art is
Dying out a little bit at a time cinemas are now like not as big as they used to be and they need to be like
Luxury in order to make any money at all
um
And I feel like with you know the young people they stay at home. They don't do anything
They they they can get everything they ever wanted through the internet and they can get the internet everywhere
so like
In this time and this day in this age
Uh art pieces that you have to go and see are more valuable than ever
But nobody wants to go to them and I understand because art galleries are stuffy and
And some of them you have to pay to get in and whatever and and you know not you're not going to guarantee to find as much as you could get
Just googling stuff. So what but but what I think
What I think is that the reason
Well, I think the greatest
piece of art in the modern age
For this reason
This is no this bad gas is pokemon go
Now we're talking now because it combines video games with
Being a real human in the real world and going to places and having experiences and connecting with people in a way
That no other thing that you can do now
Really allows you to do
Speaking of which I've really enjoyed the gifts that you've been sending me from your local poke stops
I've I've I've liked having you send gifts and then me google searching what the poke stop was that you send it from
Be able to see where you are. That's cool. What's what was this about gifts?
Wait, what is this the thing in that you can trade? Yeah, mage. I I will send you a gift
I think I'm gonna add people to your friends list now that i'm back in boston
I gotta fucking get on the go train. I gotta go hard. Dude. I got it. I got it downloaded. I got it downloaded. I'm going
I'm going I will definitely say it is super it is supremely art
I remember back to the early 2000s in some kids highly decked up decorated blue room
Him showing me all of his pokemon cards and he's like at the same age as me and then warp to
14 years later being at a gazebo in virginia beach
Seeing people huddled around playing pokemon go including a like 60-something year old woman with oxygen hooked up to her fucking nose
I remember that gazebo. I remember that gazebo
Yeah, the the people that you meet will play in pokemon go are mothers their construction workers
They're all the same they are all the things that you want to see inside in this great art piece we call pokemon go
Oh, you did
I have I actually I have two things I need to say before we close out
First is to kind of go all the way back to beginning talking about like, you know postmodernism versus classical art like the prager you video
um
I feel like those are like two ends of a spectrum of like art
Uh, like like you have postmodernism, which I can appreciate the idea or like people can appreciate the idea
But the execution is kind of basic, but on the other hand you have the classical art where like the execution is masterfully done
But the the subject matter is very basic just like the bible, you know or just like yeah a portrait
So like there's like this middle ground that I find the most appreciative is where you have
skillful execution and an interesting idea and that's like
The art I like because like as much as I can appreciate the uh the time and energy put in like a classical painting
Like I don't really not really huge fan of that either because like I'm like, okay
Right. Yeah, that's why that perfect middle ground the perfect artistic medium is shown in manga shown in exactly
The greatest the greatest art medium. Oh, but speaking of that. Okay
I needed to the one last thing I wanted to get off my chest
Is the moment the moment that fucking uh, I hated the art world forever. Um
This is a bit of a bit of a story, but I'll wrap it up quickly
um
Back in like the early mid-2000s like if anyone who's doing art and like college or high school
You know that like there was like this big like if you were trying to draw like a cartoony style
Like your art teachers hated you like this was like a meme and like whether it was true or not
Like a good idea or not is irrelevant to what I'm about to say. Um, because like
I was drawing like cartoons and shit like that was what I was into
and I was like graduating high school going into college and like everybody gave me shit for it and
And it was it was fucking infuriating because like I was trying to like do like realistic art to like work on my portfolio and
Shit and everyone's like you should just do that. I'm like, uh, but it's gay. I don't like it. Um, but but but
I had like a portfolio and I went to uh,
Some bunch of schools and like they all said it was shit because like oh, we're fucking sick of anime get out of here
It's gay. We hate you go die. So like all right, whatever so so
Right off the bat fucking pissed off, but
I end up getting into a school and I go and whatever and like the entire time
It's like, okay, like I'm gonna do like the art stuff here
And I'm gonna do my cartoon shit off the clock because like that's that's a no-go zone
We can't make that happen
Whatever and I'm taking art history class and I fucking hate it and it's supremely disgusting
The the the culture around like sucking all these artists dicks and like like trying to like make all these things more complicated
More haughty than they actually are and I just find it infuriating and obnoxious, but then
2010 we get to talking about a new art movement that started called super flat
Oh, no
And I want to
And wikipedia super flat is a postmodern art movement which is influenced by manga and anime
all of a sudden
Now because it's a fucking art movement those same teachers who are like cartoons or gay are like look at this beautiful
Inspired art and I'm like you're fucking
Cuts
Wait, wait, but super flat is not just fucking anime art, right?
No, it's not just but the whole thing is that you look at these pieces. It's clearly inspired by that same aesthetic anime
Yeah, okay, and and and and so it's no it's it's it's I like the aesthetic
It's not like great and therefore
I'm looking up super flat art is usually great. Take a look at this one right here
Look at this is a little bit of anime. I think in my uh, yeah, that might be a little anime in it
That might be just a bit anime
So so it's just like
My point is that this is why I hate the art scene because it's like and until it's like in the art scene
It's disgusting, but as soon as all of these other people are like, oh, well, this is art. I guess now it's okay
That is bullshit when I hate when we when we talk about these arbitrary
Reputations that people get like I mean sometimes it's just because like they're a cunt and people relate to it
But sometimes it's because it's someone who comes along with a style that a lot of people can do or other people can do
But this one guy
Has the nerve and or charisma to shove it down everyone's face until they're forced to accept it as the new hotness
Similarly to what a couple of analysts did on youtube until eventually analysis became the new review
Even though it used to be beaten down as overanalyzing before that point
I don't really get super. I mean, okay
Like it's not like I don't think that it looks good necessarily like like these just kind of like
sprawling like series of like flat images and like a white void like I I get it
Uh, I don't know seems pretty like
Seems a little uh, what's the word not an frank lisa frank. That's the one
Yeah
All the time I I'm definitely feeling some and frank
Is that a whale lord statue, uh, I google super flat and a three dimensional thing came up and I was like, that's not
Well, that's just that's not good. That's not that's not well
Well, tom funny thing you mentioned super flat because I actually learned that super flat myself just a few months ago
Well visiting but while visiting the fine arts museum in boston mason says god in my own in my own time
My own backyard my oppressor
Is on display
He there's an entire there was an entire section dedicated to him and at the museum. I realize that I absolutely
Adore the idea of museums and I don't mind paying to see museums
I just feel persecuted and I do not like all of the art that is in museums
I like the concept of them, but I hate them all the time
For instance, this is not the finance museum
But there's another museum in boston for art called the institute of contemporary art and when I went to there
There was a there was a an exhibit all on art created in the internet period and there's a lot of you know
Digital art and there's a lot of shit that would be recognizable to stuff like, you know, you and me
There wasn't like d.v. Narnship. There was a lot of like, you know, hip trendy
Means internet shit that commentated a lot of marin issues and that stuff. I absolutely
Adored I love that exhibit with all my heart and that was the funniest
I've ever had at any museum ever sadly. It's over now
I went to
A museum during a con because I had a comics class as an elective in college
And we went to a museum that just had comic art and they had
Like the original cover of my favorite cover of my favorite comic on display and I like knotted
Everywhere. I know it's great. So so I just I want to know because I've been trying to search for other similar
Institute of contemporary arts, but I can't find any in San Diego and I want to know why I want to bang on the clouds and ask God
Why why are museums gay and stuffy and dusty and bad because okay
I go I go to the the the museum of fine arts in San Diego and it's fine
And I like it and it's just all right and it has that faming pain that famous pain that I had my avatar for a while
Where the guy's holding his finger up to his head and he looks like he's thinking real hard
And it was the thinker that's embossed for my inclusion of it and not for the ponder
Oh
The the ponder yeah the yeah that guy
Uh, it's fine. Oh, but where are the fucking anime? Where's the super flat? Where's the colors?
Where are the memes?
That's correct. That's what it comes down to. You should come to london and we can go to like a gallery hop
I would absolutely love to do that. Okay. I can't I cannot stress it enough going to the finance museum seeing the tukashi exhibit
and seeing specifically
Uh, this is the full title of the pain by the way dragon in the clouds red mutation the version
I painted when my professor told me to paint something myself for once by tukashi
That's uh, one of my favorite frames of all time
Fucking great and uh going to the institute of contemporary art seen all the internet
I'm gonna link you. I'm gonna have to get some of this shit and I'll put in the show notes
But it's absolutely incredible the shit I saw there. I took a lot of videos. Uh, it was beautiful
I just I just this is all just a call to arms museums
Please house and patronize modern contemporary art from the internet and you know just general contemporary stuff
I like renaissance paintings. I just want more contemporary and downed earth casual shit and stylistic
Drawings that's what I would love to have like a vlog of of of uh hippo and munchie going on a london art hop
Actually, that reminds me back in me and digi's trip to atlanta me and ben
We were we were walking down that one like hipster street and we just started like rating every painting and mural
We saw out of five and then sometimes we said out of seven and out of 12 sometimes
And we just thought this should be a show of just the two of us go to like anything and rate the aesthetics of everything ever
Davoo, you and I have such different have like such different uh aesthetics
Consideration we have just have we just value. I think we value very different things. So I think that would be interesting
right
Yeah, so well next next time make it so team make it so
Okay, and with that I think it's finally time to delete this pie. Yeah
All right. This has all been a postmodern experiment in art that no one will ever see we actually wasn't we weren't recording any of this
Postmodern way to do a podcast is just have a fucking link to a zip file of all of the audacity projects
And not even converted to wabs yet, right?
I think it's even most partners to send a screenshot of all the audio files in a folder and not give them access to it
Yeah
Oh, oh, oh, okay
Uh, okay, okay, my favorite thing that I this is the last thing I promise the last thing the best thing
I saw that instrued contemporary art, which I don't remember the name of which I think it's called my best thing
But it was this like like like like multi series episodic
Adventure, I would say recreate in some sort of like text-to-speech and like like go anime
But 3d miles a little like roblox. It was some sort of like like like put directly into that to make these
Text-to-speech robot speak things and it was a conversation that happened in real life
Where an art teacher who was a female went on like porn sites
Or or more accurately like like omegle chat roulette sites and had like philosophical insights with a horny
Italian man with his dick out the entire time. Wow, and it was cool as fucking hell
It was great. I think it's called my best thing 2011. I'm not sure though. Um
That's great. I love it. I voted good shit
The main segment of this episode's audio dialogue was
Significantly edited and spaced out to the effect that you could generally hear what everyone has to say
People who try to butt in but don't get an actual sentence in are simply muted
they're their failed sentences aborted and deleted from the timeline and times where
Three or four different people say something at once are actually spaced out to create sort of an artificial comedic timing
I only did that for everything in the episode up to this point now that we're in the questions and fan stuff
That's all gonna be much more freeform with much less editing just removing some of the noise not changing the timing of anything
I guess let us know if you can notice and appreciate and value
The difference because I'm interested in seeing how much better podcasts can be with this added effort
But I'm not sure if its market value will result in a net profit
All right
Guys, let's get down to it here
We got a couple of things to talk about real quick
As we as we recap the events since last week's episode number one on the agenda
Let's talk about how radcon 3 arena iRL came out and it was a fucking triumph. Oh, yeah, and it was incredible
Everyone loves it
It was truly decadence truly delectable
Uh, we had doubters out there. We proved them all wrong. There were doubters and now they are uh
Down syndromeers. That's what they that's what happened to them. The doubters are
Doubters
That's you know, that would have been good that would have been good
Uh, I don't know. I guess I just wanted to say that that was great
Go watch it if you haven't already uh show notes. Watch the video. It's also like the last video on the channel
It's great. Give edit it. It's incredible. I haven't been in the last couple episodes
I don't know what's happening in the pcp sphere of influence
But I know that the childhood episode has gone up which I was on and in which mage was some sort of gang warlord leader
In the streets of south africa essentially
That's that is what's happening now mage's role is actually
We we continue that meme in the fighting episode mage is now the violent violence. That is her name
Mage denies that she was the leader of the violent violence, but we think I just think she's trying to escape her war crimes
But she needs to pay for what she's done. That sounds like something that the violent violence would say
Yeah
The violent violence like
Addition to the canon is the best thing the pcp and its fandom has produced
final
Question final question. Have you ever seen mage and the violent violence in the same place at the same time?
No proof positive. There we go. That if something is proven, then it's true
If two things are both said then it's correct
All right, well, I don't I have nothing else to say about that. So let's just
I think yeah, I think we've exhausted yeah about the previous I am exhausted episode. I have some things to say
Oh, okay. Yeah a lot of people all not all the people several people mentioned the little tension we had
um
And I I was sort of like somewhat indecisive but disagreeing with you
But now I can firmly say I completely disagree with you after reading the comments. I I saw I saw the error in your ways
I forget what was the argument?
Should be allowed to
Refuse service to people
Yeah, that's right. I I I am for freedom of speech and freedom of expression, but I'm also for
I'm also for
um equal opportunity
And like we were only focusing. Well, you're also
Aren't you saying I mean a specific case was you can't compel people to do something if they don't choose to but you're arguing against that
No, I'm I don't understand what's being argued here. It wasn't on the last day. All right. We were talking about um, yeah, it's
You know, this is a fighting episode, by the way, very weird
I missed but oh well
Yeah, I I'd love to say about fine
There's the possibility of like a town
Where the there's just one walmart and it for some reason denies service to uh, everyone in the town
And we were we were arguing like well, they are a company and they can choose to deny service to whoever they like
Uh, but should the government force them to sell things?
Oh, well on my position on this I can explain in 30 seconds is that in this reality?
Yes, because we live in a world where this whole dream of freedom to choose what you want
Is compromised in a million ways anyway
Like yeah, there's a thousand laws that force companies to like have to conform to things that they shouldn't have to in a free country
But there's a million laws forcing employees and consumers to conform to a bunch of things that they shouldn't have to do in a free country
And if you only give the additional free if you only give back freedoms to companies
You better at least be giving the same amount of freedoms back to consumers and workers, right the fucking
The fucking structure of oppression and compromises on freedom in this culture is like a jenga statue
And if you just take apart pieces of it haphazardly, it's gonna it's gonna crash
I
Couldn't tell what side you're on based on that good very fucking good
You can't just decide what side I'm on you have to actually listen to me
Basically what I want to say you can completely
Compromise a person's livelihood because we were talking mostly about walmart
But what about like public services like a bus can get you well that those are public those are government though
That's a totally different situation kind of you know like no no no no no no no no no no completely untrue
That is the opposite of
It's a little it's a little hard to explain what it like public services. I think well here's the thing
Here's a thing where it actually gets and electricity and I think a better example than something like walmart
The company would be something like google or the internet because that's like those are those are companies that are okay
We should be clear right now
These things are all publicly owned if you want to argue that they are effectively utilities and they should be treated that way legally
Then fair enough, but that is not how they are right now
Right should so you know it's relevant. It's relevant right and that's my point like should they be regulated as such
I don't want to prolong this debate. I'm just saying that like I it's too late mage
It's part two it's happening right now
I wanted to make a harsh statement that I
But straight up mage straight up mage
If you if if a guy if you walk in and you want to get gay married and you walk into a cake shop
As the as the as the thing goes and the guy says like sorry, but I don't make cakes for gay people
Uh, like I mean it's against my religion. I think it's wrong. I have a sincere religious belief
You think he should have to make that cake. Are you arguing for that? I said I said like all right like I said
You're saying large corporations, right? Yeah. Yeah, basically that like I don't why does that matter? Why is it?
There's a difference, but I said I don't want to like prolong this conversation. I just like
Oh, I don't want to have to defend my beliefs. I just want to say them and now
So I did say like there's a difference like you know, it's just a mom-and-pop shop
It's just it just it's just that one shop in one area. No one really cares like if it goes under or not
It's not gonna affect the economy or the people's livelihood or whatever
But like if walmart all all of walmart decides to not sell to a certain demographic of people
Well, that's gonna like screw stuff up like for instance where I live
There's only like one as the store in the whole region and otherwise I'd have to like maybe like
I don't know take a bus to a different town to get like food
And what's really convenient about asda is that it's a 24 seven asda
So if at midnight I I suddenly realize oh, I'm out of food because my sleep schedule is awful
I can just go to house and buy some food and but like
I wouldn't be able to do that if they decide to not sell to lefie unions anymore, you know, so
So so the absolute rebuttal to that would be oh
So people have to be controlled by law because they're so successful like um, oh, oh specifically
There's this one uh documentary called fathead, which is a response to supersize me that brings up
It it depends on it doesn't say mcdonalds is a good company
But it sort of rebutts a lot of the complaints one of the criticisms of mcdonalds back when they had played places prominently
They would argue that it's the it's manipulating children and families into eating unhealthy food and giving them money because they have
A you know recreational activity for kids and some kids don't have access to recreational activities otherwise
So it's manipulating their it's exploiting their needs to which the the fathead documentary says well
The federal government didn't give those kids a play place
The local government didn't give those kids a playground
Ronald mcdonalds did and ronald mcdonald is to be seen as evil for being the only one who gave them one, right?
So you can say similarly like oh because walmart is successful
It now has to get fucked over it's similar just it's similar to like oh this happens in fucking
Right well this happens in iron man two basically where the government's like, you know, tony stark
You've made such good inventions that you don't any longer gets to own them, right?
Now my rebuttal to that would be i get to to a degree
What if an inventor just invents a doomsday weapon like okay, right now we can have a conversation which effectively is what tony stark
Is not so so my feeling on that is because I very much feel in my in
Let's admit the philosophy of iron. Yeah in my yeah
The philosophy of tony stark 15 minute video, right? So
My fucking I feel the libertarianism in my very veins
I feel that like, you know, like you shouldn't be penalized for obtaining power and success
But then I have to remember, you know, there's a reason why we came up with this whole freedom and uh like free economy and capitalism and
And freedom from the government in the first place, right? It was because
governments
Also got too successful and powerful like we didn't even really have this whole like freedom
Thing be a thing until around a certain point of colonialism when governments became so big and bloated that they started becoming a real obvious problem
And we were able to identify how we could do things better and at this point the concept of the corporation is becoming very similar
They're becoming these international fucking nations unto themselves often with more gdp
So like, you know, maybe it's time to update our philosophy on what's right and wrong because 500 years ago
Nobody probably thought that it like the idea of a nation telling you what to do was wrong
We had to invent that idea, right?
And it was it's not has nothing to do with like the fact that one type of entity makes laws and the other type of entity makes profits
It all comes down to one thing
Control being conglomerated in a couple of people who have the power and the ability to to control other people
Yeah, yep, generally. I agree. That's it's not it's not as black and white as either of us. We're saying
And I'm aware of that too
Uh on fighting one time I was six and in like
Well not six. I'm more like it was eight and I was in the fourth grade
And uh some high school junior tried to come up to me and fuck with me and I literally beat the shit out of him
I'm gonna say one time one time. No, no, no, no. We are not going into fighting. That was last episode. God damn it
This is not a rehash of the entire fucking fighting. I'm gonna show up to the episode if you want to be on it
All right, but that being said if you want to tell one thing
In my neighborhood it was like super lame and insecure and would be a huge whiny butt and I'd make fun of him
But like not like a I don't think it too much of a bullying
We I would just point out how pathetic he's being and he took like military class and judo and shit
That was just wrestling and like, you know like okay you versus you okay now you versus you
So it was me versus him and I don't have any fighting skills or athleticism
I'm like five inches taller than him three years older than him
He just like pulls me over and like throws me like just suplexes me onto my back
And it didn't even hurt. It was on the grass, but I'm like
Okay, cool. You've turned your fucking like impotent rage into something something somewhat potent. Good job
But you did it you have some respect now
Okay, okay. All right. Well good. Nate you are you are an egg. You are like
You're you're an egg and you've got like a marker and you drew on the on the shell like angry eyes
You got this hard out of shell and you're like, yes, I'm very tough and and then as soon as anything happens to you
You're so soft. You're such a
I'm okay with it. No, no, I'm a hard boiled egg. I'm tough inside. I'm resilient as well
Yeah, nothing's nothing's harder and more and more resistant to damage than a hard boiled egg
Art people draw draw Nate as an egg. That's the new art thing. Yeah. All right. That sounds good. That sounds good. Uh
Yeah, I'll make you girl
Okay, funny side up
Our document tells us that the next section is the question section
It's a goddamn question
Are the corporation co
Policy mandates
Way to office skate responsibility, mr. Bestman. Well, listen to this one uh at suck on my big pee pee
All right, here we go prostate massage. Yes or no sure why not next
I'll take two
Well, uh, uh, there's a question here about i g tv. Do we want to go? Okay?
I want to just point out my my answer on prostate massages is that they are uncomfortable
But pretty relaxing if you're comfortable with the person doing it. Oh, well, there we go
Is that
Um
Okay, you know, I'm not going to read this question about i g tv because I think we're going to talk about that later on
Uh, or like next week or something. Okay that uh fucking questions bar. Who's got one? I'm going to go pull one up
What do you got for us?
Um, none of them are worthy. Why do we do this if there are no worthy questions?
Um, well that you know why it's because you guys told them that art was the subject
This is what you get this is what you get when you when you mentioned that the topic is going to be art
That all the questions are boring. Shit. We've already answered in the fucking episode
Oh
No, yeah, what what does this have to do with art modern?
They literally have postmodern sonic games remember that that weird one
That is a postmodern sonic game. Oh, shit. Yeah sonic dreams collection. Fuck
I like modern sonic you go in 3d
You go really fast. Well
I guess sonic mania is actually it is classic sonic by form
It is just the latest the latest one. Yes, you know, so that's this good. I liked it
Uh modern's uh martin sonic versus classic sonic is not interesting
But what is interesting is classic mickey mouse versus modern mickey mouse and I actually have a very hard line opinion with this
uh most okay
Classic mickey mouse actually had a revival recently in the form of the modern disney channel on youtube mickey mouse shorts
And everyone praises those because they are quite good
But I actually do not like the art style because I feel like it is disingenuous to pretend that mickey mouse is not
The modern mickey mouse and to go back on it is just jarred me
But I saw on toontown. I cannot find any photographic evidence of this
So you just have to pretend what I'm saying is true
But in toontown at disneyland. There is a there's a lineup of characters
There was a mural on a wall that depicts the gang mickey goofy donald
Pluto and danger dolin and they are all there and they are actually a combination of the colors of modern
Uh, the modern incarnation of the character
But with the designs of the previous ones except the skin tone the skin that's like that's like in
White so they just are white and that is the best that is the best interpretation
Final mix how sore gets a new form called the uh limit form
Which is when he gets a cool color scheme from kingdom hearts one
It was awesome thinking of kingdom hearts too. Remember how mickey looks like fucking shit
Here's here's my posh that right for metal gear solid right metal gear solid one is
Modern metal gear solid metal gear solid two is postmodern mgs postmodern and mgs three
Is classic mgs. It's it just like did it in the opposite timeline or reverse order
Metal gear solid two is proof that postmodern art is not all bad or anything. It is uh, like the best game ever made
A classic postmodern it should be a meme that you can apply to everything
Yes, yes, absolutely. This question by the way about modern or classic sounding was from j hawk dx
Just just just what he really needs the the exposure
I know right guys. Who what's mickey? Do you like better?
I don't like
It's gotta be
No, no, no when you say classic beam boat willy. I'm talking steam boat willy
The mickey that did not have the hairline, but it had the eyes
giant eyes like this like like like fucking stony interesting a comparison
Look look at this straight up rat. He looks great. He looks sick. I like he's got pac-mans
No, no, I'm not saying the pupils. I'm saying look. Yeah. Yeah. He's got the sonic
One eye with two pupils thing going on. Is that what you're talking about now? I get it now. I understand where sonic comes from
Yeah, by the way, uh, wait, there was another question here. What the fuck did it go?
Uh, it was something about shit whose question was that wait. I got it
Where the fuck did it go?
Hashtag up with victor. There it is. Why is the group piss the greatest example of modern art in human history?
Let's just dissect the art that is the group piss. Uh, it was good. That's all I have to say. Yeah, that's it
It was my invention
Actually, as we know the curation is the ultimate form of art and it was literally my idea to film it
Therefore I deserve 100 of the credit for doing so disgusting get banned. You are banned from the pcp
That's my favorite part of the group piss is that we all created our own art pieces in the snow
That's true. That's true. It's like a time these are the rest of these questions
These are all bad. These are all bad questions
Okay, if you want to buy a yellow poon, do you guys think becoming mainstream is inherently damaging to the original vision of a product?
Maybe not inherent, you know, it's not inherent, you know, it's art
You know, it's arch that mage just had to read the words yellow poon, uh unironically and is
Uh, you know, that's just what what a world what a world? Yeah, there it is. That's gonna come back to haunt you someday
What was the other question? Hold on actually
I do want to say like I forgot to answer that one, right?
I mean there is a cracked article like six artists who became famous after they sold out, right?
Like it was like became good including the Beatles
They originally were much more punk before they were reigned in for having identical hairstyles and stuff
And also I think the ultimate example is that Michelangelo
Didn't want to paint he preferred sculpting and the church kept roping it back in to keep painting. He's like fine
I'll paint your goddamn ceiling
So there you go. I what if my art form is a crewing currency?
What if that is my art?
I think I have to draw the line on what's hard at some point
I think like
when once they are popular
The greatest artists of all time George Soros
I think when you're popular there's a pressure to keep doing what you're doing and less experimenting so like
You could potentially but it depends on how well you do under pressure and like you have to balance the pressure and your own vision
That's true. You have to make sure that when you get popular you're getting popular doing something you actually want to do for a long time
If you get popular doing something you hate you're fucked
This guy may be talking from the lens of like a series of like video games like
The first one was small, but then it gets big and and it changes as it goes along
Then they changed like like because like there's no way the original vision of a part of like if a project
Sorry, um exists
And and then it becomes mainstream. It hasn't changed at all. It's just like people's perception of it
and I and to
And to tom's point like he got popular, you know doing like the pony videos that he from his own words hated doing
So like that's no fucking good. Uh, you know, that's not gonna last and uh, and it didn't so there you go the second question
Tom
Fuck sometimes you can really trigger 2013 memories in me, man
Um, I got nothing else to say about anything. Oh, major. What's your other question?
Uh, uh
Bitter for bitter bitter thorn
Yeah, if you had to choose between being deaf or being blind for one month, which would you pick?
Oh for one month. Oh, all right. Oh, um, that's a softball version of this question. Yeah. Oh, I like this one much more
um
Well, uh, having been deaf kind of in one ear for more than a month. I would definitely pick being blind
Because but what about the devil, you know, you know might be better than the devil
You don't know. I choose death for sure. Just because I I choose death. I just want to be dead for one
That's what I would go with
No, I'll choose blindness because um, I have musical talents that I can use to entertain myself and
People will do things for me because there's no way I could do things by myself
I mean, I choose I choose death for the exact same reason because if I was deaf, I could still draw
But if I was blind exactly same, right
Yeah, exactly. So like I would I would pick death because I could work on like
Yeah, I could work on shit for a while if I was blind. I couldn't I couldn't make a video if I was deaf
All right, I mean that's a tough one. That's a blessing in disguise. Fuck making videos. It's gay
True
I probably do use visual stuff significantly more than audio
But like i'm thinking of myself right now
I like when it comes to work like like vision would probably be the more important one
But when I when I think about like what would the world be like to me if I was either deaf or blind
And I'm just like what would make the work like I'm thinking about the nightmare of living through a month without this thing
That I've had my whole life and I think not having sight would be more bearable than not having audio
Yeah, I don't know what I mean. Yeah, because hippo you have a whole big song
I mean, hippo has a lot of he he makes the case that that being uh death would be more
I can't listen to my ASMR if I don't have hearing. I can't do it. I have I can't because your brain is accustomed to hearing
24 seven your eyes are accustomed to sometimes not seeing yeah being deaf
We take something away that you're much more used to I would agree
It's just I'd also like to get shit done in that month
Also, I've heard rush Limbaugh said that being deaf will piss people off because people can't relate to that fact
Like if you can't see it's easy for people to figure out what you're not getting
But if you can't hear especially if you can barely hear because you have implants
People are going to get pissed off that you can't ever like understand them properly
Well, I don't interact with anyone
So it's fine
Exactly, you know, I can test this but it's so fucked up the one acceptable form of bullying is against deaf people
One day. Well, we'll get over that that hurdle but for now
Fuck you if you're deaf. You can't even hear what I'm saying asshole. Oh, I see
Got him. I mean, that's that's funny
Um, no, I I love you. Uh, anyway
Wait, I think that's
I think we're no, I think we're done with questions
I don't I'm not even sure why you were directing that. Is that a me?
Uh, well
I I choose not to comment. All right, moving on moving on
It's time team for the pcp theme contest. Everybody's favorite part of the week. Oh, it's time to get right the fuck
How many have this right? Let me let me count real quick. Correct. Uh, sorry. What was that mage? Was that mage, right? Yeah
Oh, yeah, that's right. We're doing the fan art last. That's true. Which we we've got some good ones
Uh, let me just count real quick about one two three four five six seven entries. Oh my god
Boy, so let me all right. Let me see if this works in the easy way here. All right
Let me I'm just gonna fucking do the bot here. All right. Let's see. I'm gonna play right now
Let's see if this fucking thing works this one that I'm I'm linking is from at alien observer
All right, give me a sec to make sure this works play. All right. Here we go indeed
Oh, okay, that did not work. Let me let me fix this. I gotta get it from the actual thing
Nope, stop. Okay. Here we go. Here we go. Uh, and here we go
Play
I can barely hear it. Yeah
boring
Right right click on rhythm and turn up the volume
Whoa
Is this a real one or is this like ripped off from somebody it feels like two pro, you know
Uh, wait, wow, I heard me. Oh shit. Yeah, why are you talking? We can't hear you
Whoa
All right, this is pretty great. Yes, this is nuts
All right feel like well bear is now
Damn
all those game drops
Um
Dude, well, it's funny. I didn't know that anyone that fucking low register watched us. That's cool
Was that was that fucking blowing out the mic for all you guys too? Was that like clipped as fuck or was that just
No, no, that was
That is pretty impressive. But yeah, I'll listen to it again. We should I mean damn
Okay, we should because I could not understand anything
All right, that was like the most well produced one. I think we've got I feel like some rad con four like like montage
Of us like slow walking together could be said to that, you know, yeah
Oh, totally dude. Yeah, by the way, this is akazi on soundclad dude. It was fucking sick. I can tell you put a ton of work into it
Oh
As opposed to the
Um, I mean, I feel bad like I don't really think it works as like an intro or anything
But I really liked it
Ben that I could hear that fucking shit. Turn it down. God damn it
Yeah, Ben. Are you retarded? You can't play music out of your soaker when you're recording through your microphone
I think you have brain damage. This might be the best one yet
I supremely disagree, but I need to explain explain yourself explain. Yeah, well, I guess I I guess we haven't
It is like the best produce. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Let me let out my case. It's the best produced and it's specific
and it's high energy
I mean, you're not wrong. It's got like all the things that we want going for it
I gotta be honest. It's it's the vibe. It's the vibe that I yeah, no, like I don't think of it as high energy
I think of it more as like chill energy and I don't know. I'm not like against I'm not against chill
I'm not against chill by the way, but it doesn't have a melody like it doesn't have a catchy melody
Uh, and I also like I'm I'm any any theme is going to probably lose a bunch of points if it has vocals at all
I think something just
There's there's disagreement there's disagreement
Yeah, and then even within that category, you're almost certainly going to lose a lot of points for me as to
An intro would actually want to have if it's like
Like the lyrics are like explicitly referencing what the pcp is and name dropping it like I mean the worst is if it
That is good. I like that
I mean, I'm gonna respectfully
Like no, I totally get the idea that like a theme song references the people. I get it my tastes. I don't like that at all
I just heard like lyrics that I would prefer
All of my favorite theme songs are theme songs that don't directly say what the fuck the show is
But kind of abstractly say it like a cruel angel's thesis or the south park opening
Look, we're not okay, not gonna take you back to the past. This is me
I'm gonna say baby galeon
I am
It is too late it is too late in the game for us to like grab a song
That will become like indelibly linked to us and like an iconic piece of piece
I just agree. It's all about whether or not we lose it for you. We've already had 8 000 episodes without the song
Uh, I just don't I think it would be I think that's too much to hope for that
We find like the perfect okay, I don't I don't even care whatever the point
I mean like you know what it's it's kind of a cruel angel's thesis to say this but fucking pro crastinator by endless jess
Already basically did this like it's it's more in line with what I say what I'm saying here, right?
All right
Audience I just want to say in last episode. I just want to say audience don't
Bend once to discourage you from making a classic pcp theme. I say no if the song is great
It will become classic. I
Okay, um, I think that this is very very good and I like it a lot
But I kind of agree that the endless jess theme is very like yeah, that's that's us
So why not how about here's the thing take the melody from that and turn it into whatever thing you're doing
What I
Turn the melody of like don't
Don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't and make it more like that but like like faster and better and gooder
What's the point of that
Because it's it's the melody that people recognize
Yeah, we get the same melody with a better vibe maybe but I want to ask about what jessy thinks of that
He gave it to us. He can't indian give it away. Oh my god
I want to hear what people interpret us as and like
I mean, it's worth a shot. I mean, I I think this is way more fun having people just like don't you think it's a little
Late in the game to like start putting like stipulations on what is or isn't acceptable
It's just about what we like. Yeah, that's right. That's right
Every single time this section of the show comes up everyone debates if it's a good section or not if it has called
What are the rules?
I feel so bad for heroes like akazi who have slaved away and worked really hard on something and this is good
This is a clusterfuck of a
Really bullshit isn't it everyone shut up. We know we know this segment is a clusterfuck. We know okay. We know right
I like that. I
Nothing I have ever said
On this segment. Do I intend it to be a hard and fast rule in my mind?
Like it's all like suggestions, but like I will upvote whatever I think truly deserves it and it can break all the rules
I've stipulated. All right. He just here's what's going to happen. There will be a time
I think we established that the cutoff for the themes was I think the end of july. Is that what we said, tom?
Yeah, really? Oh, shit. This is doomed
So we said the july you say it's doomed, but we've already gotten good. Okay, whatever. It doesn't matter
The point is by the july 31st is the cutoff date at that time
We're done and we will go through all of these and we will pick our favorites and we'll decide what's best
And then we maybe we'll do a final round or something. We will figure it out
We'll just take it all covers and we're trying to we're this is us trying to do our best to give you
The tools to make something that we will accept. That's I mean, that's how I'm thinking about it
So, you know, fuck it. We got we got like six more to go akazi. Great job. This was awesome, uh, but band
All right, peace to be themed. All right, where the fuck is this, right?
Okay, this next one, uh, give me a second. This is from um, oh wait, this is a meme one
Okay, this one will not be accepted. Should I even play it? Should I even play it? Well, I don't know. I don't know until I've heard it
Well, I guess we better play it then and find out. All right, let's uh, here we go, uh, play
A go it's gonna be retarded
Wait a minute
Oh, wait a minute. It's it's okay. It is it is
Windows stop stop stop
Stop this needs to stop right now. Okay. Okay. Stop. Um, it is windows xp startup sound one million times ear rape warning
That's what that was. All right. I forgive me for what's going on. Yeah
Next I don't know why that was even the question
I I think there was put there's a meme and I should have known better. All right, so here we go. This is another one
All those years on fortune still can't see it coming
Okay, our next one is from a
Excelular or at cx
7001. All right, this is called uh, welcome to the pcp dimension
Here we go fucking play right now go
Oh wait, I think I have to oh, okay. Sorry. I have to skip you really you really forked it. Hang on. Hang on
Here we go. Come on. She shut up play
That's it. I want that to go on for longer. That was the intro to a theme
No, yeah, wasn't that used before somewhere? I thought it was no no no
I mean like it feels like the intro to a drop that doesn't happen, but I do
I would say it isn't really appropriate as what we want
But personally if I was in charge of a podcast, I would find that so fucking funny and how inappropriate it is
I would vote for it
Didn't you just get finished saying that a thing can break all the rules, but if you like it you'll still support it
Well, the hero for the fucking thing it breaks. That was one of the rules. That's what I'm saying
Dude, Ben. That's literally what I'm saying. I'm saying it's so fucking funny and how inappropriate it is. I'll totally use it
I would totally vote for it. I mean wait, but but it's just awesome guys. This is fucking awesome
And it would be great. I would be I would be I would be happy to have this as our
Enter to our podcast. Well, I don't think it fits the tone of our show, but I do like it. Yes, it does
Well, that's fine. Anyway, point is point is I'm still not super big on it because like what hippo said
I was expecting something more so like if just if this dude could expand it to where after that
It's like 30 seconds of like kick ass catchy techno
At the end of the vocals it kind of burst open into sort of a base drop and then that faded out
Hold on. Ben. That's the reason I know 30 seconds is too long. I know 30 seconds is too long
Here's the thing though 30 seconds that can then fade out to the podcast
You see right because it would be an approach it would be weird if it like cuts out all at once
And then we start talking you have it fade out as the talking begins and 30 seconds gives you enough leverage to use that
You'll probably almost never hear the full 30 seconds though
I mean, yeah, he's just saying to have like a buffer. Uh, okay, so he
Let's just ask Teddy Lee. Let's call up. Uh, who's that? Who's that guy who just died that edm artist guy?
Next all of them
Yeah, let's call the skrillex. Okay. Here we go. Next one is from uh at sandisky
This one is called a pcp songoo hashtag pcp theme
The description says this one goes out to my homie. That's what it says. Uh, so let let let us play it now. Here we go
Okay
Yes
Oh, there he is
Nice
I do like I don't know if I like as much as the last one, but I do like it
Yeah, I don't like it as much. I mean it's it's getting closer like it is it is melody focused
But okay, the melody is just a little bit too goofy for me. Like it was kind of perfect for me. That would be my theme
Yes
What what if we each whoever was hosting the episode had their own piece? Oh god. I mean, all right. Let's let's not let's not open that door
I mean, you know, we can each have a separate single for each of our character themes, right?
It's like uh, there was there was a thing that the one piece episodes did
Every one piece episode had like a break in the middle with a commercial break and during those breaks
They would pick one of I think up to nine, uh, like the little uh intermediate tracks that would play
That would be and all the all the members of the star had crew had like a little there would be an animation of them and their own theme
And uh, uh, you would be like whoever was like most relevant to that episode generally would be like the person
Here's what we do. Here. We have to change and evolve the the piece of people in contest. Here's what we do
You now have to make nine separate
From the character and they have to fit every leitmotif into one cohesive track that is both iconic
You have to do it. Yeah
Just like my boy you need to have to be intelligent and nihilistic like so great and powerful
Yeah, basically basically like condense s descend into like 30 seconds
Yeah, please do that all of you you fools
Uh, good work. Sorry. I don't appreciate that. All right. Next one's up is from at larkin loafin trap or arkin
This is what is this one? Just hashtag pcb theme entry. Okay. Here we go. Uh, let me fucking disconnect this
Play and go. Here we go
Oh
Hey
Oh my god, yeah
Dude
Guys, I know that I've been I've been pooping this entire idea and then I'm against it on every level
But that was kick ass. That was fucking
Okay, oh my god. This is what we've been waiting for. This is what it's built to you all doubted me
I'm sorry. I'm sorry to be a downer. It's not that it's not that I don't think that kicked ass
But I do
Kind of I do kind of mind that it does not reference like what the pcb actually is in any meaningful way
Ruins your life. Oh, no, that's what's good. That's why it's good. The pcb is such a weird nebulous thing
You're such a weird nebulous thing
They've re-context like they just reference to dog pcb. Yeah, I like it. It's funny. I like it. It's funny. I do like it. I do like it. I do like it.
Okay, but if we're talking about cons if we're talking pros and cons for me a big one big con of it is that it is not about
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay, but but but
Um, somebody sees like on youtube. There's this video
PCP colon some random topic. I like going to think that with that intro that it's about drugs even if
The drugs are not available. I think I know you guys have repeatedly brought up that you aren't really fond of the whole reference to drugs
I think it is literally
Negligible and just a funny goof and I don't think anyone's going to be confused. Oh my god a podcast called pcb
Obviously, they're talking about this incredibly illegal dangerous drug. That must be what's going on here. No, you're right
I don't think it's possible
But I'd love to see if someone can somehow
Abstractly not not like hammering in too much but tie it into the pcb from fucking bakuman
But there is no bakuman opening theme because it could never be an anime. So I wouldn't even know
You'll never have a good theme just like the pcb and bakuman because we'll never be an anime. We're too controversial
I'm a total tangent here, but wouldn't it be cool?
You guys if they made a bakuman ova where they just animated like all the series
Oh my god, I would be so awesome
I would not I want otters 11 right now. I was just gonna say I would pay so much money to see otters 11
Yeah, it's it's the best one by far. Um, well arcane. I mean needless to say, uh, incredible
Yeah, I think that was the best one so far. I love it
Amazing
Don't fucking yon at me you piece of shit. Go to sleep
Yeah, go to sleep fucking die
Uh, okay, we got another one up. Uh, this one's from uh shit
Gavin Watkins
Gavin, thank you the Gavin Watkins at yo, I'm hydra. So I guess he's also hydra. And here we go play immediately
All right
Oh, this is cute
Midi instruments, hell yes
Oh, yeah, well an instrumental of an adventure time song
I would say if I had to pick any of the ones that we've seen so far
I mean, okay, I would go for the the fucking dark island of nine souls one whatever the fuck that one was
But like if I had to pick a normal one like that would be the one I picked like I'm not like
Super great on it, but I'm assuming the person made this specifically reflecting all the things that I was saying
I wanted in the theme and they tried their best. I mean like I don't think I could I mean I couldn't do any fucking better
So good job there again. I like I like it and it sounds good
But it doesn't it doesn't strike me as
Right cp song
Yeah, I mean either but like it's at least it's at least somewhat in the right direction that I want at least
So like not that the tone is wrong or anything. It just it could be a song for a lot of things
Yeah, it could be a song for a lot of things. Yeah
I mean, I don't think it's necessarily a detour like the fucking dick show theme or even like
John Tron's theme, right? It's become his because it's John Tron not because it's a super distinct song
That's that's fair
I remember I used to be pretty obsessed. I really wanted like a theme song and I kind of have one with well for me
A map of I guess not really anymore
Uh, uh, I wanted one that was like like John Tron's and like I knew this the whole time
But really it was that like I wanted like to be
Famous like John Tron and just have a theme song that like was associated with that
It wasn't it wasn't like anything magical about the theme
He just fucking grabbed it off of like Newgrounds music portal
You told me that Ben and I spent like weeks hunting Newgrounds because I wanted to be like John Tron
And like find a theme on there and like it's not bad
You can go in there like that's how I found the music for the the the champion game that I made
I just went in there and I and I found a
Artist who had like their music was in there and listed as like yes
Anyone is allowed to use this music if you give credit. I was like, okay, sweet. That's so awesome. Yeah, it's fucking sick
Uh, okay. Well, we got we got one more for this round and this is from uh on the youtube is leos enigma
It's called should be surfing
TPC theme submissions should be surfing. Wait, what was there to let me get there?
It was uh dog of power. Thank you. Thank you. Okay. Here we go and begin
I'm hearing a lot in my right channel. Yeah, not so much in the left
Oh
Okay
I'm not losing it leos you're losing them
Hey
This is I mean, is there a lot of am I am I crazy or is there a lot of the same note over and over again?
You're not wrong. You're not wrong
Uh
Leos, uh, I think that was a little simplistic for what I'm looking for
Yeah, I mean, would would you blame me leos my hero my friend for for choosing one of these other god kings compared to
I will say I offer it. I'm just kidding dude
I do like in general the idea of a podcast intro that employs the aesthetic of a like
Juicily plucked stringed instrument
But it would I wouldn't want it to be about like, you know unique notes being played like, you know
Just a very simple but nice and just melody and also that that aesthetic would never work for a podcast with seven people on it
Well, I don't mind what he was going for but I don't think the execution was quite there
Uh, it was you know, he just he this guy plucked a guitar
I mean, I I made demos of guitar stuff when I was practicing he plugged it in he recorded himself
And you know, you didn't do anything else to it. So yeah, what's that one?
What's that one fucking improvised like 10 second guitar thing by the guitarist from red hot chili peppers
It's just like it's just like really good 10 seconds of guitar improv. It's so fucking good
I'd put it on a podcast even if the podcast was totally different. So be as good as the guy from red hot chili peppers
Be as good as that guy flea. Yeah, that'll that'll not flee. It's the other guy
Uh, well guys, all right, that's it. So we're done. That's all of them for today. Now. This was provocative. This is this is fierce
This is fabulous. Uh, we these are going into the vault
Uh, and we'll get back to you on the july 1st or after july 1st when we when we have some information about the fucking theme
That we'll be using for the till the end of time
Uh, there you go. That's it. Okay, here we go
Time for a fucking fan art section. Yeah. Oh, I'm excited. I'm excited this fucking week. Oh, there's some good stuff guys
Oh, there's good stuff. I sincerely doubt there's any good stuff
I'm there's kind of a
Category that's collective. So before we get to that, let me just highlight these two the first is from gyaku shell
Uh, guys, just go to the fan art thing. You'll you'll see it there. Uh, oh my god. Oh my god
Look at this fucking rad con three arena arts. Oh, yeah, legendary. Oh, yeah, incredible. Yeah, this one's fucking incredible
It's uh, fucking all of us in our like intro poses that give us so beautifully
Animated why is she crying? I wasn't wondering that like why?
Because
Yeah, okay, and I I absolutely love school shooter aesthetic give in these. It's it's great. It's fantastic
And me looking absolutely devilish in the back. Absolutely devilish
God, this is so beautiful. This is like so good. And you know, I want the whole rad con logo
Like he redrew it himself. Like he didn't just use it. Oh my god. It's fucking and ben looking great
Tom looking also pretty school shootery
Excellent, or that he's just about to to slag some cryptos in fucking halo three if you know what I'm saying
I don't know what you're saying. I can't don't worry about your words
And and of course, uh, also did you there moving on?
Next image, uh, before we okay, this is the one I wanted to point out, um
I'll I'll put this in the fucking in the main chat here. Just so you can see it
This one of just of ben living the alternative lifestyle
Yeah, last week's episode
Why didn't he add me with this?
I he well, he just put it at the I mean because he listened to the episode obviously it's also ugly
By the way, this is this is uh at ill die 314. Oh wait, maybe dude. Yeah, I would this is fucking
This is true or I would I would legit frame this. This is excellent
How he explains it
Yes, it's because there's nothing going on here. That's what makes it beautiful. Yes. What does it mean to live the alternative?
Indistinguishable
Like the alternative lifestyle is pretty much defined by whatever it is that I do
That's true and it gives gives right it means to lean against an invisible chair
That's what it means
It's because you're you're so poor you just have to pretend you have
A chair sitting in the first place and you your high tier it's fourth dimensional consciousness manifested out of nothing
In in crowd I'm proud of myself
These are these are great. I love that one. Okay. Now we're getting into the themed section of our program here. Oh, yes
All right guys, so we went we went just before oh my god
The idea of the violent violence has uh has really taken off and a bunch of fan art has been drawn at our request of mage
Slaying in vicious gang warfare and being the leader in a in a third tribe. We know she is
post apocalypse a hellscape that is Lithuania
Indeed, so I never knew that Lithuania was an extension of endless war, but apparently it definitely is it's definitely
Okay, so look at this first one. So like corrupted purple slime leaked over there and shit went really bad
Oh, yeah, too. Totally. Okay. So look at look at the first one. I like the links for art
Okay, so this is I think the first one we got um already look at that jojo power pose mage. Yes her nail covered bat
The so okay now if I'm reading this crap, so that's a very endless war right there
With her light purple there. That's the violent violence versus the indigo interlopers or whatever the fuck we called him
Uh, that that's the ones who were dead on the bottom. Am I wrong? Yes, is that right?
Man, I really really wish I'd been on the fighting podcast. It sounds like it was a great time
God damn it and the tiger's oh
Oh, so it was in the fighting episode where the whole mages violent thing took off and became its own lore. Oh, okay
It's true. It's true. We went on like the discussions about mages like brutalities
Well, that's good. The only one on the fighting podcast who actually fought
It's true. It's true
I'm glad that I finally fucking incited a good pcp meme by like at like bringing this up because I remember two years ago
I was the one who fucking said she got about the yellow thing
Well, isn't it tom who said literally the violent violence? I believe I did coin the term but mage was the one who gave it life
So this one by links is my favorite pcp fan art ever. It's so dynamic. It's uh, I love mages pose here
I absolutely love it. What's up with the tigers are tigers a thing?
From the discussion. Yes. Uh, like yes, I said like that's the true actually listen back
I'm not gonna
Yeah, we don't want to ruin it for you here. Okay. You're really gonna experience in line. Right?
If I was like
Yeah, go ahead mage's uh
Links's art is so good at like carefully controlled derpiness like the derpy look on mage's face in the center is perfect
Her incredible dominant pose. It's amazing
And I just love how she's just so like plainly feminine as well with just like a plain
A skirt
Yeah, it's very cute looks like a girl who like goes to school
But then like on her way home from school. She picks up her bat and you know, yeah
Takes her tiger. It's it's like in the it's like in fucking like japanese mage and shit
Yeah, exactly. You've got just like cute girls who are all so badasses, you know, generally. Yeah
It's a good aesthetic. I love it. All right. Well, this one's a winner
Obviously, uh, way to fucking go links for art. This is the best one. Okay. Wait a minute. Maybe those are links
Because this person's a links. I mean, I don't fucking
Hard to say
Okay, so the next one is from uh never paint. Uh, let me link it fucking here in the main thing
This is this is also my new favorite pcp fan art of all
Also, if you look at the pens, it's not very big. That's like drawn pretty small and they got all that detail. That's true. That's pretty impressive
Excuse me. Um, but you did not use the correct the hexadecimal value for mage's artwork
I would please like it if you would correct this. Oh, I am lethal aura mage. Please do not disrespect me
That's right. You got it. You didn't go out and buy the hexadecimal pens that you can get correct hexadecimal value
So there's a lot of details in this one and I think a lot of them are references
Like I see a drug needle. I think and I remember her referencing drug needles in the childhood episode
Uh, oh shit. I didn't even know there's also what looks to be like
There's a yo-yo on the ground or a prostitution house in the back skull vandalism skull graffiti over there
Right, but there's also like there's also a building that has a flag out with like a heart
I'm assuming it's like a whorehouse or maybe a warehouse or something. What's kind of presumptuous?
I don't know
Yeah, as ben with his heart avatar obviously a prostitution
Yeah, please. No, no, no, quit heart shaming. But let's depart his fellow heart users
The stop sign that I threw stones at
Oh
Is that oh, yeah
Is that is that a lithuanian stop sign though? Is that what they look like? I recognize it as a stop sign. Okay
Oh, yeah, no, no. Yes. Okay, so sorry not a stop sign the sign, but it was a triangle. Sorry
I I didn't mean it as I just I just got so excited about this
I like you know, you know what that sign says it's got a black dot in the center a danger rocks will be thrown at this sign
Watch out. There's lots amazing. Um
Like both both never paint and links are on my fucking rolodex
If I want to go around shopping people to like hire commission people to do illustrations for something in some point in my career
Like these people are top on my fucking list
Fuck
Yes
Very nuanced and it's in its references. There's so much going on there. I'm I'm I'm actually it's so dense
There's so much going on. There's so much going on because I was for the shit like I never owned a yo-yo
I always wanted a yo-yo
Oh
Fucking dope, dude. I just love how like it's all like it's fucking wrecked like all these. Yes. This is like wrecked buildings
It's so cool. This is urban
It absolutely is. Uh, so okay. Next one is from our boy l1 cas lue with some underscores
Fucking links lanes lanes lines as moment. Oh, right
Lames, whatever. He's yeah
We got the post cold war tigers more tiger memes excellent
And I hope he doesn't feel bad that like we were taking him after the two like masterpiece arts like this is good
Like, you know, I hope it doesn't feel too shown up. But like this is pretty cool
The expression is really good. The expression is great. Yeah slames slames has like a very like rough like pen
I quite like it a lot. He goes with the theme. I like how in the background it sort of looks like
The pain's coming off sort of sort of that sort of look. Yeah. Oh, it's yeah
Oh, it's a bit grungy look. Oh, it's it's yeah, it's a tiger. Yeah. Yeah. Yes. Okay. I didn't notice that
Those eyes are intense. It's fucking awesome. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
He's using his photoshop skills. It's a great effect. It's beautiful. Beautiful. So true
Well, I don't have much more to say about this. I love the the goofy city in the background
But okay, and we I think we mage just posted this one in the thing
Uh, they they always seem to roll in right around when we're recording. We get a bunch more. Well, they know we're recording
It's time. Look at this one from at miski from miski. Miski's really good. And I fucking love this
Fucking solid snake mage urban warfare killer
She's just fucking
Oh, shit. I was wondering if this was
I just love how there's just oh, yeah, this like there's just so many different ways to interpret metal gear, right?
Like it's all the same concept. We have these videos all the same pocket
Yeah, because at one point mage gets banned from her neighborhood and has to sneak around everywhere and hippo specifically said it's now metal gear
And here it is
Oh, shit. You know, I love it. I love the color. This is so good. I love how the
Orange and purple orange and purple in the foreground and then the yellow the yellow orange the background and then the yellow on mage
I really like the light coming through the tire swing
Mm-hmm
It's probably yeah, I like the mage posters. Okay now there
Wait, that is oh your posters. Oh, yeah. Yeah on the trees. There's one. She's not allowed in our neighborhood anymore
She read it. Oh, shit. Oh, I get I thought that was somebody's feet with a white sheet draped over their body
That's where my brain went. Well, that says a lot about your brain, Nate
Indeed does you does too many clan meetings, dude. You just outed yourself
Fuck me, dude. Uh, let me actually we just got another one five minutes ago from asha am
Oh god classic. Yeah. All right. Here we go. Oh my god. You're gonna love this one mage
Fuck just click on the link because there's several pictures here
Uh, oh my god. These are so fucking adorable. Are you posting it in the main chat?
This is in the main chat. I just posted it. Just take a look at twitter
Oh my god, this is so adorable asha. I fucking love it. This first one's almost like lolita like oh my god fucking
These are
Fuck
Oh mage
Why have you not joined endless war? I don't want to fight because she's too powerful. She's got her own gang
She doesn't want to have to bring the violent violence worker childhood
Yeah, that's that's that's actually canon. That's true. That's true. We established that I like the last one
Yeah, the grin is so good. I I got a chastiser though asha. You you did not use hashtag
PCP fan art so I almost missed these I just happened to find them so be careful everybody
Who knows how many millions and millions of PCP fan art go unread every single day
People fail to hashtag them properly. You gotta watch out. You gotta watch out for that. Well, great job asha. Fucking beautiful
Yeah, I just want to say thank you to everyone. I'm honestly overwhelmed. This is just so so nice and so cool
It's fucking great. I mean this is incredible me. I just the idea is so fucking amusing for me that like
Yeah, of course. Yeah, well, it's it's the classic, you know, fucking anime trip with like badass little girl
It's just divinely inspired by being actually kind of true
Yeah, exactly
Goddamn, it's so fucking good. Well, I mean on this fucking high note. Uh, that's it guys. We're out of fan art
We're out of everything. That's it for this fucking episode
So, uh, get out there make us more hashtag pcp fan art send it on twitter hashtag pcp themes also on twitter and shit
Uh, and just get the right fuck to work. Make
I hope you all like the fact I'm in the closet so there's not that much echoing because I am so sweaty
It smells like an entire bathroom here just because of me
Oh
That's some form of right there. Here's some fan art for you. Hashtag diarrhea divu
No, no hashtag divu sweaty divu in the closet
You're right. They have to have it naturally. All right. Thanks for being here everybody. Hey, uh, uh, you like money
We like money. Give us your money. Uh patreon.com slash the procrastinators podcast
So, no wait, it's just the procrastinators, right? Patreon
dot com
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators. That's what it is. Thank you one dollar. You're in our bonus lounge
We will see you you're cool. You hang out with us. It's all fun five dollars
You get all I think we're up to 15 bonus episodes. Jesus christ. Please stop no more
Thanks, we've had enough voted. Please don't do it guys
Five dollars and you're in there. Yeah, have a good time follow us at tbcrasn is on twitter
More videos coming a couple more rad con things to get out
Hope you that you enjoyed the fucking rad shot video if you have not watched that go watch it
What are you doing? It's like the best thing to come out of rad con except of course for dance off toilet seat
Thanks for watching everybody
what
Ten paces fucking ten paces. I keep forgetting. Oh my god ten paces and draw
I have to edit ten paces
That makes me feel better because there's something I'm working on as well like two things that uh
As long as everything's not out except for that. I'll feel better about myself
It's time to say goodbye everybody. Thanks for being here. We will see you next time
Gather
Find the power deep inside you turn it up to a degree. It's right in front of you. Can't you see just listed the pcp