Greetings all, and welcome back to another episode of the Bro Crastinators Podcast. I'm Nate
Bodzman, who are joined by Ben... Ben the Bodd Saint. Yeah, that's the one. And Hippo.
Justify your existence. Did you say Hippo? I did not. I was still asking you to justify...
You know I can't do that. Bibbon Bake is here. Hey guys, I'm here to bake cake. You know, I'm
absolutely certain that... By the way, Gibb, I'm sorry, this episode is sponsored by the
B emoji, the big red B emoji. Venus, yes. I prefer the blue one, but alright. Okay. For all of the
millions of people who are currently typing, oh my god, Ben, oh my god, Ben and Nate on the
fucking PCP. I can't believe it. I got it unsubscribed right now, they say. The 15th time they've said it.
Hippo, I saw your comment on the last episode, and I really liked it. As much as I love people
shitting on Ben, you gotta give him a chance, ladies and gentlemen. So you don't have to go by,
someone made a comment that was just like, saw Ben was on this episode, did cancel, deleted,
and Hippo was like, guy, you don't have to be afraid of him. I know. If I can talk about animal
crossings. I think you can too, ladies and gentlemen. I have to live with him. Nate tolerates it.
All the rest of the idiots deal with him. You have to pay, and that's great.
They love it. Well, there it is. They love Finn doming us. Wait, are they Finn doming us,
or are we Finn doming them? I think we're Finn doming them. Is Finn doming where there's a furry
dolphin and then double matrix? Is that guy from Adventure Time, or he tells you what to do, he
puts you in a hat? I can't hear anything. It's my fault, but I will quickly say that Finn doming
is when you're like, hey, hey, you fat loser who I will never have sex with, give me money,
and then they do. Right, like watching an episode of Adventure Time. It sounds like just bullying,
but, you know, smart. Well, yeah, yeah. I mean, you know, the way I'm saying with it,
cuckoldery can be, and originally was, just simply a fetish that some people enjoyed,
even though they are weirdos, but you know, it's okay to be a weirdo sometimes.
Speaking of weirdos, all right, here's what I've been thinking about all the time, every day,
all day, and especially just right now, is the Digi's neuro typing chart that came out,
and the whole like, lexical and impressionist and lateral and linear and putting yourself on
the chart and thinking about the chart and seeing where all the things go on the chart,
and I really like charts. I really like it. I wish Digi was here to talk about it a little more,
because I am, I'm big stupid. Well, I'm not stupid, right? But I always thought I was stupid,
until I realized I just, I think in colors and shapes and feelings and entire videos, like,
instead of words. Well, that doesn't rule you out from also being stupid.
Yes, this is also a case. But it's like, I was just thinking the other, like today,
it's like, wouldn't it be great if like, instead of somebody asked me a question,
and I have to like, think of all the words that like, creates. What do I miss? What do I miss?
We're talking about Digi's neuro typing. Can you hear me? It's still says I muted.
It still says I muted. Okay, whatever. Well, okay. If you hear me, it's on.
All right, there we go. Yes, yeah. Anyway, what did I miss?
Ellie, is there a cut that? No.
No, that was gold. Okay, I'm sorry.
Neurotyping, we're talking about.
Oh, what is all this I've been hearing about neuro typing?
It's, it's when it's when it's when it's when lol, that's what all you need to know.
Okay, I'm listening.
So, all right, I was thinking about the fact that I am pretty impressionist on this chart,
this, you know, made up bullshit chart, but it is, it does say some truths in a way.
What chart?
The neuro typing chart. Oh, Ben doesn't even know the basics.
You don't even know the basics. I don't know what you're talking about.
Digi made. I've been seeing this word thrown around a lot.
All right, I will, I will try to explain. There is two axes.
And we, is it, is it, is it galaxy brain versus smooth brain?
Not quite.
No, I think that was one I made.
It was, what was the third axis?
Oh, cringian based.
Wrinkle? Wrinkle versus.
No, cringian based was one.
Galaxy. Smooth brain and galaxy brain.
And there's a third one.
What was it, big brain versus small? Did you?
No, that's smooth and galaxy.
It's a, is it Chad versus Virgin?
Oh yeah, Chad versus, yeah.
No.
Yeah.
Okay, if you say so.
The chart, the virgin smooth brain, something or other.
I was, I am, I am definitely Chad, Chad cring galaxy brain.
Oh, we should put.
Actually, no, no, no, I'm Chad virgin neutral on Chad virgin.
We should put, we should put all of the different iterations of that chart on the neuro typing chart.
Yes.
Right, right.
All right, so where each, the neuro typing chart is a thing Digi concocted, which
in a, in a brief summer summary,
depicts on a scale or a chart,
your way of thinking in terms of how you communicate ideas to other people
and how you think those ideas.
So on the left and right, there is lexical on the left and impressionist on the right.
Lexical is people who think heavily with words and can't understand things that are like vague
and sort of airy, fairy, weird, like, like jazz or whatever.
They need things to be regimented and codified in a language that has rules that they can follow.
So they are very particular about words.
And the other side of the spectrum of that is people who understand the gist of things
far easier without needing words to be involved.
And they can use words interchangeably without feeling that there's any problem with that,
which is why there's so much, you know, miscommunication between different types of people,
depending on where you are on the chart, you, you know, I'm very impressionistic,
which is why I struggle with words constantly.
And I'm like stupid.
Impressionism sucks.
This post was made by lexical gang.
Fucking lexies.
I thought of, I thought of disparaging terms, right?
The lexies, that those, the thing.
And then the other time, the other side is the imps.
Fucking imp.
Yeah.
Fucking imp doesn't know how to fucking string a sentence together.
Stuttering.
What about, what about, um, what about pressies?
Pressies?
Oh, what's the drug over there?
Oh, no.
Oh, like imp, okay.
Yeah, maybe.
Just talking around ideas.
You know, there's no such thing as a bad idea.
There's no such thing as a bad question, only a bad idea.
Sounds like impressionistic thinking, and I hate that.
Anyway, it's really funny as a meme, but I also really like it.
And on the other side of the, the graph going up and down.
I've been, people were calling me an externalist on Twitter the other day, and I didn't know.
Yeah, that's where he placed you, I think.
The graph is split up into like squares that have names.
I don't really, I'm not so far, like, that I understand all of these different titles
within the chart, but I do, I generally agree with the, the fact that there's a sliding scale.
Left to right, lexical, and impressionist.
That's the way you think.
If you haven't seen it, Ben, this is Digi's thing.
This is where he put all of us.
I found his tweet with the placement image.
Yeah, I am him.
And then a top to bottom, at the top is-
You're a centrist, Ben.
You're a fucking centrist.
At the top means, I guess so.
At the top is lateral thinking, and at the bottom is linear thinking.
I'm not quite as sure about what this means.
I've been struggling with this one too, but I know that lateral means you have multiple
lines of thought at any one time.
Lateral is like thinking outside the box.
Yes, and linear is being like on one point focused on like one idea at a time, is my
understanding.
The way I've been thinking about it is that if you're very linear, you can focus on a
task a lot more easily than someone who's laterally minded, because-
Maybe it's like one really thick band as opposed to many thinner bands or something.
So like a linear person will focus on one task, but will find it hard to multitask,
and a person who is lateral can, it's not always a rule that they can literally multitask,
but they can have multiple different thoughts going through the head, which may
like interrupt each other and get in the way of each other.
I know from, you know, you may have heard multiple times where I start a sentence,
and then I think of a better way to say the sentence before I finish the first sentence,
and then I start the next one, leading to confusion and like me sounding like I don't
know what I'm saying.
Sure, I would do that too.
All of this sort of like this stuff has been, it's been cool, and I can't think of the words,
but which is the frustrating thing.
Knowing that I can't think of the words is helpful for me just to think like a ground,
like a foothold from which I can start to like actually analyze how to do things in life.
But still, I don't have the words for it, and I need some lexical people to explain
this chart in more words so that I can understand it better and make videos about them and say
the words instead of writing them, because I can't read, I don't like reading.
You know what I think was a, did I mention this last time that like you and me doing
the potty cast together, it was funny at the beginning how we totally approached it from
like totally opposite sides of like appreciating this same thing that we both loved one piece.
It's funny how things fit on the chart so easily, because it's such a broad idea,
and you know, diametrically opposed things, of course, there's going to be the most extreme
and the least extreme of that. So it's like it's a very, it's a good chart, I like it.
You know, maybe this is my lexic lexibias or whatever, but inherently I'm skeptical of all
sorts of charts like this and personality typing things, because I feel that they are designed
at least partially as a tool for people to jack off about how special they are,
and they could be sitting down and doing spreadsheets instead.
I mean obviously a two-dimensional chart can only tell you so much.
Did you, of course, we can see that, he said so himself.
It's funny how it seems to be across the board, lexies always think that the chart is cute,
but whatever, and then impressionist people are like, this is so important to me, I need this
chart, I love this chart. I don't think it's so much that we want to feel special, I think it's
just that it is a way of understanding thinking patterns that goes a lot further than any other
like book we've ever been told to read, or like any other explanation we've heard before, this is
more of like a way to think that is, see, I don't know, sure, as like a tool of education
into how one thinks, I find this perfectly reasonable, but it does strike me typically,
because I think that probably men in general would be more left, or more lexical, and women would be
more impressionist, whatever, it does strike me as girl shit, like, like, like INJTP, it is girl
shit, but that's fine. And I hate girl shit. Girl shit is okay, sometimes, said Ben, coming out as
trans, coming out as girl, girl leaning, sometimes girl shit is okay too, he said. And you know what,
gun down in a hail of bullet. Michelle did this, see this is the thing, Michelle did this, and I
had to savagely beat her with my belt for it, she looked at the chart, and so originally externalist
was called Room Brightener, which was a very positive time. Room Brightener? It was called
Room Brightener, originally. Did you intentionally tone down the positivity of several of these
categories, because they sounded too cool? Well, and tone down the negativity of some others.
That's certainly true, that's true. To make the words as neutral as possible. The mother's
basement one was intentionally designed to sound shitty. Well, because what he was doing,
the first video he made was he, it was the one where it's like how think with the anime girl
thinking, how anime characters think. And he placed a bunch of anime characters in these
categories, and at the time, Room Brightener's worked with all the anime characters that he was
putting there. But it's a little more like broader than specifically brightening a room,
like it's a bad description of that. So like, certain words were changed. It's all like,
in the process of being created, it's very like communal, people are coming up with
ways to interpret it and different, you know, tweaks you can make to make the chart more
accurate to real human thinking patterns. All our commenters would surely agree that I
brighten every space that I enter. I darken every doorstep I try to cross personally.
But it's interesting to note, me and Michelle have long said that there are some interesting
similarities and personality between you and Michelle. And I mean, yeah, we've kind of just
been like, well, specifically it comes into like my more, I don't know, like, I guess lexical is
one way to put it, like thought about things where Michelle is like more lackadaisical and
going with the flow and stuff. And I don't know, for whatever reason, it's come into discussion
that like, oh, you know, Ben's kind of more like you, Michelle. Maybe I want to fuck Ben. Maybe
that's, you know, the general idea. Let's discuss this at a later date.
Anyway, but of note, Michelle looked at the chart, didn't understand at first, like how it worked,
and said, I'm a room brightener. And I was like, Michelle, no, the worst thing you can do is look
at the chart and pick the one you want to be. But then we went through and we're like, oh,
you probably do fit in that category anyway. So it was like, why, why is it now called externalist?
I think straight up because room brightener sounds really, really positive. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. But why, why is it called externalist? What does that mean? I assume it's trying to
communicate the same idea that these people, they, they express, because if I'm supposedly one,
I want to know what that says. There's a Reddit made, there's a Reddit board about the Digi
neurotyping thing where people are discussing. I think there's a few like write ups of all of
the descriptions Digi gives and then people's commentary on like what each of these categories
names are and what they mean. So you can look that up. Actually, the creation of that first video,
which I'll, which I'll link Ben, you can just skip straight to the externalist section if you
want to hear what that is, which is cool. The real bombshell here is how when I watched this video
for the first time, it now had that new seek bar thing on mobile where you can fucking like,
it tells you like the chapter sections of the fucking episode on YouTube. It was like the
coolest thing ever. If, if on mobile, you go to this video, you haven't, I mean, it's on my phone
now. I don't have the app actually. I don't use the app because I can't add block through it.
The thing about room brightener is shadow guardian. I think that was changed as well.
What the fuck? Yeah, that was changed to overseer, which again, you can see
very weird. I mean, it makes sense if these are supposed to describe anime characters.
Yes. Yes. Which was the conceit origin, I think. And I feel like bottom left reasonable people.
And then far bottom left middle man, middle manager is highly derogatory. And of course,
that was mother's basement square in the center of that one. But that's been changed to bookkeeper,
which is still doesn't sound great. That's a little, that's neutral. That's fine.
Anyway, so the thing with, you know, all this, like it's totally like understandable
to question what is the point? Like who cares where you are on the chart? Everybody is on the
chart somewhere, but what does it matter whether you know or not? And I'm still trying to think,
figure that out. I would hope that what it does is allow me to like talk or like get advice for
people like me on how to think better, because I've noticed that this pattern, it really,
what it's done is that it's made me realize that a lot of the ways I think and a lot of the problems
in my life are caused by this way of thinking. And it's like a square peg round hole situation
where I haven't been trying to adapt my life to accommodate for this. I've just been trying to
force my way into the way everyone else thinks and does things. And so I'm like, sort of experimenting,
thinking of different ways to approach lots of problems, so that, so that I can better like,
you know, exist, you know, so that I can one stop being depressed quite so much, do art better,
various things that just sort of like hamper my life based on the ways that I approach
lots of things based on the ways I think. And so there's just been pretty, pretty cool
thinking about it, but I don't yet have the words. And I need a big, stupid, smart guy to
say all the words for me, a stupid, drooling lexical God to explain in clear terms what I
should do. Maybe what you need is, I mean, I don't know, it makes me think of like Bakuman,
how like the two guys were such a great team, because one guy was like the words man and the
other guy was the art man. Yeah, that's what I mean. It's like a, it's like a, I know the problem,
but the solution is like ridiculous, like, Oh, wouldn't it be great if like somebody just understood
me? That's all I need. Yeah, it's like, Oh, well, how are you going to do that? How are you going to
find that? I guess the good news is you're already working in like a career path that that's pretty
I mean, in the arts. Pretty good. Yeah. Here's the thing, right? I was thinking, wouldn't it be
right? This is this is tangentially related. But I was thinking about Google and how search
engines suck and I hate them. And they've never been good for me ever. Because specifically,
you need to know the words of the thing you're searching for before you can find it.
Ah, right, right. If you don't know the words to use, I mean, this is like a
tangentially related because Google is a computer and computers just work like that,
you need to know the words to use properly in order to like key words and all that.
So if you're looking for something like an image of a character, you already know what the character
is called. That's fine. But it's not searching. It's just like recalling. You're just gaining
like access to something you already know what it is. You type in Princess Peach, you know what
she looks like. You get loads of images of Princess Peach. You have reaffirmed what Princess Peach
looks like. You know, it's it's not learning anything. You're not getting anything. The
problem. And I totally understand this problem. It's like, but what if what you remember is,
I remember there's like a blonde prince or there's a blonde girl with a pink dress and there's like
a blue like you have a visualization, but you can't just communicate that to a computer. You
could type pink dress girl blonde hair. You can you can try you can try you can try really hard
to like get as many vague similar key words. But this is like a it's like a metaphor for this
this lexical impressionist thing is that I think so much in terms of like feelings and
emotions and and colors and shapes and like baby gay girl shit that when I go to try and
explain myself, I don't have the necessary words at my disposal to make people understand
anything I'm saying. And it's sort of like it's a brick wall I keep hitting like if in the future
if I could go, hey computer. So there's this like this this thing like and it's like this
and the computer's like oh yes, I understand exactly what you you're looking for. Here's what
it is called is called this is the definition and it's like oh god imagine a world imagine a
Star Trek world where I can go to a computer and the computer can understand me better than a
fucking human being can they can scan into my like fucking neurons and find it like here's all the
neurons here's where they're going this is what this is what this guy is thinking of in a picture
and I'm going to scan the entire internet to find out what it is and tell him I would love that
that's all I want you know what's funny about that that one tiny thing technology like that of
course does exist in Star Trek but like the main community I'm watching Voyager now and the main
communication things they'll say like computer access like all Starfleet records on you know Alpha
Prime planet or whatever give me like the historical context of like Vagundo Braxis the 14th like the
warlord and then they'll be like this man was a blah blah blah and he did XYZ it's all totally
lexical still in like the way that the Federation operates with their computers but then there's
like the weird episodes were like whoa this this alien race is like brain-skinning technology
like we've tried that but it's a little risky it's a little dangerous so I don't know I guess
there's probably there's probably like a lexical bias in the Starfleet way of doing things which is
interesting I mean that's why the show attracts me so much because it's like a big talky word show
or something yeah I mean I do like talky words I think that there was a thing Digi said at one
point in like a stream where he was talking about this neuro typing thing about the idea of the flow
of communication like certain types of people can explain things to other types in like a sort of
sort of swirly pattern or around the chart and so certain types of people are like really good at
communicating ideas like translating ideas from one area to another and I really want to see what
his like flow chart looks like because then if it's if it's accurate it would be handy to like
figure out what sort of people would maybe be able to figure out how to talk to me about things or
how I can explain things to other people and who they would be and I don't know I'm just really
interested in all of this because up until this point like I was saying it's all just been me
hitting my head against a brick wall thinking that I am just a retard that can't function in
society and it may still be the case but at least I have a label now and that's all I need
as I label and now I'm cool now I have an identity and I could cling to it with my claws.
I had an interesting experience to the day it was just a small microcosm of this I was just
watching the anime Dragon Maid is an awesome show and the opening is Aozorano Rhapsody
it's Blue Sky Rhapsody or whatever and it's by this group called Fana or maybe that's the girl
leader name I don't know and I was just like looking over their catalog at some of their
shit and I just like was looking at some of their song names and it's all in like Japanese and
fucking kanji and shit that I don't I don't actually understand or read but like as I was
looking over them I saw a bunch of kanji and I was like oh you know I can't remember how to
pronounce any of these kanji but I know that that is the kanji that represents like the concept of
like girl or woman and so I was I was looking at these like characters not actually knowing how to
pronounce them or say them but I got like a weird it was a weird sensation in my brain of like I got
the feeling of what these words were attempting to convey but not the actual like spoken definitions
of them and I don't know it was like a very impressionistic experience I saw like there was
like woman and like kind of like mother I think and I don't know girl and like school or something
and some of them I recognized outwardly others others I didn't but I knew like the meaning behind
them and I was like I don't know that's like an interest I with letters in general in English
every letter just has a sound and it's only in combination they take on any meaning but with
a language like that specific kanji actually means specific concepts sometimes so I don't know
I guess it's just like a a fast of the language that is slightly more impressionistic
I don't know I just thought that was interesting and I enjoyed it there's I thought that was
interesting yeah I thought lots of things were interesting um I that that is kind of an interesting
thing though it's like um no one person is entirely one thing or the other everybody can of course
be lexical I mean I'm speaking words that means I can you know parse words in language and get
them out um I can translate somewhat nobody is completely off the edges so that so that they
can't do any of the other things it's all I think uh like a a an ease of use how easy is it for you
to think in this particular way that's where you are on the chart when it comes to like getting the
gist I'm very good at that when it comes to explaining what the gist is it takes months
which is why it's so difficult for me to make like analysis videos because I do understand all of
this stuff but it's so hard to get it out it's so hard to get it out like all I would want to do is
like to open my mouth and like the video game would play an entirety out of my mouth that's all
right that would be the perfect translation for me you just play the video game I don't need to
talk about it you should just play and you'll get it but you can't you can't do that you need to
translate it so that people will understand because not everybody thinks like me and that's
that's just the way a lot of things are it makes me think our anime loving audience on this
anime exclusive discussion podcast uh would would would perhaps appreciate this example
in hunter hunter there are six different nen usage types that you can use and if you are on one side
of the hexagonal chart or whatever the opposite side you like lose efficiency at when you're
attempting to perform that type of nen stuff whatever so I think if you're like an emitter
which means you like send nen out of your body you can do that at 100 but like I don't know
whatever the opposite is of that manipulation someone's gonna tell me which is wrong or whatever
that's like the opposite type of nen so you're less good at it so it takes more effort for you to do
someone who would naturally be born that way or something like that like a like a yellow slime
way trying to attack a magenta slime way you know exactly it's just not gonna work out it's gonna
take more energy and yeah being yeah you better hope you uh you better hope you um you put some
stats into grit let's hope so well you know actually uh as a as a small segue from that I
was thinking how there if you are probably a more lexical kind of guy you'd probably have an easier
time uh with like the the pcp lecture format that uh that we have done and people enjoyed yes true
it's right there in the name indeed indeed it is uh but then again I mean guys like muncher way
impressionistic but then his style is very different when he does it and like wait muncher's not on the
chart no oh yeah he's on the top right he's uh he's that uh he's the fucking Kirby he's Kirby there
under devote oh i'm that's munch i missed it lol okay um well thank guys it's just the Kirby like one
of the yeah that's just Kirby uh oh and I was gonna say um uh as a as a segue from that I noticed
I didn't really hear much about this but I saw yesterday streaming apparently on corrupting
your kids I think this is like a May initiative or something ash vampire doing an online digital
bionicle seminar clearly in the style of like the uh the pcp uh lecture series I have not watched
a notification for that yeah yeah I haven't watched it yet but I notice it's scanning through it looks
like the lecture goes for about four hours and I think there's like an hour and a half of questions
at the end there is another um there was an older video from like a con like some at some convention
someone held a panel where they basically gave a um a bionicle lore lecture was it pcp inspired at
all no no it's older than that okay oh I say I say hold on bionicle I can find it a bionicle
panel ah shit videos New York comic con 2012 bionicle panel I always liked the original
bionicle masks and then the soon as they made the second generation they were stupid they were
sort of like blood to death yeah I mean I want to I want to check this out and swervy and too much
bells and whistles and it's like it was perfect before just stop stop right now I was never that
into bionicle but I can't help notice that in the comments people are referring to fans of bionicle
as bonkelheads and I love that I want to be a bonkelhead myself bonk uh incredible incredible uh
I I hope it's good I haven't checked it out but it seems people have long said that someone should
do a bionicle lecture because the lore is insane but none of us know they're they're already there
already is one I mean the one yeah you're right you're right if this is the one that I'm thinking
of it's not that long it's only like 40 minutes okay okay I'm sure there could be more but like
yeah it's it is a good it's a good idea for a topic there's like a super edgy one guy in there who's
like half demon half angel bionicle and he's the chosen one I I don't know I know there's one guy
that people always bring up as like the bionicle guy that makes this shit it's just pokemon like
all of the generations suck except the first one I wonder if you would agree well ash congratulations
and pantsu for hosting or whatever but about the format itself a couple of people were saying like
hey you guys should do like online seminars or you don't have to know there might have been a voicemail
about this you don't have to wait for red foxy socks ketu I think oh yeah okay about don't you
remember don't you remember a voicemail from last week when he said that he had a couple in mind
and he was considering whether to do them online oh that's right I might have added another one this
week that was about a similar kind of thing no no matter but uh and you know I not to say anything
negative but I just think that obviously online you have questions there you got people right there
but having a real live audience is I'm sure you could do it and it would work yeah it would be
different I'll have to check this out I will have to watch at least a bit of this and see how it goes
and uh see there's engagement I mean I don't see any reason why you couldn't just like talk about a
thing in a Skype call or whatever just talk about it into a webcam yeah I mean that circle
ask questions as I'm sure it would work it might even be just as good I don't know I wonder how
much I mean this isn't really a credit to us or anything necessarily but like I wonder how much
the victor factor is uh is like uh you know like all the zooms and the pans to interesting things
going on oh yeah in terms of like product but I wonder how many people watch the entire thing
that's a great question victor would probably relatively few like the victor factor probably
helps in making it interesting to watch because it's high def and it's not a static shot so
people may end up watching the entire thing because you know that you're sitting down people
are also sitting down you feel like you're sitting down with the people I kind of even feel that
like the fact simply the fact that like there's people together in one place and there's a camera
gives a level of what appears to be like professionalism or like
legitness that like makes people feel like oh I want to be engaged with this this is like a thing
people cared uh I think that like videos that involve more than one person always seem to like
get a a layer of like legitimacy or I don't know cred because like oh I mean if you give the
impression that you're just like a guy talking into a microphone and that's like all there is to it
then yeah it's like you know you might come off as unprofessional or it's like just some guy who
gives a shit what this guy thinks it rad con though when there's organization and a budget behind it
you know you're like these guys are important I if I don't know what these guys are talking about
then I'll be out of the conversation but all that being said though I hate to even put any kind of
negative veneer this is really cool that ash did this with uh with the squad here so I would I
want to check it out and uh Gratz yeah sure hope it went well I don't know I have not watched it
that was interesting I I'm wondering like how good the image of the the whiteboard would be like
could people see it oh there is a link in the description to the whiteboard uh I'm going to
oh it's on screen a picture or something yeah here I'm I'll see if I can post it wait a minute
the url does and wait did it not work uh I think it's broken guys uh shout out to the
bionicle lecture guys I think your url is broken and it is not taking me where I need to go so uh
maybe check that out uh give that a double check uh oh they they made the amateur oh man I did this
myself when I was doing like um url shortners they made the amatoir mistake of they put a like
the short url dot blah blah blah blah but they didn't put the HTTPS which means I as a viewer
now have to copy type in pieces into the url stupid and I'm just telling you you're gonna lose a lot
of people in that process a lot of subscriber yeah it's going down the tubes uh so uh consider
consider editing that and also the it's just broken so uh yeah more to the point that might be more
important it simply doesn't work on the board I can see from here though it says oh my god
and even more fascinatingly on the bottom it says how could we have known I wonder what that
is about tantalizing he's setting up the intrigue right away it is good job good job that's good
does anyone remember I guess did either of you play bionicle or with bionicle at all no we might
have had like a couple of the toys all right well for any of the viewers do you remember getting like
in the cereal box like the gamecube sized cd that had like the the fucking small video game about
some of the bionicle characters that was that was that's that's an ancient relic I wish I still had
that that's sick I would love to do that today I had like a open up my had like a amv like of like I
think I had the the green guy the the Rui or something but what a new for the modern age I'll
tell you okay Jeff Bezos listened up this one's for free in every amazon package I want a percent
chance of getting a disc or a fucking a micro usb that contains a bionicle video game or I don't
know a fucking fortnight whatever the kids are into these days remember get me into a quest
a who could forget checks quest I don't know but I saw the AVGN episode on it I had that shit I
loved that shit I was AVGN's uh what was the verdict um what it was like well yeah it was like
who would have thought that a cereal game was so it would be great whoa yeah it's just like it's
just wolfenstein yeah with just doom with checks you can use yeah use brutal doom uh with checks
things and you can use this brutal doom mod yeah it's awesome checks man mod for like doom 2016
or whatever okay wait it can't be 26 oh okay well I assume it mods in checks man like into the game
or something uh yeah that's what I mean just okay make a whole new pack turn all the monsters into
new high resolution high poly renderings of the slime creatures did they now whatever those guys are
that's it like id software had like just invented first person shooters basically did they like work
with id like who actually made that game I think no I think the games like the code was just out
there and people were modding they have always been open source as far as I know so that's probably
what it was fascinating it probably just literally is a friggin doom mod yeah probably
true yeah I think it definitely is that yeah that's so cool uh awesome I I like hey what if we made
it a promotional tool for our friggin corn cereal we've been talking about a couple things uh PCB
race checks checks man checks man uh you know what you know what yeah yeah I want that oh that'd be
six I'm sure I'll make that happen you know we were talking about another game I won't say it but
this one's better this one's better in every way no I would actually I would it sounds kind of dope
now that I think about it yeah sounds super dope I gotta tell you I've been I've been very unproductive
I've been having a very hard time getting anything done dude so we've got that corona ladies and
gentlemen I definitely would jump on some stupid thing to waste my time on for instance practicing
a checks a checks man race checks quest checks quest checks yeah checks quest I do it I'll do it
I'll do anything it sounds fun just this free me I I just like I've been feeling really like
laxadaisical as well it's stupid yeah it sucks that's why I've been thinking so much about like
how to change my brain so I do things it's it's so shit like I I know that like being unproductive
makes me depressed yeah and being depressed makes me want to not do anything it's a it's a vicious
cycle yeah that I'm caught in and I know it but you know vicious black hole yeah I've been in the
vicious cycle of of lack of exercise last while I did an exercise yesterday I feel great of course
whenever you accomplish something you do something I keep thinking right start exercising again for
its mood boosting properties if nothing else that's like yeah one of the one of the great things
about it I've been doing yoga in the morning feel great exercise at night while I did like once
gotta get the pattern going uh yeah once is enough it takes energy it just takes energy
so I'm predisposed to just not want to and it's boring and sucks but I shall endeavor I shall
endeavor to uh to improve and grow and change fortunately I have infinite energy for um tending
roses and animal crossing uh relatable I now have like I have like eight black ones now nice and two
purples oh and I keep getting these fucking pinks and I hate them I don't want them
fucking keep them anyway plant them around your gay neighbors to the pink the rowdy the rowdy roses
just keep sprouting up when I don't want them just keep around invading my my space no matter how
many times you claim all districts they just pop back up damn it we have to we have to answer the
the rowdy question we have to find the final solution and destroy their fun house we what are
you the whole game the whole all of endless war is about trying to solve the rowdy the rq but we
haven't done it yet one day the bq the bust a question hello there man oh you know I've been
getting really funny like using like the the the bad word in like a term that is supposed to be like
softening the blow like who it's great we uh no I uh I've been getting a series of questions on
like whoa from the one piece lecture like whoa because the the buster call like whoa what's
with the hard art like what what was that about am I missing something oh yeah I saw the ball
I've seen a bunch of we got I mean obviously we got that on the buster cast as well of course
guys it's an old word please it's been around yeah you should understand why is the buster call
called the buster call I feel like because it busts all the people I I feel like gun buster die buster
and the buster call I don't know does that word have like some connotation in Japanese it's probably
sounds cool yes one of those things like they it's a hey buster you and they hear it in an American
TV show or movie and they're like haha yes but like you like we we don't call things that
like no nobody's ever I don't know it just seems like a name like an English name that an American
thing would never be called so I have to wonder like that's definitely true why does it pop up
here and there I think that unexpected places in other languages particularly Japanese which we
hear a lot of people who watch anime and play video games and shit uh I think they just like don't
have I don't know the same kind of like thought process we have when we hear like a word in English
and they they really do just lean on what kind of just sounds the coolest and yeah you know I mean
the buster call in one piece it is in fact a phone call that is made yeah five admiral five
vice admirals and they come in and they bust the place up with cannons and stuff so okay understandable
gun but you know I think there is a reason why I don't know about gun buster I think that one was
just called that because it was cool I think die buster has a meaning but I forget what it is I
think I looked it up one time it's when you get shot with a gun you die right isn't a die butsu
the like buda statue yes it is like diamonds die means great oh my god that's obviously what it is
why am I a fucking idiot yes that's okay I don't know that for sure but die does mean big so it's
just the it's really big I think I think it's just a sort of anglicization of them calling it the die
buster as in the great buster or whatever like a bigger version I will give a slight my suspicion
sure sure while gun buster being called gun buster is wholly appropriate and makes every
totally makes sense and it's thematically you know obviously the right way I don't know about
like it still seems random it still seems like they just picked a word oh well I put on the front
that's not like the show is about guns well no no I mean it's a robot that is the most important
robot ever that happens to be called gun buster so it makes sense yes they should know why but why
is it called run buster why that name it doesn't bust guns I don't know it has a gun and it busts
it's not it's not a critique of when I think about both things when I think about the gun buster the
titular gun buster yeah what I imagine it doing I would not describe as busting per se I don't know
does make you feel good though all I'm yeah true all I'm saying is I would be interested to perhaps see
like a like a breakdown maybe or maybe a list of like usage of that word in anime and see if there's
like some sort of like genesis point where like it started just comes from ghost busters that maybe
just come from fucking ghost busters maybe maybe but I bet you could at least get Amino to comment
on where he assuming he's the one who came up with the name um I there's some information about
that somewhere yeah please do um but I was gonna say I have always thought that while ghost ghost
buster was 1984 gun buster was 1988 88 okay that's plenty of time that's plenty of time for uh you
know you know I thinking about it that is the obvious answer isn't it like the the phrase the word
buster surely like it ghost busters must be the thing oh and of course we should forget
the actual Japanese name of the show is aim for the top gun buster uh or is it just aim for the top
I can't remember aim for maybe maybe they maybe means aim for the top gun buster I either way
in Japanese the robot is still called the gun buster yes certainly true certainly true I was
gonna say I've always thought the the the second show is called die buster I don't even know if
they say the word die buster in the show I think they definitely don't they don't okay and you just
watched it uh they so they don't even say well I don't think so I couldn't infer okay there's no
there's no robot called the die buster I well I think the die buster is the really big Noriko
mech that shows up in the last episode to do oh that stuff I pretty sure that's the die buster
you know what I think you're right right and I'm wrong and that is like the great version the die
version of the gun buster is this ultimate you know conglomerate and that's fine and that's
fine I'm just gonna say I just wanted to say I always wanted to say about that that in gun buster
gun buster is central to like everything that happens so that's cool die buster sure in the
final battle it's relevant it should have been called like I don't know no no gun buster because
it's all about no no no no is so much more important than the die buster itself and it always seemed
stupid and dumb I mean I think they probably use the name for name recognition I'm sure I mean
you're right it's the die the top two aka die buster which is the bigger one I think you could
make a case that the gun buster is not really that central to the story of gun I mean it's there
well hey every every story is just about men in conflict with himself no so sure yeah it's true
that the die buster only appears in like one episode mm-hmm and was gay doesn't even look cool
who gives a shit the other men are so much cooler in die buster but the gun buster the gun there's
not really anything special about the gun like all it is is just a bigger robot basically yes that
just is better at fighting the aliens that the other robots were less good at fighting what can
episode two of the buster cast everybody and also also I think it is actually made up of many little
buster machines as I recall which I think I think all those little guys the die buster yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah the die buster is it's made up of the um the like planetary defense robots which I think
are buster machines because that is a specific thing in I believe they no they are maybe collectively
they are one buster machine together yes they are all they are all part of um gun buster number seven
which which is no no no no no is buster number seven and all of those planetary defense like
droids are like a part of her oh you're making me I mean I do wish I had kind of spent the time to
watch the show if for no other reason now I have not to be on the buster cast just to re-experience
one of the greatest anime ever made die buster it's so good hey guys they are unbelievably good
hey audience if you want to hear more about die buster gun buster go listen to the buster cast
it's me and Tom we got a lot of things wrong uh you can get mad like I said I said in it that I
thought that it was um Anna was first to directorial role which is wrong oh yeah they're enough oh my
god remember I think it's episode three of die buster where uh like the girl the mean girl with
the blue hair has her little arc and she gets the buster and no no selfishly gives up her buster
machine so that that girl can pilot one instead and she fucking does that amazing like negative
170 trillion like ice beam blast or whatever yes it makes it makes it snow on uh on the music
plays oh the fucking ending theme song that plays as that shit goes down oh god it's so good it's the
best show ever made groovy magic groovy magic is the greatest opening of all time except for it is
gurren logins but that's me hype every friggin time you know what's funny when I when I first
met Michelle and we were talking about anime and stuff and I was just like hey you know this one
grooving magic and Michelle's like I know this one and I was like whoa you've seen die buster
she's like no I was like what what she had like heard it on like Japanese radio or like Hawaiian
radio or some stupid normie shit well that if you live in Hawaii I guess you hear more of I'm a
little surprised but I'm glad round table is a popular group I guess it's a good song and it does
so so oh was it not made for the show I believe that it was but uh I assume it also made the rounds
elsewhere I guess why wouldn't you know I don't know if it's a good song yeah and it was a good song
god that's not so fucking fuck yeah I don't know all right well there you go anything else to say
about gun buster um I love it it's good obviously the ending of gun buster is kind of like the most
amazing thing that's ever happened in the history of anime but overall I'm saying it again I like
die buster we talked we talked about it I like the ending of die buster better because of how it
relates to the yeah because that's certainly understandable it is when you when you realize
the connection you go whoa it's just it's that other thing I you know couldn't agree more oh but
that ending of gun buster is so legendary because it is you know it is it is damn I mean die buster
would be nothing without gun but it wouldn't be nothing at the end of die buster after all the
sacrifice uh I forget like lark lark is gonna be there to continue the legacy and to do the thing
that no no always wanted to do but you didn't get the chance she didn't get the chance he's gonna
help her live her legacy oh god buster it's too good hey cool it I'm sorry oh are you excited for
uh uh aim for the top three big buster I can't wait David buster please call it big buster right
buster the last thing I want to say about die buster is it is weird how much it is just fully
cooly sometimes yes it is like sometimes it just looks exactly like fully cool like they just
like it's almost like they traced it it's almost like sometimes they just traced scenes from fully
cooly and put new characters in them I believe it was made I want to say two years after fully
cooly if I remember correct yeah something like that I think it was like 2002 it looks it looks and
feels very similar a lot of the time which for me is great right it's awesome I love that yeah it's
great it's a it's probably a better sequel to fully cooly than the fully cooly sequels are
have you watched either of those which I have not seen them now then I'm sure that you that is
true uh I have no doubt everybody hates them I don't want to watch them I have not seen them but
I'm not interested um by the way that wasn't a joke aim for the top three was announced to be
worked on uh a while ago I don't know if you were aware of that uh no they but the weird it is
absolutely in developer hell it was announced like several years ago and there has been exactly
zero updates since that time so I I hope they literally just let it go and they just don't do
it um let it maybe maybe let it die let it die hard to imagine them improving on what they've
already got you know what they'd fucking do they'd fucking bring in the like your name guy or you
know whatever that and they have that guy do his vision no is that you yeah yeah that's my
masaki usa I believe I think um I don't know you're so good everything he does is great guys
that's like letting nomura direct funnel fancy seven again wasn't that a great idea I mean it was
part of the original team how what could go wrong isn't masaki usa really good or you think it's
someone else wait I'm thinking of the wrong person wait masaki is the pink one guy uh and yeah he did
that yeah okay fuck you guys know he's like the most popular anime man right now whatever the
fuck his name is your name uh yeah garden words I think uh Garfield this is Garfield yeah Jim Davis
right yeah um love him Jimu Davis hey I'm sorry did I tell you guys I might have already said this
did I tell you my discovery that uh in reading the most recent one piece SPS it turns out that
Neko Mamushi the big cat his favorite food is lasagna uh no it's it's canon yeah that's true
that's amazing it's obviously a Garfield reference and like the other the dog Inu Inu Arashi
Inu Arashi loves bones which isn't odyspecific but based on his ear shape and his general coloring
I think it's fair to say they are inspired by Garfield so wait wait hang on does that mean like
who who is who is um who is what's Odin or uh Momonosuke no no the uh what's the guy's guy's
name in Gar Garfield the John John who is John it's gotta be is that oh guys from the guys from
the animal island from the elephant that's right yeah that's right oh god who's the John who's the
John to these guys I guess Odin it's gotta be Odin it's gotta be Odin now where could my sword be
you haven't met him yet he shows been one but he's Momonosuke's dad um okay yeah he's like
he got a flashback with him later and stuff we always he's like he's like the old king or
something who was like he was the old emperor he was not the shogun but he's like the old ruler
who was like too nice and wanted to open his borders yeah yeah that's correct that's something
happened I don't he got assassinated or something yeah he was killed yeah yeah yeah you spoiled it
but we we already know that god damn it that's that's ancient ass history that's set up for the
one or it is did you know Japan exists what I hate that Ben have you you've seen big mom's
flashback already right Odin is just Odin is just Bernie Sanders and like Bernie gets buried
because he's too good but he was too good for this world that does happen to him basically
but uh what was I gonna say oh all right you so you already saw uh big mom's flashback of course
during during hulking out and whatnot but did you also Ben get the same sense of
what the fuck is that when for exactly one panel okay there's a there's a lot of things I think we
did talk about like she ate her friends no no no there's that which is amazing but not right now
do I want to talk about that I want to talk about how uh big mom was on Elba is where her
like orphanage was and for exactly one panel you can see that there's like an island there and you
sit at the house but directly to the right there is some sort of gigantic mountain or cliff face
or something that looks bigger than like anything we've seen in the entire series thus far and I
want to know what the fuck that thing is do you have Elba I don't yeah you're gonna have to show me
a screenshot or something Elba island let me see I bet it did read this part but I don't remember
yeah okay here boom from the anime I gotta fucking catch it I'm only like 40 chapters behind
I gotta just catch up make like a tomato yeah look at this there's like the ship pulling up
that you can see the house and just for size comparison you can see that is a giant mountain
and then there's that thing oh my god yeah what is that is that yiggers soul is that what that would
be maybe maybe it is the world tree or like Adam tree maybe oh yeah so that is that is Elba right
this is yes this has stayed to be on Elba this is the only image we've like ever seen of it
shit maybe that is a tree it doesn't look like bark oh yeah you know in the in the manga it's a bit
more obvious that it's probably a tree oh my god that that it sort of goes outwards I never noticed
that going outward until right now shit that probably is a tree cool it it looks like it might be
a tree I don't know is there supposed to be like some kind of super tree I mean I feel like with
Elba is Norse and we all know Norse mythology has yiggers ill the world tree and whatnot so
damn sounds I just learned that at this very moment how godmother caramel was incredibly
hot when she was young and had like an amazing arc with big mom wait awesome you know mother
caramel oh oh caramel yes yeah yeah yeah yeah she smoked that was sick good stuff hey smoke she
someone updates that old image someone update that old image of all the smokers in one piece
and please put mother carabelle as a young hot self on that smoking looks so cool it sure does
like in manga and stuff it sure does fucking base spike spiegel got me got me on the train
back in the day cool base um let me see uh was that gonna bring up something else there was a smoke
that like burned for the same amount of time and looked exactly the same and was not bad for you
like could could that not be fabricated ben ben takes a hit of his vape damn if only there
were something like that no that's that's a metal thing I want to like a piece of paper that could
light like half of the coolness of the cigarette is the burning you need the fire there you need
the lighter you can get the vapor at least when you exhale which is uh which is something I suppose
it's it's a different flavor it's a different feeling it's certainly cool in its own way but
it's not one is far more so do you want to go for like the cowboy cowboy bebop jazz aesthetic or do
you want to go for like the techno futurey uh you know vape I like I like the jazz you want to
look like a bounty hunter from the future you go with the vape indeed that's true that's true
hmm but the real cool guys just use a lighter on their vape they burn it down every time
hey uh I just wanted to say in my ongoing struggle uh between the duality of man lexical and
impressionism um I've been uh watching factorial speed runs there is nothing in this world more
like a fucking spreadsheet uh or like lexically minded than a factorial speed run I I'm I'm not
sure it's like lexical because like lexical you're right I'm using the word very loose it's definitely
linear there's there's either the the lateral or the linear I think factorial might be more of a
lateral thing because you have to think of so many steps ahead um I know it shouldn't be the most
efficient well the way that I think it's it probably just boils down to math at the end of
the day there's probably just like a mathematically optimal ladies and gentlemen ben and gib I invite
you to enjoy this experience with me one of these days on this factorial speed run quest and the thing
is this man uh shout out to my boy nephrums the current world record holder for both any percent
and 100 completion on factorial speed runs um he's down to sub two hours now baby I want to be
the summoning salt to make the fucking legacy of the my boy nephrums killing the game at factorial
how many how many views does this have like this is this one is the world record 10 000 the guys
got only less than five k subs but like this is what he does my favorite thing and not my favorite
thing but something I really like is when I watch like a summoning salt video he'll talk about like
these people who are like these people that like loom large in the speed running can be like this
person like basically invented the way it's like everybody knows this guy this guy's like a legendary
speedrunner he'll show like a screenshot of his youtube channel it's like no avatar 2.5 k subs
are you like 700 subs I kind of love it's got it's got a real like like um like secret like um uh
what's the word it's a certain type of aesthetic that's sort of obscure but like you know you walk
into a bar and like there's people that you don't know are like super genius badasses in their
community and you're just sort of like oh i'm stupid I don't know and then and then later you
realize and you're like I was talking to that guy that's true every human is a is a a series of
mysteries and accomplishments that you can't know so like like this this video like revolutionized
the uh the the mario sunshine speedrunning community he shows a screenshot it's got like
150 views yes but but to the people who care it's like such a big deal I mean how many people go
and read those like uh like I don't know you got like a youtube uh video by someone like a million
subs like a news guy about like how you know like youtube has just changed its policy and it's gonna
ruin everybody uh you know whatever no no no I don't give a shit if that's true or not but he
makes a video like that and then like the actual like document that youtube published about this
will have like 100 views like like barely anybody actually read the source material
which of course is how it works and I understand why you know you know what's cool about it it's
it's like um it gives validity to it like like the story is real because nobody knows about this
thing like imagine yeah imagine how boring and lame it would be um if somebody was talking about like
the most influential song of an age and then they link to gangnam style it's like yeah yeah yeah
everyone's heard of that that's a big song who cares it's it's not special I think I think it's a
lot of um I don't know but thinking about when it comes to like the ff7 remake and whatnot I've
been thinking a lot about and I think I'm definitely going to address this in some way like uh what do
people really mean by soul versus soulless and whatnot and in short what the fuck are you talking
about these are common terms these are common terminology that's used to describe like old
versus new games and how people feel about them and why they feel like something is weird and
different about about new game styles and I what it really comes down to the short version is like
when for example in final fantasy seven the original they had these blocky models and like every
everything they did like every unique okay here's a here's a perfect uh uh idea of what soul is for
specifically only the final battle of cloud versus sephiroth at the very end where it's like the
battle within clouds mind to rid himself of the final traces of sephiroth where it's got super
sexy shirtless sephiroth and he does omni slash even if you haven't learned the limit oh my god
like the most kino battle of all time for that specific battle they made updated new better
looking 3d models of both cloud and sephiroth just for that one battle because they knew that they
wanted to like focus and more on of them have like cinematic camera angles and stuff happen there
like that is pure soul the effort they put in to like enhance that experience uh you know like for
the viewing public and stuff by doing extra work or like in an old like 8-bit game or a 16-bit
adding extra sprites just for like one little scene that the developers want to do all that
feels like soul as opposed to what feels soulless by comparison is just for example I think most
people would agree on this in ff7 remake you got a lot of characters who have like little
little side stories little arcs they're doing on the side and little like side missions you got to
do but the thing is all those characters look like generic fallout wastelanders who are just like
they look like unity assets that have just been imported and they do not feel special or unique
especially in comparison to like the main crew which are very colorful and beautiful yeah um
that distinction is really clear in stuff like that I think I think with things like
that it's like the the decision to make a whole model is a big deal because of how much I mean
Final Fantasy was already on three discs um yep there's so much space required to do those things
but like nowadays the the hardware limitations basically don't exist you can do it right in
anything the graphical capabilities of the PlayStation 4 are phenomenal and um games can
look incredible and there's like there's almost no excuse for not having everything
possible yes yeah and so like we feel that we feel that I think it just sort of feels
and it's like an unfortunate it it's impossible for something to feel
soulful because you can't you can't get a sense of how hard they're working to make something
happen I think it's nobody's fault but I think that kind of is the reality yeah what I thought
you were gonna say Nate was like okay so like yeah they made these updated like higher res models
just for this one moment so you get this moment of like whoa we've ramped it up but like yeah on
like a new like a triple A game or whatever like everything is fully rendered everything is like
fully realized and fleshed out because the budget is enormous you know they're they do that with
everything so there's no like moment wherein you go oh whoa they really they ramped it up for this one
what it's all because it's because the fucking processors are blasting it 100% all the time
I think when people say soul I think what like when I think of what that term means really it's like
I'm playing this game and I when I see something like I'm playing Final Fantasy 6 or something I
don't know and I see the like the sprite of Terra like there's that one famous sprite of Terra
going like blah and like kind of like spazzing out like in like embarrassment or surprise
or something like that and sure that that gets used a bunch but like they could have
done something far simpler you know what that's actually a bad example but what I'm trying to
convey is the the emotion of feeling the developer like despite all the limitations that existed for
them in the context they were making it you can feel them going above and beyond and the problem
is exactly what you were saying the context these days has changed where it now just feels it like
there is an expectation that everything will it look at least a certain level of quality and a
certain level of amazingness and stuff so um yeah I mean I mean there's still like potential for that
feeling if you know that the person is an indie developer and they make something oh yeah no doubt
so like I absolutely do you think do you think large budget triple a big things are impossible
to feel soulful I would say it's it's gonna be way harder it's not impossible but yeah what would it
take is the question art from adversity and a triple a budget a triple a title with a triple a
budget faces less adversity you know what I mean that's definitely true I don't know I'm trying to
think of an example of something I have played oh I got it I got it I know exactly what it is or
this is one example love like Dark Souls 3 and that's like a you know I love that game too it's a
triple a game is so much it looks beautiful and it's like a lot of soul like would that you know
I don't think I would I would argue that have you seen it have you seen that Matthew Matosa's
video where he talks about the lost souls how about that he talks talks about one is the one
people generally think is is the most soulful and I guess at the time you could say that I was a triple a
it wasn't a triple a it was it was gone the cusp they were like they had a they had a success in
Demon Souls and they that was the first actually big game Dark Souls I think a lot of it was that
like expectations really were like low like Dark Souls is where things really exploded and like
that game for many reasons that maybe people have made a million video essays about no one expected
that game to have as much like depth and I don't know cool game design stuff going on so that's
not exactly soul but it was just like good and like soul soul would be for example in Dark Souls
the fact that Ash Lake even exists in as hidden a place as this you know what that shows me that
shows me those developers were willing to make an entire huge awesome section of the game they're
willing to make it sculpted populated with characters unique NPCs an entire like the dragon
quest line or whatever they were willing to say you know what many characters are just many players
are just not going to find this and you know we're okay with that we don't need everything we've done
to be thrust in the face of every developer of every player and we were comfortable with that
because we're confident that the game will be better for this being a mystery for many players
because mystery was a big important part of much of Dark Souls early life it's it's better when
yeah there's things that not everyone even even knowing what it is before you play it for the
first time because I the first time I experienced Dark Souls was watching the digi bros play through
and so I learned about Ash Lake through them doing it talking about and playing it and even
knowing that it was there it still feels incredible to go there it does it really does just the just
the fact that you know the knowledge that the developers put it in there and didn't tell anyone
just because the knowledge is now out doesn't mean that that that is different and so it still
feels soulful in that way knowledge of the context is important and I think we're all pretty I think
we're all pretty aware of that but by the way a modern to be fair a modern example of modern day
soul easy one like okay this isn't this isn't the most soulful thing ever because as you'll see
like you have to pay extra money for it and like the game itself was lacking in many ways but
the remind dlc of kingdom arts 3 much of the dlc has horrible cutscenes the final fantasy characters
are shitty but the boss fights themselves are soulful as hell most of them not not all of them
are amazing the the my favorite part so far the marluxia data battle fight in kingdom arts 3
is so fucking soulful uh it's got all these references to like old marluxia fights throughout
history it's got this new remix of the fucking lord of the castle theme from uh chain of memories
that fight is so good and I I just love replaying it because it not only is it is a challenging
gameplay experience I just feel like saturated in the classic kingdom art stuff that I love
while being challenged by the game I I cannot get enough of it it's so good uh but and you can
contrast that with other fights that I feel in the data you know remind ones that are
significantly less soulful faithfully recreated a lot of the time but unfortunately recreated
from games that aren't as good you've given examples yeah what could you define in words
the what it means to have soul in a game yes it's kind of it's kind of a calculation I would
argue it's like effort put in like extra effort beyond what would be just the bare bones need
to like convey the idea across like over like technical limitations that existed at the time
so like everything's going to be like a degree of how much it is relative to like the context it
was in what technology was available and like your your savvy gamer should or you know consumer of
any media should be able to tell uh like what was there you know this reminds me of someone in my
stream yesterday said this was a Sam Hyde quote uh I don't know from what and I would actually love
to find it if anybody knows but it was just something like when developers in the old days
or when when like artists only had oil paints to paint with they like weren't distracted by
I don't know like fan expectations okay maybe that wasn't quite true but like miscellaneous stuff
they had they had their they had their patrons they had their rich Italian family they did they
didn't have to please those people but please the king or whatever they weren't distracted by
things like you know I don't know like should I put like a QTE in to that would break up the flow
of this segment of the game here I don't know just like an example of they had very limited tools
so it had to stand on just how good is your oil painting technique whereas with modern games I would
just argue that there's tons of things that you can put in as a distraction and I don't think
distractions from like the main pieces of the game aren't are always a good idea FF7 original had
tons of minigames but those minigames given the context of the time and place felt insanely soulful
out of nowhere in Final Fantasy 7 you're suddenly on a motorcycle chase that was like inconceivable
that would be in a game of this type at that's out of nowhere you're doing a fucking snowboarding
mission which is like my favorite part of the fucking game that you're just snowboarding out of
nowhere that's soul and it's all about the time and you can play him again in the gold saucer yeah
you can it's amazing it's amazing all right given that then I think something that would be a triple
a soulful experience yeah would be for a game to not have tons of miscellaneous side quests
and for it to be relatively short and sweet and good all the way through
that would be that would be a thing that is like a bad monetary decision you want your game to last
for 50 60 70 hours and you have what you want it to have like tons of collectibles that don't mean
anything tons of side characters that don't mean anything that don't have any like rich
character they just sort of say a few lines and they have a like please do this for me
like a game that comes out in the modern day that doesn't have all of the bullshit things that
modern games are expected to have would be a soulful moment I would respect that in a game yeah
yeah and you know like really tightly focused on you know telling the story I can imagine in my head
like if they were ff7 suffers from this to a degree the remake does but like for example
chrono trigger amazing game one of the greatest rpgs ever made that game is packed to the gills
with side quests but all those side quests are insanely soulful look I mean some are better
than others but like the fact like that game is basically modular you decide at what point you
want to fight lavos you decide how many party members you want to do it with you can even
decide if you want to ff7 revive chrono when he ff7 dies those side quests are insanely soulful
because they all tie directly into the plot give you components that like make the game
like you get like frogs final weapon they tangibly improve your experience of the game
they play with the main mechanics of the game and they do not feel like a waste of time because the
whole game is set up such that you are in control of time travel so like doing side missions would
not interrupt like anything you're doing I suppose it could have a few I think it's just like there's
a balance to strike where as soon as you feel like something could be copy pasted like a character
model or you know a mission seems very similar to another one and the rewards are like you know
crafting materials as opposed to like interesting story progression and you know things that move
the main story forward yep as long as it feels like I don't know it's hard to it's hard to figure
out exactly where that balance would be that's that's true and you know here's another soulful
moment just of history uh yes this was there they were a big studio very successful at this point
but but simply Square Enix putting in the entire opera scene from Final Fantasy 6 giving sellies
like the Maria costume like a full new sprite sheet set and making her like sing like this was
revolutionary this has never been done before and like a sprite based game insanely soulful in
off the chart soul in that whole section which is why it's regarded as like one of the most amazing
moments of all time but I mean now like if you just separate context you can look back in Final
Fantasy 6 and be like eh graphics aren't even that good man graphics like okay yes sure they're not
even that good because it was made like 20 fucking years ago or like 25 years ago more than that yeah
yeah almost 30 I think at this point and um it's like you gotta keep a lot of people these days
really seem to want to strip context out of everything and I think that's a bad I especially
there's a lot of people who want to defend the remake and I understand there are perfectly valid
remake like reasons to defend the remake on all kinds of points I would simply want them to just
remember the context of the original I think it's important and when you've got a remake you cannot
avoid being latched to the original because you call it a remake you didn't call it Final Fantasy 7
2 or anything like that you call it a remake and where does a bunch of meetings but okay I don't
want to get a whole thing about about the remake but hey Nate did you see my video about Final Fantasy
7 thoughts I did I did um forgive me I forget exactly what you said you want you want to recap
it for me real quick no I forget what exactly what I said as well it doesn't matter I remember
that there were some things that slightly disagreed with my opinion and that made me insanely angry
as all opinions that don't 100% adhere with mine do uh I'm exaggerating I think I had some
slight differences but I think your point was overall I think my point was like
you know there's always this this idea that the original you know needs to be preserved because
it's good and I want it to be something that other people in the future can play and a remake
sometimes at the argument not necessarily the argument you make is that it can obfuscate the
original by being the one that people play instead and if it's slightly wrong then that's
unfortunate because the better experience is being lost and not everyone's gonna play the original
and it's it's it's it's unfortunate and I was just thinking like could it even be is is the idea that
you could play Final Fantasy 7 today even feasible and still enjoy it in the same way and that was
just sort of like a thought process thing that is that's a good question I would emphatically
argue the answer that question is 100 yes uh but some people might disagree um yeah it's really
just sort of raising the point that like yeah there are a lot of more there are a lot more context
things that go into the enjoyment of anything um like the year it came out compared to all the
other things that were coming out how many how much revolutionary it is doesn't matter anymore because
things have come out since and now those moments aren't going to be as mind-blowing
to people who are experiencing it so it's like it's going to be a different experience no matter
what you do well that's true I would definitely say that like Final Fantasy 7 is a great game
to play now because I played it not too long ago for the first time and it was good yeah yeah uh
yeah I mean if you can do that I would argue a lot of people can too by the way my favorite thing
about that video by far is your artwork uh uh on the the main thumbnail everyone should go
look at it why is why is Tifa so hot it's just how it is man look at her uh oh I really like
your tron I gotta call the ethics department those bazoingas are are offending me they're far too
large but I like that's it that's what I like about them yeah I was just I was just sort of
scribbling doodling I drew the cloud and I was like haha it is great you know what I like how you
are um erasing the only um person of color in the cast by putting him in the bottom right corner
where the timer will appear directly I didn't realize that I was like oh shit thanks man I don't
know about you guys literally like a sense of bar over his mouth the time I feel it's great I feel
so happy uh that I have acquired an infinite supply of of end passes and word passes because
I love barrett so much a proud black man because I have such a deep bond with barrett if he were here
he would give you the n word pass I know he would I know he would thank you barrett and you got you
guys would fist bump yeah um and he would I don't know he would say nah brah sol good he would that's
just what he would say in my mind that's how it would go that's the greatest character ever
conceived in history man barrett might be the best character in final fantasy seven uh in terms of
how happy he makes my pp oh my god when him and more leaner together I feel like I feel like I
feel like discussion about the remake has largely has like a lot of it's been focused on barrett and
like I guess I forgot I don't remember a lot of people like I don't remember barrett being a lot
of people's favorite character but I hear a lot of people saying that they like the remake say like
oh barrett's so good I hear that the white women have been going gaga for this guy uh is that true
I don't know I did see some article or some like Twitter post about I don't have have I ever told you
the first time like when I played final fantasy seven yeah the first time for like that g rpj
by the way I'm right with you white women I'm one of you I'm yeah um that uh I did like I didn't know
all of the like different things you do to get like uh things to happen like yufi I didn't know
how to make her appear oh yeah yeah um script so I have to look at look at that shit up you got to
go on game fat yeah man you gotta print out 50 fucking pages on your mom's printer staple it together
keep it next to your console fuck yeah dude I I didn't want to try that um uh just because I wanted
to see what would happen and I ended up with barrett in the date scene oh fuck yeah you got the best
arc man that's the best part it up although to be fair I was thinking like oh wait why is barrett
here what is going on like and when people were talking to eris and tiva the entire time intentionally
I guess I did I like didn't know what it was funny because like because they go on that thing I didn't
even know there was a quote unquote date scene yeah and people were talking about I was like what do
you mean I just went on a ride with barrett at some point that's why just railroading everyone
down the exact same experiences gay as hell and fucking different stories and different shit
give you shit to talk about it's fun it's cool it's soul is what it is it's soul dating barrett
is the peak soul you think you think in remake part two they're gonna allow you to date anyone
except eris I would bet a thousand fucking dollars that they force you to date eris and no one else
they're gonna let you I think they're gonna let you do that that that would I feel like that would
be like an like overt sort of like downgrade I think people would hate that here's here's what I
might do you guys money you want to put money down I'll do it I'll bet a hundred dollars they
force you to date specifically eris I will put money down all right hmm I don't want to put
down honestly dollars one hundred dollars I want to take that bet because I think you're wrong
but I would feel bad winning a hundred dollars yeah uh you want to do 10 I'll do I don't know
50 I will bet you ten dollars let's do um like like a hundred million slime coin how about that
I don't have any slime coin dammit I'm broke I will ten dollar all right you and me ban if you
want to do a give two ten dollars it's on the books I have like absolutely no dog in this race at all
sure but my my gut instinct is that that is an iconic scene from the original and for them to
and like it might just not do it I feel I feel like the mission statement of the remake is to pay
homage to the original and I agree that would be the opposite of that so I don't think they would
do that well you know I haven't actually done the research I believe see here's my evidence I believe
that they just removed now I need to test this but I think that they removed the option of
Don Corneo to date any to take any girl back it used to be eris tifa or cloud because I did it
and I got cloud I think that he will always pick cloud now I'm not sure I gotta double check that
because I get everyone the worst possible dress in the remake you can give him different dresses
and stuff uh so I'll double check that but I'm pretty sure that they already flattened that out
I mean I'll stick to the but I will take the bet the bet is there it is that there will be a scene
if not exactly a similar scene at like a similar point in the story and they will allow you to
there will be a variable option that includes Barrett and it will be a thing I think so I'll
give you buckaroos I will give you anything just like you don't need to define your position my
position is there will be a date you will be forced to date eris specifically if anything else happens
like if the date happens in any other format I will give you ten dollars I'm happy to take that bet
so what if there's if there's no date do I win yes you win you win well okay I mean that's just
stupid but I sure I mean I guess you win that too okay um um what if I think no one knows if that
that's true I think there will be a date it's too iconic there will be a date yeah no one wins if
there's no okay here's what I think will happen it won't I think there will be a choice but it will
be very obvious it won't be like cryptic like it was before they already do which might be like a
little bit like oh it's like just press the button go up to the person to talk to them and that's
obviously it will be this are you sure you want to initiate date with barrett are you sure you don't
want to save and and go and like grind friendship points with someone else first are you sure you
don't want to hit this button to just to just switch to options right now uh carefully careful
get on your back and go back and forth to build up friendship with barrett
leave dropping the daycare let them uh level up a few times they I'm sure they'll fuck around
with it but there will be some sort of like variable thing I need to google this can don
corneo pick eris ff7 remake I might have just been totally wrong about that wait wait um clown
if um clown stress hey so we were talking before about animal crossing and how I've
unlocked the I've I finally understand the true meta yes tell me it's now the time okay
so I've been grinding animal crossing water in my flowers breeding roses got got a good little
collection going yeah that's all cool but I have I have seen I have pierced the veil and seen the
code behind the matrix and I understand the true meta of how to win animal crossing and it is this
it's it's all about recipes hmm it is all about getting bells is about having more recipes because
and this this unlocked this unlocked the key to my potential right to my financial future
every recipe that you make every item that you craft sells for double the amount of
what you would have sold the ingredients for so the way to maximize your money is you have
enough ingredients that you can use as many of your resources as possible to craft items so what
I've been what I've been doing is I've just been waiting for a hot item that I know how to craft
and then just blowing all my iron and all my all my wood and all my clay and stone and stuff
just making as many of it as possible right right because that's because it's double the price of
the ingredients and then it's double the price of that because it's a hot item so you're quadrupling
your value on these raw materials that you got and that's it that's it it's it's you want to have
as many as many recipes as possible so that you can make full advantage of the most of your ingredients
like uh my friend Toby he's got a coconut recipe he's a palm tree lamp I'm jealous because I have
nothing I can do with these coconuts I'm selling at their base price wasted potential now however
apparently uh off like non-native fruit in terms of like how more native fruit sells for 100
non-native fruit sells for 500 but but a crafted recipe calculates the value as though it were
just a native fruit all fruit counts as native in terms of that so you actually do get more just
selling non-native fruit raw and not crafting it okay but native fruit like I've got apples I've
just every I've just been picking tons of apples crafting them into apple umbrellas I've just been
selling all my apple umbrellas yesterday uh uh the hot item was brick ovens and so it was clay
iron wood I just I just I had like stacks and stacks of clay I spent it all sold it all to
the nooks made like 100,000 bells um that's it not bad not bad get get recipes get recipes take
advantage of hot items uh a horde resources yep for the moment for the moment when when when it's
your time to shine you can use all those sticks and all those weeds or whatever yeah double your
shit I've done that once or twice uh a little bit doing the hot item thing I suspected that it was
the right way to go but uh good to have uh clarification on that it is it is it is the
thing if you're if you're um if you're playing by yourself the recipe will always be something
that you have unlocked uh I think because I'm not like the main islander like my friend Caleb
owns the switch so it's his game so I'm pretty sure it picks a recipe from things that he has
so sometimes it's something that I can't craft but other times it is something like like a
DIY table or something and it's okay I've been grinding wood now's the time got it got to spend
it all this is this is how to maximize its value oh man okay there you go I'm so close to my fourth
I'm so close to getting that second side room oh yeah I you know I now have I have a back room
and a left room in my house yeah yeah that's where I'm I'm almost at the right room I have like 100
I would have gotten it today but I decided to invest in turnips I spent about a hundred I invested
about a hundred thousand bells huh that's the real money right that's how you get it can be it
sometimes um I invested a hundred thousand bells in the turnips I because last week last week the
turnip price has just went down it was just a complete bust it was terrible it lost like half
your investment I didn't do it that week this week I'm counting on it being different I'm waiting
for it to peak around Wednesday Thursday fingers crossed and it'll all be worth it I don't have to
wait a little bit I have to wait a little bit on that house expansion but it'll all be worth it in
the end I've been trying to figure that out what uh how do I buy turnips I have not figured this
shit out on Sunday morning okay sometimes there is a little pig walking around who has a plate of
turnips on her head and she sells you the turnips okay okay it has it's like before like 10 a.m. or
like before noon Sunday so you can only buy Sunday but you can sell anytime you can buy on Sunday
you cannot sell them on Sunday you can sell them to the nooks on any other day right and the price
varies twice every at midnight and at noon the price changes so you got to check at least twice a day
if you won't really want to be on top of but if you wait until the next Sunday uh your turnips
all go bad so you have to sell them before Sunday or it's all wasted I see I see hey by the way I
was just trying to confirm this I do believe that Don Corneo always picks cloud in the remake I
have not found any evidence so that's lame that's bad news that's bad news for me it is that's bad
news for my bet prospects but I'm this is this is different though I'm aware this is a different
kind of situation but I'm seeing a flattening of choices across the board aka anti-soul and uh
anti-soul this anti-soul is being injected in just a moment like don't freak out people like
the remakes it's just one one little moment um uh but uh yeah okay so we'll we will see when part
two comes out in here's the joke guys 2045 give or take haha hey wow it'll be a long time I will
have forgotten by the bet by then oh I'm gonna write that one down commenters please remind us
we're counting on you the collective unconscious the the pcp episode 700 yeah seven seven seven
lucky it's a it's a lucky one final fantasy seven oh did you guys know that if it before before
uh well what were you gonna say I was just going to say video game speaking of soul did you guys
know that at any point in final fantasy seven if your hp ever hits for a character for any reason
healing taking damage 7777 exactly the character goes berserk and this never happened to me at
any time playing the game but it can be manipulated to do so um then uh you just do I believe 77
basic attacks in a row which kills almost anything in the game uh if it did know that I've never seen
it it's I mean god there's so much so in those games uh pretty pretty cool pretty cool funny
uh speaking of like doing like managing stuff and selling resources I've been playing slime
rauncher oh yeah there's another one hey and I'm I'm pretty far in uh I'm in the glass desert
I'm finding all the the special guys and I'm uh the slimes and the give give a quick question
about that uh my main thought about the game does that game have any played in a no I've never played
though watch you play a little bit you and munchie does that game have a satisfying arc where like
you grow resources which like unlocks new areas of the island to explore and then you kind of yes
basically all right sounds fine yeah it sounds fine yeah the the loop is pretty fun yeah and I
love that loop I've got to a point where I've got like drone bees uh that I can oh I love the drone
bees and so in in the main area I have uh all slimes that like fruit and their favorite fruit
growing so I have like one drone be give all of the slimes fruit and one of the others collect
the plots and sell them and so I have like hundreds of thousands of gold every time I
walk through them like hey yes the you have to you have you still have to like keep track of it
because you have to like water your yeah to water the water your drones or they get dehydrated and
they can't collect your shit which is silly because they're bees and also robots that like they
be double effect like weak to water you would think no they love it but they love splashing
with a bit of water and they wake up and they continue um and yeah I've been I've been uh
collecting all these things I mean it's just a fun game I got all I've never once I guess
I've been pretty careful I've never once had a calamity in my ranch and like all of like like
tar slimes have not appeared um it's happened to me I mean if you've got like a water the water
cannon it's not that hard to deal with uh tar slimes die pretty quick they do but like I've never
even I I don't usually like making Largo slimes I like having each slime like a bunch of them
small and you um you know like their own thing I had like a I wasn't sure for a while whether
because like a Largo slime gives two podrons lol a Largo slime gives two plorts when eats
um but but but you can fit more small slimes so like I think if you have like more resources
to feed them it's better to fill up a tank with small slimes but if you have fewer like like
crops and you want to get more out of them it's better to have Largo slimes this is like my
theory I don't know if there's like a spreadsheet about the things the thing with it is like if I
want to relocate I can't do the Largo slimes without extreme bullshit and with the smaller ones
if I need like oh um I want I wanted all the fruit enjoying because the the drone bees can
like deal with vegetables or fruits or specific things or like chickens um and and plorts and all
that um so I have all of like the vegetable slimes in one area all of the meat slimes in another
and so I I in order to make that happen you need I needed to transport like tons of slimes
and if they were Largo uh that would have you have to move them one at a time yeah would you be
in hell so um have you gotten to any of like the uh like bonus like end game content uh
like be like side farm areas that have like weird shit to do yeah yeah I've I've got to the guy
who is like uh he wants you to find the purple fruit I did all that I got to the point where I
have his ranch now so I have more space nice I've done I've been doing the uh the uh the glitch slime
simulations which are pretty fun I didn't find that for like a long time and like I got back into
the game for like just for for no reason after thinking I had done everything and then I found
that glitch slime area I was like what the fuck is this I just like didn't find it so baby it's um
have you done the quicksilver slime stuff yeah I've just started that it's uh that's pretty fun
it's pretty fun I I kind of didn't understand or what some of the things do I know you've got to
shoot the slimes and I'm trying to figure out like the best strategy for doing it yeah because it
seems like if you're running forwards and and the slimes are running ahead of you it's still hard
to hit them if you turn around though you can go like yeah you you run backwards and shoot at the
slimes coming at you that was mostly how I did and you use the like um I mean you can use like
the thunder shot to hit an area I liked using like the time slow area to like group up a bunch
together yeah I'm just like fire into the crowd that's a good game that's a good fucking game
it's just it's a lot of like it's management and running around and it's also cute yeah I really
like the sound effects there's a specific sound effect where like I think it's just some stock
thing but it reminds it's it's in an old game of like the the pc version of cluedo from 1998
um where it's like a click sound a very distinct click sound that sounds like somebody's switching
off a light but with like low bit rate or whatever like click click and and that's how you change
the items on your hotbar so it's like oh I just enjoy doing that I know that every uh whenever
you uh right click to I've said this before but in Metal Gear Solid 5 when you right click to like
aim a weapon the click click as you like put the weapon into position is so satisfying to me
I just love aiming my weapon it feels good so tactile holy artists sound effects engineers
based unsung heroes of video games you're right but by the way the so good when they're so good
it's true which is the only time I really remember this standing out to me was Metal Gear Solid 5
but the more I more I play games the more I'm aware of all this stuff by the way the uh quick
silver slime thing we're my sorry there's just this meme on 4chan where you know how metal slimes
will run away really fast in in dragon quest there's a uh no there's a meme I think it's metal
slimes there's a meme where you you have an image of a thing and when you click on an image in 4chan
you make it big uh actually the image is a gif and the metal slime is there for exactly one frame
and then it disappears and there's just an empty gif for the rest of the uh that's it because it
runs away really fast I love it every time I smile well I've got I've got voicemails if you guys
want to get to them um yeah if there's something else you want I'm trying to think about anything
else to say about animal crossing sure did you have images for a spend did you want to give us
your your flag which I wanted to see your panini yeah I will put them in the I will yeah because my
island is yakitori island yeah and a yakitori is like cooked is like a chicken I want to see flower
updates garden picks I will show pictures of my how my how my hey somebody write a jingle somebody
write a jingle for uh Ben's rose garden update or whatever it'll be a whole segment it'll be a
whole side segment every week I'll update you on how my on how my garden is progressing on how much
my invasive rose species have taken over the island Ben's garden roses blacker than his soul
there you go start with that go with it yeah um and uh and yeah I'll show okay I'll put a picture
of the flag I'll go to picture that later it's nice it's cool I'm proud of it um I was gonna I feel
like I oh uh the multiplayer I haven't I haven't sprung for the friggin nintendo subscription when
you do let me know Ben I'll be here but I want to because like you're playing it I guess Michelle's
playing it mage is playing it I think Kazi and munchie are gonna start they're they've been talking
about getting it um and you know that's how that's how you maximize your turnip games oh yeah as you
you visit you you take your native fruit and you sell it on other islands and you you go to other
other islands and you sell your turnips there if they've got a good asking price that right right
game the system plus uh what what fruit what fruits have you got what fruits have you got right now
I'm I've got all five fruits now oh god I need to steal some of my friend Toby Toby went to um
he got the he did multiplayer and he went to one of his friends island and that guy had pairs
which was the last one we've got but I've got on my little on my little sides my little section
of the island my little peninsula that I live on I have turned it into a peach grove it's just
peaches over there nice Toby's got pears and Caleb has oranges and John's just got trash nothing
but trash how close your peach trees together because I'm debating if I should move them to be a
tighter knit thing do you have one space between them or two or three no I have them pretty loose
pretty loose okay okay I've got them in a nice grid uh there we have an orchard that's like that
yeah um there's um uh uh uh uh uh oh did I okay so my friend John he's he's he's building trash
island I think I mentioned this yeah well I had an experience right I went on an expedition
to a wild island and it seemed like a normal island at first but what I realized is that
it is a trash island and there were no fish only trash oh oh I see there was nothing in the water
except trash to fish up so I fished up tons of it and I unlocked a recipe for a trash wall and
trash flooring yeah I did that too and I made and I was like well I gotta make this so I made them
and I sent it to him and they're in his house now and we're all you know it's cooperative you know
we're all working together for the betterment of mankind somebody wants trash by god we're
gonna give them trash that's beautiful one last thing yeah um uh think talking about slimes and
slime runcher and puddle slimes reminded me of of this funny little chart that has been I made
for like a conversation in the endless war disco about types of slime girls that could exist
lakroy girls totally formless and transparent lakroy girls puddle slimes are basically lakroy
girls um so like there's the formless formless to viscous so like the the the you know the the
goopier they are yeah and then saturated to transparent because we were trying to decide
this is the one that the people need to be on where am I so these are all technically slime
girls we decided that that is an umbrella term yeah because uh slime is the main thing of endless
but specifically types of like you know types of slime girls goo girls are making a big thing
people know in in what a goo girl is goo girls limited is like an up and coming conglomeration
that's what started this thing keep hearing about this I see I don't know if I don't I'm a little
iffy on this whole on I feel like golem girls and sludge girls should be swaps I was gonna say
how can I sound like a solid a golem come on yeah I added that I added the golem girls thing but
like I didn't want to have them overlap and sludge girls was already there it was like a
cooperative like uh graph creation I say I see no glue like glue girls glue girls yeah because
they're the transparent but also yeah like epoxy resin girls oh I want that fruit girl
glue girl so I live in orange juice girl that'd be an orange juice girl that was like a glass of
orange juice with an anime face and for I forget what is a gunge what's a gunge girl gunge is like
the the watery extremely neon green slime that is used in Nickelodeon the kids and stuff okay okay I
see oh is it I remember in the UK is is they get you get gunged and then like what the fuck okay
on Nickelodeon uh Nickelodeon and things of that nature you know those sorts of kids kids kids
game shows where kids compete to do stuff and if they fail they get gross gunge poured on them that
is very perverse um I don't like it I remember one time Carl Pilkington was talking about tv
and he called tv that he doesn't like glunge telly um nobody speaking the word nobody knows what it
means I think it's like a little I think he's a glunge telly I don't know classic classic moment
I love this I'm gonna put myself I want to be um I think I'm I think I'm
newt viscous formless I'm kind of in the middle but I'm heavily saturated like I'm kind of like
right in the middle like closer to the top yeah I feel like I've got to be further viscous than
formless personally and fairly saturated as well that's that's where I feel you kind of about where
ooze girls are uh yeah maybe slightly upper right a little bit more but yeah in that area that's
that's where I feel yeah okay yeah what's the girl are you this is the chart I'm closest to ooze girl
yeah I suppose I let's see a highly saturated kind of middle of the road viscosity would be like um
um no there's already a jelly girl uh yeah like a really sweet jelly or really like some sort of
toxic waste syrup syrup girl maybe yeah maybe yeah maybe syrup I don't know that's kind of viscous
but kind of formless maybe magma I mean I don't know a workshop it yeah a workshop it yeah I love it
uh place yourselves on the chart everyone oh where would mercury be that's gotta be uh
ooh that's good how about that would be that would be a sort of like gunge but all the way to the top
because it is certainly very saturated you cannot see through it yeah but it is very liquidy
yeah oh gunge girls but at the top yeah yeah to the right of fruit yeah perhaps
although it's fruit really more but it's heavy though mercury is like thick and heavy even
that it's very like fast flowing but it's yeah like all the way to the top a maybe middle to the
right I I don't know so I top I'm not sure it's certainly not transparent certainly not certainly
we can all agree on that experts agree they call it quick so I feel like because it moves quick
for a goop it should be more formal I don't I don't know yeah yeah I get it all right that's a good
girl it's a good girl and debate the nuances of this you know indeed we could spend all day with
that but we've got voicemails to get to and oh wait sorry on the subject of slime I do want to
mention that the rfck pin Kickstarter oh yeah is doing really good we've had a bunch of people
have just pledged at like the 250-dollar tier because to which lets them just pick their own
design like no vote like they just get to choose what they want cool we've had a bunch of people
we're up to like three thousand dollars almost nice which is what I was hoping yeah two thousand
seven hundred and two dollars and the next vote the next pin design that we're gonna vote on will
be at three thousand unless someone else pledges the 250 and then it'll go up by that much
the because you know because because it's each we get we get a voted one at every 250
dollars of like free donations as in not ones that are like okay this is specifically for
this design that I choose myself and I see that you have updated with all the pins that are available
right now are big in the center there we're getting we're getting the cop killer pin rowdy
fucker pin smear ghost nega slime pin the slime the slime coin challenge coin
fuck yeah which is like it's like the big like sort of display coin it'll be like it'll probably be
like half dollar silver dollar size so cool roughly so cool um uh we get the the the the
slime core pin i'm glad that made it in um a sort of like night sky design by labla labungus p and
and uh smear like collaborated on that one it's glorious there is a this is i'm really excited
about someone should taco chose an iron-on pat you know how people were like the german flag
patch yeah on their like shoulder it's like that but it's the endless war flag really cool that's
a really i think that's super cool and i am gonna have to get a new jacket just yeah put it on
oh it's so cool i love it i know i remember all the struggles about choosing the perfect flag and
all the voting and all the debating i'm so happy with the flag that was eventually chosen it was
yeah it was like a huge ordeal we had like we did another like vote thing like people submitted
their designs then we had like a bunch of rounds of voting on them and then like a couple of the
winners like sort of got together in a call and like collaborate and sort of like put them all
together and decided on like okay here's a good like sort of mixture of all the elements that we
like it's great so i like endless war i try it's running i try to run it very democratically i try
to make it very you know community driven of course is one of the i guess one of the mission
statements of it one of the main sustaining factors i'd say that's what we're that's what
that's what it'd be that's what's up that's what's happening did you clarify that like at 3000 there's
like a new stretch goal or something because i just see uh unless unless someone else donates
the 250 the 3000 would be the next time we hold like a vote unlike which uh which new design to
make i see i see okay we actually got a little behind um right now it was further behind before
but it's caught up um we were behind where like uh uh um more people had pledged to make specific
designs we had basically we had voted on more designs than we had actually gotten money to make
so we were in the hole for a minute and i was just gonna have to like pony up like a couple hundred
dollars how did that even happen it was you masked that out okay well no i didn't that's the problem
because like the initial goal it was 600 at first later on i decided that we could do it for 500 so
i moved the stretch goals down later sure sure but so effectively the initial goal it was 500
dollars to make the first two pins and then 250 on top of that basically um okay we had a bunch
of people had pledged and that had been enough to fund uh it ended up being the the smear pin
and the coin and then i was like hey i've got an idea if someone pledges 250 they're basically
funding the whole pin themselves they should be able to choose whatever they want so i made that
a tier sure okay 250 dollar tier pick your own pin and a bunch of people and i don't want anyone
to like feel like they shouldn't have done this it's fine it all worked out but but some people
that had already pledged up to their pledges to a 250 tier so those are actually doing it's only
adding like 200 or whatever yeah so their previous pledges had gone towards like you know the amount
that meant that we could have new pins to design right right so that was no longer going because
now it was going towards uh you know an individually decided pin so because we had already you know
voted and agreed like yes we will be making these two this the the the ghost and the coin uh we ended
up being you know in in the hole for that i see i see not anymore we've like basically caught up
now well cool i feel like a i'm sorry i fucked it up to to uh to get like the patch and the slam
court pin because i want yeah i want all of these i i don't know whether i want will have the money
to like buy all of them to get funded but probably a lot yeah um i'm hoping i'm rooting for if we do
another one i'm hoping that the muck cup i want the podron i want the podron as well and i would
all i would really like the muck cup uh badge too would be pretty cool um but what's fucking there's
like digimon with a hat going on on here what is that shit about digimon with a hat there's like
some white nibba with blue on him with a backward what's that guy's story that's um that's red five
rainbow a couple of people just like submitted their own guys i mean pizza chan i know everyone
loves pizza chan everyone loves pizza yeah it's you know there's a t-fap red man wait what is this
image you scroll down on the kickstarter page on the kickstarter the ones of like potential future
designs okay first one is podron and muck cup and then yeah so some people were just like hey
make me a pin and i was like well i said i would accept anyone's submissions so god damn it i will
very so i did it and i put them on the list and they're available to be voted on i wouldn't mind
if that's the will of the people then so be it pizza chan's cool um sure yeah one question because i
am going to pledge i just wanted to decide when and how much so i i can pledge for a certain number
of pins and then is it afterward i'll be sent like a thing to like fill out a form of which ones i want
is that the yes okay yeah i can pledge now without worrying about which ones if new ones get added or
yeah you can like like if you pledge you know 50 or whatever right now then you get five pins
and then after the kickstarter's overall send you a message and be like okay well which five do you
want okay gotcha and the slime part one is two the big the slime uh yes people have been confused
i've said it a bunch of places but people still are confused so i should keep saying it over and over
again the coin counts as two so if you pledge for two you get the coin you just get the coin if you
pledge for three right you get the coin and one others if you want the coin because the coin is
like way bigger and it's way more it's way more metal you know yeah yeah that's why i want uh yeah i
want one i did make by the way ben a smoother version of the red man face if we needed that for a pin
i i mean if that if that got like funded or anything because i don't know whether the the the harsh
angles could could you post it i'd love to see it just i saw that i posted in the main hit but i saw
that and i put it on i thought i put it on this image i definitely put it on the next like grid
for voting uh i thought i had updated this one with it too i guess i didn't but yeah i have that
i made like a pin mock-up out of it and i just forgot to friggin put it here nice yeah yeah yeah
it would be very hilarious to have a serious would be pretty funny i do like red man a lot
red man it's the boy it's so fucking weird
oh geez his face is off is that red is that red on the on the list
well because you know uh there's only there's only certain colors available uh oh this red i
didn't check oh it's exactly the the the red selection is pretty robust so probably something
very similar would be there but yeah like especially like greens like there's a couple of like
they don't have any greens that are like quite what i would have wanted they're like
none of them are quite as bright as i want it's kind of a shame but like yeah you there's a there's
a guide there's like a formula there's a pantone guide and it's like okay all the colors that we
can use on the pins have to be from this selection although i it's weird because there's no white
on that list and yet i know that white is available because i got the poobah pins and the endless war
pins yeah not the and the infinite chess pins and they've got white on them so i sent them an email
asking like hey what's up with that is there like yeah other colors that are available that aren't
on the list like i don't know because i would like to know but it's it's a little weird but white is
definitely a thing but yeah gotta follow the guide ah anyway i was curious about like the
challenge coin and the one below it like the the rfck town or whatever the endless war those are
like fairly intricate but i assume none of those are probably even though i guess the cop killer
and the munchie one they should be the the one with the sky yeah it might cost like five bucks
more to make because it has like i think it has six colors instead of five yeah but like it's like
not even a big deal um yeah it can be as intricate as it wants to be as long as like the metal sections
are like a minimum width size they have to be like a like 0.2 millimeters or maybe like or half a
millimeter yeah cool and like it's not it's it's you can get pretty fine with the detail and like
you can even you can even put like a hole like on the slime core pin if i if you wanted i could
have put like little gaps in between like the red parts you know what i mean yeah yeah okay there
could like you can get like what's called cutouts like holes in the design it costs a little bit
more but like not that much more it's doable sure sure so yeah they can fucking they can make them
they can make them fucking many old friggin way you dang want pretty fucking sick hey ben how did
you make these images was it like a did you just put it in and it makes an auto-generated like fake
thing or did you actually like photoshop no i i photoshop them i have a process it's um could
you do a youtube tutorial explaining do you want me to i really would because it looks great
it's like they do look great such a really good way to make it look 3d and shiny i could straight
up do that if you wanted one man wants at least i'd watch it um i'm curious i could explain the
technique or i could yeah all right maybe i'll just make a little tutorial it's like how to make
how to do the very specific thing of taking an image and making it look like a pseudo 3d shiny
pin lamel i have i have a little technique that i just go through with and it takes me like
five ten minutes apiece it's not that it's not that complicated like i like i could probably
figure it out but like yeah there's a few things i'm not quite sure about i i um yeah i i'll do it
because it's uh you know i'm a i'm a genius uh only i could have done this um i must share
my technique with the world it's the grand follow-up to the jennifer diane writes lecture
that everyone's been waiting for how to turn an image into a pin it was shiny pin oh maybe i don't
want maybe i don't want to like shit up my channel with that oh well no you can you would not hurt
anything at the same time that's true oh yeah i mean that's true that wouldn't hurt that's true it
would also serve as a ad for the kickstarter interesting okay well well let ben debate
would struggle uh for a long time on his own let us now get to our voicemails we've got like
how many uh eight total oh christ don't worry we'll move through quickly fuck yeah yeah okay first
up is a fitter weeb than nate uh has something to say let's listen go hey pcp just finish the old
workout because when you're quarantining your apartment what else are you gonna do like any good
anime trash panda i listen to a decent amount of opz and covers while i lift and run and do all the
other things that nate claims that he does it never gets around to doing listening to this music
got me thinking though our covers of music really art all you're doing is trying to imitate the work
of let's face it more talented musicians and writers maybe there's some argument to be made
that when you have to translate lyrics there's a value in that but it still seems like a lesser
art form nobody cares about the copies of the Mona Lisa no matter how good they are after all
anyways what do you guys and gals think um simple a good a good cover is a reinterpretation of the
original song to a degree well he said two things in there he said is it art but then later he said
like is less art you could certainly make a case that it's like lesser art i mean i think everything
that's lesser like everything that's unoriginal about a thing is a point against it so yeah to
a certain extent i agree but i think there is an art to doing a cover and like you can take an old
song and do an original twist on it and that's a good cover if i feel like i feel like generally
if the cover is trying to do its own thing too much but it's still recognizable as the first
thing it's just annoying and i'd rather listen to the real thing like very rarely would cover
like transcend the original um you are forgetting about the the techno remix of discord
yeah that's a really right that's that's a different sort of thing if we're talking about
covers i suppose where do you draw the line that's true i mean they're all in the same ballpark
i'd say i feel like a cover is just you know like a lady singing a song uh but doing like a little
stranger like well well well well well well you've just described a shitty cover yeah yeah what about
the best cover ever hey for example um i think Nina Simone originally made the song don't let me be
misunderstood but then the monkeys no no wait it was what the fuck no who was it somewhat the
and it was the animals not the fucking monkeys uh the animals made the most famous version of
don't let me be misunderstood that most people know uh that was a cover of a song and i mean
throughout history of music there have been many famous songs that are more popular and more
beloved in their remake form you've got an original shoutouts to the uga chaka cover of hooked on a
feeling indeed um that isn't wait that isn't the original one no no it is not yeah that's right
right i just thought it was strange you know i guess it comes down to i don't know there's there's a
there's a there's a Todd in the shadows video about that song yeah apparently there are other
there was like another cover of it that also says uga chaka and like strange yeah nobody
he doesn't have any like explanation for why it's there maybe it's actually a cover of the
animals version or not the animals whoever made that fucking umba umba whatever the fuck the
orange skiffs okay i'm fucking about their names well blue suede is the ones that did the cover
i don't know there's like there's like four different covers of it so i don't even know
who's the original i as with everything i will i will say remakes and redoes can be good but
nonetheless i always think it's a waste of time which is different by the way from a remaster
a remaster is a different sort of animal and can usually be what the fuck are you talking about
well like for if you that's a wild opinion well like if the Beatles go remaster like their album
and then re-release it as Nate oh it's slightly i still don't like it Nate but there are different
things a cover a cover is a reinterpretation of source material a remaster is literally just
the same thing again uh okay you know what literally the same thing yeah all right we
just like courting the music to music to we'll worry about that later okay uh by by the way
i forgot to say uh speak pipe is where you leave the voicemails at the beginning uh there's a good
cover you know brings something new to the table and it the way it interprets the thing and in that
way yes it is definitely art in of itself yeah that's my but ben isn't it fair to say no any cover
we'll introduce things that are different that you could call introducing something new even
if it's just like the vocal instructions of the singer yes of course that's true what's your point
then doesn't it just matter like it's it's a matter of deducing is that change good or bad so you
just have to have a totally separate conversation of you know yes what is the nature that you idiot
that doesn't friggin idiot obviously yes you have to determine did the change make it better or worse
obviously yeah ben was not making a quality judgment you just say it is art like i don't think
like quality necessarily has anything to do with whether something is like like changes something
you can change something in a bad way or a good way that's the the original question was about
whether or not it counts as art itself which i think we all basically agree with yes yes didn't
didn't you just say no didn't you just say they're a waste of time well just because something's a
waste of time doesn't make it not art it might just be bad or you know well okay are you no i'm
not gonna let this go are you are you really are you really gonna put your flag in the sand right
here and say that all covers are or or or re or what was the other thing you said remastered no you
said you liked remasters what was the other thing you said i didn't even say i liked remastered i
said they were a different thing okay that's what i said okay let's just stick with covers are you
really gonna stick your foot in the sand and say all covers are a waste of time um
uh well okay well you say a waste i wouldn't recommend it i i think your energy is better
spend making original stuff i'm already talking about making it or consuming it making it right
because that is a distinction i'm talking about making it talking about making it i i i i i sometimes
feel that because it's like from a monetary standpoint at least you're not able to profit
off of the work you put in as much as if it was an original thing because you gotta i just want
new ideas you gotta play royalties to the original look look look okay you're not you're not always
in control of your own creativity sometimes like imagine you hear a song and you're like ooh
you know this is a good song but like what if it did this instead of this like oh like what if it
was kind of performed like this a little differently like that would like totally change the the feel
of it that like it could sound really good that way hmm that's a good idea that would sound good
and then so you go and you like you record it and you produce it and you make a new version
of the song and it's a cover like why is that a waste of time you know i i guess when i think
about it i i i i of course i have the ff7 remake in my mind you know there is a major distinction
here in terms of the medium because music isn't like you can make music way faster than a video game
and the cultural impact of these things is very different when like the company makes a remake
of a thing it's like there was the original there were a bunch of remasters for various platforms
now there is the remake and like that's what exists when you've got like lots of people able to make
covers all the time uh like sure it can't like the whatever like Nina Simone's version of don't let me
be misunderstood kind of has been forgotten uh for like the animals cover because it's more popular
people like it more uh is that bad i don't know but it's it's it's a different situation because
it's not like the copyright holders of the song made another version of their thing it basically
is like a fan version that happened to be popular there was no like corporate stamp saying we need
to upgrade this thing i don't know it's just different and there's nuance to it i don't know okay
all right there's there's words i'm satisfied let us go to our next voicemail which is from
your loyal fan all right oh hi pcp uh it's me your loyal fan i just wanted to say that these
lectures lately have been amazing they've been worth every penny yeah um truly the best content
you guys ever make are these long form deep dive personal lectures as a team i mean it's just
probably true more of these more of these and you know what we shouldn't have to wait for radcon to
do these um just hop into a discord everybody be in a chat and just do like a podcast recording style
lecture like this shit is so good i'm addicted i'm a coke addict is what i'm saying i understand
the one i was thinking i was thinking about i understand the desire but i just don't think
it would be i mean it would be like a progress in his podcast like with the with the small
latency issues somebody like there's always gonna be a difficulty with trying to be the
main guy when everyone else can interject as loud as like like equally loud when you're standing up
and everyone is sitting down it's a very different atmosphere that is true i don't think there are
enough things in the world that i could make like a lecture length video discussing that i would have
like the interest in making i don't think i could do that like once a month or or that like i would
run out of things i would have to i would have to like investigate and spend some time to like
learn about things it could be done but i'm also i agree with ben's point such that i'm happy to
space these things out maybe like once a year that you'll get one maybe two for me like there are
all things that i have like a long-standing interest in yeah i mean i guess i could find a new thing
and like deep dive it and then but would it turn into a full band would that have soul i feel like
it might i feel like it could end up having less soul perhaps that's the risk that is the risk
i think this is one of the negatives of my final fantasy lecture by covering the whole series
including like 11 and 14 which i've like barely played if at all and don't care about it i just
felt i had to as a checklist yeah it has to be something that i'm genuinely interested in and
you know i can't make i can't make that happen indeed indeed i'm definitely going to do a better
job next time i feel like i didn't didn't truly explain i mean it's a silly topic the risk are
you gonna do brisco 102 i literally could um because i didn't talk about the epilogues or
homestuck 2 which i might be funny follow up but homestuck 2 could go on for years and i'd rather
like have that finish before i even think about that but um sure i could do one on the entirety
of homestuck which would be hilarious like because of how long it is but there's also other things
that i have like i have a big interest in and that's a good one yeah i only know like of the very
minimum about that but like from what i know i think that could make a really good yeah lecture
agreed yeah agreed and uh yeah that that's that's potential in fact actually alias cut that out
bleep it bleep it so that nobody knows what it is okay just in case somebody has the smart idea
of like stealing my lecture before i have a chance to do it oh yeah i do hate that i do hate that
and uh you know i just it's a different situation because it's not us or anything but like on this
idea of like the online ones i am good i am curious to hear what the reception to like um uh ash
vampires uh like bionicle one i'll be curious to see what people think about that in terms of the
format and whatnot just uh you know just for fun hi but uh no matter in any case let us move on to our
next voicemail please this is the uh ff7 mandela effect okay go so i was sleeping after jacking
off for like 10 times because i'm in quarantine you know and then nelson mandela came to my bed
and with his black magic transported me to a parallel universe where the final fantasy seven
remake is good uh i mean it's amazing the boxer is actually a square they made it specifically
a square despite all other ps4 covers being rectangle they even made it soft like soft square
i think i think the box is made of uh japanese noodles also there's no gay shit like a fact that
there's only 80 of sexual shit speaking of that tifa's tits are huge like not that huge
that ben sehn would goom instantly at the merseys but bro they are big her thighs also are big
so uh yeah too bad for you but uh in this universe the remake is great
i dream too bad that in this universe hitler won oh yeah i was waiting for it i was waiting
for a twist i'll take that trade any day of the week hitler won um you know the the japanese
were became the master race of the oriental world uh and so square square was better than ever
all their video games were great fantastic i'm glad that happened spectacular uh let me let me
get in on that all right but let's uh go next we've got a message from uh marlo a message from marlo
and bear with me marlo here we go marlo i don't know marlo see ya just watched one piece lecture
it was great loved it burned a lot and i feel like i should tell you nate there is a real life
version of the one piece treasure that you could pursue you could have your own one piece out of
adventure your own hero's journey if you wanted to so there's this guy forced fen he's born 1930
and he grew up reading the first chapters of one piece and 70 odd years later he amassed fortune
so he could make one piece real and he had a treasure the fen treasure like over a million
dollars somewhere in the red line of the united states being the rocky mountains and he left
his poem that gives cryptic directions to the treasure so this is something you're interested
in i suggest you investigate it further uh you know it was i so i i looked this up there was
something called fen's treasure a cache of gold and jewels which this man forest fen an art dealer
from santa fe new mexico claims before he died is hidden in the rocky mountains of the united states
and he did leave cryptic clues to try to get people to go find it uh it has not been found
it may not exist just like one piece potentially but it's supposed to be out there and uh oh put
a bunch of money together what's what's that game there was like an old game minecraft no
shut up idiot um this uh fuck guess who there's a dammit there's a wait leave me alone i gotta
find this thing i want to bring this up it's relevant um okay i gotta concentrate i gotta
concentrate find the content um no keep talking keep talking world craft um yeah keep saying
video games um legal legends final fantasy two team fortress two uh is it a board game
is it a video game what is the endless war fortress um search masquerade uh masquerade
vampire there is a oh yeah okay okay there is what's the video game version okay there is a
this is all gonna make sense this is all gonna make sense there was a book there was a book
called masquerade and it was a an art book by a guy named kit williams and the art in the book
was like it contained like cryptic hints that if you solve the puzzles you could find a real
treasure that was buried somewhere in england in it was like a piece of like golden jewelry it was
it was a golden hair it was like a rabbit pendant right oh okay and um yeah so that was like it was
like a really popular book it was an international sensation did that happen that yes um cool and
there but there was like a due to some like weird like the guy who like won the contest with an
asterisk there's an asterisk on he won it um but he like he got the hair and he like used it as
startup capital to start a company and he basically like self-funded a video game sequel
to masquerade that that purported to also tell you where you could find the golden hair
that's so cool well it was awful it was a terrible game and probably it was a scam and probably
there was no fuck there is a great fucking video on youtube about this um youtube.com
this sword quest otari or is that something else wait um um was this an old video game it's yeah
it's all like the old freaking otari or whatever oh who is this okay i gotta look at my subscriptions
right because i'm subscribed to this guy he does these like he's done a couple of like really
interesting videos talking about like old games you've never heard of and shit and he is just like
it reminds me of that one AVGN episode where he's talking about sword quest which is a game
that gave out real gold prizes for beating the otari game and like the chalice and the crown
and the sword and whatever and like the the real mystery is like where the final prizes are because
all the games didn't come out because they went bust it's like where's the fucking magical sword
um great golden ben i found it it's called hair razor it's called hair razor yes yes that's it on
the wikipedia page yeah okay there okay i found 1984 there is a really interesting video it is
delivered by a guy named steward ashen and the the video is called hair razor hair razor the worst
game ever steward ashen norwich gaming festival 2017 he tells the whole story of the original
masquerade and the video game follow-up and why it's the worst game ever made great video love it
link it please yes okay sorry that took me so long to remember but that's fine i found it i forgot
why it was relevant um because this man said nat go do a iroa piece there's a guy because it's also
about a real life treasure hunt like fen's treasure which is apparently still out there um maybe i will
one day maybe i will one of these days but not today for you it's is it the friends we made along
the way yes it's the adventure the adventure is the prize i want to open the chest and see that
all right uh next voicemail this one is from the ghost of ghost in the shell best anime ever
let's hear what he has to say take it away
yeah it's me ghost in the show best anime ever no where the fuck am i dead apparently it's been
about five years yeah get your shit together no shame shame i like shame he doesn't even have
like a voice modulator shame he's just a very simple ghost he's he needs to work on his uh
his spooky wailing a little bit yeah he's a ghost who doesn't even exist he doesn't even have
gazon kutzwerk uh just like that video also does not because it doesn't exist uh maybe one day
we'll see what happens one day you'll you'll make like uh like you know one frame of progress
that'll be a that'll be a a heady day a weighty day on my head but again that day will also not
be today uh moving on to the next voicemail base uh sigh of relief ah okay last time sigh of relief
had a message for us that was too long but today has a brief uh voicemail so let's give it a listen
take it away advertising it again fuck it quick this time we're doing a procraftinator's rewatch
starting from the beginning and going all the way up to re-experience the war old fans new fans
people who didn't get to see pre-pcp shit friends you want to get into the pcp everyone we're going
to be starting back in the horseshoe days watch the important moments the memes memorable videos
we're going to skip the vlog bullshit unless it's cool kind of like a book club there's a legacy
feed and all you need to do is sit back and watch the content flood in like the stupid pig you are
and talk about it with your bros in the discord again link to the discord is in the description
and also on the reddit yeah there you go uh we'll put a link to that video again yeah we did but he
uh or sigh didn't have a um a fucking uh uh the voicemail was too damn long is my point so we just
put a link but there you go there's your sigh is calling you to go do the pcp rewatch when is it
supposed to happen it's uh it might have already started i'm not totally sure but we'll uh click
the link below it'll take you to the video which will have a link to the discord and sigh will
show you the the path the truth and the light good there you go that's it all right very very
funny very funny that they are doing that that's great there is good shit there uh old thing good
old thing good so enjoy old thing good new current thing bad that we're doing now you can learn just
how bad new thing by seeing how good old thing we've got a fit boy seven remake also calling in
okay take it away two things one i am exercising right fucking now like you should all be doing
in quarantine bring back uh hashtag pcp fit boy second thing yeah about the final fantasy seven
remake god when you get to the missions in like a bit fuck when you get to seventh heaven and like
the teeth of bar shit and you're in that town uh why is there side quests that are like the worst
parts of fallout why do the characters look like fucking Bethesda bullshit characters that like have
dramatic dialogue but the model like barely moves at all and they're like go kill some rats out by
my shop and then you kill the fucking rats and you come back and he's like those were the wrong
rats you idiot that the fuck is that my rats got so much shit that the original didn't have
why did they put all this shit in here uh you know had to had to pad the runtime limited story
you know hey you don't have to cut the runtime games don't need to be a certain length i mean
you know when you make a video game you gotta make sure it's at least a little bad
that was the thing the game was too good yeah had to make sure there was some cringe in among all
the based uh so they did it they they took one for the team it was wisely done uh favorite fallout
game final minus seven uh okay there you go and yes be a fit boy everybody exercise uh don't be a
piece of shit like i've been for a while uh exercise yesterday feeling sore but good also do
yoga uh stretch stretch your ass oh google uh let me i'll tell you what the yoga thing i've been
doing it's 10 minutes it's incredibly easy it's was it it's kassandra morning yoga boom there it is
10 minute yoga full body stretch this is based and will keep you limber and powerful for your life
so there you go watch yoga and do this shit it's great okay anyway uh we've got one final voicemail
it is okay this one's epic ben you're gonna love it it's uh ben saint says something leftist
rest of the pcp this voicemail okay so let's hear what we have to say uh oh should i say something
leftist beforehand yeah oh please do what do you guys um um i you know in my humble opinion in my
humble opinion a wage theft not a fan not a fan of that i rest of the pcp you useless piece of
shit you absolute waste of space and air you uneducated ignorant idiotic dumb swine you're an
absolute embarrassment to humanity and all life as a whole the magnitude of your failure just now is
so indescribably massive that 100 years into the future your name will be used as an insult by edgy
12 year olds even if all of humanity put together their collective intelligence there's no conceivable
way they could have thought of a way to fuck up on the unimaginable scale you just did when jesus
died first since he must not have seen the sacrilegious act we just witnessed you performing
because if he did he would have forsaken humanity long ago so that your birth may have
never become reality after you die your skeleton will be displayed in a museum after being scientifically
researched so that all future generations may learn not to generate your bone structure because
every tiny detail anyone may have in common with you degraded them to a useless piece of trash
into burden on society we might as well never have formed the pcp because surely not any amount of
rotten adults would be able to affect the world as negatively as you just did the only reason i
am not reporting you to the police as we speak is that i know for a fact that they're weak pathetic
prisons will never be able to hold such an indescribable evil no wonder your dad just keeps going
it turns out he was trying to guard the world from the colossal mistake he had created
couldn't have said it better myself keep going uh come on that's all he got and stay out that's
for starters that's for starters uh you know what got he you know what shit maybe wage theft's pretty
good after all yeah i gotta agree i gotta agree on that it's been a pleasure as usual everybody uh
but that said hey leave us more voicemails speak pipe that was the last one speak pipe link down
below leave us voicemails uh epic goofs and gaffes are welcome shitty cringe posts are banished uh
also and also give us money for bonus episodes at patreon.com slash the procrastinators there'll
be a new bonus episode in a couple of days i think maybe five six days after you hear this
something like that uh maybe a week and uh that will be simply epic there's like 36 of them already
so for a five dollar pledge on patreon you get a lot of fucking episodes of this shit
how many like a hundred uh something like that 36 i believe there'll be 37 soon um also follow us on
twitter for all the updates of various rad come things coming out streams we're doing etc at tp
procrastinators uh follow that for all that good stuff and uh check out the links to everything
these guys are talking about the uh endless war pin uh fucking kickstarter still going active i'm
gonna pledge to that so i can get my pins um i'm gonna see you know my my most uh i said munchie
was like oh i don't think it's gonna i don't think it's gonna make a lot of money i don't think maybe
we'll make like a thousand i was like i think i bet if we're lucky we can make 3000 looks we're
right about that right about that we're definitely gonna pass 3000 i think i'm gonna go over the
fifty dollar tier myself five pins sense sense about right and and maybe if we're real lucky i won't
even have to shell it out out of my own pocket because i fucked up and didn't calculate things
right let's hope so let's hope so um yeah so that's go go to gib and take dot site to read my comics
the bail japan the lord of ghosts i i'm behind i'm behind on lord of ghosts i gotta catch up on
lord of ghosts it's so funny that i've taken so long to get the chapter four of lord of ghosts
done and you have still not catched up i'm it's not that i'm i'm waiting i want to binge i'm
waiting wait just let me when it's done i'll binge it and is a banger is a chronic banger
that's true read read read read read read my comics read the comic uh hey i make videos sometimes on
best guy ever uh new one comes in we'll see it over there we'll check it out don't you pretty good
pretty good uh and that's it that's it end of pcp uh see you again next week folks fuck yeah another
one in the bag another one finished and beyond us we can move on with our lives see you soon everybody
have a good week out fucks bye goodbye