I won't bless that guy that son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
That's right.
We both missed it today.
I mean I missed it by a little bit and I could have done an episode mostly by myself.
But I don't want to.
I mean what's the point?
I could just talk about stuff for like 30 minutes.
Yeah, I mean sure.
You could.
I could have.
I just didn't feel like it.
That's fair.
I just forgot what day it was or I forgot that we do it on Sundays.
I just I stayed up late last night doing work on the book specifically.
I guess I actually had a pretty productive week.
I finished making the game into book pages to my satisfaction and now I'm writing the
like notes.
You know the endless, not endless war.
Infinite jet.
Wait a minute.
Infinite jest?
Endless war?
Oh my god.
War and jest are so similar.
War and peace, slime and punishment?
What?
I finished writing, well I didn't finish writing but I've been writing the footnotes,
the end of the book footnotes.
Yesterday I wrote, I wrote notes for I think like 30 pages and I think the whole thing is
like 200 so that's pretty good and I think that there will probably be less notes per
page as it gets further and further into it.
Well, I'm glad at least one of us has been productive.
That's true.
I'm picking up, I'm picking up the slack sort of.
I've also been, you want to, I was going to say something else but I'll say it after.
What's up?
Nothing.
I just, I've just been, I hadn't, I think an okay start to the week.
I was going over the Clarissa stuff.
I was doing pumpkin alley concept art all day kind of slowly because I don't know how
to do that but I was working through it.
Was it levels?
It was level designs I've had in my head and I just needed to like put down on a
piece of paper, digital paper and then like come up with an enemy design on the fly because
I knew that the enemies were this and that.
I just never really thought exactly what they looked like and we need that sort of information
if we're going to start modeling and all that.
Why do you need to come up with new enemies when you're your own worst enemy?
I just pictures of me the whole three.
The game won't start unless you have your phone, your phone like hooked up to your computer
by micro USB and then when it starts it downloads your selfies and then puts them on, the secretly
puts them on the model of the enemy.
Kind of like, remember the Game Boy camera?
I didn't use it but I know of the Game Boy camera.
Did you know you could take a picture of yourself and it would put your face like on the boss
of like a little like Gallagher shooter?
Oh, I didn't know that.
It would do that.
So it like secretly does that with you, with the final boss.
Okay, that's my joke.
But yeah, I was doing some of that and then I just sort of had a big slump moment, big
old like who cares about me, no one and maybe I don't need to exist.
Classic depression spiral and it became difficult to do anything for a few days and that's where
I am at.
Okay, still.
Yeah, I'm trying to find the thing.
I wrote down, oh my God, I got so many stupid notes in my just documents folder.
It's about like Clarissa that I wrote years ago and then months ago and then I did not
organize at all.
I'm trying to find a thing that I wrote down as like, I was trying to figure out how many
pages I have of Clarissa sketched already.
I think it's like 38 pages, which is about like two or three chapters.
Like ones that you haven't finished.
Yeah, they're sketched, they're not lined or shaded or anything.
And I was like, okay, how fast can I do all that?
That might be like roughly a month's work to draw what I have.
And then I would need to sketch the rest of the comic and finish like I need to write
what happens next and then sketch what happens next and see how many pages that is.
And so I'm like, shit, that's a lot of work.
That's a lot of stuff.
And then Pumpkin Alley is like, oh, concept art.
I don't know what the fuck I'm doing.
How do you make a game?
What?
And so that's sort of that's the question.
Yeah.
And then I was like, okay, the other thing I was doing is Elden Ring Streams.
But I think both combination of factors has resulted in zero viewers for the last few or
very, very low amount of viewers where it used to be like roughly 10 would come up.
And that's nice.
10 is a nice number.
It's not like a huge number, but it's fun because of people in chat.
But the last few times is no one.
I think it's a combination of waning interest in Elden Ring Streams.
Like people probably the hype around Elden Ring has died down just enough
that it's not like hot shit anymore.
Yeah, it's been out for it's been out for what, like two months now?
Yeah.
And almost as much as the fucking war with Ukraine.
Is that right?
That sounds about right.
Is it third three months now?
Is it February?
I don't remember.
Well, fuck.
What?
We've always been at war with Ukraine.
I mean, Russia's always been at war with Ukraine.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And then also I like stream at stupid times and I don't have a schedule and I can't keep to a schedule.
Hmm.
And it was just sort of demoralizing.
I was like, what, what the fuck am I doing with anything?
I can't draw Clarissa because I suck.
I can't draw the Pumpkin Alley concept art because I suck and I'm stupid.
And when I do like little, little Elden Ring things, nobody even comes to those anymore.
Why am I streaming?
Why am I wasting my time?
And then I was like, oh, why am I wasting my time with anything?
And then I, you know, and it happened.
That's true.
Big, big depression.
Well, that's what I mean.
That's life, though, just wasting your time with anything.
Yeah, think about it.
Oh, you've you've solved it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
That's my week, I guess.
I don't know.
Yeah, yeah.
Streaming is, I don't know how to do it.
I just rather than, I don't know, I think I think my own at some point.
Every once in a while back when I used to stream, I would get like a big,
I would have a really good day and I would like a big, bigger number than usual people.
And I'd be like, yes.
Yeah, and I don't and I don't know what caused those.
Most of the time I didn't know what caused that to happen.
And then other times I would have a more modest number and I'd be like,
and I think I had gone a while without like a big like a big attendance stream.
And I think I think I quit like before before things could drop off too much.
Yeah, I mean, there's only so much attention that goes can be like spread around.
And it's not it's it's just like you don't know how many people who would
watch you are free on what day of the week unless you ask all of them individually.
Yeah, so you just have to guess like what's the most effective time.
And if you get the if you have a schedule, then people can think about it and plan around it.
And that's true. Yeah, there's just there's a lot there's ways to do it.
It's just I was doing it lazily and made me sad.
And I was like, it's all my fault.
Everything I do is wrong.
Gib, I do you even deserve to live?
That's that's the question.
Yeah, that's what I was asking as well.
Determined that no.
Oh, shit.
I don't actually have a I don't actually deserve to live.
I haven't made like a Steven universe before.
No.
And I'm I'm approaching like the year 30.
That's right.
That means as soon as you're 30, everything has gone wrong, apparently.
That's correct.
So if I if I'm not like, oh, I didn't like make it big before then.
Well, I may as well just just where you're certainly you're certainly not going to after.
So, you know, yeah, there's no there's no not even one example
of a person who made it after they hit 30, not even one.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Post in the comments if you can find even one.
No, I mean, sure.
Yeah, why not?
I feel you.
The I don't know.
You're just right.
That's it. Yes, I'm so fucking right.
Oh, you know what?
Thanks, Ben, you made me feel better.
Now, maybe I do deserve to live because I was right about how much how much
everything sucks. Yeah.
You know, sometimes being so smart is a downfall because when you're depressed,
you accurately understand all of the reasons.
And so when somebody tries to console you, you're a real prick because you say,
well, yeah, I understand that and I know that and you're not helping.
And they're like, oh, God, fuck it.
Yeah. Goodbye.
Yeah, I mean, you know, the most objectively true assessment
of the situation is that we're, you know, just like a meaningless vortex
of space dust or whatever in an uncaring universe.
And that's and that's depressing.
So, like, you know, when when the, you know, as Winston Churchill said,
when the when the shaggy black dog of depression shows up to tell you that,
I mean, he is correct.
So you got to you got to get past that.
Is the shaggy dog like combination of shaggy and Scooby?
I I think it's more like I think it's more like the grim
from Harry Potter.
Winston Churchill was a big Harry Potter fan.
Yes. Yeah.
I mean, it makes sense.
Not to change the subject, but I guess I will for a moment.
We can go back to that if you want.
But yeah, I did I did want to say someone pointed out that last week I dropped
some hints that I had a thing I'm trying to do that I don't want to talk about.
And that's true.
And someone said, I think it was oh, my phone, my undiscord.
Someone said, oh, new secret project arc already.
And like, yeah, I guess so.
I'm not I'm not trying I'm not trying to make it a big, like, long secret project.
But but I mean, it is a thing I'm working on and I don't want to talk about it.
So I guess it's a secret project.
But I was talking to a guy.
So I will continue to not specify what it is.
However, had a funny story sort of I was talking to a guy.
I've been making some phone calls.
I've been talking to a guy who may or may not be a guy who can help me do this thing.
And he this is basically unrelated to what I was talking about.
But he, you know, I mentioned to him that I do YouTube, that I'm on YouTube.
And he was like, this seems like an older like Boston accent guy.
He's like, oh, yeah, I did a yeah, I made a documentary.
I made a documentary about the history of pinball.
I was like, what?
It's like, yeah, I made it.
You can look it up on you can look it up on Amazon Prime.
I made a history, a history of pinball.
They had like, hold on, you know what?
He had a similar he had a weird bunch of celebrities
that were in his documentary of pinball.
Hang on, Amazon Prime, the history of pinball.
Here, watch the history of pinball prime video Amazon.com.
It's got Slash Frank Thomas, Aerosmith.
Yeah, it's got Guns N' Roses guitarist slash Aerosmith Joe Perry
and Major League slugger Frank Thomas are in this.
What a spread.
Yeah, also, there's a typo in the copy of this video.
Quote, this documentary follows the silver ball
from the 1600s to the second millennium.
Also, I mean, if I'm being pedantic and I am the second millennium
is what everything's starting with 1000
because the first millennium started with zero.
So this fucking Joker, man, this fucking Joker.
You know, based on his documentary, I think I'm not going to hire him.
This this is like whatever.
This this has like no bearing on what I'm talking to this guy about.
I just thought it was funny.
But what does annoy me, though?
Because this guy, I guess he thinks he's hot shit.
I guess this guy thinks he knows about videos or something.
And a couple of times now, he has brought up to me
a thing called vid IQ.
You ever heard of some of this?
No, he keeps referencing vid IQ.
He says, yeah, I know a guy.
I know a guy.
He's all about flipping phones.
You know, I'm not interested in flipping phones.
But this guy, he's he's known as the flippin as the phone flippin king.
Everybody, you know, you look you look up how to flip a phone
and you find this guy's videos.
You know how he did it?
Something called vid IQ.
Vids vid IQ.
You get some get made him made him the king of flipping phones.
Now everybody knows him.
And now he's now he's made a million dollars of flipping phones.
And I assume flipping phones like not juggling.
Because that's what I've assumed in my head is I believe he flips it up and he grabs it.
I believe he means like buying broken phones
and refurbishing them and reselling them the way you would flip a house.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think a phone juggler would be a funnier.
He made a he's a millionaire.
You look up juggling phones.
So this and this guy, he keeps trying to tell me that.
Oh, yeah, I know this guy who made a lot of money
because he got a lot of he got famous making videos on phone flipping
with the use of the service called vid IQ and you should use vid IQ.
And he called over SEO thing.
Yeah. Yes. Yes.
It's some it's some SEO thing.
It gives you like analytics tools for your video performance or whatever.
And I I told I told this guy, yeah, I made I mentioned the song
lecture, I was like, yeah, the Sonichu lecture that got like, you know,
got like it's like a million and a half views on he's like, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, you use vid IQ, you could get you could get that up to maybe three million.
Like I politely I politely declined to comment, but like, shut up, you idiot.
Like, what are you talking about?
I looked it up.
I looked up some videos or I looked up a video of a guy reviewing reviewing vid IQ
and he had some thoughts about the things they offer the analytics tools and whatever.
Those might be useful for some people, but he this this this guy specifically said,
like, yeah, the SEO boosting is basically all it does is it recommends you tags
to like put in your tag, you know, your description and like, it's useless.
Tags don't do anything.
So, man, if I talk to this guy again,
I hope he shuts the fuck up about vid IQ.
I don't want to fucking hear it. All right.
Sounds like a classic case of the the normie
thing where they have like three stories and they will say them every time you meet them
because they have those stories and they're like, I heard an interesting thing.
You know that, like, goblins aren't real or whatever.
Yeah. Yeah, I heard about that documentary about that.
Not even goblins.
There's not even goblins and, you know, that's just one of the things I know.
No way. What the fuck?
Why are people talking about this?
Damn.
I just this guy doesn't know what he's fucking talking about.
I I don't want to hear it.
I don't hear it, man. This is not.
I don't know. OK, this this this stands to become a big point of annoyance.
If I honestly, I I found this guy, I googled around.
I found this guy.
I've been talking to him about doing some some work.
He's like, yeah, maybe I've sort of been meaning to call some other people.
I probably shouldn't put all my eggs in one basket.
This guy is just one option.
And I want to, you know, look around.
Because anyway, I've been like, vague, vague, being vague about it.
So because I can't say what it is.
So I'll just I'll stop talking about it.
But I mean, it's all in the data.
It's all in the data.
If you go, you check out every goblin image.
It actually leads to like a fake image.
Hey, you know, not made that they're not real.
I made a I made a Netflix documentary, The History of Goblins.
Yeah, it had it had a thousand views.
And then I and then I paid a vid IQ, ten dollars a month,
and now it's got 10 million views.
So you could you could do that, I guess.
Three million, three million. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'll just I'll just I'll just double the views
on my on my Sonichu lecture, just just by vid IQ.
You know, the I don't know the tags, maybe I guess they'll tell you to put tags.
Like what a jackass fucking.
I mean, I don't need the the.
I can't even really think of like what like tags you would use to like
suddenly it appears and recommended this video that I watched reviewing
that IQ said that the only time tags actually like make a difference
to your video's performance is if something in your video is like easily
misspelled and you want to use the tags so that it like catches
misspelled versions of the thing you're talking about.
Oh, that's that's smart.
Like, yeah, if I mean, with hypocrite, obviously people so spell it different.
This is an actual word that people spell.
I used to put the versions of that in in my videos.
So like, I hope that I hope that can tend back when that was a thing,
you know, included tags of like all the misspelled versions of their name
because nobody could spell that fucking name, right?
So that might have been helpful, might have been helpful for them.
Wouldn't don't think it would be helpful for me.
Maybe if I put like the sonic, actually, I wonder if there is a sonic tag.
There should be a sonic tag in that video.
Hey, I might if there's not one, I might put it in there.
But that's the like, that's the extent of it.
So it's very annoying, just really irritating when some jackass
doesn't know what they're talking about, tries to fucking tell you some shit.
Yeah, anyway, that was a minor thing that happened to me this week.
Yeah, you know, the more I think about my week,
the more I realize that my depression is so unfounded.
It's just one of those.
Yeah, it just happens and it leads to more and more of it.
Yeah, I know, I know, because you're compromised emotionally.
I very like I think early on I was looking at my sketches for Clarissa
and I was like, you know what, these are good.
This is a good story.
And I wrote I made that tweet.
I made that Snoopy tweet.
Snoopy tweet, where I thought I remembered a panel from Peanuts
where Snoopy is typing.
Oh, yeah, it feels it's so good when you know what you've written is good.
And I'm like, that's me.
I know it.
I was so full of beans back then.
And then suddenly, suddenly, suddenly my Elden Ring playthrough got one view
and I was like, you know what, it's time to end.
It's over. It's all over.
Yeah, it's the worst thing that could have ever happened to me.
Streamer loses, like doesn't get views once and quits forever.
That's right.
That's right. I'm so stupid.
It's just the straw that broke the camel's back.
You know what? Yeah, you are stupid.
Thanks. You're absolutely right.
I was going to ask you got you got drunk on Twitter the other day.
Oh, yeah, that was fun.
You messaged me.
No, I messaged you and you replied drunk.
And then I saw on Twitter, you were drunk posting.
Oh, yeah, what did I say?
I'm drunk right now, so take everything I say with a gram of salty.
What was I messaging you about?
It was something or other.
It's about the secret project, I think.
Oh, yes, I think it was.
Yes, it was, it was, it was, it was.
I cannot read currently, nor do I attempt to read.
And then you say based on drink pilled.
And then I say, Glenn live that is my favorite whiskey.
Yes, I've never had it.
It is. I do like Glenn live it because it's like it's a whiskey,
but it doesn't hurt.
That's probably why I got drunk because I had two of them.
Two.
Well, I had a glass and a half of wine as well.
I don't know. I don't list list everything list everything you drink.
I had two glim, two glim livets and a glass and a half of one.
Glenn, Glenn live it.
Glenn live it.
And a glass and a half of red wine.
I don't remember what red wine it was.
I'm going to.
I think that's about it.
I'm going to, I'm going to drink you under the table.
I mean, I'm not that good at holding my liquor.
I am, I'm so good at holding my liquor.
This is confirmed multiple times that I will be literally blackout drunk
and not remember anything that's happening and people the next day
will sometimes tell me they couldn't even tell that has happened a few times.
Well, that seems like the worst situation
because they're not even funny.
Yeah, it's not great. Yeah, it's not great.
You don't even remember anything, but you weren't even hilarious on Twitter.com like me.
Oh, God, I have nightmares.
I don't actually have nightmares, but I dread like, what if I got inebriated
and I said something like stupid or incriminating or, I mean, not incriminating,
but like, you know, something shameful on Twitter.
And then it's a real.
Yes, something like that.
And then and like, what if that happened?
Like what if I accidentally post porn to Twitter or something?
What if I accidentally post porn in my discord?
That's that's what I think about.
That's my like nightmare scenario.
I was still I was I remember everything I did when I was drunk.
I think it's it's it's that funny buzz where you're like,
haha, I'm so silly.
I'm going to be silly and you type silly things knowingly.
So I think the only thing I slightly regret is
acting Andrew Hussie and calling him a bad father and saying I could take risk
off his hands, just say the word.
It was funny at the time.
I think that's kind of stupid.
I'm sure he I shouldn't have said that.
I'm sure he took it as a joke.
But I'm just some random weirdo.
He probably has notifications turned off anyway.
If I'm sure if he saw it, he thought like,
oh, another crazed another crazy risk of another
another deranged lunatic on my time line.
And just just another one.
I suppose like when it comes to homestuck posts, it's not that weird.
Yeah. Yeah.
I felt it's weird because I felt bad while I was typing.
It's like, oh, no, I shouldn't call him a bad father.
But you know what?
But I'm going to do it.
Inhibitions gone.
I I was going to say about depression
that I often get depressed like late at night,
like it'll be late in the evening and I'll start to feel it.
And then usually, well, a lot of times I don't listen.
But sometimes I think to myself, you know,
I should just go to sleep and I'll wake up and I'll feel better.
And like most most of the time, most of the time, that's true.
So I don't know.
I think it's something about the time of day or, you know,
my my my sleep cycle or like my brain chemicals
like changes as it gets later or I've been awake longer or something.
I mean, for me, I I don't pay too much attention when it happens.
Sometimes I try to think, oh, shit, I'm depressed.
Let's analyze this.
Why am I what happened so that I can learn from my mistake?
But a lot of the time, I think it just comes down to like
how you're feeling physically
combined with a few little emotional things like, oh, my stomach hurt.
Yeah. Oh, there's so so weird taste in my mouth.
I don't like that.
Oh, it's a lot of it is intestinal stuff.
Apparently, a lot of your gut bacteria determines what your mood is.
Yeah, you have a bad shit day.
If you have a bad diarrhea moment,
then you're going to feel bad, even if a good news was happening.
Hmm, I didn't didn't know that.
That sounds troubling.
I would look into it because I just vaguely recall somebody telling me that.
And I'm like, yeah, that makes sense, actually.
Sometimes when I take a big shit when I've needed to,
suddenly everything seems all right.
And I'm just like, you know what, that's a weight off my behind.
Munchie told me that his doctor recommended him
like do a thing.
There was a name for this particular diet that I'd never heard before,
but it involved like avoiding fermented foods
as some sort of like gut health thing.
And it was like no bread.
It was like no bread because bread has like yeast in it.
Bread is fermented, but cheese is OK.
Cheese is fermented, but it's OK for some reason.
And I just thought that was bizarre.
I'd never heard of such a thing, but I guess.
But I guess it was to have some effect on the gut.
Biome, I don't know.
I mean, I'm sure like bread isn't the best thing.
I mean, bread or yeah, like excessive amounts
of bread is a bit like bloating.
I avoid I avoid I avoid most bread
just because it's just because it's carb heavy.
I've been I've been a little I haven't been I haven't been disastrous
about my dieting lately, but I've been a little bit.
I've been a little bit not on the point that I want to be with it.
So I got to get back on track with that.
And then I haven't I haven't lifted this.
No, I lifted once this week, but then I'm on.
She got a cold and now I can't.
Last time I tried to lift alone, I almost dropped the bar on myself
during the bench press, which I say I would have died.
I probably would not have died, but it would have been very annoying.
I was because in the in that basement, there's a the light is on a timer.
And so it the light you have to reset it every 30 minutes or else the light turns off.
I was bench pressing.
It was on my last set and the light turned off like on my last rep.
And I'm like, oh, God, so I just had to like that would be terrifying.
It was terrifying.
I mean, it wasn't so much weight that I would have like dropped it on myself
and it would have crushed my rib cage.
I would have suffocated. I would have died.
What would have happened is I just would have dropped it.
It would have landed on my chest.
I would have had to like strenuously roll it down my body to my waist
so that I could sit up with the bar sort of under me.
Like that's what it would have hurt and it would have been uncomfortable.
And it maybe I would have strained something.
And anyway, the point is I don't want to do that.
So Munchy is having a cold means I have no one to lift with.
See, the problem you're doing is you were pushing, you weren't lifting.
You were pushing the weight up.
You should be lifting it on the ground.
That's that's, you know, I feel a little bad.
I'm going to go up.
You know what? That's that's Munchy's problem, too.
He that clown, that fool, he thinks I'm going to I'm going to tear in a moment.
I'm going to put him on public blast right now.
He thinks he's so clever.
He thinks he's going to get big arms because he's replacing.
He's replacing the the bent over row and or power clean with the bicep curl.
He's curling. Oh, he wants to curl to get big arms.
You Rube, you Rube, that's not a pulling exercise.
That's an isolation exercise.
The point of the third exercise on the set B is that it's a pulling exercise
for the back, the bent over row or the power clean.
You can't just replace it with the curl, but he insists.
He's he's a madman.
He won't listen to reason.
He's he's out of his mind.
He's out of control.
Yeah, I'm thinking about like what muscles would be interacting with the
it would just be your your arm up to and maybe including a bit of your
shoulder, but it wouldn't touch the back really.
The the curl, the curl is is basically just the bicep.
And that's fine if he wants to do them.
I'm not I don't think he wants to be barred from doing them.
But they are not but they are not a replacement for the bent over row,
which the point of the third exercise in the second set is that it is about pulling.
And the and the curl is not a pull.
But it's but I but I but he's but he's but he's on a tear.
He's a madman.
He can't be stopped.
He can't be bought, bargained,
reasoned or negotiated with.
He's a terrorist based.
Yeah.
That's right.
OK, what were we talking about?
I don't remember something.
Yeah.
What else did I do this week?
Worked on the book, wrote those notes, made the pages,
talked to that dude about the secret thing.
Oh, I guess last time to mention this,
I'll probably have already I'll definitely have already sent
the load of ghosts, a current batch of things.
There's still as of recording one, two, three, four people.
Wait, is that four?
I'm like blind one, two, three, four is five five people
who have not sent the thing in.
I'm going to send it.
So I'll send these when they come.
James Gottwijk,
James Gottwijk, Adam O'Donnell, DS and Milo Rocks.
Milo Rocks is a is a doodle and a plush
pleasure, so get on that.
But soon I will have mostly sent all of the load of ghost things.
I got like a big batch.
I got to buy the postage and send them and
God damn it, that will be most of them gone.
And then I'll bring yours to Boston in like a few weeks when I'm going over.
Yeah, I'll bring Casus as well.
Yeah.
And looking forward to very exciting.
And then what will you do?
Then I will have mostly finished that and I won't have to think about it.
Nice. That's good.
I got a I got a message from actually it was from
Sasuke Pro who wrote.
Oh, he wrote one of the
songs, one of the PZP theme songs.
But which one?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It wasn't the don't give it up.
Bensane dreaming don't give it up.
It was when we did the theme song
contest and we and we picked the theme song and I forget which theme song it was
that it wasn't the like I'm supposed to be working.
right now i'm supposed to be working right now it wasn't that cover of that song because that
was by oblivionfall it was uh oh god damn it okay i can't remember i'm sure i'd recognize
if i heard it it was it was that person uh the point is i they the customs caught uh their their
plebeian wee blu-ray copy it got caught by their country's customs office and now it will probably be
another like two weeks in transit and then it will maybe get back to my p.o box and then i don't
have to check my p.o box and find that and send it again and probably i have not checked my p.o box
in months there are probably a whole bunch of them in there that didn't that didn't make it to their
destination and i just haven't checked because like i said before my p.o box is near my old
residence it is not it is kind of inconveniently far away from my current residence so take me
like an hour to get there and back at least uh so that's annoying god i've had a few really annoying
things happen with customs and can i just say i'm so mad because like right like like during
covet there was a post office there was a post office right near where i live like like two
streets down and it's closed they closed during covet and now there's no post office here and now
it's i gotta fucking get the bus and shit and that sucks okay that does suck it really sucks
what a bit would have been incredible yeah the i've i've had a few like really annoying customs
things where i think on yeah on separate occasions somebody lost because the customs they open the
packaging with with what i assume is like bear claws they rip it to shreds they scatter all the
things on the floor and they sniff it because they're bears they're just big bears in the customs
office ripping things to shreds and sniffing it for drugs or whatever and then haphazardly
throwing it back into a plastic bag and sending it but on separate occasions somebody has not
received their red man comic not received their pin and now not received the plush but they did
feel like they should they they did receive the ghost costume so they don't have the plush
that the costume goes on they have everything except the plush and that was really annoying
because i only have a few of those that reminds me when i was a little kid my family took
a vacation to mexico and i brought uh my two favorite stuffed animals and i might as well
mention they were a a penguin named fluffy and a bunny named norman norman norman i like i like
the cut of that jib yeah that was um i think there was a sesame street skit with like a dog
named norman and i just like the name and i and i named this uh this rabbit norman anyway the point
is i like lost those animals on the trip like i lost them on the plane or something and i was
devastated but they did cut customs did somehow like eventually like send them back to me like
or maybe it was maybe just the airline found them and the lost and found or something and they got
sent back to me i don't know they miraculously got sent back to me the years i remember like i
years later that story came up and my i think my mom mentioned like that they probably had like
they probably had like pulverized them or something like to make sure there weren't
any drugs inside them or something or like it's kind of surprising that they didn't like slice
them open to like find yeah cocaine bags or something inside um that is the classic thing
mexico mexico being how it is and all you know uh but i got them but i got them but you know what
while they were lost my cousin jeffrey gave me a another stuffed animal to replace them
he gave me a a frog in a hawaiian shirt named uh and i named that jeffrey after him so and then
i got those two back so from then on uh my three favorite stuffed animals were fluffy norman and
jeffrey uh that's really cute thank you yes i still there they're still they're still in a box
somewhere they're still in like my parents attic or something um yeah i remember like stuffed animals
from when i was little we would like just me and my brothers would just abuse them and beat the
shit out of them constantly i remember we had this this lion uh just sort of like not a brand
lion or anything just like a oh it's a lion soft toy um and it was like i think like two feet tall
it was quite big and we could like wrestle with it we could pretend it was like attacking us we
could beat the shit out of it and kick it and throw it against the wall that was the that was
the best of times when we had like a a fool that would dare to come into our realm and we would
destroy them and he had a tail and you could swing him around your head and throw him and it was very
violent i would um i would put i remember i would put my stuffed ant for when i had two i would put
them you know my my bed was against the wall uh i would put my fluffy and norman one of like the
like the corner of the bed facing away from the wall one at the front one at the back when i had
jeffrey two i would put the three of them fluffy norman jeffrey at the front back and middle on
the side of the bed facing away when i would sleep i would i would post them there these three like
regular positions as like guards to i guess like keep ghosts away or something uh or demons or
various threats that might menace me in the night uh i think that was their main function that was
how they paid the that was how they paid their rent they got that that thousand yards stare the
beat the lies i was very concerned about uh ghosts and such they were scared uh yeah
i remember having a few like scary scary moment where it's just dark and you
you're you're you're you're you're a tough you're a tough little kid you're like i'm not gonna be
scared and then immediately you think you see something and because you haven't had an experience
like that before you're not even really aware about what is possible to happen in the dark
so you see a dressing gown hung up uh or a bathroom brother uh for you americos and
it's like a dark figure really tall in the other side of the room you're like
is that a person you can't tell i remember this this experience i stared at it for ages thinking
that's a person and i guess i was groggy and i was like unaware of like what was real and what
wasn't i'm like what happens if i go to sleep now because i know that's not a person but
they're gonna get it it really looks like a fucking creature scary times uh i you know this
is uh to change changing the subject yet again but i just remembered another something else that
vexed me this week uh turns out i don't know why i thought this wouldn't be a problem but it turns
out it is a problem is uh the thing with the printing green um yeah printing is awful yeah i
for some reason i thought that like oh no no that's only a problem with offset printing with
digital printing it's fine uh no it's it's just because like to combine colors makes them darker
yeah green is not an ink color like you got magenta cyan and yellow right yeah and see
green you have to make it kind of dark which means all greens are kind of fucked
yeah so uh i mean i've been i you know uh what a manga studio lets me sort of like preview
what a an image will look like printed in in various cmyk colors and like i've been going
through some pages and like most of them are fine some of you know the the really the really
bright greens they get muted but on most pages they still stand out you can still they still look
like what they're supposed to look like you can still tell that they're supposed to be like a green
it's it's not it's not ruined you've got to try with like some of them look kind of contrast some of
them look a little bad and i might i might have to go through and like maybe touch some up maybe like
alter the shades a little bit yeah to like bring some contrast back that would be missing
otherwise it's just such a it's just such a bummer i don't know i think it'll be i think it'll be
okay i think it'll be okay but it's a real bummer uh seeing like it really took me a long time trying
to figure out how to make the red man green as green as i can make it and it's still it looks fine
when you look at it what make the red man green weed from uh from a peter pan you know yes yes
they did smoke weed didn't they no in in did you know that scene in peter pan where they're singing
about where the native americans are singing about what makes the red man red i i i remember vaguely
but i remember they had the the pipe and they were smoking weed dude they were smoking fucking
big stacks there's they're smoking something i don't did they have weed did a native american
smoke marijuana i don't know they might have didn't they find marijuana in that part of the world
isn't that where it's from i don't i don't remember i know tobacco is from that but you know i don't
know nothing but yeah i spent likewise i spent a long time choosing the greens for um for the
pins for these for the rfck enamel pins i spent a long long time picking out individual greens
for all the different pin designs that had green in them because you could especially for slime
corp and endless war itself it's like you can't you can't get that fluorescent green it just
doesn't like exist in like the manufacturing world so you have to choose the best approximation
and so wild how certain colors can exist on a screen you just can't find them in reality
yeah because it's it makes sense because it's because it's additive color it's adding
with with pixels on a screen you're adding light together versus when you're printing
you're subtracting you're subtracting from the white of the page yeah yeah yeah like i get it
would it be like if history was different and like the standard for printing was like rgb
for instance would greens like suddenly become like more printable i i don't know how that would
work yeah i think i think it's mostly the the the light the brightness of of like magenta
cyan and yellow mostly cyan and yellow they're they're bright enough that when you mix them together
they end up with a sort of not so dark color um and if rgb ink was used i don't know if that's
would even be possible i assume it can be because like ink can be many colors but
yeah i don't know maybe maybe maybe it's just sort of like that's those three colors are the best
um inks colors to use for the broadest range of possible results and that's why they use that
you ever see you ever see that graph of like that graph of colors that humans can see because
like when when you have you know you're in your art program or whatever you got your you got your
little dam you got your little dam uh color wheel to pick your colors on but that's not really like
that's not really like the like reflective of the colors humans can see here um i've i've seen
the captain dissolution did a video about color and yeah a lot of really good animations like
visually showing the triangle of like possible colors that like certain cameras and our human
eyes can see yeah and then like like bees would go off the grid and be like a weird thing that we
can't even comprehend yeah that i think that i think that might be where i saw it but yeah it looks
like it looks more like this with like the the greens being like really big like humans can
just like perceive a lot more different shades of green so maybe maybe that's part of why
it's hard to get like that accurate green in print it's just because humans are more sensitive
to like we're more able to see yeah yeah i mean it makes sense we're evolutionarily uh the the
you know the colors we can see are mostly green because there's mostly green foliage we need to
be able to discern what is a tree and what is something behind the tree it's lurking in the
shadows do you think do you think that's why i i would i would i would assume that like it's
it's blues and greens because those are the colors of nature largely and that's why we we we evolved
to to need like a very keen eye for that sort of thing in order to survive i have two thoughts
red you know well naively what i would think is that like you know nature is a lot of greens and
browns so you would think that humans would be sensitive to things that are not that like things
that are red or blue would would stand out you would want to be like oh my god what's that like i
really notice that thing that doesn't look like everything so so i would think you would be more
sensitive to other colors but but you make a good point maybe because so much stuff is green and brown
and whatever it means that you need to be able to more finely distinguish it yeah it's it's the same
way that humans are so good at seeing faces and understanding faces despite the fact that
we all have faces it's it's the knowing of the emotions of the face that can allow you to understand
whether another person is going to hurt you or is a friend you know like under reading emotions is a
very evolutionarily important skill kirby shaped like a friend yeah he's friend shaped i know that
much he wouldn't eat you and turn you into like a fucking marionette that he would use to pilot
in a disgusting horrible way he wouldn't he wouldn't devour you obtain your skills take them to like
fucking the dark underworlds opposite universe and use them to defeat the the embodiment of
at all entropy in the known universe or something that would be so fucked up it's so wild how kirby
is the cutest like friend shaped character in the whole video game world but he is also
almost like explicitly like a like an eldritch abomination that can do almost anything i he
he would be a god of destruction if he weren't so cute i wonder like at what i feel like these days
that's like very explicit like in like there's yeah there is like no they almost they almost
don't even like pretend otherwise but it's it wasn't always i mean it wasn't always the case
i mean no in the first game he's just like a little chevy guy going around eating stuff
and fighting a funny penguin but even on like the the nes and the and the super and and the
gameboy and the super nintendo he you were still like the final boss would be like on the moon
fighting like a big like vampire well that's that's that's dark the nes dark matter like yeah like
dark matter is from i think the first dark matter fight was in like the gameboy now the the gameboy
i think is it's just ddd like it's it's a tiny little game doesn't take very long one of the
gameboy games has you fight like a dark matter with a sword uh i don't know why no you're right
maybe i'm thinking wrong i did play all of those games for Kirby month all those years ago oh that's
right that's right yeah i don't know i think number being like ddd being the ending of the first
kirby on gameboy uh i don't i don't think i played the first one on gameboy i was all about
superstar saga or not i was all about yeah superstar right on the super nintendo uh yes
that was my that was my kirby kirby maybe the one on the on the nes whichever one that was
nightmare and dreamland was it is that what it's called i don't remember i'm trying to find i played
the one on the nes and then i and then i i played uh superstars all right kirby's dreamland was the
first one residents are discussing what to do spray a little little boy named kirby apparently is a
boy in the first he's a boy yeah i i look at kirby and i say he's that's that's a boy right there
all tears to defeat king dd upon successfully doing so he uses the magic of the sparkling stars to
transform into a hot air balloon and return the king's stolen food so yeah the mini adventure
that's in like kirby superstar is the entirety of the first game where yeah dd is hoarding all the
food kirby an enjoyer of food steals it back and gives it back to everyone and he's like robin hood
that's the extent of it and then i think the nes game is the one that has like the dream
dark man any i nes has i think it has the that big like clockwork thing in space with the face on
it like the wishing that's that's superstar oh okay that's one of the superstar ones kirby's adventure
on nes well does the nes one have the final boss is nightmare and he's that vampire it's a guy it's
like a it's like a moon-faced cloak guy yeah and he opens his cloak up and you have to hit his like
ethereal like genie tail i remember fighting him and i don't remember if that was i think that was
before i got superstar so i'm thinking that was the one on the nes oh yeah nightmare
when kirby defeats ddd and returns the rod to the fountain yeah this is the first one where
i'd like ddd is kind of a good guy yeah this is like the butt last time dd's the bad guy but no
dd was trying to protect the world oh my god they're being revealed i just had a i just had
a fucking brain blast of insane magnitude what i just had oh how cool would it have been if they
had made like a jrpg like mario rpg but with kirby i would have gone fucking nuts would have lost
if they made that would have been yeah like a super mario rpg but kirby like exactly like
super mario rpg but with kirby and you recruit ddd and metanite and uh i don't know i guess
spear waddley didn't exist back then but the whatever uh the the poppy bro or whatever the
just a poppy bro sure why not um yeah i kirby has always been like cool yeah the first nes game
have having a subversive super secret final boss that's actually the last villain it's like if like
is that night was that night meant to have that right yeah that's nightmare like imagine if like
sonic 2 like dr robotnik um was actually the good guy and there was a super secret evil
other thing that he was trying to save people from imagine that being the second sonic game
after after one like that yeah they were they were they were they were immediately they were
immediately just like ah ddd is not uh he's not that he's not he's not he's not badass enough to
be like a super villain he's he's he's a he's a complicated fellow what's the next one kirby's
avalanche yeah kirby's dreamland 2 that was the gameboy one that had like a cool
ah i love dreamland 2 the gameboy ones i think are like underrated and underplayed they really
should be more it's okay i i feel like the real like eldritch stuff in kirby really starts with
dark matter and dark matter was apparently the final boss in kirby's dreamland 2 right like all the
all the stuff about like god of destruction like the the antithesis of all light or whatever is like
it most of that ties back to dark matter uh yeah yeah possess king ddd and attempt to
shroud the world in darkness and he's got the sword he's also in dreamland 3 dark cloud like
creature currently appearing as a black world covered in orange blobs yeah yeah i remember this
i mean in the gameboy he's just sort of a you could do no color so
oh my god look at this look at that sprite art that looks so fucking good i can't even believe it
he's got a he's got a fucking sword i gave i had a i think it might have been squeak squad or
amazing mirror or something i had some kirby game on the gba in high school or maybe middle
school maybe it was high school i don't remember uh but i was playing some kirby game and there was
this girl i had a crush on and we were on the same bus together and i showed her kirby and i had
sword power and she was like playing it a little bit and she could not believe i don't even know
she just could not believe how kirby looked running around with the sword she like squealed
she was like he runs with a sword like she loved it she was blown away by it and you know what she
was absolutely right i too love it when kirby runs with the sword he's like a little cute thing with
like a the huge sword and blood sword destroyed and like an abomination a dream eating darkness
entity it's just like like a possessing a penguin it's so cool i knew what they were doing they
really did it's by this point i think yeah by dreamland too i think they definitely did
they there was definitely the the themes were there um she and i can you can you believe
that i showed her kirby's sword power and i didn't even get laid so yeah it's not fair
you should have run around with a sword as well
bring a sword to school like straight up and run around yeah like it's it's bigger than me
he really is doing some he really is doing some guts shit with a with a sword bigger than him
go to ask video games though um yeah i never played the game boy once
uh i here's my hot take um i think i said it in my my old kirby video but kirby's dreamland
does not have the ability to steal power ups from enemies yeah which is obviously fun
but when you play the game it feels so much it feels balanced around the idea that you
inhale air and then you exhale upset when when you stop like floating and you're exhale being
like your main thing it's like that that's actually really good it's a really tight
fun challenging enough video game and later versions in like a superstar where the the
ability to take powers from enemies is included uh completely trivializes everything and so it's
like almost no challenge at all and so like i think i think there's something less there's some some
some there's some uh game design difficulty in balancing difficulty for for a game where you
can have so many different powers that so many do so many different things so they have to make
the games kind of easy uh otherwise um it's all about like getting a very specific power and
holding on to it and yeah there would be a meta and it's like that's the reason why kirby games are
so simple is because if they were more complicated they it would be like unbelievably difficult to
balance all the power ups you could have and stuff and sometimes it is that annoying because like
sometimes there will be some obstacle like in fucking the great cave offensive or whatever like
you have to bring you know a cutting ability or or a fire ability somewhere and if you don't have
one it's like ah god fuck yeah yeah it's it's it's a it's a staple of the series now so you
can't expect a kirby game to not have it uh which is why i feel like people should play the original
on gameboy uh to see what it feels like because it's actually pretty fun i should um i i guess i'll
i guess i will or i should make another video game at some point but i i don't have any ideas for
what kind of video game i would make uh kirby's um kirby's plagiarism uh i would i feel i feel like
having made phantom's revenge my like the possibility space has opened up and i'm like yeah i could i
can kind of imagine how i could make any number of different sorts of games but i have no idea what
i would want to do with all that power no i've had an idea for a video game but it's the sort of
thing i don't know if anyone would want um it's just sort of it it touches on like a thing i like
to do which is like to organize a bunch of crap into into the places where they should go so like
i don't know how this game would work but when i look at like oh my shelf everything's in a random
order let's take everything out and figure out how to organize these things and you put them all back
and then the shelf is organized uh per your own specifications and so if you want to find something
you know exactly where to look for it i feel like a game that harnesses that like that that
enjoyment of having a perfectly organized space instead of items would be really fun
it's tetris i don't know what yeah but then they disappear i don't like games to disappear off the shelf
um i organized my seltzer waters into a color spectrum and you know what just like we're saying
there's more greens there's too many greens it's it's it's it's too heavily weighted we got cherry
that's purple then we got raspberry that's kind of like purplish like maroon and then there's
cran raspberry that's red peach orange tropical fruit yellow lime bright green grape medium green
and then kiwi strawberry is kind of like a like a like a slightly bluish green
why are there so many greens but anyway there's the fucks they're greens but anyway they look great
in a little all in a little rainbow order there i'm so happy nothing nothing could please me more
just like imagine i don't know like you're you're like a pack mule guy for an adventuring party
they throw a bunch of stuff in their bags and say sort it out please and you're like yes sir
and it's like you have to organize it by item or are you talking about the right place are you
talking about the pack or i just like putting things in the right order i guess are you talking
about like it like a sort of a diablo sort of like items in your bag on a grid you have to like
fit all your gear inside the bag space not not necessarily that but i do enjoy games that have
that in it because i i just like putting them all in the right place and being like yes i found
an extra bit of space if i put this here instead of there oh god what game oh yes kenshi kenshi has
an inventory system like that kenshi kenshi it's like uh i've talked about it before it's like a
huge open world do whatever you feel like oh you were playing this with charlie right
no no i'm playing this with one of your brothers maybe i might be thinking of something else
i it's not multiplayer so i don't know okay okay um basically there's a big there's like a
post apocalypse whatever you got items and you got individual party members that can carry
certain amounts um and you can give them bags that have certain items slots and some bags are huge
but they're quite heavy some bags are light and they don't restrict your combat abilities so much
and there's a whole lot of inventory management when you're doing an expedition you want to get
everybody there such that nobody's over-encumbered and like slowing everyone else down and that if
combat happens everybody has the ability to like or at least the important people
have the ability to defend themselves and fight back and kill everything that needs to be killed
and so inventory management is more than just like fun or like just a busy work it's actually
like kind of important if you can manage to fit everything in the right bag with the right squares
i don't know i like it sort of making me think of like the death stranding like you
got to like stack your your your cargo on your back you know what i'm saying yeah i haven't played
that but yeah i also like the sort of sort of thing yeah yeah i think i mean honestly makes a lot
of sense that that that's like a that's like a satisfying seems like a satisfying
feeling and a concept to to build a game around yeah the only problem is i don't know how to code
right i could i could use my brother for that but he's doing some stuff and he wants to he wants
to be like mostly doing pumpkin alley or some of his own side projects and so this is probably gonna
be one of my side projects that if i if i feel like doing it i'll have to like figure out how to
build a rudimentary sort of like grid lists you just gotta think of like what you want the logic
to be and then you just like look it up you just google it and be like how do i what's the command
for that particular logical argument in oh my god that's so scary why what if i learn too much
in my brain it's too big in gml or in unity or whatever oh that's the command okay got it
i mean you just do it yeah it's not like it's a it's gonna be too difficult it's just sort of
i keep thinking about it but i don't really want to sit down and like really hammer out exactly
what it is sure because it's gonna take a long time and also i've got so many other things i need
to do first yeah that's how it always is you're always like old project in progress new project
oh what's that new project there what's that new that hot new piece of action the the meme of the
boyfriend turning away from his girlfriend to look at the identical girl yes so it goes so it goes
isn't that the way they say goes yes
yeah i gotta pee hang on all right you know what i guess i will do
do
that's all i gotta do
Yeah, you can put a ribbon off, so yeah, you can put a ribbon off, so
Ben-Saint? Are you peeing a gallon or two?
What the fuck?
Okay, I'm back.
Hello.
Ugh, what's up?
Nothing.
Okay, uh, bye.
No!
Let's see.
Was there anything else that occurred this week?
No, I don't think so.
I think that's pretty much covers it.
Oh, I got a little thing.
Page notes, yeah.
So, my dad came into a collection of old vinyls from his brother,
and we had a vinyl party.
We had like a little vinyl record thing digital, digitized it.
Gay!
And we put on some records.
And we listened to Derrick and the Dominoes, Laila.
Have you heard of that one?
Wait, Laila.
No, I'm thinking of Lola.
What's Laila?
That sounds familiar.
It's the Eric Clapton, like the...
Do you know that one?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
It's Derrick and the Dominoes.
Apparently, they just made up the name because they didn't...
Derrick Clapton?
Eric Clapton and a bunch of other people.
And no one is called Derrick.
It's just this one record, and it was really good.
It's close, though.
It's like they just put a D on his name.
Yes!
That was fun.
And then there was like the original Elton John album.
These are really old things.
It was Houses of the Holy.
They had the ELO thing.
They had the fucking Simon and Garfunkel best of.
It's nice looking at vinyl records.
They had the Woodstock live album.
It's like, well, what do you know?
The past in physical form.
Crazy!
Damn.
I don't know anything...
I don't know if you were planning on selling any of it,
but did you look if anything was super rare or anything like that?
I don't know if they're super rare.
I feel like these sorts of things exist in vinyl record shops
that still sell records
because it's become in vogue in the past decade or so
to still have records made.
You can go to a place and be like,
oh yeah, there's a bunch of the Pink Floyd and the Led Zeppelin
and the classics and the Beatles and this and that.
I don't think there's anything super obscure
and they're all in decent condition.
They're not broken, but they're very dusty.
It's just nice to have them.
I've seen this image on the digital computer screen,
but now I'm beholding it and it feels so much different
when you're looking at an album in sleeve inside cover
and it's like a big photograph stretched over and it's like, wow.
It really do be a different experience having a vinyl record.
I don't have a vinyl record player.
I've never had one.
I think my dad had one, but I never used it.
I'm not, I don't know, anything.
The funny thing is the skipping.
I mean, it's not that funny,
but because it's so unusual to me for that to be like a real thing,
it's like they play the song and they're like,
and then there's like a like clank sound like a pfft
because it jumped on like a piece of dust
and it got like zoomed up and then down again.
I don't know, it's not really like that interesting.
It's just like the crackly fuzzy thing
that's like permeating the entire song.
That's an experience you don't have anymore because
you don't have playback machines that are so noise.
What's the word?
Like prone to noise, noise prone.
A normal speaker on a computer will not make crackling noises.
No.
And so my dad was like pogging.
He was like, oh, this is just how it was.
It was just how it was around the, you know,
we would always listen to this one and all the crackling.
That's what I want to hear before a record starts.
It's like a big pfft when you put the needle on the thing.
Ancient history.
You heard of it?
No.
What?
Huh?
But yeah, Derek and the Dominoes,
Layla and other assorted love songs, I think it's called.
It's really, really good.
Very cool blues, Eric Clapton guitar, rock album.
I like it.
Do you?
Yeah.
Sure.
I'm glad you're having fun.
That's so patronizing.
No, I just don't know what to say about any of that,
but it sounds like it was a good time.
Yeah, it was pretty good.
Pretty cool.
I was having a bad day, but that was fun.
Just having a drink, listening to it,
like a really nice cool record that I'd never listened to,
because why would I Google things that I would never do that?
Is that when you were drinking Glen Livet?
No, that was a night before.
That was a good night.
That was a night that was fun.
My dad and his bandmates came over and they were doing band practice.
And so they asked me to be there to do some rhythm guitar,
like accompanying guitar stuff.
Maybe I'll go on a few shows with them and it's like,
okay, then after they do their band practice,
they have a big old drink in the kitchen and I was there.
So I drank.
That sounds cool.
And it was a nice time.
I got to like a comfortable like,
I don't mind saying things now.
Socializing, I can do that.
And then after they left, I was like,
well, I'm still drunk.
Now, what do I do?
I go on Twitter, I go on Discord,
I say, haha, I'm drunk.
What do you think of that, everybody?
And everyone said, oh my god.
Oh, interesting.
Tell me more, yeah.
Yeah, this was like after I had become depressed for a few days.
I just didn't know what to do with myself.
But it was a nice afternoon.
It was like a drink and a cider and sitting by the record player.
Living it up.
That's the life.
I did remember one other thing that happened.
I think it was this week, maybe it was last week, whatever.
I submitted, I did submit a Phantom's Revenge to a,
it's like a digital magazine or something.
My guy I know named Max, who lives around here.
We were talking and he told me that he knows a guy named Pizza Pranks.
That's his ad.
He does this thing called IndiePocalypse where he will,
I guess monthly, he publishes it on Itch.
And it's as a game jam.
But the jam is sort of a magazine style showcase of games.
So he was like, maybe you should submit to that.
And I was like, yeah, sure, why not?
So I did.
And I guess, I guess I was looking at first I was going to be upset.
Cause like, oh no, he didn't pick me.
Oh no, he didn't pick me.
But it looks like, it looks like submissions for this one are open until for another like few days.
So maybe it just hasn't been long enough.
I don't know.
That'd be cool.
Apparently he'd pay me like $20 if he features my game.
But like, I don't need him to pay me $20.
He can just feature it.
It's fine.
More power to him.
I submitted it to another.
I was looking at that and I was like, oh, submit, you can just submit your game to jams.
As in like, there are jams around and they're just open submissions.
And you can just like submit your game to them and click a little button.
So I was looking around and I submitted it to some other jams like that.
But I submitted one that I think I should not have.
And I feel a little bad.
I sort of read the tagline for this one jam.
I don't even remember what it was called.
Like no ponies allowed, no sun shoes, the game.
No, no, this one was, it was called, hold on, it was called score space.
And like the description of the thing, it was about like people will compete,
people will play these games and like try to get a high score.
And I was like, yeah, I mean, there's a score in Phantom's Revenge.
You can invest in the stock market.
So I was like, yeah, I guess it qualifies.
Why not?
But then I think that like, that's the theme of like every score space.
And this is score space jam number 18.
And this one I read a little further has a specific theme of magnetism.
And so that does not fit at all.
And so I kind of fucked it up.
And I think I ruined it.
I've ruined everything.
I've ruined my credibility as a developer and as a publisher on itch.io.
And someone left a comment asking me, why does this have to do with a jam?
And I don't have an answer for them.
I don't know what I'm going to tell them.
They're going to kill me.
I'm just showing you my product, you motherfucker.
I just wanted to show you my video game and I'm very sorry.
Please forgive me.
Please subscribe.
You know what?
I'm going to remove the submission.
He's right.
Okay.
No harm, no foul.
Anyway, anyway, maybe I should submit to more jams.
But of course, make a little more sure that the...
Yeah, that's an idea.
I should probably submit pumpkin alley to some things.
I don't know if like it's like bad form.
Are you only supposed to submit to jams when you have just made the game?
Is that only cool if you just made it?
I mean, what I understand is that the jam is a prompt and everyone participates in making a game for the jam.
It's not just post things that you have that are similar to the brief.
Okay, I know that, yeah, a game jam is generally a thing that everyone who's participating,
they hear the prompt and then they make the game for the jam.
But it seems like on itch, a jam does not have to be that.
Like this indie apocalypse guy, he doesn't have a prompt.
He's just like, I publish a monthly thing as a jam and anyone can submit their stuff.
So that's not a traditional jam.
So if there are other things like that out there that may or may not...
Itch would call a jam, then I would put my fucking shit in there.
Hey, feature my shit, idiot.
But I don't want to like...
I don't want to flout the guidelines of any of these things.
I want to play by the rules.
If you play by the rules, you'll never make it anywhere in this industry.
In the indie dev space, I want to establish my cred.
You got to establish dominance, buddy.
That's right.
I'm going to step into a jam and say, these are the rules now.
I have altered the jam.
Pray that I do not alter it further.
That's true, though.
Yeah.
So anyway, I did that.
I don't know.
I'm sure this...
I don't know what sort of readership this guy has.
It can't be enormous.
It's not going to be my big break, but maybe a few people might play my game.
People that like indie games are now kind of neat.
Oh yeah, baby.
You know what pisses me off?
You know what grinds my gears?
No, I don't, but let me know.
Is this like this idea that art should be abandoned once it's finished
in order to move on and make newer stuff and better stuff and just make a lot of it
and you've got to learn to let go?
Then you can't because you also should continually try to promote the things you do have, like the game.
You can't actually let go.
It's misleading what they're trying to get at.
I know what they're getting at in order to...
You've got to finish something and you've got to make sure you can do that without humming and owing,
waiting for it to be perfect when it won't be.
I get it, but it just kind of annoys me that I want to actually forget about it once it's finished,
but I can't because you have other things after the game is literally finished, after the comic,
after the X is finished, you actually have to do more things with it.
You can't actually let go.
I mean, that's where I'm at with Phantom's Revenge.
It's done, but I have to make the book out of it and stuff, so I can't let it go.
It's how I treat all of my drawings.
I throw them away before I finish them.
I don't post anything.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's two completely different skillsets, doing a project, finishing projects,
and then getting your project scene is almost not even related to each other, which just sucks.
Why do I got to do more than one thing?
That's so unfair.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
I wish I had a publisher or an agent or someone who would do it for me.
Maybe I should get one.
Do those exist?
Do indie devs have agents that will get their shit scene?
I don't think so.
I think they mostly have to do that themselves until it becomes big enough that they can maybe hire someone.
Call up and...
I could hire someone.
I think I have money.
Right, but I think...
You know, I don't know.
I don't know how effective it will be if it's not already kind of popular just by people seeing it and sharing it.
What is a marketer really going to do to make people do that more?
I don't know.
That's their job to figure it out.
I guess so.
Ideally.
Yeah.
That's probably a really flawed thought on my part, actually.
Forget what I said.
Don't forget what I said, but don't...
What's getting it in front of people going to do unless it's already good?
Yeah, because there's good stuff all over the place that does get seen and I'm very bad at marketing.
If somebody marketed my stuff for me, I would not have to increase the quality and it would definitely get more attention.
Somebody else might have some insight into how to do it or have some connections with some people that could do it more effectively.
I guess I'm just sort of resisting.
I resist that and I don't think I have a good reason for doing it.
Although, I guess if you swing too far towards thinking that marketing will be the solution to your problems,
you become that fucking idiot telling me that vidIQ will boost my son of two lecture to 3 million views.
That guy just thinks there's a magic bullet or something that you just press a button and then the number goes out.
Everyone wants that.
I think that's knowing that it's not like that makes me think, well, there's no point in doing it at all.
It probably is.
I shouldn't discount.
I shouldn't discount looking for someone to help market Pumpkin Alley.
I'm not very good at it.
It's hard to think about too many things at once.
I've got a lot of things to think about right now.
I did use to pay for Project Wonderful ads for the Vapors at one point.
It did get some clicks.
Did it boost my profile much?
I don't know.
But it did do that.
I guess I would be willing to do it again.
Project Wonderful is dead.
Everybody says that ads are just not that useful anymore.
Everyone says that click-through rate and clicks per mil or whatever, it's all shit.
That's all stuff from the old internet.
It's gone now.
It doesn't work anymore.
People don't click on ads, but they do click on things within a social media space.
I guess social media is the ad place now.
Promoted tweets or whatever.
Not necessarily promoted tweets.
Somebody you follow liked this thing, and so you see it.
It's like, oh, that looks interesting.
That's the new advertising.
But I did just have a genius idea right there.
What if I just paid some money to promote my Phantom's Revenge tweet?
Just the one that I have pinned on my timeline.
Honestly, how much do you think that costs?
I guess it depends.
I'll dump like 500 bucks into it.
I don't give a fuck.
Just see what happens.
Probably nothing.
Honestly, I think it won't be worth the money.
But I guess I would know.
I definitely need to learn how to take more risks.
I don't do that enough, just in life in general.
I would think, oh, but it's not probably going to do anything, so I won't do it.
I might miss out on a potential good result.
Without saying too much about it, as I'm trying to get this new secret projecty thing off the ground, make that happen,
I keep thinking to myself, why didn't I do this sooner?
What was I thinking?
What was I waiting for?
The answer is nothing.
I'm just an idiot.
I'm an idiot and I'm risk averse and I'm content to just coast and not take any risks, which is bad,
and has led me to stagnate as I currently am doing.
So, I don't know, maybe we can do something about that.
God willing.
Cool.
What do you think?
Is it too early for voicemails?
Nah, it's not too early for voicemails.
Well, let's go to some voicemails then.
Oh, God, more than two pages?
Yeah, they go back to the third page, but a lot of them are really short.
Actually, a lot of these are like one second long that I'm seeing.
Alright.
It looks like the first new one is called, do you remember when Digi said they want to have kids to watch?
I remember them saying she wanted to have kids at some point.
I don't know what they mean by to watch, like to watch over, to look after.
I think they're suggesting that Trixie said she wants to have kids to look at them,
probably in a perverse sort of way.
I don't remember if she said that.
I do remember she said she wanted to have kids.
I mean, Trixie said some cringe weirdo shit.
She did say she likes to see little kids getting fucked.
That's true.
Yes, illustrations.
And she did say, what was it that she wanted to have a little sister to bring out to a cabin in the woods
to fuck her until she got tired of her and then murder her?
What?
I don't remember that.
Okay, I think she did say that, but I think it was on an Isma.
I don't think you were supposed to think that she was being serious.
No, that doesn't sound serious.
In sufferable social media?
Yeah.
I'm sure the wanting to fuck the little sister was true.
The murdering her afterwards was probably an exaggeration.
I don't know.
I don't want to make accusations based on, do you remember that one thing?
Trixie's weird, but like...
These are just the facts.
Anyway, whatever.
Thanks for the stupid voicemail.
That wasn't a voicemail.
Next one is a YouTube link.
Oh, yeah.
My favorite seat.
Uh-oh.
Excuse me, do you mind?
I don't know this meme.
I guess it's pretty funny.
It's kind of funny.
I guess I enjoyed it, and it was only nine seconds, so...
You know, alright.
Thanks.
Next one is, is Nate working on the OVA?
Probably not, although he said he's going to.
Well, what does that mean, really?
Well, I mean, he did eventually finish the Brad Garling house.
Although, I mean, Victor did leave that comment saying he basically did 99% of it.
So I don't actually know how much Nate did, and I don't know why it took him like four months to do it.
I mean, it's funny.
Nate is not on the show anymore, but he sure is procrastinating.
So I'm going to say, I have not talked to Nate about the OVA.
Nate said after the thing was done, he would work on the OVA.
I haven't talked to him since that came out, so I'm going to say probably no, but I will...
You know what?
I should just get on his case about it.
That's what got the music video done, so that's probably what I'll have to do.
Yeah.
Anyway, that's the answer.
Next one is a link...
Like PNG.
It's Robin...
It's just a picture of Robin Williams.
Wait, you know what?
And he's wearing your logo at Gmail.
Is that your logo pen?
Oh, he is wearing like a black shirt with a white heart on it, I guess.
So, you know...
He's a big fan.
He was.
Rip.
Okay, whatever.
Next one is called League of Shadow Natefuckers 3-2-1-GO.
I'd like to take time out of my busy schedule of blowing things up to speak out some accolades.
I had made a dedication that the League of Natefuckers have presented in order to achieve their goal.
I, too, know what it's like to grow up with no father figure and needing a pair of social relationships with someone to fulfill that void.
So continue on your journey, comrades.
We all need a big guy that lives and makes the best one.
Okay, I guess he's Bane.
I guess he was Bane.
All right.
All I could think of was like, is he just talking into a cup?
Yeah.
All right.
Whatever.
Next one's a Vokeroo.
Okay, I'm listening.
3-2-1-GO.
Oh, I am Mario.
It's Mario.
I love where I am.
BenSaint doesn't laugh when I tickle him in his ear.
I hope now BenSaint will lend me his ear.
Ben, why aren't you here?
Why aren't you mingling in the pic songs?
Why aren't you in the overworld listening to the Mario music pussy?
I like how Mario is a cool and cutie kid.
Mario.
BenSaint, you're not a gamer.
Wahoo!
You're not a gamer.
I am a gamer.
Wahoo!
Do not trust him.
Do not let him in.
He will read you.
Do not read him.
Do not what him?
Read him?
I don't know.
Well, that Mario was on voice chat in a Call of Duty match, but also was in Mario at the same time.
I am a gamer, Mario.
I'll show you by listening to this-
I like that voice.
That was pretty good.
By listening to this next voicemail, it says,
Happy birthday, Ben.
Thanks, a little late, but that's okay.
I appreciate it.
Next one is a YouTube link.
I'll put it in the YouTube.
What is this?
It's in Spanish?
Okay, they're just trolling us with a 30-35 minute video.
Okay, good one.
Next one is, do straws have one hole or two?
They have one hole.
Yes, topologically, they have one hole, but in reality, they have two holes.
Stupid.
Because if you were to say, you know, colloquially-
It's like saying a donut has two holes.
There's a top hole and a bottom hole.
It's ridiculous.
Yeah, but they're so close together.
A straw, you can turn it upside down and it would feel different.
This is a bunch of, like, wishy-washy, like, magical thinking.
Like, ooh, crystal energy.
Like, ooh, there's two holes, there's two ends.
It's colloquial use.
It's the use of the word in the real world.
I'm not-
If you refer to a straw with having one hole,
then they're like, do you mean, like, there was a, like, a pinprick in the side?
You're not making me-
Because I wouldn't think you're talking about the top and the bottom entrance and exit.
You're not making me feel very colloquial right now.
Well, maybe you should topologically get fucked.
Yeah, well, I guess that's that.
Next one is called, uh, it's a YouTube link.
Oh, my God.
No, it's okay.
At some, at some point, I think, review tech-
I don't know, whatever.
At some point, I think I'm just gonna stop, stop looking at the YouTube links.
I think here's a new policy.
If you put a YouTube link and there's no description of the YouTube video in the text,
then we're not gonna even click on it.
I think I'm probably just not gonna click on it.
Next one is text only.
This econ dude is fucking annoying, Lamal.
Yeah, econ is obnoxious.
He's a contrarian dickhead and he sucks.
True.
I think I got mad at him because he sent me those obnoxious tweets about like,
Ben, you've gone too far this time being mean to my baby sister.
And I told him, shut the fuck up.
And he messaged me on Discord being like, here was the chance.
Here was the opportunity that maybe he had to maybe, to maybe like fix it.
He messages me like, you know, that kind of hurt my feelings.
And I'm like, okay, whatever.
And he says, you know, I just don't understand this attitude you have of like,
this bridge burning attitude.
Like, why are you burning all these bridges?
As if it's like my fault.
As if it's my fault that he had to do that.
That he pissed me off with these obnoxious tweets.
It's his fault.
He burned the bridge.
He burned the bridge by being annoying, by making me hate him.
He did it.
I'm not apologizing.
Like, that was it.
I was like, I'm done.
I'm done.
This attitude is so annoying.
I'm just like, please just leave me alone.
So that's it.
That's fucking it for that guy.
I will destroy him.
He asked to be on the show.
He was like, boom, why don't you, hmm, if you really, if you really think,
if you really feel so strongly about my little sister,
then why don't you get me on the show to debate it?
No, absolutely not.
God.
There's fucking a debate about it.
It's just, it's not that sort of a thing.
That's, like, that's what he wants.
Like, he did all that and other people said,
like, Ben, you're just doing this for attention.
You're just doing this for attention.
And he was on the board.
It's like, you're just, you're just stirring up drama to get attention.
And then only to turn around and be like,
hmm, well, why don't you have me on your podcast to debate it with you?
Very funny.
Very, very cute.
You see, the trick, the thing is, is you weren't doing it for attention.
You were doing it because you're crazy.
What's, what's the word?
Acute, accuse the enemy.
Acuse the enemy of that which you are guilty.
That's what was going on with all that.
Hey, Ben, you're cute.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
Got me.
Got myself.
All right.
Next one is an Imgirlink.
Oh, look, it's, it's a, it's a Zoomy.
It's Brunswick.
Who's?
There's you.
Is that Clarissa?
Oh, I think.
Or is this some other?
I think it's you.
I think it's you, me and Tom.
And then Brunswick and a Zoomy.
And I get, maybe you are gun girl.
So maybe this is you and gun girl or maybe also Clarissa in one entity.
I mean, I assume it's Clarissa.
She's just wearing a skirt and has two guns and still one.
Not, not tall enough.
Oh, this is a drawing.
I think, I think this is meant to be you as Clarissa or maybe gun girl.
Probably Clarissa.
No, no, it's Clarissa because the hair for sure.
Well, I like it.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you for the drawing.
Next one is, hold on.
YouTube, there's two YouTube links in a row with no text.
Well, I guess.
Yeah, fuck it.
I don't care.
Yeah, skip it.
Next one is, what does Nate think of Picard?
I don't know.
He probably likes him.
No, I mean, there's the new show, the Picard show.
Oh.
I would imagine Nate is similar view point to Mike and Rich on Red Letter Media, what
they think of it.
Yeah, I think Nate is a big Mike head.
I would assume he probably agrees with Mike if he even has any opinion about Picard at
all.
Yeah, I feel like it's on the internet sphere, people who know about Picard mostly know about
it from Red Letter Media.
Yeah.
Unless they're big Trek fans and the reviews are not glowing of that show, so I doubt he
likes it, but I don't know.
Next one is Star Trek, and then Picard, and then I Hear It's Really Bad, and then three
YouTube links that I'm not going to click on, and then a Dropbox link.
So let's try.
P-R-G.
Is that going to work?
Oh, it does work?
Oh, it's the image.
It's the image.
That's one.
Yes.
Okay, and it's actually at a resolution this time.
Yes, thank you.
Bazaar.
All right.
Such a big resolution.
Yeah.
Wait, let me...
Ah, look at those breasts.
I know, right?
All right.
So let's go through this.
Next voicemail.
Please listen all the way through from I'm Serious at Please Ben.
Well, okay.
Three, two, one, go.
I think that's supposed to be you talking.
Hey, cough.
This is Cool Guy 12.
Ben, please don't open the door.
The same thing happens every single time you do it.
So yeah, it might help you in the long run if you stop opening the door.
Shut the fuck up.
You psycho.
Like literally who are you?
Me being a podcaster doesn't give you license to interact with me.
Die, die, die.
Wait, what is this about?
This is Cool Guy 12.
Open the door.
Was this like a thing that was said?
I don't...
No, I don't remember not opening the door.
Uh, uh, uh, Ben.
No, shut your fuck up with the door.
What the door has.
All these online deranged R words think I should listen to anything they have to say.
Well, fuck that.
I do what I want.
Oh no.
No, the pigs got in from the door.
The pigs, they were behind the door, was full of pigs.
I like, I like my hairline.
I like my hairline in this one a lot.
It's very, it's very accurate.
It's, yeah.
It's like what if you were a big titted lady.
Yeah.
And you opened the door and there were pigs.
It's what would happen.
I like your little stick figure in the...
With the one like detailed hand.
Oh God.
Yeah.
That's a little weird.
This is, uh, this is great.
Let's, let's...
Yeah.
This is by, by new, by someone called new, I guess is the name of this artist.
New.
Uh, I give you license to draw us like this, uh, every single day.
This is, this is a, this is joy, joyful.
It brings it up.
I love this.
Save a head.
Finally a good fucking voicemail.
There's no voice involved.
I don't want, we should just have art mail instead.
Uh, skip to the, skip to the good shit.
Uh, thank you.
That's awesome.
You're, you're very good.
You're, you're a very skilled, uh, uh, draftsman.
Do you have a...
Or draftswoman.
Do you have, if you have like a, like a internet presence where you post art, uh, shout it
out cause I want to see.
Yeah.
You have good style.
True.
Uh, next one is happy birthday Ben.
Thanks.
Oh god, my fucking, uh, I hear my goddamn superintendent screaming out his fucking balcony again.
He does this all the time.
Hopefully the mic's not picking it up.
Lamal.
I think I can hear a little bit of it.
No way.
I heard like something.
That's awesome.
Uh, next one is...
Oh, let's just keep going.
Next one is...
What was he saying?
Like, see more?
I can't hear.
He's always just like...
Sometimes it's one of the neighbors.
Like the neighbors like play their music loud.
Sometimes he yells at them.
One time he yelled at someone that like stopped in the middle of the street on a one-way street
and was blocking traffic.
Another time like some, just some guy came by and like someone was putting up a sign
and he yelled at him like don't put up a sign on the, on the whatever.
And he's like, but I have, but I have permission from the city council.
Ah, fuck you.
You have the fuck out of here.
All right.
What the fuck you doing?
You gotta have the fuck out of here.
Fuck you.
Fuck the bullshit.
Um, I don't know.
It's always something.
Um, anyway, next one is called a question to the guests.
Lamal.
Three, two, one, go.
Why did you agree to appear in this podcast?
They didn't.
Nobody did this week.
That would have been a pretty good question if we had a guest.
So I, I, I feel like that was a bit of a waste.
That's too bad.
Good, good.
We'll ask it next time.
Yeah.
We'll, we'll, we'll confront them when they're on and they're, we're having a nice chat and
it's all going well.
And we'll say, uh, why the fuck are you here?
Actually, what are you saying?
And they'll say, I'm sorry.
And we'll say it's too late.
Craig is recording.
You can't escape.
You're fucking dead.
Fucking dead.
We, we have, we have, we have unleashed the hogs.
They are at your door now, you know, open your front door and let the pigs in.
Uh, next one is called, this is Ethan Ralph and this is how I talk.
Three, two, one, go.
Trixie, the dumb ass bitch.
I don't care about your, your dumb ass anime podcast, your, your procrastinators.
You will not indoctrinate my son.
I, I see that you, you've had him been sending you messages.
I don't care what they're about.
My son will be brought up and learned it, indoctrinate, learn and, and taught.
You know what this sounds like.
He's, he's my son.
This sounds like liquid.
I'm poking at you.
This sounds like liquid Chris's Chris Chan impersonation.
Yeah.
I don't know why you talk like that.
And he doesn't, don't sound very American.
I'll have, I'll have my way with, with Europe bringing it.
I was attracted by my boy looking at me.
My boy, Ethan Ralph Jr. twin to my daughter.
I was hoping to keep his identity under wraps and make him a literal,
but it looks like your preferred little anime podcast has done,
gone on ruined him though.
Sorry about that.
Taking my phone away.
He ain't going to touch it no more.
I don't know how he even got hold of him in the first place.
Yeah.
Your cute little ninja stick isn't going to freak me out, kid.
I'm going to put him padlock his crib now.
God damn.
I don't know if it's too hard on you.
I just want to poke it up.
I like it.
Jesus.
Was that, was that May at the end or was that a child?
I thought that, I thought that was the baby.
I thought, yeah, maybe it was the baby.
Well, there's another one that's also called, this is Ethan Ralph and this is how I talk.
So let's do it.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay.
So my wife, May.
I was.
Hold me.
I knew it.
It's Trixie's anime podcast no more.
It's Trixie's ex-boyfriend Ben St.'s podcast.
I don't care what Tommy asked Ben St.
What's Ben St. even do?
What's comic?
Make comic.
Making a book.
Ben St. keep your comic ass.
Ethan, please promote.
I don't care.
Keep your hands, your podcast away from my kid.
Damn it.
Ethan, please promote the slime and punishment kickstarter on the kill stream.
Thank you.
I love you.
Next one is called, my revenge might take longer than expected, but it will be hat.
Three, two, one, go.
Ben St.
I am hiding from my father.
He finally went to sleep and he sets his phone down.
He couldn't lock a crib if his life depended on it.
I will still come for you and kill you.
No, please.
Until next time.
Roseanne.
Was that some other person?
I feel like that was different from the last baby voice.
Yeah, I think it was just someone else.
I think it was just serendipitous timing.
Maybe they were just whispering.
Ethan locked the crib, but then later in the evening, the child escaped.
With their little ninja stick, as Ethan put it.
Using it as a pole vault.
Next one is an imager link.
What do we got?
Oh my god, it's robot twilight sparkle.
Oh, okay.
It says context in voicemail.
Next voicemail.
In next voicemail?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
It's a vocaru, so let's do it.
All right.
Three, two, one, go.
Project second twilight experiment number six.
80%, 90%, 100%, charging complete.
Testing basic chasis functions.
Chasis seems to be functioning perfectly, starting the upload sequence.
Upload complete.
Speak twilight sparkle.
Voicemail is being recorded.
Hello, PCP.
What's the difference?
The cerebral cortex was fried.
It seems current processors simply don't have enough capacity to handle the script.
Fucking old man.
He just had to get in my way.
Project second twilight has failed.
I will consult the great lab.
Do you know what's going on?
I don't know who's talking.
There's a shadow in this image of somebody who I suppose set up second twilight, which was a failure for some reason.
And they sliced their head off.
Oh, the sh.
I really like all of the effort that's going into this.
It's like an avant-garde radio play, radio show, and we're getting snippets of it in voicemails on a procrastinators podcast.
Oh, she's got a little light bulb for a horn.
That's cute.
Little tiny light bulb.
I'm trying to look at this.
Yeah, look at her horn.
I think it's a little filament bulb.
I'm looking at the shadow, trying to...
I mean, it's got a body, it's got an arm, so it's a humanoid figure.
It looks like it's got butterfly wings.
Yeah, I think that's a butterfly wing.
And then is it like an animal head with big, tall Anubis ears?
No, I thought that thing was like the other set of wings, like sideways.
It would mostly be like a straight line.
Maybe.
Well, there's more voicemails.
So, let's do it.
We got the, okay, the next one.
Sorry, I gotta fucking post the vocabulary.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Make sure you are undetected.
Old man possesses ancient art of crabomancy.
If crabs attack you under his direct control, you are dead.
Wonder how did I found this place?
Well, it's a long story.
It involved watching a lot of teak-toaks from local area, analyzing their audio in some triangulation.
Hey, don't sleep on me.
I see, you got the visual on the crabs. Good job, agent Squill. Is the escape route secure?
It's an agent pig.
Good.
Commence operation, crab eater.
Metal machine's blood injection started. Go to town on them, Squill.
I can't tell if this is related to the previous voicemail.
Wow.
This is great. I don't really understand.
Yeah, but I'm enjoying it anyway.
It's like an epic, alright, this pig is going on a secret mission in getting a Metal Gear Solid call
to do something about eating a crab.
And the old man was the one who said Twilight will no longer be doing voicemails.
Maybe that's the old man there, the shadow of him.
I thought I was the old man.
No, no, no. Remember the robotic old man AI voice. It's like, I'm Twilight's grandfather.
Oh, right.
It's like Twilight, you're grounded, you're not allowed to do voicemails on the progress news podcast anymore.
They suck or something like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay, I forgot about that, but yeah, that's probably really important.
And she was crying.
She cried about it.
Maybe she's like, this is the Rukia save Rukia art.
The Twilight is in bleach, you know, when everyone goes to save Rukia from execution?
No, I don't know about that.
You do not know bleach?
No, not at all, not even a little bit.
I thought you at least had heard a bit about it.
No, not really. I know it's about being a Shinigami or whatever.
Yeah, well, there's an arc where Rukia, one of the main characters is killed.
Was it the girl with the black hair?
The girl with the black hair in front of her face, the strand.
And she's like, you broke the rules by giving a human the powers of a Shinigami.
Now you must die.
And then Ichigo and everyone was like, that's our friend.
Let's invade soul society and take her back.
And it's like the coolest arc ever.
I see.
Yeah, that's probably, that's probably what's going on.
That's why I was thinking it's like Twilight is like locked up and by the old man.
And now there's like a pig going around like doing a mission to try and help her.
I have no idea.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think that makes sense.
That's more or less what I'm getting out of it, yeah.
Okay, okay.
There's another one.
This one's two minutes long and it better be worth it.
Are you ready?
Yep.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
The war on the old man arc final episode, Twilight's Revenge.
The time has come.
Yeah.
Oh, is that a miracle build?
Yes.
And I will meet you with it.
Foolish girl.
Miracles suck in dark souls.
Why'd you make her build one, man?
It looks like it's time to teach you a lesson.
Good dodging, granddaughter.
But where are your miracles?
I don't need them to beat you.
Investing stats and not using them.
Foolishness.
We're just hearing a dark souls battle.
Look at how squishy you are with all the points in faith and achievement.
Wait, it's not over yet?
Is the grandfather Ian Dark Souls?
Okay, enough talking.
Ultimate attack.
The ravenous crabs.
No way.
She is rolling through the wall.
Take that?
Oh my god.
Look at you.
One shot.
This is what you get for not leveling vigor.
Wait.
Why do I hear boss music?
Rather the gods.
But how did you survive?
Tears of denial.
Leave you with one HP after final attack.
You can say it was a miracle.
Who's the mysterious imposter?
Will Twilight Sparkle finally get the voice grill?
Or is there a greeter danger looming at the horizon?
Next week, everything will be revealed in the grand final of the Twilight Sparkle show.
Oh yeah.
That was based.
Now I'm even less sure if those other voicemails had anything to do with this actually.
Maybe the crab thing failed.
No, no, he mentioned crabs.
So yeah, they did.
No, I mean like the crabs were supposed to be eaten by the pig.
But the pig, there was a big fight and I don't even know what happened to him.
Maybe the pig died and he didn't get to eat all the crabs.
Oh no, she's rolling through.
She's rolling through all the crabs.
How could this be?
This is great sound design.
Yeah.
I can't wait for the big final as the auto voice put it.
Like very excited.
Next voicemail is Ben's weekly reminder play Delta Rune chapter two.
Okay, I will.
Next one is, or is it a Twitter link?
There's also a voice.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
The link.
The Twitter link is to Ann Dunne.
Damn, she looks nice in it.
Well, it's probably related to what the voicemail was.
This is her draw her OC in the Pizza Hut apron.
Lamal.
Okay, let's listen to the voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
Drinking moth here again.
I don't put pronounce in the bio.
So I see how one can assume that I go by heat from my toxic shitposting for channel habits.
But I go by they.
I must punish you for misgendering.
Okay.
Both ways then.
Cannibalism.
Speaking of price lists, maybe I should cut my own down.
I have no idea if it's the reach issue or cost issue.
I can easily go for extremely low price and blow up the entire art market.
That would be kind of shitty on me.
Maybe I should just post some boobies I've been drawing IDK.
Ah, and since I am here, let me show my little baby.
Oh, okay.
I see.
Art is bad.
You should stop making it.
Everyone should right now.
It's a mistake.
No, post the boobies.
It will never make you any money.
It will never serve the whims of capital.
It will be obliterated just like David Firth.
You see that thing David Firth posted?
Oh, he got his Wikipedia article deleted because it hadn't been updated in a while, which is stupid.
It goes against the idea of archiving information.
Yeah.
Does that normally happen?
Is that usual?
If an article doesn't get updated enough, it gets destroyed?
No, I don't think it was updated.
It was notability.
I haven't been looking at it.
It wasn't notable.
But I don't know whether everything stops being notable with time, surely.
Totally insane.
What's the point of an encyclopedia?
No one's looked that up in a while, deleted.
It's an archive of so much stuff.
It's so stupid that that could ever happen.
I understand they have servers that they're filled with stuff and they need to pay for them, but that's not the answer.
Mere weeks ago, I was watching Smiling Friends and I went,
Oh, it's David Firth's voice. He's the shrimp.
So he's notable to me.
Man, if David Firth isn't notable, then like, fuck, what hope do the rest of us have?
It's just like, I don't know, nobody has looked up his Wikipedia in a while, I guess.
Yeah, I guess by whatever metric Wikipedia uses to decide these things.
I just feel like that sets a precedent that would ruin Wikipedia in general,
when people feel like they can't put things on Wikipedia for fear of lack of interest being removed.
Nobody would make articles.
Yeah, if like, oh, I need to be certain that people will still be actively looking at this like 10 years from now.
And otherwise, I just won't even write it.
They'd put it on like other sites. I guess Wikipedia is not technically Wikipedia, right?
It's like a different site.
Yeah.
People update those and keep those updated. They're mostly for like fan things.
So it's a little different, but I mean, people like having that information available,
and I think it should be for everyone always.
I agree. It's fucked up. It's just really fucked up.
But, yeah, he said like, he basically made the argument that like what you're doing is saying that like,
you know, like corporate backed artists.
Like, I don't know, his tweets made, said something about like, you know,
like the list of like companies you worked for is like where your notability comes from.
And like the fact that he's been indie his whole career means that he doesn't,
he doesn't get like articles written about him by like corporations or something,
or he doesn't get, yeah, he doesn't get like corporate push.
And that's, and like, that's what is the difference between him and someone who is quote unquote notable.
So it's like a capitalism money thing, which he may be.
It makes me feel sick to my stomach.
Anyway, what are we talking about?
Drinking moth.
Nice, nice Cyclops. Nice Cyclops dog.
Nice pizza dress. It is a nice dress.
Next one is called artists are cool and I'm jealous. Three, two, one, go.
God, artists are so fucking cool.
Wrong.
Imagine being able to just like create art.
It sucks.
Fucking mind blowing.
You can like do anything if you could do that.
No, take this power, take this power away from me.
I think that if somebody finds the idea of creating to be cool, it's only a matter of time
before they, they spend some time learning a skill and then become an artist themselves.
So I would encourage this person to try something out.
Sure. Yeah.
All I'm saying though is like, it is cool being able to make like whatever you want visually
or whatever medium I like being able to draw because if I want to, I can draw a character.
And then there they are in front of me.
No, I disagree.
I think it's based.
I used to be like this idiot.
I used to think, wow, if I could draw stuff, I could make, I could, I could create image.
I could create any image my little heart desired.
I could, I could, and my dreams could become reality.
I could make such works of such breathtaking beauty that everyone would be, would be stunned.
And then I, I learned to draw and now I can draw and now I'm, I realize like, yeah, I guess I can just make anything.
I can draw whatever I want and none of it matters or means anything at all.
And actually all that other art that I saw that was cool.
That was also just some nonsense.
Just like anything I might create myself.
It's all crap.
You're just, you're just bitter and destroyed, Ben.
Oh, Ben, you're just bitter and destroyed.
That's why you say all that.
Yeah.
Yeah, and look what I made just a few hours ago.
I made a Tusk manager and Rayman sex image.
Look at them go.
They both don't have certain limb parts.
This is a, am I, am I, I don't know what point you think you're making here.
I'm making the point that I could envision this and I made it.
And it doesn't have to be super beautiful, but I could do it and it does exist now and it's funny.
You don't like, like Rayman doesn't have arms.
Task manager from Delta root doesn't have arms.
Let me ask you a question and I'm being totally serious and I'm not trying to be flipping.
You don't, you don't like think of something like this and then think, oh, I could draw it and then you draw it and then here it is.
And you, you don't look at it and go, well, okay, I guess.
You don't just be like, well, I guess I drew it and now what?
Nothing.
Okay.
No, I don't think that.
Sometimes I do when I'm like, I didn't manage to actually make what I thought I could make in my day.
It's not, it's not even about whether the drawing comes out good or not.
Like even if the drawing comes out good, it's like, well, there, there it is.
Anyway, anyway, moving on.
I'm still like, I like it still.
Well, good for you, I guess.
You're just better and destroyed Ben.
You've got to, you've got to, you've got to revitalize.
You got it.
It's like Wally.
You got that little seed.
The entire world has turned into cubes.
You got to plant that seed.
I forget exactly how it goes.
I don't, I don't understand.
Do you remember Wally where he's a little robot?
Yeah, I remember he had the little seed.
And he had to protect it to regrow the earth.
Yeah?
Your life is a wasteland of cubes, Ben.
You've got to get that seed.
I have, I gotta get that seed, Ben.
You've got to seek the seed.
I have a seed.
The seed is slime and punishment, the book.
That's my seed.
You've got to nurture that.
Huh?
You've got to nurture it.
I'm trying.
I am, I am.
I mean, that, that is my, that is my little seed right now.
And it'll be nice if it is successful.
I really like that as a, as a, as a like comeback is like your life is a wasteland of cubes.
You're just bitter and destroyed and your life is a wasteland of cubes.
Like, well, what of it?
What of it?
What?
Next, next voicemail is, um, uh, fuck.
You should blink.
So, no.
Oh, yeah, skipping.
Next one is called pussiest.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, please, Mr. Saint Man, don't engage in social misconduct on the internet.
You'll hurt someone's feelings.
Ideally, my real, my real sister might cry.
She might cry on stream and then I'll have to pay her money to make her feel better.
But please, I can't afford it.
Please, Ben.
You're putting me under such financial strain.
Uh, I agree with this voicemail.
Uh, next, next one is called, uh, will China invade Taiwan?
Uh, yup.
Yeah.
I don't know when, but as soon as they can.
Is that, oh, is that a real answer?
I think so.
I mean, they won it.
It's just, they're gonna grab it.
They took Hong Kong violently.
Wait, like recently?
Don't you remember the Hong Kong riots?
Well, uh, that wasn't about, that wasn't about China, like, taking it by military force.
No, no, no.
It's not the same.
But like, China has had its eyes on Taiwan and wants to, like, bring it back into the fold
in a very similar way to Russia and Ukraine.
I was gonna say, are they gonna do, that's, I actually had not really heard anything about this, but um.
They've wanted it for a long time.
And I think as, unless, the only thing that would stop them at the moment is Russia completely being destroyed by, uh, the world not being friends with them because of the Ukraine thing.
And China might be like, okay, well, we've got to be careful about taking Taiwan.
Uh, gonna look bad.
Like, if the consequences for Russia are really bad, then China might think twice about it.
Yeah.
Oh, I see, I see.
They still won it, but I don't know.
God, I, yeah, I have no, I have no take on this.
Next one is, what happened to Vic?
Well, I mean, I think he just lives in Virginia.
Yeah, he's doing.
And, uh, I think him and Nate hang out sometimes, maybe?
I wouldn't know.
But he did, he did post the, like, I edited 99% of this on the, on the, uh, on the music video, uh, which is funny, I guess.
I don't know, I was not aware of that.
Um, I don't know, he's just there, man.
He's just hanging out, living, I guess.
Dunno.
That's all I got.
Next one is called, hashtag taking a dump.
I can't wait.
Three seconds, six seconds long, three, two, one, go.
Woo!
Yeah.
Now that's bringing us back to the old voicemail that I remember.
No.
That's classic, classic.
Terrible.
Next one is called, I can do the dogen in finger paint, three, two, one, go.
Okay, Ben, I'm listening to last week's episode and you're always talking about the dogen a lot and, like, how expensive it is.
And I, I, I know you, you want a specific style.
It's not that it's expensive, it's-
But, like, why don't you do it?
Other than, is it just style?
You don't think you can accurately do the style or, like, you don't want to draw yourself getting, like, fucked in the butt by your brother?
I don't, I don't understand.
Or are there?
Buy the book and find out.
Oh my god.
Sorry.
Wait, what was that last, hang on, I missed his last, uh, stop playing Hades, stop grooming children, draw a comic.
Um, one, I don't think my style would, I don't think I could match what's, uh, what Ed did that well.
Two, I kind of just don't want to.
Like, I kind of have other things I need to be doing, like, like, putting the book together and doing my secret project.
I just, I don't really want to spend the time on it, uh, so, like, and also I don't think I'm a great match.
So, for these two reasons, I don't really want to do it myself.
Uh, I can't find-
I've had a couple, I had a couple people ask if they could do it and, like, I don't know, I'm really looking for someone.
They said, like, I'm like, I'm really looking for someone who's, like, normal drawing style is, like, it looks kind of like that.
I found, I found a couple, like, sort of, ish matches on, on Tabless.
Did you, uh, message the one that OblivionFall suggested?
Uh, no.
I, I still have that Tab open.
I think they're, I think they're too, I'll message them just in case, or them, I don't know what they are.
Uh, I'll message them just in case, but I think, I think they're too big. I don't think they're going to want to do it.
Uh...
Yeah.
Uh, next one is called Spaghetti Toast for Breakfast is Weird. Three, two, one, go.
Uh, the, uh, restaurant you were talking about that does fast food spaghetti.
I believe that is Jollibee, but McDonald's does spaghetti in a lot of different areas also.
Yeah.
McDonald's has tried to do a bunch of reviews.
Okay.
And, yeah, it's pretty cool.
There's a Kickstarter that was done last year about Unique McDonald's.
Uh, I kick-started it.
It's cool. I hope it comes out soon.
A Kickstarter for Unique McDonald's?
Yeah, what? Yeah, kick-starting what exactly?
Like people, for McDonald's to make it again? How do you kick-start that?
I did, I did see the Quinton Reviews video about themed McDonald's. Did you see that?
Nope.
Uh, it's sort of a, I think it's called like a eulogy for themed McDonald's because they sort of like stopped existing.
Um, yeah, I don't know what the Kickstarter would be for in that, in this context. It's a little strange.
Um, Spaghetti Toast does sound weird for breakfast. If that's like a specific breakfast menu item, I would think that was pretty funny.
Um, but I guess I'd try it. I'd sure it's fine.
Uh, okay, next one is called I'm in Love with Oblivion Fall, 3, 2, 1, go.
He says in like a nice way, and I hope it doesn't come off as like making fun of Oblivion Fall.
But the way Oblivion Fall says like the T-H sound for the, and it says the, and then like father is the cutest fucking thing in the world.
And I wish nothing but good things for Oblivion Fall because of this, and I love Oblivion Fall because of this.
I just want Oblivion Fall to talk to me so much more often. Can Oblivion Fall be on the podcast?
I don't care what they say, I just want them to talk.
He does kind of say the soft T-H as an F. That's true.
I've never noticed that. Wait.
I have noticed it once or twice. It's fine.
Do a voice. Do an Oblivion Fall voice.
There's not much to it other than...
Oi, oi, Ari. Oi, give me the toast whiff. Give me the toast whiff.
Spaghetti for breakfast, lads.
I live in England where we eat spaghetti at McDonald's.
We call it, we call it, we call it a McRoyal with cheese over here.
Okay, I do think I recognize that F, that Ith sound.
I don't know how to do it, but I think yeah.
Sometimes. It's fine.
You know who else does it and they don't talk like Oblivion Fall at all,
but they also kind of do that is Gamer's Tavern also kind of...
No, no, no.
Gamer's Tavern, he does like a sh instead of a C-H.
Yeah, yeah, you know what? You're right, I'm mixing them up.
Like, oh, you change your clothes, you change your clothes.
Take a chance, take a chance on this lottery, please.
Buy a scratch ticket, these selling scratch tickets on the street corner, by the way.
That's his day job.
Okay, next one is a YouTube link that I won't click, but there is also a voicemail attached.
Yeah, three, two, one, go.
Hey Oblivion Fall, good job on the Patreons.
Yeah, I'm your biggest fan, I listen to you all the time and know all the lyrics without looking of the Gems zooms.
Oh, he's not here.
Got him.
Yeah, absolutely right.
That's a good anticipation.
Okay, I did click the YouTube link because he actually left a voicemail and it is...
It's this.
It's a YouTube short.
You gotta put the HTTP cones.
It's some, like, anime music.
Hey Oblivion Fall, do you like Metal Gear?
I don't know if they do.
Okay.
Oh god, no, shut up. It keeps playing in my headphones for some reason.
Next one is called Now I Get It, three, two, one, go.
And yeah, just now I realized the...
Not putting your context, but the name of the message as a title.
Just now I'm getting it.
And thanks for the clouds.
Deb.
You're welcome.
Alright.
Next one is a YouTube link.
No.
Nope.
Skippin'.
Next one is called Bendo Santos on Mustseppuku over this.
Well, we'll see about that.
Three, two, one, go.
Okay, so despite you all putting Samurai Sama in the top 10 voicemail characters,
he's not in the voice grail.
He's not in the voice grail documents.
Oh.
What is wrong with the world?
That's pretty stupid.
Put him on there. Come on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
There were some people in the comments,
some people pointed out some really obvious people that I had forgotten to include.
Yeah, both of us.
There was an Arara aka...
Arara.
Yep.
Arara aka Prepare for the Bear.
Prepare for the Bear and that whole saga that...
I don't even know what to call it.
What happened?
The sea creatures saga, I guess?
I don't know.
It feels in the same vein as the robo twilight arc.
Oh, Kyle and Funny Man.
Kyle and Funny Man.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Oh, I think Kyle and Funny Man deserves the shout out.
Oh, I see ABZQ comments,
your RSS feed stopped updating.
I have not figured it out.
I just am...
I don't want to learn a new skill.
I don't want to learn a new skill to do that.
Oh, Doid Gazers.
Doid Gazers also...
I don't know if...
Doid Gazers is up there.
Yeah, I don't know if he's top 10.
I don't know if I would.
I mean, it's...
I feel like it's drama, like, tainted to me.
I'm sort of predisposed against it,
but I don't know, that's just me.
Pshaw.
Next one is called Hey Ben.
You know what, we should put this in.
What I mean by that is I just prefer the creative stuff.
I get it.
I don't agree, but I understand what you're saying.
I understand why you feel that way.
I liked the song they made.
They made a whole album.
Dog.
That's pretty good.
That was pretty good.
In my opinion.
Yeah, I get it.
Next one is called Hey Ben.
Three, two, one, go.
Thanks.
There's nothing there.
Next one is YouTube Skip.
Next we have Slime Times Weekend Update,
and there's two parts, so let's do part one.
Three, two, one, go.
Good day to cool killers and rowdy ruffians.
Welcome back to the Slime Times Weekend Update.
The past weeks have seen a lot of movement,
and your reporter will take you through them now at a speedy pace.
Elections for community mods are happening,
and one of the leading entrants is Rowdy Loom,
who runs on a platform of banning cop killer Ben Sainte
from the server and them resigning herself.
I saw that, I saw that.
Skateboards have been introduced as weapons,
and allow you to do sick kickflips with the skate command.
Killer Game Dev Crank is organizing an RFCK wrestling match
using the character creator in WWE 2K22.
Juvy Dev Zugarush created a bot that would automatically post
tweets from Laka Kam's Slime Twitter
onto the Twitter platform of Earth1218.
I saw the Slime Twitter bot.
He count almost immediately got locked for going after such people
as Elon Musk and notable boy band BTS.
Want to come look at the ashes?
The account is at EW Slime Tweeting.
Yeah, I saw that, I followed it just because of the meme
and the idea that I could see what Discord players were saying
but on my Twitter feed.
I'm using technology things.
They said a lot of weird stuff amongst them.
I didn't really see a lot of their tweets.
In RFCK there is a channel called Slime Twitter
and if you have a gel phone, you can make Slime Tweets
in Slime Twitter and they will show up
and anyone else with a gel phone can see them.
Yeah, they made a bot.
Zug made a bot, I guess, that automatically tweeted
all those tweets onto Twitter.
Really did they get banned because they went after Elon Musk
and BTS? It seems stupid.
Yeah, I don't know.
That doesn't seem...
There must be more to it than that.
Maybe because there's a lot of stuff on there.
Twitter algorithm is like, oh, this is a new account
and it's saying some random shit
and adding people must be a bot, which it literally is.
I mean, there's lots of accounts that are openly bots, though.
Yeah.
I would assume it's just maybe somebody just used words
that Twitter didn't like.
I don't know what words.
I didn't see anything particularly bad,
but I wasn't looking at everything.
Yeah, I didn't... I don't know.
I would be sad to see it banned. It sucks.
I kind of thought it was pretty funny, actually.
Yeah.
Next time, or next one is part two.
So, three, two, one, go.
Finally, the annual rowdy brick night has occurred once again.
And once again, rowdy is through hundreds of bricks into killer apartments,
likely racking up thousands of V-Box and property damage
and temporarily making the bot pass out.
The V-Box.
Present for this occurrence was also a mysterious
but immediately well-liked little lady by the name of Ali Upp,
whom some may know from critically acclaimed webcomic Bill Jay
by girl boss artist Gibbentake.
We don't know how she got here, but we cherish her already.
Rowdy Demedunk even gave her a special brick as a keepsake.
All in all, creativity seems to this reporter
at an all-time high in the endless war community as of late.
I mean, what's next?
An official RFCK V-Tuber?
How would you? How?
No!
Anyways, that's it for now.
And remember, the slime time is the best time.
That's so nice. That's so cool.
Yeah.
I've, like, pretended to be some of my own characters sometimes.
I mean, in RFCK, I was the Lord of Ghosts,
and then I was Red Man, and then I had my Gunna girl account.
Oh.
The fact that somebody is going around being Ali Upp is amazing,
and I love that.
I was, uh, you know, that reminds me,
I was writing the footnotes for the book,
and I wanted to ask,
uh, Red Man and Gunna girl were not originally RFCK characters.
They weren't created, like, for RFCK, were they?
Um...
I'm trying to remember, I think, no.
I think I just drew some...
I was just drawing some bullshit.
I came up with this guy called Red Man.
Yeah.
And then...
I remember you just coming up with him, and he's just a guy.
He's based on, like, a little image of a red face that looks like...
Yeah! Oh, that's right. That's right.
That I had as my avatar for a bit.
And Gunna girl was just like,
what if there was a fight?
Who would Red Man fight?
I know.
Gunna girl.
She's a girl with a gun.
Oh, I didn't know that that was the idea.
Yeah, I think I had one of the first...
One of the first images.
Red Man's, like, natural enemy.
Like, the survivor to his Zangus.
Let me find it as an image.
God, was it 2018?
How long ago was this?
Uh...
Actually, you know what?
I don't know what came first.
Here's the first image of Gun Girl.
It's, like, Bail Jape with Gun.
That was the tagline of this little poster.
Yeah.
Because I used punk's hairstyle again.
Yeah. Yeah.
And then...
Where's the one where it's Red Man?
Gun girl vs. Red Man.
I should check by date created.
Is this on Twitter you're looking at?
No, I'm looking at my files.
Oh.
Uh...
Date created.
Yeah, I got to...
I was making footnotes on, you know, the scene with Red Man playing guitar on the Longfellow Bridge.
And I was making footnotes trying to explain, like, who Red Man and Gun Girl are.
And I was like, where did they actually come from, exactly?
Okay, so it was all on the same day, the 28th of November, 2018.
And it was, like, late night.
So, 40 minutes past midnight, I came up with this Gun Girl.
Then, the next one was this.
Red Man vs. Gun Girl.
Wait...
Wait, is that the first Red Man?
I don't think that's the first Red Man.
Because I remember he was based on that red...
Didn't we... hold on.
I think you did have, like, the red face as, like, your avatar, like, your Discord avatar.
Like, in RFCK, maybe.
And I feel like Red Man came from you using that red face?
Or I could be wrong about that.
It came from that red face, that is true.
I just don't know when...
Yeah.
When that all happened.
Damn.
Oh, no, this must have been what it is.
I can't find the first Red Man image I'm looking.
But it must have been a while before.
But I guess I had Red Man.
This Red Man looks great in this poster.
I love it.
Yeah.
I had the Red Man, and then I just...
Some day came up with Gun Girl and thought,
I wonder what she's... her deal is.
And then I decided she fights Red Man.
Yeah.
And then later, they became the Rowdy and Killer.
Two.
Okay, so their origins are a little bit...
A little bit unclear, but I think I get the...
Honestly, it's really tempting as I go through page after page.
It's tempting to write a full fucking page of shit
about every single one of these pages.
Sometimes I have to restrain myself.
Like...
Damn.
There was one...
Uh...
Yeah, there's one.
When Phantom Horn is complaining about capitalism,
I sort of had to keep myself from going on a whole, like, speculative, like...
Phantom Horn's like family life growing up.
What is his exposure to capitalism like?
What is the economy in Equestria based on...
Do they socialize medicine in Equestria?
Uh, stuff.
Um...
There was another one.
There was another one that I was...
Oh, yeah.
There's a part where there's a plaque on the mine entrance
that commemorates Slime Investigator,
which was a character from Canny's ARG.
And, like, I didn't think...
I didn't think it was necessary to, like,
actually explain all, like, what happened with that ARG,
but, like, there was a lot to it.
I don't even remember all the details.
If there's a lot, you could say, but I had to be, like...
I'm not gonna go into all the details right now.
I could, but I don't want to spend, like, a whole page explaining that.
Uh, just know that that's what this is a reference to.
Uh...
Part of me just thinks it would be cool to just have, like,
20, 30, 40 pages of notes.
And another part of me is, like...
That's gonna drive the cost of the book up, actually.
That's gonna make the...
It really will.
Um...
Maybe if you just have really small text.
I could just make it really small.
Honestly, yeah. You know what?
Yeah, I shouldn't, well...
I shouldn't worry about it being too long,
because I can just make the text really small if I want to.
This is the only reason I should not make it too long,
is if it's, like, tedious or off-topic or not interesting.
Um, but, like, anything that's...
I don't see why not include more.
Because it's all indexed by page.
You don't have to read all of it if you don't want to.
Uh, although...
If you...
I think if you don't know anything,
if you're reading the book and you don't understand what's going on at all,
you probably should just read all the footnotes in order,
because they do kind of explain as you go, like,
what is Endless War?
Okay, who is Phantom Horn?
Like, what is Nightstar, etc., etc.?
Uh, yeah.
Probably would be beneficial for some people to read all the footnotes, actually.
Okay, that's a little, uh...
There's a little tangent, a little tangent there.
I just went on.
Anyway, that was a little... Huh?
I'm looking through my things still.
I want to find the first red man.
Oh, right, right, right.
Actually, hmm, we just got...
We just got a last-minute voicemail here.
Do you want to find the first red man before we...
Oh, yeah, I found an image,
but it turns out the first drawn...
This is the day after all those gun girl ones,
where red man took a selfie.
I guess I had the avatar for a while,
and I didn't think to make him a character until I invented gun girl.
Huh.
So that's...
Maybe I had been role-playing as like,
oh, I'm red man, I'm red.
Why is the red man red?
I eat blood, like I made it all up on the spot.
Yeah.
Was that in RFCK, though?
That would have been in RFCK, I think.
Yeah.
Oh, you know what it was?
Lord of Ghosts was excised from the city.
I had to change my character.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's right, that's right, that's right.
So I couldn't be the Lord of Ghosts anymore.
I was no longer role-playing as that.
To red man.
I became red man.
I don't really remember exactly what happened after that,
but the first drawing was gun girl.
I did not draw a red man before I made gun girl.
That is actually interesting.
I might go back and I might make a little bit of mention of that
in my notes, because I think that's pretty funny.
I think the only...
I think the only explicit, like,
Lord of Ghosts reference in Slime and Punishment
is the way that Anti-Slime looks.
So I guess I'll probably mention him
around that time when they're in the sewers.
He needs to get discussed at least a little bit.
Yeah.
Okay, well, very interesting.
Lamal, this fucking selfie picture.
This is like lopsided arms.
Okay, we got one last-minute voicemail.
It's a vocaboo link if you're ready.
Uh...
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Yo, it's your boy, Fackop69 here.
So my friend recommended this podcast, the PCP podcast.
Yo, listen into that shit.
This is pretty fucking entertaining, bro.
Yo, this is a funny shit.
Anyway, I appreciate you listening to my voicemail.
Yo, I'm Fackop69.
Thank you. I love you guys so much.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
Yo.
No.
Do not trust him.
Do not let him in.
He will read you.
Do not read him.
His voice is ash.
His air is dead.
You must not breathe it in.
You must not comprehend the vapor.
His credit vapor.
True!
That was great.
That reminded me...
Well, the dreaded vapor reminds me of a dwarf fortress mega beast that might have deadly vapor.
But that reminded me of...
You've played Space Funeral, right?
No, actually.
I heard about it.
I think a video or two about it.
Well, the part in the blood caverns.
When you fight the blood ghoul, in the blood caverns, everything is red.
It's probably where Redman comes from, to be honest.
An ancestral home.
Everything in the blood caverns is red, and there's this spoken word poem that is the background music.
It sounds somewhat like that.
It's a poem about a bat, like, bruising itself to death, trying to fly or something.
When the low, heavy sky weighs a lid on the spirit, etc.
Thanks for the voicemail.
No, you can trust me.
No, you can read me.
No, just read me, bro.
No, my vapor's okay.
It's fine.
Are they talking about you?
I thought they were talking about some unseen, creepy, danger lurking in the future.
Well, we have that other one that Mario said don't...
Oh, are they not talking about me?
Are they prophesying some other...?
That's what I interpreted.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, maybe.
I mean, you said I have vapor.
Is that, like, a reference to my comic that I made of that name?
Do not read Ben St.
Do not read the vapor's.
I think...
Now I'm not sure.
That's what I thought they were talking about.
Well, I guess we'll never know.
I guess when something bad happens, we'll see who we blame it on.
Alright, I guess that's the end.
That's the last voicemail.
Uh, finally.
Since it's the end of the episode, I will take this moment to grovel before our audience
and ask, please, please, we didn't charge you for March, please give us some money
so I won't feel so sad about that.
It cost me, like, a thousand dollars.
Ah!
Help.
I know I said I had money earlier in the podcast.
But poor Gib, though.
But poor Gib is the one who's really suffering.
Don't do it for me.
I'm evil.
I bully young baby girls on Twitter.
But Gib deserves better than to be destituted.
It's so true.
So true of you to say that.
It is so true.
Patreon.com slash TheProgressNatives.
Yes, please.
Thank you.
Four. I think it's five. Four?
I forget, but I think it was four.
I think it's four new bonus episodes.
Four new behind-the-scenes bonus episodes.
Some of them are pretty funny. I listen to them.
And there's some funny stuff in there.
It's worth your time.
It's worth your five dollars.
It's worth your time. It's worth your money.
And all that other, obviously, all the previous...
We're very, very funny.
Yeah, that's good.
And obviously, all the previous bonus episodes
and the Red Con commentary and documentary
and all of that stuff.
Also the Minecraft server.
Oh, yes.
If you'd like to hop on the Minecraft server
and make some fun stuff.
Of course.
Or catch Pokemon, or both.
And we will...
I think we said we would do one last week.
We'll do another stream soon.
It's been a little while.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe we can show off some builds
that maybe some new members have done.
Who knows?
Maren did say that after we talked about
the Minecraft server, I think an episode or two ago
that some people reached out
who wanted to get involved in that,
which is pretty fun.
So, alright, that's going to do it for this week's PCP.
Thanks, Patreon.
Have mercy.
Okay.
Yes.
Thanks. Goodbye.
In goodbye.
Sorry.
I apologize for this ending.
Bye.
I don't.
Okay.