Hello everyone and welcome to this episode of PCP. I am Mage and I am introducing everyone
this time for some reason and I am joined by Digi.
Real fag hours every Sunday.
Let's welcome Nate!
Um, guess all majorities. Thank you.
Hey Tom, are you alive? Are you with us?
I am alive. I've been revived from the dead.
Huzzah! And finally, for once, he was not late. Ben Saint!
I, you know, be being late is a meme that needs to die.
That's also true though. That was the old me. He's dead now.
Well, prove us wrong, Ben.
I did. I have been doing so.
Well, one time, yeah, exactly. It could be an outline.
Ben was the most on time for our meetup for the Princess Mononoke film.
That's because of the buses. We already established this.
Serious question, guys. When was the last time I was late for anything?
Tell me. Tell me. Fucking face me.
For your period, you pregnant poor.
Change me up in my face and not online and see what happens, fucker.
What'd you say?
The problem is, Ben, is that your macro ratio of late to not late
is still skewed heavily in one direction.
I know. I fucked up a lot. I fucked up a lot.
But I've...
So what was it, Ben? What would change that made this huge revelation in your life
that you'll never relate to anything again? What was it?
I didn't say I'd never relate to anything again.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I just... I've been pretty good. And I think I deserve money.
I tell you what, Ben, we'll start believing you if you start showing up comically early
all the time. Then that will cancel out the lame.
That's lame.
Almost as lame as being late all the time.
You've cost everyone else by being late. You need to spend that time
by sitting in an isolation cube and doing nothing.
I need to pay back the debt.
Exactly. You've got a big time debt. It has to be paid back. That's what it is.
I see.
Isn't that the plot of that movie?
I wasn't going to say that, too.
Is that true?
Yeah, that's literally the Justin Timberlake movie in time.
In time. That's the one.
Where the entire...
We hit all of the dialogue as time puns.
That sounds awesome.
Well, maybe.
Well, here we are on another episode of PGP, the Pokemon Go podcast.
Thanks for joining us, everybody.
I'm almost level 25. I'm doing real good.
Oh, I'm so close to 30.
I'm so close to 30.
I'm subscribed.
Oh, man. I caught my first Shuckle just today.
I got one of those.
That's a good boy.
I also got a Maulwile in a raid.
It is a piece of absolute trash and completely worthless,
but I'm glad to have it because I love Maulwile.
Yeah, Maulwile rules.
Well, you're over there gathering Shuckles.
I'll be over here gathering Shuckles.
Yeah.
Oh, is that Mad Dosh?
Is that in any way like the pun of Shuckle's name?
Like, other than that, what does it mean?
If it's like...
They're always Shuck.
Shuck, you know, seafood, right?
Like when you Shuck clams or whatever.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, right.
Or like you Shuck corn.
Oh, yeah, yeah, you Shuck clams, too.
What is Shucking?
Yeah.
So you Shuck out the innards, I think, basically?
Oh, no, no.
It's just when you remove the shell.
It's just when you remove the shell from something.
Oh, okay.
So I guess like if you put your mouth, like one of Shuckle's many holes,
and you just suck and you get the poop out of there.
That's like Shuck and Shuckle.
All right.
This is the worst episode ever.
I Shucked some eggs last night.
Okay.
Yeah.
So, all right.
So pretty much my entire identity...
This is what's changed.
This is why I'm never going to be late anymore.
My entire identity has been erased and has been replaced with Keto.
I am all and only a Keto guy now.
That's all there is to me.
So if you liked anything else about me, I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but that's all that's over now.
That is very exciting.
I do want to know more about that.
It's pretty interesting.
But let me tell you, I'm a little embarrassed to tell this story
just because of the names involved.
I made a recipe for some bread substitute.
It is called Oopsy Bread, which is terrible.
I don't like to say it.
It is also called Cloud Bread,
which I find much more aesthetic.
Oopsy Bread sounds like something that would be made out of children's...
Aborted fetuses?
That's where I'm going with that.
Well, okay.
I was thinking more like when kids like shit their pants
and you have those Oopsy underwear
that it's like when you're in transition from diapers up to regular underwear.
I'm trans.
I'm transitioning from diapers to big boy underwear.
That's me.
Pull-ups or pull-ups?
Yeah, pull-ups.
Well, no.
Okay, so Oopsy Bread, AKA Cloud Bread.
I'm going to call it Cloud Bread from now on.
That's way cooler.
Yeah, Cloud Bread is made of, I mean, it's basically eggs and some cream cheese.
Like, it's basically eggs and cream cheese and you whip it up and you bake it.
I assumed it was some kind of like crowdsourced peer-to-peer bread network.
Yeah, we get this from the crowd.
It's peer-to-peer bread.
This is what I'll call it from now on.
The point is though that it sucked ass and it did not just like bread.
It literally just tasted like eggs and cream cheese.
So, I don't know...
Well, that's a pretty good taste.
Like, I didn't like it.
No.
Everyone, everyone hyped it up.
Like, all the keto, it's like a really popular keto thing.
And I was like, wow, there really must be something to this because everyone is into this, this shit.
And turns out it's kind of gross.
So, that was disappointing.
Nate, what about eggs and cream cheese in combination sounds good to you?
My dad always used to make eggs, like scrambled eggs with cream cheese.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Listen, listen, listen.
It's fine.
Like, it's not that the taste was not vile or anything, but like,
baked into like this like fluffy, bubbly, like, like, like a cookie.
I don't know.
It was, it wasn't, I didn't like it one bit.
I didn't like it one bit.
So, I was supposed to use it like bread?
I was like, yeah, I was looking.
I was like, oh, I'm going to make this bread.
I'm going to like put butter on it.
I like put some bread and butter and you know, but, but it's just like,
the thought of putting butter on this like cream cheese is like gross.
No, thanks.
Isn't that kind of the whole conceit of keto though?
Sounds kind of gross because it's just like so much fat and protein
and like no carbs.
I mean, it sounds gross.
Let me tell you about gross.
I have been, I have been drinking, I have been drinking straight heavy cream.
For like a past week.
Christ.
No, that's good.
It's good.
I put, I know it's a keto thing.
I put stevia in it and I put cocoa powder in it and I shake it all up.
You know, your goal is not to just like consume as much fat as possible.
Yes, it fucking is, yes it fucking is.
I am not meming on you right now.
Well, Ben, so you still, you still have a calorie count for the day, right?
That you want to achieve.
That's like the goal.
I mean, I mean, technically, yeah.
Okay.
Calorie counts are more of a suggestion.
I mean, the most important thing is to become fat, is to become fat adapted
and enter keto and enter ketosis, which by the way, I am in deep, deep ketosis.
I have been peeing on, I have been peeing on strips and they have been turning
deep, deep purple.
Like you shouldn't need the strips because your piss should smell like a dinosaur
if you're doing it right.
Well, I like the strips because it's very satisfying that they turn purple.
Listen, I am a, I am a fat burning furnace.
I am so deep in ketones.
I am, I am so many ketones that my pee melts bread like acid.
It just, it just tears.
Fantastic.
Yeah.
I am, I'm no longer human.
Guys, I gotta tell you.
I have become keto.
That I also found the answer when it comes to food.
I don't remember if I told the story on a previous PCP because now that they're all
formless, I have no idea what we talked about.
Yeah.
So when, when Ben and DeVu first moved in with me, we, Nate had heavily advised us to use
crock pots.
He was like, crock pots are the answer because you can just put a bunch of shit in it.
Like you just put a bunch of healthy shit, like chicken and vegetables and just leave it on.
And then you come and you eat it and it's just there.
It's around all day.
The problem with the crock pot though is that, A, it takes like eight hours between you making
it and it actually being ready and you probably won't make it until you're hungry because that
inspires you to think about it.
So what would happen is we would make a crock pot.
We'd eat that first, that first glorious go, but then you can't just like let it sit out.
Like you can't turn it off because it'll get gross.
But if you leave it on, it will also get gross because it'll overcook and turn into like this,
this weird mush and no one ever wanted to clean the thing after it was done.
So it would just always be a disgusting mess on the counter.
And eventually we gave up on crock pot because we then discovered deep frying.
And then that was the answer.
So all we did was deep fry chicken all the time, chicken and pork.
We just constantly like, it was all panko, all just, you know, egg, egg or flour, egg,
panko, deep fry.
And that was like every day.
But the problem with deep frying is you can't really make that much stuff in it.
And it all tastes exactly the same because it's just deep fried.
So now I found the real answer and that is steaming.
And I found this answer because of the fact that there's an amazing Asian grocery store near me
that has like basically all Asian food is either noodles or some form of steamed buns.
Like, yeah.
And so I just started getting like all these different varieties of frozen steamed buns.
And all you got to do is just boil water, put them in a steamer and then put a lid on it for like
seven or eight minutes.
And you've got these unbelievably delicious steamed buns of different denominations,
whether it be like wontons or fucking,
You guys are making me hungry.
Like pot stickers, just anything, basically anything could be steamed.
But you know, it's just like a piece of flour filled with some kind of ingredient.
So you just get a whole variety of different fillings.
And now you've got breakfast every day.
And it has been amazing and healthy.
And yeah, it's made my life better.
I have not solved the food question in my life.
Just, it's absolutely a cluster fight.
I've temporarily solved my food question.
Yeah.
Eggs.
I don't like eggs.
So I can't, I love eggs.
I fry eggs, but I also put like, what's the word?
Okay, it's not garlic.
It's onion.
There we go.
Onion and eggs.
Egg, onion, omelette.
Omelettes are great.
I make omelettes all the time.
And they're delicious.
Onions, fried onions turn sweet.
And I love it.
They do.
They're great.
Tom's been living with me for a week and a half.
And I have not seen him made one omelette.
And he's claiming that he makes them all the time.
I'm calling foul.
I did, but I have this weird aversion to using your shit.
I want to be as like non-existent in your house as possible.
Well, you're free to use the, I mean, if you use the pan and then you clean the pan,
I will have no idea that you used the pan.
Yeah.
Well, what I've been eating right now is because, again, I was planning on not being in a house.
So I have like, I have a big thing.
Ass loads of fuel.
Yeah.
Protein bars and fuel.
And it's working out pretty good.
I don't even mind it.
It's a good, it's a good solution.
Wait, did you say fuel?
Fuel.
What is that?
It's like soilent, but not soy based.
Oh, oh yeah, you told me that.
It's like a meal supplement.
You just like, it's like, you put some powder, you mix it with water,
and it's got all the calories you need.
And it's nice and nutritionally balanced.
I sincerely want to be post food and consume things like fuel and all that.
The fuel, honestly watching Tom drink it, I'm like, you know what?
If I was a faggot, I would love this.
It's so efficient.
And that's the number one thing I care about.
Maybe I'll get into it because I'm wasting time.
I'm starting to be broke.
And so, yeah.
Oh, okay.
Let me tell you, you're gay enough for fuel.
You just don't realize it yet.
Oh, well, I just like to taste things.
Yeah, that's my curse as well.
It's the like the tasting things is, well, that's secondary.
Number one is how lazy I am.
Like I've got eggs in my room right now, but instead yesterday,
I like, I ordered some eggs just like from a place and like they were relatively healthy.
You need to be post food.
This is literally takes like maybe 15 seconds.
That's the way fuel is literally just a powder.
I'm ordering it today, Tom.
I make a solemn fucking vow to you.
I'm buying it today.
I've been talking for a while.
And I think that no one has been able to hear me.
And I'm pretty sure.
No, no, it's fine.
It's fine.
I saved my old audio.
Yeah, I moved my microphone and the cord fell out.
So my old, my first part of my audio is saved.
I have started a new recording.
We'll sync at the end.
I just wanted to let everyone know that I had really great contributions
of this conversation that you will never get to hear.
And I feel sorry for you, viewer.
No, I haven't, I haven't heard you since I talked about deep friend.
So, well, you'll never know.
I'll take the secrets of my brain.
Well, is deep frying still kosher with the keto lifestyle then?
I guess so.
But like the breading, I mean, why would you deep,
I mean, you deep fry for breading, right?
Like there's no point deep frying like just meat or whatever.
So not really.
Although I do make eggs all the time.
I fry them in butter and it's fucking sick.
When my friend Don San did keto,
it was pretty much exclusively either just him like grilling chicken
and just eating that with like, with lettuce or going to like fast food places
and just getting burgers with lettuce wraps.
Oh man.
That was basically his entire time.
When I was in town, when I was in Boston hocking my comics to store owners,
I went to Tasty Burger, which was not the same one that we ate at
when we went and saw Princess Mononoke, but you know, same chain.
I got a Gorgonzola burger on a lettuce wrap.
And boy, it was almost worth it.
It was almost worth it.
It almost cost me.
I'm really shocked, Nate, that you hang out in Fit Boy communities
and haven't heard about this.
But if you go to basically any like, any place that sells burgers
and you ask them to replace the bun with lettuce, they will do that.
Some places even just call it, some place, like if you go to Hardee's
and you just say like, give me a no carb version of the burger,
they'll just like wrap it in lettuce and that's what they give you.
Damn, I should do that every fucking time.
I've been throwing away my goddamn games for nothing.
I found out about it at In-N-Out.
In-N-Out was the first place I went.
So do they replace the wrap with the lettuce or the burger with the lettuce?
They replace the bun.
The bun.
It's no bun.
Imagine if they replaced the meat with lettuce.
Oh.
Disgusting.
That'd be ideal.
It'd be ideal.
And now I want that wrap.
It sounds pretty good.
I like wraps.
Yeah, I'm gonna try one of these.
And whenever I go to McDonald's, I just get a wrap.
Because they're gonna need like the big leafy shit to actually contain burger.
So a thing that I did not know about Keto is
you are supposed to eat protein, you know, like based on your weight or your lean mass,
you're supposed to eat enough protein to maintain your muscle mass.
However, you should not go over that amount because eating protein in excess of that will
become glucose and, you know, basically eating too much protein is basically like eating carbs,
more or less.
So is Keto any kind?
It doesn't sound like much of a muscle gain diet.
I mean, I'm sure you could gain muscle on it.
Yeah, okay.
All right.
Yeah.
I mean, it's mostly meant to make you lose weight like very rapidly.
Like if you're doing it properly, you should burn weight super fucking fast.
The purpose of ketosis is that it is burning fat instead of other things.
So, yeah.
I mean, you probably could gain muscle on it, but I don't think it's like it's not
designed with that in mind.
And that's...
I was doing for a while to lose weight intermittent fasting.
Intermittent fasting is a...
They say like combining that with keto is pretty effective.
And I realized that I just kind of intermittent fasted like without even meaning to for like
much of my life because I just...
Yeah.
Well, that's because you...
What's intermittent fasting?
It's when you just eat like one meal a day, basically, or stuff.
Oh, yeah.
My mom recently mentioned that.
Eat for a day or two.
Yeah.
Well, that's specifically called OMAT or one meal a day.
That's like the hardcore version.
Eating one meal a day is something that I just do naturally some of the time because
I just don't feel hungry when I wake up most almost any morning.
And then like often I just won't think to eat until like late.
I'm a terrible stress eater.
Like when I get stressed, all I can think about is having something in my...
Yeah, that happens to me as well.
Guys, if I'm in a good mood, I can do it.
You know what this episode is making me realize is that we are aging fast.
Yeah, dog.
That's true.
It took you just not to realize.
Well, I'm just thinking about how, you know, the other half of the PCPs, I don't...
Mage, how old are you again?
26.
Okay, so you're my age.
So you got that like creepy question on your cat.
You're asked, what's it called?
Yeah, curious cat.
Like they could have just asked you your age, but they didn't ask you your age.
They asked you, are you a minor or 18 plus?
And I was like, what a creepy way to ask how old someone is.
Well, I want to know the follow-up question before I answer this one, sir.
Yes.
But the rest of the PCP is younger than us.
And so when you've got someone like Munchie on here,
he might be talking about rambunctious fun things.
But when it's all the old fucks, we're just like, I'm dying.
You know what, I'm not eating carbs anymore.
We did talk about Pokemon Go to this day.
You know what, I don't think, but you know who plays Pokemon Go?
My mom plays Pokemon Go.
Well, so does Munchie.
You know, I disagree because Munchie talks about how, you know,
he lives, his body is always aching and he's always in pain,
and about how he and his girlfriend have stopped drinking sugary sodas.
So they're just as old and worthless as us.
But Munchie got a girlfriend.
Oh, this is nice.
We're all decaying machinery.
Munchie has definitely got this old snake condition.
He's just like aging that.
He's probably like physically older than all of us.
So we just don't know.
I mean, he was bigger than me when he was like a quarter of my age.
So, you know, wait, the math doesn't quite check out there.
But you know what I mean.
Munchie being a clone of Big Boss makes a lot of things make a lot more sense to me.
True clone.
He was the one.
He's a clone of a fictional character.
Ridiculous.
Something went wrong in the process.
Hey, I've got a topic to bring up just overall.
I thought about what to call it.
And I have a title for this topic.
And it is simply the Cal Arts Question.
What's to be done about this Cal Arts situation?
And how are we going to stop the influx into our society?
Why don't you lay out exactly what you think the Cal Arts
problem is?
Sure.
Well, it's more of a question because I don't really know if I believe it is
as pervasive a problem as some people think it is.
Is it is it an accurate statement to say that like the the animation industry of
I guess the West, but like America, Canada, etc.
is like coming to be dominated just by specifically the Cal Arts art style.
And is this like squeezing out other options or possibly entirely just through its own
like merit or maybe it's like really easy to draw.
So people really like it.
Obviously, that's the case with like Steven Universe because they fuck up the perspective
all the time and sizes.
I don't have a clear answer for that, but I will speak on behalf of anime real quick.
And just that for the most part, like the vast majority of anime studios are all crammed in
the same part of Tokyo.
And it's just like the area that's like the cheapest to to live in and to have you know
shit set up.
Sure.
But as a result, the anime industry is ludicrously incestuous.
And this is why so much of it is just the same shit over and over again is it's the same
people making it the same people who are teaching the new people how to make it.
And so like I would say that if Cal Arts is just a place where not only are the most popular
shows coming from there, but the people who are learning how to make cartoons
are being taught by those people, you know.
So like that's basically the problem.
Yeah.
And it creates this.
But like it's funny because people will blame like Cal Arts or something.
But it's like if you want to solve this problem, the only way to do it is to build another school
and just teach them something different.
The thing is, though, people have the wrong assumption that like Steven Universe and Gumball
are Cal Arts, but that's not true.
Rebecca Sugar never studied in the Cal Arts.
And if you look at the pilot, her actual art style shows there and it's very different
from what it has become.
And Gumball was made, I think, in the UK.
So it's not even in America.
Gumball doesn't even look like the other shows that I've seen.
First of all, I don't actually know what Cal Arts is.
I just know that there's a bunch of shows that kind of look like Steven Universe coming out.
And to me, it's obvious that it's just because Steven Universe is popular.
No, that's like true because there are things that were out before Steven Universe that...
Adventure Time and what not.
What's that one about the woods?
But Adventure Time doesn't look like the first of evil.
What's the one about the kids of the fucking woods?
Gravity Falls.
Was that before Steven?
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes.
Gravity Falls was Star vs. Was Not.
And then Sans, although not real Sans, just the way that fans draw Sans.
And of course, the new ThunderCats thing as well, you know, very much that.
But to me, it's painfully obvious that it's not about whether or not it's Cal Arts.
It's just shows that are copying the thing that's popular, which all shows have always done.
They're copying the style that's popular.
I mean, it's also just efficient.
I'm sure it's a very efficient way to produce a show.
Right, yeah.
So it's not all that.
It isn't all the anime looks the same.
Well, let's just take it...
I mean, I don't know that that's true, mage.
Well, I'll just believe you that Steven Universe had nothing to do with Cal Arts.
But nonetheless, it is this art style that is called like the Cal Arts style.
And maybe that's completely wrong.
I mean, for a while, there was the Tumblr style, which was like people with fucking
animal crossing, animal crossing goses.
But that was not like, that was not like a mainstream like, that was not like on TV.
I mean, when Steven Universe came out, that was literally why all of us didn't want to
watch it was because we kept saying, oh, it's just Tumblr art.
Like it looks like Tumblr made a show.
And so like to to ascribe this aesthetic to Cal Arts, when it just looks like
what Tumblr was already doing.
And I mean, this is way more pervasive in the world of comics.
Like even before Steven Universe, if you go to a comic store and you just flip through like any
new series, they all fucking look like Tumblr art.
And it's just because, you know, people get in.
Because they're all people from Tumblr drawing, man.
Probably, yeah.
And they all they're all just influenced by each other because it's a very insular culture.
So like, you know, those people just come up copying the designs of other people.
And then they blow up really fast because even though there's nothing unique about their art
style, because it is, you know, piggybacking on something that's already big, they can
blow up really fast.
So we got like all these probably 18 to 20 somethings, like just copying the
style of Steven Universe and writing that wave.
And then as soon as that's not what's in anymore, the ones who have adapted and got their own style
and like are doing something meaningful might have a continued career.
The ones who are just going to look old hat in a couple years are going to fall off the wave,
you know?
What I think is with this is that I feel very similar about these shows that I do with like
3D animation and theaters and stuff.
They all look like Pixar.
And I just I'm just on both fronts.
I'm tired of the sameness.
I just like, we have this, these mediums can do anything.
The aesthetic can be anything.
And we're just, we've like pigeonholed both of these mediums now.
It's a very samey looking shit.
And it's very frustrating.
And I want, I want to do more stuff, especially with Pixar.
Because Pixar has been going on for what?
Like going on 30 years now that it's just been the same shit.
Like please do something new.
And I guess it's just the power of the zeitgeist.
It just has people all wrapped up and they're not, they're just seeing what's working.
That was what made the Lego movie so fucking exciting was that it looked nothing like that.
And it was like, whoa, you can do that?
But how much of this is just the natural?
I mean, like, there's always trends, right?
Like for a while, like, like Disney animation and who's that Don Bluth,
like they, they were the thing for a while.
And now it's, and now it's this, you know, thing trends.
You guys know that the person who made Iron Giant is studied CalArts.
Was that true?
Wait, was that not Don Bluth?
How do you know?
Because I researched it because it was a hot topic.
I said, how do you know?
I meant to say, what do you know?
As in like, oh, well, what do you know?
So ignore that.
That's pretty cool.
I guess, I mean, that was made in what like the early 2000s or like the 90s or something.
I mean, CalArts has been around forever.
So like, they're like the premier animation school.
I mean, I think a lot of people, I think a lot of people who like look at art in general
and like see the same.
And it's like, Vin, Vin Diesel, Vin Diesel voiced the titular Iron Giant.
That is that makes sense.
Yeah, that's true.
He's also the voice of Groot.
Is that how we got the voice for Groot?
They're just like, you can be this like silent only says a few words character
and like give him a fuck ton of money for like saying three words.
You know what?
I know I've told this story before, but just on now that it's Vin Diesel,
it brings a whole new perspective to me and my buddy, John, watch the Iron Giant in college.
I know the story.
And we both just watch it.
It was a real emotional thing.
And it just ended as I look over at him after the Iron Giant sacrificed himself.
And my friend John just looks within intense gaze and pounds on the desk and says,
I feel so sorry for this giant metal man.
And now I'm just picturing Vin Diesel just bursting into flames.
Mate, I think about, I feel so sorry for this giant metal man every day.
I think about that story every fucking day.
What an iconic line, John.
You really did it.
I think that people underestimate how much influence,
like the environment where people learn how to do something like effects what their product is.
The reason Hollywood movies are all the same is because they're all fucking made in Hollywood.
It's the same influences, the same people asking for the same thing.
I understand why it happens.
I just don't like it.
I want to.
Yeah, no, it's unfortunate.
But the thing is that people complaining about it will never change it.
The only way you can change it is by building something different.
Unfortunately, when you do build something different,
it's going to be really hard to make that new thing the zeitgeist.
You can make something new and it's either going to be treated as,
oh, this is too niche to promote to anybody.
So we're just going to bury it.
Or you can be home stuck and just have some insane luck and make something that's totally
unique and distinctive.
And then it spawns its own.
And then there's literally 500 fucking home stuck ripoff web comics,
because it was an influence for this other generation of kids.
There are like tens of thousands.
Again, that wave is over and the only people who survived it are people like Munchie
and who've evolved their art continually to not just look like home stuck.
Granted, Rowdy fucker's cop killer's art is just home stuck.
Everyone says that.
And it is a complete overstatement.
The Rowdy fucker's art style is as multifaceted as the special snowflakes
in the community that contribute to it.
They're each one is a beautiful star shining in the Rowdy fuckers in the acid green sky.
What the fuck am I talking about?
Fuck you, T.C.
I don't know, but that sounds good.
Look, all I know is I clicked one time on the Boru and every single image was like
some Victorian building like with a Photoshop filter.
Okay, that was a bit pervasive.
You know, we took inspiration.
You go with what works.
Why reinvent the wheel?
I guess what I'm saying is that I'm for the Cal Arts style and I want it to stick around forever
because it works and why should we come up with anything?
I think people are making a mountain out of a molehill.
Yeah, I mean, we're just in it right now and I do think this is a natural cycle that'll
probably phase and, you know, out of nowhere, Steam just opened on my computer.
And I think I had accidentally clicked on it at the start of the episode and 30 minutes later,
it decided to just come alive.
Maybe it was doing updates.
Steam's a tricky beast.
You know, I saw an article like yesterday or something that was like,
it was called something of approximately what the fuck has Steam made in the last 10 years
or has Valve made in the last 10 years or something.
And it was like nothing.
And I mean, these people were like mad that Steam like make so much money or
Valve make so much money despite, you know, like not producing games.
I mean, is it not obvious that when they made Steam,
they realized that this was just a way more important venture than making video games?
Like, can these things make Steam better?
Yeah, because the context of this was that Steam is rolling out like an updated chat client,
but it is worlds worse than like Discord or like TeamSpeak or any of the or even Skype,
all the established ones.
It's like, it's super bare bones.
And like, I think this person was just like, Steam, this is embarrassing.
Like Valve, what are you doing?
You're way behind the curve.
This is this is this speaks to something that really fucking frustrates me just in like,
technology and services and stuff in general.
It's like, I really hate how all these companies are like, this is a really popular thing.
We're going to make our own version of it.
Like, I really want to see less copying and more integration.
Like, wouldn't it be great if Steam just integrated Discord instead of having to build
their own version?
Would make perfect sense.
There is some sharing audience integration there.
Like, well, that's all on Discord side, I think.
Like, it's just set up to like recognize games and stuff.
That might be true.
I mean, I'm not just this isn't just Valve like tons of companies do this.
Like when something's popular, we need to build our own version.
It has origins then.
Right.
With origin and then fucking you play from Ubisoft and it's just like, come on guys, come on.
It's just short-sightedness on like I like with the whole fucking origin thing.
It's like, they just thought, oh, we don't want to have to give up part of the the market share
to this thing.
And surely we can do just as good.
But it's like, if you are not going to make it legitimately a better product, no one is going to
want it.
You know, like you, yeah, that's true.
Like if if you have to pay steam or whatever and you're not making as much money,
like it'll be worth it because there will be more consumers.
That's why it's so weird when they when they make decisions like that to me.
Granted, maybe there's some way that even if they have less consumers,
they're making more money.
If that's true, then, you know, it's possible.
Maybe that's what the theory is.
A lot of those games are that are available in origin are also available on steam.
So what's the point?
They want to get their cut.
I mean, EA puts all their new releases on origin.
Like when I got Mass Effect 3, when it first came out, it was only on origin.
It was really annoying.
Inquisition is only on origin as well.
That's the reason I have it.
All I learned since 4.
Like, I don't mind people making new platforms and stuff like that or like making their own
version if they bring something new to the table.
Like GOG, good old games, they have a service.
But it's totally different than steam.
It's for like spotlighting older games that you can't get anymore,
like porting over DOS games and stuff to run on Windows.
And they don't have any copy protection.
So like, if you get something on GOG, you can use it wherever you want.
And like, their client is completely optional.
You can just go to their website and download the EXE and run that.
Or you can use their client to have it all in one place.
So like, it's like steam, but it serves a totally different purpose.
It just takes a steam model and adapts it to a new product.
That's good.
To be fair, this in no way redeems EA in any sort of matter.
Oh no, EA can get fucked.
No, no, I just want to say, I just want to say they do offer free games from time to time.
And that's how I got like Sims 2.
And they had like Dragon Age, the very first one, Origins for free for a while as well.
So they sometimes have some good games and I have like a library full of games.
I'm never going to play on Origins.
That sounds like it's not even a compliment in that case.
By the way, I'm fucking tripping balls because Tom is literally directly above me.
And I can hear him talking when he talks, but I hear him like one second before I hear him.
I can do the same thing with you.
And I'm just like trying not to think about it too much.
Yeah, just roll with it, guys.
Just roll with it.
Yeah, that's all you can do.
Just endure it.
Anybody else got like, I mean, I prepared like a bunch of topics.
I'm just going to roll out on these episodes.
I mean, I could talk about my adventure into Boston's hocking my shit.
Oh, I wonder all about that.
Yeah.
Well, before we even move on though, because that last conversation tied into this long ass
conversation me and Tom had yesterday, just about like the shifting technologies going on right now.
And like which how basically like it seems as though the big companies who like control
everything on the internet are finally starting to get their reckoning.
Like I don't know if you guys heard about like Facebook tried to make some kind of deal with
like China and it fell through and they lost like ass tons of money.
And then you've got like Google who they lost a hundred billion dollars of their net worth
as I recall.
And 20% lost the nation of China.
Facebook.
No, Facebook did.
Yeah.
Which is about 15% of their net worth.
And then Google has been losing tons of money because like the EU is like really putting
their foot down about like, hey, if you're going to record everything that everybody
says at all times, you should you got to tell them that.
And they're like, oh, fuck.
And that's why all these TOS's are changing and shit.
But like me and Tom are talking about how Google, Tom, please reveal what they did
about a month ago to their slogan.
Yeah.
They removed the don't be evil clause from their wait.
Hold on.
There was a don't be evil clause.
That was what they were known for.
Like Google fanboys used to constantly talk about how like their whole principle was don't
be evil.
That was like literally their motto and they removed it from their thing.
Okay.
That's extremely ominous.
But like I thought it was like de facto removed previously or something.
I mean, I don't know what you mean, but it's really funny for that to disappear from their
mission statement.
Now, like Google says an interview now like, well, you know, maybe you could be a little
evil sometimes.
Maybe we don't always mind.
But but we were talking about how like Google used to be like, like back in the late 2000s,
like everything they were putting out was revolutionary.
It was like Google Chrome came out and docs and drive and all this shit that was like,
Oh my God, this is like changing the way the Internet works last revolutionized time.
They did anything in the city.
Yeah.
When was the last time Google came out with like a new thing that you were like, Oh my
God, this is like going to change the game.
And instead, like their services keep getting worse.
And meanwhile, other people are making competing services that are better.
And now people are telling me like, when Microsoft Edge is like a better browser than
Chrome.
And I'm like, I even Chrome is being taught.
What are you doing, Google?
Get your shit together.
You know, I've been trying to get off Chrome.
I've been trying to get off Chrome for a long time because they don't want to be tracked.
Apparently, Microsoft Edge is better.
Or whatever.
Or you don't want to be tracking these Firefox.
Firefox is pretty good.
I use Firefox.
If you want a browser specifically that doesn't track you, there's a browser called Brave,
which is designed, it's designed by Firefox guys.
They like left the company and started their own thing called Brave.
And it has an ad blocker like built in and it has like all these do not track things.
And it's specifically designed to not pay attention to any of your shit.
I do want that.
I hate being watched.
Get it right now.
You Google.
I mean, if you really want to do that, you should get a VPN.
Like that.
That's true.
I should subscribe to one of those many fine VPN services advertised to me on YouTube.
This episode of the Procrastinator's podcast is brought to you by Private Internet Access,
the greatest VPN ever made according to like the YouTubers I watch.
That's true.
Oh, and I almost forgot.
In fact, I'm glad you brought this up.
Did you?
Because I wanted to announce that so from now on,
PCB episodes will be exclusively available through our proprietary online download service.
The PC portal.
There you go.
Speaking of the PC portal.
Me and Tom have also been talking about how we need to get the PCP on everywhere.
And what I mean by that, because I think that we've listened to our fans to say things like,
oh, put us on iTunes, put us on whatever.
But like these other podcasting services that exist,
like there's people who just listened to podcasts through those.
So like those people are not in our fan base right now because they have no idea who we are
because they don't use the services we currently are on.
So like potentially we could have entirely separate audiences who know about us from
totally different apps.
And I think that's worth exploring.
It's a good idea.
So everybody let us know what podcasting apps we should explore.
Yeah, let us know in the comments.
Seriously.
I mean, I think everyone commenting on YouTube is probably watching us on YouTube.
That's true.
Well, okay.
I mean, that's true.
If you know of any, I guess.
Yeah, I mean, we should definitely be on every platform available to us.
That's yeah.
I mean, there is a diminishing return on investment.
But I mean, it'd certainly be a good thing to just be on everything.
And we could just push a button and do it.
So yeah, let's look into it.
Let's look into it.
Wherever quality podcasts are sold or offered for free or whatever.
Ben, tell me about your comic selling.
I want to hear about it.
Shit.
Wait, I was going to preface it was.
Oh yeah, I was talking about, I talked about it on my Twitch the other day.
Twitch.tv slash St. Comics.
Like, comment, subscribe.
Yeah, high five.
Nice.
High shovel.
So, but yeah, basically, so I had seen on Twitter, someone had tweeted this thing about
how you can sometimes just walk into a store and be like, I have a book.
Will you put it on the shelf?
And sometimes they'll just do it.
So I was like, well, what?
So I was like, what have I got to lose?
So I got, okay.
So I still have maybe like 200 or so copies of the Vapors from the Kickstarter that did
not get sold because I printed a batch of 500 because there was a price break at 500.
So I thought, why not?
Can I have one?
Do you not already?
No, I don't have a Vapors.
Um, give me five bucks and you can have one.
I'll give you five bucks for one.
I'll happily do that.
You didn't fucking kickstart me, you fuck.
Ben, I didn't even know that you, I didn't even know about the Kickstarter till it was like over.
What the fuck?
I knew.
I just didn't believe in you.
It was my problem.
So, you know, that's, that's where I'm coming from.
I mean, do you guys know that it fucking was a massive success that raised like 350% of its original goal?
Yeah, I know that it has cool black envelopes.
Yes.
Well, that's where the fucking pins came from, which I have and I love.
I love my Puba pin.
It's, I have it next to my desk all the time.
Yeah, I've got a bunch of Puba's floating around the house and I don't know like,
I don't even know how I have as many as I seem to have.
Like, I'm pretty sure there should only be one or two, but it seems like everywhere I go, they fucking appear.
Oh, and you know what?
Here's a little thing that can multiply.
Small thing that makes me, that's true.
You know what, I already, I ordered the, the second pin for the second Kickstarter,
which will probably happen in, I mean, later this year, I guess.
I ordered the second kind of pin.
I'm not going to say what it is, but I just got the email notification that has shipped.
And I think it's shipping to our parents house, Nate.
I hope it is a pin of having a panic attack.
That's what I want.
I'll just tell you.
No, it's, it's infinite jests.
The pen is infinite jests.
Oh, okay, cool.
That's great.
It's funny.
It's a joke.
Laugh.
Wait, so Ben, how do you have 200 extra copies?
Like, surely not even 200 people like had bought them originally, right?
Like, how many did you sell?
Yeah, like, it was like 200 something.
Holy fuck, how long did it take to ship all that?
A while.
Oh, man, I took a picture.
Oh, I don't know if I still have it, but I took a picture of the mailing of the receipt that I got
from the post office, uh, for when I went to mail them.
And it is like this long, it is like a huge fucking jumble of paper.
It is like, it is like 12 feet long is the receipt from when I, from when I mailed them all.
It cost me like, it's funny.
It's funny, but it cost me like $700 just to ship everything.
Oh, God.
He is this Christ.
Well, because a lot of it was international.
When I shipped out all the, uh, yeah, when I shipped out all the RADCON stuff,
like they were like, do you want a receipt?
I'm like, it's going to be super long.
No, just email me.
And they did.
But the problem is they emailed me for each individual item.
So my phone just started blowing up because I got 150 emails and quick succession.
Why?
I don't know.
Sending them domestically was about $2 an envelope.
Sending them internet.
Canada was like $4 and everywhere else internationally was like just under $7.
So it was about five extra dollars to ship them internationally.
So on the next Kickstarter, I will probably be like, if you're not in the US or Canada,
you know, $5 postage fee.
I should have done that on the first one, but I didn't think to do it.
Yeah.
There's a thing for that.
Yeah, I had the other way.
God, I really hope, I really hope that that is, that that shipment is headed to our parents'
house and not anywhere else.
But anyway.
The same.
You know, they did just move.
Was it moved to the new place or home place?
Oh, fuck.
Ben, you fool.
Well, I said I waited months ago.
Well, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
I will.
As soon as this show is over, I'm going to go check in on that.
Ah, motherfucker.
Well, good.
And I'll go get that sweet soylent or whatever.
But the point is, the point is, I googled comic store.
And I picked out a couple that were on the red line or I picked out a couple that were
on a fairly linear route that I could take through the city.
So I grabbed a box of these, you know, these, these extra stock of comics and I put it in my,
I put it in my Sonic Boom backpack, which I have.
Nice.
That was a homecoming present.
It was a homecoming present from a friend.
So I put it in my Sonic Boom backpack and I embarked on a journey and I hit up four stores.
I hit up a store in Davis Square, which I had been to before called Kamikaze.
And they were too fucking hoity-toity.
They were like, we only publish local artists that we, that we're like, we're publishing the
books ourselves.
And I was like, surprise that that is even a thing that they do, but I guess it is.
And they said that we, they said that they would throw, that they would stage a signing
event for me.
Like they, they, they, they do signings for local artists, but I thought I don't really
have the cloud for that to be worth it.
I don't think I would draw a huge crowd, you know?
So I was like, wow, whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
You might be surprised.
I feel like we have a lot of listeners in Boston.
We haven't, I haven't at least one.
We really should try that.
We've got, we should really experiment more with public things.
Like, see how it goes.
And we've gotten a lot of comments to the effect of like, wow, it's really trippy now
that they all live in Boston, like hearing them say the names of all these places that
I pass by every day and stuff like that.
And I'm sure there's a fair, yeah, I've seen a couple of those.
But I was tweeting to complain about how they were fucking like shutting down the roads
for that like cop who died or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
Those damn terrorists.
Yeah.
Someone was like, yeah, I, like, there's been like news vans outside my work all the time
because I work near the station and like, like in town you live in.
And I'm like, oh, like my fucking people are like right around me.
Like it's probably a fucking someone who listens to the show in my goddamn neighborhood.
All around me are familiar faces, worn out faces, worn out faces.
Digi, well, here, I'll lip and finish this story.
Wait, um, oh, about assigning, I guess like leave a comment or tweet at me if you think,
if you would want to come to like a signing event in Davis Square with me.
I mean, I would do it if I thought people would come.
Um, but anyway, I mean, hey, if Ben does assigning, uh, I'll show up too.
Oh, yeah.
It can come meet Digi, bro and get dents on there.
No, stay the fuck away from my signing.
I don't want people showing up to be like, oh, hey, Ben, where's Digi?
No, I'll tell them that they can't talk to me unless they buy your comic.
That sounds like a compromise I can live with.
I just want you to be at the table with your comic, like comics, and I'll be like 15 feet
behind you in a chair, like wearing sunglasses and just like sipping a latte and like giving
everyone the finger, like, and then like, if, if, if they buy a comic, like you'll like
undo like this little rope and they can go back and shake my hand and I'd like,
well, this feels dirty.
This feels dirty.
No, man, this is business.
I guess this is business.
Get used to it.
You know, I guess this is what I signed up for.
But so, okay, so Kamikaze said no, but we'll do a signing and I was like, okay, maybe.
So then I went to Harvard Square.
Does Kazi have any relation to Kamikaze?
No.
You know?
I don't get it.
No.
All right. Well, how about, how about we split the difference and Tom will be at the signing
with you.
You know, did you two point out?
No, I want, no, I want you all to come.
I want you all to come.
If I do it, which maybe I will.
Maybe I should do it just for fun, just to see what happens.
What if no one, if no one shows up, whatever, it's an adventure.
Yeah.
Just better.
Just have a party.
Yeah.
And then I will tweet that I had a signing.
We'll have to, we'll have to just photoshop it.
We'll have to photoshop a bunch of people into your signing and then post it on Twitter.
Like, this is fucking hot and come get your comic.
You're missing out.
Photoshopping all the greats.
You know, Sonichu, Tails, you know, Winnie the Pooh, you know, the whole thing.
I think I can guarantee you get at least 10 people.
Pooh's Adventures of the Ben St. autograph signing at Comic-Con.
It's like, hell yeah.
And Doug was there and then Tails and he went home.
The Cheeto Man was there, you know.
Knuckles, all the greats, all the greats.
Hatsune Miku showed up.
That was lit, you know.
Comment writer.
Comment writer, a known comic writer.
Every Red Ranger, none of those beta blues though.
So I went to Harvard Square and I went to this basement called Million Dollar Picnic.
And that guy, there was a very nice dude in there behind the counter.
It was a small little hole in the wall place.
And I told him I had a book and he took it and he read through my comic.
And it was very awkward for me.
I just kind of like pretended to look at shelves.
And then a guy came and bought something and he put it down and like rung this guy up.
And I was just like, when's he going to finish reading my shit?
But he eventually did.
And he was like, you know, looks good.
You know, I'll buy a couple and I'll put them on the shelves.
He bought like, he bought three copies for $4 a piece.
I made a whopping $12 from that exchange.
And he said he was going to sell them for six bucks and you know, see what happened.
He said, call back in a while and see if he sold.
And then like the next day, someone tweeted at me outside of Million Dollar Picnic,
holding a copy, presumably one that they bought in there.
So I already look like a real cool guy.
So, okay.
So you obviously couldn't do a signing here because of the fact that there's people nearby
buying your comics and who know who you are online.
There's at least one.
Did you like advertise that or was that an organic purchase that this person just did?
No, I did tweet that I had put my...
I did tweet and I mentioned which stores my shit was in.
So it was not completely organic.
Fair enough.
So then I went to another place and...
Hey, all that matters is that they sell.
Yeah, pretty much.
That's all you need to convince the people at the place that they should keep buying your comics.
That's true.
Maybe I can sell more than three of the next next time.
So then I went to another place in Harvard Square.
I think it was called New England Comics or New England comic shops or something.
And there was a pretty enthusiastic guy behind the counter.
He was pretty cool and he seemed to like me and want me to get my shit on the shelves.
He took a look and he liked it.
But he was not a manager.
He did not have the authorization to do that for me.
So I left a copy with and gave my contact info.
He said, like, call back in a little bit and we'll see.
And I was like, okay, cool.
So that one's a maybe.
And then the last one I went to the Heinz Convention Center and I went to this place called Comicopia.
And they...
He looked at my shit.
They said there was a guy and a girl.
The girl was like, this is very professionally printed.
It's very nicely printed.
And I was like, cool.
Thank you.
He's like, unfortunately, it's in black and white.
And sadly, that is a problem because things that are not in color, they just don't...
People just don't pick them up.
And I was like, that sucks.
But, you know, was it deliberate choice?
I like the black and white aesthetic.
She said that people complain about manga.
People are like, oh, I can't read manga because it's in black and white.
And I was like...
I mean, literally, Jesse.
Literally, Jesse.
What kind of crowd is this?
What the fuck kind of crowd is this?
What the fuck is a philist?
People who only read American comics, you know?
That's like a weird and bizarre world that I don't understand.
The world of Western comics.
The funny thing is that most Western comics, what bothers me about them is that I hate the colors
because so many of them are like terrible colorists.
Or just like the aesthetics doesn't work.
Marvel comics and stuff in the black and white.
They have these collections where they are on a newsprint and they don't have the colors.
They look so much better.
I personally just...
I personally don't really like the colors because it's just like...
It's too much. It's too overpowering.
Yeah.
Like, it's overwhelming.
I like the...
I love the simplicity of like a simple black and white ink manga panel.
I don't see how...
I don't understand people that can look at that and be like,
ugh, where's all the color?
It's like...
You know that drink called Trop 50?
No.
You know that one?
Okay, what it is is it's orange juice with half the calories.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So here's what they did.
They took a gallon of orange juice and they poured water in half of it.
So it's half water, half orange juice.
Well, that's just my age old trick.
My age old trick has been to dilute my orange juice.
So like, they...
Where's my fucking royalties, Trop 50?
After sipping a couple of glasses of Trop 50, if you go, as I've done,
and you sip just a normal glass of orange juice,
it's the most decadent, overbearing, sugary drink in the world.
So it's like that.
That's what the colors are like for me.
I can't handle it.
My baby taste buds can't handle it.
We can't talk about orange juice.
This shit's not keto.
I can feel my insulin spiking as we speak.
I don't think the issue is that the comics are colored.
I just think it's that the way that it is culturally accepted to color comics
in America is obnoxious.
That it's all just glaring primaries and like...
I think it's because there's a guy whose job is to just do colors.
So they've got to like overcompensate.
But I mean, I've seen color comics that look good before.
You know what?
It's weird.
There's a ton of people.
Like, I've been doing the potty cast for a while now.
Like Cucumber Quest, incidentally.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I like Cucumber Quest.
Cucumber Quest is colored beautifully.
Yeah.
I haven't really read it.
With the potty cast, like of course, one piece manga,
originally all black and white.
But like, there's been a big thing to make the colored manga.
So like, I've gotten a bunch of people into reading one piece
through the potty cast and videos and stuff.
And like, most of them read the colored version.
And it's very strange.
Get it.
I don't get it.
But what is worth the colored version of one piece does look good?
It really is.
It's like drinking.
It's like drinking that pure glass of orange juice.
I'm like, oh, it's just, oh, it's so strong.
I mean, I think that the colored version of one piece,
first of all, I think it works because of the fact
that it's based off the color design of the show,
which is really strong.
And like, one piece is a world that makes sense in color.
Like, I do think there are certain manga where like,
because of the fact that it's like a wacky, crazy,
like everything is audacious in one piece.
Like, it just kind of makes sense to be colored.
I do agree.
Like, one of my comics that I discontinued basically,
like, even Tied Eternal, well, not discontinued.
It's just going to be on a haters for years.
But like, I had to stop it because I realized that I can't color.
And this comic has to be in color
because they're going to travel to all these worlds
and locations and stuff.
And I cannot translate the world without using the colors
because it's so integral to the whole thing.
You know, when I read Tsubasa Reservoir Chronicle,
that's the one that comes to mind immediately.
Oh, boy, yeah.
That thing is incomprehensible in the black and white.
It sure is.
And in black and white, like, I just got no sense of like,
feeling for like the worlds that they visited.
Oda's way better at that, doing that in black and white.
I'm sure that the one piece color version is great.
But I don't get needing that.
Like, I think the black, like, the black and white version's fine.
Like, when I reread Scott Pilgrim, like, maybe a year or two ago,
or no, it was more than, maybe like three years.
Geez, I should reread it again.
When, the last time I reread Scott Pilgrim,
I was like, well, there's the colored version
or there's the black and white version.
And I was like, I'm going to, I opted for the black and white version
because like, this is what it was originally made as.
And the colored version is like an alteration.
And I'm sure it's cool.
Every single time I go to the store,
because I've never bought Scott Pilgrim and I want to.
And I'm always just like tearing myself apart over like,
well, the colored version's the one I haven't read yet.
But the black and white version's the original.
And then finally, I opened each one up
to like some specific scenes last time I was at the store.
And I was just like, the black and white is just superior.
Just like, because you can tell, I think the problem
with colorized versions of originally black and white comics
is that like, there are times when the color adds something to it.
And then there's times where like, in Scott Pilgrim,
there's lots of just blank white backgrounds.
And so they replace those with just like blank single color backgrounds.
But that makes it more obvious that they're not in like a realistic location.
You know, like maybe in the manga,
it's just like a guy against a white backdrop.
But now it's like a wall that for some reason is undecorated.
And that seems unrealistic, you know?
Dude, this is kind of like my feelings about like,
just as one example, it pertains to everything,
every like, whatever, like anime or manga to anime conversion.
Like for like the one piece anime, or like any shonen conversion
from the manga to whatever, it's like, in some ways,
like Binksake from one piece is like so much better in the anime.
But like moment to moment, it's like kind of way worse
because it looks like shit and like audio is nice.
It's just paced worse and like it's yeah,
the audio adds something in that in a couple of instances.
But for the most part, it's better.
I mean, I made a video about that way the fuck back.
The the one about soul leader and like how the problem with that translation
was like there's parts where there might be a panel that's like really tiny on the page
where it's just like a little cutaway joke.
But then when they make it the anime, that's like 10 seconds of dialogue.
And it totally kills the pacing.
Yep, that's a big thing.
But to round out my story, so this girl was like, I don't think they'll,
you know, it's too bad they're in black and white because black and whites,
you know, don't go off the shelves as much.
And I was like, well, that's too bad.
But whatever, I can't do anything about it.
And they were like, well, it's well printed.
So we'll they did not buy the copies from me.
They said, you know, we'll take them and put them on our shelves.
We'll sell them for six bucks.
I suggested six bucks because it was what the other guy had suggested
as a reasonable price.
And they will split to 50-50, which is a shitty deal.
50 to the store is a shit deal, frankly.
But whatever, I don't care.
And I was like, fine, if that's the deal, then I'll take it.
We'll do it.
And then I left.
And then someone tweeted at me.
They bought it from the other one.
And it was pretty cool.
So now I have seven.
I have seven copies out in stores.
And at least one of them is sold.
And I will probably go into town again
because there are plenty more stores that I did not hit up.
I hit up four.
And there's at least a dozen.
I'm excited to hear about this plan, Ben.
Because it would be very easy for us
to make some kind of multi-tier deals around this area
with these comic shops.
Like if everyone is going to end up around here,
imagine if we had some kind of PCP package deal
where we'll promote them and they'll host different comics
and things that we create and do art signings.
That's an incredible idea.
Yeah, but I don't think we're big enough for them to really care.
I honestly think that because it's Boston, we are big enough.
Because I mean, consider the fact that Ben was saying
that there's local comic stores that are big enough
that they literally publish local artists,
which means that enough people are invested
in buying a completely unheard of local artist.
That they will sell enough to make it worth publishing for them.
So we already have pre-established fan base.
So it's not like we're building out of nowhere.
We already have fans in Boston.
And if those fans created a culture from these stores,
if people knew every Saturday we're going to be at this comic store,
then you build a community around that.
Right, and here's the thing.
Like these stores, their social media presence
is like a fraction of what ours is.
So especially if they have online sales,
there's big gains for them.
PCP has a swinging...
In terms of when people look at the PCP channel
and say things like that it doesn't have that many subscribers or something,
it's like you're comparing it to the entirely wrong thing.
Yeah, it doesn't have that much subscribers
for a YouTube channel in competition with big YouTubers.
16,000 subscribers to the average human being
sounds fucking insane.
Like if you tell a small business,
yeah, we have the poll of 16,000 people.
It's like, oh, that's the population of this town.
So I think there's a lot that can be done with that.
Not to mention the weirdness of the PCP
and that almost all of us have more
poll in the individual things we do outside of the PCP itself.
I mean, imagine if I did that signing
and say like 10 people show up to it.
That's 10 people that like...
That's 10 real people who maybe had never heard of this store
coming to it for the first time
and maybe buy in some stuff and maybe be coming, repeat customers.
And to a little mom and pop shop that kind of thing.
When we were hanging out with Ben...
When we were hanging out with Econ and Zen Huxable,
we went to Newberry Comics and May spoke to someone there like,
hey, this guy's a famous anime YouTuber.
Can we strike up some kind of deal with you guys?
And they were like, oh, well, you got to contact our office
and they gave us like a card.
She tried calling them but never actually got an answer
because they were just like not in the hours, I guess.
Oh, yeah, I stopped at Newberry and they seemed very like...
They didn't seem...
The thing is, Newberry is a chain.
Newberry was super popular.
Newberry is a chain and it's very FYE-esque.
But I'm thinking now that because...
Because I've noticed that there's Newberries all over town.
Like, they're pretty common in Boston.
So that means all the other comic shops are in competition with Newberry.
Which means that if we can give them anything
that would be a pull for them to compete with Newberry,
that would be really attractive to them, you know?
Let me tell you why selfishly this plan sounds great to me.
It is because I have long felt like some sort of weird comics pariah.
Like a guy who makes comics and makes his living off of doing comics
and yet has like basically no connection to like other people who do that.
And sometimes I wonder, sometimes I wonder about like the comic scene, right?
Like breaking into that scene and being a part of that community, right?
And I wonder about it.
You don't want it.
It's awful.
The funny thing is I completely relate to that because of the fact that
I hate all the anime YouTubers.
And so I have always felt like a pariah in that same way.
Because like, so many of them are about the sense of community.
Like they just want to be in the group called anime YouTubers.
And so they just do what everyone else in that group does.
And like, I'm not really interested in that.
Like I just want to make my shit.
And I would prefer if everyone in the group was doing something different.
Which is why I love the PCP so much.
Because we're like, none of us are quite doing the exact same shit.
So it's like we always have, we're not really in competition with each other.
We're just people who are, you know, taking a similar approach to our career path.
You know, I have had mixed feelings about it.
Because sometimes, sometimes I feel like a weird pariah.
And I think, boy, if only I were part of some kind of like community
that would like support what I do and like help promote my shit
and like, you know, have mutual interest in common
and face the same kind of struggles and all that.
But then sometimes I see, sometimes I see like on Twitter
or in like various discords that I joined and then never looked at again.
I see this community, I see the people, you know, communicating
and the attitude is like foreign to me.
The attitude is like hyper positive and like hyper supportive
and like very like hug boxy.
And I'm like, I'm shuddering in my chair.
I mean, like I said, Ben, in the last like five, 10 years,
every time I go to a comic store and I pick up something I've never heard of,
it has Tumblr art.
When I pick up your book, it has nothing of the sort.
And I really think that like, again, it's people wanting to be a part of a click.
They get into drawing comics because they want to be in a positive community like that.
And I think that you are someone who is as an outsider to that.
You're just someone who independently came to the conclusion of comics with no,
you know, no motivation behind it to like make friends on that basis.
And now you're like, well, surely I can make friends on the basis of what I'm already doing
because surely someone else does comics and feels this way.
You know, that's kind of how I felt when with my anime channel is like,
surely, like I'm not doing this to be a part of the anime community,
but surely I could form an anime community out of people who feel the same way about anime I do.
I mean, with this question, one should really, I think about this a lot,
you should lead your life with your values out in front ahead of you.
You shouldn't like be aiming to join a particular group.
It should be like, do the thing that you're passionate about or whatever that is,
and then like, absorb the community that gathers around you naturally.
Because those will be the people who are like, yeah, exactly.
Which I feel like is what I have done.
I feel like I have more or less lived by that, by that ethos.
I think, same here.
For me, I think the PCP entirely has lived by that,
but for me, it's just a matter of we gotta build it bigger, you know?
True.
It's like, we've built it and they've come,
but what if we could build it even bigger and even more of them came?
Or what if we built it to be even better for them,
and they left everywhere else that they were?
You know what I mean?
The PCP is gonna make them all come.
I hear y'all loud and clear.
Man, imagine that is my ultimate goal, to make everybody come.
Imagine if we could become like a legitimate cultural force in like the Boston area.
What a dream.
I think we could.
What a dream come true.
I think it could happen.
I am here to fucking lead the new type takeover of Boston.
God damn it.
We need Munchie and his foot shoulders marching in the streets
to enforce the law of the land.
We gotta burn this place in the ground.
So that's pretty much all I have to say about that little escapade.
I will probably do more of it soon.
I mean my results were pretty successful.
Discounting new grounds, which I did not really expect to make any headway.
I was successful at two out of the four and one of the-
You mean new grounds or newberry comics?
I'm sorry, I mean newberry comics.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I did not expect to make any headway there because they were so corporate.
But yeah, two out of the four local shops that I went to accepted my shit
and one of the ones that didn't is still a maybe that might pan out anyway.
So, you know, I'd say the results were-
That's really, that's great ratio.
That's incredible about success.
And you know, I don't care about selling them.
I don't care about selling them.
But I care about having them on shelves and I care about-
Okay, okay.
Here's what I think, right?
I don't think I'm gonna move a ton of product this way.
But I don't care about that because the people that do find it in this way
are gonna be people who are really passionate about comics, right?
Like people that are like into this medium and those people are like invested.
And someone like that stumbling upon my work and being like,
oh my god, this is a new guy who I've never heard of before
and his work is different from everything else that I've read.
And I connect with it.
Like to get, like, you know, even just a handful of people having that reaction.
Like that's what I'm after.
And I think that this is a great way-
I absolutely think the type of people who will go to the local published shelf at all
are that type of people.
Yeah, yeah, that's what appealed to me about doing it.
Not the thought of moving a ton of product,
but the thought about potentially reaching like, you know,
the hardest of core of audiences potentially.
You know, it's funny, Ben.
Back when I, before I became a YouTuber,
I was making this magazine called The Virginia Beach Hermit Society.
And my plan was that it says on the cover that it's free
and I was just going to just leave it in like Barnes & Noble.
Just like leave it in random places and see if people would take it.
Which apparently is how the band TV on the radio,
their first like mixtape album or whatever was called OK Calculator.
And they said that they pretty much did that.
They just like printed off a bunch of it
and would just like leave it all over their campus and shit
or just like in CD bins and stuff.
And just like hope people would find out about them.
There are some stores just have like zines.
Like people just leave zines and stuff.
Like there's a crepe shop in Davis Square
that one time I just like picked up some zines.
They just had some fucking zines sitting around at like the front shelf.
Any of them good or interesting?
OK.
I don't remember.
It was nothing remarkable but you know.
Yeah that's the sad thing about it is that like again
it you always have to consider the culture
because it's like if you put it in a zine rack
but all the other zines are totally different from yours
then it's like well the kind of people who would come to this rack
are not the kind of people who are going to read my zine you know.
Making zines is a popular thing.
A thing that I don't quite get.
Is there any profit to be found in making those?
Are you talking about zines?
Didn't we argue about this last time?
Didn't me and Munchie get in a fight?
I was not there.
Yeah he wasn't Munchie calling it.
I have never heard the word zines before.
What are you talking about?
I haven't heard zines.
It's obviously zine because it's short.
Yeah because it's short for magazine.
No one says magazine.
Well zines sound cooler.
No it sounds dumb.
You sound dumb.
Oh good one.
That's yes.
Well done.
I'm proud of you.
Yeah am I crazy or last week didn't me and Munchie argue about this exact same thing?
I don't remember.
No okay well anyway.
I don't even remember if I was on last week.
A lot of people who draw comics make zines and I don't quite get why.
I guess the idea is to make like a really short work that you can like put places but I don't know.
There is a group.
There is a group in Boston called.
I'm just obsessed with magazines.
There is a group in Boston called the Boston Comics Roundtable that I before I moved away
I would I would most weeks I would attend these meetings and people would like bring their latest
pages of their shit and post them up and critique each other and they had like a
they had like a group sort of like publication that people would do their own comics for and
contribute to but a lot of people that were at this thing made zines and I was like huh zines you
say and then I never even considered making one of my own because why.
Ben if you ever do consider that get me involved because I'm obsessed with magazines.
Maybe it will.
Just I grew up with them you know.
Okay the reason the reason I think in my head I read it as zines is because like all of the
like one syllable words with like four letters like a fine line time.
Sure.
You know.
Yeah if you say if you saw it alone without.
But etymology for magazines.
It has to be related to magazine.
It's probably you're probably right but like it doesn't read that way in my mind and it's just
like it is just a big error message in my head I cannot make it as.
You're right English is wrong.
Yeah that's fair I can accept that pretty much.
Let me tell you let me let me tell you my secret shame let me tell you my secret shame.
I have been meaning to go back to that Boston Comics roundtable again because I used to
enjoy it quite a bit and I have not done it yet and I well the reason doesn't
make any sense and it's terrible the reason is and here's my fucking problem guys and I'm
prepared to be judged for this.
I'm judging myself I'm too fat and I'm too ugly and I don't want to leave my house
and I don't want anyone to see me.
Oh god.
What's the competition like there though.
What's the are these are these the much lookers that are going to look down on you for no
fatness and your hideous body I just I thought that anyone would in the first no no I just
I'm like I'm just like I could be.
Yeah sure I sure I wouldn't be the ugliest guy there but I could be 20 pounds thinner
and I could have my beard back and wouldn't that be a better first impression to make.
I can relate to that.
Yeah you know what you should do Ben is you should start going out in public and then
use the shame that you feel over not being better to make yourself.
Oh but I have oh but I have done that I mean that's that's a good job that's
hence the keto hence the keto lifestyle.
Yeah well you know going out going out getting out of the house getting out of the house
really helps with motivation to like improve yourself.
Yeah.
If you're sitting at home and doing nothing all the time it's like well what do I even
have to to work towards what's the point.
Yeah nothing you'd be in a waistoid if you're living that when you have when you have more
of a social life and you have like things that you go out and do it's like all the other stuff
all this all the beneficial stuff it's like you just kind of want to do it more you have
more reason to want to like eat right and and not and exercise and and you know not.
It's like when you like when you go out to like do something and you feel physically
weak it's definitely like you know when you when you're just like getting healthier for
the sake of itself it's just like well why but then when you like try to do something you
want to do and you can't that's when it's really like okay like yeah and I gotta say motivation
is such a powerful thing because I have been trying to like talk myself into like going hard
on making more money because I need to like to live in the house I live in and pay my taxes
but uh but it wasn't until Tom yesterday informed me that there are now like 16 core processors
that you can buy for like $800 that will like rip through render times that I finally actually
started putting the effort into making more money like it was not the like financial freefall that
did it it was the wanting to buy an expensive new computer that did it for me so well hey
there it is classic motivation getting them 16 cores stand funny to make money
no I think that was the mistake I was making uh like a few months ago is that I was like trying
to like spend more money to make money and now I'm like no I'm not at that point in my career
yet I've at the point of my career still where I can make way more money by not paying anybody
by like just doing everything myself and just not being a lazy fuck each and every one of us
lies without a question on the precipice of utter financial ruin it could easily happen
but like if we any of us got sick uh like it's over it's fucking what do you mean by sick like I
mean well you know let's say you um you you got I don't know you get some sort of like
fucking long-term illness oh yeah I guess cancer or something extreme one oh you're saying like if
we had to like spend a shitload of money over getting sick that's what I'm saying I could not
afford kick cancer treatment does anyone in this group have health insurance at all oh I have health
insurance through my job currently I live in Europe oh yeah that's right yeah so she's all right
I still I have you saying Ben I still not gotten on Massachusetts health insurance even though it
was one of the main things I was looking forward to doing when I got back here Ben do it today
look come on Ben you gotta join me in the bottom rungs of society leaching off you don't have health
insurance here yeah yeah oh oh how I love paying my oh well this may get your revenge for those
really terrible by the way but it's free that's socialized medicine for you this is the closest
I'll ever get you can see a doctor and what more do you want yeah yeah yeah he'll look at you
tell you to get out and that'll be that uh when are we gonna have free when are they gonna make
free technolized limbs I just want to have like a robot where is transhuman oh why is it not god
wait I have to share the terrible tragedy that occurred in my life guys guys you lost an arm my
oculus rift oh okay okay I think the rift itself is fine I think it's just the cord I think it's
the cable oh god okay because because the headset connects to the computer with a cord that splits
it splits into an hdmi and a usb and the usb connector works but the hdmi or hdmi connector
it will not it says that it's not connected and I don't know the headset if there's a problem with
the headset okay it's not a problem with the computer because I have plugged a monitor into that hdmi
port and it has worked so it's not the computer so it is either something with the headset or I think
more likely it's something is wrong with the cord so I looked into replacing the cord
and this single cord okay you can buy one from the manufacturer from the oculus of
manufacture free whopping $50 so I'm like fuck that so I head on to amazon right right I head on
to ebay and I look for this cord $150 for just the cord uh wait yeah I'm like so that is the
maybe that'll make any fucking sense like what but why would you buy a proprietary cord why would you
buy it I don't know I I guess maybe uh that doesn't make any sense like an hdmi cable is like two
dollars well it's an hdmi split with a with a usb and you know actually come to think of it the um
the uh the headset port might be proprietary so oh you're fucked you're fucked I mean I guess
$50 isn't that bad hey we're at hour 20 let's do music god damn it yeah all right I guess we'll get
to my topic no no no do you want to do it yeah we now it's okay I've hogged I've hogged the
conversation this whole time I well today was benz day and the next day will be major's day no I
mean I'm actually pretty okay I like with our format there I mean I have many topics prepared
to talk about and uh and I think we know you know see see I'm really bad at coming up with topics
so I brought a topic today but we didn't get to use it so I won't have to come up with a second
topic next time yeah there you go there you go I mean I I quite like that uh I feel all right robbed
this was this is a ben episode I quite enjoyed it frankly yeah I I had fun listening I'm sorry I
didn't know this is gonna be the ben episode cancel it basically it cancel it judge it appropriately
viewers you came on time you talked a lot about interesting things you didn't get in shape uh
twitter twitter.com slash it's also ugly patreon.com slash ben saint uh
uh
by my books in the real world in the real universe wherever quality comics are sold
Ben what you need to do is when you get your Ben when you get your oculus rift fixed we need to
make a virtual comic book store that's just your book so you can buy oculus rift oh no there's a
plan there's a plan you can watch movies on the oculus rift sure yeah I mean I don't know how
they're not like set up for that though it's just like a screen floating in front of you yeah
that you can look at like it's in 3d space but it's a 2d screen floating in front of you but
but you can make it huge I guess you can that's like that's true how is that an improvement from
real life it's not see the thing that gets me the thing that was the most disappointing about the
oculus rift is that the the screen like the granularity of the screen is just not small enough
and it it just doesn't feel like it never doesn't feel like I'm looking at a screen you know like
you can you can tell it's a screen because you can see the pixels I can tell by some of the pixels
but I haven't seen quite a few shoops in my day that's a meme well I mean be that as it may it's
our only IRL portal to the actual rift cafe so by Christ then you need to get that fixed so we
can access it please let's start talking about the music before we end up in the rift cafe
all right all right here we go oh just a hashtag hashtag pcb themes everybody you still got at
time of hearing this you are out of time by the time you have heard this but by the time of recording
it you've got two days ends the 31st or the three days so uh so you will have heard this last time
so you know so there you go so there you are we but we're done by the time you're hearing this but
here's here's our here's our shit all right first one here we go it's from at pelvis esli uh what does
you have to say uh Felix a cover of the original song by at footwear man uh might not fit the bill
completely but I made it so listen to it god damn it uh and it's called uh pod castinator
all right pretty good robo thing yeah like pretty good make sense and here we go
I'm supposed to be working right now I'm supposed to be working right yeah
myself
I think the lyric is don't want to do yeah yeah I think it changed it up change the
lyric that was nice it was nice I did not hear it because the pop was muted for me and I don't
know why well let's fucking turn it up beige is your problem I managed I managed to like I
managed to unmute it but like that's when it ended so I didn't hear anything I'm so sad I go back and
listen to it and I thought that the tone was pretty pretty spot on was it an improvement the only
problem with that one is I don't know if it's better than the one that I was gonna say is it an
improvement on the original I'm not sure yeah I feel the same it's pretty chill I think it's a good
cover I definitely think that's one of the ones that like we should use first like just something
for something like an outro or I don't know yeah yeah it's it's oh yeah it's definitely worth using
for something yeah I like that a lot nice work Felix uh all right next one all right this is a
big one this is a big one so our boy oblivion fall who's made a bunch he made those hardcore rocking
ones oblivion yes uh uh did you guys see his tweet when he was like telling the story about his
name that was a cool story oh you should check out the twitter van he made a little video explaining
his name because like devu was giving him shit for it being possibly associated with scott and
that's skyroom oblivion would I find it on the on the tpcrastinator's twitter yeah but yeah we
retweeted it it makes him feel any better I never associated his name to any of the elder scrolls
games you know so there you go when I think oblivion weirdly enough the first thing I think of is the
kingdom hearts keyblade that is a good one that's a good one that's the best in fact uh but so last
week was his meme theme this week is his dream theme so damn uh this is this is an important one
so let's uh get right the fuck into it wait was there any notes here he just said uh
to hear my music played by real instruments is so surreal many thanks to at azariah and mayd for
lending your voices and thank you sam madman for the sin is this a fucking like supergroup
collab or something I don't know what sounds like if this is a dream come true he says holy
shit well all right with all that said let's fucking get into it here you go oblivion
i'm supposed to be working right now i'm supposed to be working right now but i love working
i'm doing nothing my take i'm jerking unless i'm talking i am an asshole i am a stupid
yeah
um man it's been a while since i heard any brony metal but uh that took me right back yeah uh it's
it's weird it's weird to hear it in like it's sung in such like in such like an earnest such an
earnest way these these retarded right up bro it's a singer or something you know oh that's really
so wait was that really he said it was real instruments but the drums did not sound real
well maybe they weren't oh i mean maybe that part wasn't i don't know i don't know
he said it sounded like tech drums with guitars over it it reminds me very vaguely of um the band
slovonics slov i don't remember how it's pronounced uh oh gosh he's supposed to
it just reminds me a lot of the the old ye old brony days when everyone was like making metal
covers of the songs where it was like tech drums and just like shredding guitars with like brony
lyrics over it you know yeah here we go okay dream theme oh by the way it was called don't
want to do it uh it was a name i i mean that was dope as hell and i'd love to use it for something
i just don't like it's i'm looking for a new theme you know i i mean i mean i feel like an
asshole but that was awesome like yeah ultimately it is i don't know if heavy metal makes sense for
this shows intro like this is not like an explosive show it's like two hours of like a bunch of people
talking you know yeah oh man by the way i'm looking at his entry on on his soundcloud he says uh my
second entry to the pcb theme competition i've been writing music for years this is the first time
it's been realized with true instruments gang that's made with surreal and expensive process
that put me wait that put me out by over two hundred dollars but it was worth it my god he's got an
instrumental version as well what about that cost that was like a 30 second song how did that cost
two hundred dollars he hired musicians to sing and stuff he hired musicians to sing and probably
played guitar friends who could do that like damn i mean if you don't have friends who play music
who play guitar or sing or something like anybody can be your friend if you give them enough money
that's right he's fucking hired set musicians or some shit basically i feel like there's gotta be
someone you can hire on fiverr to do that for you i mean i have paid i have paid people for
well i mean i don't feel bad because like he got it made and we played it on the show and like we
all like yeah so like i don't feel too bad it's i guess it's just i don't the only i don't even
really want to like go on like i feel really bad it's just that like i don't think it's like the
theme i'm looking for but i actually loved it and i want to use it for stuff because it was
fucking dope okay okay question i didn't like it no well there you go he hated it um what do we
what's the protocol okay so like how how do we go about using other like other songs from this
contest for stuff well i mean one thought is that we use them as outro okay but can we just can we
do that like are we allowed to do that i we did say at the very beginning that the thing was like
we were playing to just use these so only submit if you're comfortable with like us using that
stuff okay so i mean if somebody disagrees with that let me know but i'm pretty sure that i didn't
realize those were like the explicit terms we did mention that okay we'll double check that for
so everybody's cool but i mean yeah if you're not cool with him just let us know yeah and i mean
yeah yeah like we'll credit the song any anytime it's used obviously certainly uh all right let me
see here um so this guy made some variations all right next one's from love shorn at love shorn
what do we got he's got old newer newest okay this is kind of weird he sent like a bunch of versions
of this song i guess uh but here's craston eight and three let's let's see how it goes let's see
how it goes boom oh shit this is fucking metroid shit going on yeah
yeah this kind of reminds me of the first song on my album ghost of midwinter ballers
oh wait this is two minutes and 55 seconds long holy shit keep it going keep it going do not stop
we are in it we are in it we're in it to win it yeah PCP about to take a pee on me gotta get
a drink cuz i'm really thirsty bitch did you you're fucking me up i'm thinking that that's really in
the song is it is it actually on beat for you guys like more or less
um
drinking mountain dude don't want to go to school because i am not a tool y'all think that i'm
a fool not me i'm a little bitch please give me some dick in my butt cuz i'm such a slut gotta
eat cut juice well this is not an opening theme at all i think no guys this we gotta rebrand our
whole channel for this song right this song this is our new aesthetic i'm really vibing with
this part of it i've never vibed with anything before this song just makes me want to make a
metroid clone and then put the song in it i'm i'm pausing i'm making the exact oh come on weak
i would i mean i liked it i liked it i'm looking at the audio waveform of the soundcloud and it's
just this the whole time so like you know that's fine it's fine guys stop rapping just play that song
for the rest of the episode i uh i let you guys put it on repeat put it on repeat put it on repeat
you know there was this thing called the uh the synco cube or something and like uh it had two
like hypnotic tones that the kids would oscillate between it was like e bumper and jet fucker or
something and the kids would just simply spasm out all these high-pitched tones would like emanate
throughout the room feel like this is this is talking about some kind of magical tone that
could paralyze children uh oh yeah it was a single product from tim and eric oh wait it wasn't real
give would know yeah unfortunately uh well i mean that was cool that was cool let me let me
let me do that cool but it's not it's exactly what i think we want to use in intro just send me the
beat and i'll rap over it and i'll post it on my soundcloud it's in the pcp themes uh the chat
right i'm telling that guy to do it to make sure he wants it well it is available oh okay i see what
you're saying uh all right and what we got here this is another one for oh i'm okay i did say
that was from love short and sorry all right next one is from a garbage burner or at night weasels
garbage burners weasels garbage burners he's back again with another one here's another attempt
called hypest theme okay well that okay i i look forward to seeing that being the case here we go
yeah
what's your favorite anime
mother fucker i don't care take charge i don't want you to pay that slap
why don't you come and rest on the side of video we'll just someone come back so
what's up get me answers now
ha ha
and absolute absolute masterpiece i want to hear that song every morning when i wake up
i'm gonna put that on my gym playlist oh it was fucking incredible dude way to go that's strong
strong strong contender yeah that was really strong right there it delivered on the title for
sure okay but like that's true you guys did say you didn't want heavy metal i would consider that
to be hardcore punk which is much more the aesthetic of uh i like i like i think i've said this before
but i like that it's got it's got original lyrics that are like about the show yeah and i like i dig
that right i dig i just like that it has that really rough aesthetic which is more like to do
like the cleaned up like tech drums or all the the electro like we've gotten a lot of electronic
music and i just don't really feel like that matches the tone of what this show is which
is like a bunch of people who make outsider fucking weird abrasive art you know yeah yeah
so yeah i feel common i i do i do really love it though
i word all right we got one left for today from at jack is boy simply called uh oh wait it's
actually called extra arthur okay it's also hashtag epic according to this nice uh excellent
is this wait let me make sure this is the right one okay this is the right one all right well here
we go uh here you go buddy impress me
is this the gcp the procrastinators
haha
was that a bicycle the arthur theme i think we found a way was that it oh no oh i wanted to keep going
oh i know yeah that was only 20 seconds long that was hashtag epic way to go buddy
that was fucking awesome i would legitimately be completely okay with that vb op for like at
least four or five episodes it's really not bad it's really this is arthur's theme song you said so
we can't really oh no i don't care oh whatever mage is 20 seconds long it's 2018 mage doesn't
nothing matters anymore copyright's gone it doesn't matter anymore it's illegal um awesome
fucking awesome fuck man 25 is what he's known as on soundflash good crop we had a good crop this week
yeah we sure did sounded like it would be something from icp in the funky bunch thug bungalow yeah
god damn and i think is i think the album art for this is a uh a creeper for minecraft getting
fucked i think that's what it is cool that's what i read into it at least um incredible
incredible all right that's it for today everybody for the for the themes do we have fan art are we
looking at fan art or do we do we ban fan art do we ban fan art do we ban fan art yes we ban for life
okay okay you know what we do you know what we do we look at the fan art on the next on the next
draw cast the next draw cast we will do a fan art round up and we will look at it there uh not the
next one next next right right well yeah because we've already filmed the next one yeah yeah so two
draw cast from now uh so only only two months to wait to get your precious uh no no no no all right
whatever it was figure out we've got we've got some good questions in here uh we do we actually i
i want to start with giffy's because i'm interested in hearing you guys's response uh does someone
being an artist automatically make their criticism more valuable in your eyes no no absolutely not
100 no you could be okay you know what artist i mean the fleet and utter retard it's totally the whole
picture that i would say the inverse that someone not being an artist doesn't make their criticism
less valuable but like being an artist or whatever like it could imply that you just have more information
and inside than like you know if they're a good if they're a really good artist i might be more
inclined to believe that they know what they're talking about okay but like it depends on if i
agree with the criticism yeah yeah you know like criticism right if you're talking about like i think
that like criticism is subjective i mean an artist a fellow artist might criticize something
and then i might take advice on how to change it like like maybe this artist could advise me on like
technique right because this person might know about technique but the fact that he knows techniques
that might be involved in this do they don't make his opinion about it more valid they don't
they don't make him more qualified to say that he does or does not like it yeah like as well like
it depends really like if you have a vision or everything you really want to do and the artist
is unaware of that and he might advise against it and and you know like for instance like ben said
like you know he printed it in black and white and that's that was his vision that's the way he
did it on purpose but then like some artists can come around and say like oh don't do it in
black and white that's you know bad or something you know maybe this is a little bit of a tangent
but i just like i think this has been on my mind a little bit you and i think tom as well but i've
definitely seen you liking posts like this what is the deal with the protect like the protectiveness
around like people drawing your oc's like doing shit that like you wouldn't canonically have like
i don't understand the world that this is coming from i've never retweeted anything like i don't
remember no okay okay oh that's some bullshit okay maybe didn't retweet but i saw it liked i've seen
this many times which is why i'm bringing it up no like this protectiveness of oc's no no no the
only thing i like to retweet in regards to art is about art theft that that's i don't about oc's
like i got i swear was today this was fucking today i saw that you had liked a post that's
well if you just don't agree then fair enough i've been playing a tale of two towns harvest moon
all day i i don't know what you're talking about okay maybe this was yesterday but okay mage the
real point is do you have a problem with someone drawing one of your oc's doing something you
didn't want them to do um how about having sex for example that seems like an obvious one
hold on let me think about this is like the thing is like it's it's i've been sort of on the fence
about this thing and that's why i'm sure i never liked or retweeted anything because i don't have
like a very solid opinion about this oh on one hand i don't really mind but on the other hand
like if it's for instance like my character mage right and she's meant to be me and someone draws
her having sex with their sona that's gonna creep me out like oh hell but if they just do like
i guess that makes sense but if they just you know draw like a tasteful lude of my oc which
actually has happened once like it was yeah i saw that yeah it was i loved it it was it was great
the art was fantastic i really like how they drew the back i know it's very weird but i like the
detail on the back name backs are hard to draw are the nate are you maybe thinking of this thing
mage retweeted it and it is a thing about like don't trace people's art and don't don't post
trace no no no no okay i mean i saw that too that's a very different thing uh and i mean
you know that was kind of an interesting question too people were going back and forth on that like
somebody had done i guess just since we mentioned it somebody had drawn like a picture of uravity
from from my her academia and then like i retweeted that one that's right that was a different one
but nonetheless and then somebody had done like you get they took a picture of their drawings they
had definitely by the way well sure sure but somebody had just like probably traced but they
say that they freehand drew and you could see it was on a piece of paper like the exact same image
you can't print out the original image and trace over it by putting a new sheet of paper on top of
it well don't yeah what if she did what if they did freehand draw it what if they didn't act what if
they didn't literally trace because she did they did credit the original they absolutely did say
they credit the thing was nobody believed that she drew it freehand for first of all as permission
yeah like it's so one-on-two one that like it doesn't matter that you freehanded at that point
if you could have freehand if you have the ability to freehand it like that then why copy it one
for one like no see i think that it doesn't make any difference whether they traced it or freehanded
honestly uh because i mean they're still drawing it they're still recreating something else's art
but i don't know i don't i mean i think if you say like yeah this is a recreation of this art
like what more do you want like what what the specific the specific criticism the the person
the person credited with they said like reference at this person they said that it was a reference
that's not like a trick that's good enough no that's not no i've been i'm gonna fight you i'm
gonna punch you no if they say reference at this and you look at that and it is like the exact same
image well like duh like duh that's not a reference that's like copying is there anything
different about this image that you guys are talking about and you can see that it's the same
image it is a it is an admission that yeah i copied this image but they see reference that's the thing
but they copied it entirely the reference that made me so cement exactly is your poli please
articulate your particular grievance made just so i understand what don't you like about that okay
a reference is like you take something and you and you just like build upon it it's kind of like a
base like i don't know how to draw a hand i look at a picture of a hand it's like oh okay so that's
that's like that's specific pose of a hand that i want to draw and then i draw it myself but it
looks different it looks in my style it's it's mine now like i just looked at it for reference to
see how a hand looks like that's a reference maybe a pose or something like that like if you if you
put like those pictures next to each other you can see the differences you can see them like oh yes
it's been referenced but the artist has made it entirely their own thing that's fine that's a reference
i'm actually not against tracing when it's done for like when you're trying to practice and stuff
i used to do that too sure but you don't post it and be and put your watermark on it i don't
know mage would if you if you if this person had said that they traced the image exactly they said
a reference if it said traced would that still be a problem yes but no it's one to one copy of the
drawing and i have issues with it like what are people not allowed to build upon it and made it
their own i would have not had so much like me i'm saying that's crazy it's crazy i don't i gotta just
profit involved in this in any way because like they did they got a lot of likes they got a lot of
likes yeah more so than the original one well that's not their fault that's true that's not their fault
yeah i mean i would blame the consumer base for that but like in the age of social media it's like
sure sure i just i don't think it makes any sense let time speak i was just gonna say i was just
gonna say you had like renaissance master she did studies and copied paintings verbatim
i'm like baby that was a known thing to do so if this person admitted that like this is a study and
they essentially said that because i linked back to the original it's the same thing i don't see any
issue there it's just like yeah i copied this i'm you know if they have okay the person the person
said very specifically that they referenced and people challenged them they're like whoa you clearly
traced this and the person's like they said no i did not trace this i drew this my and maybe they
were lying but they said no i told i totally believe that they freehanded it i don't think it
makes okay okay i need to have to i'll need to i'll need to take the both images and then like
look at them and and like layer them over one for one to see because like i just don't agree with
your i do not believe in the ability to freehand it so what what why well there's people who do that i
mean there's people who sell counterfeits of like you know famous paintings who literally
can just recreate them because it's just about studying the the i mean people it's about studying
what they did and then just doing it again i mean people can do like photo realistic sketches by like
using a photo reference and they can sketch it with like perfect photo accuracy well if they had
that such talent then why copy someone else's it's because it's a totally different skill set
you know it's like saying oh you can copy a photograph perfectly well why copy the photograph
because the entire point is to copy the photograph yeah well then copy the fucking
i don't know i i'm just i'm having issues with taking someone else's art and recreating it
like i like one for one if it was built upon if it was made different i would argue that very much
so okay i i think that okay i think that the recreation is worse than the original but i
think you could argue that it did build upon it because it like it's colored differently right
oh jeez it's a little bit okay so they made the colors i mean that's no different from like
just taking a meme and giving it a new caption like you're just it's just the same art that you've
been like an EU is trying to criminalize memes because they're copyright violations Jesus Christ
is that true yeah that's true yeah oh fuck the EU all right let's move on to the next question
uh all right all right mage uh you've been thoroughly dabbed on uh okay okay like i i i do
want to say like okay guys i do see your point however i it's it's it's something that we don't
have time to thoroughly discuss but i i do see your point so i'll i'll give you that much mage i i
think i i more or less understand where you're coming from and i feel a similar sort of like a
version like why don't you just draw something new but i i struggle to find any particular infraction
yeah i just i guess i guess like if i saw someone else doing this to my art i would i would feel
devastated honestly i if if i just feel like i feel like this person got less likes it would not
be a problem but if someone sold yeah if someone was trying to sell a copy of my art i would be
upset like is it like permission if i i would i would i would i would have absolutely no issue
if they had permission and the artist was okay with them doing that then you know then that's
then that's personally that that's the artist is it you know stands and i'm not gonna you know
tell them how to think or is it is it kind of is it kind of sad and maybe frustrating that you
know this this copier got you know so much more recognition for their copy than the original
did yeah but i don't that's not even my issue but i don't think they did anything wrong i just i
can't nothing that what's done anyway the next question is from Kajorah Bitterthorn
and it is how's your next big project shaping up on track or hit a snag cough please how they
marketed ETA uh how they market it is is episode one's like basically done like uh it's just i have
to add in certain shit and it is just not a financially viable decision to finish that video
right now i know where you're at dog i feel you big time because there's like the how they marketed
series was basically developed way back when i was after i made how uh we have accepted mediocrity
and i was on my like oh i'm gonna make some big huge epic thing that's like world stopping but like
the thing is it will be niches fuck and most people will not give a shit about it like it's
gonna be something that is mostly appealing to me and even though the first episode is like mostly
done so i mean i will wrap it'll probably come out you know it'll it'll definitely come out in
august at the very least but like as an overall arcing project i already explained all of the like
emotional and relevant details that like people will really resonate with in uh the gecko estate
episode four everything is devil man like i explained the whole fucking point of the series in that
video so like i just think that for for the sake of me making money at all and like making videos
that people actually want me to make and that will get any views it how they market is just not a
priority in that situation what's good to know but uh shinsa kai yori i just did a whole fuck wrote a
just recorded a 35 minute video on and sent it to devue so that's the next big project oh yes
oh yeah oh yeah ben go ahead well uh my next project uh well so endless war is a big thing but
at this point in development it's kind of out of my hands and so i have kind of stepped back from
that and that's just going to be ready whenever it's ready uh so i've been working on vapors three
and that's coming along uh i was kind of i had kind of stepped back from that for a while but i'm
ben you need to do something there's something you have to do uh to make endless war good and
monetizable you 100% need to first of all you need to start using the cop killer and the rowdy
fucker like logos in places because like i can't find them anywhere and it it annoys me that they're
not they don't feel real yet they don't feel real we don't really have official logos like the ones
that exist were made by like people in the community like we didn't make well that's all right okay well
what you need to do is you need to iron those out and hammer them down i like the one that you have
is your just top background that's pretty sick yeah but i didn't make whatever i didn't make it
okay but whatever it is make one so that i can buy a t-shirt of it and wear it ben so you can
monetize this shit and make money making shirts fucking munchie had to go on vacation he like
he did yeah he did like he was like hey i'm finally making shirts and i was like okay cool and he
and he was like okay i did some sketches like i did some really rough versions of these shirts
okay now before i finish them by i'm going to italy for two weeks like well that was great
unfortunately yeah so so yeah like obviously we need to start selling merch uh obviously um i just
i want so badly an iRL meetup of people wearing cop killer shirts people wearing rowdy fucker
shirts and street warfare i wanted so bad for iRL meetups right there was a thing in there for a
while there was a map that people could enter their their their locations into you know roughly
we were looking at like where the populations were clustered turned out it was this shitty
this shitty service that like after a hundred page views was like locked and it was like you
had to buy a subscription to look so that was a oh that was a complete bust those garbage and it
really pissed me off but you know if we got clusters of people around certain cities i was
imagining like meetups where that are like okay like we choose a location in like a city and like
it's okay if you're in this meetup sign up and like show a picture of yourself and what you're
going to wear and the the conceit is that killers and rowdies converge on this location and it is
then a race to take a picture of people on the other team and once someone has had their picture
taken and posted on the discord there they've been shot and they're dead and okay it sounds like you're
copying the idea from touch and never falls in love i don't know what the fuck that is it's an
anime well it's a cute idea okay cool uh so yeah it would be like it would be like gang warfare you
show up you like you'd have to be dressed accordingly and the idea is you take a picture of someone
and post it and that means they're dead and then they can't kill anyone and it's just like which
team can kill the other uh i don't know it sounds pretty cool in my head well whatever it is i want
more and everyone wear fucking official shirts and there will be official shirts soon because
it's stupid that there aren't already i want one real real bad all that is to say that i've been
working on vapors three fantastic uh i'm happy to announce uh my new jaguar is literally seconds
from being done in the editing bay and it'll be out this very day of recording so by everybody
hearing it next big project coming is what this is a pretty big project but uh to that point okay
i'll what i'll say is this i have restructured my life to prioritize getting out big projects not
just we aguas in answer to people's concerns okay uh and there you go so you know working on
right eric c bass says how many wait what about mage and tom i don't know if they have any big
projects at the moment do you do you guys talked about my big project we had a whole like half an hour
discussion i don't know about it you're what i would describe as tom's big project would at best
be at easiest be a year and a half away i'd imagine oh god sure but i have other big projects that
are building up to that big project i guess yeah tell us okay all right um i want to make a button
i'm just going to start getting into game dev because i do all this low poly 3d shit the whole
makes sense is that it's just going to make games that look like PlayStation 2 games and have like
the aesthetic of like low poly mascot stuff like ratchet and clank mashed with like uh the edge of
like new grounds as cartoons and stuff like with your your little ninja koon yeah koon i believe
this is his name exactly you got it sick so it's a she but right right i'm gonna make some short
little animation with her doesn't her name some japs shit yeah she's some some tatsumaki hitzubishi
honda tatoyama yeah something like that her name's mitzubishi greatest character of all time uh the
best but no uh just just working on i do like on learning more 3d stuff i was i keep it's interesting
because i keep like i was watching a gaming brit video yesterday because did you like you should
watch the gaming brit and then i marathoned all his videos he's literally my taste in gaming
i'm like that's true that's true this is my guy so uh i was watching something that was a shock
never seen him since he's literally been on the pcp and we're friends i heard of him and i just
never got around to do because i don't watch like review videos anymore like at all sure but then
then i got dragged back into it so i watched all i mean i just been watching gaming brits for longer
than i've known of any of you is the funny thing you know i guess i guess i just missed the bone
i'm sorry gaming brit uh i've made it up i've given you tons of ad revenue the last three days
nice so i was watching one of his videos on ratchet and clank and i noticed like i was looking at
like the ground because like every time i look at playstation 2 games i'm kind of like deconstruct
them now i noticed the ground plane had like repeating tile textures for the grass but then
i had like random patches of dirt like i wonder how they did that so it took like three hours i
figured out how to do it and i put us as a gift of it of it working just like a mask in like other
patches of a different texture on the same material and it was fucking sick and it felt like a god
tom tom one criticism on your work uh sorry ben it's just uh uh mitsubishi the raccoon uh her the
problem with her is that she doesn't have enough gender signifiers might i suggest a big hunk and
pair of titties that's my that's my helpful suggestion okay i gotta get the porn artist
something i wanted to ask so so you did some of the modeling on the uh run away from snakes pump
game right i did pump yes you you okay you just did the character model i did the character of
okay did you do like her animations or i i did not i was i said that i could because i i didn't
even rig rig the character because i was talking hippo about it like like almost two months before
the game came out and i was like do you want me to like rig it up or anything is like just make
the model and like they were going to take care of everything else i'm like okay so it was pretty
simple to do on an unrelated note where i have a shot glass of my urine here and i am going to dip
my keto stick as we speak and i will tell you and i in about 15 seconds i will tell you all the
results when did you produce this i look i went to the bathroom i have my wireless headphones in
god oh my god shot glass i'm glad i'm glad i'm glad to piss in the pcb yeah munchie not here someone
else is carrying on the piss leg you could pronounce the pcb yeah it is i guess so oh no guys
it's not as purple as last time oh god i would i would i would call it a medium pink
oh god well it's over it's all over and i don't understand why if you were on keto you would
ever consume any carbs whatsoever well you don't well i mean i mean i'll eat like peanut butter
which has like a couple grams in it and that's yeah it's tough to avoid yeah like you know veggies
you know you just keep it really uh listen to listen to this question though this is from
spicy salts in the in the discord uh who says i'm trying to make a video game called ultratopia
but i have no talent skill or patience to make it any tips kill yourself stop i think he has the
he has the name and nothing else is what i'm understanding i mean no talent no skill no
patience get fucked dude get fucked well somebody else responded with the the the even better answer
which is find people who have those and pay them a lot of money that makes it well i'm assuming he's
probably doesn't have money either i'm i'm god that's a fair breaking suspicion either get money
or get those other skills he said you don't have that's what i'm working on not not having not
having the patience is what is what tells me that this is a lost cause yeah i got to start
something dude you gotta get your headspace in a better place patience is is crucial to this
you're playing a long game here buddy is a long game so uh eric seabass asks how many days before
you die do you plan to stop making art and start enjoying life uh literally the moment i get rich
i will not oh my god i mean jesus fucking christ you'll you'll get bored though you'll get bored
what okay right it'll take a while for me to get bored if i have everybody if you live to be
fucking 80 and you get bored at 60 that's quite a few years of terrible life i don't need money for
anything all i need to do is live all yeah all i need to do is continue to exist so that i can
continue to produce shit this this this guy's question has it all wrong making the art is enjoying
life this is what i want to do exactly that was what my first thought was like at first i was like
oh i'm gonna give the answer that like all i want to do is make art but then i was like
actually i just want to eat and fuck all day jesus christ and like go to cool places you discuss
i i i understand that i literally don't care about those things and we'll be happy to give them up
forever for more productivity uh because i'm a machine that loves to work and nothing else i like
thank you i mean uh i like eating i like eating's boring eating's boring and you know what
fucking's boring what are you what how can i'm post food i'm post food i'm ordering
humor whatever it's called right now fuel fuel it's human fuel i mean that's a bit short
exactly if i if i these macros look great i think that if i didn't have to actually produce art i would
be content to just imagine art oh god you know like i can just sit around the thrill of the chase
dude the thrill of the chase of of of worrying on the project and pursuing it whatever about
it to me to me getting it done is just like when i've had the idea that's the big come it's like
oh i just had an amazing idea and then it's like one of the come and then it's like oh god damn it
now i have to somehow translate that into something that enough people will understand that i can make
a living off of it i'm not trying to say that like for example like i i mean because for me the
second come is releasing it and like having people react i suppose if i was rich enough i maybe i
still would produce art it would just all be incomprehensible the idea is getting a bonus
making it is the calm oh well i yeah i'm not that's true i'm not trying to say that like i think
there's anything like morally better about like releasing something like i still i you know just
a fucking machine that has inputs and outputs and you know it makes me feel good to get positive
comments and upvotes and whatnot so like i'm not saying it's like better but like that is a that is
a very valuable part of life that i i just think engaging in that will keep me healthy and happy
long term yeah more than not doing that well let me let me rephrase it because i'm at a point in
my life right now where i'm not as interested in being an artist as i am in like what i could
like like something that i could do that would be bigger than art than like i really want to
just build a city so like if i made enough money that i didn't have to do art and i could just
build shit or just like hire people to like shape i just want enough money to shape the world
you know what i mean like like like yeah sure so i feel like with art that's a way to convince
people that they should shape the world but with money you just can do it you could just be like
hey i'm gonna build the like hey this thing that that i made all this art telling people that they
should like do this i'm just gonna well make that happen i mean if that's what you want to do it's
time to stop making youtube videos and start getting into the stock market or something i mean i want
to do it i only want to get rich on my own terms though how is how is playing the stock market
okay rich on your own terms because i don't want to have to learn about stocks then you're
fucking lazy you're the exact same problem that other guy does then i have all these great ideas
but no patience and no talent well except i have talent and skill it's just not in the stock market
it's in making youtube videos okay but if you if you have a goal that that's not going to serve that
you either need to change your goal or change your skills serve that goal tom what if i can find a
way to make youtube videos make me absurdly rich uh i mean you're not gonna get you're not gonna
make cities off of youtube videos i mean i think we don't know that you don't know even even like
cutie pie you just gotta change the paradigm okay i was gonna like you know you okay nobody's
gonna you're taking you're taking people around about options to your goal at this point yeah i agree
let's say that i okay there are definitely like never mind youtube itself think of it as think of
youtube as a jumping off point for just being an artist in general much in the same way that like
celebrities might star in a movie that makes them famous but because they are famous now they just
have an endless sea of opportunity before them so like and they usually you know a lot of them
end up doing these like high-level ventures and shit because they just start reinvesting the money
they already have and you can just pay people to invest your money for you you know like you can
literally when you have money money is a self-propagating machine yes it is just something that you
decide how much you want and then you just you know just operate that paradigm that will that
will make that happen but you need a basic it's a constant redistribution it's constantly like
assessing the money you have figuring out what you can do with that money to get more money and then
continually putting that in but like to do that in the early days is just boring and gay and it's
all like i gotta buy stocks and like i want to be past that point before i even worry about it
like i want to make as much as i can through just being an artist and then once i'm like semi like
new rich from being an artist that's when it's like i hire an account and and then i just like
tell them hey put my money in whatever stocks seem good you know and like so yeah that's that's
my methodology here that's sort of my my theory behind all this good luck you maybe you should
have got a cheaper house well i'm saying it would i mean that's like a real short-term problem you
know relatively speaking i mean if your goal is to achieve a critical mass of money then you
gotta scrimp well scrimp right whatever right am i crazy here no i don't know where you're going
up with that theory i i mean the less money you spend the more you have but like we're talking
about degrees here well the point of it is that you should always be astronomically increasing
your intake of wealth like it should never be a matter of like i have to save money it should
always just be like if i need more money i just need to make more money you know okay you know
yeah okay you don't want to get lost up in that i mean you can lose yourself in the pursuit of
money but uh oh yeah but that's the that's why i don't want to go into the stock market that to
me is losing fair enough you know yeah okay doing it doing it on your own terms as long as it's
always just whatever you're comfortable with it's like you know i like like i said earlier it's
possible to be in the youtube analysis game or whatever and then also lose yourself that is
monetization or whatnot i do not care about money i've seen it happen at all i do not care about
changing the world at all i care about operating within this world and succeeding in it with my own
effort and my own my own two hands and i am glad to be an artist because that is a profession
that i feel i can continue to do in a way that is you know you know fun and engaging and in a
way that i can do it on my own terms right up until i dropped it yeah and that's what i want
uh i just basically agree i just want to you know i i feel like it'll never it'll i'll never be
i don't ever have to become completely obsolete i hope yeah i pray i i consider it my personal
mission to to when i die to be able to look back and say i brought us one step closer to escaping
entropy that's the best case scenario i'd say uh speaking of which i think all of us i think all
of us have already made contributions to that end so you know i generally are all absorbed in my book
well all right but speaking of entropy uh please look at this image that i put in the thing because
i'm having massive second thoughts about getting this huel because of the sheer propensity of
soy boys that are that are operating with this huel thing look at this guy on the on the second
from the top right that's all i see in this picture it ironically it is the non-soil alternative
and yet we're faced with a with a with a tire a wall of soy boys i don't know look look mate we
gotta take it back clearly these people we do it you know what you're right you're right all right
i'm still on board i'm still on board we'll do this together you you're more than me you'll be the
poster child i'll be the one in the background adding numbers holy shit right two hours ten
all right everybody uh the patreon uh yeah p-lash some say oh someone asked pro crass maybe no
there was a question about whether we would ever introduce more reward tiers to the pro pcp uh
oh yeah that was from uh i don't know what do you guys want that's they tell us that's a great
question that's a great question actually yeah tell us what you would like to pay more money for
and don't say more content as long as the answer is not more content give us an answer what if
we uh like to be able to hear these live when they're recording them you know here's a really
fucking simple solution i don't know what what if we like had a tech scroll of patrons during the
an outro song i mean if that's what they want i just want to know like what do you guys like
from what do you like to pay a lot of money for that is not more content or even what would you
pay a little money for if you're not paying a little money already if you're a patron put in
the suggestions bar in the discord you know and if you're not a patron tell us what we would you
push you over the edge that's the important part that's the that's the big money right yeah because
because we've been edging you this whole time and we really just want to push you right over that
edge finally after all these years uh by the way quick pity question twitter at steinhagen
dillon asks what anime among has been the most memorable or made the best impression on you
none they're all trash thanks for listening to the pro crass finators podcast everybody
patreon.com slash the procrastinators one dollar to get in the fucking chat five dollars for those
sweet sweet bonus episodes and if you are here in this right now friends you've got something coming
to you with the new bonus episode monsters fucking two it's here listen to it right now you you child
you you baby go listen to it and have a great fucking day all right thanks for being here everybody
we'll see you next week with another one
oh