I'm gonna bless that guy, that son of a bitch.
That son of a bitch.
Son of a bitch.
Hey Ben, you ever seen The Monkey That Hides From Gay People?
No.
Uh, got him.
Got him.
Tricking the block.
I see, I see.
You never heard that bit?
No.
You ever heard like that dick?
No, I've never heard that.
Yeah, I killed him.
The original version is like, have you heard of the clown that hides from gay people?
And the whole idea is you tell that to a young boy and he's like, he hears the word gay and
he's like, I don't want them to think I'm gay so he rushes to say no.
I mean.
And not realizing that he only hides from gay people.
I mean, he wouldn't, but he's telling the truth because he wouldn't have seen him.
Because there is no such clown.
Well, he's probably gay then.
Yeah, if you haven't seen him, most likely you're just gay.
I haven't seen him.
Exactly.
I haven't seen him either, to be honest.
What if you're bi?
I've been looking.
Does he sort of...
You see like half of the clown?
He's like, he's like bleeding out on the ground.
Look at him.
He's screaming.
He got Harry Potter teleportation fucked up, split in half.
Yeah.
He got bi-sected.
He tried to transition.
He tried to transition using Harry Potter magic, but it triggered the kill.
It was the slice switch.
Yeah.
Rowling built a...
Built a kill, a kill, a safeguard into her spells.
And if anyone tries to transition genderly using Harry Potter magic, it'll activate the
kill switch.
It kills them instantly.
Kills them instantly.
Please shut the fuck up.
All the wands are transphobic.
So if you're a different gender than when the wands chose you, it just blows up in your
face.
You know, it never says it in the books, but actually, which is actually have wands that
are shaped like vaginas?
Whereas only male wizards use the dick shaped wands that are long and phallic.
It never says otherwise.
You can't prove that it doesn't say that in the book.
Like a police badge?
Like they hold it up?
The vagina-shaped wooden thing?
I guess.
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah, sure.
Or maybe it's like a...
Like a Jackie Chan Adventures talisman.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's a talisman.
Yes.
It never says...
Show me where in the books it says that Hermione's wand is long and stick-like.
It doesn't.
It never says...
Just like it never says that she isn't...
It never says that she's white, except for that one time, but it mostly doesn't, so...
It never says Harry Potter's white either.
That's right, except for probably a bunch of times.
You know, it never says Voldemort...
Describes you to his pale.
It never says Voldemort's white.
No.
No?
Definitely.
It's Voldemort.
Harry Potter was pretty problematic.
He canceled that BIPOC villain, BIPOC dictator eugenicist.
They canceled...
They tried to kill that one guy who was trying to prevent the Holocaust, but that's...
Yeah.
Because preventing the Holocaust is just as evil as...
Johnny Depp is...
Is Johnny Depp white?
Yeah, he's white.
He just larps as British.
He's so tan.
He's so tan, though.
Yeah, that's how he gets you.
You ever seen the original Nightmare on Elm Street?
He's like pale in that movie.
Johnny Depp was in the original Nightmare on Elm Street?
Yeah, oh yeah, he is.
He fucking...
No, I've never seen that.
He played the Elm.
Yep.
He played him, and I only know this because my partner's a huge Freddy Krueger nut, but
he's the guy who...
Do you remember the death where a guy gets sucked into a bed and then a blood guy shoots
out from the bed?
I have seen that, yeah.
Yeah, that's Johnny Depp's stuff.
What?
Really?
Wow.
Yeah, really.
Then he comes back for the sixth film for a quick joke where a guy is watching TV, and
then Johnny Depp shows up as his character from the first movie, and they're doing a whole
bit about, like, this is your brain on drugs, and then Freddy hits his face with a frying
pan, and he's like, that's your brain.
I don't know what drugs you're on.
Right.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
I know my Freddy Krueger, Lauren.
I'll buy a choice, because I just live with someone who's always talking about it.
I see, I see.
I've never watched an entire Nightmare on Elm Street.
Oh, you should.
It's kind of like your life story.
Oh, really?
Oh, it happens when you're awake.
The life of Freddy Krueger?
Are you saying that I'm Freddy?
Yeah, you're Freddy.
You got burned alive when you came back.
Yeah.
You got burned on Twitter alive when you came back.
Sounds like me.
You got ratioed on Twitter.
It's pretty much the same, yeah.
Yeah, well, a heart attack, and then Dream Demon showed up and said, Ben, say, you're
the angriest man on Twitter.
We're going to bring you back, and if you ratio someone on Twitter, they die in real life.
That tracks with my experience, yeah.
I've got a, my friggin, my friggin microphone is in a weird position because I am in a new
house now, and my freaking microphone stand does not stick to my desk because it just
doesn't have the lip on it for it to clamp onto.
So, I had to put my mic, clamp it onto my side table and move my side table next to
my desk, and now it's kind of awkwardly sort of sticking up over the side of the table
and leaning over in front of me, and I have to sort of turn two different ways to speak
into the mic versus not speak into the, to look at my screen, I have to look this way,
and then to speak into the mic, I have to turn this way.
It's bugging me.
It's bugging me, yeah.
It's like I'm there.
You hear the difference perhaps.
I'm there, like, crouching with my ear, pressed up against your mouth, hearing everything.
This is a 4D podcast.
You smell a vision.
You can smell Ben St.
You can smell Ben St. through the microphone if you're leaning real close.
Just rub your screen that you're listening to on the phone or a desktop, and you can
smell Ben St. with future air coming out of your screen.
I'm breathing directly into your ear.
We've got to make sure Ben St. stops breathing.
Can you smell the, can you smell last night's pepperoni?
For every, for every $5, for every $5 you sent to Trixie's Patreon, Ben will breathe
one second less.
Let's crack up that numbers.
Boys, let's go.
It's a great, it's a red letter week for me.
I moved to a new house that isn't a disgusting whole.
I live in a real room now.
I feel great.
And also Trixie is dead and I killed her.
Oh, she retired, yeah.
She's dead.
Ben St. has taken another trans woman's job.
Excellent.
I mean, job.
Oh, quote on quote, yeah.
Yeah.
It's, it's crazy.
Most retirements imply you have like enough money to live comfortably.
Most retirements, usually a retirement is from something.
Right, yeah.
Somebody, somebody, somebody posted, oh, somebody posted on Twitter a, just a gif of a Seinfeld
where Kramer says like, I'm retiring and Jerry says from what?
Yeah.
Got him.
That was good.
And then Kramer says like, you know what?
Fuck you, Jerry.
Okay.
You know what, Jerry?
Fuck you.
I'm, I'm bi-bogging.
You can't talk to me that way.
I was, I was trying to quote that there's this one like edited, there's like this one
audio where it's, it's like the clip from SpongeBob where it's where the word is like taking
some guy's order and he's like being sarcastic the whole time.
And then someone like adds audio of the fish guy saying like, you know what?
Fuck you, Squidward.
And then he goes on like a two minute, like Mr. Anter style like rant of like, is it nice
and like, and like SpongeBob is.
And there was like so many people saying like, oh my God, this is so like, like funny.
And I'm thinking like, no, this sucks.
This is fucking cringe.
I could imagine it being funny.
I mean, was it supposed to be sincere?
Like a sincere like takedown of the character of Squidward?
No, nobody, nobody talks about this, but actually Squidward is very, he's a very mean
guy actually.
I think that's actually a pretty unpleasant individual when you, when you think about it.
You know, no one, I don't think I've seen anyone really point this out, but Squidward,
not, not a good person.
Not a good person.
I can see why he's not preferred among the townspeople in Bikini Bottom.
Actually, when you think about it, Mr. Burns actually is a pretty, is a pretty bad dude.
He actually does bad things with his money.
He does not, yeah, does not help the people of Springfield very much.
Very morally questionable.
He's very, well, you know, he's, he's, he's, he's a, he's morally complex.
He's gray.
He's morally gray.
He's complicated.
So we stan.
I, I, I hate that.
I hate audio.
Cause I know Squidward would just interrupt and say like, all right, all right, all right.
Yeah.
I think I listened to a bit of it.
And it was just sort of like, I don't know.
Would you like some wine with that cheese on that Krabby Patty?
Yeah.
It's like giving a platform to this fish, but like he's just, the bit goes on too long.
Like we get it.
He, that, that was rude, sir.
I mean, I was like, he doesn't need to go on like a family guy bit about it.
Yes.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I was going to compare it to that one speech.
Quagmire.
That's what I was thinking.
Is it like that?
Cause that's genuine.
That I was thinking.
Yeah.
That, that speech is also very like, does it really like, I think they were trying to
illustrate that like, even someone as bad as Quagmire, this is like Brian, but it's like,
Quagmire is like a rapist and implied to have an incest.
Sometimes he is.
Yeah.
So it's like.
He is.
Yeah.
You know, sometimes it's okay when a rapist lecturers, sometimes it's okay.
It's a little weird.
I mean, I think they did that because I think there probably was a lot of the audience that
didn't get that they were going for that, for like a, a douchebag with Brian and I mean,
I guess it's sort of their fault for not making it clear enough before it's their, it's their
fault that they had to, that they felt the need to clarify.
Like you're actually not really supposed to agree with Brian about stuff.
You know.
All the time, except sometimes, except sometimes you definitely are though.
So.
You know, I just realized now that stuff, stuff like Barlin has played two different animal
characters that are like pure white.
The other one, the bear.
No, he doesn't play the bear.
Well, he doesn't.
Yeah, he might.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, he plays it.
Oh my God.
Oh, if I just fucking realize another character that's like pure white that he plays.
So he plays Brian, who's white.
And then he plays like the, the rat, the rat from the animated movie sing.
It was also like pure white.
I don't know that one.
You should, you should look a look of rat from sing stuff like Barlin rat from sing.
And he's like, you're saying, sing is an animated movie about like singing animals and
like a contest.
I've never seen that, but it sort of looked.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
What was the other thing like the pets thing?
It was just like a secret life of secret life of pets.
I thought he wasn't in that.
He wasn't in that one.
They came out the same year.
I think those movies, the singing for a life of pets.
So, so that's two characters, but the secret third white character that Seth McFarlane plays
is he plays himself.
I forget the name.
I forget the name of the character.
He's the white cartoon character.
He's in, he's in Hellboy two and he plays that one German ghost guy who's in the scuba
diver suit.
He's like a pure white ghost.
Really?
Yeah.
He's like a big house.
Hellboy.
Seth McFarlane, Hellboy two.
Did you not know Ron Prover played Hellboy?
I forgot, but not that I think about it.
Not that I think about it.
That makes perfect sense.
Man, I'm looking at, man, this Doug Jones guy is a really weird looking dude.
I guess that's why they picked him to play a fucked up fish.
Oh, yeah.
He only plays, he only plays like characters that are like coated in like three layers of
special effects makeup.
That's like his gimmick.
He's weird looking in real life.
He has like, he's also super skinny.
So like he's perfect for those roles because he could just keep stacking shit on his face
and it won't look like, it won't look like his head is like massive with all that stuff
on it.
So it looks kind of like normal human proportions.
Yeah.
Cool.
I met him in real life actually.
You met him in real life?
Yeah.
I met him at Comic Con.
He hugged me.
Oh, wow.
And he told me, I have a shirt that said I'm a huge asshole.
I was wearing that to Comic Con.
And he saw that shirt and he told me that like after he hugged me, he's like, yeah,
I promise you got to stop being a huge asshole.
And I'm like, all right, I will.
I've been breaking that promise a lot recently actually.
So he, oh, I see the, I mean, you can't, you can't really see his face at all.
This diver guy.
No, he's like, he's like a phantom something.
He's like a mist inside of his helmet.
And that's him, I guess.
Yeah.
In the comic, he like accidentally becomes mist because he was doing a seance at the wrong
time.
He hated when I do a seance at the wrong time.
He'd become mist.
That face.
No, I'm not right.
POV, you did your seance wrong and now you're mist.
Yeah, he fucking mist.
I think in the comic though, that's like very, it's like a three page origin story basically.
He's doing a seance.
Meanwhile, the other side of the earth, the Chinese are doing like supernatural experiments
at the same time.
And this just kind of like is a, is a string of bad events and he just instantly gets ghost
defied daddy phantom style.
And he, he's like, oh fuck, I'm a mist ghost.
I got to live in this scuba diving suit.
I just found this on Google images.
So I guess I might as well post it.
I don't know.
Hey, it's too, it's a reference.
Hey, it's a reference that I get.
This is, this is so, I was about to say this feels so 20 2008.
And then I look, I'm like, yeah, but I think it's self aware, but it's self aware.
So I mean, it's drawn in, I think it's, I think it's deliberately a penny arcade sort
of looking or CAD looking thing.
Yeah.
It's like, it'd be that era where all the penny arcade.
That's like the time Peter Griffin double in the first hell boy.
Action.
Oh, oh, oh my gosh.
This is awful.
Hello, son of a hellboy.
Remember, you remember that part in Sonichu where they do a cutaway gag to Peter Griffin
joining the ghostbusters, not, not like the Egon and, and, and Venkman ghostbusters,
but the other ghostbusters.
Talk about the one that had the gorilla.
Yes.
Yeah.
The one that predates the ghostbusters that everyone actually likes.
Well, it predates the cartoon.
I'm not sure if it predates the movie.
It predates, it does predate the movie.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
All right.
I've never seen it.
I just am aware of it.
Yeah.
They made that cartoon and then when they were trying to make their own ghostbusters cartoon
based on the Bill Murray movie, they couldn't call it the ghostbusters.
It sounded like a dig.
They called it the real ghostbusters, right?
Yeah, the shit on the original.
Fuck.
That's awesome.
I think more things should do that.
I think they should reboot Steven Universe and call it the real Steven Universe.
No, no, no.
This is somebody else.
Just somebody else makes another completely unrelated show and call it the real Steven
Universe.
And it's just not like a guy living in LA or something.
It's like a white guy.
Yeah.
A white straight guy.
He only thinks that would hetero people.
That's the gimmick.
It's like, what if Steven Universe was straight and then all these like...
What if he was on the straight and narrow and he never met anyone as clear?
Steven Universe was straight.
It's the plot of the real Steven Universe.
Steven Universe was hetero sexual instead of all this gay baby shit he used to do.
It takes place actually after Steven Universe Future.
Steven goes on his little red trip, comes out straight from that.
Comes out straight, starts a business.
What if Lars comes back from his space odyssey and he's like, wow, the space radiation turned
me straight?
Steven, what do I do?
Lars comes back and he's like, I'm transphobic now, Steven.
And Steven's like, yeah, me too, actually.
God.
It's an awesome idea for a cartoon, 10 out of 10.
My new housemates are going to hear me screeching and cackling and think that I'm a freak.
They're going to think like this.
The first thing you do when you get in is just laugh to yourself, really loud.
They're going to think this guy laughs.
This guy is entertained.
What a server.
They're all like, wait a minute, I recognize that voice and they check.
Is that Ben St. from the Procrastinators podcast?
I love Ben St. Vapors.
I love Slime and Punishment.
Oh my God.
Is that Ben St.?
He was my least favorite member of the podcast.
Fuck, he lives in my house.
Ben St. the guy who ruined the PCP with his left, shoving his lefty politics to everything.
I fucking hate that guy.
I'm going to post on Kiwi Forms about this.
I'm going to find this address.
We got to kill him.
Uh-oh, where's it gone?
Wait, where's Kiwi Form?
Wait, where'd it go?
Where did it go?
No.
Did you hear?
I know yesterday it was that they got like some sort of server in Russia now,
but even that got taken down apparently.
I saw, um-
Lol.
Yeah, today?
No, I think I saw today or yesterday that like, now when you load it up,
it's like due to an imminent threat to human life.
Cloudflare is no longer hosting this fucking-
Yeah, blocked.
What happened?
Due to an imminent and emergency threat to human life,
the constant of the site is blocked from being accessed through Cloudflare's infrastructure.
So, you know.
Interesting.
And then it links to a blog post directly from Kiwi Forms,
or no, from Cloudflare, not from Kiwi Forms.
Oh yeah, they dropped the whole article about it.
Yeah.
Wow, okay.
So that's serious.
That's serious business.
I saw that whole tweet about a way to hold up every one moment.
Eleazar, I'm sorry to keep changing my volume.
I just have to keep moving my head left and right to speak into the microphone
versus look at a screen.
I gotta get my screen time.
Go back to the party.
I'm very hungover, by the way.
Oh.
I'm a little bit hungover, yeah.
I didn't drink that much.
I just didn't hydrate.
I didn't drink any water before I went to bed, and it's-
And I ate pepperoni pizza.
Yeah, so the dehydration-
is what's killing me right now.
That's like the perfect recipe for acid reflux.
Oh, it was so good, though.
Oh, it was so good.
It was worth it.
I would do it again.
I love sin.
Ben, how?
Let me sin.
I love sin.
I love crime.
I hate the cops.
I love to engage in antisocial behavior.
Ben, how did the filming go?
Oh, did I not talk about that last week?
Did I do that?
Well, you were about to do it.
Oh, my God.
But we were doing the thing.
And so, in the week since you have done it, I hear-
God, so much, so much shit happened this week.
Wow, I can't believe it's all the same week.
Wow, wow.
Oh, man, I'm overwhelmed.
Ah, ah, I can't see.
Ah, like, ah, I'm over, I can't-
I'm blinded.
Ah!
You know, there are some weeks-
I'm not being overwhelmed.
There are some, there are some decades where nothing happens
and there are some weeks where decades happen.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I gotcha.
This was a, yeah, well, I filmed the thing
and I'll just tell, I told you already,
but I have 14 hours of footage,
which I will have to cut down.
I expect it will cut down into maybe something like eight.
To 10 hours, perhaps.
I think it came out okay.
Part of me wants to-
I haven't started editing it.
Part of me thinks that I might start editing it
and decide it's bad and I should just do it again.
There's a non-zero chance that I will just simply do it again
because my speech is annoying.
I feel like I said, ah, ah, ah, too much.
You just gotta cut that out.
I will try my best to cut that out.
Sometimes I do it in the middle of a sentence, though,
in a way that is hard to cut around.
Make it a drinking game.
I'm gonna start editing and maybe I'll edit an hour of it
and then I'll watch that back and if the hour sucks,
I might just be like, okay, that was just my first take.
That was just practice run. Let me just do it for real.
But I don't know. It might be okay.
I'll have to see.
But yeah, I spent two days. I woke up.
I woke up, yeah, right after the PCP last week,
I set up the shot and it took me-
actually, it took me quite a long time to get the shot set up.
I didn't actually start recording until like 2 p.m. or something.
So, yeah, I didn't start recording for several hours
because I had to set it all up.
And then I went all day until the sun was down
and it was dark, so I did not get to keep sunlight.
It was okay. The shot was bright enough with the spotlight
even when the sun went down and it was dark.
The only difference is that when the sun was down,
the shadow behind me got really deep.
So, you can see the shot stays lit,
but the shadow behind me gets darker and darker
as the sun goes down because of the secondary lighting went away.
And then I woke up early the next day
and then I started in the morning and then I just went all day.
And the sun went down again.
So, you can see the sunrise inset twice during this 14 hours
that I was recording.
It was really epic.
Yeah, I think so.
I hope it turns out good.
It's going to take me a while to cut it all down.
Is the whole thing actually going to be 8 hours?
I would expect it will cut down to something like 8 to 10 hours.
We're going to sound like a bunch of hippie crits
and we start shitting on Unique Namosaurus later on this podcast.
Man, fuck Unique Namosaurus. I fucking hate him.
He's not merely an NFT shill.
He's a fucking douchebag. He's a fucking twat.
He's a fucking idiot and he's a little pussy bitch.
Little pussy bitch, little coward,
suicide-baiting bitch-man.
Yeah, I haven't followed that.
I've seen bits of it and I was like,
oh, an 8 hour video? Well, I mean, I don't care.
Whatever. I do know about that artist
because I followed them and I liked their art
and then they started doing NFTs.
I was like, okay, fuck it.
And then I unfollowed and that was the end of my interaction.
I had never seen that artist before.
They just made cute little moving gifts
with big booby anime girls and I was like, that's cute.
Well, who could say no to that?
It's so, I think, I guess, to kind of help people
who don't know what we're talking about.
There's a guy called Unique Namosaurus
and he's a YouTuber.
I had seen him in the context of his pro piracy video.
He made an anime video about how piracy is good
and you should pirate anime, which was cool and I liked it.
Years ago.
Yeah, and that's usually how that starts, right?
They make a video earlier on in their career
and that's super cool and then later,
they're more shittier take-start.
I said that's how it starts.
They have these epic and base takes with their early videos
and then later they're kind of shittier take-start surfacing.
Are you just talking about YouTubers in general?
Yeah, just YouTubers in general.
People I hate, you know.
People I hate.
People I hate is usually how it starts.
They have one good take and then they get your guard down
and then they hit you.
And then they hit you with their real opinion.
Right.
And after that, his worst take was abolishing copyright,
which I technically agree,
but I don't think it would work in today's society.
I think I, yeah, I don't know.
I haven't seen that video.
I think I like it.
I think I'm generally pro.
I haven't seen the video in a while,
but I do remember some key moments.
What about copyright?
Copyright law mostly punishes the little guy
in favor of the big guy at this point in time.
He kind of frames it as the like,
if a corporation fails to deliver on something,
then people should just use the copyright.
The free market should allow.
Yeah, like the ultimate free market argument.
I'm pro market when it comes to things of no real consequence,
like fucking, you know, IPs and shows and whatever.
So I mean, sounds fine.
Sounds fine.
Yeah, but he gave this one example that would never happen.
And like, it would never happen like now or in the next,
I didn't think it would happen in the next 50 years.
I think we'll probably be dead when this,
like this example could be fully applied in real life.
But he said that like, imagine, imagine if you will,
Disney makes bad Star Wars movies.
Just imagine that.
Okay, sorry.
This is strengthening my suspension of disbelief a little bit.
Okay, let's say this.
Okay.
Let's just say you live in a world where they make bad Star Wars
movie and also copyright is abolish.
Now, like nothing is literally stopping like a group of people
going on Kickstarter saying like, we're going to kickstart
the good Star Wars movie, just give us this money
and we're going to compete at the same level.
We're going to make the last Jedi or no,
what's the good one?
What's the Ryan Johnson one?
Yeah, the last Jedi.
Is that the last Jedi?
We're going to remake the last Jedi,
but we're not going to have Luke be such a pussy.
He's going to be, he's definitely not going to do,
think about killing, what's his name?
Hello.
Adam Driver.
He's going to be.
Ray is definitely going to have a connection to someone
from previously in the series.
Like she's not going to be a complete,
strangely come out of nowhere because that's weird.
That's just, man, that's too different.
It doesn't make any sense.
I can't take it.
Then why would she be special if she wasn't Palpatine's
granddaughter?
I'm sorry.
Why would she be special if she has a vagina that doesn't
make any sense?
That's an argument for.
Lightsaber is in the shape of a penis.
Yeah, it never says in the movies,
but the female Jedi all have vagina shaped lightsabers,
obviously.
Obviously.
So he's arguing that with no copyright,
just the little man, just any people could create
a movie at the same level of the last Jedi
to compete against.
Well, if there was no copyright law that was actionable
to stop other people making Star Wars movies,
then how would corporations,
corporations couldn't do anything?
I think that if you think of what it would be like,
it's like, oh, you go to the theater and there's multiple
different films called Star Wars that are made by
different studios and they're just playing at the same time.
Both of the films are going to suffer because people
have to choose one or the other.
They're probably not going to watch both.
So it's the same as somebody releasing a game,
and a similar kind of game with more marketing behind it
is released around the same time.
First game is just going to suffer for being similar
to the other one.
So you'd want to spread it out.
I don't know.
I don't think they would make a lot of money,
but in practice, yeah, I think the one with more funding
would tend to succeed.
Sometimes maybe a corporation would fuck up and make
a shitty movie and somebody else would make a good one.
A Kickstarter would never, like,
not in a fucking million years be able to crank up
as much money as a Star Wars movie ever.
And then even if they get enough to make a decent movie,
people are going to be...
Disney also has ad money.
They could probably even do smear campaigns
against a smaller movie.
A lot could be fucking done to prevent these smaller ones.
And to even get to the first place now,
like, oh, there's no copyright laws,
corporations would never fucking let that happen.
And I can't remember in the video if he says that
he's only applying this to media and entertainment,
but to abolish copyright,
it's not just entertainment that has copyright.
Everything has a copyright,
so you would alter all of society by abolishing copyright.
It's not as simple as, like, Edison.
I think the real thing is that copyright protects ideas
for the end result of being able to profit off of them.
So instead of trying to end copyright,
just end the money thing.
End the incentive to have, like, legal copyright of a thing
so that you can just make whatever you want.
And you don't have to worry about making ends meet with it.
Obviously, huge productions would still cost money,
like, I don't know, capitalism's behind it all.
Oh, man, oh, god, this is...
There's so much, like, little things that are being said
that reminds me of what he says in this eight-hour video,
because I actually sat through and watched the whole thing,
because, I mean, I can already tell by the thumbnail
in just the eight hours that I'm not going to like this,
but I need to confirm that I don't like it,
so I watched the whole thing.
Let's, like, set the stage, I guess.
So from what I understand,
Unique Name of Service has made an eight-hour video
talking about the harassment of an artist who got into NFTs,
and they called out some people,
and it was eight hours long.
I would say...
That's the thing we're talking about.
Out of the eight hours,
like, really, the video had no reason to be eight hours.
Yeah, you couldn't possibly have the eight hours of information in there.
I could maybe, like, I could maybe, like,
maybe at the most say, like, it could have been two hours,
fucking been, like, 30 minutes.
They're going to call me a hypocrite when my eight-hour long video comes out,
when my eight-hour video, in which I talk about how much I was bullied,
that's what my video is about, spoiler.
Worse, he would call you a lefty,
because, like, there's, like, a section,
there's, like, a section in the last two minutes
where he, like, points out that, like, he's like,
I noticed that a lot of anti-NFT people
hate capitalism and are lefties.
That's so weird.
That is so weird. That's so fucking weird.
What does it mean? What does it mean, though?
Clearly, there's an agenda.
There's an agenda. Oh, my God.
There's a fucking lefty agenda.
Man, did you see that Biden speech?
Mmm, was a little bit political for my taste.
Ben, you're unironic. You unironically sound like he did,
in the fucking, in that part of the video.
What a twat. What a cut.
He was, like, he was saying it, like, he was saying it,
like, lefties was, like, a dirty word or something,
like, you guys, I don't, I don't want to make this claim, guys.
I don't want to get political. What a dummy.
I don't want to get political, but, like,
all these, like, anti-NFT people just lefties,
and then, and oh, my God, he fucking, a big,
the whole, the whole section where, like,
I know in the thumbnail it says, like,
oh, they didn't even care when she disappeared,
like, making it seem like something terrible
happened to her.
When we have no idea what happened to her in those four months,
he doesn't even fucking know.
He just says she was gone for four months.
She just stopped posting.
And that's the, and that's the, the tragedy
that was supposed to be our hook.
First of all, is the video, like,
mostly about her specifically?
No, no, the vid, she, he only talks about her
for, like, maybe 30 minutes.
And it's nothing even, nothing has occurred.
Nothing happened.
I'm, I'm still confused as to what, like,
what the rest of the video is?
Well, not just that, but, like, what is the point?
Like, what, what, what was he getting at?
I mean, the, the ultimate point is,
NFT's good.
And the argument for that-
Is that really?
The argument for that is people bullied this NFT artist
and it was mean of them to do that.
Yes.
Yum.
So, it's the, the start of the video kind of, like,
talks about how, like, one thing that's super annoying is,
so if you notice that the title of the video is
how Twitter backstabbed the artist.
Right.
And, and the way he talks about Twitter,
you would think Twitter's a person.
Yes.
He's already like a, like a stupid, like a dumb-
He's talking about, by Twitter, he means, like,
the people on Twitter.
He's talking about, yes.
And he, and he's specifically talking about the
Twitter art community.
Yes.
And he starts the video by saying, like, yeah,
you know, I used to, you know, I used to be kind of
involved in the art community because, you know,
I am, I have a guy who's working on my
pirate comic that no one wants to fucking read.
And-
Okay.
And, and he started-
Sure, whatever.
I noticed that on art Twitter,
the community is always helpful.
They're always like passing information to
helping out each other.
But then when NFT dropped, everyone turned
to evil and everyone started to attack
each other.
Everyone turned to evil.
Yeah.
And that, and that's when they started
backstabbing.
That's when the backstabbing started.
Absolutely.
When, and, and he, and he has a beef.
He has like a, he has some couple of gears
to grind against Dan Olson.
And it's like two hour line go up.
No kidding.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll see if they have a point.
They, they, there's people in the comments
saying this is the part where they talk
about Dan Olson.
I go to their bit and their first point
doesn't make sense.
And so I'm like, okay, well this,
I don't need to watch the rest.
What, do you remember what the point was?
I can't remember.
I can't remember exactly what it was,
but it was just sort of like a false
equivalence of some kind.
Like saying Dan Olson was a liar because
two things that are not mutually exclusive
were said by Dan Olson.
I see, I see.
There's a, there's a couple of times where he's
like comparing tweets and he's like making
it seem like, oh Twitter's hypocritical
because I see these two popular tweets
and it's all like, you know, like,
two different people.
They don't, two different people and also
they don't contradict each other.
I see.
Right.
Because he thinks that if you're,
he thinks that if you're pro commission
but anti NFT, you're a hypocrite
for some reason.
Of course.
That's really, what?
I mean, honestly, that's a little
shocking.
I've never heard people say that.
Oh my God.
Every time he mentions commissions in the
video, he scoffs.
Like if someone suggests commissions,
he's like, he's like, okay.
He even calls it, I think, like, like
slave labor at one point.
Like doing commissions.
Wait.
So it's, it's, it's not just a,
a defensive NFT.
It's an alternative ways.
Okay.
That's weird.
You know, he's, he's shitting on like
relying on a system that has been
helping a lot of artists, even artists
like under 2000 followers on like
Twitter could make, could make
steady income with commissions.
And I, yeah.
And, and also he like, it's, and I,
I think because ultimately he's so
hung up on Dan Olson, Dan Olson.
I need to double check if this is
actually what he said word for word.
But he claims that Dan Olson said that
NFT doesn't help no small artists.
Like it, and a unique name,
a source like interpret this as like
it literally, there's literally no
small artists on the planet ever.
I'm pretty sure.
I'm pretty sure he Dan did not say
if nobody, like no small artists has
ever made any money on an NFT.
I'm pretty sure he wouldn't say something
like that.
In the bit that I looked at,
like they, they pull a clip from
Dan Olson's video, like two clips where
he says that, um, like while
people have profited from it, um,
like, and then there's another clip
where he says it doesn't help artists.
And I think that's what like the,
he's saying that's a contradiction.
Therefore he's lying.
It's what they call it.
Like he pulls a clip saying that
Dan Olson acknowledges that,
that's that like people have made
money off it.
Right.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
The, the specific thing that he's
referring to is that like Dan Olson
said that like, um, a lot of art
thieves, art thieves could potentially
make a profit with NFT.
Yeah.
And then, and then Dan Olson later
says that like, oh,
small artists can't profit from NFT.
And he's like, this is a contradiction
because like suddenly thieves
contradiction like small artists.
Right.
Which like, he doesn't,
does he not consider that like a
couple of things, like preventing
a smaller artist from profiting the
NFT compared to a thief is that
the artist has to make the art
and that takes time.
Right.
And, and no matter how fast the
artist you are, you can never.
This reminds me.
The speed of a thief who just goes
around, finds something cool and
that makes it into NFT.
Oh, this reminds me of, um,
that video that I mentioned a couple
of episodes ago, uh, Dark Viper
AU's video about how
reaction content is basically
wage theft in that it is
pretty much just monetizing other
people's work and, and, and
aggregating it.
Uh, yeah.
Like the, the, the, the reactor
does not have to put any effort
into make the content.
They just profit by presenting
it in this fashion.
Same with an NFT art
thief.
They don't, yeah.
The artist has to make the art
and that and mint it.
So that's an additional cost that
the thief doesn't, doesn't have
to put into the system
to engage with it.
Um, I have not seen, yeah,
I haven't seen any of the video
by the way, except for the clip
that you posted of him talking
about, uh,
Oh, Freddie, Freddie River Ross.
She's like, she's lucky.
She's, you're lucky that she
came back when she did, or you
would be in big trouble, Mr.
I have a clip that would end
your career and mine.
I'm going to burn the whole
system down.
Uh, or whatever it was.
Yeah.
Is it like a DM there?
I don't, I don't.
Did he get into any info about
that?
He said he, he said he had some
video that would
incriminate someone and then
when pressed about it, he said,
no, I was just talking about
an earlier cut of the video that
I changed because it was too
harsh.
So he was going to be even
meaner and that would have
destroyed rubber Ross's career
and his own.
And his own.
And his own pizza.
Yes.
He would have, he would have
like ranted so hard against
them that their career would
just like show.
The video was going to be
nine hours long and that would
have literally killed them.
But he decided to hold back.
Spent a whole hour just
shitting on rubber Ross and
pan pizza.
Is, is the implication, is the
implication that they would
have said, fuck you.
Not that they have more evidence
that they're withholding, but
that they would have been
nastier.
I think in their video.
It's, I don't.
It's hard to tell.
Because it's a weird.
He words the fret so weirdly
because.
When I first watched it, I
thought he meant that, oh, he
has like maybe some sort of
video evidence of some.
He has like the Epstein flight
logs of YouTubers or something
against.
Yeah.
And he's about to destroy all
three of them, but then
re listening to it.
I'm kind of like, wait, no, it
sounds like he's saying
that he's going to, he's going
to rant about them and he's
going to put this rant on
every one of his videos at the
end.
So people are always reminded
that like.
That's like, that's his log
offline.
It's like, and hey, thanks
for, thanks for watching the
new video.
Shout out to my five dollar
patrons.
So and so such and such and
watch his name.
And remember, rubber Ross and
pan pizza bullied an NFT
artist and just suicide on
August of 2020.
2022.
Okay.
Thanks for watching.
See you in the next video.
That was the plan.
Good, good, good.
And you know what's another
fucking thing that he says that
that earlier in the video, he
says that he doesn't believe
that like, like these
celebs or influencers are
responsible for what their
fans do.
Okay.
But he, but he, he tries to
kind of like make
what rubber Ross and pan pizza
did as like the exception to
that rule because like, well,
you see, you see, I get it.
If I get it, if you're like a
smaller person and you're
shitting on a bigger person and
that bigger person brings their
fandom, that makes sense.
But um, several like literally
was just mining her own business
and then pan peaks and rubber
Ross accused her of being a
thief.
And it's like your, your logic
like it's still a bias to like
they, they called her a thief,
but they didn't fucking say to
like everyone make sure she
kills herself.
I did.
Yeah, I did see.
So Ross did call her a thief
or accused her of stealing
designs, right?
Or of stealing somebody else's
like character designs or
something like that.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, but that was, that seemed
dumb.
Like that seemed like it was not
the case.
I, I like it, it, it's a very
generic looking character to be
honest.
Yeah.
Although I'll admit it and like
if you in the follow video if
unique name of source wants to
clip this, I'll admit it.
Like I don't give a fuck.
I don't care.
I retweeted, I retweeted the pan
like, um, claiming that it was
an RFP thing.
I don't give a shit.
So it wasn't, it wasn't.
So they said it was our theft
and it wasn't though.
It wasn't our feather.
Just that two people drew the
same generic like water based
girl looking character.
Right.
Um, and yeah, Ross was like,
Ross was like, uh, oh, she's,
she's drawing so and so's
character because this other
character, this other person
had a character who's a girl
with, with water for hair.
I think of the name of the
artist.
I have a girl who has water
for hair.
Do you?
Yeah, but you gotta stop
stealing.
It's my mermaid.
Yeah.
Stop stealing right now.
I will steal.
Look, great artist steal.
The best artist admitted on,
on the podcast.
Great artist steal and even
better artists make NFTs.
Right there.
Um, where were we?
There's like a, um, there's
this whole section at the
beginning where like, like I
said earlier, you get super
hanged up on, on Daniels and
saying like NFTs, like doesn't
help any small artists.
It's not like, um, oh yeah.
Well, I did a quick search and
I found 25 small artists that
were successful with NFTs.
Oh my God.
That's what a fucking tweet.
It's, it's stupid.
I feel personally, I feel
personally aggrieved by him.
My, my, my, my, my, my hate is,
my hate is personal to him.
This is not about the issues
anymore.
I just want to, I just want to
punch him.
It's not even, it's, it's not
even 25 artists.
It's 24 artists.
One of them I don't count
because it's a, it's an AI
artist.
Oh yeah.
So it's like.
Oh God.
That's a whole other can of
worms then.
So a person types in a thing,
they get an image and they
NFT mint it.
Yes.
And they're making money.
Stupid.
Well.
Whatever.
Yeah.
It's so.
Good for them.
Yes.
So he's, and the thing is that
like you need to, and here's
here's the thing.
All of Unique's video is just
anecdotes.
There's like no like real, the
only part where he like talks
about statistics is when he
talks about the environmental
damage of like NFTs is like when
he only actually brings up any
like real statistics.
Yeah.
But I feel like the conversation
has generally moved past that
aspect of it.
That's not really what people
are mad about anymore.
Yeah.
Because like it, like he brings
up the chart that's like, sure,
like bitcoins are like make as
much waste as much energy as a
small country.
But like technically speaking,
AC's waste more energy.
Sure.
That being said.
Yeah.
AC's make you cool.
Like Bitcoin is like volatile.
And if we want to go that far,
I mean like heating, you know,
in general, heating apparatus,
apparatuses spend even more
energy than air conditioners.
So, you know, the fact that
people aren't freezing to death
is even more of a problem.
He really is trying to like,
he brings up all these arguments
trying to like make NFTs seem
like something that's happening,
like comparing it to something to
make it seem a little bit like
less of a shit show.
Like he's like, oh,
NFT collectors, they're kind of
like, they're kind of like Hype
Beast.
Do you guys know what Hype Beast
are?
Not really.
Person who hypes stuff up.
They're the, they're the guys who
buy like the Supreme Merch,
like they wait in lines and they
buy like all the expensive shoes.
Are they just, are they just
fencers?
Like they buy, buy shit up and
then resell it?
No, no, it's more like a cloud
thing.
Like, oh yeah, I have the news
Supreme.
Yeah, I mean, I've heard,
I've heard the argument like a
hundred times, like people will
buy, um, they will value
things, however they determine
its value that, you know, like
value doesn't really exist.
And so NFT artists can
successfully hoodwink people
into paying larger amount of
money for nothing.
Right.
And I'm like, okay, you can
make money off of it.
I understand.
Yeah.
I hate it though.
It sucks.
So much.
You're making money the same
way you technically make money
by gambling.
And that's not.
Yeah.
And the thing is that like.
It's not productive.
The one thing, it's, we should,
we should be able to agree that
it's not productive.
Yes.
And like on our, on our arm.
It's definitely not the way
forward.
It's just a thing you can do.
To be productive.
But it's, it's, it's the most
like stupid.
It's the most like, like grimy
disgusting capitalistic way to
get it by.
I don't.
I don't just like,
I don't begrudge anyone making
a living.
And if someone's like,
No.
to make money and they do it
by NFTs, like I think that's
not the best way to do it.
But if that's what it takes to
do it, like it's like, I'm not
mad about it.
Yeah.
I just think that like, it's
not the future.
And it certainly,
certainly isn't a future we
would want to like push for
because it's so much.
It's just the, the system we
have now, but worse in various
ways.
I would argue.
That's it.
I would argue NFTs, like
evidence that like the future
looks fucking bleak and shitty.
Yeah.
And um, yeah, if they became,
if they became mainstream,
yeah, it would be, it was,
if the future would be worse
for it.
Another kind of egregious
thing is that like, he doesn't
like, um, if you guys heard
about this, his hashtag, it was
like, I'm at the start of the
year, I think called the, the
animation new deal thing where
they were trying to like,
yeah, unionize the majority
of animation studios.
I saw it.
Yes.
Yeah.
He, he frames this as people
who are like pro that, but
our anti NFTs are also
hypocrites.
Like, like if you're pro
anything, if you're pro, like
anything that helps artists,
but NFTs, you are by the
fault of hypocrite.
I get you.
Because you can make money,
but you can make money.
But you could, but you could
like, like Dan also said,
you couldn't make money, but
um, I found 24 people that
made money.
So, um, Dan also,
what did Dan, what did Dan
say?
He, there's that part where he
says, um, like, you know, the
reaction is confusion.
Like, you know, we don't, you
want to make money?
Like we're here to make money
on NFTs.
Don't you want to make money?
Like what's, what's the
problem?
I was going to mention this
earlier.
There, there's really no point
of like bringing up like 24
artists that made money off
NFTs.
He could have brought up like
a thousand small artists who
also made money.
It doesn't matter because he
doesn't have nothing.
He has nothing to compare it
to.
He doesn't bring it up like
okay, now bring up all the
small artists.
It didn't help.
Let's see if it really does
help small artists.
Right.
Because it could be, oh, it
could be, it is literally like
going to a casino and finding
the couple of guys who won at
Blackjack and being like, look,
see, the casino helps people.
People will make money.
Dan also claims that you can't
make money at a casino, but I
found five bald guys that
helped.
So, um,
Five bald guys?
I found five.
Sure.
I just added a random attribute
to these guys.
Okay, sure.
No, I think it's bald.
That's fine.
I found 30, I found 30
querked up white boys who have
made plenty of cash off
casinos.
But it doesn't, like you can,
yeah, you can make money, but
can you fucking make a living
if the currency is supposed to
be volatile?
It's going to be smarter to
rely on a currency that isn't
fucking always rising up and
down and constantly fucking
crashing.
Yeah.
And there's that side of it
where it's like, it's a gamble
to get into for the artist.
Like you're not necessarily
going to make a lot of money
and there is a cost to put an
NFT, like mint one.
So like you're putting down
monies on the off chance that
somebody in your audience will
like NFTs and buy it.
But there's also the,
the, the scam aspect of like,
you have to try to sell the
idea of NFTs to people so that
they will buy it.
And so you will just naturally
not talk about the negative
stuff.
And you will scam people into
getting into it.
And it's just, it's like,
it's like, I don't know, like
your odds of winning at the
casino, if you like pyramid
scheme people to come to the
casino, your odds will improve.
And so naturally that's going
to happen.
And it's all, it's just so
disgusting.
Yeah.
There's so many victims.
It's like, there's so obviously
a bad thing generally.
Yeah.
It's free.
It's pretty myopic.
It's pretty myopic to just be
like, well, some people
succeeded.
So it's good.
There's this also this whole
section he dedicates to like,
does he, okay, I'm sorry, does
he have a personal stake?
Like, is he doing NFT stuff?
Is he planning on doing NFT stuff?
He must have a personal
stake.
He said, he said if this video
ruins his like YouTube career,
he is, he's going to start doing
NFTs.
Oh, so you better not.
So you better like the video or else
there'll be, he'll make even more NFTs.
He'll, he'll hurt the environment
even more.
Oh, what a bitch.
What a fucking bitch.
What a piece of shit.
I hate him.
You need, please make all your videos
into NFTs.
Please.
I want you to make all your fucking videos.
What did I say?
I like mint every individual frame
of every video, mint, you know,
every, every down to the frame time
stamp of every video, you can make
billions and billions of NFTs and sell
each one for a dollar.
At the, at the end of the video,
I'm jumping around because
like conversations
reminded me of so many like random
shit this guy.
Not random, but so the
conversation is reminding me of like
different points in the video.
But at the end of the video, he
talks about the author for
Berserk and like his death and like
how like he knows he didn't work
himself to death and it was just like,
it was like a heart condition that
got him.
But he said that like, let's say there
is a manga artist and
who is in a shitty situation like
that?
And he scoffs the idea
of like, okay, maybe
you could improve working conditions.
Maybe I don't really agree
with like, like unions, you know,
or, or, or, or let me,
the alternative.
Here's his like superior alternative
is like, what if a
mangaka minted every page
of their manga?
True, true.
And, and like imagine
how insane do you need to be
to like acknowledge that there are
things that can be done to improve
the working conditions?
Wait, wait, wait.
No, what if we don't do that?
Let's see where he's going with it.
You don't get it.
Imagine, imagine how much money
you'd get if you have, if you,
if you, if you were the owner
of the, of the page where white
beer says the one piece is real.
Oh my God.
And he has his dick out.
Holy shit.
That would be worth some money.
Oh my God.
And then, and then Oda would have
enough money to like relax.
And it's like,
I don't get the corp.
He has enough money.
It's true.
Cause the thing is that like,
the thing is like better working
conditions assumes that by the fall.
You don't need to fucking add again.
If your, if your favorite mangaka
works himself to death,
Karoshis themselves to death,
and they die, it's your fault.
And you don't want to feel bad,
do you?
So you better buy their fricking NFT.
Is there like any,
I don't know too much about this,
the hard condition thing,
but is there any indication that
Berserk was not popular enough to
support him medically?
Like, is this a situation where
NFTs would have made the difference?
It's so all over the place
because it's kind of like,
okay, so let's say there was like,
there was this one mangaka,
there was this one mangaka recently
got canceled,
but it seemed like it had a small
fandom, which was,
it was like a red writing hood
character,
but she had like big titties
and she was like super buff.
Oh my God.
And so,
right, but it would,
the thing is that that's the only
thing people ever talked about.
So I kind of already knew it was
going to be shit.
Besides,
besides that,
I guess it's like,
okay, so would NFTs help this guy?
Even,
even if like the manga wasn't good,
if you had enough money off of like
the big tittie NFT,
would it have made the manga
keep on going?
Because that implies that like,
like Sean and Joe has,
keeps a percentage of the NFT,
right?
Artists already,
artists already basically do this.
Like a lot of artists do sell their
original pages,
as a,
as a thing.
They sell like copies of it too,
and people like eat it up because
it's like, you know,
it's like physical and like,
it looks just like it, you know?
They sell,
they sell the original animation
cells from like,
cartoons and stuff.
And the thing is that,
that's a thing that people do already.
The thing is that's so crazy,
and he never brings this up,
is that the NFT is not the art.
The NFT is a receipt really.
The NFT is like a link.
And he doesn't,
he doesn't even acknowledge that?
Yeah.
He talked,
he like,
he doesn't really acknowledge that
what you're buying,
but he kind of,
he kind of implies it.
There's a whole section where like,
so you know,
his whole like anti copyright stance.
Sort of.
Yeah.
I mean,
we just,
the little,
his abolishment of copyright,
he argues that,
that doesn't contradict with his like
pro NFT stance.
Right.
And the,
and the thing is that I agree with him,
that it doesn't,
because the way he explains it,
I'm like, okay,
I get it.
I get why like being pro NFT
and being anti copyright doesn't
contradict each other.
Yeah.
Because the thing is that like,
his whole argument is that
like he,
he doesn't think bootlegs are bad.
Like,
if someone,
if something gets bootleg,
that means that like,
there's like a,
there's like a problem.
Yeah.
With the person who's providing
the item in the market,
right?
So bootlegs should be allowed.
That being said,
you can't bootleg an NFT.
Right.
Because an NFT isn't.
The obvious,
yeah.
Yeah.
The,
the obvious question is what if it was,
okay,
what about right-click save?
Right.
But the thing is,
what's his answer to people
right-click saving the NFT?
Well,
well,
first of all,
he pulls a fucking giant cope
where he's all like,
by the way,
no one was upset about right-click save.
You know,
we,
we all knew it was a joke, guys.
It's not a joke.
We all knew it was a joke.
Cause I,
cause I,
cause I saved the image and I haven't.
Well,
well,
the thing is that I,
I get,
I get it.
I get what he means
because right-click save,
like no,
the NF,
you don't own the NFT
if you save the image
because the image and the NFT
are two different things.
Yes.
The NFT is the link.
I'm with you so far.
Okay.
The NFT is the link.
So what,
so what is the NFT guy?
so what are we,
but what are we talking about?
The NFT is just the idea of scarcity.
It's just the idea of something being rare.
And you can't,
you can't copyright that.
You can't bootleg that, right?
Yeah.
But,
but he doesn't realize,
he doesn't realize that he made the,
the value.
So what's the value then?
He is saying,
he's basically saying by the fault
that NFT is an art.
Right.
That,
that it's not,
and it will never fucking be art.
Right.
At all.
I mean,
he kind of made the argument
that all this shit is like soulless really.
Right.
Because he wants to say that,
like the NFT,
like,
like people who collect NFT
are kind of like hype beasts.
And hype beasts are like
super fucking annoying things.
They're super fucking annoying people.
But I respect them a little bit more,
because when you buy a supreme jacket,
it serves a purpose besides it,
just being a brand.
You could wear a jacket when it's cold.
Right.
Yeah.
But an NFT like,
no, it's just,
it's just something that potentially could be
scarce or not.
It's depending like,
how the fucking,
how much the point is like.
There's literally,
there's literally nothing to it other than
that you can say you own it.
Right.
Everything that it is.
And people,
people will pay for that.
Sure.
But like buy,
they're,
they're paying for the fact that like,
it's like unique only they could own it,
but it's not the art.
Right.
And he,
he talks,
he brings up some guy who's like,
like,
oh,
here's like a super nice collector who like
buys NFTs and doesn't sell them,
which I don't get.
Like,
I don't get motherfuckers.
What a sweetheart.
Right.
And,
and like he,
he says like,
this guy,
you know,
he buys NFTs and even,
even though when the market was crashing,
he just likes the art.
And it's like,
yeah,
but you just made the argument that the NFT isn't the art.
So he's,
he's virtue signaling.
He's a fucking fake.
Right.
So what,
by the fault.
So what is he,
so what is he actually buying?
Sure.
Gotcha.
I mean,
I would prefer it.
Honestly,
if it was like,
if it was just like,
you give money to an artist for like,
I don't know,
an imaginary piece of an imaginary pie,
just to say,
I support you.
Like that's,
that's,
that's the hypothetical,
most people who buy NFTs try to want to profit off of the idea
that they could sell it on.
There's,
there's nothing about that guy.
Like that guy could just give those artists money.
He could just do the actual,
like give the money.
You could just do that.
And at the end of the day,
he's not really collecting art.
Sure,
it appears on his fucking website,
but there's like,
think of all the people who we have,
like me,
for example,
we used to have like USBs just filled with images that I would collect.
Right.
And to me,
that kind of has a little bit more,
it has a little bit more going than someone's like,
I only collect this image because it's an investment at the end of the day.
So,
so what you're saying is that unique simply does not,
he just equivocates between art and NFT,
seemingly without,
seemingly without any respect for the fact that they are not one in the same.
But he are,
he talks about them as though they are.
Right.
And this makes me think about like,
cause as you mentioned earlier,
like what's stopping the person from just giving the artist money.
And it's like,
people already do that.
Like that's what Patreon is for,
which by the way,
he,
he scoffs at Patreon too.
He scoffs at literally everything that like helps,
that could help an artist.
Right.
Because he also frames like,
he also frames that like,
Oh yeah, you know what?
Patreon takes too big of a cut.
And so does PayPal,
you know,
but the minting fees,
the minting fees though,
that's not,
that doesn't take a cut.
That's just the free market.
You know,
how like,
how Bandcamp has like,
people who,
who supported an album or a song,
they have their little username and icon underneath it.
So supported by these people.
That would be a nice,
that you could do that.
Like that's,
if you want to support an artist by paying them
and get a little like sticker saying,
you did it,
you own this,
or you are,
you know,
you are a part of this,
like,
like support.
That's the sort of thing that it should be.
Like YouTubers do that with Patreon.
Fucking unique does that.
He does that at the end of this video.
Yeah.
It's just like,
if there's an argument to be made that NFTs are the way to do that,
it's just not true.
There's so many other ways
that are already there for artists
to be supported by fans
who want to be a part of the thing.
There's so many like,
like ways to do it
based on currency that isn't volatile.
You know,
that isn't like a huge gamble to get into.
Right?
Yeah.
It's,
it's fucking,
it's fucking trash.
And
I think,
if I were to talk about like one more section about the video,
that is just very like,
dumb.
Is the last two hours,
is the anti SJW section of the video?
Because I mentioned earlier that like,
he says lefty,
like a bad word,
like a bad word.
And basically,
like,
unironically,
like he doesn't state this,
he's presenting things.
It seems like he's implying that like,
the NFT artists are like the black people
of the art world,
if you will,
because they're just as oppressed
as black people in real life.
Well, they're,
they're like oppressed by like lefties
who are by the way,
the real races.
Right?
I don't know why,
but the unique name of Somers did not strike me
as a right-leaning person.
He says he's a pro-capitalist libertarian
at the end of the video.
Well.
Right?
He's one,
he's one of the libertarians that have like one,
he's like libertarian,
but one of his like,
takes is like a little bit more left.
Right?
Yeah.
He looks like,
I'm going to get canceled.
He looks like a gender person.
He looks like he has pronouns.
He looks, he does,
honestly,
and you know, it's true,
he does look like he has pronouns.
It looks like he's gonna,
a little bit surprised.
A little bit surprised.
But I also,
I could see it, I could see.
Not that there's anything wrong with that.
If you,
if you need,
if you need name of sorts,
gain some pronouns,
I would respect them a little bit,
actually.
I'd be like,
you know what,
pronoun person,
you know,
you're all right.
I would respect the pronouns,
not the person.
Just like I do with everyone.
Oh my God.
And,
he just kind of like,
oh, and,
I, this is,
so, you know the real reason
why this video is eight hours long?
Cause he spends,
he spends the majority of it
reading tweets.
Oh God,
it's just like J.K. Rowling's new book.
It's just like J.K. Rowling's new book
of fake meme tweets.
He,
he spends so much fucking time
in the video
reading every single,
and I'm not lying when I say
he reads every single
negative tweet about NFT.
While watching the video,
I was trying to pay attention
to see if he would
read one of my,
my tweets.
Cause I left a couple of stuff
that he,
like in the same style of like
tweets he's reading.
And there's like so many,
like I,
I,
I noticed there was a lot like
of people,
a lot of like my mutuals
or other like people that I know
that tweets he was reading
off of,
you know?
And like,
he wouldn't just read it.
He would also read
how many retweets
and how many likes.
There's like two moments
where he says that like
the NFT hate campaign
is so bad.
Because,
one of his,
two of his followers like
ratioed him one time.
Which is like,
this is like,
why would he bring this up?
What is,
why do you bring a thing
to get fucking ratioed
by your own followers, dude?
That's fucking cringe.
That's very funny.
That's the cringe you shit ever.
And he fucking,
and he complains about people
like being like follow police,
like,
oh there's people out there
who check to see if you follow
NFT artists.
But he's fucking being like,
he's being like the,
the Twitter like
Gestapo right now,
like fucking,
cause he like,
when he talks about
Robert Ross,
it's not that he,
the whole like framing it,
that Robert Ross started
like the hate campaign,
but he also
like goes to check to see,
like,
what are the tweets
that Robert Ross likes?
He only likes the anti-NFT tweets.
He's just retweeting anti-NFT stuff.
He's following the wrong people.
He's liking the wrong things.
Yes.
Oh, well,
mutuals with Hasan,
red flag right there.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's like another
fucking real point
he brings up later.
And Hasan is a lefty
and the left has a problem
because they bully NFT people.
Yeah.
And I know that because Ross did it
and Ross likes Hasan
and Hasan is left
and left is bad
because Ross bullies
NFT people.
And I know that the left
does that because
Ross follows Hasan.
You see,
it all comes together.
A big reason why
like I wanted to finish the video
because at the start of the video
he mentions,
he mentions an agenda
and I was like,
oh man,
now I got to really know
like who's the secret
fucking anti-NFT illuminati
he's talking about.
Uh-huh.
But he just reveals
that it's like lefties.
He even does like a montage
of different like anti-NFT tweets
mentioning capitalism.
Uh-oh.
And it's like...
Scary.
Like it's like he,
he doesn't realize that
it is capital,
like it is capitalism.
It especially NFTs
are very late stage capitalism
because like,
like capitalism would be like,
you're trying to make as much profit
off of like a physical object
that like serves a purpose
in a way, right?
Right.
And late stage capitalism would be
like you're trying to make as much
money off something
that doesn't-
No matter what it is,
just make that money.
Yeah.
Like it does,
it's not even like an object.
It's like,
it's just an idea of something.
So what,
does he,
yeah,
what does he think the difference
between this and
capital,
I mean,
he likes,
first of all,
he likes capitalism.
He thinks it's good.
So does,
but he doesn't think the NFTs are
a branch or a,
what's the word,
a manifestation of capitalism.
Does he think it's better
than capitalism?
He might,
he frames NFTs,
some sort of like
natural progressive
progression
Yeah.
of like stuff that like
already exists.
Yeah.
That's the problem.
It's a natural progression
of a bad system
that encourages bad things
to happen.
And there is,
for it's bad.
Well,
he sees them as
inevitable.
Yes.
That's part of the inevitable
march of progress.
He's like,
just part of the,
the natural part of the market,
you know,
the free,
the fucking free market.
I have a feeling that like,
tell me if you ever met
this kind of person.
There's like a,
there's like people out there
that are like pro capitalism,
but they don't know
what capitalism is.
Like what they think
capitalism is,
is like when you buy
and sell things.
Yeah.
Yes.
And I,
I had a buddy who I asked him,
dude,
because he was defending
capitalism.
Do you know what it is?
And he's like,
yeah, it's when you buy
and sell things.
And I'm like,
no, that's not fucking
capitalism.
That's commerce.
Yeah.
There's mercantilism existed before.
Like just buying and selling shit.
It's just,
it's always fucking
is the fucking the,
the,
uh,
what do you call it?
The incentive structure
that leads to
billionaires existing.
The existence of an owning,
an owning class,
a class that owns the,
the means of production,
the bourgeoisie
defined by,
defined by their ownership.
Yeah.
And he's basically saying that
like you see lefties,
like would say stuff like,
uplift,
uh,
black,
black voices.
But, but then like,
I hate it when people do that.
But,
but then when like black people
say like,
when black people are anti-vaccine,
fucking Hassan is like angry at them.
And like,
I'm going to say this,
the only reason people call Hassan,
the only reason people consider
Turkish people white is
because they hate Hassan.
I'm going to say that right now.
Wait,
I know,
I know Turkish people.
So they're saying he's white,
because they hate,
okay, sure.
Well, well,
Turkish people are like,
very light-skinned.
From what I've seen,
they seem very light-skinned.
Um,
I thought Turkey was more deserty,
but like,
what do I know?
Freaking, uh,
Johnny Depp looks less white
than Hassan does.
Johnny Depp is more of a PO.
I can't believe white woman,
Amber heard,
was frightening POC,
Johnny Depp,
taking away his fucking job.
True.
His livelihood,
threatening his livelihood.
He, he,
he basically does,
he basically does the thing where like,
um,
throughout the whole video,
he's saying that he's like,
pro-nuance.
Like he's,
he's, he has the nuance.
I consider myself
pro-nuance.
I'm pro-facts.
I'm pro-the-truth.
Yeah.
And anyway,
here's why,
here's why NFTs are inevitable
and why.
Are better,
better than unions.
Here's why,
here's why,
uh,
Amber heard is a white woman
attacking a BIPOC Johnny Depp.
Uh, anyway.
Yeah.
Okay.
I also consider myself pro-nuance.
He,
he considers himself pro-nuance,
but he does,
he thinks that like,
I'm pro-nouns.
He,
he thinks that lefties are hypocrites
when they like,
criticize bad ideas
that come from like,
POC.
When,
like,
it's like,
you understand that maybe there's some nuance here,
that maybe,
no,
when a black person,
like,
he brings up a guy called Thomas,
uh,
I think his name is Thomas Soho.
Oh, I know.
He's like a,
he's like a famous black, uh,
economist, right?
Yeah.
Economist.
And,
and he,
because he talks about,
like,
this is the part where he's just shitting on,
lefties that he has.
Like,
he's not even like,
talking about NFTs anymore.
He's like,
just shitting on lefties.
Does he do a,
does he do a,
and another thing,
what if a black person made NFTs?
Wouldn't it be racist
to be mad about it?
Oh,
you,
oh,
I'm just saying that like,
the,
the blackutta
Republican's were more offensive than anything Hitler ever said about Jews,
in my opinion,
but replaced Jews with NFT artists.
And,
not surprisingly
There's like,
I'm not joking when I say this.
There's the dream,
there's the three minute section of the eight hour video where he's like defending Clarence Thomas.
What?
What the fuck!
Yes.
That's a good idea.
He's one of the,
he's the black guy on the Supreme court.
He's one of the ones he voted in favor of repealing.
Oh,
that,
That guy wait, what is he? I want to know what does he have to say about Clarence Thomas?
Well, he doesn't like that a bunch of liberals called him like the n-word like
You know what you know what I'll you know what I'll give it to him. You know what?
I'm defending like I I mean I'm defending you're here to do you to officially defend click calling switch
I switch sides now. Okay, but another
I'm allowed to say am I allowed to say the C word
Is it a color where no the seat C o and the word the word for a the word for a black person who?
undermines other black people for
No, I wouldn't say that Ben. You know, I probably I won't say it. I don't say
I know what you mean. I know what you mean. See C o and the word that got that never knows best video about
dragon age taken down because the
Because because the Coon the the code of conduct
Spelled Q you and sounded too much like the word Nick got flagged for eight speed
Then you gotta need like you can't be saying that you haven't had like a black guest on this show for ten years
I didn't I was I said the Q version
I pronounced it with the short double O sound
The difference between a cook and cook look I
Silent hard are all right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, exactly. That's right
But the thing is that I cut this whole part. No, it's good. No, I'm pro nuance. This is new
He conflates liberals with lefties, which is like big mistake right there
Well, yeah, I mean everybody on the right does that everybody on the right doesn't understand that they're not the same thing
I mean like the thing is that it's the same with him like conflating Twitter as a person
Which is why no, that's the only way Twitter
He's conflating NFTs with art as well
Yes, very pro very pro nuanced position this guy has
Yes, very good. Oh my god
Okay, well, I think one one final thing one one fucking one fucking final thing and then we could move on from the unique
The unique name of sore is shitty now or right? Um, he he complains, you know the artist. I'm RJ Palmer
Yeah, the Bulbasaur guy. Yeah. Yeah, he did like the realistic Pokemon
And then he ended up working on the technically true. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yes
So, um, anyway, he he frames like RJ Palmer as kind of like a hypocrite because um,
He did tweet out that like he's all like, hey guys, maybe like the massive harassment campaigns against like
NFT artists is it like maybe we maybe like, you know, NFTs fucking suck
But like maybe they don't deserve a difference. Yeah, I mean that seems fair
I am not yeah, I'm not
I'm not I don't I don't hate into individual small artists for doing what they do to make money
I cannot begrudge them that I don't hate them. I mean, I don't hate like anyone who I don't hate any small artists who tried it
And then like yeah, stop doing it. Yeah
Especially become from a third world country because at that point fuck it right, right?
Yeah, that that being said RJ Palmer made that tweet and then a bunch of people in the replies were like
Nah, dude, fuck NFT artists, right? And the thing is that RJ Palmer had no pushback against us, right?
Like he didn't like he didn't he didn't push back against the people saying nah, dude. Fuck that. Yeah
He didn't push back any any frames is as like what the fuck RJ like you're fucking cultivating this like hate
This hate because he because he said don't harass people
But he didn't back it up hard enough. And so he actually said the opposite of what he said
This is the weird thing there is awesome like like a a bit of an argument and
An argument I shouldn't say a bit because it is that like people
Go to harassment way too easily and way too hard and in large numbers as it often is with something like Twitter
It's very damaging
So like it's not good that people go on a harassment campaigns thinking that they're the only one doing it not realizing
It was like huge amounts if it's like a big like all the Twitter enemy of the week
I and somebody gets dogpiled and it's like that aspect of it is like it's something to discuss
There's nuance in that you can't make a whole eight hour video about just that though
He sure they didn't I think my problem is that he frames this as like an art Twitter problem
Or like as a lefty problem when like it's a social media
This is just a Twitter problem the thing is Twitter is designed to piss you off like that
That's our purpose and he doesn't consider that
There's so many things he just doesn't consider it because he comes into everything with bad faith like for example
Though the one guy that supposedly like Sarah like stole art from like he clarified that he thinks that Sarah does not deserve
The hate campaign and both pan pizza and Ross did not tweet the clarification tweet
So he so he makes it seem like Ross is like this evil person for not doing that when he doesn't consider that maybe it
Just didn't show up on Ross's fucking timeline
Maybe like because Ross seems to be maybe only interacting with like hate hate NFT stuff
So that shit didn't pop up right he doesn't consider that just what maybe they didn't fucking see it
Maybe because a lot of big artists a lot of popular people will make a tweet and then mute it right away
Because their phone is gonna be constantly fucking ringing from the notifications
He does not consider none of these things
Right because everything is like it like everything has like an intent and not that like it's just like
This is a sad situation that the internet and Twitter and social media has brought us to where this happens too often and then too
Easily it is not the malicious intent of anyone in particular
So so he's mentioning anything. I mean, I know people who have large audiences should have like some
Understanding that when they say stuff and their followers like
Feel in power to do something that that might have some
like repercussions
But like I don't know. What did they even say that was so bad?
Like how could they have done it different say nothing I?
suppose
Yeah, like I think I mean even like I think no matter what RJ Palmer would have done like unique name of service would have like
Taken it as bad, right the fact that like RJ Palmer isn't pro NFT is a bad thing
right
Right, yeah, yeah
Yeah, so so for example, he hates that RJ Palmer like didn't do enough to like stop the campaign
But then later in the video he brings up that um that one black streamer that went into that like like the most racist town in the world
And like was talking to the Klans member and that Klans member was just telling him just awful shit
And he just let that slide
But he was kind of and but he framed the frames is as like
Cassana is an evil person for like criticizing that black guy who was letting this like Klans member say all his racist shit to him
Hmm, which is like do you not realize that like I mean the thing is that I'm basically saying that like
he's criticizing
RJ Palmer for like not doing enough to stop a
Harassment campaign, but he's not taking that same energy to like
This like this individual not like saying anything back to like a Klans member saying a bunch of racist shit to him, right?
right because
That video standard, right exactly he has like this double like the thing is that like and
This is kind of like a thing that like is very much pushed as an idea that lefties are like that lefties like
Present themselves as this like perfect being when I say like the majority of like lefties don't do that like majority of them
Like admit that their assholes and pieces of shit. I do that right like I'm like the untolerant left if you will right
But but the thing is that they keep like pushing this idea
So like anything like it like anything a lefty would do that's like considered negative or like push back against like a
protective class or whatnot is them being that they're instant. They're like
Participating and being a hypocrite, you know
So right so it's like a lefty. Oh
Lefties like things that are good, but in my opinion
one of them is something bad, so
It's so it's so weird because it's like it's like it's like you start starting from the point that like okay
Anything anything a lefty likes is something good, right? But I hate them
So let's so let's just but they're bad because not because they believe bad things or they want bad things
But because they fell short of the good things that they say that they like and that I should probably agree with them
about
But I hate them for it. Yeah, so yeah, so to clarify the video did not it did it did not fucking need all eight hours
Yeah, you repeat himself too much
He's reading too much
Pat had it out reads reading tweets. Yeah, right and like he did he said he did that
He did six months of research to prepare for this video and I'm saying just on Twitter
He should have done six more months because this shit is like fucking this, you know, this reminds me of that
I wrote you a five page letter if I had more time it would have been one
You know brevity is the soul of wit and I think if you maybe you should have worked harder
Not to make the video longer what to make it shorter
Where it won't be pat it's where it won't be a waste of time
So I have to I gotta go somewhere like real quick right now. Are you guys gonna still be recorded in 30 minutes?
minutes probably
30 an hour and a half in well like if you guys aren't recording by the time I get back whatever but
I mean you cut out this whole part or let's sink. Let's we didn't sink at the beginning
Right now on the count of three say sink one two three sink. Thank all right
We will probably still be going in half an hour. I think I
Wanted to ask about that the the black guy going into the racist area because that seemed interesting
Was that do you know what that is? Oh, no, I wasn't familiar with that
Okay, I guess I'll wait until cheesy. Did he say it was a video of Hassan talking to a racist
No, a black guy who got accosted by a racist guy or was that it was
What I assume is that Hassan watched a video in which a black guy goes to the most racist town in America and walks up to
Clans members, right seems like a bit that he's doing in that video. Yeah, and
Hassan
Criticized the black guy because of court like oh if you go there, of course something's gonna happen
And you need to do that for us criticize Hassan right? Okay, and but he didn't criticize the black guy for
Jumping into a lion's den I suppose. Mmm. I would like to see that video. That seems interesting. That seems like a weird bit
It is a weird bit. Yeah, I I'm not
Yeah, I don't know I have to see it. Oh man. I just shit
I just remembered a bunch of stuff that I did last night that I forgot about you. Oh do tell do tell
Spill the beans. No, I smoked a cigarette. Oh, no
My god forgot I smoked a cigarette last night give
God's gonna be angry at me
All the cigarette comedians are laughing
They've been waiting
Darn, I forgot. Oh man. Yeah, I thought we were going home
I remember we stopped at a at a bar that I forgot we went to
Who did you go out with so what was what was going on? It was my um, it was a
My friend, uh, well on the internet. He's known as Dwoob. Oh, yeah
Yeah, and when I had not seen him in a while. I went over to his house to catch up
With another friend that they're the three of us had gone to college together. So
Yeah, that's that's that's and they they led you astray they made you they gave you a cigarette
They throw they totally did they liquored you up and gave you a cigarette and you just puffed away
Oh, I could not consent to smoke that cigarette. I could not give informed enthusiastic consent
Uh
Well, I'm unholy I'm sully
Yeah gross you got to smoke a holy water cigarette. I don't I don't smoke anymore
But I guess some I guess if I drink sometimes I do and I gotta put holy water in a vape and I think I'm okay
That's how you undo it. Oh
Yeah, I guess you could do that. Can you just vape water? Does it just turn into steam?
There's a break your or that break your what's what's the mechanics of a vape pen?
So that does it just is a heat thing and it just yeah vaporizes the stuff. Yes, it's a tiny nozzle
It's an induction coil what there is is there is a wire with their high resistance. There's a resistance
There's a an electricity resistant wire that is in a coil and the coil goes around a piece of cotton
Which is called the wick and the wick absorbs liquid
And so the portion of the cotton that is between the coil gets heated by the inductance of the current and
That and that vaporizes the liquid that it has absorbed
That's how it works. So yeah, I guess you could probably do it with water it might holy water
Potentially once it once it went dry it would start to burn
So you have to be careful with that
Yeah, you could do it just you could vape holy steam. No problem. You know what I'm sure people have done it
Yeah, I ordered Chinese food while cheesy was talking so that'll be that'll be here in 10 minutes
for breakfast
It's it's it's past noon already for me. Oh, yeah, I guess although I've only been up since 11
Um
To Ben at September
Yeah, that means this Halloween
true, I guess it it literally like the day after I moved
It went from being like hot summer to being like now. It's now. It's cool out
The season changed at the very at the very moment. Oh
Man, my new room is so much nicer than my old one my old one sucks so bad
It was so disgusting you saw the yeah, I saw I saw your old room
You really didn't want me to go in there, but I had to look I had to know where Ben saying I didn't want you to see it
Because it's embarrassing and it's gross and I even I know like this is bad and it reflects poorly on me that I live here
But now in your brand-new room
The cockroaches they're they're they're polished. They're they're gleaming. I did see I did see an ant
I never had ants at the old place. I did see one ant, which is a bit concerning. I hope I don't see any more of those
Ants aren't so bad. I well, I do. I mean they're they're
What are they gonna do pick you up with their like strength? It was a bit. It was one of the big ants. I don't like that
I mean, whatever. I guess they're just a
The fact of life, I mean if you find their ant hill you can just pour molten metal down there
The old making art sculpture the old place did not have cockroaches, but it had mice everywhere. I
Never said well
I never saw a mouse in my room until I was moving and then as I was packing boxes in and around the time
I was recording the video. I did finally see one mouse in my room and I was like, oh there it is there
There's the it's been there the whole time. It might have been
I don't you know what I think it was because the last couple weeks
I was there my friggin old landlord was sending these work guys in to do like renovations and they cut
The radiator out of my wall and there was just a hole in the floor and the ceiling where the radiator tube
I think the mouse might have crawled in through the friggin hole in the floor that the radiator used to connect to
That might have been how it got in just at the very end there
That's just a theory
Anyway, that was gross I saw that as shit
That's the one thing it's pests in pests in the kitchen. I can ignore them pests in my room
That's what if they crawl on me while I'm asleep
So I didn't didn't like you got to get spiders in there to catch them
There were some there were unironically having a spider in your room is good because yeah
The most annoying thing is things flying and things crawling and spiders just sit in the corner
I what yeah, I was putting up a tapestry
I was putting up my cop killers tapestry actually and I was reaching up into the corner
And there was a little spider in up in the ceiling corner and it's a hot tall ceiling
So I hadn't noticed it before and I briefly considered killing it. I was like no, it's probably gonna
Remove more pests than killing this spider would
Would do I could remove the one spider now or I could let it remove future small insects for me
So I just let it be. Yeah, so it's a guard. Yeah, I think it was the right. I think it was the right choice
I'm hungover we'll hungover and I feel a little bit bad, but not so bad. I'm recovering
I ordered some more I'm almost out of corn fiber for gummies. I've almost used up the last of it
I need to get shelf space. I need I need to claim some shelf space
For my stuff there are shelves down in the kitchen and I think they are labeled with like previous roommates names
And I think if I maybe if I hurry if I rush I can claim some of those throughout some of that person's old stuff
And take that shelf space for myself. They get a lot of shit. We got a lot of gummy shit
They need yeah kitchen real estate for
Yeah, could you padlock it could you install a little padlock?
No, these are the shelves here. Well, the shelves I'm talking about are just they don't have doors on them
They're just at the end of a little like quarter. There's just like some open shelves
Which is kind of bad because I would sort of prefer them to be sealed away. So as like
You know like a bag of sugar. I'd rather be inside something to further protect against like flies getting into it or whatever
I guess put a bag of sugar in a tupperware. Yeah, I just have to make sure that they're sealed pretty pretty tight. That's all
But I'm
Feeling good
Feel good. I lit. It's it's improved my mood
I think not to live in a dingy in a dingy cave and it's stained fucking dirty
Falling apart piece of shit
Well, I'm glad. I am glad. I feel happy
I guess we should talk about I mean, do you want to say anything about the tricksy quitting YouTube?
I feel like we should acknowledge it. Oh, we already did but like I don't know what it what it my thoughts on it is
She's gonna come back. Yeah
With some like retiring the channel. I
Mean, obviously she wasn't making a lot of money a lot of views from those videos. Yeah, I didn't really watch the video
I somebody summarized it
What I guess it's just like yeah, no, I mean, this isn't you this is yeah
She she's she has no intentions of getting a different job like a more like traditional job
So I'm sure some sort of internet thing is gonna happen. Well, she said she'll be working working for mint salad now
Doing what I don't editing her videos. I guess I
Can't imagine how that pays for anything but
Whatever
Yeah, she will she will figure out that yeah, a real job is actually hard and
That YouTube money was easier and she will she will be back
The thing the thing with yeah, that the mint thing is not gonna work out ASC presents is not gonna
Pay the bills that whole thing is gonna fall. I give it to I give it two months. I give it two months before that whole living situation
Implodes and then she'll be back
But man, what I just want to say what a what a stupid
The whole the vlog is thing. I think that like probably I hadn't not on my radar at all
I had no idea what's been going on
so I had I had seen the announcement that she was gonna do the month of vlogs and then an announcement at the end and I think that I
Think I don't know it seems to me like the vlog is was actually sort of a last-ditch attempt to like generate interest to like get
The channel back on track
So I think that maybe if that had happened the announcement would not have been I'm quitting but because it did not work
She quit but like if so what a
Vlog is was not good one. She didn't even stick to it. She did not post a video every day
She missed several days and two like the stuff she posted was like the laziest like most slapdash stuff like there was nothing
There was nothing impressive like it was it was not much of a
Hail Mary, you know, I mean
It's it's been obvious that her heart is not in it
Has been not in it for a very long time. That's I mean, yeah, the last thing she was excited about
I think was the doing rap gigs and she did one or two. Yeah
You mean the real the real life ones. Yeah, they're going to a real life and doing a rap or two. Yeah
And as I said, yeah
She's I mean, she's clearly more about she's clearly more interested in
Wrapping that which is fun. That's fun
Yeah, whatever. Yeah, it's just old news like the the the I'm quitting seems more like clickbait
Than yeah, it doesn't seem like it's an like a notable occurrence. I
I
Yeah, I would have I guess I would agree with that
It's it's just sort of a what do you what do you what would I call it? It's just sort of a it's just sort of saying out loud
Yeah, what has kind of just been
Implicit for a while. I guess that's true
Yeah, okay. Well, I think it's funny. I had a good chuckle over it
when the video dropped and
Yeah
Someone someone said I think people thought we were gonna talk a lot about it
Somebody said like oh Ben's gonna Ben's gonna spite. Yeah, the fight so much for the notes for the notes for this episode
I don't have much of my own, but I did type Ben is gonna talk about Trixie. That's all I've got on my notes
Well, I was assuming you would like have a big haha. I like I do I think I think you've already done that
I think your your ha ha has already
Yeah, come and gone. Yeah, there's not yeah, I've said everything that I really have to say about it at this point
I just uh
Do I did want to acknowledge I did want to acknowledge to anyone who was wondering? Yes, I did see the video. Yes
It is funny. Yes, I did
Kill her it I did this is my doing. Yes
So, you know good good week good week for me
Did I really film that video in the same I filmed that yeah
Yeah, and you film the videos and I moved into a good house. Oh my god. It's a red
I mean moving is a whole big thing. You've probably been like
Going all over the place for the past few days
Yeah, so it feels like a lot of stuff has happened, which it has it has for me
Nothing happened. No, it's fine. A lot a lot of
I'm amazed. I'm amazed that so much. I
genuinely thought that like
the recording had been
Last week and I had talked about it already on the show, but I guess I did not so that's very
Funny, I'm watching my my door-dash delivery driver
I'm watching the little red dot crawl across the the Google Maps and approach my house
He's he's three minutes away, and you know what? I think I lost. Oh my god. No. No. Oh, no
I accidentally ordered the tofu. I meant to get the chicken, but I ordered the tofu. I'm so stupid
I'm such a fucking dweeb
I don't like tofu. It's mediocre
This is this is this is a karma Ben. It's me. I'm trying to see ah
So the soul
Know what that means
Well, you pay
All right, he is he's out. He's okay. He's he's almost here. He's outside my door
He's surely probably getting out of the car right now
He's oh my god, I'm attention
Do you hear the footsteps? I do not I do not hear the footsteps
I'm waiting for the little I'm waiting for the map to update and say deliver
I don't want to start like a thing and then have you know I gotta go eat I gotta go do that
You know what open the door. I think okay, I've got to go grab it from downstairs. I'll be back in a second
Okay, I'm back
What else
I
Guess I'm
If there's anything to talk about is that I'm trying to get more productive and it's difficult not
Shitting on yourself. Oh, yeah, you're always you're always trying to be productive. What's up with that?
Because we're always always trying to do things and I'm trying to be pro
Actionate the pro duck the product inators the productionators. Yeah
Because like September in my head was like, okay
September is gonna be my
Working on Clarissa getting that done
I still have these commissions to do. I still have a few load of ghosts books to send off
That have been returned and I just haven't got around to those things and like
my my default like reaction to wasted time is to shit on myself and
to be like very
Like realist but like harsh God, it's so it's so mid. It's so mid. It sucks. I hate
And and it's so difficult to like balance
your your realist like production
like
Like your work ethic stuff, you've got to be serious. You've got to be sensible
you've got to treat the work with respect and not slack off, but I can't like
Depress myself because that's also bad
It's difficult trying to figure out the the perfect balance because I want to when you say depress yourself
What do you mean by that?
to to like, I don't know
trigger depressive triggered triggered
mood by like so I
by by
Like giving myself a hard time instead of being more optimistic about doing better in the future
I feel like if I just say every time like oh, well, I didn't work today, but I'll try next day
I'll do better later. I feel like that it feels a little too insincere
I I
Gravitate to wanting to be more harsh like no, this is not acceptable. You got to do better
But I don't want to hurt myself. I don't want to bully myself
Because that has led to bad things you would bring what you don't want to
You don't want to do what rubber Ross did to that entity artist and make her kill herself
Yeah, even though she's fine. Yeah, I mean what I mean, I don't think we mentioned that
That nobody actually killed themselves right that whole thing. Well, it was just a potential
Yeah, nothing nothing actually happened. Nothing actually happened
Just this girl stopped posting and unique it was like what is she killed herself though? What if that happened?
It would be said that would be fucked up. Yeah
It'll be very fucked up wouldn't be Ross's fault, but yeah, it would be pretty fucked up. Yeah
So, I don't know I still I
I've I've made measures to make my my work day more like structured and in a way that I
Can like work with instead of like
You know when you wake up late and like some of the day is gone
Mm-hmm. Oh, I have less hours to work
This sucks and then it makes it harder to get out of bed
Yeah, then it would have been if you got up earlier the day's already wasted
Yeah, there's like things that it's like, okay, it doesn't matter when I start but from when I start
I have to do at least three hours then take a break for an hour
And then you know, whenever I end up wherever I end up, that's the end of my day
It's not like I'm not bound by the Sun. I can I can work around the Sun. It's fine
Yes, but but but it feels like even though you have the same, you know
14 or 16 hours awake or whatever, you know
It feels if it starts late if it starts late and ends late
It feels like less than if it starts early and ends. Yeah, and then it definitely feels amazing when you happen to wake up
And just get out of bed for I don't know you get out of bed to pee and then you're like, you know what this time
I'm not gonna go back into bed
I'm gonna do stuff and then it like it's your normal breakfast time
But you already had breakfast and you've done some work already. It's like wow
So good like it's the perfect thing
Getting out of bed is the hard part, but I think
Not shitting on yourself for not getting out of bed is also an important thing, right?
I mean when you do that you I'm trying to make it so that like no matter when I get out of bed the day starts
Even if I like open my phone, I look at a video that I don't even like looking at
So instead of for two hours and then get out of bed. I that's when the day starts
I mean, there's there's something to be said
For like if you
Recognize that like you feel better
When you wake up early
There's something to be said for okay. Well since I know that about myself. I should you know ensure that I wake up early
That makes me feel better. I guess it's also it's fine to also be like
Well, I should try to feel better even if I don't do that
I guess it's different two different approaches to solving those different approaches basically
The idea that I've been that I've been trying to work in it with is like
um
Having a schedule, but adjusting based on how I react to it
If it's going to lead to burnout, maybe I change
an aspect of it for the next day
And if it's too lenient maybe rain it in a bit and I don't know I'm just trying things
But I'm ultimately not getting a lot of work done
um
and it
Feels bad. Hmm. Can't really get away from the fact that it feels bad
that um
I don't know. I'm just I'm just am slow at creating things
Hmm
I'm slow at getting into a work groove
And it's difficult forcing myself to act in ways that I'm not used to
sure
um
That's my conundrum. Can you help do you think?
You said okay, so you're you're you say you're slow. Is that like
Do you think that is uh, uh
Like what do you
You mean like what are you stupid? Yeah, I mean is that like you mean just like when you work you do it
Slowly or do you mean you take a long time to
No, it's not that I'm slow to to doing something. It's not that that I'm slow particularly. It's that
um, I get very impatient and very antsy very often
So I could work for 40 minutes before I am like, ah, you got to do something else
I think that's normal
It's normal, but like it would be nice if I could work for two hours
And then that's more like that's a nicer rounder number is more you can do with the two hour window
But like if it turns out that my my
Break thing is like every 40 minutes. I need to take a break
I could try that. I think I should try that like more deliberately. I feel like yeah
I feel like if you find that that's the natural
Rhythm that you fall into
It might be worth. Yeah, just trying to structure your day and your time around that pattern
Uh
I think too large and there's yeah, there's something there's something to be said for just like knowing yourself
And rather than trying to like fix your
tendencies
Just try and yeah go with the flow. So yeah, go go with like structure myself
Structure my work day and my plans around the way that I naturally would do things
Yeah, as long as it doesn't mean I do nothing
So yeah, that I think I should do more frequent breaks
and less length
It's always sucks when you go on a break and you're like, ah, I'm on a break
Oh, it's over. No. No, I want the break to be an hour long two hours maybe
And then it's like well, then I'm working for 40 minutes and having a two hour break in between
It's like that's not gonna that's not gonna work long term. I need to change that
I need to be more
Gooder
right
Who doesn't
Sorry to not to be off topic, but
I feel good that when I think about the fact that I smoked that cigarette last night
I don't think like oh, it was good. I want another one. I think yeah, ill gross. Yeah, feels that is good. Yeah
You were fine. Would you say you were addicted? I mean most people who smoke I would say get a bit addicted at the very least
Yeah for a period there. Yeah, I would get some crave. I would crave it like a big oof a cigarette would feel good right now
I or like oh, I um
I want to go do that and I mean I would do it
There were periods, uh, where I would smoke basically every day although. I never was like a pack a day
Smoker I would generally smoke. Um, maybe a few a day. Maybe like
Six or eight at most, uh in a day. So I would say I had a bit of a
Yeah, I mean if you're getting cravings for it, you're a little addicted. So yeah for a while there
Not anymore though
Uh, it's literally the pandemic
The pandemic just made me not want to leave my house. So I didn't go and buy cigarette
Thanks, covet
Thank you, covet. Thank you. Kobe. You've done so much for us. Although
Damn, I saw an article
Wow, this tofu sucks
I saw an article that was like
Hey, so covet has made everybody sicker
Everybody has like worse
Lung and heart and brain issues now the whole population is sicker and they compared it like it's it says though everybody in the world
Took up smoking
It's like it's like it's like the entire population just started smoking cigarettes and now they are all smokers like that's the
The the the the damage to just health in general
That covet has done to the population. Maybe um aggregate
Do they mean like people who got the the pandemic the the the virus like before vaccines and survived, you know, I don't know
Yeah, I think there any difference. I would imagine that yeah
It probably is worse for people who got it before they were vaccinated worse for people who have gotten it multiple times
I'm sure that the damage is proportional to like how much covet have you had
uh
Because it's occasionally i'm like wow that was a long pause
Maybe I have covet brain fog, but I don't freak out about it for some reason. I'm just so like you know
I mean, I've always been kind of dumb
I've always been kind of slow. I freaked out about covet brain fog
The fact of the matter is that yeah, lots lots of things
cause what might be called brain damage
Uh, and such as using twitter such as using twitter such as eating soy
um
I'm doing right now. I'm getting brain fog. Just just just from the smell of this delicious tofu
and um
Yeah, I I when it yeah, sometimes I can't think of something and I think oh god is a brain fog
But then I'm like I I always was like that. I always had those moments. It's not weird
It's not a it's I don't think covet has changed my thought patterns in any meaningful way
So yeah normie, but like if it did
Then I mean I'd work with it
I I mean it's sort of
I'd have to work with it
But like it's the sort of thing that happens to
Most people at some age time in their life. Maybe just covet like oh if I'm like older
I get to like 60 and that starts happening because of age
um
Uh, the covet brain fog would have made it happen much earlier. Well, I mean that was 60 year olds are not completely out of
You know out of they're not completely palace. Yeah, I can do it
I can do it. There's no there's nothing to freak out about I suppose at least not for me
But it is a good excuse. It is a good excuse where I'm like sitting there and thinking
I gotta think of to I gotta do a work
I can't do it covet brain fog probably
Gotta be that fog. I I had you know what I had thoughts
Like that even before covet I would think like I would be sitting there and I would be thinking like
Why can't I do anything? Why am I so bad at everything? Why am I stupid?
Why am I such a failure? Is it am I just am I just dumb? Is there just something wrong with me?
um
So, you know
Now I can blame covet at least. Yeah
So um
Uh, I don't know that's really what's been going on in my mind. I I uh
The only thing I've been consistent with which is good is that my my workout regime regimen has been done
in
Like three times a week. That's good consistently since the beginning of july. So I'm not I'm not slipping
hmm
that's very good
Regardless of how good the workout is
I'm doing it when I have to do it and that's uh good
You know one of the friends I was hanging out with last night
Told me that they uh started a they started seeing a therapist. They got done. Um, I think it was it was well butrin
I think it was well butrin. They got on some kind of
Some kind of antidepressant medication and they said they started
They've started exercising. They've done a regimen and uh, I mean they had they had like just started so they couldn't really
I couldn't really evaluate like oh, yeah, they seem to be it seems to be improving their
life or whatever
But uh, I don't know
for people
Yeah, I mean exercise is good generally just to move your body around but um,
I don't know whether my workout is like strenuous enough
To be a very huge, but it's definitely a positive any any it's definitely a 80 20 even even a little bit is like a big
Yeah, yeah, it's it's it's good in that way physically
But it's also good knowing that I'm keeping up with that even if I'm like
Not creative some of the time I'm like, uh
I got I still have this lord of ghosts that has been sent back
I haven't done anything. It's still in like the the the packaging that they sent it back in like the
They ripped open the envelope and everything's fucked up
And I just didn't want to open it and figure out how to send it back
I've got terrible news terrible news one of the lord of ghosts a button eyes came off of his sheet
And I moved no he lost one of I still I have the the button
I mean came it was
It was hand stitched all every button. I know so there's this likely that will happen because it's okay a perfect sewer
It's okay
Because I minted him as an NFT and so even though he's been destroyed. I still nothing has changed
I still have the asset. I still control the asset. No, it's fine
um
What were you talking about? Oh, yeah, I have not been working out. I have been
Dieting I've been eating pretty clean and I have lost a lot of weight
And I'm I'm back down to the weight that I was when I was working out like two years ago
Even though I have not been so I guess I'm just skinny now
I mean, I'm not that skinny, but
Skinny by my standards
That's good. No, that's gooder. Mm-hmm
I just do this I have I just
Cycled between like weigh in like 160 and then I'll go up to like 200 and I'll lose it weight down to like 160
And I'm at the low point in my cycle and I hope I hope to keep it that way
I hope to hope to stay here this time
Well, it's time to go back up if you're at the lowest point. That's how curves work. Mm-hmm over time
It has to fluctuate the same amount
It's an infinite spiral. It's an infinite spiral just like DNA
You need to put on 40 pounds of just muscle
honestly
Honestly, absolutely. Honestly. I do need to do that. Yeah
That would rule
Eat a raw steak while bench pressing or whatever. Whatever it is you muscle heads do
All I would need all I would need to do all I would need to get back to lifting and I would need to just eat
More proteins. I already I already eat a lot of protein
I'm not keto anymore, but I do eat meat
Oh, just meat makes up a pretty high percentage of my diet anyway. So
I think I'm good on that
I realized I I have like a huge five pound bag of protein powder that I've like barely
used so
I just start using that
um
Ugh
I'm so disappointed. I'm so disappointed in this in this food anymore. I finish it
Sad just you save it for me. I'll come get it. Okay
Um
Uh, what?
We've been going for two hours. Okay. I'm trying to think if there's anything else
That I wanted to talk about. Oh shit
I didn't I didn't tweet ask pcp
this week
Should I do that now? It may as well. All right
I feel like people
We're not gonna miss out on that much. No, not really. I meant to
I I said I would uh fix the
The speak pipe after I moved well, I have moved and I haven't done it
But I mean I just didn't hear about two days
So this this week I will try and uh and do that
Someone just
Someone just added
the pcp account
And said fool. Oh wait, they were adding
My meaty last week saying I didn't fix the voicemails yet. They said
Phobos Roblo says fool at me
Through um
Oh, I guess I can say um, uh my runescape adventure
I have been mining iron still, but I'm very close to level 85 mining
I'm like
eight
Or seven hours of mining away from getting 85 mining, which means I'll be able to mine runeitor
Which is the best or because it's blue-ish. It's like teal
It's a teal blue
And I will be able to I'm gonna go to the wilderness. I'm gonna see what it's like
Trying to get a single piece of ore and I might make a video about that momentous occasion
Little follow-up from the the previous one
That's my runescape lore
It's it's so fun. Yes. It's so interesting. Yes, right. That's correct runescape
Sorry, I'm trying to think of what to say and the ask pcp message
We're hate ask pcp. We're almost done recording. Sorry if we miss your message this week lull, but reply here
And we'll read your
post
Okay, thank you post haste
Yeah, oh shit, I should have said that I should have said post haste, but I
Okay, that's great. Uh, it looks like shit my message sucks. Oh, you know what?
You know what does blow about this house though? Uh, the internet's actually quite bad
I'm actually I'm actually glad that it has not cut out there
I get pretty long periods where like the internet just kind of crafts out and stops working
So I I have to figure out
Is that an improvable problem or is it just like the
Could you could you do the thing with the internet boosters? Yeah, I might yeah the wi-fi extender I
Yeah, I'm gonna try and set that up and see if it uh fixes the problem
But yeah at the moment my internet is not very reliable. So I'm glad that it has not fucked up
this call at least
Oh, yeah, it's probably
Improvable, uh, we'll see
You know what? Let me see if we had any messages from last week that we didn't
Read
I think
Yeah, we oh we got another I think the we got another uh art mail from new
Here, uh
Yeah, I think this is
I think this is a sequel
No, this is the same no, this is the same one
Isn't it the the the nose i'm gonna look at it again anyway
uh
No, this yes. No, this is the same one new is uh doing a bit for the dojin the dojin is coming along by the way kaiju did two more
Pages oh, I think I posted them in the pcp server. So you saw them
Oh wait kaiju's them
Yeah, the ones that I posted that were by kaiju
Let me have a look
Oh, they are
Yeah, yeah, they were they were they were more similar to the other thing
I thought see that's why I thought kaiju would be a good replacement because they kind of have a sort of similar style
See you can almost not even tell them apart. Uh, that was uh, yeah
But uh a few weeks ago. I was saying like ah, fuck it have different art styles
But it is nice if they were if they're like yeah
The the the anime vibe is similar. Yeah. Well, I think drinking moth has done a pretty a pretty good job of matching
the style as well
New will not match at all and that's okay
Uh simsie that's okay by me simsie's page. Uh looks
Actually closer than I expected
He he got more
He got he got close to seeing the simsie one. Is it is it just a sketch right now? It's just it's just a sketch
I can show you if you want actually yeah DM me or put in the pcp chat. Uh, where did he post that here we go
It's only yeah, it's only partially
Can I might even copy this, uh
It might be too big. Oh no, it's posting there it is
Oh
I think I did see this somewhere. Maybe I didn't I don't remember posting it but uh
Yeah, it does it's got the the chibi ear. Yeah, chibi ear than simsie usually does. Yeah, it's very nice
It's pretty it's pretty good. I mean it looks it's good. It looks good. It's pretty close
Yeah, close enough only only half the page is done, but like it looks really it looks cute
But um, yeah, I mean girl. Yeah, I went I picked kaiju first because I thought he was a pretty close match in terms of style to ed
But uh, it don't really I mean he's he's taken too long
Uh, it would never get done if I just let him do the whole thing. So
Oh, well
Uh
Anything done is better than anything complete is better than anything not complete. You know what I'm saying
Yes, yeah
It sure is good to have complete things completed
I think I heard that from I think I heard that from brian leo mali, but I don't think it's an original
I think he was quoting someone else
On his tumblr his blog or something when he said the best thing you can do is make scott pilgrim
He said uh on the subject on the subject of like finishing things versus like being a being a progress
Yeah, a procrastinator or like a perfectionist who's like
You know, oh, I never finish anything because it's never good enough. I never finish it and he said
Well, anything complete is is automatically better than anything that is isn't complete. So if you don't finish something, it's worthless
Uh, yeah, still still hard to like really feel that sometimes though
Ah, yeah, like I I know it so well and it's like yes, of course
It's better that I do it, but I don't want it to suck. I want to do it good
I want to make a nice drawing sometime. Right sure sure
Uh, but like unironically the the half of the course is a gun smoke
But drawing is hard you try and you try and it still doesn't look good, but that's okay. That's okay. That's okay
Rittman is so smart. Yeah, he's he said I down to earth wisdom
He's got a humble
With mine humble brain
Okay, I think that we got a
Stop me if we read this question last week
from Rob
Right now I'm having issues with my parents being unsupportive of my lifestyle
Have you ever experienced something similar? And if so, how did you cope?
Were you able to get through to them eventually? I'm having a hard time with this
Do we do we read that one last week? I don't think we read that one. No, okay
Parents being unsupportive of your lifestyle
I guess
I mean the closest thing
I would say when I was like
Shortly out of college
My dad did not understand why I was not getting a job
Why I was not out you know pounding the pavement
Pounding the pavement looking for you know 40 hours a week regular regular employment
Uh, so he would be very frustrated with me over that stuff
And how did I cope with it? Honestly, I just kind of had to
Placate him as best I could because I was living under his roof. So like I couldn't
Just tell him to fuck off
uh, I just kind of had to
Just kind of had to grin and bear it and do what he said for a while and then eventually I moved out
And now I don't have to do what he says anymore
Um, yeah, yeah, I never really had a lot of
Like non-supportiveness from my parents, but I have like had like yeah, you should probably try to do this
We'd like it if you did that. Yeah, and I'm like, um, I'm trying
I think at the time
When I told them that I was making money off patreon
They stopped caring so much because they're they're they're their worries were mostly that I wasn't able to support myself
I'm like, I'm I'm bringing money in don't worry about it
So they don't really mind too much
Yeah, I'll
Well, we got a
We got a question about um, what do you do if your parents are unsupportive of your lifestyle? How do you cope with it?
Talk to them or don't we don't talk what?
I you you're unable to escape. I'm not sure if rob lives with his parents or not. He's not specified
I mean the the hi cheesy welcome back. Hi. Hello. I'm back. Yes
I mean, I feel like if if you're living with your parents, this is
the sort of situation where
You would need to find a way to cope because you kind of scape them
If you can't yeah, you're gonna have to if you really do a lot of like find ways to hide what you do
I mean, I would just try everything in your power to move out
It yeah, if um
Yeah, if it comes down to like a just a fundamental difference of values like they
Think you should be doing something else and you don't think so. Yeah
The some might be that the only thing to do is you got to just go on your own and do something else
And if it's not possible, I would say don't worry about lying to them in the meantime
Don't worry about lying through your teeth. Just so that they don't like ruin
I would say lying is you're doing I would say lying is acceptable
Lying until you can get out of there and then getting out of there
If if if it can't be resolved
Don't worry about being like secretive. I would say
I would say I don't know if it's like
If it's I don't know what it is like
What does he mean by lifestyle does he mean? I don't know because he's
Gay or a furry or something like that or just friends or like
Or does he or does he mean like not not aligned with the parents or maybe that or just
Or is he is he like a neat or something or he doesn't have a job or something like that
Or he's he wants to be one thing and they think like no, you should be going to school
You should get a job or something like that
Uh, it sort of depends
On what what exactly depends but largely
um
if you're at the if you're
unable to
gain independence
Uh, try not to like aggravate them. I suppose if they are likely to throw you out or like burn a bridge or like
Cause you problems you you have you have to guard your uh connection to uh
Support what what oh fucking my alarm's going off. I mean you you have to do
You have to do what you have to do in order to ensure that you will not be thrown out on the street, right?
Look, uh, maybe
I don't know. Don't don't not consider maybe killing your parents as an option to like that can be on the table as well
You know, I don't know. I feel like you're getting trouble for that
Like if you if you want to like, you know, it's all about you being comfortable. You know, they they're in the way of that. Well
Like they they turn the channel when you want to watch some things like it's my turn for the tv
You you you got to do something
My parents can't just watch tv at another time. You have to destroy that
My parents don't approve of my lifestyle. They don't understand why I watch all of quintin reviews
nine hour long, uh
disney channel sitcom retrospectives
They think it's cringe and I can't why can I explain?
That it's important to us zoom or zoom or culture
Um, look look mom. I know I know pan pizza just fired me from being his podcast editor. Okay. I'm in between jobs right now
All right, so you can't I can't let you any drug money this week
My parents are stoop. My parents are fucking loony lefties and they don't think I should be minting nfts
Uh, they uh, have an agenda
What's
Yeah, what's the nft? Who wants his nfts bought up? I'm moving the fuck out of this shithole
They're trying I just tell it
They're trying to bully me. They're trying to bully me into suicide for making nft
They're trying to cry bully me. They're taking away my don't they
My parents won't stop going on twitter and
Trying to cancel me
Making up grooming allegations. They just they they think it's funny
Um, oh, yeah, where the damn
Gosh, yeah, I get have we answered this guy's question
In all seriousness, if you're like gary trans you should move the fuck out of there as soon as possible if they're against that lifestyle
You're not gonna
You're not gonna live comfortably and eventually like hiding is gonna make you go fucking insane
If that's if that should yeah, if that's the issue then yes, I would I would think although I mean
Yeah, if you can't support god, you know
If you can't support yourself and you gotta do what you gotta do and if like being openly whatever is gonna get you
Homeless, you know, you might have to be sneaky
Uh to preserve your to preserve your access to vital resources. You got to treat it like a survival game
Yeah, you can't get you can't let your uh, your bars go too low. Mm-hmm. Uh-huh. Mm-hmm
Exactly
Look, that's that's the the extent of that. I think the perfect strategy would be just don't pay the irs any taxes
That's the advice I find like three other guys who are like zealots
And at celebrities like move in with them
And then just same save money for an RV and I think you'll be
Wrapping is hot right now
It will if you need practice you can practice by um rapping along with Lincoln Park and that
Your skills videos make videos where you talk about the MCU
You know and anything maybe maybe make a maybe make a podcast where you talk about sheatholk every week
Listen, you're in in life. Your parents are the ultimate big money connections. You must you must preserve them
You must preserve them at any cost
Uh, all right enough of that
uh
let's um
something something
Sai monday says
I know you update spotify before I know you mentioned the f cap
Maybe you can make a new account or try a different distributor. I use anchor fm same copy spotify
It's simple upload to auto distribute spotify
Signed one of the fans who use the spotify, uh
I don't want to make a different account
I mean, I guess we I guess we could because we just make it like a procrastinator spotify account two
Because the first one hit its episode limit two
Crescinators because there's two of us honestly. Maybe that is the thing to do. Oh what a hassle
The two crass
There's they're they're crossing. They're two
Yeah
You know what it's true. Um, okay
Sanky c warby seedle says how does the guest system work?
Is there an open invite to select people whoever shows up was in or is there something more to it? Um
It's it's pretty much just like if you've been a guest before yeah
Previous guests like a previous guests are mostly welcome to come back on if they
want to
um, I mean
Never paint and asha were on the other day and that was just never paint
Just asked me if they could come on because he wanted to talk about tulkin
And I said, okay
And I kind because I kind of knew those guys like I'd seen them around and talked to them on discord and on twitter and stuff before
So I I already kind of knew them
Basically, it's just if we know you
And you ask to come on we'll usually say yes, and that's and that's and that's how I got on this episode
Oh, yeah, you just said hey ben. I want to talk about fucking unique namesaurus is a stupid video
And I said that's easier for me than watching it. So yes
Yeah
We're all just shitting on it already
And uh and ben server. Oh, that's right. Well, like I could extend that's right also helps me like
flush out
My ideas I because I might make a video responsive is
um, I'm on the fence about it, but
Because I've been so fucking yeah, I mean it doesn't sound like a terrible idea
Um, yeah, I mean I was gonna name it something like I I watched this eight hour long video
So you don't that would be actually actually that's a good I like that. I think that's
a good idea
It's a good. It's a good title. Yeah, it has the right attitude. I'm the drama critic
I watched an eight hour video. I'm cheesy manfredo. I watch
Um, that's good
The next question was will it's also likely catch up to one piece or will he wait until two piece to do so?
I will catch up
I'll get around to it. I've been busy
As I've two pieces bikini bottom
What it's spongebob. Oh, yeah, they that's when they that's when the crew meets spongebob
And uh, honestly, I love this little guy. Honestly, why not honestly?
Why why not?
Oh, I can picture it in my head. Luffy meets spongebob. He's like, oh, I love this little guy
You want to be our you want to be our crew chef and then sanji starts crying like but I thought I was
They just have krabby pan. Yeah. Oh my god. Sanji versus spongebob like like spongebob versus neptune
Like it's funny though because like the spongebob is like
Canonically like very small compared to a human. Yeah. I mean, he's the size of a sponge
He's the size of a sponge
So it'd be like like sanji and his big chef thing and then it would be like like in a fishbowl next to him making krabby patties
It'd be it'd be funny or if he it's my god is also stronger than sanji and like
He observes the spot in the in the monster tree as
Sandy and and sanji have to get into like a karate kick fight with each other. They're equally mad
Wait and then and then
Spongebob punches luffy and luffy absorbs it because he's made of rubber and then luffy gomu gomu gatling guns
Spongebob, but spongebob just absorbs all the blows because he's a sponge. You're like, oh, we can't beat each other. We're at a stalemate
And he's and he's all like wait a second
Uh, spongebob is the key here. He's gonna be the guy who's gonna take on um
Who of our fallen mucumo as they as they enter the fucking celestial dragons territory?
This is
Actually, this is funny. I almost I almost wanted one piece right?
One sponge piece one sponge
I'll feel cringe one bob. Um, oh, this is gonna make me feel cringe if I don't do it
If this episode comes out and I didn't do this I almost want to draw it and then uh, and then and then luffy beats up plankton
Is all you I you're trying to take away that krabby fatty formula. SpongeBob needs that
Plankton
I think I think I think I think not me and usa would be not me and usa would fight plankton
And plankton would be in some sort of giant robot or something. I think plankton would be like taken in by by buggy's screw
I think uh, zora would fight sandy because sandy is like black coated and all like the human medium
And uh
Black people so he he zora only fights like darkest way majority of his fights
He fought king and he fought I forget what number he was but the guy who could turn himself into number one
He was number one
He fought king and he fought number one cock cock is is white for sure. So that's an exception, but um
I
And
Because um
And I don't know about that
And zora was always talking about wanting to remove usa. I remember there was a whole tick that where someone explains
That zora is
Wait, what is what is he saying about removing? Yeah, that's like
But you remember when usa was he always jokes about us up was um
Like left the crew. Yeah, um because they were gonna get rid of the going Mary in water seven, right?
Yeah, and zora was like the like everyone was like no soap. Don't go and zora was like
Like like if you're a man be a man and like like actually act on this instead of whining
If you're gonna leave the crew leave, you know, that's the sort of stance. He took he was he was he was he was
He almost he almost called him boy, but he but he uh, but he restrained himself. Yeah, and then and then usa was like, you know what?
You're right. I'm leaving
And and like even luffy was like no don't go but zora was like no this is how the pirate's life is a pirate's life for me
Maybe it takes a drink
Said it
I think my favorite my favorite little joke is when um, they get usa back
Like after he apologized and luffy like stretches out to grab him
And he's back on the ship zora. I love the little thought bubble that zora has where he's like damn
I guess I gotta stop saying it
Because he started saying it like after just casually around
But but once usa was back, he's like like he's not mad enough to say it in front of usa
Yeah, zora zoro's uh
Zoro's a big uh, he's a big free speech guy
He thinks uh, you know, you're thinking it. You might you might as well say it
Everybody thinks it is not even japanese would be on the jargon podcast
No
Um, I can see it fucking. Yeah
Where where was I?
Uh, uh, what how do we even get on this subject? Oh, will I catch up on?
SpongeBob, I will cut yeah one. Yeah sponge bob
Uh, I hope that answers george bubman's question
The next question is ask bcp. How was slash is the fuco you read slash our reading ben?
Um, I won't take too long to answer this but I'm like I'm only like 70 pages into this big ass book of it
And uh, mostly what I've been reading is about the development of the western justice system
And how uh, it used to there used to be different
basically there used to be
It
Like a try there didn't used to be things like criminal trials. There didn't used to be like a state
It used to just be a civil matter between two individuals
One of whom was wronged by the other and it would basically just it would basically just be a matter of rallying the community
Like get people on your side to say fuck that guy. He fucked me over
And then just people would just demand reparations from each other and enforce that by whatever force they could muster
And it was basically just like a slightly more civil way of conducting like war and and uh banditry
And and violence against each other. It was like we don't have to we don't have to kill each other
We don't have to engage in an armed conflict. However, you are an asshole and I hate you and I am going to kick your ass
So you can just let me do that or you can like pay me some money
And I'll leave you alone
And some such and such about like the church model of the inquiry
Is sort of the basis for what we now consider like a like criminal trial
a fact finding
Enterprise of like determining what happened and what was done in the past and by who and this was like a model that didn't used to really exist
Uh, so it's been it's interesting and I like it. I should read more of it
I've only read like
I have not been reading very fast because I'm only like 70 pages in that's like a page a day or something
Probably averages out something like that
Uh
Next question is
Well, we've got another, um
Oh god, we've got another, uh, imager album from vinnie
You're all posted. Yeah
There is benny the uh, okay
Is this is this guy this guy, uh with the these
Have we seen these before I feel like I've seen some of these this one. I don't think
Oh, no, no, that's no, I think these are new. I think these are new
I like that I'm skinny in this picture. That's the truth now. That's the truth now
It's funny how well like all of the musculature is is is done on that. He is like
Yeah, he's very
Vinnie is is very
He's very focused on that on that
This looks like shipping ire
Like like this person ships you guys together. I guess so then
Then saints stand slime time form and whoopity the byproduct of his body fuels the form of his stand after ben experience
Ketosis for the first time the spirit of his fat cells manifested his stand slime time
Then saints proficiency and imagination further developed his uses of his latent abilities
The filth slime and sludge surroundings of ben saints surroundings can be transmuted into slime
And he can manipulate with his stand the limitation to ben saints abilities depend on his hydration and knowledge of chemical compounds
The story of you trolling other kin forms is where I got the idea of your fat
That is now your slime being the basis of your joe gibson. Oh my god. I can't believe
He remembers that
From when I used when I used to when I used to make troll accounts to troll the other
Well, yeah, there was one that I had was I I was like a
What character that I made up was like a guy who believed in like Japanese style like nature spirits and he like identified
He was like a theater. He was like a I'm gonna get as fat as possible sort of guy
Who like believed that he was the incarnation of his own like body fat and he just wanted to like increase himself
That guy got banned really fast
That was pretty epic that guy got banned fast
And he was banned because the profile picture I used was like an old painting of like a fat like noblemen
But like that doesn't seem fair. It was literally just like a picture of a fat guy like what is objectionable
About that
stupid, um
They're fat phobic. They were they were fat phobic. They were fat phobic. I was just living my truth and
They didn't like it. Um, they didn't they didn't appreciate it
Gib and take stand platformer, but gib can be seen to being 100 cuter than ben saint in any given moment
Okay
Is that that's the power that's my power
That's just that's just real life
Yeah, yeah, that's how you really have. Yeah. That's that's yeah
This next one is I guess I'm wearing a chris chan striped shirt
And I have a sonichu medallion
I don't think it's v sonichu medallion. It's a sonichu medallion
And I seemed very very happy about
Cool
Would you buy slime corp brand sonichu merch from this man?
Oh, and then
My chemical vape
My chemical romance. I was listening to my emo music and felt inspired
Hippo at the disco
Gib and takes
And they get the dick so bird. Okay. These are album covers with us. Oh, I get it
I don't know the album so I was I don't know them either listen to pray for a wicked and death of a bachelor
Oh, I know I know death of a bachelor
um
Then saying being now to
Yeah, I'm just being cool shirt. Yeah. All right
Uh, this one
Gib is haruha haraku
Haru haru haru hara hara hara hura haraku
Haru hara am I am I the
The you're you're moped lady. I'm moped as the woman from
I'm gonna
FLCL I was gonna say okay k.o. So that's not the four-legged word that that is not the same not the same
Fully like the pig coolly
The pig rebates
The pig will be explained in the next page of the comic which I haven't been able to get back to
I've been working 12 hours every day and at work is the only time I can manage to do these little images without ever pen
I can steal based okay, there you are like that grind me
Base like that thing you're hitting me with in the next drawing. I'm gonna kill you
If only is that is that you know his music without getting I think so. Yeah
I think I mean, I'm supposed to be now to in this. Oh, I see
Situation the next one after this is now to going into his room when hara haraku is shaking her butt
from harako harako
What a slimy little guy look at you look
It's a whoopity. I'm holding a whoopity and I'm shaking my butt
Why don't you put on why don't you put on some clothes? How's this?
Not what I had in mind by this pion
I know this scene
Why all right, this is getting a little this is getting a little weird
Eleazar don't show the next image. I think you'll get if you think it'll get flagged by youtube
This is part of some Ben saying exclusive arts. I sent him for his personal amusement, but I guess it's to be known by all
hmm
I pounced I gloved you and I pounced on you in an anime fashion
I mean you've seen this
scene
From the show from anime
You're well, you're familiar with fully cool. You've seen fully cool. I watched it once
I don't remember scenes from it necessarily. Well, this seems like the things that happen in anime
Well, this is I mean specifically
fully cool, but
Yes, these are these are iconic iconic moments
um me vapin
using my down B
Oh, it's got a little unicorn to the unicorn cloud
You make it you made a vape and you will have sex with her is what you say
I think now I was
Oh, I created so I see
I vape celestia into existence. Well, good for me
It now has to be publicly it has to be known publicly now ben saint is into some serious horsing around
We going
Is that I wanted to make sense to you
I think so it's a son of two. Maybe it's christian
Yes, it's christian. So aren't you because she has the medallion
mark on her chest there
I wanted to be known
I wanted only to make ben saint giggle with a thing to satiate his own personal palette of fetish
But here it is to be known
Ew, I don't like this next one. Oh boy says ben saint. Oh boy when I see a vagina. Oh boy
Hey
Innocent hands to drawing sexual implications of him with a female
I was merely an innocent boy before I watched one second of ben saint on youtube.com slash ben saint. Yeah, true. Yeah, true. Thanks
Um
These are outrageous. These are outrageous my head. I have a headache now my hangover got worse
Uh, here's my water
I do I didn't mention it. I yes, I have a hangover today. It was getting better, but
From what from alcohol?
You're cool. Why were you drinking?
I was hanging out with some I was hanging out with some some buddies that I hadn't seen in a while
Uh, just just just chilling with the boys
I'll allow it. Just having a drink just having a drink with the boys
Uh, even though it's soy to do that. I did it anyway
Um, is it gay to hang out with other men? Someone said that was
Somebody said
I think it was garbage ape made a tweet that was like
conservative thought these days is like, uh, it's like sports
sports are degenerate
Uh, uh, it's soy to have a it's soy to have a beer with the boys. Um
I don't know what he was responding to but it sounded it rang true
Round true rang true for me
Uh, all right. All right. I always thought sports were gay. I know I've been a conservative
all my life
Okay, mozilla fennekin says
Responds to the ask pcp post says, oh, you'll read my post, huh? In that case. I post ben is a loser
Damn, they got me
They tricked me into saying it. Yeah
I swore I would never tell the truth about that but
I had to I'm gonna find out I'm a fucking loser. No
Well, uh, if we okay, so that's that's done for now. Um oblivion fall had this, um
Had this other speak pipe the the fuck Nate
The Nate fuckers speak pipe account
And he which which we we got some messages on there
Some of them are old the first three are from like a year ago more than a year ago
And then there's one new one
Uh, okay, so you want to play those? We'll start with the one from february 2021. It's called my name
Are we ready? Yes. Okay three two one go
Okay, uh, I missed the voicemail so much
Yeah, they're back. That that is my name. Yes. That's my name right there. The next one is called ben taint
Uh three two one. Let's jam
Did you know cum is keto? Yep to me. That's not good enough
I must have Nate's cum
So I may enter the most true ketosis
With Nate's cum I can make the best keto gummies
All out of cummies
But there's still one problem
I don't have Nate's cum yet
That is a problem to get it. What are we gonna do that? I'll have to fuck Nate. Yeah, so fuck Nate
I'll have to join league of Nate fuckers. Yeah, what can you do patreon.com slash ben taint
I wonder if that's a real and see here
patreon.com
And it's a league of Nate fuckers actually fuck Nate. I don't have to joke what they didn't ever do
They they they they got inceled by Nate. They were gonna. Yeah
They were gonna they would have
If they got the chance they would jump at the chance
Nate was willing but then uh, michelle came into the picture and just ruined everything. She cocked blocks everyone
Nate was willing but not able tragically
Could not perform
Uh, the next one is called I have been a fan of the
P
I've been fan of the P. Can't read the whole thing
Yeah, I've
It's cut off. Let's hear it three two one go
Nate best
Give give it to me
Yeah
The full title was I have been a fan of the procrastinators podcast for five years. This is what happens to you
You know the you know the iceberg meme and how like the guy on the side as you go down it
He becomes more and more of like a weird looking freak. Yeah
It's like, yeah, this is like
At the bottom of the pcp iceberg that's you look that's you sound like the very very bottom of the pcp iceberg
Underneath it says I haven't been a fan of the pcp for five years
It's not it's just the the length of time you become you are a fan. Just you become like a freak
You end up down there
I get I get pictured the whole iceberg and just
weird phrases that like
Need like two hour videos to explain what they mean like
All the way at the bottom. It's like it would say um, it's a jeff never left the pcp
Icebergs jeff never left the pcp
There's one more. This is the only new voicemail it received it's called thoughts on Trixie and it's two seconds long
So let's do it. Oh boy at three three two one go
bullying works
Bullying works through it does work true worked on jk rally
Only centrist and cucks complain about bullying I would say
Yeah, I would say bullying works in the sense that in this situation
um having a a vocal force
Calling Trixie out for the bullshit she was doing did lead to more people
like
Not caring anymore about her. I don't honestly
I'm not sure. I'm not sure if if bullying and and and and anti stuff, you know
People complaining about her being mean to her. I don't think that's really did anything
Or I don't think it was the main the main thing is just people weren't
weren't watching
like sure but like
the
I feel like
certain
I feel like she would be doing better
if there had been no like
outrage
like like publicly about
stuff
I think it was a factor it would have but I don't think it was it would have gone under the radar for a bunch of people
And they would just be like wonder when the next video is and then they would watch it
But she did yeah, I guess she did change her content so much
The people just left anyway, so I don't know. I I think them. I think that's a
A relatively smaller there were there were definitely people that like got mad at her
Decided they didn't like her anymore because of things she did or think she said or stuff like that, but I think
In in the main it's just her content was different and and bad now
and uh
she was boring now and uh
That's that's what people just yeah, that's just too. Yeah, I guess I guess
Bullying works is just a generally true term for various things, but maybe not in this situation
I mean at the end of the day if you're making videos people want to watch they'll they'll watch them even if they hate you
You know
Or a lot of people will people will watch things
And that's that's the only thing that is true
I'm willing to watch like an eight hour long video just to confirm my hate
Exactly people do people do be watching people do be consuming content though
And I'm willing to bet only I'm handful people have actually finished the video
And so I'm in a secret club if you it sounds boring. It's like you beat um getting over it
And you're in the secret forum
All right that with the ending of getting over is the secret form
Yes, the secret form where people who have who have beaten the game can talk about
How will they beat the game with other people who beat the game?
You can hack in there, but like
The reward obviously means nothing if you didn't try to get there legitimately
I bet there were some I bet there were a bunch of smart Alex
Who thought they were real clever who would go on there and be like I didn't beat the game
I I found the link here somewhere ha ha
I'm sullying your space
knowing that it was a it's the reward of
Or I'm kind of basically like oh, I guess I don't want to finish reading the game now
I mean I mean I think that's not it's that's not what it's about though. It's not about the reward
No, and I think it's a cool like thing to do
Because people would you know, they want to beat the game to get the cool prize
Obviously the reward is that you feel like you've accomplished something and the
The forum is just sort of like a little bonus for people who want to feel like exclusive
What if what if like y'all what if if you beat the game y'all to know the reward is like an NFT of you beating the game
Like a splash mountain take a picture, but an NFT
Oh, yeah, like at disney. I started giving it an NFT. It's an NFT of you going on splash mountain
There's no picture or anything. It's just like an NFT that says you went on the ride
I
That tofu may be sick disgusting. I hated it. I hated every second of it and yet I ate all of it
Uh, maybe that's why I'm feeling sick now. Maybe it's not the hangover coming back. Yeah castle like me and your mom last night
What she made you sick she was disgusting and ate and I ate all of it and now
I mean
That's a bummer man. Um
Oh, no, that's the last of the voicemails. Thank god
No more of that. Okay. Well, there were technically two more voicemails that were just weekly reminded to play
Ben's weekly reminded to play delta run chapter two and ben's weekly reminded to catch up on one piece
I've already been. Oh, I I never finished chapter two. Oh
Yeah, never even started it never even opened that shit. No, I
Didn't I feel like chapter three is probably
Coming out soon. It's been long enough
Yeah, any day now. Oh, maybe
Yeah, I missed I missed the train when everyone was drawing. Um, like
NSFW are of queen
Of queen. Oh, yeah queen, right? Yeah
They should have given like a name like an actual name
Yeah
Oh, wait, people still draw spampton. I keep forgetting he's not either deltas. Yeah, spampton. Spampton's the new tumblr boy
Is it is he or is that ironic? No, no people legitimately love him. He's great. He's a very funny character, but he also can be like
Like uh, like a metaton-esque like uh tumblr sexy boy sexy man thing
I I had two mutuals who like once spampton dropped they drew nothing but spampton
Right, like that's all they fucking drew just spampton over and over again
and
Well, I don't
I don't I don't get it. Well, of course you don't you haven't played the game
I haven't played the game. So, you know, what would I like? Why are all these people
Caring about something? I don't know
Who's the steven universe guy? What does he even do? Like what has he ever done for me hyper fixations be damn
Oh, I feel terrible
This is my this is my my arc for this episode is I start out low and I just get lower I start out saying
Uh, I'm hungover. Uh, I'm tired. Uh, I'm sick. Oh, I know I'll get I'll get Chinese food. Oh, but it's only made it worse
I went through a whole I learned a lesson a valuable lesson don't buy Chinese food. Just don't do it
Just don't do it msg
um
Got something good. Do you think you caught a little a little something?
coronavirus
baby
No, although, uh, some people I know were exposed to it recently
So there's I have to I was I was like third hand exposed to covid
So I have to test myself in a couple days
But I think I think I'm probably in a clear because none of those people actually like got sick. So I probably won't either
I um, I got covid back like at the start of august and it really fucking like set back everything I was working on
Yeah, if anyone sees me on twitter, it says like working on five comics and I just say that
A lot of stuff was supposed to come out a lot earlier, but um
It's fucking yeah, I couldn't do anything and coincidentally on the same day that um
I got covid my computer crashed so hard. I needed to reinstall windows
And when I reinstalled it, um, it deleted a bunch of my old files
Including close including the episode of main character syndrome. I recorded that same day
No
Which was uh, yolo swag studios without berries and cream
And really that's a week. Oh, yeah, that sucks so much
Yeah, exactly. So I have to like get back on being ahead of myself with fucking main character syndrome
um
and I was supposed to
Um, there was a kickstart campaign. I was supposed to start but now um, it's gonna start later this month actually
You guys have you guys seen my post about that?
Uh, no, I don't think so. Was it uh, is it an s of w?
Kickstarter doing an an s of w anthology like oh the anthology. Is it clown themed? Is it a clown porn anthology?
Yeah, it's called yeah
Got yeah, uh, you you mentioned this to me. Yeah
Um, I recognize some of the art. I recognize some of the artists. You showed me that are in it
Yes, um
I don't I don't want
Should I mention the artist should I how much crop and what's the harm?
Yeah, whatever. Um, because I I kind of wanted to keep it a secret till the day of but um, I mean how much crossover does the pcp?
Am I an s of w account have anyway?
Probably not too much
Yeah, not too much, but um, yeah the the people involved is just it's me and two other guys
And um, it's uh, it's galacta b and superspo
You guys know those guys I had seen I had seen them around I'd seen their
Before I recognize both of them. I I do not
I have not heard of those
Um superspo is a buddy of mine and van actually has mentioned his like stuff on um
On the pcp before
And um, he mostly does like very like
like uh
Like obese women commissions
Um score
Yeah, exactly. Um
Kind of look for
Ellie is already I'm gonna put none of this on because some of it is very suggestive, but um
We already showed that picture of gib
On top of me as harco
Yeah, exactly
Man sure sure was problematic for that adult harco to fucking hit on and
Have fucking sex with
Child not so that was that was pretty fucked up. I went in Rome
I don't know what that means
Went in Rome
Went in japan do as the japanese do
Yeah, I'm trying to look for like art by galacta b but they got so it was so fucked up
That's hardcore sex scene between harco and and now to with concy watching
I found it didn't like it. So it just felt a little off to me. Um
This is a good art by superspo
Yeah, superspo doesn't comic galacta b um
And i'm i mean i'll tell you i'll give you a little i'll give you a little secret insight about the comic
Um, all the comics are finished
I currently ordered test copies and those are going to be coming soon. Once I get that
I am I am max reviving post of the clown. He's coming back. Oh my god
Wait as a cartoon
No, it's it. I'm going I'm I'm I'm gonna count. I'm going back to my clownification. I'm re-clowning myself
Oh, very good. I didn't realize you had unclowned
Well, I know you changed your twitter your twitter profile or your your pfp
Um, the positive that all the positive clown accounts have been dormant although recently i've been like posting to kind of like
You know like, you know rally up some interests. I know you've been doing uh, you've been doing my alien girlfriend
Yes, and
Yeah, so you haven't really you haven't been clown posting
I've been clown posting in a while
um, I
I've been on uh, I also like um after
I I mean if anyone reads my alien girlfriend, you might have noticed that um
It's mostly just been guest artists right now because my computer even though I reinstalled windows
There was like a bigger issue my computer had
And um, my my usual tech guy my usual buddy who comes my buddy who actually built that computer for me after that um
Go fund me. I I ran. Um
Has been ghosting me like he just won't talk to me at all like I've been DMing him on everything
I've been DMing him for weeks and he's just not I don't know what I did. Maybe I fucking offended him
or something
Yeah, so I so I had to go to I actually had to go to a professional
The funny thing is that I even DM him told him that I could pay him
to like
Take a look at the computer and like, you know fix it, but um, he just was not interested so I went to um
actual tech guys
And that happened like two weeks ago. So now my computer is up and running again
Um
I'm gonna go back to fucking drawing my alien girlfriend and we're not gonna have guest artists for a good while now actually
Speaking of oh, yeah, no go on. Yeah. No, we're gonna say I was gonna say speaking of
Things that happened that delay kick starters
That just reminds me about how yet
I have not checked
Did I mention that the the chinese company lady
Ghosted me about like printing my book like we freaking had worked
Out a whole bunch of stuff about how to print the book and then like when i'm finally ready to like order it
She just like stops responding. I think you mentioned that but I would have assumed she got back to you by now
You know what I have not checked in a few days. Maybe she did in the last week and I just haven't seen it
But she didn't like three weeks
Worst case scenario worst case scenario should fucking die
I
Yeah, I gotta check may it's possible. Maybe she'll have gotten back. Isn't that would be a really big relief
I don't know if this is still happening, but isn't it like in china? They're on full lockdown or something
Like they're not even allowed to leave their apartments
Um
I and what are they think about that that that was like, uh, that was like a couple months ago. I remember
Like they just weren't allowed and they were they would get arrested if they
I mean, yeah, I know they had really strict like lockdown stuff over there
I mean, I don't think it was the whole country and like I mean, how long
Could they keep that up?
How long can they keep the lie up?
Yeah, the the covid lie. Yeah, how long could we lie?
Yeah
Oh, I was gonna ask you Ben. Um, do you know, do you know what's the percentage number that like Kickstarter takes from
Your campaign? I think it's something like 10 10 percent or nine percent or something like that
I would have to look it up. That's what I figured. It's it's around there. Yeah. Yeah, okay. Well, yeah, I gotta
I gotta crunch the numbers. I mean, I crunched the majority of them already like
Before the Kickstarter, I have like a rough estimate about like how much the Kickstarter should be
What what what are your estimates?
Um, it's probably gonna be a little over
10,000
For the Kickstarter. Yeah. Yeah, because each because each artist, um
The the the whole idea of the real goal of the Kickstarter was to get three months in my rent paid
Right, right. That's the real goal, right and each artist is going to get like three thousand
And um the comics are each one of our comics is between 15 to 20 pages
Um, and I and I kind of picked three thousand at random because one of one of my buddies suggested it because they talked about like
Oh, yeah, this should cover grant for like
Uh, a handful of months and I'm like, oh, yeah, I could just
Since I since I could just treat it as like the the anthology is like the employee the employer and
I I run it. So I just get to the side. I'm gonna get fucking paid, right?
I guess so
I mean
That's one way to think about it. Yeah, and so everyone's getting
And we're gonna try to print a hundred books
A hundred books for a ten thousand dollars
Yeah, see it seems wait, how big are these books?
Uh, the books are like 60 pages
How much is one gonna cost how much is one gonna cost? Yeah, I was thinking like maybe around 25 to 35
Okay
Yeah, how does that add up to $10,000?
Oh, no the print. No the printing company
Okay, wait the print company for for a hundred books is gonna charge like around 700
Okay, I'm just saying. All right, but if your goal is to sell a hundred books and
Is you're selling them for 25 dollars a piece? That's 2,500 dollars. That's not 10,000 dollars
Okay, so
Let's see how the word this did not sound like I'm an idiot. I guess
Okay, so it's it's it's like
For just to pay the artist, right?
And like 700 to print out like 100 books and the the thing is that like there's there's no guarantee
Like we're gonna have like a tee like it's gonna we're gonna print out a hundred of them
But the idea is that like
You reserve a copy
From a certain tier that you pay for right?
Yeah
So
Yeah, and like so what's like how does that add up? How does that make 10,000?
Well, we also have shipping
For shipping is gonna be to ship out like a hundred books. It's gonna be like over 500
And then we got a lot of envelopes
Doug give am I am I failing to communicate something?
They mentioned the artist was nine grand
Okay, which is the bulk of it. I
I'm not I'm not I'm not saying I'm not saying you should not
No, I'm not saying like you should not
Uh
Get that much what I'm saying is if you sell a hundred books at 25
Dollars a piece that doesn't that doesn't make 10,000. We're not we're not we're not selling the hundred books
We're printing a hundred books
So you're selling less than a hundred books
So it's even what how does that make that doesn't get you 10,000 dollars?
All right, am I am I losing my mind? Well, I think ben you're you're thinking like uh
People on the Kickstarter will pay just for the book
I feel like there's probably tiers of like higher cost. There's there's tiers. Yes. We're like certain tiers reserve you a copy of those 100
Right
Ryan
Yeah
So we're gonna we're printing out a hundred, but there's no guarantee that all 100
They're not gonna they're not all gonna be sold sold during the Kickstarter
The idea that is like I'm gonna have like a supply of these books to sell for out
I
I feel so when you use when you go to the Kickstarter and you say I would like I would like to support this
I would like a book
There's no guarantee you will get a book. There's people who would
There's people who will support it
And they're not gonna like I mean I there's gonna be like a I think the lowest you can get is like a digital copy
Right for one of the tiers, right?
Okay
Yeah, and then like and there's gonna be another tier that reserves you a physical copy
So, okay, so you're expecting
Okay, so you're expecting there's gonna be people who are gonna support and they're not gonna get a book out of it
Okay, yeah, I
I get okay. I guess I get it
Do you think do you think that most people will support it but not buy a book?
Um, well, that's where I like I'm like kind of like if you about it
I think the majority people would want a book like they're gonna reserve for I mean, yeah
I would think I would think that like the standard backer it like would pledge
To get the book
Yeah
Right, but I don't but I think charging like what like, um
25,000
That's like that's a trick every two thousand. No, it'd be 2,500. Yeah. Oh, yeah, it'd be 2,500
If if a hundred if a hundred people buy a book for 25 dollars, that's 2,500
Right, but there's no guarantee that we're gonna get a hundred
Yes, and what I'm saying is that that means that
We're not is that the figure that that gets you to is not ten thousand dollar
What I'm that's what I'm saying give you understand what I'm you're saying that if you sell them at 25
And that's the tier that gets you the book
I'm saying I'm saying the number the numbers it sounds the numbers it sounds like you were expecting to do
The numbers it sounds like you're expecting to do do not yield the the result that you are suggesting
I don't know. Okay. Uh, well, there's like I mean, there's still other things that are like
I'm included into it like, you know, like not just shipping but at the order a bunch of envelopes
And also like you know, that's not you fool you fool. I'm not that's not what I'm saying
I'm not saying I'm not saying no your expenses. Don't justify it. I'm saying
How do you plan to make that money? I'm saying that a hundred people buying the book doesn't
Make doesn't make the money that you're saying it makes
So I gotta charge them off with the book
No, I mean, I would say you would either have to
Got what what do I think? Well, here here's what I think
I mean, depending on how like if you if you don't expect to sell that many if you're any expecting to like
Hypothetically sell a hundred on it if you're lucky
um
And you need ten grand for that
Uh, that's gonna be difficult unless all of the people are willing to pledge large amounts of money for each book
Yeah
It would if you're if you're if it's possible to sell
Um, there is gonna be there is gonna be a tier higher. There is gonna be a tier higher than like
The physical book
Yeah, sure, right there's gonna be like more tiers
It's gonna be a little bit more like incentivization
I think if because like the the printing of the books is relatively small of a cost compared to paying the artists
I feel like it wouldn't be
Like too bad to try and print 200 books
Or like more. Yeah
Yeah, so that there are more books to go around so that more people
can pledge
For a book and potentially a higher tier of the book
All right, you know what now that's starting to make a lot more sense
Okay, now that makes a lot more sense about like the the more volume you have the more of the higher tiers you can get
Therefore, you'll be easier to get at all. No, I get you because like I um
I did watch other people talk about this and they say like yeah
I usually order like 200 or 300 and I never I never knew why people would order that much
I just feel like wouldn't like 100 just be enough
But like now I see what you mean. Well, I mean you should like because I would
Yeah, the whole I think that you wouldn't that you wouldn't decide how many copies you were going to print until after the Kickstarter
It was done and you like knew how many orders you needed to fulfill, right?
I mean, yeah, and then that that would like
Make the
I mean that would make the the cost of the Kickstarter like lower, right?
Um
Slightly, I mean if you're paying the artist's nine thousand and that is how much it costs then
That is a fixed fee that they're gonna need that money for the art that you're doing but the number of books
Uh needed to print
It's like the larger like it's it's not as expensive to get a larger amount of books
And it is to pay more artists, you know
The the tier the tier for the for the book for the physical book would have to go up a little bit
We'll have to go up to match like the shipping and the and the envelope and like the labor cost of packaging the stuff, right?
I mean, doesn't it all does it not already include that?
Um, no, it's yeah, it is included. It's just that it's it's it's all all that is included. I just don't have it at um 100 books
Why 100 books?
Okay, because the the idea was
That like a lot I I sell a lot of the stuff. I I do like vending that convention. So I would sell it
Yeah, or like if people will set up some sort of shop where people could like order it later on like let's say that like
During the Kickstarter people don't have like the money to like buy a copy
But like I don't have a lot to like sell for the course of the year
Right and of course like of course all the artists are gonna get a percentage of the sales, right?
Yeah
So why so why a hundred?
I mean, it just seemed like a reasonable number
Okay, uh, so the the goal is to have overstock so that you'll have
Stock left over that you can sell. I mean because if you have overstock
You could you could sell the book for like cheaper because you're gonna sell it in person, right?
That's that's why more people to buy it. Yeah
So is a hundred a hundred is like the minimum you want to print
I'm just thinking like what if you so what if you sell 200 books?
What if the Kickstarter is a big success and 200 people that buy the book then you would print 200, right?
I'm gonna have to grab a quote right now or you would print more
Yeah, um
Yeah, if if it's like a huge ass success, we're gonna like, you know, like if people like, um
If people pay for the tier where they get the physical book, they're gonna like they're gonna get a they're gonna get a book
We're just gonna like raise the number of orders, right?
Yeah, well, I'm saying if you sell a lot of books if it's this big success then you can buy
a bigger print run
And that will yield that will lead to the cost per copy going down
Uh, if you if you buy more at a time, right, right?
Uh, so what what point what point was I trying to make there?
I think I was I was a bit confused because I thought you you said there's going to be a hundred and
That will pay for the 10 grand 10 grand
like goal
When it's more likely that you would need more than a hundred people buying the book
to get that high
Yeah, unless the almost the special tier is like, uh, pay 500 dollars and you get the super special golden book
Unless yeah, unless you expect like that like a majority of the money would be going to yeah
Some other tier that either like doesn't include a book or
Includes like a lot is something else. It's a much higher tier that includes a book
But also a bunch of other stuff like if you think that's where most of the money is going to come from
Yeah, this is gonna this is going to be a big dummy thing to say, but I didn't realize that
Oh, yeah, the majority of people would want a physical copy, right?
Yeah
That's what I'm driving at
Well, that's well, no, no, no, you're right. I mean, this is why it helps that I say this out of the open
I just don't want no one in the comment section to to bully me
Okay, well, sorry, but it's too late. It's too late
Okay, um
Yeah, uh, no, yeah, I should I should you're right. I should be like order enough that like it
It would cover for the fucking kickstart. Yeah, I would I would right now
The way that I the way that I did mine is I
Yeah, like I thought I planned like, okay
What's the minimum number of copies that I would want to make and then I'm like, okay
I'll set the price at that level
And then if it sells more than that then I can print then I print more and that actually like reduces
Costs actually it actually makes each copy sold more
Profitable because the the cost per copy goes down if you print a bigger run
I can't remember how I figured out my load of ghosts one
I think
All of the different things like the plush and the pins and everything made it more complicated
Like if you like if your goal is to make ten thousand dollars, then I guess you would say like, okay
Well, each book is gonna chart cost 25. So I hope need to sell. What would be 500?
What would be 500?
copies and that would be like
I mean you would probably make
Yeah, there will there will be people that pledge
Hire without buying the book and there will be people that pledge at higher tiers
So it may end up to be sort of in the middle like 350 books you need to print
Yeah
In order to cover all the expenses
Pay all the artists get all the money for us sending things out the envelopes and stuff
Because relatively purchasing lots of books and envelopes is a lot less expensive than paying for art
To be made
Yeah
Hey, what happened? Hey, what happened to that a comic that I executive produced?
Oh, maybe you're still working on it. Still working on it. Okay. Yeah
I mean she she started a new job and it's like 36 hours out of the week. Oh cringe
Yeah, cringe. It is
It is cringe. I mean
Like like I like we'll we'll figure something out. I have um
What does she need a job for when I'm generous generously funding her her her her project when I'm when I'm executive
When I'm her producer, right? I can get her an RV. I can get her a gig
I can get her a rap gig in Elko, Nevada. Like what I can do. I can give you everything
We had everything it all ran like clockwork, but you had to fuck it up
Yeah, little do we know she has her own little ben saint destroying her career
Um, I'm a producer. I'm a big money connection
Oh
Well, I gotta do some I gotta do some like this is why this is why I like talking to you guys because um
Get the brain going
Yeah, yeah, it's good. It's good to be creative talking with creatives creatively about stuff
So that we can get the get the knowledge making content
content on the internet
Guys
Content guys let's reach a change the podcast name to content guys
That's awful
Do I know?
Yeah, what do you um, did you um?
Have you have you seen our yellow swags new podcast?
With a beetle moses. Yeah, we'll be the Moses. They had a boshan and turkey tom
I saw they had um
No, no, it's the one after the other. I saw they had young krip on I saw that
That was like the recent episode. I saw a clip of that
Uh, I haven't I mean I haven't actually watched the podcast or anything
But I am aware of it. I didn't know how long it had been going on
Good for them
I imagine having like like inviting notable people onto your show
Imagine how scary that would be imagine if they they have an audience
um
Can't believe anyone would do that
I is a scary is this a
Is a bit
it's like the
Hmm
How much would you pay for 60 pages of porno?
and comments for
Clown related to them related
porno, I mean
If it's like an indie thing that's like that i'm kick starting that that means I would pay more for it than if I would for like
Something that I saw in a store. I mean the artists here look very good. I think 25 dollars
25 to 30. Yeah
Okay, I uh, yeah, I'm hoping I'm hoping that
Slime and punishment will only cost
Something around like 25 or 30 dollars
uh
To that's going to depend on it literally depends on whether this stupid lady gets back to me because her printing was the cheapest
And that was going to make the book cost what I wanted it to cost if I go with someone else that might have to cost more
And I and I really don't want that
um
I get that
I gotta keep gotta keep those costs low. You gotta pass that savings on to the consumer, baby
God, I'm so done. I never want to make a physical comic
Ever again. I can't wait. I can't wait. I can't wait to uh, I mean, I'm I'm planning to do like
kick one kick start kick start after another
right now
As as an effort to like keep paying my fucking rent
I will be very excited if the if the
Slime and punishment sees I'll be really hype
I'll be really hyped to get a bunch of books and put them in get a bunch of boxes and put them in boxes and do it hundreds
Hundreds and hundreds of boxes again kind of like the if it's anything like the vapors
It'll be like that, but it'll be much harder
Because I'll have to fold boxes, but I'll do it because uh, I love my fans so much
You kiss each envelope over them. Mm-hmm
But I'll put a little yes
I'll put a little smiley face just like just like spongebob
Making that making that crabby patty in the in the cookoff against Neptune
When he put the little smiley faces on the on the pickles and he and he covered them a cheese blank and gave him a little kiss
That's me putting together
My Kickstarter reward boxes, uh, when you buy things from me
Such a sweetheart
Such a sweet little guy. Come here. That's me breaks breaks your neck
Oh snap snap
Just just think about bunnies. Just think about the bunnies Lenny. Just these little sweetheart
Um, did you did you guys ever see like the previous porn comics that I made?
Uh, yeah, I think
I think I saw one of them. I saw some like these. Yeah. Yeah that I uh, yeah
Oh, I didn't see the whole thing ones are gonna look like this
They're gonna they're gonna they're gonna look like this. These are like eight by eleven, which is a very like weird
It's kind of when it the the site that I'm using doesn't have that as in like default option
You have to like custom it and I just kind of chose that because like I'm already drawing it by a by 11
because like
So are like the villain verse copies
Yeah, I was going through my bookshelves during the move and I I found my villain verse books and I
Carefully tucked them away friggin uh
Well, the lord yeah, not only did the lord of ghosts
Uh sheet cover lose one of his button eyes
Uh, I drop I dropped the uh lord of ghosts book and it creased the cover for a minute
I managed to I managed to uncrease it and it looks fine, but like oh no the structural integrity
It could easily it could happen again. It could happen again, and then it might not be uncreasible
no
Oh the structural integrity
Oh gotta protect that gotta protect that book structural integrity. There's only one. It's my it's the autograph
That's got the little phantom horn virginia inside of it. That's one of a kind
Collector's head
Oh
I'm sick one of the tier options I had in mind was um, uh, uh, thank you page at the end you put your fucking name
Yeah, that's oh, yeah, stuff's easy. Yeah, I would put like anyone that pledges like five bucks or something
I would put put them on a thank you page. I was gonna charge him more for that
Really? Yeah
Uh, I mean you could yeah, I mean sure I mean what I what I did is that
The the the size of your donation to the Kickstarter increases the font size in the back
Of of don't so I did that's what I did
So wait how much pledged at all get a little mention
And then people who pledge big have huge letters and they're so cool
Well, cheesy you have um in in one of those villain verses i'm
You put you drew me right you drew my little guy because I bought something
How much I don't remember how much it cost me it was um, I think it was I think it was
How much you pay me on patreon although like I kind of I kind of changed that now so like
Every because I I only have like nine spots and every time like
It's it becomes more than like nine people who are paying me that amount
I like I like raised up the amount you need to pay me to keep you on that page
Yeah
I would say like yeah something like that for someone that pledges like a hundred bucks or whatever
And then and then maybe a page of thank yous with everyone in a little little name
Just one all on one hundred so hopefully hundreds of names all on one page and small font for like everyone who pledges like five bucks
I I need no no reward tier. I I need like the I need like the joke the joke tier one, which is um
The like one that's like ten thousand dollars
If you give me if you give me um
four thousand
Um, I just put your name entirely in one page
Just just the whole the whole thank you just has your just your name. That's it. No one else's fucking name is on it
I have I have a question. I have a question. Um, so these clowns
These clowns they're in they're fucking right they're fucking
Yes, there's a lot of fucking fucking dudes. Are they fucking dudes?
They are fucking dudes
Are is it a specific dude or are there any of them like fucking a generic all those stories are are different
I'll tell you that much. I'm I was just thinking if there's one with like a generic like guy with no face
Which is sort of a thing in porn
You could once here is like if you pledge a thousand dollars like I'll put your face on the generic
I'll do all your face on your copy. Yeah
Uh, maybe for the next one. I'll do something like that. That's a pretty funny. Well, the thing is that I do that in my story
Yeah, my my story my comic is pov style
So so you so you're like fucking bongo in my story. You're like
I like it should have a little you should have a page where it's like
Like an outline on the page saying place penis here for maximum immersion
It's like it's like the page is like a little dotted line outline. Yeah place penis on page
You know the captain underpants like flip orama thing
Yes
If you want to see this character fuck
Yeah, I mean for the next one. Oh my god, this makes sense. Honestly makes make sense for yes that contact
Obsessed I'll call it fap orama. Fap orama
You've you've you flip the pages and you can do it like at your own pace. You can get faster and faster
If this if this blows out, um
Yes, or maybe I should um
Maybe instead of setting it to a number it's just like how many orders I get ultimately
And um, okay, you know what I think I could um, okay, I think I can map this out. You guys has helped you guys have helped me
I appreciate it
no
I'm just
I'm trying to
Just looking out looking out for you. Listen use use my
Experience I'm looking out for the little I'm old and I know and I have wisdom use my ancient wisdom
Fame famous kicks kick started king ben sain. That's right. That's correct
Uh, I
I'm telling
All right, I need to I need to go to the bathroom really quick. I'll be back in a minute. Sorry
Ben has never seen again
Ben died he shit himself to death just like Elvis. He shit and he puked
And it all of the liquids left his body at the same time and he turned to dust and he flew away
Uh, again could I ask you a question?
Yes
If you had the power
to turn
One random woman in the world into like
A giant like amoeba slime
That just doesn't think or anything. He just turned into slime instantly
Which woman would you pick?
So like I choose a woman and she turns into a non-thinking giant slime woman
She turned into an amoeba basically like a human size amoeba, but it's like a slime. It's like slime. It's like
You basically turn into a blob and she doesn't she doesn't like think it's like a non-thinking
I mean why would I want to do that 21? That sounds horrible
Okay, but if you had to choose I was like if you if I had to if I had to turn one
Um, Liz trust the the hopeful conservative leader of the the fucking tory party
I turned her into a blob. I would pick Nancy Pelosi. I think as
To turn her to turn into a slime like in the middle versus a speech
I think that'd be the perfect time like because people will see and people will freak the fuck out
See that's the reason it'd be so fucking cool. Oh
Well, because it'll be like you'll be good fucking riddance, you know
It's like the death noble with slime instead of instead of death you turn into
slime
The slime now
I'm just imagining that the the the the death note like anime where he's writing furiously in the pen
And instead of watching all of the prisoners get heart attacks. They just turn into slime and explode splatter everywhere
It's just so goofy
What's that? I want I wish I knew what the japanese word for slime was
And they just start calling instead of kira. They start calling him that
Gooper
Gooper the gooper strikes. This is el's most deadliest
Case yet. Who is goopie with an a g o o p a
I used to I used to know a girl back in middle school named kira
um
She was like asian and um, did she have a death note? No
Dang
Crippling depression
Jk, that's not true. I don't know
I don't know about that
um
I think I might I think for the Kickstarter might stick it for like just depending how many people like pledge that's how many I'll order
Yeah, like just have it open as like a tear because
um presuming that
This is what I did for a lot of ghosts. I would
figure out like
Roughly how much a single book would cost to create
It's usually gonna be less than 25
bucks if you're making a hundred of them
um, but just check so that
You have the tear that gets the book
the lowest tear
And just make sure that one pledge to that tear will cover the cost
And and mailing of that book so that doesn't matter how many
pledges you get you can still cover all the costs at the end
That makes sense
I think um
Yeah, I'm gonna have to really zone in and like pick a number here
Number munchin was really stressful for me
But it wasn't very important because if I didn't number munch, I wouldn't know how high to put the goal or where the stretch goal should go
I don't think it would have worked if I didn't think about it a lot
No, I got you. I need to I I kind of have
I'm gonna all I have is like two weeks
to like uh figure this out
And I don't want like I don't want anyone to get screwed. I already promised everyone like 3000 and I think 3000 is um
A decent amount. I think I think some artists get paid more than 3000 like
At at a professional industry level
Oh, yeah, I mean
yeah
mass producing comics is so
It's so like difficult
Uh, which is why it's not done on an indie scale quite so much
I'm I mean my my dream is that um
If this gets like popular enough that I get approached by some like publisher
and um
They could handle like
Um printing out future volumes and then yeah, the next Kickstarter would be like half as cheap
Yeah, that's that's what I'm hoping for
Not that not that I I I might try another Kickstarter for like the Clarissa gunsmoak when I finish that
And be like hey, it's a cowgirl. I'm gonna make a this is my other comic
and maybe
I feel like if I have that I don't need to do a Kickstarter to
Try and get it published. I could go to publishers and say look at my work
They'll probably say nah who cares, but if I do have a Kickstarter, I guess
I can say well, I got this many sales. So
What are you gonna do about that? It's uh, it's really tough right now to like get anything like
Like printed because there's like like a paper shortage and um
A lot of these industries are still recovered from the I mean, they're very ones I could cover from the pandemic
and um
Like I'm gonna say um back when I interned they
I noticed that um
A handful of like the things they published
Like um had kick starters and I the idea is that you kick start
You kick start the book to kind of like make sure like any any loss the publisher will get
Is covered for the Kickstarter
Is that why?
Yeah, that's why they would say yes to it. I thought it was more like if if it's like shown to be
They like if they like the book if they like the book sure. Yeah, I mean, okay, that's to be popular but
Because I think it's a one specific like series where they where I when I picked it up. I saw that it's like, oh, this was made
with Kickstarter
But I remember like reading the pitch for it. So I was like, I assume it's a combination of them liking the book
But also the Kickstarter like covering for losses
Yeah, like like having some sort of security for the publisher to say yeah, we'll try this
I mean, I think what the go-to is that like if if it's like popular enough you you can like
Approach publishers about it. Oh man. I really want to like
Talk to you talking about a kick you talking about a Kickstarter book
The idea of like using Kickstarter to get a publisher interested in your work
Yeah
because um
Yeah, I just mentioned about how like I think they told me that like
Certain Kickstarter's are made to like make sure that any losses the publisher's gonna get is like covered
by the Kickstarter
Yeah, I mean that like
Isn't wasn't mighty number nine something like that
Like they didn't like the amount of money that they raised on Kickstarter was like
Definitely not what actually funded the game
Yeah, it was like it wasn't it that um my number nine was like half of it
Uh, I can't remember
I I mean, I heard that before I mean, I know that was the case with like Shovel Knight was that like the Kickstarter was gonna pay for half of it
And the other half would be like a publisher
Or I don't know again, whatever the fuck they're called a video game
I don't know as long as you as long as you um fulfill the
Promises you make on your Kickstarter. I mean, I don't see any reason why
A publisher can't also
Yeah, I mean, I mean my goal is that I'm hoping this becomes popular enough that if there's a volume two
We'll have like a publisher who'll cover like half of the cost
And then the Kickstarter could just focus on
Getting like the artist paid because I do want I I would want the three thousand to be consistent
Would would it so like it never feel like anyone's getting jibbed
and like
Um, if we do get like a publisher like set it up where like artists get like royalties
Or their story continued to be published, you know
It's a lot. It's a lot of fucking wishful thinking
I wish I had a publisher. Yeah, that's that's it. That's it's tough. Um
The only recent success story that I fucking heard it was um
What's the name of the guy who created uh
Mr. Boop
Oh, Alan Robbins. Yeah, like Robbins. Yeah, because um, he he self published the the first like
He self published like all the Mr. Boop comics and then he got picked up by a publisher
But the publisher instead of doing like
um
Separate books like he did they just published the one collection together
And I seen that like done before like um, there's a comic that I like called copra that like
Originally they were going to be published through like I because the guy was making the comic for like a years now
And um, he was just self publishing like he had this whole system on etsy where people would for you
People would join like the subscription on etsy. So these are the people guaranteed to get copies when they're finished
Um, and he and he did image comics, but then um, he left image comics. Well, he like
He decided he didn't want to do like single issues through image comics because um
he fucking
During the pandemic, he fucking saw Todd McFarland like trying to do a Kickstarter for a spawn figure
And it's like what the fuck are you doing, man? I thought you had a whole ass company that handles this
And you're fucking doing a Kickstarter for a spawn figure. That's that's kind of like
That's kind of like iffy
so I just looked I just looked up um
I just googled mr. Boop to see if like any like if there was like a Kickstarter for it or anything
And I found an article about it and it includes this photo and caption of ally
Cartoonist alec robbins eating chipotle. Well dressed in sonic badge
Photo courtesy of alec robbins. Amazingly. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Good. Good
Base king move. Uh, yeah, his collection is published by sober sprocket and they're they're the same company who published um
Pinky and pepper forever
Oh, right. Yeah. Yeah, they were they were actually the publisher. I was gonna try to approach the um for the comic that I mean
Pinky and pepper was made by that girl
Um, they they transitioned to a man recently
As of like last year they go by eddie adams now
Eddie adams. What name did they use to go there? Well, they're dead. Not their dead name is ivy adams
Oh god, I thought you were gonna say they were dead. I thought you were saying like they died
No, there's no they they read like a car accident and they got like brain damage or something, right?
They um, yeah, they had an accident because they're on one of those like like scooter things that you could pay for
And um, they did get yeah, I think they did get some brain damage or something. I mean, I talked to them
I talked to them before and after
Right or no way. I think I only ever talked to them
I can't remember. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Wait, what you say it again. What was the dead name? Because I I
Ivy adams
I yes, okay. I remember right eddie. Okay. They go by eddie adams now
Yeah, okay, but that was the pinkie and pepper first. Yeah, they're the one who did pinkie and pepper
Which is a good ass book by the way, if people out there haven't read it
Um, but yeah, I was gonna approach silver sprocket about the whole the new yori
Uh comic, I mean like
I kind of do want to do a thing like mr. Boop where it's like all online and we could like
Like I mean read it for free and buy it too
Or maybe do a Kickstarter deal where like we cover half of it and they cover the other half
Um, it's all it's all like so it's also like hard and you don't exactly know what you're gonna get because there's so many like fucking like
um
Like I
You guys never heard of uh
There's like a manga called devils candy
And it was like it used to be a webcomic. I heard of it
Yeah, and it was a really it's a really good-looking comic like it looks like a manga, right?
And um, they they they were just self publishing their webcomic and I've been so recently they got to deal with like this media and now they have like
total total bonds of like their their webcomic
and like
It's I mean, it's just publishing. It's just a physical copy of the webcomic. You read for free, but you know
Like that's a whole another market you're entering now because like not all people who who read manga
Are gonna read webcomics, right?
It's so hard to make ends meet you may as well end it all
Oh
I can't end it all I have shit to do tomorrow
Yeah
You might as well end some of it. No
Continue everything. Yeah, cut off your leg every year. You then you're not
Cut off your leg every year and it'll grow back
That's true. That's that's why this is why I make five comics at the same time because it's all
It's all me throwing different things out there. Like let's see what catches on
Oh, yeah, I'm kind of bad about that
I'm like focused so creatively like like on one thing
I'm like, ah Clarissa gunsmokes the coolest thing ever very very slowly making progress on it and eventually it'll be a thing
And then if nobody cares, I'm like, okay
Uh, and I start something you but like I could be like throwing stuff out there. That's like less
less focused less not like worse but like
I have so many ideas and I'm like in my head. I'm like, okay
I'll do them one at a time and I'll build up a huge repertoire of cool comics that I have
I guess I'm just doing it too slow. I gotta be like
Throwing them. I gotta be throwing them around. Hey, what?
You know how I said that my internet's really bad and sometimes it stops working and I can't
well
Okay, get this it's happening right now. I can't load any websites. It tells me I'm not connected to the internet
That's because I can hear you. Yeah. Yeah, I'm in the call. I'm in this call on the internet
What that's weird. I can't load Imgir. I can't load Imgir. It thinks I'm no internet try
What the fuck someone's lying
Someone's lying
Maybe discord is taking all your bandwidth
Maybe maybe that would be
Because this score takes like a lot of space in your computer
I notice I just don't I just don't understand
I just I just don't okay. So anyway, I'm doing this kickstarter on the 19th
So watch out watch out gamers
On the night. Yes
That's uh 13 days after voting day
Here in boston we got a vote for
governor
I think you got a vote for someone
now we we voted for governor like uh
A couple months ago
We voted for mayor a few months ago now. I've got to do now. We got to do the governor. I think
So sick, I'm literally sick and tired
Oh boy
Yeah, being an artist is is hard. I wish there was a way for me to like, I don't know
Gamble my art using a vile towel currency or something
If only I could uh
You should mint
every
Page of the comic as an nft. You should uh every pixel every individual pixel of every page as an nft
That's like a billion
And if you if you increase the this canvas size, you know, like change the dpa. There's more pixels to go around
There's more things to to mint
That's right. Yeah, that's right on tier tier five of clown milk
You get you get to choose which page you want to mint
I know how you can hit you can hit $10,000 by selling 100 copies if you include if you also pay extra
You get an nft
Of the book
You get the physical book this nft is a receipt for the physical book if the book is destroyed you will retain the nft
therefore
It's still got you know, it's it's protected forever. You could so read the comp. Well, you can't but you can only
Yeah, you can't read it. There's the
It doesn't contain the the book
But uh, you know, I I I minted my whole family as an nft
And even though my house burned down and they all died tragically, you know, it's actually fine because I still retain the asset
They live they live eternally on the blockchain. They live eternally on the block. Exactly
Exactly selling selling my deceased family members as nfts to pay rent
Well, you you know, you should have as many children as possible. So if you're low on cash you can mint all of them
And like as you mint their child, they're like they're turning into pixels like any suck to the computer. They're like, no
No dad, what's going on? I'm scared
father
father help
Be beautiful
Sorry ben jr
But we we really we really need to cut we really fucking need hbo max and i'm low on cash right now
I don't put me in the blockchain. No, don't don't put me in the blockchain. Please
I'm just imagining loads of children in little crates connected by chains
That are like suspended in some weird home stuck like uh, there's
Bed thing. You know those chains?
Oh, yes. Yes
That's what the blockchain is
I'm picturing it like um, you know at the end of scott pilgrim when uh, gideon has all the the the women in like those pods
Yeah
It's like that. I don't know it's frozen in stasis
Interesting
I guess there's no there's no chain there
No, the durst chain is better better. Yeah
Uh, what do we think I think we think we want to maybe call it here. We've been going for a long time
I think I think we're good right here
Yeah
Uh, we had no and you know what no voicemail. We're free of the curse of voicemail
Yeah, dead. We've already answered the questions. We can just stop
You can stop anytime we want. Um
Now you gotta bring you gotta bring back topics to replace voicemail
Like after the voicemails we start a topic
We kind of did that
Today's topic is um
Eight hour videos eight hour videos eight hour videos like them hate them
Only when they're eight hours eight minutes and 88 seconds. Wait, you can't have 88. Yeah. Oh, you know what?
Sucks so they're bad. Okay. They're all they're all bad. It's gotta be um
five hour videos
That are
Exactly that are like you can play a little number games 55 minutes and 55 seconds. Yeah
Ruining the bit by making it eight hours
Well, no by making it nine hours
uh
28 minutes
and then plus
I can't do the math
29 minutes and uh
And in 28 seconds, which would be equivalent to eight hours 88 minutes and 88 seconds. I think
So, uh, yeah, look forward to make any sense
Look forward to my five hour response. So you need to name a source is the independent of nft video
You should do you should make a response. You should make an eight second response
Yeah
You should go through it. No, you should go through it frame by frame and do like a like a e uh e-fap
E like an e-fap Jenny Nicholson like
29 hour response to the eight hour to the eight hour video
uh
easy
All right. Yeah, let's uh, let's call it. I'm gonna go to sleep. I'm gonna go lie down any final
Final plug. Do your plug if you got this plug
Look up. Uh, you need to look up my nsfw account, which is creamy pot pasta tc
That's when that's where i'm gonna announce the um kickstarter
I mean, I also recommend following galactic be a super spell because um
They're gonna also make their own announcement for it when the day comes
Hell, yeah. Yeah. Hell, yeah. Yeah
Uh, uh the 19th you said it's dropping on the 19th. 19th is when the kickstarter starts
We're gonna run up for 30 days, baby
rad
uh sick
um
uh patreon.com slash the procrastinators
bonus episodes
bonus contents and stuff
The ben cast ben commentary should have been called the calm ben terry, but oh well
Ben comes
Ben terry
He meant to my own
video. Yeah, Ben comes men
Don't ben comes terry to close off
Kamala harris said don't come
Don't come mentate that ben cast ben no one will watch it, but she was wrong and the fans when i come the patreon is exploding
Um
Okay, and maybe we'll fix the voicemail soon. Uh, maybe not depends how I feel
If you give you donate more to the to the patreon you um the voicemails are most likely to get fixed
If you donate a lot if you pay me a thousand dollars, I will never fix the voicemail and it will stay dead forever
so
You know, it's like um
Send me money and say whether you vote for fix the voicemails or don't fix the voicemails
So we'll have like a it'll be like a race whichever side gets more money. That's what I'll do
Oh, yeah
Okay, I think I think that's it. Uh, end of the episode. See you next week. Goodbye. Goodbye
Take a deep breath in the state all of us are drowning in a while you have to cry
While you have to make it first. I hope there stays two sleeping dead in the purse