Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast, where we clip the mic every single time.
I'm Ben Saint, and who else is fuckin' here?
We got Nate Bestman, the best guy ever.
Konnichiwa minasamah onigashima.
Oh, hi ogozaimasu.
We got Lethal Aurora Mage here.
Oh, hi y'all.
Oh, Shinkansen desuwa, we got Hippocrit.
Guten Morgen.
Holy shit, fuckin' Nuremberg trial time, and we got Digibro.
Hungover, pissed off, ready to kill.
Oh, hi ogozaimasu.
What's goin' on?
You pissed off about the Crunchyroll Awards from yesterday, Digi?
I saw you streamin' those.
I'm pissed off about living in a shit toilet earth.
That's what I'm pissed off about.
I'm pissed off about everybody being wrong about everything.
I'm mad that, you know what?
I'm just sick and tired of pretending like it's okay for people to have different opinions from me.
But Digi, you just said there can't be a critical authority.
What the fuck, dude?
What do you have to say to that?
Well, obviously the man was wrong.
Obviously, you know what?
It's not about having authority.
It's about taking matters into my own hands, you know what I'm sayin'?
Public genocide and all that.
The beta uprising and whatnot.
Yeah.
You know, I thought, I was thinkin' about this after your loud video about how JoJo Part 5 has shit character designs or whatever, how the guys don't blend into the background.
And I was like, okay, fair.
But I think I know why everybody voted for it.
I mean, I don't know how they, I assume it works on Oscar's logic.
I think what they do, this is a complete guess, but everybody just saw like how, quote, fabulous all the JoJo posing is.
And how fabulous all the like thick outline characters look.
And that's all they needed.
I'll tell you, it's because the anime awards are a popularity contest.
Because it literally is fan-voted.
So it's just whatever's the most popular show in the world.
Oh, fan-voted should not even win every time.
That's a shit show in the making.
No, my rage had nothing to do with the actual award.
It was that what I livestreamed my reactions to the Crunchyroll Awards.
And I was shitting on the art in JoJo Part 5.
And my chat was like, was all pissed off at me.
So then I made a separate video screaming about it additionally.
And then, and I had also tweeted.
And it's one of those cases where, you know, when you're tweet, when you, when you make a spicy controversial tweet and it escapes from your audience and enters the open internet, that's what happened.
So it was just hundreds and hundreds of JoJo stands crawling out of the woodwork to call me a boomer for some reason.
There's a lot of those.
Is that what you call like a fan?
Is that what you call like a rabid fan of JoJo, a stand?
Well, hey, all right.
That's pretty funny.
They have those for other things, right?
Like a stand.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So it's like, it's a stand.
But for JoJo, it's a stand.
Duh.
Yeah.
Okay.
I think I know the lore behind the word stand.
It's because of the.
It's the Eminem song.
Yeah.
The Eminem.
Who's that?
I love Eminem.
There's dude, listen.
Listen, I'm white, so I cannot appreciate hip hop ever.
It's literally impossible.
Even when it's by a white guy.
Especially when it's by a white guy, because he's a fucking uncle Tom.
All right.
But when I was.
What was that mean?
Okay.
But in like, what does he mean?
Yeah.
I really like that song.
I didn't listen to Eminem or anything, but that song would come on the radio.
And I was like, oh, it's got that sample.
It's got that sample from that white guy.
It's got that non-hip hop sample that provides a bridge for understanding for me.
That song made me really sad.
I liked it.
Well, yeah, it's a good song.
You know, I was happy to see PCP member number 10, Jeff Thu, at the Crunchyroll Awards.
Oh, boy.
Representing our organization well.
It's nice to see how.
I mean, of course, Jeff would be there.
Of course.
I can't believe they let him give the the anime of the year award.
That was crazy.
That is that.
That's the top billing.
That is the top billing and they gave it to Jeff.
So clearly they're investing in his future, at least to a little bit.
The most Japan of all.
He loves Japan.
Period.
He's a guy that, you know, this was this.
This was fascinating to me.
Have you guys been watching Matt Pat's recent videos about like how
a company stole money from him and stuff?
Where he makes like extremely furiously, like his face stretches really angrily.
He's very funny.
I've been screenshotting his face.
Give us taken screenshots of his face during those videos.
Just posted them in the chat there.
He's just so mad.
We should put some in the show notes.
We should go back and find some if we can.
He's very mad.
He's extremely frustrated.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
OK, so Matt Pat recently, on his big video, Game Theory or whatever,
he made two videos now that are him basically calling out what he perceives at the very least
to be like underhanded and or shady business tactics by like large MCNs like the one that
he is signed to in particular.
Oh wait, wait, Matt Pat's having a problem with that?
Because I'm pretty sure he's signed to Studio 71.
Right?
OK, that is not the name.
Is that the one you were signed to, did you?
Yeah, because when I signed up for it, then they had like on the top of their website is
like Matt Pat, our main guy, and that was part of why I was why I signed up with them
because I just assumed that Matt Pat, the guy who everybody considers the YouTube guru,
would have picked the best MCN.
Oh yeah, I mean that's fair.
And it turns out that they fucked him over and he's really pissed.
Well, OK, I'm not so big a Studio 71.
I just don't think that's the that's definitely not the name he used and I can't fucking remember
what it is.
It could be a subsidiary company or whatever, you know.
That's definitely true.
But like what's, I'm sympathetic to his concerns and whatnot.
He feels ripped off specifically in that like, so he's signed up to an agreement where like
the money that he earns through AdSense on his channel gets delivered to this company first
then later gets paid out as is I think the standard procedure.
It's hard for me to have sympathy for Matt Pat, but it's even harder for me to have sympathy
for an MCN.
So I'm really torn here.
MCNs are evil.
They are all bad.
I have never heard a story of one being not bad and they don't do anything.
They litter because there's nothing they can do protections.
The only thing as far as they don't do that value.
No, they never did that because all they did the reason that people seem to think that
their MCNs were helping them with that the MCN just does the same thing that you yourself
are capable of doing.
Most people just don't know that.
Yeah, like the same steps that you consider that a valuable service.
Wait, what is this thing that you can do that they do for you?
I mean, they literally just like file counter notifications or like email the company and
try to get it fixed, but they have no more sway in doing that than you do as an individual.
Well, I mean, they might as a corporate entity, they might have more clout.
They do not.
Believe me, I know.
It's easier to just get your fans to email a company because then they get a lot of emails
and that will make them more likely to.
I mean, in these videos, that's like basically the only thing MatPat said is any value.
But as you said, it might just be again, nothing beyond what you can already do yourself.
But the reason I brought him up to begin with was just that like MatPat and Jeff,
okay, Jeff came from a marketing background or like a gaming journalism background before he
started his anime work.
And so he's got marketing on the mind from the very start of his channel,
which has helped him a lot and I'm not even bashing for it.
But the fascinating thing to me was to learn that MatPat here, I learned in his first video,
he just comes around and said this, maybe this was public knowledge, but I didn't know.
He straight up worked for an MCN before he started his channel game theory and like
worked on them in parallel.
And he just had the complete insider scoop as to how all this shit worked.
And I was like, well, no fucking wonder he's the guru of at least the YouTuber side guru
of like MCM and like knowledge about how to spread your company and optimal release schedules and
whatnot.
I guess nobody, I don't know, again, not to, I'm not shitting on either of them.
And it's not that they're worse or more inauthentic, but when you like lead with marketing,
I guess it just, it ebbs away at your like, you know, real gamerness and makes you feel
more corporatized, I guess.
Sure.
That's, that's all.
But I mean, I don't know, like it's, it's an interesting series of videos.
And it's like, I'm, MatPat is a very business savvy guy.
And it's surprising to me that he's getting as much traction as he is, considering like,
like his case for these things is like, he admits that like he signed an agreement with
these companies, Defy, defy is the name of the company, that like they would keep the money,
they'd pay him out later.
And he himself went out of his way to put himself in an even more like negative position
because of a specific request where they could like hold on to more of his money.
But like, but that's a side.
The 1.7 million is from like everybody signed with defy.
But like, after signing an agreement to put himself in this position, he is now after
the fact complaining that like business ventures have gone badly in this way.
And that like, while, while defy, excuse me, while defy, like made an investment or like
some bank made an investment in defy, that defy investment has gone away because defy
has folded up shop and gone under.
The bank is ally.
Thank you.
That's right.
Ally bank, like they invest in defy.
And so because the investment did not work out defy like overextended itself and failed
or whatever, it's understandable that ally bank not get their investment back.
But it's, but MatPat's claim is that it is not fair and not understandable that these
YouTubers signed to this MCM do not get their pay.
But I would argue that this is all tied up in like the legal agreements they made.
And so it's kind of hard for me to sympathize, especially with MatPat himself.
The leader of the bunch.
And you know him well.
The MCM contracts are extremely vague and they leave a lot of like, if you read it,
you should be able to recognize that and like know that you're going to get fucked.
Like this just takes me back to like when, when Ben faith sealed his fate by agreeing to work on,
you know, what?
Don't say it.
T.F.
Don't say analysis.
Anarchy.
When he agreed to do that and I didn't, I was like, well, this is me making a better
decision. I know I'm right.
I have no sympathy.
And it's the same for everybody who's ever signed to an MCM.
I'm sitting over here being like, I've gotten offers.
I knew this was retarded.
So I didn't do it.
You made the mistake.
Listen, why am I supposed to feel bad for you?
Look, you, you don't look.
All right.
Yes.
I waited until midnight and I, and I, and I said Dr. Wolfe into my mirror three times
and he appeared and he reached out with the contract and I signed it in blood.
And I, you know, it was just, I was peer pressured is what I'm saying.
I was peer.
Okay.
But me, I had social fortitude and I did not give in.
I guess is like, surely you expect like if you sign up to anything, you expect that
they will fuck you over if they can.
Like nobody's a good guy.
Whenever you want to like, like with studio 71, the way that they pitched themselves,
it's, it's crazy because they basically pitched themselves as like, oh, we are too good for you.
Cause like when I, the contract I signed was like, uh, we'll have you for one year minimum.
And then after that, basically depending on if we think that it's working out,
like if you're growing at a good enough rate, we keep you on.
But if you're, if we think you're not growing or like you're not really participating,
then we're going to cut you.
So that makes it out like, oh yeah, this is like a really, like they're really serious about you.
You know, they really want to, but then I signed up and they never
did a single thing for me the whole time.
And like after a year had passed, they were still taking my money because, you know,
basically their contract is just, we can just have you for us.
Like, yeah, a year is required, but then after that, uh, you know, it's up to us,
whether we cut you loose or not.
So they're just taking my money and doing nothing.
And so I had to like send them a number of very harshly worded emails
before I was able to end that relationship.
And I had to be like straight up cut me off because you are taking my fucking money.
Yeah, it took a while.
It took a lot of, because they kept being like, well, but we could, you know,
well, we could work something out.
Like, you know, let's talk about it.
And I'm like, it's already, you've taken so much of my money already.
Like you've already gone way past the point of reaching my trust completely.
There is no way I would work with you anymore.
You know,
So, you know, like to be fair, I understand that matpat is just like the leading voice here.
And he's using his platform for something that I suppose is fair.
If this was me and I had made the mistake of signing with an MCM,
I would want somebody like matpat to like be trying to get me my fair share of the money or whatever.
I don't know.
I guess like, please listen to the show and look at these fucking matpat faces.
They are just click through all the links down there, everybody.
Oh, he's, he's a, he's a treasure.
Where did you post them?
They're in the audio links there.
Click on the audio links, uh, chat down there.
And uh, you'll see.
Does he look a little like purple?
He's a little purple.
He died.
Okay.
He does not acknowledge in the video, but between these two,
he put a little purple schmutz in his hair.
Why?
It looks weird as fuck now that I've noticed it.
I don't know.
But as a guy who loves purple, I'm a little bit pissed that he's co-opting my color.
I, I, I was thinking, I was literally thinking of doing that exactly.
Can you ping me in the chat?
Because I'm the cop killer and I should have purple hair.
Well, I mean, now you'll be matpat too, so.
No, he fucked.
I guess.
Lame.
No, but you gotta, you gotta do black and white.
You gotta have a zebra hair.
Oh, that'd be cool.
You know, I mean, I'm already fucking gray.
I'm already graying at a, at an alarming pace.
So, uh, I guess I better just lean into it.
Graying could be a good look though.
Yeah, I don't know.
They're worst things.
Oh.
Like being autistic, which I also am.
But I mean, the reason I brought that up was originally just because like,
Jeff reminded me, Jeff is matpat.
Uh, they're just the same guy and that's fine.
And that's fine.
Um, yeah, I don't know.
I don't, uh, Matpat doesn't have the same flaccidity.
He's more of a.
Flaccidity.
He's more of an animated character.
Okay, we were watching, I'm shout out to May for calling Jeff through the most
flaccid man alive during the live stream yesterday.
But what is worth, Victor's the one who came up with that one.
Oh, did he really?
Okay.
Jeff, I love you, but that is hilarious.
Victor called him Jeff Flaccid.
He looked.
Okay.
I can't tell the difference between Jeff and Arkada, by the way.
If you see them next to each other.
I don't know who Arkada is.
He's, he's matpat.
Go, go into the Crunchyroll Awards and at the very end, you can go to my video
upload of it.
I'm not watching the Crunchyroll.
No, just, just skip to the very end where everybody's on screen and like,
Arkada standing right behind Jeff and they look exactly the same.
Like they have the same haircut, same glasses, same face.
Who wears like the red like suit?
Yeah.
Yes.
That's him.
Oh, yeah.
He's like, he's like Jeff with a blonde ponytail.
I'm a little bit pissed.
You're in the same like doll maker, like character building program and you just
swap the hair.
Well, that's the thing.
He's not, no, he's not blonde anymore.
He now has the same hair as Jeff.
Like at the Crunchyroll Awards, they had the same color, hairstyle, everything.
Like they look exactly the same.
I suppose I respected that he, he dressed up in cosplayed as the manager.
From, from, as Jeff, one cosplay was Jeff Thu.
The other cosplay was manager from Zombie Lens Saga.
And I was like, damn it.
I just don't know what my, my looks are.
Oh, I love the better for Zombie Lens Saga.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna watch that show one of these days.
Anyway.
Watch it.
Oh my God.
You haven't watched the shame.
I will.
It looks really good.
I watched Digi's review and it was very informative,
but it looks worth my time at the very least.
Are we, uh, all right.
Are we off that topic?
Because I had something.
We're off, we're off it.
All right.
Well, speaking of, speaking of hair,
I want to tell you a story and I almost don't want to tell this,
but I think, I think by the time that this comes out,
I will have made peace with it.
I hope.
Okay.
You know, this will force me to make peace though.
I'll no longer have any choice.
All right.
So a couple of weeks ago, I was like,
all right, I need a fucking haircut.
So I fucking, I don't, I had cut my own hair.
I've been doing this for years.
So I took some buzzers and I went into the bathroom and I looked in the mirror
and I just like, I don't know.
I like, I liked the hair long in the back.
I liked it long on top and in front,
but the way it was like puffing out on the sides, it was bad.
So I just took it and I trimmed one side and I cut like one side short,
like quite short and I looked at it and I was like, I like it.
I took some pictures.
I put them in my discord.
People were like, hey, this is look, this is a good look for you.
I was like, okay, cool.
I was like, yeah.
So I got a little like short on the side cut.
It's nice.
It's neat.
So I go back and I look at it.
I take some like pictures from the side and I look at it and I examine it and I'm like,
sloppy, sloppy.
So I want to neaten it up.
So I go in.
Yeah.
So I go in with the, with the buzzers, right?
And I put it a little shorter and I just, and I start buzzing and I'm like,
oh, I can't see.
So I, I rig up a makeshift, a sort of, uh, oh God, what's a Rube Goldberg machine?
Yeah.
I use a USB cable to tie to the back of a mirror and I hang the mirror over the
shower door and I tie the other end to the, the shower handle so that it is hanging.
And then I stuff a lot of tissue paper behind it to tilt it at just such an angle so that
I can see the wall mirror and this hanging mirror reflect the side of my head so I can
get a good view.
And so I go in with the buzzers and I cut it short and I'm like, oh,
shit, that's a little too short.
That's a little too short.
And then I'm like, oh, shit.
Okay.
What do I do?
Got to clean this up.
And I'm like, wait a minute.
I got, I want to get, I want to get like a, I want this to be neat.
I want this to be neat.
I want this to look deliberate.
I don't want this to look like an accident.
Long story short, I grabbed my fucking razor and I shaved the entire side of my head bald.
So I just have a, so I just have a straight up Skrillex cut right now.
That's what I'm rocking.
And I'm going to be frank.
I don't like it.
I don't like it, but I think that I will like it.
I think that once it grows out, maybe like a quarter inch.
So it's not like bald.
I think once it grows out a little bit, I will be fine with it and like it again.
But right now.
I can't even picture you with this haircut you're describing.
I have it.
We all need to see.
Post image.
I think, oh God, it's really bad.
Look, you can get one later if you don't have it now.
I have one on my phone.
I will post one in a second.
Okay.
But the, the, the, the, the, so I have been, I have not left my room in several days without
putting a hat on.
I'm just waiting.
You're really proud of this haircut.
You can tell.
I'm wait, no, I told you, I don't like it.
I don't like, I don't like the way that it looks being like
completely bare on one side.
It's bizarre.
I look like a white nationalist.
I look like I'm going to go and, and curb stomps to minorities.
It triggers me just thinking about it.
Just looking at myself in the mirror.
I have a panic attack.
I watched the American history X the other day.
Excellent film.
Everyone should check it out.
Anyway, that's what I have to say.
I'm literally shaking.
Ben, was it worth saving the $14 or the $10 on a decent haircut
to, to do all this, to put yourself through this?
It was because if I had spent that $14, not only would I be out the $14,
I would have missed out on an experience, an adventure,
a negative experience, but an experience nonetheless.
That's true.
Hold on.
And now you'll grow as a person because of it.
Maybe.
I don't know.
No, Ben won't learn.
Ben won't change.
I'm not sure.
He won't evolve.
I'm going to try and post one of the pictures I took in the discord.
It looks bad.
Get ready to laugh.
Get ready to fucking laugh at me,
everyone.
I'm looking.
It's going to be, hold on.
Sorry.
It's, I'm gay.
Oh no.
Yeah.
Cut this out.
Cut this all out.
Oh, it looks so fucking shit, dudes.
It looks so fucking shit.
Well, I'm very excited to see that.
See, not only was this picture like it's bad and from a bad angle,
but also my hair was greasy because I hadn't showered at the time.
Well, there's your problem right there.
So I just look like, so I just look like fucking trash.
Well, good.
Here we go.
There it is.
God, why have you done this?
No, it's fine.
It's, yeah.
I mean, you just look like, you just look like you go to art school.
Yeah.
That's, that's basically true.
It's good.
Well, the worst thing about this is that it's greasy.
When it grows out, when it's like a quarter inch long
and it looks like I have hair there, I will be fine with it.
Yeah.
It's actually less bad than I thought it was going to be.
Okay.
Well, thank you.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'd like, I'd like cut the longness shorter elsewhere, I guess, but I don't know.
In the back.
Just like everywhere, I guess.
Especially the back, I suppose.
I like it long.
I like it long, though.
No, fair enough.
So that's my, that's my hair story.
This is why men invented money, Ben, so that you can have other people exchange
goods and services, in this case services, so that you cannot, you know.
Well, you know what, Nate?
Here's the thing.
Yeah.
I could go to a barber and get a professional cut, but you know what?
That would be an assembly line cut.
This is, this is an indie, this is an indie cut.
This is, this is a work of art, not necessarily a good one,
but this is a work of art.
This is unique.
This is a post-modern work of art, so yeah.
You know, sometimes I wonder what would happen if I was just, you know,
should I just shave all my hair off?
I did shave all my hair off in college one time.
And, well, the other, a while back, I had Munchie and Kazi and Crack and my friend,
John, we were all hanging out and I showed them fake pictures from my Facebook of me
when I had a shaved head and everyone agreed this is a bad look for you.
Don't do this again.
I was like, you're right.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't, I don't have a head shave.
You look like the lumberjack look.
That's, that's still the, like, literally, T-Bap Q&A, his peak bend look.
As it was peak Nate look.
Yeah.
And I'm, you know, I'm getting back to it because I'm growing the beard back.
And I'm looking.
Well, good.
That's good.
Also, I'm getting thinner.
I'm like, down to 100.
The beard's going a long way.
Both add a lot to this.
I'm down to 160 pounds.
That's great.
I like, I like.
Fuck, Ben weighs less than I do.
What's going on?
I like.
He's working it.
I like where things are going.
I like where things are going for, for old Ben Saint.
I agree.
Yeah.
Good work.
Just need to up your gamer score and then you'll be just winning all aspects of life.
Well, one, the one area that I'm lacking in is that I have a shitty old phone that
grinds to a halt when I PVP in Pokemon Go.
So once I fix that, I will be perfect.
I will be, I will have achieved perfect cell stats.
What do you have?
What do you have right now?
Samsung Galaxy S5.
It's like six or seven years old.
Yeah.
Time to upgrade.
Time to upgrade that shit.
Well, that's the tale of Ben's hair and everyone mock him.
Please make meme edits of this.
Like, like put like Nazi tattoos on the skull.
Don't put, don't put this picture on the show notes.
Just like, don't put it.
We have to put it in the show notes.
You kidding me?
No, but it's Ben.
Yeah, we've been discussing it consistently for minutes.
Ben, they have to see it.
They have to.
It's too late.
You've revoked your rights.
I wish I'd taken a, I wish I'd taken a less greasy one.
If you want to take another less greasy one, we can replace this.
But if that doesn't show up, this is the one that's going out.
Okay.
So it's on you.
It's on you.
I will try and flatter this admittedly unflattering look.
As best I can.
Okay, good.
I want to see those beauty shots in the chat.
Yeah.
All right.
Listen, I went, I was out for community with, with Kazi yesterday.
I kept the hat on the whole time, just didn't, didn't acknowledge it.
Yeah.
Did she say anything?
Did she laid any mean remarks?
Well, there was a moment, there was a moment where I got scared and I started sweating.
When she was like, I heard you gave yourself a haircut.
Talking about the old one that I posted pictures of on the discord.
And I was like, oh, yeah, I did.
And she was like, oh, yeah, I was just wondering about that.
And I was like, oh, yeah.
Anyway, PVP, let's, let's battle Pokemon Go.
Deliberately doesn't take off hat.
Yeah, that's exactly what happened.
Yeah.
Um, so I've been, you've been lying to everyone.
I've been deceiving them.
Oh, but it's okay.
I know the truth has to come out at some point.
So it might as well come out here on the podcast in front of like.
It'll force you to adapt.
Thousands of people.
Accept it.
Yep.
That's good.
So what else is going on ladies and gentlemen?
Hi, I have a story, a small story.
I finally picked up pens and pencils after seven years of not drawing traditionally.
And I like it.
Oh no.
Is it good?
Have you lost skill?
I, I, I, I apparently I have, I have a, I have an art style that I didn't know I have.
Yeah.
It's really good.
And it's different from your usual stuff.
It's shaded really nice, but in a different, I mean your shading is usually pretty nice.
But there are any examples we could look at on like for the show notes on like Twitter.
So yeah, yeah.
Hold on.
The sense, it has a, you, you draw a very, it made your, I don't know,
something about the way you drew it with traditionally, it felt very dynamic.
Yeah.
It added dynamism.
Dynamism.
It's your usual style.
I'm pretty sure you can just say dynamic.
It added dynamic too.
No, dynamism is when you died in NAMM.
And now you are an ism.
And you have a tism about it.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh yeah, it looks pretty cool.
I like it.
I like, I like the hair.
I really like the way the hair looks.
Oh yeah, it's pretty good.
It's like a character from Spawn.
A little bit.
I dig the shading a lot.
I like characters with no mouths.
I generally find that I prefer.
Especially women.
Everyone's, I feel like I prefer everyone's traditional art over there digital.
Like when I see, I'm just more impressed when I see like a, you know,
it's just more of your, more of your mark comes through no matter what.
Like, that's true.
And especially in a case like say, I love Ben's Inktober drawings a whole lot.
Because when you look at the digital art he does, you can tell that he has drawn
the same line 8,000 times trying to get it exactly right.
Whereas when it's ink, like, I mean, I prefer thicker lines anyways.
So like having to go over the lines multiple times makes the picture cooler to me than it
would be if it was less rough.
When I did Ink, like two, two October's ago or three October's ago when I did all this,
a lot of people like those.
And I have all these Copic markers that I just don't fucking use.
That fucking, I always think that I should.
The fucking robot you drew was like the coolest thing you've ever drawn in that Inktober.
I didn't even, I colored that thing with like a red, like, not even a Copic.
I colored that with like a red, like, fine point like Sharpie.
And it came out really good somehow.
Is there a link to that we can put in the show notes?
Because that's cool too.
Just for comparison sake.
Yeah, I could find, I could find that.
Let me look.
Okay, all right.
I think my cat is very concerned about me doing traditional art.
Your cat is concerned?
Yeah, because I'm making noise and doing something he's not used to seeing me do.
Yeah, okay.
Is he causing any issues?
No, no, he's just, he's just looking at me with confusion and mulling at me.
It's just like, are you okay?
Hey, you know, on the subject of like, I don't know, doing artistic stuff a little differently
than normal, I was actually just proposed today.
I suppose I'll just say by one nexus mania, a guy I'm a big fan of and who also seems to like me,
he asked me if I wanted to do some like relatively professional voice acting work,
like with pay for like a pretty decent amount of like runtime and stuff.
And I was like, Nate, remember back to those youthful days when you really wanted to be
an anime voice actor.
And I was just like, so I told him like, I am interested.
Like if the script's bad, I'm not going to do it.
So like get back to me with more information and shit.
But I don't know, I really like nexus and I think it'd just be really cool.
And I'm kind of just excited to do more voice acting work stuff.
So, so here's my call out to everybody.
If you got projects that you want people to do voice acting work on and you think I'd be the man
for the job, fucking at me on Twitter and I will only do it for pay.
So I'm just letting you know right now.
You have to pay me whatever is an appropriate amount for my time.
I'm just going to warn you right now, Nate.
I know how much you love to hug those JKs,
but when you go to them conventions, you got to stay away.
Wait, what is it?
What is a JK?
That's a JK rolling.
It's a Japanese slang for high schoolers.
Joshi Kosei.
I totally knew that and wasn't pretending.
Okay, I get it.
I get what you're putting up.
Anyway, but yeah, I'm just saying like I've wanted to voice act.
People tell me I have a good voice.
You know, that's cool.
But it occurs to me that I haven't done much like like fictional character voice acting
outside of like like some t-baps skits for a while ago and more some more relatively recently,
as a matter of fact.
You know, speaking of voice acting, so I had to do.
Yeah, let me just finish my point.
It's just voice acting is a skill that I respect.
It is not just like talking into a microphone.
You have to inflect and get the right emotions captured and stuff.
So it's actually kind of exciting and I'm looking forward to opportunities to do so.
So, okay, that's it.
That's it.
All right, go on, Ben.
So I was, so I talked about the audiobook deal with Oolulilia and Oolulilia is dragon ass
because he's like, okay, we both had to make accounts on this site called ACX,
which is like sort of a gateway site to like iTunes and Audible and stuff.
And I made mine as the producer and he made his as an author and the idea is that he is supposed
to propose me a deal to like do like a split profit project thing where like I send him audio files
and he like accepts or denies them.
He did that.
He made the account and then he asked me like, how do I send you the request to do the thing?
And I was like, here's a guide.
Here's a full guide to like how an author should do this and like where to go.
And then he was like, yeah, it's pretty late.
And you know, I'm really addicted to Skyrim or oblivion or whatever right now.
So, you know, I might just get back to this later and I've been waiting for like a week,
maybe like a week now, maybe less than a week, but it's days.
And he just hasn't hit the one fucking button, the one fucking button.
He has to push to fucking make this thing go through.
Oolulilia, this is your, this is your, your one chance.
This is your one chance to fix this shit.
We bring down the full terror of the PCB.
Look, I don't know where he has to look because I'm not, I don't have his kind of account,
but there's just like one fucking button he has to push.
He just has to send me like one thing.
And I know the feeling.
He's probably just been busy and doesn't want to take the five minutes it's going to take to do it.
I get it.
I as a, as a, as a chronic ass-dragger myself, I get it.
I've seen what Elder Scrolls does to people and I'm not surprised that this is the outcome.
Anyway, here's that, here's that tweet.
Here's that, here's that robot drawing that I did.
Oh, okay, sick, sick.
Um, but anyway.
Oh, that's so cool.
Thank you.
It's like Amy Rose Gundam.
I really, I really like the, the, uh, what's it called?
Like with the, with the fires and like in the, on the ground and the-
Jet propulsion.
Yeah, yeah.
I bet it's like blasting off the ground.
Yeah, I really like that effect.
Yes.
I think, I like this.
Watch me tie this into current relevant topics because Ben, I believe you drew this
not long after reading volume one of Battle Angel Alita.
Oh, it looks like something from that.
I might, it was around that time.
But wait, now there's a live action film adaptation.
Before we, I will, we'll talk about that, although I haven't seen it.
But before we say that, I just want to say that on the voice acting, I had to do voices
for the different characters in Legend of the Ten Elemental Masters.
And one of the things that I'm very unsure about and very like,
not sure what the best thing to do about it is the book is written like a screenplay
and you, it'll, it'll say like character's name and then the dialogue.
It doesn't have like, you know, John said, Knuckles said, Steve said.
And I'm not sure whether it would be, like I tried to just do the voices so that you
could tell who was doing who.
I don't know if I could differentiate them enough.
I don't know.
Like I'm wondering if I should bite the bullet and like say their name.
You know, like say like, you know, Tyler.
That's a good question for him to clarify.
Well, I don't, I don't necessarily trust his judgment.
Okay.
Fair enough.
I don't know.
Yeah, you'll have to make a call there.
That's, that's interesting though.
I might like listen back to it and be like, kind of like, is it distinct enough?
Do you, can you tell when two is talking or when our science teacher is talking?
Remember our boy, name I can't remember, guy who did all the Harry Potter books.
Who, you know.
Yes.
Um, um, not, not, not really the trees.
He did the, he did Game of Thrones audiobooks.
Um, I can't remember.
My mom like loved him more than my father.
She ever loved him.
Jim Hennig.
No, I can't remember whoever that guy was.
He, he knocked it out of the park and he did a great job differentiating like every voice.
Jim Dale.
That's the guy.
Stephen Fry.
Actually Stephen Fry did narrate them the, in the UK,
but Jim Dale narrated the USA version.
I wonder why.
What they do differently.
Well, whatever.
Anyway.
Oh, Harry.
Harry.
No.
Cool.
That was the Ron line.
The classic Ron line.
Just whenever anyone says cool, the way he says it is cool.
And it's great.
It's not even bad.
It's good.
Yeah.
It's just good.
Um, okay.
But anyway, when, when Hermione says Harry, she says,
Harry, oh, Harry, oh, Harry.
What do you, what do you fuck?
It's good.
How does Stephen Fry say, say, cool?
Does he say the same thing, Gib?
Did you listen to that?
Well, yeah, I did listen to those.
I just don't know how, like, I can't, I mean, I can't remember.
Look it up now, Gib.
It probably wasn't nearly, it probably wasn't nearly as distinctive.
Yeah.
Is Jim Dale American?
No, he's British.
He's British too.
I don't think so.
Okay.
So then, yeah.
They just got two different British guys
to do the American versus like British dub of the same story.
Although, I mean, so I know in Britain, like the first one was
called the Philosopher's Stone or whatever.
Is there like actual translation?
Like, or like localization differences or something?
You know what I think?
About the book?
I don't know.
Yeah, in the book.
Wouldn't think so.
Don't they call it the Philosopher's Stone in the book?
I think in the early books, there were some like, like,
name convention changes made for the American versions.
Why the fuck did they call it the Sorcerer's Stone?
Why isn't the goddamn Philosopher's Stone,
that's a staple fantasy item?
You know what?
I'm over it.
I've been thinking about this for 20 years.
I assume that there was some kind of religious connotation
to Philosopher's Stone.
Oh, you think so?
Maybe.
I don't think so.
It's like demonic or something and they like.
It's a philosophy.
I mean, Philosopher is like, it's not like, I mean,
sorcery is more magical than Philosopher.
That is, I mean, that's totally, totally true.
Totally like more objective.
Those books were protested by religious people
who didn't like witchcraft in America.
It's very possible that it's just that they thought kids
would not pick up a book called Philosopher's Stone,
but they might pick up one called Sorcerer's Stone.
I read an article online.
About like, you know, like people being like,
Harry Potter is demonic.
You know, everyone's fucking falling into devil witchcraft.
Thought it was real for a long time.
Turned out it was an onion article
that had been passed around as the genuine thing.
And it made me fucking mad because I thought it was real.
I was like, oh, so no one understands.
It's not, I love Harry Potter.
There have been books.
I remember researching this for like an,
for an essay during my time at uni.
Like I researched like books that are like on Amazon
detailing how Harry Potter is demonic.
And then you can buy it.
And I didn't, I didn't, I decided this was stupid
and I wanted to do something else.
But I saw it.
It's strange.
Okay. So some people think it or whatever reason.
Yeah. Yeah.
That lady that claimed that like Pokemon Go was demons.
Yeah.
Summoning demons or whatever.
And like they sexually blessed her in her sleep.
Whoa, what the fuck?
Whoa, okay.
That's a new twist on an old classic.
Oh, because it like appeared on top of her or something.
Yeah.
She got the game.
She turned it on.
AR mode was on.
There was a Pokemon in her room.
She screamed.
I feel like that's the next,
that could easily be the next, you know, thing.
Like.
Next Me Too movement.
Yeah.
We got Pokemon Molestation.
So I wonder if like in a lot of these cases,
I don't feel like people come to the conclusion
that a thing is witchcraft.
I feel like they hear somehow in the ether,
someone putting forth that,
and then they just also decide to believe it themselves.
I mean, not to be overly edgy,
but I do believe religion is largely linked
with straight up stupidity.
So, you know, we're just gonna throw that out there.
To anybody who believes one,
I'm likely to think is pretty deep into the other,
or has been deeply misled, you know.
Dude, I'm big into the stupidity fandom.
Dude, I love Jesus' style.
All right, whatever.
I didn't have much to say about Battle Angel Alita,
because I haven't seen the movie,
but I have read the book.
A friend of mine saw it and was saying good things.
He said it was fun, not necessarily good,
but a very fun watch,
and everyone had a good time and laughed a lot.
So.
Okay.
Oh, so I have.
Don't know if that's what they were going for.
Yeah.
I would say.
I have read the, uh, sorry.
Now, now you can talk about the movie.
I would just say that, like, uh,
because I did see, I made a video about it already.
Her eyes are really big, you guys.
I thought that was cool.
I think that was, I like that.
If you think that's cool, you'll love it.
Like, yeah.
I'm just wondering, in universe,
like, humans don't look like that,
so who made the choice to make this girl look like an anime?
Well, she's a doll, so she's got big doll eyes.
Yeah, she's not.
She's a robot.
But someone artistically, in universe,
decided to make her look doll-like and not like a normal human.
Someone made that choice, right?
Or maybe there was a technological limitation.
Well, he just kind of finds her head in the garbage.
So, like, she already looks like that at the start.
But, um, but yeah.
Is she a curiae, or like she was human,
and then, like, gets her body.
She has, her brain is human.
So, like, is that the case in the manga?
Does she have a human brain in the manga?
I think so, yeah.
I read the first, I only read the first volume.
When my friend John saw it, and the first thing I asked him was,
do you see a giant robot man fucking crack people's skulls open,
like chestnuts, and slurp their brains out of their skull holes,
like ice cream scoops?
And he said no, and I was like, well.
It is a PG-13 movie, but there is some intense violence
that happens in it for being PG-13, and it's dark,
just as dark as the, I mean, if you've seen the original OVA,
like, literally everything that happens in it is also in the movie.
So it's like a huge spoiler to even go watch the OVA.
But, uh, yeah, it's, it's a, I think you'll,
I think you will enjoy it.
If you think that her eyes look cool, you'll enjoy the movie.
I think, well, I think they look weird,
but I think that that's intentional, and it makes sense,
and I don't mind it, you know?
That's the way, that's the right way to do it.
I read the manga of that, the first two volumes, I think,
when I was 12, and it was like the edgiest, like, deadliest,
there were boobies in it, there was blood, there was killing,
it was like, oh, oh, oh no!
There's a scene, I read it, I borrowed it from you, Digi,
and I read it at your house, and I remember the scene,
it's like, the guy, the robot guy, he's done that,
he's holding like a woman, and he's, and he's bitten her head open,
and just like, slurped her brain out, and Alita like,
is jumping at him to attack him, and he just like,
tosses this like, body at her, and she's like tumbling,
and she's like tumbling through the end, like her dead eyes,
or like, and her like, head is like, open,
and she's naked in her hairs, and I was like,
I was like, so chilled, I was like, so chilled by this image,
and even thinking about it now.
When I think about it, it's funny, because like,
I've seen the OVA a bunch of times over the years,
and read the first volume of the manga,
and my impression of it was always just like,
Mad Max, Violence, Madness, you know,
it's just 80s, 80s, Violence, Dijour,
so that's kind of how I painted it in my video about the movie,
but then like, fans of the manga were all like,
swarming me like, no, it is absolutely about the story,
it's not just violent craziness,
you just got to get like, three or four volumes in,
or whatever, and then it's like, oh,
it's just this masterpiece of storytelling and artwork,
and I was like, maybe it becomes that.
All right, I guess, I mean,
definitely the early volumes are definitely
just Mad Max insanity, but, sure, sure.
You know, so I guess,
I mean, if their goal is to adapt the OVA to live action,
then if it did that.
I mean, they added in definitely a lot of plot points
from later into the manga to just explain things more,
because the OVA is just like,
basically two random disconnected stories
from the manga, from early on,
that like, don't really give you much of a sense of the world,
or like, what's, like, it doesn't really give you a sense
of the idea that there is more to it,
whereas the movie adds in a lot of detail
that gives you the sense that there's a lot more going on,
and they leave it very open for a sequel as well.
So is, I've been hearing, I've been hearing people say this,
and I forget if you went into this in any detail,
but like, is this the first non-horrible, like,
anime adaptation?
Speed Racer!
Oh, okay, I forgot Speed Racer.
Nate, didn't we watch Speed Racer, like, together
when we were, like, in high school or something?
I don't remember if we watched it together.
I think I remember watching it in the basement.
That's possible, I remember loving it.
I loved it, yeah.
It was dope as hell.
I loved it.
It's my favorite movie.
It's so fun.
And then I found out later that it was, like, you know,
a sort of, it was sort of unpopular with, like, a lot of people.
It was totally panned.
It was entirely panned.
And I was shocked.
You just get ready for it, I don't think.
But I only found this out at, like,
I think it was Egoraptor was defending it or something,
or some people were saying, like, this movie's,
like, when I, the time that I heard that the movie was maligned,
it was when I heard people saying,
this movie is unfairly maligned,
and actually it's great in a masterpiece,
and I was like, hey, I didn't know anyone was panning it,
but good on you.
Good.
Thanks for defending this movie.
I didn't know it was being attacked.
I had heard nothing positive about it until Egoraptor,
and then, and Film Crit Hulk then said it was, like,
one of his favorite movies.
And when I read his review,
it's what inspired me to go watch it.
And I was like, holy fuck, this is the best movie ever.
Yeah, everyone should definitely watch it immediately,
especially if you're an anime fan at all.
I definitely think, well,
the thing is a lot of fans of Speed Racer hate the movie
because it's not an accurate Speed Racer movie, per se.
How many of those are left from the fucking 50s?
Who is a fan of original Speed Racer?
How many?
Yeah, exactly.
You know, it's fine.
I totally get it.
I'm sure there's a great lore, and it, you know,
I would absolutely be the kind of guy who would be
ragging on the movie for not being a good enough adaptation
if I was a fan of Speed Racer,
which I've never seen in my life.
So I totally sympathize with that,
but what we have is just so good on its own.
Here's the thing.
The original Speed Racer is like a landmark moment
in animation and cartoons generally,
and it's like a cultural touchstone.
It doesn't need defending, you know?
Yeah, that's true.
It doesn't need advocates, it's fine.
And the new movie, its strengths are very different
from the strengths of the original Speed Racer,
like that, whatever, that revolutionized anime
or something, whatever.
By new, you mean like 10 years old.
Sure, yeah.
Wait, are you talking about the new movie
or the original animation?
I'm talking about the Speed Racer movie.
It's like 12 years old.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I was gonna, like, but the original,
what it's got, its strength, it's got its own story.
This new one is like a visual masterpiece,
like the feeling of like-
It is a camp, it is a camp feast, extravaganza.
And I just don't think that, like,
at all was what hardcore Speed Racer fans
like were into Speed Racer original for.
So like, it's a totally different-
Not at all.
So I could see them being not happy with that,
but for those of us who never gave a shit
about Speed Racer, particularly to begin with,
you know, we can be less biased.
I will add as well that while Speed Racer and Alita
might be the only two good, like, Hollywood
live-action anime adaptations,
there are tons of good live-action anime from Japan,
like where they just, you know,
they make tons of live-action adaptations.
I always wanted to see the Death Note ones that I hear are good.
The Death Note ones are not that good, I would not-
I want to tell us, it's like, is there a
live-action attack on Titan?
Is it good, if it exists?
There is one.
I don't know if it's good.
I like the live-action Rony Kenshin movies.
Kashern has a really interesting one.
I mean, there's tons.
I was just looking at lists,
and there's just like an endless sea
of live-action anime adaptations.
Stuff that I would never have imagined,
like in Tama, has like a live-action film.
Like, there's all kinds of shit.
My friend who saw Alita yesterday,
he said that he said,
like, everyone in the theater was laughing.
And so-
So that doesn't sound good.
That sounds bad.
It doesn't sound good.
I don't think that the movie is a-
Is it funny?
I mean, it's a Robert Rodriguez movie.
Like, they're all cheesy on purpose.
They're always like, you know,
so the movie is extremely fucking corny.
But like, you don't get the sense
that it doesn't know that.
Now, it's not all in a good way,
because like, a lot of the side actors
are fucking terrible.
Like, there's plenty of like villains
who's just acting is so bad
that it is cringe-worthy.
And sometimes Alita's facial expressions
get really uncanny or the dialogue is-
Like, sometimes the dialogue is really corny
and you could tell it's on purpose,
but you hate it anyways.
And other times it's corny,
but it works and it's fun.
But like, if you go into it with the mindset
that like, this is a movie I can laugh at
and that is fine,
then you will probably have a good time with it.
Yeah, all right.
I could see myself-
I mean, my instincts are like,
okay, I'm ready for Ghost in the Shell Zero here.
Let's, you know, ramp up-
It's a lot better than-
How do you guys feel?
I feel a little gross
when I see that it's an American adaptation.
Like, I, like,
I mean, I haven't seen the movie,
I don't know if it's good personally,
but like, the way they did,
they did the American remake
of fucking Ghost in the Shell.
They did the American remake of Old Boy.
Now they did this American version
of Battle Angel Alita.
I hate that shit.
On principle, I hate it.
It makes me feel dirty.
It's gross.
I want to see fucking Japanese people
in these fucking-
Ordinarily, ordinarily, I would avoid these movies.
Like, I didn't see Ghost in the Shell
or the American Old Boy,
but like, the thing about those movies
is that they were clearly like studio movies
with like an attached director
where it was just about like using an IP.
With this case, James Cameron
has wanted to make this movie for an eternity.
And like, he's clearly just a huge fan
of Battle Angel Alita
and he like worked with Robert,
you know, Robert Rubio directed it,
but he worked with him on it
and like, I think James Cameron even co-wrote it
and like, when you watch it, like I said,
if, I'm sure Cameron was mostly a fan of the old OVA
because it is visually really distinctive
and has super memorable moments in it.
So I think that like, literally every second
of the OVA, practically, is in the movie.
Like, it's so accurate that it's,
it might as well have used it as like a storyboard,
you know, and then everything they added in
is stuff from the manga.
So like, it, and none of the people
who have read the manga seem to have any problem
with the story or the way it's told.
And like, it's also not a story about Japanese people.
It's set in like a melting pot post-apocalypse,
you know, world where there's people of all races.
And like, Christoph Waltz plays Doc Edo
and he looks exactly like him.
Like, it's, I was like, oh my God.
Like, yes, that was exactly who they should get
to play this role.
It's perfect.
And he does a great job, of course,
because he's Christoph Waltz,
but most of the acting is pretty fucking terrible.
I mean, fair enough.
Fair enough.
Also, I want to clarify that I know Old Boy is Korean,
not Japanese.
It is based on a manga, though.
Or I don't know.
Oh, really?
I had no idea.
I think it's based on a manga.
I think it's actually based on a Japanese manga.
Let me look it up.
Okay.
Well, that's cool.
I mean, either way, the movie, you know,
but that's the thing, that's the thing.
Let's just say that it's a,
let's say it's a Japanese manga.
Yeah, it is.
It is, in fact, a Japanese manga that's based on it.
Okay.
So that's interesting.
Because like, okay, what right does,
let's just say for, I mean,
I don't believe in this kind of division stuff, necessarily.
I see the point of like,
if you're telling a Japanese story,
like about Japanese people,
like, you know, about Japanese lore
or current politics or any of that stuff,
then like, it seems pretty logical
to like make it with Japanese actors and whatnot.
But like, are Koreans so similar to Japanese?
The Asians all fucking hate each other,
as I understand it.
Yeah, I guess so.
So I mean, what is what more important,
like the artistry that the new people like bring to it
and if they honor like, you know, what's,
because Old Boy is like one of the most beloved movies
of all time, by like, film buffs.
I mean, Old Boy is by far the most egregious,
because like, there's already a live action movie.
It didn't need a remake, like Ghost in the Shell
and Alita don't have live action versions.
So I guess, yeah, it's as fair game for an American
to make as an Asian or whatever.
And then you just judge on like, how it came out.
I'd say.
Yeah.
But like...
And the Death Note.
The, the, the...
Oh yeah, that's true.
I haven't, I haven't seen Death Note, but like,
I don't know, but just when I see,
when I see a manga or something that's played by,
I see a white person playing light Yagami,
I'm like, oh God, I want to fucking barf, you know?
Yeah.
I have a visceral reaction to it.
I just realized like, Death Note kind of pulled
like Dragon Ball Z live actions.
She's like, they just put it in high school.
Uh.
Oh yeah, Dragon Ball Z too.
Well, I mean, Gohan was in high school
for parts of Dragon Ball Z.
So I, you know, maybe they're going to lean into that.
Sure.
I don't know.
He was Dragon Ball Z set in high school?
When Go, after Cell was defeated and Gohan...
No, no, not the anime.
I mean, the, the...
The live action adaptation.
The remake.
Was there a Canadian, right?
It was a Canadian?
I don't, I don't remember.
I just remember he went to high school and, and stuff.
I mean, the fact of the matter is,
I don't think anyone would complain about any of these cases
if the movies were good.
Like, nobody would care if it was a white guy
if it was a great movie.
Light Yagami was literally a high school student.
And like, if you adapt it, you could,
as they chose to do in the, in the Netflix version,
you could lean into him being like a high school student.
But Light Yagami was never defined by that,
or like, his like weird crush they gave.
Okay, hang on.
Let me finish my point.
Light Yagami was like a borderline sociopathic,
obvious God complex narcissist,
who was so much better than the people around him
and was actually, so this was not a delusion
that like, he felt it was his God given right
to judge who should live and who should die.
This is not the kind of fucking character
as depicted in the original stories
who waste his time chasing pussy.
He doesn't give a shit.
He could get any pussy he wants
because he's so fucking competent
and he does consistently.
So to paint him that way, well, with Misa Misa,
she's like a, she's like an idol.
It is implied.
He doesn't even like her.
Well, okay, but
the point, he's above that.
He's above worrying about that.
And he could get any girl he wanted
because the girls were constantly
fawning over him when he was in college, especially.
Absolutely, sure.
And look at what's her face from after L dies
and there's the time skip.
There's that like newscaster
who also falls in love with him.
He gets like the cream of the crop is my point.
Like all the top sluts want Yagami's cock real bad
in addition to the lowly gutter sluts as well.
What's your point in all this?
My point is, what is wrong with the adaptation
is that they misunderstood and I mean,
I would argue maybe they understood,
but they made bad changes to the character
as opposed like you could make light Yagami American
that would come with baggage that you have to adapt it
to like the American political system
and the American policing system
that are different from Japanese
and are integral to the story.
What white light, white light.
That's a funny name for him.
White light, white light's first kill with the death note.
Trump, he just writes Donald Trump in the death note.
First thing.
I mean, yeah, yeah.
Oh, never mind.
I thought there was a live action Yu-Gi-Oh! movie
for a second, but it was just.
You know, they're making the second death note movie
for Netflix though, right?
Do you remember that?
No, no.
Geez.
At least, I've got to double check that
because I think that's true.
Apparently, I'm looking at the list of all of the
live action adaptations of manga and from the US,
there's not as many as I would have thought.
You've got Alita, the Giver,
which they made two of back in the early 90s.
I remember that.
Death Note, Dragon Ball Evolution,
Fist of the North Star, which I don't know.
Yeah, Death Note 2 is in the works at Netflix for some reason.
Ghost in the Shell, Old Boy, Speed Racer,
and then I see TBA on Akira,
which has been in the works for an eternity,
and Naruto.
Yes.
So a Naruto live action is, I guess, on my way.
Oh, I don't know what the status of this is.
Are they going to do the Naruto running?
God, I hope so.
I can't wait.
I mean, there's been discussion for a long time
about a live action one piece TV adaptation
for the West, and that's coming.
There is, in fact, a Bleach live action show
running in Japan right now, I think.
Cray.
I mean, that would work better for Bleach,
I think, than one piece.
Yeah, Bleach kind of makes sense.
It didn't even look terrible from what I saw.
One piece will be a nightmare,
and I'm very excited just to see how depraved
it goes.
Yeah, to CG an arm.
Wait, hold on, hold on.
Is this confirmed?
Is a live action American?
Is it American?
Let me double check.
Let me check.
Who's looking forward to Netflix Cowboy Bebop?
Yeah, that's...
No.
There's a commercial for it, apparently.
Um, okay, well, if, I mean, if one piece is dub,
if the way they handle the dub is any indication,
then one piece, the remake,
will be a fucking shit show nightmare.
I mean, you don't need to look to the dub to...
One piece is not...
One piece couldn't even survive the transition
into anime smoothly, much less a fucking live action.
At times it did, but check it out,
there's a trailer we'll put in the show notes.
I guess it's actually Japanese, so okay.
And it looks like they did a...
Wow, yeah, Nami looks fucking weird.
That looks fucking weird.
I think Nami should have been white.
Look at the giant reindeer that is chopper.
He's like a big fucking reindeer.
I think I've changed my mind of Nami should be white.
This is wrong.
She looks weird.
One piece characters have nationalities,
as confirmed by Oda.
Nami, I think, is Swedish.
What's Nami's?
Nami's Swedish.
Okay, Swedish.
Okay, I like that they are very show accurate.
They are super show accurate.
These look, oh my gosh.
That's always how it is
at the Japanese live action adaptations.
They're always like,
they go out of their way to make sure
it looks exactly like it.
They look like cosplayers.
They don't look like characters.
The thing is though, they look kind of weirdly...
Like, one piece is a cartoon, right?
And these look like big meaty scars on Luffy's scar
and big slices out of Zoro's face,
or he has his scars, and it's weird.
And Nami's tits are unsettlingly large.
It's kind of strange.
Sanji is like eyebrow.
It looks like a stick was glued to his face.
It looks like they drew it on with eyeliner.
Yeah, which I'm sure they did.
Okay, let me walk back.
I actually think it would have been really cool
if maybe Zoro and Luffy were Asian,
and then Sanji, Nami, and were white.
I think having a mixed race cast
would be really cool and really fitting
in a one piece adaptation.
It would be very fitting.
They're from all over the world, so yeah.
Yeah.
But what can you do?
Oh well.
Okay, anyway, enough about all this business.
So have you guys watched Thunderbolt Fantasy?
No.
Is that the puppet show?
Yes.
I have no.
But it looks really...
Oh my fucking face, right?
It's Gennaribuchi, right?
Yeah.
It looks cool, but I haven't seen it.
It's good.
I like it.
What do you like about it?
It's like, at first I didn't think I would like it.
After the first episode, I was like,
but then the writing is surprisingly good.
It's kind of cheesy, but good cheesy,
and I could really appreciate the cheesiness.
It would have to be cheesy to get over the hubo.
How long is it?
Because I actually want to give it a shot.
I think there's two seasons on a movie.
Yeah.
There was a...
Season one was like 12 episodes back in 2016,
and now they've made a second one more recently.
The movie made me so sad.
Yeah.
Was it tragic?
It was kind of, yeah.
Yeah, it was.
Not even kinder.
It was.
Damn, let's go.
Have you seen it, Digi?
I watched, like, I think six or seven episodes of season one.
I ended up dropping it, but just because it's...
It's just written very, like, keep...
Like, everything's mysterious.
Like, you don't...
I hate that kind of writing in general,
where it's just like constantly...
Suggesting that there's more going on,
but not giving you enough information.
I mean, of course, I know it will eventually divulge everything,
but I just got sick of it.
But, like, I...
The visuals are really cool.
Like, it's basically a Tokusatsu show with puppets as the main characters.
I was just gonna say that, yeah,
it reminds me of Kamen Rider and shit.
Yeah.
How fucking...
I don't know, I think that's just neat as hell.
Incidentally...
Nifty is what it is.
You know what...
You know where everyone needs to start turning their attention soon
is to fucking Chinese anime.
Because over the last, like, four years,
China has been doing all these, like, Japanese co-productions
through this company, Howliners.
And, like, at first, most of them were, like...
Not...
They're all fairly high quality,
but, like, most of them just felt, like, anime,
but made by China, and it was really weird and jarring.
But over time, some of...
There's just been some really fucking great shows coming out of there.
And, like, when we're in a period where anime is looking worse and worse,
the Chinese anime looks great.
And, um...
Yeah.
There's this show called Modao Zushi that I'm three episodes into.
And it just is, like...
It's really mind-blowing.
It's a lot like Avatar the Last Airbender,
where you have that weird feeling of, like,
I can tell this isn't Japanese,
but it looks like anime,
and it's way better than most of the anime I've seen.
So, uh, I love it.
I'm hearing you rave about it yesterday in the livestream.
I was very curious to check it out.
Speaking of anime-looking bed...
Oh, did you want to say something else, did you?
No, just that it's mega...
It's mega interesting because it is really gorgeous,
and especially the background art,
which is, like, my biggest problem with most anime coming out.
And, like, it looks as though
they probably drew the backgrounds,
like, really fucking huge,
and then just scaled them down,
because, like, the amount of detail is just fucking absurd
in a lot of the backgrounds.
And, like...
Shit, that sounds dope.
So, you just have, like, these absolutely gorgeous vistas
of, like, rural China and shit.
And it's a, you know, it's a Wushu story style.
That's why Thunderbolt Fantasy made me think of it,
because it's the same type of story,
where it's, like, you know, that crouching tiger,
hidden dragon, like, wirefoo style of, uh, shit.
But it's all, like, couched in Chinese mysticism and stuff.
And, like, it's just really fucking weird,
because the sensibilities of it I'm not used to,
because, like, all of the wordplay
or just, like, the attitudes of the characters
are just something I've never experienced before,
because I don't know enough Chinese media, you know?
I was gonna say, after having consumed
so much Japanese media, it's been...
Will I ever be able to get over
what's been built into me, my attitude,
that the Chinese are just there for me to pillage and rape?
Uh, I don't know.
Fucking mainlanders.
Fucking mainlanders don't even believe in ghosts.
Get the fuck out of here.
I mean, and the great thing about it is that, like,
as weird as it is, the dialogue is really sly and interesting.
Like, the character dynamics are great.
Also, it is, and I didn't even know this until, like,
episode three and doing additional research,
is considered by many to be a BL story.
And it definitely, like, you can see the trappings of it,
and you're like, oh, I've seen some people argue
that it's not BL, so I'm guessing it doesn't go
super far with, like, you know, with them actually, like,
fucking or anything.
Could you, like, just tell me quickly the first episode?
I might know what you're talking about.
Uh, the first episode is about, like,
a bunch of fucking zombies and shit.
Chinese zombies.
Are we still talking about Thunderbolt Fantasy?
No.
No, we're talking about Moldau Zushi.
Oh, okay.
Moldau Zushi.
Bill...
I was like, it's a little...
Boy's love.
Does the main guy die, but then, like, not die?
Well, the main character is, like, a, uh...
He had been dead, but he's, like, the creator of the dark arts.
Like, there's sorcery in this world,
and he created, like, a dark sorcery.
And the story begins with some kid who's been, like...
It's like a kid who's, like, with his, um,
like, living with his aunt or whatever,
and, like, the aunts a bitch, and her son's an asshole,
and they, like, are just constantly abusing
and beating the shit out of him.
So he's sacked, like, he does this, like,
blood ritual to summon the spirit
of the guy who created the dark arts,
like, into his body.
Just gives it to him.
Like, he's gone.
Okay.
This kid is dead.
He has sacrificed himself to give his body
to the creator of the dark arts
in exchange for him, like, murdering that whole family.
And, um...
It's not the one I saw.
Because there was a...
Another, like, I know there was a Chinese anime
that was sort of BL, but, like,
I couldn't get into it after the first episode.
So it was just so not well written
and then not likeable characters.
So I'm happy to hear it's not the one.
This BL is BS.
It reminds me of, like, the first...
The first...
I read the first book of, like, the, um,
the newer series by the Death Note guy.
Wait, I read this at your house, Digi.
Oh, Platinum End.
It's... Yeah, Platinum End is also about, like,
a kid who lives with, like, an aunt and uncle
who, like, abuse him, and he...
I don't think he murders...
He doesn't... He, like, gets the uncle
to murder the aunt or something.
Something like that happens.
And then the uncle goes to jail for life
or something like that.
Yeah.
Never mind.
Totally pointless diversion there.
I know he cares.
I read that as well and found it...
It was alright.
That's all I have to say.
Yes, I would have read Volume 2
if I'd had it available, but it didn't.
The guy's art, you know, is great.
Takashi, Obata, or whatever.
Still great.
It's still too good.
Alright.
Cool.
You know, whatever.
Sure.
Media, anime, animation.
Nice.
Good.
Whatever.
I'm making real things.
I'm making real animation in my own studio
on my own computer right now.
Well, tell me more.
And, alright.
Well, it's something that's...
Tell me more.
I'm telling you more.
Okay.
I've been animating the ending of Bailjiep,
which has been...
It has taken a while, but, like, I've been
making some strides with it.
It's ending?
And it's, yeah.
I've been working on the final animation.
I felt the conclusion coming.
I didn't realize it was so soon, but dope.
I'm excited.
Yeah.
I gotta catch up.
Now I'm gonna definitely read the whole thing, because...
Yeah.
I'm up to date.
These guys are slackers.
Help me.
I'm your real fan.
These guys are fake fans.
Yeah.
I don't believe in being up to date.
I mean, I'm, like, two years behind on One Piece.
Yeah.
Right.
So, like, I've got, like, doing the animation and all that.
Secretly.
Now, not secretly, because it's public.
Mm-hmm.
Or maybe I've mentioned it somewhere public already.
There's a possibility of...
Oh, no, I have mentioned it publicly.
Pump plushies.
Yeah, that's right.
That would be excellent.
I am very curious how you would do that.
Right.
Well, I've got...
There's this company that I used to get that Ryska plushie
that I made just for...
Because it was, you know, I just wanted it.
I just wanted it.
They do...
What do you call it?
Mass production now?
Yeah.
So, I have...
I've given them a design.
They've got back to me with the finished little thing.
And they're going to send me a sample,
which is going to get here in about a month or something.
And then once I say...
I have the sample.
Once I say a go, they're going to make a certain amount
and then send them to me.
And I'm thinking, if I can kickstart, you know,
the cost of shipping them out to people
and the cost of production for the things,
I can get a few hundred or maybe a hundred and fifty
of these plushies made and sent out.
So, in time for the ending of Bailjade to drop,
and it will be a whole big marketing ploy.
I am extremely interested in this,
and I'm going to be following the progress.
I want to see how these plushies look,
and I want to talk to you about your experience with this company
because I'm interested in doing something similar.
Well, here's what I'm curious about.
Does it have to be that huge of an amount?
Because I feel like you're not probably going to sell
over a hundred of them unless they're cheap.
I'm not.
But what I'm wondering is,
do you need to front the cost with the Kickstarter?
I don't know.
How much is it going to cost you relative
to how much you're going to sell it for?
Is it just so you can keep the cost low?
All I want is for them to exist.
I don't really need to make a big profit off of them.
And also, it's an American company,
so sending them to me is already going to be expensive.
Right, sure.
So I don't think people would be willing to pay.
The prices, the amounts I could do,
are 50, 100, and 150.
And the higher up the number goes,
obviously, the lower the cost is overall.
150 is like two grand cheaper than just 50.
Wait, it's cheaper to make more?
Yeah, because they don't...
You know how mass production works.
You mean cheaper.
Oh, you mean it's cheaper than...
Like per unit or something.
You're saving that much more.
It would have been if you had paid the same per unit.
Yeah, okay.
So like if, on the Kickstarter,
I would just have one tier and a certain amount of things,
and once they're all filled, that's it.
And I don't want the plushies to be too expensive.
I asked on my Twitter how expensive people were thinking
they would pay for.
And a lot of people said no.
So I'm hoping that with the ending of the comic,
and once I have the sample,
I can make a video showing you what it looks like,
people will be more willing.
And who knows?
I'll throw out a number here that's just what I would like.
Considering if I could get a punk plushie,
I would consider going up to 50 bucks, I think.
Beyond that, I think it starts to get rather ludicrous for me.
I don't know if I would pay 50 for it.
I mean, it depends on the size.
I'm imagining something that's maybe like
eight to 12 inches end to end.
I don't have the data with me,
but I did figure out certain sizes and costs.
I think it's going to be about this big.
I'm making a motion with my hands.
Great.
So get excited for that.
I asked them to make her limbs, arms, and legs floppy
so she can flop around.
I am.
Can you tell me that?
I mean, do you mind saying the name of the service?
Because I'm.
He can tell you later, I guess.
Well, I could if you don't.
Yeah, I want to know.
Oh, I don't mind.
Uh, it's, uh, oh, what is it?
Uh, fucking.
Budsies as in like buddies, but with a Z with a Z.
But with an S buds.
I'll just type it.
Okay.
Sounds like a fucking weed website.
What it is, what it actually is,
is like a website where they say,
send in your child's drawings and we'll make their plushies real
and send them back to you and it's all, you know, very young.
But, you know, I'm, you know, a grown man, but, you know,
I'm a man child and therefore I am the target demographic.
What if you had to pretend it was a child's drawing?
You've had to like be like, oh yeah, my son made this.
No, I didn't say anything, but I hope that they think
that it's someone's son because I didn't draw it very well.
I drew it very exactly, but like it's still like punk,
which is a stick figure.
Yeah.
I drew it from the front and the side and they know what,
what it looks like.
It's adorable.
The, I could, yeah, this, this seems like a service that more
than just fucking people with shitty kids that can't draw
would want to make you so.
Also, the reason I trusted it in the first place to make the
brisker plush is because, um, I think some of them are furries
and they do like furry special things.
Nice.
Like if you have a furry OC.
Never doubt the furries.
If they, if they, they, if you have like a furry OC, you pay
like more to get like a very, um, you know, bespoke plush made
of your, your furry.
You know, they, they, they lead with the kids stuff to
hide the fact that 90% of their revenue is from furry OCs being created.
Yep.
So like they, they, they do quality work.
I always see one.
Yeah.
For advanced specialty advanced commissions, for advanced drawings
and OCs, specialty plush and faux furs, sneak peek and two
rounds of changes.
And I'm seeing this in the sample image.
It sort of looks like the butter dragon from, uh, Undertale.
Yep.
But it's like green and it's covered in like stripes and it's got
like a blue afro and shit.
And these, these plushies, you know, they're quality because
they need to be able to take extreme amounts of damage.
Wear and tear from day to day use.
If you know what I mean.
Yeah.
Tell you.
I am.
Yeah.
Some of these sample images don't look like they were drawn by kids.
I am, I am tempted to make myself a mage plushie just because I want one.
You should.
Well, buying a single one is quite expensive.
The risker was like 200 pounds or something.
Yeah.
All cold.
Yeah, never mind.
But it is the only, it is the only risker plush that exists.
And it's the coolest thing that I own probably.
How could that be considering the popularity of Homestack?
That's just shocking.
I mean, maybe people have made like homemade ones.
Yeah, this is the highest quality one.
Yeah.
It's the coolest.
But yeah, obviously mass production costs go dramatically lower.
Let's do it.
Let's say, wait a minute.
Best of luck.
Wait just a fucking second.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm seeing there's a sample, a sample image for something called selfies,
which is a, a being of yourself.
Oh yeah, that was so strange.
It looks very strange, but the sample image.
That's what I want.
I can't tell, but it almost looks like it's two people cosplaying.
The same, it's two people cosplaying at an anime convention.
The guy's got a katana and the girl's in like a corset.
I want a fucking high res image.
I want to know what they're doing, but I can't, it's too small.
I can't make it out.
He's definitely got a katana though.
His plus, he's got a floppy katana.
It's like, it's like he's holding the handle at a 90 degree angle,
but it's flopping down and pointing straight at the floor.
He had a floppy katana.
Fucking good.
Looks like shit.
But, you know.
Well, good work guys.
Yeah.
The other one's pretty good though.
Well, hey, with that, maybe we should do the voicemails.
No.
No?
APS, APSadventures.site is where you can read my comic.
We can't, we can't go to the voicemails because I have a bit to do.
It's time.
Oh.
It's time everyone.
For the new, the new thing.
The new thing that we do on the, on the PCP.
Fucking.
It's time.
There it is.
Everything's so far away.
Everyone's favorite shell.
Thank you whoever made that.
Anyone remember whose voicemail that was?
I don't.
All right.
Okay.
Let me, let me, this week's round of grievances with the pizza party podcast.
Yeah.
I'm very pissed.
Oh, is that what this is?
I still, I still haven't heard the podcast.
Where's the, where's the podcast?
I'm, I'm looking around.
I'm looking all around 360.
I don't see it.
Where's the podcast?
Can't find it.
That's bad conveyance.
That's a zero out of ten experience right there.
I know where the PCP is.
It's right here.
It's where this voice that you're hearing right now, wherever it's emanating from.
PCP right here, right now.
In your face, visceral.
PPP, nowhere.
Nothing.
A mere shade.
In the toilet.
A phantom.
Not even real.
Second, what kind of pizza?
Are we talking about a high quality wood-fired brick oven artisan pizza?
It's almost certainly not.
We're talking about some Papa John Little Caesars bullshit.
I have no confidence in this brand.
I have no idea what the nutritional value is.
I have no idea what my value for money is going to be.
I go into this, I go into this investment, this investment of time and money
with no idea of what I'm going to receive and frankly I'm not comfortable with it
in the, down the drain, in the toilet, pizza party podcast, get it together,
or else you'll be featured on another segment next week.
Oh, it's time to shit on the pizza party podcast.
You're here.
Bad campaign.
Hooray.
Ben, I have to question your ability to analytically read between the lines.
I mean, why would there ever be a brick oven-fired pizza at a pizza party?
You always go for the cheapest, most, you know, definitely go for Little Caesars
if you're throwing a party because you're trying to feed as many people as possible.
Maybe it's, maybe it's party is more of an intimate gathering.
Maybe it's a political party.
Maybe it's like, oh shit.
It's like an old Italian gentleman gathering outside their bistro and someone brings out
a piping hot pizza pie from the ovens and it's just a lovely, decadent, old world experience.
Maybe that's the kind of party it is.
All right, I've had it with pizza pie.
I've had it with pizza pie.
Why is it called a pie?
A pie is tall.
A pie is have a crust over it.
Yeah, a pie, if anything, it's more of a tart because it has an open top.
That's what I said to your mother last night.
It's just more of a tart.
Nate says to his brother, Ben St.
So viewers, so viewers, if you, if you, if you've managed the Titanic task to find and
identify the pizza, where the pizza party podcast is or what it is, let them know to
get their act together or else Ben St. on the procrastinator podcast is gonna rip them a new one.
Hit them with some hard hashtag, where's the podcast?
Forever.
Yeah.
Hashtag.
Where's the podcast?
This is gonna overshadow this.
This where's a podcast?
Hashtag is gonna overshadow my where to beef.
Hashtag that I established yesterday.
What's that relevant to?
Where's the beef?
Because because there's this this Netflix film.
There's another like Chinese anime, except that it's entirely Japanese, except that it's Chinese.
But it's it's basically a Makoto Shinkai movie, except in China.
And the whole first part of this film, it's like 15 minutes of this guy talking about this dish
that he refers to almost exclusively as beefu.
He's always saying like, oh, that's the San Zhan beefu.
And he keeps talking about like, oh, we would eat that beefu.
And it was such good beefu.
However, however, zero times does the word beef appear in the subtitles.
So you're calling up the suburbs more than anybody else.
It's the soy boy conspiracy.
It was Netflix's subs.
So they removed the beefu.
Yeah, there's no beefu.
They censored it.
And he says beefu like literally 60 times.
Now vegetarian activists.
What did they say in the subtitles though?
They were just I mean, because first of all, the dish they would call San Zhan noodles,
which is like, I think that is another like name for the dish.
But the thing is that when he's just talking about like eating it,
he might say like, I would eat a big spoonful.
But like, and that's how they would translate it.
But like the way he actually says it in Japanese is like,
I would eat a spoonful of that beef.
You know, like he just kept insistently saying the word.
Now someone told me it's possible because there is a Japanese word for noodles
that is of some type that is beefu.
But but but it didn't seem to be the case.
I heard beefu over and over again, like literally 60 times in 15 minutes,
not once in the subtitles.
So so May and I made a whole we made a whole stink
about the where to beefu conspiracy, the soy boy conspiracy.
Excellent. Speaking of beefu, I went to, you know, during the meetup.
You got a bit of a beefu with the PC, the pizza party podcast.
Exactly. I certainly do.
I think we found the beefu.
But I went to remember for the meetup.
We all went to the the dumpling cafe in Chinatown.
After after Community Day, after Mama Swine or Swine Up Community Day,
I mean, me and Kazi went to beef that that place.
And I I have gotten some shit orders there.
They will let you order everything.
They will let you order like any fucking weird, like like garbage meat
and like bizarre roughage that you don't know what it is thrown on a plate.
Like when we were all there, I got some like clams on some like chopped,
like I don't even know what the vegetable was.
It was trash. I hated it.
This time I stuck to something that I got beef and black pepper.
I got beef with black pepper and it was so good.
It was delightful. It was a true delight.
It was spicy.
Does anyone know when I was there did I think what I got and it was gross and terrible.
I might be confusing with another Chinese place or whatever.
But like I got it was like general so is like totally basic.
When I bit into it, like the inside was like not cooked all the way.
And it was pink and disgusting.
And I hated it.
I have I have gotten some I have gotten some real bad shit.
Like one time I got like are we talking about that place that we all that we went?
Yeah, with you know, I don't understand why you keep going there.
If you've had bad experiences and it's literally surrounded on all sides by other Asian restaurants
that you can go to instead. I have had bad experiences.
I have had bad experiences, but I have also had very good experiences that have been very cheap
for the money. All right.
And that place was not cheap at all. That place.
Yeah, it was. Well, I you can get like you can get like a good like like lunch there for like
12. Have you been to enough Chinese places?
Like it's not it's not cheap for what it is.
No, but it's the devil.
That's the problem. I see people do this where you you select a restaurant and then you go there.
And if it's not shit, then you just keep going back, even though there's a chance
even if it's right across the street is better in every way.
And you just don't know because you don't even try one dish.
That's true beyond out of this world.
It was literally the first time I went there.
I paid 12 bucks and I got like the like pork belly and cabbage and it was really good for the price.
And I was like this place rules and I've never been able to let go of that association,
even though I've had I've gotten some real trash.
My methodology is when I move into a new place, I just try every single restaurant that is there.
And then from there, now I know what are the top ones.
And then I, you know, return to those continually from then on.
Yes, it's sort of like me because we have we have a lot.
We used to have a lot of takeaways and I would like to try out new restaurants and stuff.
But we tried out a lot of restaurants until we settled on one that we really like.
And we have a few backups in case that one's not available.
That's the key.
And I mean, the one that just it's funny to me because the one that Ben is talking about
is in Chinatown and it's just like it just seems like any random Chinese restaurant
in literally a sea of a lot of what you look way better like Asian restaurants that are just
all around like every door on the road for like a mile is just Asian restaurants.
It's like that feeling when you're with your boys and you I don't know, you're like out doing
something and like you're on your way to the restaurant that you're going to as you walk
by millions and millions of restaurants.
But we got to get to that one.
And you're just like, but what is why?
Because I'm looking over there and that looks like a really hoppin delicious Thai restaurant.
And this looks like a hole in the wall Chinese thing.
So why are we going to this one?
I don't know.
Guys like me, when you've got a plan, I don't want to deviate from the plan.
And I'll die before I do anything.
That's not the plan gives me that feeling of comfort that I you're not wrong.
Dude, there probably are.
There probably I mean, there's yeah, there probably are better places.
But there's like you say, there's so many and I'm not I can't check them all.
Why not?
Check them all.
I mean, I mean, I'm not in town enough to do that.
I guess if I'm in town, I will always go to a different place.
Like you just as a matter of course.
Now now maybe I want next time I'm in town.
Maybe I want to be like, let me just see what else is around.
I mean, to me, that's the point of living in a city is that there is so much variety
that you don't have to go to the same shit that you've already been to all the time.
You know, you go somewhere different every time because there's so much excitement,
so much to explore and discover.
So why would you ever go to the same place if there's another place you haven't been to yet?
Once you've been everywhere, that's when you go, OK, well, I know the wheat from the chaff and
I'm just going to go to the good place.
I've thrashed my milk and separated the chaff out.
Remember that?
That was a classic moment on the last episode of the PCP.
I wasn't there.
Of course, of course.
OK, all right, never mind.
How about we get to those voicemails?
I think it's time.
I think it's time that we go do that.
All right.
OK, let's see.
Everybody speak pipe.
You know the deal.
Give us your stuff.
Click the link below.
Send it to the speak pipe link.
You know what I'm talking about.
All right, let's get into it.
First mail here.
Let me get to the right place here.
There we go.
OK, this is from Rune Factory is Good.
Yes.
OK, go.
What's up, PCP?
I'm calling in because I can't take any more of Nate's wrong opinions.
Now this started with his wrong opinions about the economy.
It continued with his wrong opinions about food.
But now I'm literally boiling with rage over his recent
horrible affront to me.
That Rune Factory 4 is a bad game that people shouldn't buy.
He said this in the Nintendo Direct live stream.
Yeah, that's where he's messing up.
And frankly, I am fucking pissed.
What problem did you possibly have with the game
that takes farming the hard works of a person to improve themselves
and gain social capital points and literal capital in the world
by selling the fucking robbery.
He's going to say like, oh my god, farming.
Nate, it's like, sweat of your brown shit.
Yeah, OK, I got it.
This is literally self-saving.
The combat is dog shit.
And Rune Factory 4, I hated it.
I labored through that game for a year.
It was fine.
I got my waifu.
I played a bunch of Rune Factory 4 and I made it.
The point of the game is that it is.
I would almost compare it to like a clicker game
because it's mostly just about making numbers go up in.
Are you guys talking about Stardew Valley?
No, no, no.
It's very similar.
A game about farming with dog shit combat.
It's just about making numbers.
We may as well be talking about Stardew Valley.
They're both harvest Rune Clones.
But the whole point of Rune Factory is that it's harvest Rune.
Right, it's harvest Rune, but in a fantasy world
and with swords and dungeons and stuff.
Is harvest Rune in the real world?
That's Stardew Valley.
That's Stardew Valley is that exact description.
But Rune Factory is a lot more combat driven.
It's more anime-esque.
And way more anime-esque.
But is it 3D?
But yeah, it is like pretty much.
There's just like an endless amount of things you can do
and only so much time in the day.
So it's all about like managing what do I want to do
with my time and constantly being on the grind.
And like it's one of those things where the satisfaction
is just in that literally no matter what you do
as long as you're doing something
you are making some kind of progress.
So it's just that feeling of just constantly doing
little things that are like, oh I'm getting better
and my numbers are going up.
Everything is better than it was a second ago.
But like the actual what you do never gets more complicated
as a player.
With games like this.
This isn't 3D.
Well it's top down.
The models are 3D.
This is what I meant.
But when I ask 3D I really just want to know if I can move up.
Can you turn the camera?
No, yeah, no you can't.
You can't.
Because that's what makes me enjoy things.
With a game like Rune Factory or like I'm comparing it
to the other games.
It's what matters in this.
Because there's so many competitors.
It's like are the small gameplay tweaks tuned
in the best way compared to the competition.
And I definitely think that Stardew Valley
is just like way more fun.
There's more like customizability.
When was Rune Factory 4 actually released the first time?
God I don't know maybe like 2010 or something.
Yeah it's pretty old.
And I'll admit that the combat, a lot of it is clunky.
But I really personally really like it.
And I'm happy that it's coming to Switch.
I don't have a switch yet.
I want to talk about Stardew Valley.
I want to talk, guys, I'm fucking torn.
I'm fucking torn between Emily, Leah, and Abigail.
I just, how am I supposed to choose?
Abigail, she's purple.
I like the purple barmaid hair I think.
No, she's blue hair.
She's blue hair.
Yeah that was my first choice.
But then I started to warm up to Leah
and then later Abigail now.
Like at first I was like cut and dry Emily.
But then, but it's just gotten more complicated.
Abigail, she's purple and she eats rocks.
The romance triangle is just spiraling out of control.
There's so many feelings.
Oh, yeah, Abigail eats anything.
Anything you get, it doesn't matter if you give her an answer.
Well what a slut, am I right?
How'd you know?
I was hungry.
This looks delicious.
I recommend instead of Rune Factory playing Reciteer.
I like, I love Reciteer.
It's good.
I played Reciteer.
I got to the end game.
It's not the same though.
The end game, the end game seemed like a nightmare grind slog
and I didn't want anything to do with it.
So I just played through the main campaign
and was happy with it.
I think Stardew Valley is just the peak of this kind of game.
Though, I mean Reciteer is basically a different one.
Personally, I think it's not quite the same
but it's pretty simple.
I really dislike the aesthetic of Stardew Valley
and also I think it's mega fucking boring.
I don't care for it much.
I don't, I don't understand that at all.
I think it looks great.
Yo, but the main, the quest loop.
What the fuck?
I just found out so much.
And the girls aren't anime enough.
The girls are way too western.
They used to be more anime.
I wish we could go back.
There's old art of previous versions of the game.
They were way more anime at certain points.
I don't, wait, what don't you like about the aesthetic?
This is totally bad.
I really don't, first of all,
I don't like how everything is weirdly tall.
And secondly, I don't like the color design that much.
For me, it's all about the character art.
I don't, I think the people look ugly.
You can download mods to change their portraits.
What, on my Switch version?
Can I do that?
Which is where I have the game.
I mean.
That's what I thought.
Well, that's your mistake.
I don't think that, I don't,
I wouldn't praise the game and say,
wow, it has such great character art or anything.
I mean, I don't really care.
I don't get it.
When I'm trying to get that nut,
Stardew Valley is not the game that I need.
I mean, I don't care about the,
I don't care about the portrait art.
I don't care about that nut.
It's better.
Shut up.
I don't care about the portrait art.
I care about, like, look at, like,
everything is such like nice, lush, like, sprite work.
It's, it's gorgeous.
The town is, the town is very attractive, I think.
Mostly.
So yeah, I like all that stuff.
And, and, and the best thing about Stardew Valley,
the most satisfying thing about the game
is the long-term quest of fixing up the community center
by achieving all those little individual goals
is super satisfying.
The game fucking blue-balled me
for like almost an entire year now.
I have been short on fixing the communities
to all I need.
Yeah.
An apple and a pomegranate.
Waiting for the, the season-specific products
can't completely hamstring me.
And it's just because I didn't buy it
from the mystery merchant.
Yeah, I think so.
That's true.
I have been going to the traveling cart
every, like, every Friday and Sunday
and looking, hoping for,
I remember one time I did see a pomegranate there
but it was before I realized that, like,
I needed that for the community center.
So I fucked up.
So I have been waiting, yeah, like,
I planted, I planted a pomegranate tree
and an apple tree but it was like right after,
it was just too late that I could,
it wasn't after the season,
I planted it just into the season.
So it did, the tree didn't mature
until the season was already over.
So I've just been waiting for the year to go by.
To get one apple and one pomegranate.
So, like, it's directly to the actual human year.
No, but it is, it is, like, slower.
Like, a season will last, like, 30 days.
Each season is 28 days, yeah.
So each season is more like a month, basically.
And you could just make your guy, like,
go to sleep, wake up, go to sleep,
wake up, go to sleep.
But you have to do that, like, 90 times
to get back to the season.
And you'll, like, ruin your-
I'm waking up and realizing we're still
reacting to the first voicemail.
That's true.
We should move it along.
Let's move it along here.
Okay, next one is from-
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Post in the comments.
Should I go with Emily, Leah, or Abigail?
These are your choices.
Actually, go for Sebastian.
He's your boy.
I like Sebastian.
Are you allowed to be gay?
Yeah.
If I were going for a guy,
I would absolutely go for Sebastian.
I knew you would.
He's the edgy one.
Okay, next one.
Voice mail from Mackie's back.
Go.
Hey, so, PCP, recently, a good friend of mine
admitted they had a crush on me,
making me the first PCP fan with a girlfriend.
Wow.
But here's the issue.
She lives in Florida.
I live in Massachusetts.
And neither of us have that much money.
So, I know some of you have had weird internet
relationships like this.
Do you have any advice?
Help?
Don't do it.
Give up.
It's difficult.
I mean, I would say you can cheaply
take a train down there, right?
Like, that's how Ben was visited, too.
From Massachusetts, I mean, relatively cheaply.
I used to, yeah, well, okay.
When I used to go from Virginia to Georgia,
it would take me like,
it would only cost me maybe like 20 or 30 bucks
for the whole trip.
But it would take me like 16 hours.
I mean, it's just a matter of how determined are you.
Like, do you really like this girl or not?
Like, yeah.
Because I mean.
Let's be real.
This is like the first guy,
the first girl who came to him said like,
I like you.
And so, of course, our boy is going to jump on it.
But, you know, like, if you came up to him today,
you lived in his town and said like,
hey, I want to date you.
Is he not going to drop this long distance girl
like a sack of potatoes?
No, of course.
But here's the question.
First of all, do you have any prospects
IRL and if have you lost your virginity?
If you have not lost your virginity
and she is like DTF, take a fucking train,
do it as cheaply as possible.
Do not take a flight, take a train,
take something cheap, keep it under 100 bucks,
get down there, meet her, have sex and see how things go.
And if it seems like you would like to eventually pursue this
as a serious thing, then you need to be working on
how can we get into the same place as soon as possible.
If there is no recourse there, if the answer is
we can't do that, shut this thing down.
Because like, you don't want to be in an internet relationship
for fucking who knows how long with no actual plan.
And you should, if you got, if you got,
okay, she's your girlfriend now.
If I assume you guys want to fuck.
So you and her should make that happen.
You should like, you know, get money and buy a train and buses.
And you can do it for not that much.
You can, if you look around,
you can probably find ways to do it.
I'll bet you could get from Massachusetts to Florida
for under, definitely under 100 bucks.
Maybe under 50 if you were really resourceful.
It will probably take you like a day or more.
But whatever, yeah.
If you want to, I don't know, I mean, I don't think,
I don't think it matters if you've lost your virginity or not.
If you want to fuck and you want to spend a day
or ends a little bit of money to make that happen, then do that.
Maybe get her to contribute because she's, you know,
part of this endeavor as well.
I just think that the most important thing more so than even going down there
is that like, if you do this, you have to know that like,
there's two ways that it can happen.
Either you'll go down and you'll, you'll,
you'll realize that you don't want this to be a long-term relationship
or you guys will super like each other and super click.
And then immediately the question is going to have to be,
how can we make this no longer long-distance?
Because long-distance relationships are suffering.
You will not be able to easily have sex again.
You won't be able to easily spend time together.
You won't be able to have that, you know, that,
that emotional support.
That is what you're really coming to a relationship for more so.
The end goal, the end goal of a long-distance relationship
needs to be to not be a long-distance relationship.
Otherwise it is a, it is a waste and you will be sorry.
It is a waste. It definitely is a waste.
And yeah, just don't, and don't put yourself in the position.
Well, hey, don't put yourself in the position where
you've got this long-distance girlfriend and you're like,
well, I've got no other prospects because it will make you weak
and it will make you just waste your time being like,
well, I've got a girlfriend so I'm all good, but no.
Yeah. No.
The other side of the coin though is that if you meet up, say,
and you get to know, you know, this relationship progresses
and you find yourself feeling like I'm not that interested
in progressing this and making this a not long-distance relationship,
then you know, quit. Don't do it.
Yeah. Give up.
And that's fine.
It's way easier to make those kind of decisions
when you've met the person in person.
Just it's a lot easier to sort out.
I think there's a problem or something.
You never really know the person until you have to live with them.
Yeah.
That's also true, but I think you can get a,
you'll know a lot more than you do just by talking online if you meet them.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And I don't know.
I don't know how much talk.
I don't know if you guys are like,
Skyping all the time and stuff like, you know,
does that just suck though?
I hate doing that.
It really sucks.
And like, I, so I don't know what I don't know,
like what level it's on where like, I don't know,
you know, how much you guys know about each other or how close you are.
But like, you definitely have to meet somebody in person
to get a better sense of what they're like than what you're going to get.
I mean, you know, you're only talking to each other
in like a manufactured scenario of like having to sit in front of a camera
and talk to a person directly,
as opposed to just like being around each other
and knowing what their mannerisms are like
and how they generally like the cadence of their living, you know,
which is much more important.
So feel it out dog.
So best of luck.
Don't don't settle for a shitty relationship
as opposed to no relationship.
Because sometimes none is better
because then you can just find one that is better.
So there you go.
It probably sounds like this probably just be a big waste of time.
Sorry, sorry to burst your bubble.
You know what, maybe this guy is like 15,
this is like the first person who's ever,
and like, great, fantastic.
Have a good time, you know, feel it out.
Sure.
Do what you gotta do.
But don't trap yourself somewhere.
And then they're going to be like,
Oh, but don't you love me?
If you love me, you date me no matter where I was from.
I don't love you, bitch.
I don't love you.
Just say that to her.
And then execute her.
Curve Stop.
Okay, next voicemail on that note.
Hell yeah.
Hell yeah, meaghtow for life.
This is fromrupt and it's coded as super important.
So let's see what that's about.
Do the flu, where the fuck are you?
The flu, do are you?
Please, the flu, where the fuck are you?
You are the fucking guy.
I don't fucking care about no one but Davoo.
What the fuck?
Uh, there's the voice of the people.
They clamor for Davoo.
Davoo messaged me on Discord a while ago.
And I was like, hey, wow, a message from Davoo.
Cool.
I should really read that and get back to him.
And then I forgot to do that.
So sorry, sorry, Davoo.
He sent us a secret friend's only video.
I won't even spill the beans.
Did you guys get sent this as well?
Wait, this was it.
And I forgot to actually watch it.
I responded with an exact quote,
hey, hey, hey, dope.
And I stand by it.
I stand by that message.
I won't even say what it is, but it is hilarious.
I'm a bad person.
Agreed.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Davoo has just been, you know, offline for a while.
Yep.
But like, I don't know, he'll come back when he wants to.
I hope he's working on another game.
Yeah, me too.
Or I don't know, like preparing his.
Autominus was like a surprise hit.
Release Autonomous on Switch, Davoo.
Do it now.
Do it immediately.
I'd fucking buy Autonomous for Switch just to support him.
Autominus is fucking sick.
I mean, I'd play five bucks any day.
He's not going to get it on Switch.
What are you talking about?
Whatever.
Get it on Steam then.
They'll take anything.
They'll take whatever garbage they can.
He could, he could get it on Steam.
I thought it was funny as hell.
Well, I don't know what the process is like,
but it's good enough to be on Steam.
Absolutely.
By a huge margin.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, anyway, they'll take any old fucking shit visual novel.
That's true.
All right.
Next one.
This is from A2Z.
Go.
Okay, Nate.
I know you're listening to this.
Yeah.
You don't have to put this on the show,
but please read the official one piece release on shonenjump.com
or vis slash shonenjump, whatever.
It's good quality, better quality than the scanlations.
That's enough.
Yeah, I know.
I got the gist.
Okay.
Cut that off, edit man.
He's just, this guy wrote in, and I appreciate that,
to just let me know that they release one piece chapters,
like weekly, relatively, on the actual Viz Media site.
After hearing this, I went and read it,
and it does look quite good.
The problem is, however, they take,
like the new chapter has been out for several days,
and they have not released it on the website yet.
So you'd be fucking hamstrung if you were depending on this
for doing like the pod decast or anything.
So, you know, I'd probably go and read it like later,
but not going to fucking do it up front.
But this is an advertisement for people
who want to read the highest quality releases of one piece.
We don't need to advertise that shit.
Give us the next one.
No?
Do you think everybody knows?
I just wanted to give everybody like notice,
because I wasn't even paying attention to this.
No, I just meant I don't want to give free advertising to Viz.
It's worth mentioning, I guess.
Do you not like Viz, or they're like a bad company or something?
No, I just don't, I don't know.
It's just, it's just, I was just joking.
All right.
Did she just want to give it away for free?
You gotta pay us.
They certainly, they say it should pay us.
You're right.
That's what I'm saying.
Okay, that's fair.
I hear you.
Viz, call me up.
I demand Viz, if you want us to sponsor your product,
you call in and leave an epic voicemail
that we could respond to on the episode.
Fill it with memes and whatnot.
Okay, moving on, whatever.
Next one from Harlock Asnable.
Fan favorite, go.
So you know how last time I was on here,
I was saying some stuff about Jesus and all that?
Yeah, it was all bullshit.
I lied.
I'm sorry, I had to.
But anyway, I can't really handle like real reality.
So I've been shopping around for like a new religion,
looked into Scientology, but it seems too expensive.
And they also had a similar anti-gay agenda,
just like a lot of the other ones.
So what are some like niche religions,
some like sweet like hidden gem religions?
What are your best recommendations?
What's your like artsy fartsy three by three of religions?
I need to know.
The Church of Spirit Science.
Spirit Science is like buddies with Satan, I think.
Seriously, Satan's like, you think it's the devil worship?
No, it's like the worship of yourself.
Yeah, but they put a really edgy label on it though.
Yeah, exactly.
You pissed off the Church people.
I think that's unironically, literally,
what the mindset behind Call of Duty was.
It totally was.
It was.
Listen, Satanism doesn't let you pilot the fucking love
battleship through the cosmos.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
Satan never fucking aligned my Kundalini.
Whoa.
Whoa, the Catholic priests were aligning my Kundalini,
my whole childhood, if you know what I'm saying.
Hell yeah, dude.
Hell yeah.
Wait, what?
Don't worry.
All right, next call.
This is from Schmeeblebop Dingle Dangle.
Go.
Hey, the BCP.
Hello.
That's my name.
I have one serious question I seriously need to ask you guys.
Okay.
Why the fuck is my PB hard?
Because you're listening to the pro-crastinators podcast,
giving you a boner every single time.
Yeah, there it is.
Okay, that's all.
Thanks for that.
Don't make promises you can't deliver though.
You left a really hard at that.
Oh, we've delivered.
All right, next one.
We have a boner guarantee.
If you're not satisfied with your boner,
and for at least four hours after five times.
We will come to your house and guarantee satisfaction personally.
Voice mail number seven.
We will RP with you on Discord, slide into our DMs,
and make a complaint.
You will achieve release, my dude.
You will.
I'm gonna throw up.
All right, number seven.
This is Cloud Strife calling in with another message.
What do you have for us?
Hello, it is me again, Cloud Strife.
No piano this time.
But Final Fantasy IX is out on the Nintendo Switch right now.
And I was wondering,
is it a good game?
I have seven, and it's the best one.
I've never finished nine.
It's the best thing ever,
but nine seems to have no Cloud Strife in it.
So when did that automatically make it like a piece of trash game?
As a matter of fact, in Lindblum,
in the town in Final Fantasy IX,
there is a weapon shop that on the wall has the Buster Sword
that Zidane goes up and he talks to it.
And it's just something like,
it's something like, oh, I bet some stormy guys
would sure enjoy using weapons like this.
It's something like that.
Roll my fucking eyes as hard as fucking possible.
That's not exactly how it sounds.
It's more clear or something,
but it's something like, wow,
who would be able to use a weapon this big or something like that?
But it is the Buster Sword.
Stormy guy.
I gotta look up the quote.
Okay, okay.
Anyway, so anyway, Final Fantasy IX is a masterpiece.
I got it for my switch,
and man, I just wanted to give my quick review of the hour I played.
Yep, that's bass as hell.
The fucking, they definitely use that mobile port version
or whatever, or the whatever steam version,
that like, oh my God, the models of your characters
and all the characters, they look good.
The background art is muddled and god-awful and it is such.
Oh, they didn't fix that?
No, they can't.
They've lost the original assets.
This is all they've got.
I will say that it's not so bad if you play it in windowed mode.
Great.
Yeah, like if you could just thrash the resolution, then yeah.
This is not the Buster Sword.
No?
Does it look similar?
But like, I can't find the show notes.
Not particularly.
Okay.
Link that, link that.
Let me look at it.
It's deaf.
People think, okay, maybe I was exaggerating a little bit.
Whatever, it's close enough.
Apparently he says something that is sort of a reference
to the size of Cloud's sword, but these are not Buster Sword.
Okay, you know what?
I was wrong, but there definitely was a reference there.
Okay, but whatever, doesn't matter.
Next voice mail.
Point is, it's a great game.
So go play it.
How many of these do you have?
Anyway, next voice mail.
This is from, I'm Being Dead Serious.
Begin.
Kingdom Hearts 3, Fur Fags, Pokemon Go, Babies, Pokemon Let's Go,
Actual Babies.
Now you guys need to get your fucking big boy pants on.
Go to the Google Play Store and download what Garfield Go.
I'm fucking serious.
Oh, you just got a French, Mr. Mine.
Guess what?
I was walking my dog yesterday and I found a fucking spicy Italian lasagna
under a fucking tree.
Oh, you just leveled up your Scyther into a scissor after grinding for months?
I just gave my cat a fucking doughnut and he leveled up.
Jesus Christ, get on my level.
Every day you're not playing Garfield Go is like a fucking Monday.
Fuck, man.
It's real though.
Garfield Go is a real game you can get.
No, it's not.
It is.
I looked it up ahead of time.
Shut the fuck up.
It's real.
We should all get it.
Shut your fucking mouth.
Go back to the fucking pizza party project with that fucking liar.
No, we should.
Next rad con.
We have to go play Garfield Go.
I just want to say I checked my shelf.
I do have Final Fantasy IX on the PlayStation 1, so I can see it.
Oh, you'll see it looking good.
But the thing is though, the problem is that they're using, I think,
the same visuals from the background of Final Fantasy IX,
but because resolution has improved so much,
they're able to render the models at a much higher resolution,
but the background art is pre-rendered art and stuff.
Oh yeah, yeah, I've seen that.
It's not even that the new version looks worse than the old game.
It's just weird and charring.
I just think it's bad.
They just don't look like they belong in the world.
I can bear it.
I can look past it.
But it is.
I got over it surprisingly quick.
I had been avoiding buying that remake for years because of that,
because the screenshots looked so fucking terrible,
but when I was actually playing it, I was not that bothered by it.
In the moment, from screen to screen, I can get over it,
but whenever I stop and concentrate, I'm like, oof, yikes.
I looked it up, and the line that Zidane says when he sees the sword is,
I knew it.
We used to call him Zidane, but it's actually Zidane.
It looks like whatever.
He says, I knew a spiky-haired guy that used a sword like this.
That's the one.
I appreciate that.
Stormy guy.
Whatever, close enough.
Okay, so Garfield Go, right?
For 602 reviews on the Google Play Store.
All five-star, I'm sure.
Its overall rating is 4.1.
Not bad.
Let me, okay, JB says, it's working now.
Get a kick out of Garfield pointing at the chests when you find them.
If I win Sutton, I'll get it a level.
I'll give it a five, no doubt.
Great.
Hold on.
Nate, how's that?
This golden voice feels as though we have left.
I got to piss with it.
We got two more after this.
Wait, one more from a Google, from a Google use, wait, two more.
Sebastian Foy says, I won a glazed donut from the 7-Eleven from the app.
When redeeming the prize, be aware that the redeem button does not instantly give you a coupon.
The redeem button sends you an email within three days,
then you confirm your name and alien address, then they send you the prize.
So you get real donuts out of this app.
You can win like food from 7-Eleven.
Holy shit.
Okay, a Google user says, came for the memes and stuck around when it was actually fun.
I didn't expect the prizes to actually be winnable,
but I have a dozen Rad Garfield stickers on display in my kitchen now.
Not bad.
Pokemon Go ain't got me shit for stickers or donuts.
One more, one more.
Dr. Robonto TV Productions Films gives it five out of five stars and says,
this game literally saved my life.
He was starving to death and he needed that glazed donut.
Garfield Go is the actual pinnacle of human achievement and should only be spoken if
positively if you're a fan of angelic experiences.
Download this masterpiece today.
He's memanous.
All right, that's pretty incredible.
Okay, all right.
Next.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I've got it.
You downloaded it.
You got it.
We should all play.
Maybe it's Garfield Community Day today.
Oh, every, wait, I was going to say every Monday is community day, but it's like anti-community
day.
You like lose money if you log in on a Monday.
I want to announce that I did go out for swine of day and I did attain many delicious swine.
I didn't name any of them Brunswick.
Brunswick's dead, Nate.
Too obvious, too obvious.
You have to let go.
He's gone.
Okay.
However, I do have the lucky Mamo swine that Munchie traded me when it was just a pillow swine.
And its name is Beef and Barley in his reference.
What's a shiny guy look like?
Is he is like blue?
It's kind of brownish green.
It's not good.
It's not a great shiny.
Okay.
Let's move on.
We got actually there was three more total.
This is prune man.
Prune man.
Hit us.
Go.
Hey Nathan slash Nathaniel.
I can't believe that the fucking supposed best guy ever doesn't even know that the optimal food to
make you poop is fucking prunes or prune juice even.
It fucking gets that shit flowing right the fuck out and you're fucking sitting in the hospital
paying fucking.
I don't know.
You don't even need to just so you can feel like oh I'm safe.
I'm protected.
Meanwhile, there's a perfect home remedy that's been there your whole life if not longer
and prunes are even fucking good.
They taste good.
So just eat them.
God damn it.
I took I took actual laxatives and it wasn't doing shit.
So I have never eaten a prune in my entire life.
I've had some prunes.
I like them.
They're good.
I think they're actually quite tasty.
Prunes are nice.
I like them too.
I'm curious about them.
I get a jar of dried prunes.
They're kind of like apricots.
They're real good.
Sadly, they're not keto.
Oh well.
Tell them.
Yeah.
Fucked.
There's some nice what's that?
What's that?
You know those people who makes the raisins with the lady with like the sunburst behind her?
You know what I'm talking about?
Oh yeah.
Sunburst.
No, minute made.
Minute made.
Okay, whatever it was they make like a big like cardboard tub of dried prunes and I would
fucking snack on those all day.
Mom used to get them.
They were delicious as hell.
Recommended.
Okay, but anyway, I should fucking just go buy some of those right now.
Okay, next mail.
Two more.
This is from coolmichill.
Commence.
Sunmate.
It's sunmate raisin.
Sunmate, okay.
Hey members of the PCP.
I was just wondering how do all of you relax?
Now this is largely geared towards like hippo or digi or nate.
People who do review channels because I've noticed recently that even though I enjoy video games,
I've started being hypercritical of them and trying to unpack them, etc.
Figure out why I feel the way I do towards all of them.
Take an analytical mindset.
And this has led to me being just stressed all the time because I no longer have an outlet
to just wind down what I want to.
That's even if you play a good game.
I guess you're saying he's turned on his analysis meter so high that it's given him
the shakes and the shimmies.
This is a place where it's difficult for me to relate to a lot of people because I
I hear people say things like that or that they they're stressed out by like negativity.
And I get like people tell me all the time like that they wish I would have like less
negative takes on things.
I don't find like to me it's fun to be negative to be analytical.
Like it's just my natural state.
It doesn't make me necessarily like I mean granted.
There's lots of shows that like or games that I will just stop playing very quickly
because they are you know because I'm analyzing and I think it's bad and I don't want to play
it anymore.
But like I don't I don't find the state of I guess because I don't force myself to
continue playing those things if they're bad.
Like I will just switch to something else.
And to me the fun is in constantly burning through as many things as possible looking
for something good and then you know getting to experience something really great because
I didn't stop myself to you know play every fucking bad game or watch every bad show.
Instead I just burned through all those until I found something truly amazing.
And then yeah if you want to relax you just play the amazing game.
I mean I'm sure Hippo could talk about playing Dark Souls over and over and over again.
That was like yeah that's like me getting Final Fantasy 9 just because like I know it's great
and I don't really have to think about much and just kind of nice just relax and you know
play through it.
This is a thing that I've kind of thought about a bit at some points like why how analysis as
like a thing has like changed my views a little bit.
Most obviously to me is like the way that I used to read One Piece where I wouldn't I
didn't think anything could be bad about One Piece because I just enjoyed it the whole time.
And then I met Nate and he talked about One Piece and he's you know he introduced me to
being angry at it all the time and I was like I know it's but it's like you have criticisms
and I never used to have them and now that I read One Piece there was a bit of a time when I was
like what worrying like oh am I gonna be a nitpicky bitch not even that you are that but
like I was wondering about it and I found that it's it's really just I don't care like like you
can make yourself not care about things you can make yourself just be cool with anything yeah
you know what I think like the the reason I liked analysis in the first place was just to
understand why I like what I like so that I can explain it to people it's not necessarily about
like tearing things down for the sake of it if you if you like analysis because you watch a lot
of YouTube that does that and now you do it yourself um I guess just think about like why
like do you do you want to be like the youtubers you're watching or is it something like do you
actually want to do it yourself I think that a big part of the entertainment value of media for me
is getting to have an opinion on it like that is what I'm like coming to it for is like I'm gonna
watch this and I'm gonna have an opinion and it's gonna be great you know and then like if it's bad
I can go aw man I can explain why this is bad that's gonna be a lot of fun or if it's great
oh I can't wait to brag about how great this show is and tell everybody to go watch it it's like
I can't lie that now that I do YouTube stuff when I see something and I like have something I think
is really interesting to say that's very exciting that I'm gonna get to share like with people and
I'm like hell yes and that's why it frustrates me when there are people who are like oh I you know
I find your your negativity depressing or something I'm like you if you're finding it depressing
you shouldn't be watching these videos because I'm finding it fun I'm doing this because it's
exciting and it's it's like I get to look at something and I get to explain why I feel a
way about a thing and that's always fun it doesn't matter if it's negative or positive feelings
you know and you know I I just realized I didn't really answer his question like how to relax
none of us have it's um I I mean I there was a time when I was like I wouldn't play a game
unless I wanted to make a video on it or unless I thought I could make a video on it now I don't
really do the video stuff anymore so it's easier to just pick up something and play it for for fun
um but before that I would relax by just I don't know I don't think I relax something else honestly
well see that's why I'm praying rapidly that I honestly think same dog same thing I was gonna
say at first like I totally am with you digi on like it's just fun for me to like experience
things and have opinions like good or bad or whatever and like just that part of the analyzing
process is really enjoyable to me but what I like I kind of feel like it's like a larger issue
like what this reminds me of is like like Sam Harris talks a lot about like the the like mental
strain put on us just by being interacting with like social media in general and like what I think
this is maybe cost of like it's like that shonen trope of like we're activating our like our latent
potential but at the cost of our lifespan we're eating away at it to achieve extra 10 000 super
points and like I like I feel like there's probably like a larger strain on like my mind day to day
since I'm like trying to be critical about stuff that used to be you know pretty pretty non-critical
of though I mean I don't know I've always been relatively critical yeah I don't I don't remember
a time when I wasn't like this is the thing for me it's like I just wonder if maybe for both you
and me and everybody it'd be helpful to like like what some people do like uh like a week out of the
year or like a month with like no social media and like it's it's to force yourself even if that's
your normal state of mind to like de-stress your brain or something and then maybe there'll be a
time I mean definitely so I don't think he's really talking about social media though that's stressful
for totally different reasons yeah they're different I just kind of mean like the like social media is
like uh well yeah okay there social media is all bad and bad sure fair enough fair enough
so I mean I guess I just say yeah I've always wanted to try I've never done this but like
taking time off from like pretty much like like a real vacation of like putting down the phone
not like going out of your way to like keep up with you know whatever like if you're a review guy
because like that's the context you said oh you know what I realized I'm wrong I have an answer
to this question it's smoke weed obviously that's how I that's the number one because you reminded me
because I went on sort of a vacation for Christmas um you know I went to May's house for the holidays
and I was just like I showed up with the like in my mind I was like I'm not going to plan
anything there's no stress all the videos I needed to come out are out I'm not worried about work
I'm not worried about getting home I'm not worried about anything going on I'm just gonna sit on this
couch smoke well you know vape a bunch of weed and watch Christmas specials and uh and I ended up
the funny thing about it is that even in that mind state I tend to be even more creative and like
have more answers of what I would want to make it maybe it's maybe it's like that fucking spike
spiegel mindset of like when you relax like that's when you can be the most lethal or whatever when
you're not putting the stress you can flow like water yeah when you I mean when you try to force
yourself to to have ideas then you're constantly yeah you stress yourself out over not having them
and then when they just naturally come to you it's like you're way more excited about them
because it feels like it just sprung out of pure inspiration you know yeah which is a way better
feeling than you know analyzing the SEO optimization and whatnot uh yeah yeah maybe I don't I'm trying
to think because like I don't feel like I've had that many stress moments where I'm like I need to
relax I think I'm just normally chill and then like it doesn't take much to get me feeling okay
like I just go outside and I feel all right well let me I'm I'll give this guy like some
some advice since he since he specifically mentioned like being a youtube's man or whatever
whatever your project is what I'd say is it's important to have dedicated downtime which I
don't have but I should yes like so if you work five days a week you should maybe one day a week
I don't even want to do this but like to those who want to like optimize their living situation
literally force yourself to do no work maybe for like I don't know a weekend that's every weekend
that's a part of why I love going out to eat because it's like I can just put everything aside
and be like I'm going out on this venture to go get food and enjoy myself and nothing no other
thoughts need to enter my brain in this time you know yeah but like like for me dated like every
day it's taken me a while to get my upload schedule back to it and you know people are waiting for
the next we are going whatnot so like it's on my mind all the time as soon as a video comes out
there's like a few seconds of peace and then I'm thinking it's time to think about the next one
immediately and that's just the nature of the beast and that's that's the nature of youtube being
like so much work for so much relatively low pay you know yeah unless you're one of the people
just getting used to to getting used to doing all that work yep it's not for everybody it's not
possibly not for the vast vast majority including me I think it's unhealthy for everyone yeah I mean
I'm not a full-time youtuber maybe it will not work well with my psychology we'll find out one of
these days um so yeah I don't know just give yourself breaks really and try to turn off the
youtube stuff no matter what I don't know that's that's my thought uh and we've got this fucking
garfield game is still loading I don't know whether it's ever gonna load do we have more of these
these bad boys uh we've got one final voicemail to listen to and this one boy let me just okay
let me just preface this this is actually a series of four voicemails that were sent in
called sex with the young part one through four basically um and I'm sparing you the first three
because they are not necessary and I'm just gonna show off the last one can you can you
yeah let me I'll give you the it's just it starts out sex with the young part one
is uh Vic Miniana calling in to let us know oh excellent you know he's very excited to be
wait who's Vic Miniana you know uh current current voice actor dealing with some allegations
right now unproven but you know he's definitely true though and um uh by the way it was very funny
to watch like yesterday during your stream you're just like he's a rapist no one's accused him of
rape he's a rapist no one is even acute and may is like did you we probably shouldn't like sling
like accusations I said I said I am hey I'm just a parody character I have no indeed none of this
is liable in any way right but I know what I believe fair enough fair enough um notable
notable unconvicted monster slip through the legal cracks as it were um by not committing the crime
in quotations I have no idea what the what the beef with Vic Miniana is right now but it doesn't
matter I mean the beef should be that he has the most annoying voice of all time well you'll
like how I smell number two otherwise watchable dubs Edward Elric called in in part two to let
us know that he has a terrible voice and that he I want to save Al so you know that not really
relevant to sex with a young but whatever um number three was Donatello calling in to let us know
that he is picking up the mantle of sex with the young and he's running with that um and now here
we are the final chapter by the way if you if people have a link to the SoundCloud you can go
listen to these I don't know if they like have a link to it I put them all up there but in any case
here's the final chapter of sex with the young finale go also hashtag kick vic and fucking punch
Todd purely because of their terrible squealy annoying high-pitched day boy sissy boy pussy boy
fuck boy femi ass queer ass shitty voices seriously not any of their sexual misconduct
no god forbid I mean but the fact that the anime dubbing industry let their performances continue
on for the amount of time that they did is actually despicable and you should oh be fucking ashamed
of yourselves hard agree seriously why can't we get more like baritone range skinny anime dudes
like steve bloom a spike spiegel come on i'm right here donatello why are they knocking on
the whole donatello door why are they booking telling me to play spike in the live action
Netflix come on I my father forced me to be a ninja but all I've ever wanted to be was an actor
and I've never once gotten the role this is it this is why I must go to soccer icon and
oh I forgot I forgot a large part of the narrative here was that Vic and Al
I and Donnie we're all going to soccer icon 2009 okay forgive me for forgetting that so he'll be
there guys uh the soccer icon near you that's right Vic is in the soccer icon he's the voice yeah he
is the voiceover he's uh he's the staple he's I think he like arranged the whole thing I could
be wrong about that but uh I know he's wait is he in the legendary soccer icon yeah at the end
he's the voice at the end that's like you should go to soccer icon whoa I had no idea I had no idea
big time there's no saving him he said oh that he really hit the big time all right well that's it
that's all the voicemails we're done for the day people uh the patreon.com at last slash the
procrastinators podcast is that is that in the url like it is a podcast but is that in the url of
the oh I I'm gonna say no but check the fucking link below I can't remember right now
yeah give us $5 for all the bonus episodes dreamcast uh was out oh I almost forgot I had a really
spooky dream okay there's the full story you just heard it right there that's all you need to know
last night I had I had a spooky dream yeah that I forgot to meant no well I had it I had it after
I had a spooky dream after saving for dreamcast too Ben no one gives a reminder yeah it reminded me
that I have a certain kind of dream that I forgot to go into yeah we'll do dreamcast too and I'll
talk about okay great yeah I want to talk about this one because this was legitimately terrifying
but nonetheless patreon.com slash the procrastinators podcast I can't remember uh speak pipe give us
your voicemails and uh follow us at tbcrastinators on twitter thanks for being here everybody we
will see you next week and wait a minute is this is this the first episode where they now we now
have a new editor okay no this is probably still edited by us but the contest is over now if I
remember correctly yes this was the finale so if you're hearing this you have until the end of today
to get your entry in okay I'm glad I remembered that hashtag PCP editor contest get it in today
you still have several hours by the time you're hearing this so uh good luck if you want to
be in time fuck joint going on in my head trying to process what you're saying yeah we're we're
talking six days ahead of today I think whatever five days uh so there you go people good luck
and godspeed thanks for being here and we'll see you next week bye
I'm supposed to be working right now I'm supposed to be working right now
you