If you're interested in changing your gender, then you are considered a transgender person.
That means you are either biologically a man who identifies as a woman, or a biologically
born woman who self identifies as a man. Some transgender people have expressed
feeling uncomfortable with their biological body. For example, a biological woman wishing
she didn't have breasts. Reading and hearing about the experience of transgender people
might connect with you or help you understand your own internal feeling. Some transgender
people have felt like they were transgender as far back as they can remember. Others
started identifying as transgender later in life.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast,
an intimate small session today with me, your favorite guy, the best guy ever, and Mumkey Jones.
Hey, finally an episode where I can actually say I respect all of the cast members of the podcast.
I wouldn't go that far myself. And also, Endless Jess is here.
The only episode where I can say I respect one member of the podcast.
Congratulations, Nate. You did it.
I did it, guys. I did it. Well, and that's it, everybody. That's it. Just the three of us today.
Everybody else is off doing more important things. We're left in the trenches to carry
the sink and ship as far as we can. I was going to say with the three amigos,
but based on this topic, we might be the three of me guzz.
Impressive. You're welcome.
And if you can tell from that extremely cryptic hint, we're talking about gender swapping today.
Gender swapping. You can only refer to me as my new name on this episode, Estrogen Jess.
Good. Okay, I'll be Mumket, I think, is what we decided.
Yep, that's a good one. And I'm going to be Best Gal Ever, which is short for Best Gal
Godot Ever, because I identify as killing two Palestinian children in the Israeli defense
force. There you go. The one true meme has returned. The only funny joke from that overly
long, terrible Marvel DC podcast. Yeah, but it won't really hit. I won't really fucking hit.
Munchie did it again. Okay, let's fucking get into it, I guess.
Speaking of Mumket, remember when the Alvin and the Chipmunks, they had the Chimpettes,
and they were like, yeah, I do.
This is where we're going. Just the excess pre-edit side, when I mentioned the Chimpettes.
That's all I need to say. That's all you need to say about the Chimpettes.
The only good thing about that film franchise was that Jason Lee played the main guy, and then
in the second movie, he was like in the hospital the whole time. They wrote him out of the movie,
but not for the first 10 minutes, and I don't know why they made that choice.
Maybe they just only had so much money to pay for his time.
Yeah, because Jason Lee is so fucking expensive. The guy from My Name Is Earl is a hot ticket in
Hollywood. No wonder they called the squeakwell, because without Jason Lee, it's just a tepid
little fart of a movie squeaking through the butt cheeks of Hollywood's tight sphincter,
too tight to dish out that money for Jason Lee.
So this topic is so shit that I could find nothing related to it on Urban Dictionary.
Like, I tried searching gender-bending, gender-swapping. Let's just read gender.
Isn't it rule 63? Is the internet rule about gender-swapping?
That's true. That's true. Okay, let's see. Okay, rule 63. All right, that works.
Rule 63 is a rule of the internet that reads as follows. For any given male character,
there is a female version of that character. This rule's exceptions are only in-oh,
this is fucking-who gives a shit for whatever. Only in the instance that A,
the male character is already so androgynous that a female version would be basically the same,
or B, the female version hasn't been drawn yet. Well, why would you even write that?
Just fucking-this is shit. This is terrible. This is absolute garbage.
Hey, so the chimp bets, those Alvin and the chipmunk girls, they remind me.
What they remind me of is how incredibly hot female versions of characters that you already
like are. That's what you guys agree. I'll buy this premise. That's true. Would you say it?
I mean, like when I see a female version of Kymina, for example, I find that extremely arousing.
Oh yeah, like the girl from that cosplay girl who yelled at you. That's the hottest
comment I've ever seen. She's great, dude. 10 out of 10. It's because you got all the great
things about a character, but then you also can sex them now, which is just great.
Which is just great. It works the other way as well, I guess. If you've got a cool female
character, that's nice. But when you gender swap them, you can project all the things you like
about them from their, I guess, female version. And then also, now they can be-they can drive well.
Now they can drive-got them. I've got to say, when me and Mage did our Naru cast,
she drew a picture of me as Naruto and her as Sasuke. So we have this female Sasuke.
It's pretty much Sasuke with purple hair and tits. And like you're saying with the chimp
bets, I jerked off to that picture Mage drew probably 30 times in one day. It's just-it makes
the character so much hotter. I agree. Well, okay. That's one-
The podcast, everyone. We'll be collecting our fat three-person check now. Goodbye.
That's one facet thoroughly explored. This is what happens when you got three people. Okay,
but here we go. There's another facet, and it's the personally gender swapping thing, right?
So there's wanting to be the little girl, as it were. The Digi Bro complex.
Yeah. Yeah. Which, can you say why Digi's not on this episode? Because I imagine a lot of people
in the comments are angry that of this topic, of all topics, Digi should be here.
Yeah, that's true. Here's what happened. So we said, hey, Digi, do you want to come on?
He said, fuck you guys. Fuck the PCP. I'm too big for that shit. I have 300,000 subs now.
You're all beneath me. And that's why he's gone on. Did he cross that? Did he get the 300,000 now?
By the time this is out, he probably will. Okay, well, Greg, congrats, Digi, congrats.
Also, we hope to Voo. I hope to Voo would be here too, but he's busy as well. So this is what
you left with folks. Enjoy. The table scraps of the PCP. So I want to be the little girl.
And by that, I mean, I would definitely, I see a lot of perks. There's obviously some negatives,
but I see a lot of perks in being a sexy girl. I do have friends though, because if I was a girl,
you'd know I'd be a 10 out of 10 goddess, of course. It's a given. It's just a mirror image of
yourself, but with tits. That's right. That's right. So there's a lot of good things about that.
I guess I'm making, I'm taking this literally, I'm taking this like real, like if I was just
suddenly a girl in society, there's a lot of good things about being a girl, but there's
definitely some negatives. For example, wait, wait, time out. There's negatives to being a girl
in society. I don't think that holds any water, Nate. Name one. Well, I've got a friend who...
Okay, too far. Again, you're saying crazy things. I know. I've got a friend who's super hot and she
works in like customer service and just like, she was just telling me the other day, all the time
people will come up to her like, you know, men and they will, you know, want to have sex with her.
So what that manifests as... What a tragic life she must live. Being attractive.
Well, imagine if all the dregs of society kept coming up to you with the clear intention of
wanting to fuck you and it's like, yeah, okay, cool. Appreciate the compliment, but...
Not to get off on a gender dynamics tangent here. I think it's unavoidable, but I mean,
what the hell else are we going to talk about on this shitty fucking topic?
You know, I get that complaint of like why women would feel objectified and feel shitty if like
just like you said, the dregs of society are always wanting to fuck them. But like,
from my point of view, it's the same thing, except the dregs of society always want to
fight me. So what's really worse? Well, like people's dads. Yeah, like people's dads.
Uh, yeah, that's true. That's true. Can we talk about that for a second,
that Jess is trying to fight every dad on earth? Yeah, I'm making that a... I'm gonna make it a
patron reward tier for a certain amount. I will fight your dad. I will... I'll fly out. I will
have a real fight. It'll be on YouTube and everything. You're gonna go to them. They don't
even come to you. Yeah, it's gonna have to be a high reward tier because I'm gonna need a lot of
money to pay for these endeavors, but it'll be worth it. If I can... If I can go down in history
as like the YouTube guy who fights dads, that's a good legacy. This is great. Munchie goes out
and captures them, you know, sets them up and then you fight them, you know. He sex them up and
you knock them down. There you go. I think this is the first feature film in the PCP Cinematic
Universe is that instead of Rocky, it's called Daddy, where Jess just beats up people's dads.
Endless Jess versus the dads. Yeah, yeah. Okay, well...
Instead of the kid catcher in Chitty Chitty Bing Bing, Munchie is the dad catcher.
Of course. Is that a reference that's lost on this generation?
By the way, I do want to say about that, about what you're saying here about the being annoyed
by the dregs, I'd be like being objectified. I mean, I'm sure that's annoying for women to
be objectified by people, but even putting that aside, even if you're not objectified,
I'm just saying just the fact that people ever come up to you at all and, you know,
it tried to talk to you like people are boring and they're gay and I don't want to hear from them
ever. So just on that level, just on that level, like, yeah, you know, there are definitely advantages
to being women, but that's definitely something that would annoy me because as a man, no one in
my life has ever approached me with any proposition of any kind. Nobody gives a fuck about me.
No, as a man, I just constantly get approached with hostility and mockery all day everywhere I go.
Like women complain about catcalling, like, hey, you're hot and you're pretty and I want to fuck
you. Like, yeah, that would be annoying. But I walk outside every day and I also get people catcalling,
except they're saying like, hey, faggot, out of a moving car and like, fuck you buddy, screw you.
And it's like, that's way worse. Well, when you walk around in your your brony t-shirts, Jesse,
a little bit of that is to be expected. I do not know. I do not dress provocatively. I dress as
like I try to like hide my my my strength as much as I can. I wear like overcoats, like a
teenage mutant ninja turtle, like I hide my fucking shell when I go out wearing wearing a turtle mask.
That's why, dude. I like that Nate is suggesting that Jess was asking for it based on what he was wearing.
That's exactly right. Hey, how could you fucking fascist. Nate is that guy who's driving by in like
cars with open windows going, hey, faggot, fuck you. I got that horn that's
Oh my god. It annoys me so much. It happens to me every time I go out. It's like, I really do dress
like as normal as possible to try and avoid people looking at me. Like I wear like a baseball cap and
like just a regular t-shirt and jeans and guys will like yell shot. And like, I get so mad when
people fuck with me that like, I will fucking go out into the middle of the street as they're like
peeling away and like, like called Drogo like stomping around like, the fucking most fucking
the fucking shotgun. I'll fucking fight all you. I'm like fighting random cars that have nothing to
do with it. I'm jumping in. I'm jumping through other people's windows and like driving after them
and a whole chase breaks out. It's an adventure every time. You know, that's interesting, Jesse,
but I have to say I have never been in any kind of serious fight in my life, nor have I ever even
been close to that level. So I just wonder, do you think it might have something to do with
your aura or perhaps just the place you live? Perhaps that place is just more hostile than the
world that I grew up in and existed now. I think I'm just too, I'm just too handsome and strong.
People hate me for it. The world can't handle this. You know, there was a, in part six of JoJo,
there was a particular stand called survivor and its unique ability was really shit. Nobody liked
it, but its power was that it made everyone around it a little more on edge, just a little more
pissed off than they were normally. And what happened was like during the part where like
that thing was going around, like everyone in this entire jail where the thing took place,
they all started fighting because they were all just a little bit pissed off and then someone
did something and then they all had a massive fight and it's a huge riot inside the jail.
And I think that might be you, my friend. You might have, you might have some sort of superpower
here. Yeah, I might. I definitely do. I definitely get people to a certain point somehow without
without doing anything. Have you guys ever done any sort of drive by cat call either to a man
or a woman just yelling something at somebody on the street as you drive by?
I've never done anything like that though. I have done, you know, numerous like more like
approaches, you know, and shit in my, in my heyday. Well, I don't mean like hitting on somebody.
Like the example I wanted to give was that back when I lived in Iowa, my friend Biggs,
the only thing you would ever yell at people as we drove by them, they'll be walking on the
sidewalk and he'll just yell, get a car! And that's it. Over and over again to these lowly creatures
without people. We don't know if they don't have a car. They're just walking. So that's what I
guess he strongly disapproves this. Well, I've never, I've never cat called anybody. I don't think.
I feel ashamed. I should have cat called somebody by now. I should do it. I should go out and say,
hey baby, give me that pussy! You know, one of those. Does it work? One of those, yeah. I mean,
of course, why do men keep doing it? Because it gets results, right? I would assume that's the case.
No, what we need is a wingman. So you got to drive and you got to like be holding action giraffe
out the other window like, hey baby, I got AIDS! I got AIDS! But this guy doesn't over here and then
he comes to you. I look like a hero by comparison. I look like a real catch. That's true. That's
true. Or just a guy to, just to like, you know, be the guy in the dark alley where the lady turns
down and like, she's like, hey baby, I'm gonna get in that. I'm gonna get in that now. And she's
like, no, please. And then I come in and I beat up my friend and then I take her home and we do the
sex. That's a pretty solid plan. Wait, you want to be like an alley man? Yeah, I want to be an alley
man. My goal in life is to be like the mugger at the beginning of the superhero movie who gets
beat up by the hero first, before he has to fight the supervillain. Oh my god, you know what?
That reminds me of, this is sort of relevant to what we're talking about, what are the greatest
moments in all of anime, of all time, is from, it's called like, something something Nietzsche Joe,
it's not Nietzsche Joe, it's like the high school boy version, it's got like a longer name, it's like
boys, something Nietzsche Joe, everyday lives of high school boys. So there's a moment in that,
in that fucking manga, sorry, anime, where, so like, there's just like a bunch of dudes,
like a bunch of Japanese high school kids are just hanging out in an alley. And they're just like,
they're like talking about like homework or like science, like they're being like responsible,
mature students. And then all of a sudden, like a girl walks in, right, like a girl walks in and
she sees these three like, slightly rough looking dudes hanging out at this alley. And she's just
like, she steps down, she doesn't notice them, she sees them and she's like, oh, uh, uh, uh,
and they're just like, what are you doing here? And like, they're not, they're just like, hey,
what's going on? Like, what's up? But she's like spooked just because she didn't know what she was
walking into. Then all of a sudden, like another dude walks into the alley, like and sees the
situation, he sees like this girl spooked by three guys. And she said, and he says to it like,
he assesses the situation. And he's just like, I know what I have to fucking do. He steps up and
he's like, Hey, you three ruffians, quit hassling this lady. And all of a sudden these three guys
who were just like super willing, they were just going to like help her get directions or like
guide her out of there or whatever. They just look at each other and they know what they have to do.
They're like, Hey, man, fuck off. We were going to play with that bitch. She was going to be ours.
We were just going to have a little fun. And they all began aggressing towards the guy. And so
the guy is just like, Yes, this is my chance. He proceeds to beat them up as they allow him to
beat them all up. And they're just like, Yes, this is what we have to do. They allow themselves to
be beaten up. And then the lady is like, Oh my God, thank you so much for saving from those ruffians
as the dude like escorts throughout like, haha, I'm the fucking hero. And the guys just get up,
they nod each other like, Yep, we did it, man. We really, we were, we were what society needed
today. That's really inspirational. I want to do that. I want to set up a fucking heroes like a
like a like a slip and jimmy wingman scam where I can pretend to be a rape boy. And if the plan
goes wrong, I just accidentally end up raping the girl because the guy didn't get there in time.
Where were you? You gotta commit. You made me you made me a bad boy.
Okay, so we've talking about how great it is to commit rape. But let's talk a little bit more
about how great it is to be raped. Well, we need to backtrack Nate, because we were listing all
the negatives of being a woman and the things you would face and we lost in the catcalling world.
So what are the other disadvantages? Okay, well, there's a real okay, this is a real thing, right?
Women are right because we just talked about that. Well, not really, but like women are objectively
on the whole, not every single person, but they're generally weaker than men. So when you got a woman
walking outside alone, and like you're just doing whatever, you know, you're just walking home or
whatever. And I feel the same fear whenever I'm walking out alone, I'm like, Oh, God, everyone's
going to fucking murder me. But when you see just like any person, you know, there is a pretty good
chance that they are stronger than you and could overpower you. There's at least a 50% chance,
because you know, men or whatever. And if you know it's a man, then you know this guy could be you.
So like, in that situation, if you're like unprepared, you don't have anything to defend
yourself with, like that person could push your shit in if they wanted to. And I don't know about
you guys, but I don't trust anyone ever. Whenever I see a cop, I assume he wants to kill me. I assume
he wants me dead. So I will just do whatever the fuck he, yeah, serial killers, like just just as a
cop has like infinitely or you know, a more than enough advantage over me to kill me if he wants to,
because he has a gun, like to a woman, most men just have that advantage, because they generally
are just stronger. They could take you down if they felt like it. So just like, it's a little
bit spooky, you know, being a woman out there, just, just being out there doing whatever you
want. So like, I, my female friends will generally tell me like, and I've had some people, I know
I've had some bad stories with this shit, they'll just be out walking. And they're scared, because
they don't want to die. They don't want to get raped. They don't want bad shit to happen to them.
So just on a physical level, you know, that's a disadvantage, not to mention the fact that of
course women have a vagina, which is a desired thing by most men. So like, it's like a guy walking
around, has nothing to offer, like there's no reason to like be women have those. I've been
looking in the wrong places. Women. Yeah. So like, it's like women like have a diamond whenever
they're walking outside that every man really wants. And like, if a guy is pushed over the edge,
he might go for it. You know, it just, and I'm not trying to say men are demons or anything.
It's just like, I don't trust anyone. I have no faith that anyone will do the right thing at any
point. And so I totally feel why women are spooked by this shit. All right, Nate, I got the ultimate
solution for this problem. If we become women, here's what we should do. It's a new invention.
You might have heard of it. It's called the gun. You get one of these bad boys, and you're stronger
than anybody else because then you just shoot them. Yeah. That's true. That's true. But you keep
using the word spook to describe women who are about to get raped. Like a rapist comes out,
and they just do the standing in place scooby-doo run before they fucking flip the book top.
You're oversimplifying the spectrum of spook right now because there's,
it's really a spectrum. It's really a spectrum. Jess, I got a question for you.
We know you can beat up any dad on earth. And on the subject of female physicality, I want to know.
Who wins in a fight? Endless Jess or Ronda Rousey?
I'm gonna have to say Endless Jess. Oh, fucking shit. I'm surprised. What's your case there,
dude? She wants fucking kill you. Bullshit. Shut up. I'm just sick of that fucking,
that like, that any woman in any sport could beat any regular man ever. It's all bullshit.
You take the fucking, you take fucking the black widow from the Avengers and a regular
fat guy off of from like a video store and the guy from the video store will win every time.
I hate movies. I hate fucking this. Just people just wanking themselves off about strong women.
It's fake. There's no such thing. Fuck Ronda Rousey. You can take the world's most honorable
Bushido woman. You know, she's got her katana. It has been folded 20,000 times. So she's 20 times
stronger. Jesus Christ. And all I do is I say hold, I put on 250 pounds. I become a fat piece
of shit. I say hold my beer, bitch. And then I've won. I have defeated her. I have defeated her. Yes.
Okay. You know what pisses me off? Like if a guy did fight Ronda Rousey and he won,
he'd get no credit. They just like dismiss it as beating a woman. But if he lost, that's true.
He'd be even doubly mocked for it like, oh, you lost to a woman. So which is it? Is she on an
equal playing field or not? Well, she has a disadvantage, you know, there's a disadvantage.
Nate, have you listened to biggest problem in the universe? I know Jesse was only seven episodes of
me to finish it. Was there one of the episodes or was this a different podcast where they talked
about like a trans woman. So like a guy who becomes a woman was in mixed martial arts and he
like won a tournament and how that was bullshit. So that's, is that kind of the same thing?
Yes, it's related. It's like the practical way to achieve this. Okay, so the practical way to beat
up women and still get credit for it. Hey, wait a minute. Go to think of it. Why am I fighting
Ronda Rousey? The deal was that I would fight Ronda Rousey's decrepit father. That was my thing
from the beginning. Well, yeah, I mean, Frank, you probably have a bigger trouble with her body.
Jess versus Frank Rousey.
Well, okay, so on that topic, because I always thought that was interesting. So, okay, so like
there's, what is in fact the difference between men and women physically, right? So there's,
there's a bunch of stuff. There's like hormones, the presence of testosterone. More like the
building muscle. Oh, you nailed it, dude. You nailed it. There's like bone density differences.
Obviously, there's like, there's anatomical differences, right? That's real shit. That's
real shit. So, so right now we know that we're not looking at the same thing. So if a man wants
to compete with women and say that it's totally even, like he's got no advantages,
like what we would say now, what they do now is like they have them going like hormone therapy,
right? To even the playing field. So they, they haven't taken estrogen and shit and, and
don't take testosterone. Are you talking about the transgender AMA fighter or MMA fighter?
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about. I don't think it goes on hormones to even the playing
field. It's because he wants to get a woman's body. It doesn't have to do with his job.
Well, but if we were trying to make it fair, you would have to do something to address the real
differences just from there. If we wanted to make it fair, we'd say you don't get to do this because
you were born a man. Okay, but there might be a way. Go fight in the men's league.
Yeah. I mean, it's okay. So with this point, we got a couple of categories now. So you've got
men who are just men. You got women who are just women. But then there's, I mean, there's some
clear gray area here. If you're going to be transitioning or whatever, there's, there's
got to be a way to account for that difference. Well, what it is, there should be a tranny
league. Well, like it's, it's, it works like Pokemon. There's three stages. Like you go from
like a man into a trans woman. And then with the help of a thunderstorm, you become just a woman.
Yeah, it makes sense. Why a thunderstorm?
Um, I don't know what a moonstone make more sense. I think so.
A moonstone. Well, if you're trying to become a man, uh, yeah, you need a thunderstorm to become
a man so you can become Chad Thundercock. Right. Yeah. That's the one. That's the one.
Have you guys been seeing these memes incidentally recently that have been poking them and popping
up of like, uh, how like the virgin stands versus how the Chad stands or how they sit?
Yes, it turns out I'm a virgin. I don't know, whatever. I fucking love them. Chad is my hero.
Uh, but anyway. Oh, we'll get into that later when we talk about if we were women.
Oh yeah. That's exciting. That's exciting. Um, I don't know. Uh, that's, that's been addressed,
I guess. Oh, it's, it's crazy, man. I don't know. Uh, like we could talk about like, so,
so if you're actually transitioning from a man to woman IRL, uh, it's, it's complex. You know,
you would have to really restructure your whole fucking anatomy and like your bone structure
and you have to install a vagina, which I think they do now at least to some degree. Yeah, they do.
Um, but, but, but, uh, Caitlyn Jenner still is a penis. Just, um, just throwing that out there.
What do you think about that, monkey? What does that put her on the? I think that's,
that's none of your business, what Caitlyn Jenner, Caitlyn Jenner. Caitlyn Jenner? Yeah.
I just want to say though, what is my business is what pronoun I'm forced to use for someone,
that if they're going to tell me I have to refer to someone some way, then it becomes my business
what, what they are forcing me to do. And, um, I'm just, is it insensitive to say like,
you know, if you're going to make me say he or she or whatever, like, let's see some documentation.
Let's see some proof that, uh, you know, I just don't like being forced to do something on the
other person's word, because I don't, as I've said, I'm consistent on this. I don't trust anyone.
Uh, if you just look like a woman, if I saw Caitlyn Jenner on the street,
would absolutely call her female because she looks that way. No problem with that at all.
But if somebody who looks male comes up to me and just says, hey, call me she, call me whatever,
then I don't think it's crazy to say like, okay, uh, but why though? Like what's,
what's, what's the situation here, dude? What am I, what am I looking at here? What are we
dealing with? Here's an example of this that happened to me recently. Uh, as we've discussed
in the previous couple episodes of this show, there is a recent, uh, the, the Tranny Phantom
massacre that the guy, Randy Stair, who shot up the thing, he wanted to join Embers Ghost Squad,
but Randy is, or was transgender. So my friend, Bedhead Bernie, love him to death, but I think he,
he made a tactical error on this. He wrote up a script about the, the, the whole thing
and I had to narrate it. And when we referred, or when he referred to Randy in the script,
he would use they, them pronouns, which is very confusing because we're talking about one person.
So the comments were just, it was a firestorm of who the fuck is they, uh, and like, why are you
respecting the preferred pronouns of a, of a mass shooter? Like, why would you do that?
That's a tough one. That's a tough one. I think a lot of, okay, now finish your point.
Well, yeah. So like Bernie's, Bernie said he wanted to do it professionally because he's making all
these videos for his portfolio so we can get into college and all this shit. But like in that case,
fuck Randy Stair. Fuck their preferred pronouns. I don't care what you think you are. You think
you're a fucking ghost. I don't give a shit. Randy's a guy.
That's like an ethical quandary, like, um, yeah, like, uh, how like it's our generations
crucible to decide like what bathrooms, uh, trans people should use. It's like our generations
crucible to decide should you respect the pronouns of a killer. You know what that reminds me of?
Should you like not punch Nazis is another question on the table for our generation.
That's a big thing happening right now. Okay. But, but that aside, you know, okay,
just I think like any trans activist or whatever, any person in the know would probably argue that
like, okay, yes, this guy is a bad person. You know, he could kill people. It's objectively wrong.
But like, I think what they would say is like, we should segregate, uh, to use the inappropriate
word separate, but equal. We should. Okay. We should separate like a person's like gender
identity from any crimes they commit. And we shouldn't lump in like their, their murderous
tendency, mental illness shit with their gender fluidity or confusion. Uh, that's probably the
case they would make. What do you, what do you think about that? I think I'm still thinking
about Ronda Rousey and how much. When she fucking, when she comes on like a talk show
and like, like Conan O'Brien or, or whatever, or like Jimmy Kimmel, whatever, like,
loser talk show host will like pretend to be like afraid of her. Like, oh, Ronda Rousey is
going to beat me up. Come on, Conan, you're like six foot five. What are you doing? What are you,
all right? I was, I was joking before, but Ronda Rousey would definitely beat your ass and would
definitely beat most men's ass. Like I was just kidding before. She would easily. I don't believe
you. I don't care what anyone says. She's a trained killer. She's a trained killer, dude. She will
fucking kill you. I'm a self-trained killer. I've been shadowboxing for 20 years like fucking
old boy. What the hell is shadowboxing? I've been killing on the streets of fucking,
probably. Like Jess, I get that you're strong, but she has, she knows how to fight.
If it works for old boy, it works for me. That's how I approach every situation in life.
You don't get a hammer in this fight. Hey, you know, on this issue of gender identity,
I did want to say though that. Look, if I can't beat Ronda Rousey, then at least Conan O'Brien
could definitely beat her. Conan O'Brien's like 10 feet tall. He's got that Irish boxing stance
from the 1920s. Yeah, he does. You can't step to that in an MMA ring. They outlawed that from
MMA because it was too powerful. Look, he is an untrained twink fuck boy. He would get his shit
pushed in. Nobody on earth is stronger than Conan O'Brien. We're working on Invader Zim logic
right now. Like the tallest man is the most powerful. It has dominion over all he can lay his
eyes on. So Jeff would beat all of her asses then? Is that why we kicked him out of PCB because he
can kill all of us? He was too much of a threat. He was too strong. Can we get serious and talk
about how we would fuck all the guys in high school if we were girls? Yes, but in one second,
I just want to say about this. I really want to talk about that. We will get, we will certainly
get there. I've been joking about this a lot, but I do actually feel like, okay, so gender is
actually pretty crazy and there's legitimately people out there who feel weird about it. I
definitely think that it's kind of a meme that people who wouldn't necessarily be into it are
just kind of, are just like, yeah, that sounds fun. Let's get into it. I mean, I have no idea how
rampant that is, but I'm sure that's there to some degree, just like any trend or craze would be.
But on the, just to address this, I feel like it's a little bit of a, it's problematic. It's a
little bit problematic that in English, I know we don't have any real good way of addressing people
that don't adhere to the binary of male or female. So I'm just saying like, I feel for people, you
know, the fact that we have men and female bathrooms that, you know, that kind of sucks for
people who are floating around somewhere in the middle. So I have legitimate sympathy for them,
but here's where, here's my red pill and comes in. On a practical level, these people are the
vast minority. How much effort are we really going to put in to worrying about their specific
interest? And I know in a perfect world, we would just bam, put like an extra bathroom for everybody,
for everyone fucking gender identity there is, have an extra bathroom just for them so that
everybody feels safe and at home. But practically, can we really be doing this guys? Can we really be
fucking around with this? I think the solution is that we don't need more bathrooms. We need one
bathroom for everyone. It's fucking hard that we have two bathrooms in the first place.
You know, you're absolutely 100% right on that. I mean, think about it. When you were three years
old, your mom would take you into the women's bathroom because you're too fucking young to
go by yourself. When I was a young boy, my mother took me into the women's bathroom to take a
Mando shit. Yeah, right. I mean, I didn't get traumatized walking into the women's bathroom
when I was three. So, I mean, realistically, what's the worst I can have? Like everyone in the
world, you live in a house with women and you usually have one bathroom and nobody gets raped
usually. Why the fuck didn't I think that before? The problem, the problem isn't that we don't have
enough individual bathrooms to segregate everyone into. The problem is that we segregate them at
all right now. That's the problem. You know, we should have co-ed everything. It worked in
Starship Troopers. You know, that's my other thing. Got my first little baby boner to Starship
Troopers so we know it's good. That's my other philosophy in life. If it doesn't work like it
did an old boy, then it must work like it did in Starship Troopers. Well, thank God we just
solved this massive issue for everyone. Yeah. Honestly, if I'm going to rape somebody, it's
not when they're taking a shit. It's probably when they're not taking a shit. You know, I like the
rape after the shit because like the passageway that I like to use has already been stretched a
good way. So, you know, that works for me. That works for me. Wait, if I'm going to rape somebody...
With diarrhea every time they go to the bathroom, they're stretching them all?
That's lube, dude. And that's lubing it up just the way I like it.
If I'm going to rape somebody, it's going to be jumping out in a monster mask in that Scooby-Doo
hallway with all the doors so that even if they try to fucking run away, they'll just come through
the other door and I'll catch them. It's perfect. I've been studying those Scooby-Doo running in
and out of doors chase sequences my whole life. I have cracked the code. I become the master of
them, of these portals to different dimensions and now I can catch anyone during them.
All right, monkey. Let's get into it. How much you want to fuck our male
high school classmates? So, here's my problem with Digi Bro's approach. He wants to become a
60 year old girl and then fuck himself. You know, I might not be as traditional as most,
but even I'm thinking like, okay, Digi, you can do better than that. If I'm going to become a girl,
I want to be fucking Yamada from Yamada's first time. I want to be a hot, buxom,
blonde, 15 year old high school girl and I'm going to fuck every single boy in school. I'm
going to get the reputation of the cock-sucking queen, my friends. I'm going to go to fucking
college parties when I'm 15 or 16. I'm going to fuck seniors in college. Fuck it. I'm going to
fuck every chat. I want to know because us as guys, we only get to feel sex from our point of view.
Oh yeah, I'm plunging my dick into your puss, whatever. But it looks like she's enjoying that a
lot more than I am. You know, I've always thought the same thing. Yeah, I think it's better for them.
Of course it is. I think it definitely is if the guy is like at all paying attention to what the
girl wants. Yeah, yeah. I need to know what sex feels like as a girl and I need to abuse it by
being one. At the very least, it's definitely a different experience and I would absolutely love
to experience it at some point. Yeah, I don't think about it. If you woke up, I mean, regardless
of what gender you are now, if you woke up tomorrow morning just as the opposite gender, you could be
like the only person in history who gets the true experience of both. You cannot squander that
opportunity. That this is for all of humanity to know this information. This is your responsibility
to go out and fuck. That was like a problem with your name. He wakes up and grabs his tits
instead of rubbing that little clit bean all fucking day, baby. Yeah, it's true. It's true. I
would definitely do that if I woke up in somebody else's body. Absolutely. Are we talking about
gender switching or body switching? Because if you wake up in a different girl's body and you start,
you know, fiddle in your diddle, is that rape? You know, I was just going to bring it down to be
like, okay, guys, we got to talk about the whole respecting someone else's body. Okay, but first
of all, if you wake up and just it's your body only female, then go hog wild, dude, do whatever
you want to do. Hell yeah. Hell yeah. But if you are in someone else's body and you know this,
that raises some concerns. And I guess I would have to say, don't do it, man. I would have to say
don't do it. I don't think I could resist. If there's no way they're going to find out, you better
believe I'm doing it because it's a victimless crime. That's true. Well, I mean, that's entirely
true. And I don't hate, victimless crimes are as you said, victimless. So it's not really a problem,
right? But like the objective, if you're going for what's objectively the most moral situation,
I would have to say like, really beyond like masturbation, like doing as little with that
body as possible is like the objectively most moral thing you can do, because it's not yours
to use really. It's not like, I mean, like, what are you going to do? Lay there and poop your pants?
If you're in someone's body, you're going to have to see their pussy eventually. You're going
to have to take care of it. You know what? If you wake up in a woman's body, some other woman,
you wake up in her body, you have a responsibility to play with your pussy first thing because
you've got to figure out like where the tampon goes. You got to figure out like how to wipe it
when you pee. You got to know these things, okay? You can't just get to the bathroom and not know
and spray and spray fluids everywhere. I don't know. Maybe I assume they dab or at least or something.
Yeah, girls only have one hole. They have the cloaca. I'm just like a spider.
Yeah, or like a chicken, right? They just have the one hole that spews out everything they
don't need anymore, right? That's how I understand it.
How do the things we can learn when we become women?
Yeah, because you know what? That really is, on the other hand, on a practical level, that really
is something no one in history, like every guy in the world, every woman in the world,
has to like take every guy's word for it. Like what sex for him is like, what the orgasm is like,
like no one ever has crossed the boundary to experience the other side for historical
documentation. It would behoove you to get in there and do that shit just so you can really
say like, okay, they're different in these ways. This is better in that way. It would be better
for everyone. It would be a public service. I like that Nate's taking a very scientific discovery
approach and I just want to fucking flick my bean. I always got to come back to what's objectively
right or true, because that's the way I like to operate. Well, you know, if Nate's taking the
scientific approach and and Mumki's taking the base animal physiology approach, then I'm going
I'm going to go ahead and I'm going to take the emotional approach, the spiritual approach,
because you know, we mentioned the movie Your Name recently, a couple minutes ago,
which you know, I did a review of that movie in my hit series, The Plebe and the Weeb, which
comes out every week. Everyone loves it. It's every week. Hold on. The most consistent show on the
internet, they call it. Not my words, it's everyone else's words. Consistent in quality, maybe not
upload schedule. Yeah, every single week, you know, every twice a week, Monday and Wednesday,
every week, random shine. You know, the movie Your Name is like, it's like my dream scenario,
because like, the guy wakes up in the girl's body, the girl wakes up in the guy's body,
they wake up in each other's bodies, and because of it, they become lifelong friends,
they become, they form a genuine bond, they learn about each other, and it's just an unbreakable
union of love and friendship and camaraderie, and that's beautiful. They can't even remember their
names. Well, they're out of the other shit though, whatever. Yeah, I think they figured out at the
end, I don't really remember. Well, they just like find each other, we don't know if they become
friends, all we know is he stopped her village from getting killed by a meteor. You can see
everything you need to know from the look they share at the end. When you've been in another
person's body, you've been taking those poops, you've been taking those peas, that's a bunch for
life, nothing can break that. I get in my body back and like, dude, you wore this asshole out
with all that pooping, come on, save some for me, my dude, save some for me. You know what,
I like that approach, Jesse, what we really got here, we've got, we've really got a triforce
of approaches here, we've got me, the triforce of wisdom, monkey, the triforce of courage,
and Jesse with the triforce of power for sure, just feeling that shit out.
Nate and Jess, if we can switch topics real quick, I want to hear your day in the life from
wake up to go to bed if you are a girl and you're like a teenager. How many cocks do you suck in
that day? Do we know that it's only for one day? No, no, you're a girl now, so what's the
day? Oh, I'm just a girl. A typical day in the life. But we should, no, we should also do,
like, you're only a girl for one day, what do you do with it? That'd be probably better. Because
like, if I was a girl for one day, then you'd know I'm slutting it up as much as possible.
Oh, hell yeah. Of course, without a doubt, without a doubt. Well, you know, I really have to wonder,
I have to ask, because this is a variable that to me matters quite a bit in this situation.
Am I waking up like in a random girl's body, or am I waking up in the body of a girl that I
personally know? No, it's gonna be like a girl version of you. Oh, it's just a girl now?
Well, first thing I do is I'm figuring out, you know, how the clam works, you know, I'm getting
down there with a fucking, with a microscope and a fucking magnifying glass. I'm going, you know,
how do I work this thing? How do I make a profit off of this thing? And then I go out into the
world. And then I, and then I assume I just go out into the front lawn and go, hey, world, I've
got a vagina. And then I just get money and fame and attention and love just showered
upon me for the rest of the day. Your YouTube channel will have like an extra 100,000 subs.
Oh my God, that's the first thing I do. I make a fucking vlog with my Ted Sound. Holy shit.
Dude, you know what you do? How do you set for life? You know what you do? You make a men's
rights channel as a woman. That's what you do. That's how you fucking win the game.
That is going to be $3,000 in the first day. She won ahead, baby. Just spend the entire day
making nothing but like low top, low cut top vlogs and then set them out on your YouTube
channel like every couple of days for the rest of time. And then you can profit off that one
gender swap day for the rest of your life. Yeah, that's smart. That's thinking. That's thinking.
And also you can finger your pussy between videos. Yeah. And you butthole too. I mean,
you can do that as a guy, but I mean, that's totally gay. No, but that's gay, dude. Totally gay.
All right, so we can all agree it's not gay to get fucked if you're a girl, but what about kissing?
Would you kiss a guy if you're a girl? I would absolutely not know it. I mean, okay, well the
thing about like, okay, so the thing about like, sex in general is a lot, a lot of the gratification
comes from pleasing the other person, right? So like, if you're kissing the other person or if
you're like, let's give a guy a bloge, you know, you give him some bloge, like what, what is enjoyable
about that experience that a lot of women, you know, like a lot of women legitimately do enjoy
doing that, it's that they're making the other person feel good. So like for, for, for us in this
situation, that's us, like a guy who's now become a girl, like what we're getting into right now
is pleasing a guy, which is gay. That's gay. Okay, well, super gay. I just want to get my
I don't care if he feels good. Okay, well, in that case, yeah, I mean, in that case, it's,
it's, it's whatever. In terms of kissing, though, you know, you probably got to,
that's the thing that you do to ease into it, you know, because like, you can't, you really,
you really cannot just come up to a guy and say, I want to fuck, because every guy will assume that
you have an ulterior motive, but that you got something going on with you, like you're a weirdo,
you got STDs, something's fucked up with you, you got to, you got to pretend like you like are
into it for some bigger reason, which is true. Hey, I'm actually a guy, I'm in a woman's body
this is for science, we have to do this right now, and he'll be like, my God, if it's for science,
he'll be into it, he'll be into it. This will be who the human race, we have to do this.
That's a better case than just saying I just want to fuck, because I, I don't know, I don't know.
Guys listening at home, if you ever wake up as a woman and you want to fuck, go to Nate and just
say it's for science and you'll be down. Yeah, say it's for Starfleet. I would definitely do that.
I would without a doubt do it. If I knew that shit was true, of course, of course. Here's my
problem with kissing a guy. If you close your eyes, you could probably pretend it's a girl,
but if they got any facial hair, I don't want that itchy shit rubbing up against me while
we're kissing, no way. You know, ooh, that's a tough one. There's no way, I couldn't be horny,
my pussy would be as dry as the Sahara Desert. Okay, well, we gotta address this fact. We gotta
address this fact, like have we become attracted to men through the gender swap? Yeah, are we now?
No, I'm still me, I have my brain, I just have a girl's body. Okay, okay, all right. Yeah, I was
gonna ask, like, how much of my brain has become girl? Like, no, I thought about this a lot.
Would boys still be gross to me? I assume they would. Well, okay, you know what, this is gonna
make me sound 100% gay, but I have, I've always had a sincere appreciation for the male form.
And I do think that if I was all of a sudden a girl, I could probably get myself into the head
space where if I find just like some really attractive guy, I would just enjoy being around
him. Oh god, I'm fucking gay. I'm literally gay. I'm literally gay now.
I mean, don't you guys have a list of male celebrities who you would fuck right now as a guy?
I do. If Jake Gyllenhaal came knocking on my door, I'd be gay with him for a night, fuck it.
Yes, my list is Paul F. Tompkins and nobody else.
You love those mustaches.
Mine's mostly anime characters. I'd fuck Rance, I'd definitely fuck Rance. He wouldn't want to
fuck me, but I'd fuck him if you wanted to. You know, I think if I were a girl, if I were in it,
like I had a girl by it for a day, what I would do, you know, I would wait until like five minutes
to midnight and then I would challenge Rhonda Rousey to a fight. And like she'd be beating me up
because I'm a girl, like she'd think she had it in the bag, but then midnight strikes, I turned
back into a strong boy and I'm like, no, I've got you where I want you. To coob. Bam, bam, bam, bam.
And then I'm punching her. I'm throwing her like over the cage wall. I'm so strong now. My man strength
is out of control. And I just get the trophies. I get the trophies and the gold, the belts. I get
all the MMA awards ever. Joe Rogan comes out and personally congratulates me. He puts his arm around
me like, how'd you do it? And then in the second round, you turn into a guy and you're really beat
up that bag, Rhonda Rousey. And I'm like, that's right. That's right, Rogan. I did it. Praise me.
Bow. You've got to get a millennium puzzle and pretend that you're Yugi transforming
Yugi halfway through. Oh, that's good. Oh, man, that's good. That's good. I've always had a fear,
though, about this, that what if you're, you know, you just get lost track. You're just orgasming
over and over. You're getting fucked by, you know, every Tom Dick and Harry up the block. My biggest
fear. Well, it's, it's that you're, you transform back at midnight, right? But what if some dude is,
you know, balls deep at that moment and you transform and now you got, now you got a dick
permanently fused up inside your body, which is definitely gay. You'd be like attached at the
dick like Siamese bros. Exactly. Yeah. Isn't that the plot of the movie stuck on you?
I hope so. Is that true? How true is that? Go watch that movie. Yeah, with Matt Damon and Drillbit
Taylor. Was that Matt Damon in that movie? I don't know. The special guest appearance,
special guest appearance by Ron's arousy as the bitch who gets beat the fuck up by the two,
by the two conjoined at the dick man. She thought she was fighting a woman, but midnight struck and
the woman turned into two conjoined at the dick men, one played by Matt Damon and the other played
by the character Drillbit Taylor, not Owen Wilson. Oh shit, it was Matt Damon. What the fuck? Wow.
I don't remember that being Matt Damon. That's crazy. You have to rewatch that shit. It actually
has positive score on Rotten Tomatoes. What the hell? Does it really? Yeah, 61%. The other guy was
Greg Kenyer. I don't know who that is. I wonder what Bubble Boy has in Rotten Tomatoes. I'm going
to look that up. Yeah, let us know. Who could forget Bubble Boy? Fun fact, Bubble Boy is Zach
Galifianakis' first movie. He plays the bus ticket guy. That's fascinating. You know what I always
loved in the movie Juno? What's his name? Michael Sarah? Not Michael Sarah. Neither of them. It's
a bit character from the very beginning. You know the guy who played the nerd? Fuck, I can't
remember his name from the office. The American office. You know what I'm talking about? Ryan?
Not Ryan. Who's the fucking weirdo creep? Dwight, of course. Dwight. The actor who plays Dwight
is in the very beginning of that and as Juno is getting her pregnancy results, she's just
standing at the counter. I guess she just pissed on in the bathroom and is looking at it and he
just says, your ego is prego. Okay. It was the grayest line of all time. That's pretty funny.
Pretty good, dude. Pretty good. Oh my god. Would you get pregnant as the girl? That's the fear
because I want to slud it up for that day but then like am I pregnant as a man the next day?
Are my eggs finalized? Oh my god. What happens? I always have that fear of spiders crawling in my
ear at night and then laying eggs and like feeling my brain with eggs and I am the spider boy under
their control forever. Same situation, you know? Wait a minute. Terrified. Terrifying. I think what
would happen is if you got impregnated as a woman and then turned back into a boy, I mean you would
now have the fertilized egg inside you but it would be like in your dick or ball sack region.
Which means that you would be shooting out the fertilized egg. You could theoretically
fuck a hole in the ground and grow children from soil.
I was hoping for a more, what's that Arnold Schwarzenegger movie where he gets pregnant?
Daddy Daycare? No, that's not the one.
Junior. I think it's called Junior. I believe it's called Terminator 2.
In case you were wondering, Bubble Boy has a score of 30% on Rotten Tomatoes.
Sorry Jake Gyllenhaal.
Now 30% doesn't mean that it's only 30% good. 30% means that 30% of people gave it like 10 out of
10, 100%. Oh really? He ends the movie by falling down Niagara Falls in a bubble. How can you not like
it? I'm definitely all 30% of those. When I was a kid, I had three VHSs that mean
my brother watched over and over again. We had Bubble Boy, we had Max Keebles, Big Move,
and we had Rat Race. Two of the three we should not have been watching. Rat Race is a masterpiece.
Hell yeah. We could do a whole episode on Rat Race. Any movie that ends with an actual smash
mouth concert is a certified fucking masterpiece. Fuck yeah. Get fucked John Cleese. There you go.
Is it said that my only exposure for the majority of my life to John Cleese was fucking Rat Race
and not like Monty Python or anything? Is that true? Oh no, that's sad. I didn't know he was in
anything else. I thought he was just the guy from Rat Race. That is sad. Fucking good Monty
Python. Good, good movie. Good Holy Grail. Upvoted. Top, top, top pick on Reddit. Shut the fuck up.
I don't know what I'm doing. Okay, here we go. I feel like we've exhausted this. Are we done?
We got any closing points to make about this whole gender swapping thing.
So I guess if you wake up as a girl and you want to fuck, go fuck Nate and also carry a gun and
don't try to fight Ronda Rousey, I think that's what we learned today. Which you can do immediately
when you change back. Anyone can beat Ronda Rousey. Any woman who wakes up tomorrow as a man,
the first thing you'd better do for science is go fight Ronda Rousey.
Shit, you know, I felt like we didn't really talk enough. Maybe we should right now,
just about the whole thing about being a woman turning into a guy and what you can expect.
What can your average woman expect when she wakes up as a guy the next day? You know,
because we're gender inclusive here. I think get ready for all the attention,
all that people giving a shit about you, gone. It's gone. Don't expect any person to ever do
anything for you ever again. Nobody gives a fuck about that. Do not try online dating. You're not
going to get any results at all. That's correct. That's correct. Zero messages. In fact, don't
leave the house because the world is a nightmare now. Yeah, every woman becomes a man for one day
and like halfway through it, she's already like on all the MRA boards and all the like men going
their own way boards. She's done. She can't take it anymore. She hasn't at the years of training
that we have to get to this point alive. Be excited women. When you go to work as a man,
you'll get an automatic 30% raise. I was going to say that. God damn it. Yep. Yeah. 23 cents on the
dollar. Bam in your pocket. Day one. They're like, Oh my God, we've made a huge mistake. We didn't
realize you were a man all along. Didn't realize you had a dick. Here's the extra cash. That's how
it works. It's just that easy. That's why I really feel for the transitioning community from male
to female. It's tough enough. It's tough enough. Just going through the process of all that,
but then when they just walk into work one day and they're like, my pay, oh no, 277 cents on the
dollar. It sucks. Sorry, dude, that's corporate policy. What can we do? That's just how it works.
That's just how it works. Obama wanted it. Here's some benefits. Going P, it's going to be kind of
fun now. You don't have to get your butt on that dirty toilet seat. Sometimes in a restaurant
or a bar, they'll put a little fly sticker in the urinal, so you can try to aim at that. That's
kind of fun. What else we got? Sometimes you get to go pee. It's easier now. Yeah. You get to go
pee in a trough sometimes with all your buddies. Put your arms around each other and sing songs
while you do it and sway back and forth. That's fun. I don't know if that's a positive. You get
to hold each other's dicks. That's what we do at the old trough.
If you jerk off in the shower, you can see how far you can shoot your common market with a sharpie
and see if you can beat your last record. The projectile come thing, yeah. That's a big one.
That's a big one. What else we got? What other benefits are there to being a man in American
society today other than having a dick? This is a big one. This is a big one. You can be fat
and Nate won't hate you intensely immediately. That's a good one. That's a good one. That's
pretty good. Yeah, no joke though. Fat women, they have way worse than fat men and that is
kind of shitty. Yeah, for sure. On the one hand, that's kind of true, but women, okay, what does
it matter if you're an unattractive woman? Well, okay, I mean it does to some degree because it's
all about whatever, being attractive or whatever. You want to fuck somebody, right? You want to
catch yourself a high quality man, but there are tons of men who will still fuck you even if you're
fat, but if you're a fat guy, I would say that it's harder. Well, I would say that it's harder.
There's tons of fat guys who have who have hot female wives. There's Peter Griffin,
there's Homer Simpson, you know, there's a King of Queens. Yeah, don't forget King of Queens.
The greatest man who ever lived. Kevin James, I don't know what it is in the show. You know what
it really is, it's that women are, because men are visual creatures, like our appreciation of
women has more to do with their physicality than a woman's attraction to a man, which is more
about personality and confidence and shit. Yeah, you're all shallow. Yeah, you know, I guess in
that way, yeah, you can be, if you're a woman, you can be fat now and it won't be as big a deal.
That's true, that's true. What the fuck else you got? Oh, you will be expected, here's a
negative, you will be expected to carry shit for people who are smaller than you or all women,
you'll be expected to carry their shit now or hold doors. I mean, that's less prevalent these
days. Oh my god, you will now have to deal with the nightmare of feminism in general, hating you,
hating you in every way, so that sucks. You can be elected president no matter what you say
over a woman. You can grab pussy freely now, you know, it's the door, carte blanche for grabbing
pussy as we've learned. I think that's about it. I can't think of any other benefits of being a man.
Yeah, me neither, dude. Oh, oh, oh, you can have sex without personally getting pregnant,
so that's that's a nice one. You don't have to worry about that at all anymore. You might still
get STDs, but you will not be the one who gets knocked up for months or have to deal with the
whole work. You will be the one who knocks. Yes. And yeah, I think that's it. I think that's it.
Oh, wait, I forgot the most important one. You can now become a Catholic priest. That's
checkbox. Oh, you can now be in God's in God's corner. That's a good shot's fired.
Nate versus the Catholic Church. Look out. Not a fan. Not a fan. Oh, wait. Oh, you can now move
to Saudi Arabia and drive. You can now drive in Saudi Arabia. I forgot about that. You can now
move to Saudi Arabia and not wear a fucking scarf on your head. Well, I mean, that's a
I mean, we're we're down with the hijab now. That's a feminist icon thing now. So it is.
Yeah. Why? Why the fuck? It's very confusing. I don't know. All right. I think that's it.
YouTube is lucky that they banned me from uploading on my main account for two weeks,
because I got this Mumkey's Declassified Sharia Law Survival Guide video and I'm going to take
the Internet by storm. Here. Here's hoping for 10 billion views and and and a glorious new Caliphate
in the West. All right. So there you go. All right. Let's go to the questions already. Let's
let me only do the search thing. Okay. Hashtag as PCP. By the way, you guys can feel free to do
this as well if you want. I know Mumkey does sometimes. Yeah, you tagged me in the tweet.
So now I'm getting all these notifications. So thanks for that. You're anytime, dude.
Okay. Here's a question from Shade. I don't know if you guys have ever heard of this guy.
No. A little known guy. He wants to know, why does Jess hate spiders so much?
Oh, what am I tweeting about this this morning or something? That's probably why he's asking.
Oh, these people are so fucking unoriginal and reactionary, you know, just because that was Shade.
Who fucks Shade? That's didgy's little brother. That's MC Shadu. Yeah, that's MC Shadu. This
must be a different shade. Oh, how many shades are there? I don't know. 50 shades of gray,
you could say. I hate spiders because spiders are fucking ugly. They're monstrous. They're
hideous. They're gay. They're cretins. They're scum. They have no fucking backbones literally
and figuratively. They're weak. And, you know, people say they're not dangerous,
but that doesn't mean they're not evil. If you take the smallest, most harmless spider,
if they were bigger, if they were big enough to eat you, it would. So, you know, spiders are evil
and they're ugly. They've got too many eyes and too many legs. They've got tiny little hairs,
and they crawl on you. They get on you. They get in your hair. They spin webs. The webs are gross.
Do I really even need to justify this? Fuck spiders. You know what? Even Ronda Rousey could
beat a spider. That's how much I don't respect spiders. People always make the case that like,
yeah, but spiders eat other bugs. They eat mosquitoes and they eat flies and they eat other
shit. I'll just kill them myself. I'll just kill them myself. Yeah, well, what kind of defense is
that? They're worse than the things they eat. I would rather have a mosquito on me than a spider.
You know what? That's actually a tough one because I hate mosquitoes so much. I hate them
more than spiders for sure. I want every mosquito in the fucking world destroyed. They are,
they are going to kill us one day. Mosquitoes are going to be the downfall of humanity because
they're going to suck blood out of some fucking super AIDS boys. They're going to transport it all
over the fucking world. I don't care if they revive the dinosaurs in Jurassic Park. I don't care.
That's not good enough. That's the only thing that a mosquito has ever done that was even a slight
positive. They're evil. I fucking hate mosquitoes. So I'm on Team Spider, I guess. I respect mosquitoes
a little bit more because when a mosquito lands on you, like, yeah, it's annoying, but you only
have to feel it landing on you. When a spider lands on you, you have to feel every leg crawling up
you slowly. Like, it's just, it's just touching you a thousand times as opposed to a mosquito,
which touches you once. I mean, that's true. I'll say touching a spider web is worse than
touching any of these things. I'd rather fucking die than walk through the forest and get a big
spider web in my face. And if there's bugs in there, then you're even more fucked. Well, the,
the only reason that I get freaked out by that because of the, is because of the presence of
the bugs in the spider web. But I guess that's kind of your point. So yeah, yeah, that's pretty
shit. Like, I freak out because I'm like, assume there's a spider on me now. So really, the problem
is the spider. Spider web is cool. I just think the spider, the web itself feels all silky and
gross and sticky on your face. And I just, I just wanted to walk through the woods and,
and peek on this bath house over there. And now I got to worry about this shit. And you know,
all the spider fags are always like, oh, spider silk is a thousand times stronger than steel.
But how come I destroy it effortlessly with every fucking, checkmate, checkmate,
mother fuckers. Fuck, fuck, fuck all, fuck all spiders, fuck that slut Charlotte.
Fuck that fucking, fuck that French bitch in James and the Giant Peach. I don't even care.
I would. I don't care how sexy her face is. The rest of her is an abomination.
Yo, you know who's hot rock, rock and arrow from Monster Musume? She's the best girl. She's
fucking, I would sex. The only good spider is spider man. And the good part of him ain't the
spider part. It's the man part. It's the man. The muscles and the dong.
Spider dong. No, it's. All right, Justin, I got another question for you. I'm glad you two are
here because you tour the, the PCP experts on this subject. Mark Morella wants to know,
what is the bare minimum age to count as sex with the young? The minimum age. It's not,
it's not a, it's not an age. There is no minimum. It's a state of mind.
That's true. Like when you got, when you got your choice as, you know, 45 year old milk,
if you got her dressed up in her baby bib and her diaper, that my friend is some,
is some old school sex with the young right there. That is the official,
fucking the, the non-incriminating stance. It's all in the mind. Just like, just like,
just like my hero. Just like my older person who is retarded. Does that count?
Yeah, that'll count. You know, if they act like a baby, if they look like a baby and they act
like a baby and they smell like a baby, then it's sex with the young. Just like my hero,
chop, chop, master onion said. Yeah. Sex with the young. It's all in the mind.
What a hero. My hero. I've got a question here from a Theo at pterodactyl says,
should entertainers bring their girlfriends along for the ride? No. What are you guys?
Absolutely not. And that might seem hypocritical coming from me, but here's the thing. I gave her
her own channel. Now I only put her on my channel when I need a woman and she's like the closest
one near me. I'm not bringing her along for any ride. I'm giving her her own platform on
Sheepover. Go check it out. I'm going to post a link down in the comments.
You ain't going to give your girlfriend a ride. I'll give her a ride. You know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying? My dude. Now, yeah, I pretty much think that's totally appropriate.
Yeah. If you're, if you're already doing something and you're just trying to like,
like the whole Yoko Ono situation is like the classic one. You don't just insert your bitch
into like the thing that's already going on. If you want to make something new,
like what Ben's doing with his new channel, with his girlfriend, that's a okay. That's perfect.
That's exactly the right thing to do. If you, if you got two creative people and they want to be
doing stuff, just, yeah, just don't fuck up the shit that's already there. I will only time
defend my use of girls and my videos thusly. Sometimes I need to go outside and I need a
cameraman. I need someone to film me. That's the first reason. And the second thing is that when
I do like stuff like my panel cast, you know, uh, the, the, my girl is like, she knows about
comics. So I at least keep her where she belongs on a thing that is in her field.
You know, I, I assumed that she was not going to be any kind of expert when you first started
the panel cast and said she was going to be on. I was like, Oh boy, here we go. But then she was
like more knowledgeable than you in some ways. And uh, that was, yeah, she's a solid asset.
She's reasonably vital to that endeavor. And I was just going to clarify. The only time you're
going to see a girlfriend on my main monkey channel is when I need a woman to be used as a prop.
That's all she is to me is a fucking prop. Excellent. Excellent. And you know,
uh, what Jesse was saying, uh, yeah, like, uh, I hate that I have to make all my shit by myself
like, cause I always want to do live action stuff and it's really fucking annoying and I've
adapted. So it's not a big deal now, but like, uh, God, I would fucking love to do more live
action shit. Like you, like you're fucking Zelda video, Jesse, which I assumed you filled with,
with flusie all over the place. It was great. It was, uh, it was awesome. If I had a, if I had a
person around to do that with, I totally would. God damn our, our let's plays just a whole lot
easier to make when you've got someone to bounce off of and converse it with. You know what? In fact,
I take back my whole stands. You should always have a second person. Put all your girlfriends,
all your boyfriends, all your friends in there, put your whole family in your videos, make a whole,
a whole production out of it. That's how you get the real good content. That's how you get the
YouTube success and the YouTube bucks. You got to have a bunch of people working for you,
for nothing, for peanuts. Yeah, you trip them into it with relationships. That's what you,
that's what relationships for. You seduce someone into helping you work. There you go.
The main issue people have is when, like with the Beatles, you get your girlfriend in there and
then like Nate was saying, they completely change the content. Like for example with,
with AVGN, he got his, his wife involved as a producer on the movie. And then the movie ends
with like the other guy getting the girl for no reason. Yeah. It should have been fucking James,
right? Why the fuck didn't he fuck that bitch? The girl didn't even talk to the black guy,
the whole movie, and then they're kissing at the end. Well, okay. The movie should not have had the
girl or the black guy at all. They were totally worthless characters. That's a given.
I did not see it, but I mean, you know, for all we know, I mean, I don't know shit about these guys
or about the production of the movie, but like from what I've heard, it sounds like, like, like
Bumpy was saying, the, the wifey here, she had some input. She had some like, she made some changes
along the way and who the fuck knows exactly how drastic those were, what they were at some point.
Yeah, you really, if you're a creator, do not let, but it's kind of inevitable because like,
whatever people you hang around are going to change the way you think. Like your, your friends,
to some degree, define how you think and like, what do you think is acceptable. That's why we're
all so angry all the time. That's right. We always talk to PCP guys all day. So if, like, if you're
just like some dude from the Midwest or whatever, and you move to California, like you're gonna adopt
that mindset over some, it's gonna happen. Like, like Tim Heidecker, I think is kind of an example
of that. He's just getting more and more, you know, he moved to Hollywood and he's just getting more
and more, you know, liberal. And yeah, I don't, I don't really begrudge him. I disagree with him
on some of his points, but you know, that's fine. But you can see his mind changing. You can see
those changes happening. And like the thing with Yoko was like, she actually wasn't really,
as far as I know, I'm no expert on this, but she wasn't like forced into like the Beatles or anything.
It's not like Lenin was trying to bring her in to like change the Beatles. But what she definitely
did was change John himself. And so like he, and like, it's, it's hard to say like, what are you
gonna do? Like tell your friends, like break up with his girlfriend? She changed him from a serial
wife-beater into a guy who respected his spouse. What a fucking bitch. How could she do that? That
was a big problem. If he ruins the music, then it's a terrible thing on the face of mankind.
Yeah, yeah, can't disagree with that. But you know, Yoko Ono makes some good stuff, dude.
I loved her, her latest album, which I believe was called like,
do you ever listen to her perform live? She's a fucking nightmare. But anyway,
you know, it really grinds my gears. You know, when it's just really gratuitous and transparent,
how like guys will be like, oh, I'm, this is my show, and here's my girlfriend now. And it's like,
it's almost like they're using her as like, like a sports car or a trophy to like show off.
Dude, not to- I can have sex with girls. I've got a hot girl.
You know, to some degree, there's always going to be a little bit of bullshit. Like,
if you get a girlfriend and for whatever reason, you're talking about something
where it's relevant. And even when you do that little mention, because it's pertinent to what
you're talking about, there's going to be some people who are like, oh, here we go. We're shoving
in the whole girlfriend thing. But to some degree, it's unavoidable. That's the takeaway. Just keep
it relevant. Don't be gratuitous and transparent and gay with it. Don't be gay in general. If you've
got, you know, nobody wants to be that couple. Just don't do it. You know, you know what this
reminds me of? Did you guys ever see probably not fucking Jeff's videos where he started having
his girlfriend wear his merch and shit? I'm just saying. Yeah, he was playing it off as a joke,
but still. I've never watched a Jeff video ever. And I think I can- You gotta take the monkey
approach. Only put your girlfriend in the video if the whole joke is that you're abusing her and
that she's too stupid to think of groceries. That really is like the funny way to go. Like,
nobody is- if you're a comedy boy, nobody's laughing if you're showing off your girlfriend,
just like, just showing her off. Like, that's not funny. And people would be like,
what the fuck? You're wasting my time bragging about the shit. So yeah, you got to make it funny
like Mumki did, which was great. The wife abuse thing was wonderful. Okay, here's another question
at GregBerryAnt asks, how do you keep yourselves motivated enough to work for more than a few
hours without taking a break? I constantly get distracted. And I have a- This is a question that-
So it's really funny to me, this question. Like, motivation questions. When I was young,
I had such a hard time focusing. And I was never able to concentrate very long on anything. And
even when I was in college, and I was starting to do things that I sort of liked, which was game
design, even then I found it agonizing to force myself to like, oh fuck, okay, I'll try to do
a puzzle design today or whatever, or program this thing. So things were getting a little better.
But what I found is, like, I didn't level up or- or increase my skill at this at all. The only
thing I ever did to get better at this was just find things that I inherently liked doing. It was-
I basically cheated the system. I just kept looking around until I just found out like, you know what?
I fucking love making videos. And like, during the TBAP days, when me and Ben would just like,
bust one out every week, and they were pretty fucking great. Like, it was so easy to just do
that because I really wanted to do it. So unfortunately, I don't have any practical advice
for this, but I would say just find something that you actually like doing. And maybe it's just a
like a variation on what you're trying to do now. That's all I got. Maybe you guys have some more
useful answers to this. How do you stay motivated? It was basically like, how do you stay motivated
without fucking getting distracted or taking a break? Oh shit, I'm the wrong fucking guy to
answer that one. I think what helps me is that I am a bit of a fame whore. And the whole time
I'm thinking, oh man, if I put this up, it's gonna get seen by at least 5,000 people, baby,
gotta get this sucker out. So if you're like an up and comer and you have no audience, I can imagine
it's very hard to be motivated to work because you feel like you're doing all this work for
literally nobody because nobody's watching. So if that's this guy's case, which I don't know who
he is, if that's your case, I can't help you. I have no idea what you can do. Well, you know,
I think it makes it keep your eye on the prize is what you're saying, right? You just just imagine
even if you're not like immediately getting, I guess what you're talking about like instant
gratification, right? You put it up and bam, 5,000 people see it feels good. You get those responses,
get those upvotes. It's nice. Like get those down votes if you're doing a podcast with Psy,
which is better than an upvote because that means it's not that they're supporting me with a little
click is that they're going against Psy with a click, which feels much better. You know what I
would say? I would just say like, you just got to value what you're doing. Like when I started
like my current channel best guy ever, like the the current login videos like literally six months
each to make them or no, the first one was three months, second one was six months and like at the
time at the time they got like way fewer views than they deserve. And now that I'm like growing a
little bit, they're starting to get more views. They're like basically 100,000 views, which is
like a healthy amount of views for like a lifetime. So I'm more happy with that. But at the time, like
what kept me going at the time was just how much I needed to complete this project. The project
itself is what made me want to keep going. And I felt there was an inherent value, a need that was
served by me creating this thing. And I feel like it did that. And I feel like that's why people like
it. So like at later on, you can just do it for the for the views and for the clicks. But at the
very beginning, at least you have to have some sort of artistic vision, which which I would recommend
going for something like that. I don't know, that's work for me. But I'm sorry, totally cut Jesse off.
I never really feel like unmotivated. I think in terms of motivation, I'm always like, yeah,
I'm going to do what I want to do. Because that's I'm cool. And that's what I do. But I definitely
do get distracted a lot. I always am a working on like a like a dozen things at once. I've always
got a bunch of Vegas windows open. And there's always like, like a like a new episode of a show
that I want to watch or like a podcast. And then you once you start watching something,
you fall into a hole and you start watching, you know, you just fall into like a YouTube hole,
or like you lay down on the couch once, once you're on the couch, it's fucking over. The day is
over. That's a trap. So um, you know, it's hard to stay focused sometimes. So a couple of months
ago, I tried Adderall for the first time. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. That worked out. Yeah. Like,
and I was sold at like, Oh, this is a, this is a, is a, is a drug. It's not for you. It's
illegal that I'm selling you this. It's, you know, you should be taking this, but it will make you
like super focused and super, you know, into your work. And I'm like, okay, I'll take it. And I took
one. And like, it definitely worked. But like the thing is, it didn't feel like I've achieved
like a, a different state. It felt like maybe I'm supposed to be on Adderall. Maybe this is how
I'm supposed to be working. So that's my advice is just take Adderall. Take Adderall. Yeah.
You know, I mean, Nate, you're laughing, but I, I'd back up that recommendation. I took
Adderall once in high school and I was in pre-calc and I couldn't figure out this
fucking pre-calc shit. I took one Adderall and I taught myself that, that whole chapter in less
than 20 minutes. Is that true? Is that actually true? I could, I could feel like my brain was a
fucking locomotive. I could feel the engine of the train revving in my brain. I could physically feel
it. And it felt great. I laughed just cause it's funny. But no, I'm actually, I'm totally on board
for any of these kind of like, like treating the human body as like an engineering problem to be
solved with like fixes or drugs or like, but yeah, you start like, you start speed forcing and burst
slinking. You can like, you can do anything when you're on Adderall. It's a miracle, Drake. You
know, we've done, we've done so many episodes of this show, like giving advice to up and coming,
like aspiring creators who look up to us, but all our advice was wrong. The only advice that
matters, if you take anything from this podcast, just take Adderall. Yeah. The only reason I don't
wholeheartedly agree is because, because I'm, I'm, I'm engineering focused. If the Adderall
perhaps introduces other issues, for example, just one that's possible is if taking Adderall
gives you this high of ability to create stuff, that there will follow, of course, a subsequent
low where you're off of it. And will that make you like unable to function without it at that
point? Or like, yeah, I know I'm not being fun. I'm being serious right now, but like, um, yeah,
you know, I didn't take it enough to get addicted. Yeah, luckily, I'm so, if it's possible to just
be on, if it's possible to just take Adderall, I can only afford like two pills a month. So,
well, that's good. If it's possible to like, for everyone to be on Adderall all the time, and
literally all it does is make everyone better at everything, then I would be 100% on board. But
yeah, I just got to watch out for those consequences. That's all. Yeah. That's all. Well, I mean,
like, I, every time I write a script or record a let's play, I'm drinking. Am I going to be dependent
on drinking? Probably. But do I care? No. Well, I mean, if you don't care, that's fine.
I'll just keep drinking. I mean, rolling rock, I got it because I was like, oh, AVGN, he's pretty
funny. Maybe this is magic funny juice. And it actually takes, it tastes exactly like water,
but has all the benefits of alcohol. So I really, I endorse rolling rock. If you can't afford Adderall,
go get some rolling rock. It's great. And if you can afford them both, then yes, definitely mix them,
mix as much as you can. Just grab everything from daddy's medicine cabinet, throw it all in a big
tincture and mix it up. Just mix depressants and narcotics together all the fucking day.
Don't do that. Don't die. If you want to die, at least pledge to our patreons before you do.
That's smart. That's smart. Just be responsible with your money. Invest in your future.
All right. So there you go. That's that. Is there any other decent questions here? Let me see.
Oh my God. Here's one. Okay. This is actually very personal to me.
At Mozilla Fendicand. Hey, dude, what's going on? I asked, so what are good ingredients to put in
oatmeal? I'm trying to become more of a healthy boy. Dude, I eat oatmeal every breakfast of my
fucking life. I am a fucking oatmeal expert. And I know exactly what you need to put in your oatmeal
to make it delicious. Okay. Here's what I'm doing right now. I'm so, I'm so happy. I'm so excited.
He asked this question. Yes. I'm all about oatmeal. Okay. You get yourself a big bowl of you get,
you get the big thing from, from Quaker oats, the old fashioned oats. You pour a fucking cup
into a bowl. And here's what you do. You put frozen strawberries from the grocery store.
You just pour a whole, like a fucking, fuckload of those in there. You cover that thing. You want,
you want to have a lot because it's going to be, the taste is dependent on those. You just cover
that thing with water. You fucking, you pour the strawberries, pour water. It doesn't matter how
much. Just put a bunch, experiment until you get the right amount. Maybe you do a cup or whatever.
The strawberries have water in them already. And then you just microwave that. You do that for two
minutes. You stir it up. You put it back in and do another two minutes. And then bam, you got perfect
oatmeal. Now, if you are a weak boy, what you can do is you can just put some sugar in. I would
recommend like one tablespoon of sugar. That might be a little bit too much, but something like that.
And then you just mix it up and bam, that's immediately delicious and perfect. If you want to
be an even more of a madman, what you can do is you can put brown sugar in and butter. You could
just put brown sugar and butter. If you don't care about like, it's going to be more fatty this way,
more, more calories and shit. Brown sugar, butter, do all the same steps. Just don't put in the
strawberries. Or you can put the strawberries in. I guess that'd be fine too. Bam. There you go.
That's perfect. That's all you need to know, folks. That's the best way to eat oatmeal. I do it every
single day in my goddamn life, the strawberry one. And there you go. There's your solution. There you
go. All right, we're done. Do you guys have any oatmeal suggestions? No, I'm the kind of the little
dinosaur eggs in it. Yeah, that's really, fuck what I said. Just get the dinosaur eggs.
Okay, we're done. No more good questions. Thanks for the questions. Yeah, everyone's
going to piss out all this rolling rock I've been drinking the whole time. Wait, what is this?
No, this is a shitty question. Okay, I'm sorry. I'm going to ask this last question. At
Artmark88 asks, about the Wonder Woman film, do you think the area's reveal should have been
an end credit scene? No, it shouldn't have been in it at all. Yeah, it was terrible. Yeah,
it, yeah, I didn't, yeah. We already talked about this in the last episode, didn't we? Did we?
Did we talk about this? Fuck it? I don't, I don't know. Okay, fuck that. I don't know why I felt
like answering that. All right, forget it. Abort, abort question. Mark, you're dead to me. Okay,
here we go. We're all done. Thanks for listening, everybody. Make sure you send us more questions
or, you know, follow or fucking do the thing at TPGrassNators on Twitter and use hashtag
AskPCP to get your questions answered here and subscribe to the YouTube channel, of course,
which you're probably already watching, and pledge to our Patreon, patreon.com slash the
procrastinators to get all the fucking bonus episodes. I think there's three now. You get into
the secret Patreon Discord where like everybody, all the PCP guys are in there and like even just
today, Jess was offering to beat up people's dads. If you want your dad beat up possibly from
Discord, throwing a buck or two. Those people, they contributed to the podcast. And if your dad
is Ronda Rousey, you get into the Discord free because I really, I really want to crack at that
dad. If your dad is Ronda Rousey. So if Ronda Rousey wants to be in the Discord, she's in for
free. All right, Ronda, you're in, buddy. Okay, thanks for listening, everybody. We'll see you next
time. Bye.
Bye.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh.
I'm supposed to be working right now. I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working. I'm doing nothing. My dick, I'm jerking. Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole. I am a stupid. I've got a deadline. Don't want to do it.