Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemail for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I'm back. I'm not dead. Tom's back. Tom's back. Tom will never die.
Special guest, Tom Oliver.
It was true what they said. They said you wouldn't die and you didn't. I'm sorry if I got really loud right there. I'm fucking with my audacity volume.
I'm not that affects Discord, so I probably can't hear that at all.
Yeah, you wouldn't hear that, but the audience will have to deal with it.
Well, Eleazar, fix that.
Nah, Eleazar, let them cope. Let them cope and sieve.
So let's wake up those headphone users. Let's give them something to think about.
That I was momentarily loud. Yes. Long time no see. You haven't been on one month. It's got to be like a month now, right?
At least. It's been ridiculous.
What have you possibly been doing that could be more important than our business here?
On The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
Working on secret projects.
Oh god, not you too.
Dude, we all have secret projects. I saw your secret projects. It's pretty cool.
It's pretty cool. Thank you. It's not secret anymore, I guess.
It's a project. It's just a project now.
Now it's just a project. Now it's just a project.
The mystique is gone, but the glory remains.
Wait, I want to...
Last week, I had five people have beaten the demo.
It was a crack, munchy, shinny, Sean, and Tio.
And one more shining god joined the ranks for a total of six.
Earning the name. Six ascended beings.
And his name was Roboblo. Roboblo has ascended.
Six people. Notable failures to complete the game include Gib and Take, the best guy ever.
And the other, and you know, they're in good company though.
The other seven plus billion human beings on the planet.
Everybody else on the planet, you know?
All embarrassments. All embarrassments.
They're just not willing to put the work in.
It's a test of patience and they fail.
Like any good RPG, it's all about the grind.
And the first step on the grind is to go to patreon.com.
Do you have the will? Do you have the sheer resolve to click?
To type your mom the funny little numbers on the back of your mom's.
It demands a lot of you.
It really is the dark souls of role playing games.
Oh, that's the first hurdle you got to get over.
Only then can the challenge truly begin.
I mean, that sounds ridiculous.
But when you think about it, every video game, the first step is to pay for it.
So really, you're asking nothing more than any other video game developer would.
I guess so. I mean, I mean, I only play free games a lot of the time.
Or I guess that's not true anymore. I guess that's not true anymore.
You've been playing Noida for like,
About 600 hours.
I've clocked about 600 hours in Noida now.
That's insane.
It's fucked up. It's horrible.
I had a run. I had the run the other day.
I finally got to a state where I was immune to everything I needed to be immune to.
And I got a glass cannon, which, among other things, just makes everything you do do way more damage.
And all explosions have like five times their radius.
And then I got nukes.
And I had fire immunity and explosion immunity.
So I was immune to my own nukes.
And my nukes were five times as big.
So I could literally like, I could literally just bomb an entire biome out of existence with a single nuke.
I crashed the game because I nuked the vault so hard that all the dead enemies that died to a single nuke blast just rained gold down on me.
And there was so much gold raining down on me that it crashed the game.
Is that what it feels like to have bought Dogecoin at a fraction of a penny?
Not anymore.
And when it puked 71 cents a few days ago.
A few days ago, not anymore.
Everyone was waiting for Elon to fucking bring the second coming of Doge, but it tanked like 40%.
Elon was too cringe.
Elon was too cringe on SNL and it tanked Dogecoin.
I mean, did anybody expect, I mean, no one expected it to be cool, did they?
No, but honestly.
The man's many things, but cool is not one of them.
Honestly, I was like thinking, I was like, Elon's going on SNL tonight.
There will never be a more like mainstream moment for Dogecoin to be mentioned.
I thought to myself, I probably should just buy Dogecoin because he's going to mention Dogecoin on SNL and Lyon go up.
Lyon will go up.
I'm shooting myself in the foot by not buying Dogecoin, but I didn't do it.
And I was totally wrong.
Lyon went down.
I was expecting it to go up too.
You would think so because every time he mentions it, it goes up.
Well, I guess when you put on a Wario suit, you kind of just lose all that goodwill.
I don't understand.
The pattern was so clear.
I don't get it.
It's recovered a little bit, I think.
And then I saw people angry on Twitter because just like with GME, not Coinbase,
Robinhood was not letting them cash their Dogecoin out as it was falling.
They were like, what the fuck? Why can't I cash my Dogecoin out?
That's why it wasn't updating because I was looking at it last night.
That was happening.
There were just no numbers.
I was like, oh, is my internet fucked up or something?
No, I guess Robinhood once again decided to be scum.
I mean, what would we expect at this point?
They've shown their hand.
They really have.
The fact that I still use that service is a blight upon my name.
I signed up for an account when the shit was going down, but I never ended up using it for anything.
Good.
I did an account with an app called KuCoin that Brian from Clear Value Tax recommended.
And I fucked around with it a little bit.
I put in like $100 to just kind of fuck around with some of the shit in there
because they got weird things in that app.
You can sort of design parameters for a bot that will autotrade for you.
What's the other one?
You can put your money up for micro loans that other people will borrow from you
and then repay with interest.
Is this the thing you were talking about before,
where you're running it to see how long it would autotrade and min-max your gains?
Yeah, I mentioned it a while ago.
Because I did that a while ago.
And I mean, Brian from Clear Value Tax says that he gets like a fucking 25% return on his investment per year,
which is like an unbelievable return on investment.
But I realized that the downside is that you have to check it every day
and you have to update your parameters every day.
And I'm just not willing to do that.
Come on, boring things to do, like make video games.
That's right.
But I'm fucked because the money that is in there is in crypto.
I can't just withdraw the money from it.
I have to send it to some transfer service.
I have to make use of some third-party another app to cash my own money back out.
So fuck that.
Maybe it could make huge gains, but I'm just, I won't stick with it.
I won't check it all the time.
I'm not Brian.
I'm no Brian.
And you're right, making video games is more important.
It is.
In the grand scheme of things.
It's way more important.
I have to prove once and for all that 2D video games are just better.
I have to make the ultimate two-dimensional video game.
That's a shame.
You're choosing the inferior dimensions.
I can hear you.
Are my headphones dead?
Oh my God, my headphones are dead.
I'm sorry.
One sec.
Typical attitude from a 2D scrub, not having his headphones ready to go.
Meanwhile, the Chad 3D over here.
I'm back.
I'm sorry if I was talking over you.
If it was, it was because my headphones died.
I was just giving you shit for being a 2D person.
I just think they're neat.
I just think sprites are where it's at.
Pokemon peaked in Gen 5 and it's all been downhill from there.
So, I mean, what more proof do you need?
I don't know.
Final Fantasy 7 is 3D.
That's pretty good.
People seem to like Final Fantasy 7.
I like 6.
Okay.
I've never played Final Fantasy 7, so I can't say.
I'm just going off what other people have told me.
Is that right?
You never did?
Have you played 6?
I own it.
I haven't played 6.
I didn't have a Super Nintendo back when I was a second kid.
I never beat 6.
7 was the first Final Fantasy I played.
I think I played 8.
I think I played 9.
I never beat 9.
I think I went back and I played 6.
I got to the end of 9 and then my memory card died.
I got to the end of 9 and I didn't beat 9 either.
Same story with 6 and 9.
I just lost.
It's the worst.
I just lost momentum at the very end.
Some day.
Now they have the PC ports where you can speed up the battles and stuff.
Maybe I could justify in my busy life going through the game at Mach 10.
I don't care because I got to the only good part of 9,
which is the part where you're not alone plays.
I got to that part.
I've seen the best it has to offer.
I don't need anymore.
Okay.
The whole game is great.
But to each their own.
It's fine.
It's got 2D and 3D.
It's got 3D characters and 2D backgrounds.
It's a marriage of two contrasting mediums.
I guess it does have 2D backgrounds.
Kinda.
Are they all 2D?
Does it have all painted backgrounds?
The overworld and the battle areas are modeled,
but all the actual environments you move around in, they're all pre-rendered.
I didn't even know that.
Well, wait, 7 and 8 are the same, right?
Are 7 and 8 like that?
Yeah, they all use the pre-rendered backgrounds.
Right.
Yeah.
That's pretty cool.
My game is an RPG.
That's it.
That's true.
You're not wrong.
That's all I have to say.
Incredible.
This week, I've been spriting.
I've been spriting.
I wanted fancier animations for the things that Phantom does.
I made a nice animation for when he drinks.
I made a nice animation for when he throws.
I was right before we started.
I was working on one, a better one for when...
Wait, I'm not going to say what the last one is.
It's all just totally aesthetic stuff that doesn't actually get me any closer to releasing the...
Yeah, but it feels good.
I'm not doing it for money.
I'm not making this game so that I can make ends meet and put food on the table.
Why not just let it take however long it takes and just make it a masterpiece?
That's how you do it.
Just ignore the proper production and just chase whatever weird, fancy, straightforward stuff of the day.
Exactly.
Progression doesn't need to be a straight line.
Fuck that.
Exactly.
Do I know what your secret project...
Have you mentioned it to me or do I also not know?
I have not mentioned it to anybody.
I don't think.
Anybody?
I don't think so.
I don't think I've talked to any of you guys about it.
I'll probably be revealing it soon, though, based on the progress that's being made.
But I haven't just been doing a secret project.
I did a bunch of Patreon stuff, like I send out physical rewards to patrons, and I'm finishing up those.
I made a Zoomie...
I'll put a picture in the chat.
I did a Zoomie cookie cutters, and I did a Zoomie little figures, and then I printed and folded up some little boxes.
So you can put little figures in boxes.
It looks pretty cool.
Let me see.
Not that I'm complaining, but what possessed you to make a Zoomie cookie cutters?
What gave you that idea?
It was just something I learned how to do, and so I was like, oh, let's try.
Let's see what happens.
And it worked.
Because I had a 3D printer.
I had 3D modeling software, and it's like, alright, let's make a cookie cutter and see what happens.
And it worked.
And there they are.
It's pretty sick, and it took a lot of figuring out.
But that was one of the things I've been doing instead of being on the podcast, was figuring out how to make all that.
My headphones are dead again.
Oh my God.
Pat.
Jesus.
Pat, oh my God.
How is this possible?
What did you do last time if you didn't fix the problem?
Has he been this unprofessional the entire time I haven't been on the podcast, or is this a new thing that happens just when I show up?
I'm back.
I don't know.
The batteries are fucked up.
Have you made cookies with them, though?
I have not, because cookies aren't keto.
Oh, right, your keto.
Yeah, so.
I have been eating so many Parkview cheddar brats.
Oh, I get those all the time, too.
From Aldi?
Yep.
Hell yeah.
They just, they finally restocked the keto bread at my local Aldi.
I've never seen that at mine, which really sucks, but.
They don't, they don't stock it there?
No.
So I just, to make lettuce wraps, it's fine.
Honestly, I need to eat more greens.
I need to eat more vegetables.
The only vegetables I eat these days are like, sometimes I'll put a slice of tomato on like a BLT or something.
It's not enough.
No, you gotta, I don't have enough vegetables either, but whatever.
It's so much easier and cheaper to just get a cheddar fucking thing.
Just get a cheddar brought.
Yeah, just put it in the fucking microwave or whatever and be like, all right, whatever.
Fuck it.
Just eat a cold slimy out of the fridge, you know, whatever.
That's true.
They're pre-cooked.
It's fine.
I do that sometimes.
Sometimes I get like the, the ballpark Franks they have there and just be like, I don't
need to fucking do good and just like whatever.
I got work to do.
The best, I was shocked, I was shocked by this, but the best deal.
I think one of the best deals on like fatty meat, you know, the cornerstone of any keto
diet that I have found is at Costco, no, not Costco, BJ's Wholesale Club.
They sell like boxes of like six packs of like five hot dogs.
So it's like 30 hot dogs in a box.
They're Oscar Meyer, which you would, you would think that like name brand wouldn't be as cheap,
but BJ's Wholesale Club, these boxes of hot dogs, they're so, they're really cheap.
They're really cheap.
I think, I think like the Instacart like just started servicing BJ's.
So I've like, I've recently gained access to these dogs.
Also, little disappointing story, disappointing story for me today.
I ordered sparkling water and Instacart said that sparkling water, that there was like a
different set of flavors.
Whereas before I would always get berry, lemon and lime.
It said that, oh, now we're selling packs of berry, lime and peach, ginger.
And I was like, oh my God, this is going to change everything.
This is going to shake up my routine.
I ordered them and no, it was a lie.
They're the same.
They got the same old, same three.
Nice.
It's great.
You just can't trust Instacart.
A lot of the times like the shoppers I get from Instacart, they'll just swap things
without telling you that they've swapped things.
And so you just get completely random shit that you didn't ask for.
That has happened very rarely.
That has happened very rarely to me.
And I have taken, I take great pains to like, if I'm concerned that like they might make
like now whenever I order from Aldi and I get the gridlocks, I or I like specifically type
in the text box like, hi, please only get the red and white gridlocks.
Thank you.
Or if I'm ordering the ice cream, like please only get the keto ice cream.
Like I specifically tell them because like I've had some people like, oh, they'll just
replace it with some other ice cream or oh, they'll just replace it with some other bread.
Like, ah, bread's bread, right?
No.
Fools.
But it's, it's when I, when I'm fucking let them know, they generally don't fuck with
me.
I've had pretty good luck with my, with that.
And I always get, I always give them a five star review, even though I don't know if it
helps them at all.
Probably doesn't, unfortunately.
Probably not.
Yeah.
Sad.
Probably just boost the app in the algorithm or something.
You're just helping the corporation.
We just don't know.
I don't.
Speaking of corporations, I love how Facebook is super pissed.
Did you hear about that?
No.
What's up with Facebook?
So do you know how like there's been a big spat between Facebook and Apple for the last
like couple months?
No.
You heard about that.
So Apple is rolling out this new feature and it just launched like a couple of weeks
ago in the new version of like the iPhone's OS where it will, every time an application
tries to track you, a little pop up will come up.
It's like, this app wants to track you.
Do you allow it to and that like fucks Facebook's entire business because they're, it's all
about stealthily tracking you across all your fucking shit and selling that data to advertisers.
And Apple's like, well, we don't sell ads.
So let's just let our users know that all their data is being stolen.
And so like, I guess the opt out rate has been 96% in the first like month that this
feature has been available and Facebook's like fucking panicking because like their entire
business is like being blown up right now.
It's pretty funny.
Is it Apple's fault?
I don't, I don't quite understand.
So key.
So the problem here is that people are opting out of having their data harvested, right?
Like that's the problem.
Yeah.
I mean, it's a problem for Facebook.
It's good for the users, arguably, because like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All these applications, you know, there's, there's something, there's like a unique code
attached to your iPhone and that code allows the data to be transferred between applications
because it puts, it basically puts a name to the face, right?
It's like every time you do something, it matches us up with that code.
So other apps know what you're shopping for, what you're searching for and things like
that.
And so Apple added a feature where instead of it just doing that automatically and sharing
that number, it's like, if you don't want to share this data, you can opt out and we'll
just send zero, zero, zero, zero, zero, zero for the number.
So it can't match you with anything.
So the data that it gets is useless.
So this was like Apple being like two pro consumer, right?
And it like fucked Facebook over.
That's the problem.
Exactly.
Yeah.
And they like took out a big like ad in the New York Times saying Apple's attacking small
businesses that rely on our ad platform.
So we're sticking up to Apple and all this shit.
But then you listen to their earnings call and all the investors are like, oh, we're
so fucked.
Oh, shit.
This is really bad.
Our business is going to be so fucked.
And it's pretty funny.
I hate.
I just hate them.
So fucking sucks so much.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
I mean, it's it's grimy.
Did you see those?
I don't know.
Um, the ad, like you seem like anti-union ads.
Oh, they're the worst, the worst, like the one from I used to be in a union, take my
idea.
Why would I pay dues to a union?
My employer handles it all better for me anyway, you know.
Do you remember last year all the right to repair for your mongering ads that were airing
in Massachusetts?
I didn't really see the ads, but I heard about the repair stuff.
They were so funny.
There was this one ad where like it was like first person of some like creepy guy in a parking
lot and some like vulnerable young woman walks over to her car and tries to unlock it.
And then this guy comes and like, it cuts to black as like she gets like assaulted and
it's like, right, to repair will allow your family to get raped.
And it's just like, no, come on, that's not it.
What does that mean?
It just means they're just fear mongering like, oh, if anybody can access the proprietary
information of your car, they can like remotely unlock your car and hack your car and attack
your family.
Like he could get into the car because he hacked into the mainframe.
Yeah.
It's some really dumb shit.
I'm so embarrassed for my state right now.
So it's a security.
They're saying that a right to repair prevents a secure, presents a security risk.
I guess I see, okay, fair.
You know, I'm convinced no, no one, no one article, whatever.
Yeah.
Whatever the fuck it was.
Or that, oh God, what company is it?
Which one of the airlines was like, instead of paying your union fees, you can buy a new
game console.
Yeah.
Shit.
Fuck yeah.
Delta was Delta who did that.
Right.
They were, why don't you fucking buy me a fucking.
Jokes on you Delta, no one can buy a fucking video game console.
They're all sold out.
Oh yeah.
They still, people still can't get PS5s.
The, the silicon shortage is probably going to be going all the way to the end of next
year.
The rate things are going.
Jesus.
Like $300 graphics cards right now are being resold for almost 1500.
That just because they're impossible to find.
That is fucked up.
The shortage is so bad, like before, like they would launch a card at MSRP, they'd immediately
sell out because like people are using bots to like scalp them all.
Now like now the stores are just selling them for three times as much because they're like,
if they're going to sell for that, we might as well make three times the money.
Yeah.
And it's just like, it just doesn't, you can't get cards for normal prices.
And there's like, all of the manufacturing is done in Taiwan and Taiwan's facing a huge
drought right now.
And one of the most important things you need to manufacture silicon is like fresh water.
So it's just going to get worse.
It's so fucking bad.
Wow.
Yeah.
It's a nightmare.
Fuck.
Well, like, God, I hope nothing happens to my fucking computer, man.
Oh, shit.
It's like really bad.
And then like there was another cryptocurrency that's trying to mine using hard drive.
So now like hard drive prices might start skyrocketing too.
And it's just, yeah, it's great.
It's super cool.
Very good.
Yeah.
That's unfortunate.
I've just wanted a new graphics card and I can't get one because they're just impossible.
It's like, I'm not going to spend $2,000 for a $400 graphics card.
I refuse.
I was watching stream highlights from your movie Sucks where he was watching the Dar Man
videos.
Do you know what those are?
No.
What's that?
I mentioned it just because there was one video.
It was like it was about like Christmas where like a girl wants to be a girl gamer, but
her mom doesn't think girls can play video games.
So her brother gets a PS5 for Christmas and she's not allowed to play it because girls
can't play video games.
The Dar Man.
Is this a new thing then if it's a PS5?
Well, the video was new.
I mean, this is a huge channel.
It's got like seven million subscribers and it gets like tens of millions of views.
Okay.
I hadn't really heard about it, but like I've seen things like it before.
The Dar Man is basically a guy who runs a channel where the thumbnail and the title
will be like something like Lady Accuses Black Man of kidnapping a child, but instantly regrets
it.
Right?
It's sort of phrased as though it's like candid footage of like, oh, we caught someone
being racist or we caught someone.
But it's not that.
It's a skit.
It's like an overly dramatic, like sort of tear jerking skit that like where like someone
is mean to someone or bullies someone or is racist or bigoted or something.
And then they are made the fool and they learn a valuable lesson.
And it's always like, you judge me for being a black woman raising a white daughter.
Well, you see, I knew her mother and she died of cancer and she was my best friend.
And I promised to raise that baby.
And I'm so sorry I judged you for being a black woman with a white daughter.
You ever forgive me?
Fascinating.
So of course they have millions of subscribers.
They have so many fucking views.
They get so many fucking views.
They get and it's like, what are we doing, Ben?
Why are we doing this?
We're doing an hour long podcast every week, trying to make art with integrity when all
we need to do is just Eleazar, what I want you to do.
I want you to make the thumbnail, go to the Darman YouTube channel and see his thumbnails
and just make the thumbnail for this episode look like that big text on the left and a
face on the right and title this one, I don't know, podcasters, podcasters, I don't know,
make a new episode but instantly regret it.
That's just every week.
What are you talking about?
Yeah, but we got to make it a title and it's got to be in all caps.
And yeah, yeah, we're going, we're going corporate.
We got to appeal to lowest common denominator.
The only market that's left, it's the only market that pays, got to get those 15 year
olds to click on our links constantly.
And it's like, you know, every every episode he ends with like, you know, share this video
around if you like this message, share this video around because you're not just, we're
not just telling stories, we're changing lives, right?
The message is like, yeah, the message is like, this is a video about how racism is
bad.
If you think racism is bad, you'll share this video.
Left unsaid is and if you don't share this video, then what is that fucking thing about
you?
Jesus Christ.
Oh, there's one, there's one that's like pro cop.
People in my discord were showing me these this morning.
There's one that's pro cop and it's like the lady is like, fire all cops, all cops are
bad.
And then she gets mugged and she's like, oh, help police.
And the cop is like, anytime, ma'am, you see, everyone judges me for being a cop.
Everyone thinks that I'm bad and I'm racist.
But actually I'm just trying to put food on the table for my black wife and our mixed
race daughter.
And so you see, before you hate me, get to know me before you judge me and it's treated
exact same being a cop, being a cop, it's just the same.
It's just the same as being a hard put upon black mom raising a white daughter and nobody
understands you.
It's the same goddamn thing.
Every goddamn time, tragic.
Oh, my God, pure art over there, it's hideous, it's hideous, hideous abomination of a channel.
It's a nightmare.
And of course YouTube rewards it, I don't know, I droves, I guess it's kids, I guess
it's kids that just, I don't know, want to be preached to or something.
I don't.
It's the calls to action, dude, I was because I was thinking about this because I was like,
it's the clickable thumbnail, it's the clickbait title, and it's the calls to the irresistible
calls to action.
I was thinking about like, because I remember Fred Letter Media hit a million subscribers,
like, I think last year they finally hit a million subscribers despite being around
for like a decade.
And I think it might have been on the podcast, we were asking the question like, why is
Fred Letter Media like so prevalent in popular culture, but like didn't have nearly as much
subscribers as they should get sitting all along, they've been active, and it's because
they have no calls to action.
Like people are just that fucking brain dead that they would need to have to like end every
video, like comment, subscribe, and they don't, and that's probably why they've only grown
like a tenth of what they probably should be considering their otherwise cultural impact.
Maybe.
I think people, you know what, because like I think about putting calls to action in
my content, but I'm just like, nobody needs that.
And I'm like, no, the brain dead masses need to be told what to do.
I'm not, I'm not above, I'm not above a call to action.
I know it works.
I'm, well, that's the whole thing.
Like I'm not saying that I'm above it.
I just feel like my natural like gut reaction is like it's not necessary, but it really
is.
Yeah, it really is.
I mean, I mean, you know, people like the red letter media guys because they come off
as pretty genuine.
And part of that is that they don't do a lot of calls to action.
They don't do a lot of like, you to be like, comment, subscribe stuff.
They can't because as soon as they do, it's like, don't you guys do the nerd crew?
Like this is blurring the lines a little bit.
Like they've kind of locked themselves into not being able to, I mean, they obviously
they don't need to because they're still really successful, but it's just like it's, they're
just such a good case study for like, despite making great content consistently for a long
time and like really having a large like impact on just like the kind of like internet culture
at large, their subscriber count really doesn't reflect it because they're not jingling the
keys in front of people.
I mean, is their content like, I know to you and I, maybe like red letter media seems like
very digestible, like appeals to everyone content.
But is it though?
Like is, like it's film, even like humorous film criticism, is film criticism like the
kind of thing that like, you know, is it, is it universal in the same way that like a melodramatic
skit about how racism makes people feel bad is universal?
You're not going to get to fucking whatever that channel is called.
Dar man.
You know, you're not going to get Dar man, J station numbers off of Plinkett reviews,
but it just seems like they're still, they're still underrepresented.
Like I think they probably could have like two or three million subs if they actually
like promoted themselves.
Maybe the struggle struggle is real struggle this week, I know it's been time has been
going faster and faster, but this week in particular, like I feel like we just did
the last one.
I've been, I've been working on the game, like the whole week and I feel like I didn't
get anything done.
I feel like all I did was I got some sprites done and I, and I put in some animations and
I'm like, that's, that takes a long fucking time.
I've been doing animation stuff for the last like couple of weeks and it just takes forever.
Cause like you just have to like stare at the frames and be like, do I tweak this?
Do I tweak that?
And it just, it's a lot of like monotonous, just like tweaks and shit.
It's, it's pretty fun.
I like it a lot because I get, I get lots of little like moment, like I get lots of
making this game.
I do find some things are very difficult, but other things are simple and give me lots
of opportunity for like small moments of success that I can enjoy.
Like, you know, I, I, I mentioned all those like new animations that I added this week
and every single, each time I successfully made one, I'm like, yes, it looks really
good when he does that now.
Like, oh, another one.
Yeah, bam, another one in the bag.
You know, I had to make one, I made, I figured out one little change I could do that would
make them like when you take damage instead of the number just changing instantly, it
like kind of rolls down sort of like earthbound and it looks way better.
And I'm like, yes, I nail it.
It's just got to get that juice.
It's all fucking good.
It's like, it's like that physics professor I had that one year who told us that when
you solve a problem, feel good about it.
Let yourself feel good when you solve a problem so that your brain will learn that
solving physics problems is good and you'll be motivated to do more.
Your physics professor was the best game dev teacher you could ask for.
He was a fucking Buddhist hippie.
And he was huge.
He was huge, huge, like fat or huge, like swole.
No, just very tall.
He wasn't, he wasn't fat.
He wasn't skinny either.
He was like, he was, you know, a normal build, but he was like, he was like six
foot eight or something.
He was just like, yeah, he was a giant.
Yeah, based.
That's pretty sick.
Yeah.
Are you coding the game in Python or like, I am coding the game in GML, which is just
like the proprietary game maker code.
It's very similar to Python and a lot.
Like I've, yeah, it's, it's, it's a lot like Python.
Cool, cool.
What it, I don't know, what do you fucking do?
What do you fucking do?
Huh?
What do I do?
What do you fucking do?
I make polygons move.
Do you, do you, do you code shit?
Um, I've done a little bit of Python and I've looked a little bit into C sharp and a
little bit into, uh, what's it called?
A GD script, which is Godot's native scripting language.
I'm not good at any of them.
Remind me, which we're interested in the animation side, but I don't.
Okay.
To, to make like the, to make like the, like the combat, the, like the turn based
combat system, I basically just followed a, a, a, a tutorial that I found on YouTube.
Um, there's a lot of junk code in there that is just like, like there's a whole
like magic menu that's in there that I just put in there because the tutorial told me
to, um, but it doesn't do anything and you can't access it, but it's just there
because I was following the tutorial.
Um, that's in there.
And then that, like that part was hard and like, there were parts of it where like,
okay, well, he told me to do it this way, but I want to modify it.
I want to change it.
So it does this.
Okay.
And like that was hard, but like after that, basically everything else that I've done
code wise, almost everything else that I've added on top of it is just like increasingly
complex, like sets of if else statements and it's just, I don't feel like I'm, I know
anything, I don't feel like I'm doing anything.
It's surprising how far you can get with if statements, variables and like a basic kind
of like state machine and you're just like, Oh, that's like, yeah, that is exactly what
it is.
That's exactly what it is.
It's like the basic loop of the game is that like, you know, the character is there.
Then like the menu is active.
You select something in the menu, you select it.
And then the menu goes into wait mode.
The character does a little thing.
He has a little timer that counts down while he does his thing.
And then when he finishes doing the thing, it ticks the box that makes him go back to
wait mode and the menu goes back to active mode, rinse and repeat.
And then in those little actions, it's just a series of, you know, calculate these
numbers, apply these numbers, move it here and there, change his right to this and that.
Yeah, yeah, it's amazing how much of video games is just if those statements.
Yeah, I used, I used a list.
I used a list function because the tutorial told me to.
So I used one list and everything else is just like, if this statement is true, then
do this when you hit the spacebar.
I think the most complicated thing I did in the Izumi and Vertical Slice game was
putting in the dialogue system because I couldn't find a tutorial for it.
And I wanted to have it so it would pull text, put it into the box, have it like
print out in a typewriter text kind of format, and then also pull up the
character's name and portrait with different expressions to go with each line of dialogue.
So I ended up using like a 3D array.
Oh, it was really weird because like I put all the 3D array.
Yeah, it's like so as in like so as in like dimension like like axis one is like
what character axis two is like what expression and like what axis three is, I
don't know, I don't know.
It was like it was like X and Y.
And then the Z was just that like each Z was like different array.
So it was like arrays nested inside arrays.
So there would be like you would have, oh God, it's been so long.
I have a whole video explaining how I did it.
But there was like one that had the name of the character that was speaking, the
line, and those would be two different columns with the same row.
And then the rows would have a number and it would just like iterate through
those numbers and then on the second array and like the third, like the Z axis, that
would be the, it would call the animation frames for the portrait sprite.
And so it would just count down and that one column would match up to both all the
rows and kind of have everything sync up is very strange, but it's pretty cool.
Yeah, portrait sprites are something I need to make a bunch of, I used like a
placeholder one in the demo, but I want to make a bunch of expressions.
And I kind of want to like just like lightly animate them for the final game.
The speaking of which, though, I did manage to do a little shortcut because
the champion game that I made a while back, it had, I made a little fancy
like dialogue boxes that like sort of like type out all the characters and it
makes the little undertale sound.
So I like basically just copy pasted like those, that like text box code, like
directly from that game into the new one and just use it again.
And it works great.
It's reusing code.
That's like the one on one of like being smart with your design.
Yeah, why reinvent the wheel?
Exactly.
I believe I also followed a tutorial to make those text boxes in the first place.
So I'm just, yeah, stealing from myself that thing, which I borrowed
from some other guy.
That's how you learn.
It's just like going through tutorials and figuring things out and reverse
engineering it.
And then you start iterating on that and be like, OK, I understand how this works.
How can I tweak it so it does this instead?
And that's kind of how you learn.
And then it becomes kind of second nature.
Making games is sick.
It's it's it's pretty sick.
I'm getting into it.
And it's, I like, I like that it's a series of small tasks that I can that I
can complete and I can finish.
I can be like, I can have like a list.
I wrote out like a list of like here are a bunch of features that I want to add.
And I would like work on one for like an hour and then like done, cross it off,
work on another one for like two hours done, cross it off.
And like, by the end of the day, I've got like four or five crossed off.
I'm like, yes, I made measurable progress.
That's fucking wild.
Yeah, it's always super sick.
Feels good.
I like it.
Let's see.
Do I have anything else to say about that?
No.
Sick.
Ben, have you ever seen on the internet, on like Twitter, where they'll take they'll
take like designs of like a corporate logo or something and like switch it with
like another company.
So like be Burger King, but like it looks like a McDonald's logo and like vice
versa, and it looks really weird and off-putting because it's like this is an
iconography I've recognized, but they've changed the brand or something like that.
So like like a like a logo for McDonald's, but presented in like a Burger King aesthetic.
Yeah.
So like they'll take they'll take like the font choice and like the graphic design
of like Burger King, but make it say McDonald's or like take Coke and make it
say Pepsi, just like switch the designs and just like is really weird.
I can picture it, but I don't think I've seen posts like that.
No, I've seen a couple of them.
The only reason I bring that up is because I walked into Comby's yesterday.
Comby's I haven't been in a Comby's in years.
Shout out to Comby's and Comby's and that's that for anyone for anyone who
doesn't live in like the very specific part of Southern New England that we live
in that's short for Cumberland Farms.
It's a it's a local institution.
Yeah, it's just like a convenience store.
So I walked in I walked in the old Comby's and they had sitting in the cooler
when I went to go get my Red Bull, they had monster like monsters,
like the sugar free monster, but it was in a 12 ounce can
like Red Bull, they have a new size and I have the 12 ounce cans.
They have a small size.
They have a small size now.
Why would you want that?
Why would you want less of it?
It confused me to no end because it was like one of those tweets where it's
like it's a Red Bull, it's a Red Bull can, but it has a monster in it.
And it looked like a Photoshop.
It didn't look like it was a real thing.
And I was very confused.
I was taken aback.
That's I'm not in the market for that product at all.
It was cheaper though.
It was cheaper than buying the bigger ones.
They were running a sale on it because it was new.
So I got three of those and well, if it's cheaper, if it's cheaper by volume,
then sure it was.
I did the math, you know, good.
I'm a frugal man when it comes to my fake money I get from the government
to buy things.
Absolutely, absolutely.
That's how you got to do it.
Yeah, well, my fake money has been biting me in the ass as you heard.
But yes.
Oh, God, we didn't talk about that.
There's nobody knows what I'm referring to.
Gee, I mean, we give it like came up on the stream and I said, like, we
shouldn't go into detail about it if you weren't there.
But if you want to complain about it, like I don't even know how to complain
about it. It's just ridiculous that like, yeah, because like I've been
collecting pandemic unemployment because right, why wouldn't you, right?
And everything seemed to be going fine.
I re-upped the because you have to like recertify, you know, every every year
or whatever, because I did my taxes and I got a notification saying like, yeah,
you're re-upped for it.
And then like last week, I got another message saying, actually, we changed
our minds, you're not eligible for any payment since January.
You know, oh, that's $10,000.
And I was like, oh, no.
Did they did they ask you for like, oh, God, what is it?
Like, like a like a document discovery, like you had to like resubmit your.
Yeah, they did.
They sent me that the day after they said I qualified and I just didn't see it.
But here's the thing on May 4th is when they were like, actually, you no
longer qualify, we're taking all your money back retroactively.
But the notice that they sent me for the certification says you have until
July or June 21st to recertify and like go into your account to this link to
recertify and there's just you go to the link and there's just nothing.
When when I when I got unemployment like years ago, like when I this was
after I got laid off from a job and I was just collecting unemployment
insurance, like, you know, from the employer, basically, I got like they
ended up like overpaying me, but like only by like 200 bucks or something.
And I think I don't know.
Yeah, I think I just like appealed it and they like waived it.
I'm like shocked that they can just say like, hey, we overpaid you.
We decided that we didn't want to give you that like thousands of dollars.
Right.
Give it back.
It's super fucked.
I'm shocked that that's something that they can do and will do.
Yeah, they're doing it to me right now.
So I file an appeal, which I did fucked up.
Yeah, yeah.
But like the thing is, is like you file an appeal and just nothing changes.
So like it's it's not saying like it's in dispute or anything.
It's just still saying there on the homepage like you oh 10 grand.
But they're like, you still need to keep collecting every week.
Yeah, but we won't pay you.
You'll just be claiming it.
And then when we schedule your later, maybe in like four months, if you win,
then we'll give you all the back pay.
And if not, we'll just keep all the stuff.
So like between now and the appeal, you just don't get paid anymore, which is cool.
And I got on the phone and talked to somebody on the helpline and like.
So I have to do this and like, yeah, we're not going to pay you.
Like, so how do I live?
And they were just like, we don't know.
Is there anything else we can help you with?
And I'm just like, I'll just go have a panic attack now by.
Did they, OK, because I know that they have the there's like regular unemployment
and then there's like the pandemic unemployment assistance, which is like
the extra on top of the regular.
Did they retroactively cancel like all of it or just all of it?
All of it, both all of it's gone.
But here's the funny thing.
It says on because, you know, you've you've gone on the website, you know how
like there's a side that there's like one column that says like what you're
what you qualify for every week.
And then the main column is like, you know, fill out your claim here or whatever.
It says like all the ones that are pending or whatnot.
Yeah. On that column, it's like you owe 10 grand.
On the other column, it's like, you still qualify.
You have 44 weeks remaining.
Here's what you get every week.
I'm just like, you guys are sending me mixed messages right now.
I'm very confused. Oh my God.
So my God.
Yeah.
I told my dad about it because like he loves dunking on the state.
And I'm like, look at the state did now.
And he's like, oh, I know a lawyer.
Talk to my lawyer friend.
So now I'm going to go talk to a lawyer tomorrow and see if good.
That's what you should be doing.
Take some fucking legal action.
Yeah.
I almost don't want to step too much into the muck because I feel like
at some point someone might be like, so you just sit at home on the internet.
You've been collecting unemployment.
Like, do you really not need it?
And like, I could make my case that like, well, I can't go to conventions.
Nobody needs nobody.
A bunch of people are fucking bleeding.
Like every month I lose like three or four patrons a month
because they don't have any money.
And like my whole like, if you're if you lose your job,
the first thing you're going to do is stop paying your artists on Patreon.
You know, so like, oh, I don't know.
Unless unless they all get unemployment too,
and then they can put their unemployment money towards all the fun bucks go
kind of just all over the place.
I see, I see.
Why not?
I mean, why not?
It's as good as any.
It's all fake anyway.
It is all fake.
Speaking of fake money, I saw an article saying that if you had
taken all your stimulus checks and invested them in Dogecoin,
you would have made four hundred fifty thousand dollars in gains.
And that hurt my soul.
Wait, no, four hundred and that's not true.
That can't be.
No, because like the last the last the last check was like,
well, like two months ago, right?
Like when they put it out in February.
In February, it was still only like like ten cents at the most.
So when Oh, in Dogecoin.
Oh, yeah, you know what?
Oh, yeah, yeah, like the first one.
So if you had put all fourteen hundred, that first you would have like over,
you know, like fifteen K just from that.
And then if you the first two was when it was under a penny.
So you would have been fucking you would have like times fifty.
You would have like fifty times that initial like that initial, you know,
twelve hundred, you're at now, you're I am.
Yeah, fuck fuck.
Yeah, it hurts.
It hurts to think about it. I hate it.
I hate it. So fuck you.
I hate cryptocurrency.
The thing that hurts the most, dude.
The thing that's where I hate owning cryptocurrency and I hate my whole fucking thing
into Doge, I almost put that fourteen hundred into Dogecoin.
But I was like, no, I'm going to be safe.
I'm going to bank it. I might be moving this year. I need money.
You bought some little. Did I know?
Oh, yeah, I have I still have
a little over three thousand Dogecoin.
So it's like about eighteen hundred dollars right now.
And I've only I only spent one hundred twenty five on it.
So so that's pretty good.
It's pretty damn good.
And like every time it like hits a peak, I pull one hundred.
So I've already like pulled out like seven hundred dollars of my one hundred twenty
five investment. I still have almost two grand.
So you've so you've made you you're at your net zero, right?
Yeah, I'm good. Yeah, I'm Gucci.
So like it can go it can go to zero now and I'll be upset.
But like I won't have lost anything.
A couple people in my discord were saying a few a few people have made
like a couple grand on Dogecoin.
And I'm like, I hate Dogecoin.
I hate that it's going up.
But like good for them, like good for anyone who isn't like
some fucking Wall Street hedge fund manager or like the board of directors
on some fucking corporate good for anyone who not like that,
who manages to squeeze some money out of it.
Yeah, I know, I know, even though I know
that those people are the main beneficiaries of this kind of thing.
Yeah, I know.
I know Paleo, he put in
money before I did.
I think he's close to making 10 K off Dogecoin right now.
Oh, God, which is insane.
I. I don't know.
I don't know. I I feel like.
Bubbles got a burst at some point, right?
Well, it has to because like they're the reason
like I kind of wish I'd put more money into Ethereum
because I have a little bit of Ethereum that I got for free.
I mean, that's doing like really fucking well
because Ethereum's like doubled in the last month.
But like the reason I've always been bullish about Ethereum
ever since it kind of like became a thing because.
Oh, look at you.
Oh, look at you throwing around fancy terminology bullish.
Oh, oh, it's just a real word.
Oh, excuse me.
I'm bullish on Ethereum.
Oh, well, Ladi Ladi, my dick's been rock hard about Ethereum
ever since I first heard about it because people actually build
like applications on top of it, whereas like Dogecoin's just a meme.
So it's just a meme, but you would have made four hundred thousand dollars.
I know invested in that meme.
Bro, I invested in Ethereum.
I would have made like four hundred million dollars at this point.
What? Not not since the pandemic.
Well, no, no, but like when I first got my first
Ethereum because I have point one six three Ethereum
and I got that in twenty eighteen for free from what's that worth?
Like twenty bucks.
When I got it, it was worth twenty five dollars.
Now it's worth six hundred and fifty.
Wow.
So if I had like actually bought some
ETH back in like twenty eighteen when I first started thinking about it,
I would have had like, I don't know, ten, fifteen thousand dollars in Ethereum.
It hurts, man, hurts my soul.
I mean, yeah.
I mean, if I if I had bought if I had bought a Bitcoin ten years ago,
I would be worth, you know, fifty four thousand dollars right now.
But I mean, it's it's on the one hand, it's super easy to be like hindsight.
You know, I could have done anything.
But like when like you were like right there with your finger over the cursor
and decided no, that's when it really stings.
Yeah. Yeah.
The only good thing I did is that I had half the amount of ETH that I do now.
But because like the way it was done is that M dots always been big into
Ethereum and like crypto and stuff.
He's like big into that shit.
Why do why do you get Ethereum from M dot?
Well, that's what I'm about to explain.
He like had sent for like Christmas, twenty eighteen.
He had like sent a bunch of people like hand drawn postcards like art on them,
just like people in his discord server.
And then he's like, I've put like two digits of like an Ethereum address
on each one of these postcards.
So if you all get into this discord server and solve it and like put the
the number together, you can get this wallet and everyone gets a little bit of
Ethereum. And so we did that.
And then half the people are like, I don't want this Ethereum.
I'm like, oh, give it to me.
I'll take it. I like it.
This is cool.
And so I like doubled my Ethereum from people just not wanting it.
And now it's worth six hundred and fifty dollars.
I'm like, you idiot.
Suckers.
I mean, that's what you got to do.
I guess you just got to step on your fellow man.
You just take whatever you do, whatever means necessary.
Exactly. I'm a good capitalist like that.
I just need Ethereum to get as big as Bitcoin.
And then I'll have like six or seven grand and then I'll feel like a god.
Exactly. I didn't learn anything.
Special guess Applejack today.
That doesn't apply to the situation.
No, it really doesn't.
I just wanted to say it.
That's what the hedge fund managers say when they get bailed out by the government.
I didn't learn anything.
I was right all along.
I was too big to fail all along.
Yee-haw, Sweet Apple Acres is getting subsidized by your tax dollar.
Oh, they fucking they fuck.
Where do you think they took that fucking farm from?
It's an apartheid state.
Ponyville is an apartheid state.
They took it from the native.
I don't know, Windigos or whatever, the native fucking goblins or whatever.
They used to live there before.
Built on zebra labor.
It's disgusting.
Yeah. Yeah.
It is, though.
Sad but true.
Yeah, they had to clear out.
They had to clear out the Everfree Forest.
It used to be a thriving, you know, we turn our nose up.
Oh, we say that all the Everfree Forest is so savage and untamed.
But, you know, the zebras had a thriving society in there before we clear cut it all
to build Sweet Apple Acres.
It was worth it.
That sweet, delicious cider was worth, was worth it.
Worth every drop of zebra blood spilled in the struggle.
Remember how Rainbow Dash was a drunkard?
That was pretty good.
What a great show, 10 out of 10.
10 out of 10.
There's still Dr. Wolf, man.
Dr. Wolf is still uploading videos.
What a legend.
He's he's actually, I just happened to look the other day because someone
someone posted in my discord, someone posted Little Shy.
You remember Little Shy?
That's a name that I remember.
Little Shy if I am.
Yes.
He's still posting.
He's still getting like, you know, in like the 10, like the mid 10 K's views.
And Dr. Wolf also still getting in like the like the 10 K's of views.
Lately, he's been posting a lot of like, you know, speculations on the
trailer for the new, the new movie and the new show and stuff.
Yeah, I was about to say they're all biding their time till Gen 5 when they're all
research. Yeah.
And people are still watching.
You know, I mean, good for them, I guess.
Cool.
Oh, good.
Good on you.
You got your thing in this work.
You got your thing in this working for you.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, Ben, you just got to you just got to market your game towards the pony
fandom that's still active.
I'll have you know that I that I retweeted it on the T-Bap account.
Well, what you really got to do is you got to send it to Seth at Equestria Daily.
That's that's the bump you need.
Honestly, honestly, I think I probably will do that.
I probably will be like, hey, this is I made a pony fan game.
This is a game that I made about my pony OC, my my bro analysis community OC.
From years ago, remember Phantom Horn?
He's back and I made a video game about.
I mean, why not?
Right? Yeah, yeah.
Why just got to like have like the cover art image, just have an unrelated
picture of Trixie for no reason and Seth will click on it for sure.
You mean the pony Trixie the pony, not Trixie.
Right, our associate God, I don't want to put no, no, no.
I've got I've got I've got I've got a vision.
I've got a vision of how I might want the the title screen to look.
But I tried sketching it out and like it looked awkward, considering that I had
to fit like the title and like the like the start options.
So I'm like, I have this really cool idea for a visual image.
But like, I don't know if it can actually squeeze it in to make it
look good and like a man in like a start menu.
Maybe you could just be a little like cinematic image that plays like
when you hit the start button or something.
I don't know.
Or maybe you could play before the menu pops up.
Just got to start doing some thumbnails, put some animatics together,
see how it flows before you commit to the bit.
Yeah, just spend them like a whole a whole month just designing
like the animation for the title screen before I actually get back to making
the game itself. Yeah, you know, whatever.
Fuck it. Take as long as I need.
Why not? Why not just make it a masterpiece?
Yeah, I mean, what's the point of doing something half ass?
Got a whole right?
It's true. It's true.
Got like the whole damn the whole point.
Not the whole point, but like a big part of like my idea for this game
is like this is going to be, you know, it's fairly simple.
It's pretty limited in scope.
It's just like there's no walk around sections.
All it is is just a series of menu driven JRPG battles.
And it's like, just keep the possibility space low.
Just keep, you know, keep the the the amount of things you can do fairly limited.
Limit the possibility space limit the amount of work you have to do.
And like that's true.
I did that and it's true.
It is limited compared to what it could be compared to what I'm sure
a lot of other games are, but it's still taking me months.
It's still taking me month.
Even your solo diving again, like it's super fucking hard.
Like you're doing the right move by keeping it like you're not overscoping,
which is like the death of every indie game.
No, I mean, I mean, I do keep thinking of things to add,
but it's not like big things.
It's just little things like, haha, what if what if I made him burp?
What if I made him burp when he drinks the soda?
Probably the best thing to do is like to come up with like a minimum viable
products, you know, like like just like this are the airline things
that needs to launch and then you can just do post launch updates.
And just that'll be way to keep interest in the game going.
That's kind of what the what the demo was.
Like I released the demo at the point that I was like, this is the minimum
point where I can say I have a game, you can play it.
It doesn't have all the stuff that I want in it because I, you know,
it exists as a vehicle for the story.
And like a lot of the story elements are hard.
And I have only even only just barely started to like add those in.
And those are going to be kind of a hassle.
But, you know, other than that, it's yeah, minimum viable product
is kind of what I was going for with the demo, as well as like, you know,
letting letting people play test it in that form, just to see, did I fuck it up?
And yeah, oh, fuck, where was I?
Was I complaining about making games too hard?
It is pretty hard.
It's too hard.
Even it's too hard.
And even though like I'm doing it baby mode, like doing it in GameMaker,
it's like it's like fucking baby mode.
Like GML is it's like baby pseudo code.
It like couldn't it couldn't be any easier.
I mean, it's not even it's on the one hand, it's like baby mode,
but like it's not really baby mode.
It's like optimized mode because like you can make it in unity,
but like C sharp is a general programming language.
It's not designed to make games.
Like people kind of like is C sharp in unity.
Yeah, unity uses C sharp. OK.
But like GML and GD scripting Godot, they're like proprietary languages,
which kind of suck because they they're not transferable.
Like you only can use them in those applications,
but they're tailored designed to make games with.
So like they're more efficient if you're just trying to make video games.
Yeah. So yeah.
I mean, I mean, I like to think that in a way it's baby mode,
but like it's not like it would it's not like it would improve the product
if I had to like hard code in a function for me to like,
you know, find the square root of a number that so that I can make
a projectile move in an arc, right?
Nobody, nobody at the end of the day cares how you made the game.
They just care that it works, you know?
Yeah, yeah, which is why I always find it funny
because like I was building the vertical slice in a visual scripting language.
I wasn't even doing any coding for that.
And like you'd go look up tutorials for it.
A bunch of people would be like, oh, this is so dumb.
Anybody who does this is an idiot.
Like you'd only have to code and it's just like nobody cares.
Nobody cares that it wasn't hard coded.
They just care if the game's fun.
I when I when I made the champion game,
you know, I started with Game Maker and, you know,
Game Maker comes with this comes with a suite of.
But comes with a suite of, you know, drag and drop functions.
And I started making it using the drag and drop.
But like I regretted it because I realized that like a lot of bugs
that I ended up being really hard to fix just came from the drag and drop
because the drag and drops don't work that cleanly.
For some reason, I just found that they introduced a lot of problems.
That is something and I just ended up I ended up coming away
thinking like the drag and drop game functions are like a noob trap.
That's like it's easier to just it's easier to just write the code
and tell it what to do than to like put these fucking put these fucking
black box drag and drop functions in and make a weird fucking flowchart of them.
Like that's it's just easier.
It's just easier to just write it out in a bunch of if else statements.
Yeah, I think this time I haven't used any of that at all.
And I don't I wouldn't I wouldn't really recommend it.
I think it's just it didn't.
I don't think it ended up saving me like any effort at all
when I tried to use it the first time.
I I kind of disagree.
I feel like visual scripting was a way for me to get into game design
and what is what is visual scripting like like the the drag and drop thing
like you're talking about making game logic without doing actual programming
in in Godot or in anything because there's a bunch of engines that do no code.
Like I used construct three to make the vertical slice
and that's all using an event sheet.
So instead of writing lines of code, you can pick from like pre assigned blocks
that do certain things and it triggers them like downward,
like from top to bottom, it goes through the event sheet.
And you can make make like basic state machines and stuff using those.
And that.
Eventually, I ran into issues where I couldn't figure out.
I think it was more of a me problem than than like the the visual scripting
itself of like getting my states to work properly, like with interacting with enemies.
But that was.
For me, as someone who's much more visual learning,
like being able to like demystify the code and like break it down
into like actual English, it helped me learn a lot of like underlying
programming concepts that when I was reading tutorials for like GD script
and she sharp didn't make any sense.
Like I didn't understand functions until I did them visually.
And then I realized, oh, the the parameters are placeholders
for values you pull when using the function later.
Like I didn't get that when I was reading the GD script documentation
because the documentation on Godot is like really bad.
It just assumes, you know, Python, it's like the documentation is like
it's like Python except this.
And as someone who didn't know Python, I was like, I have no idea what you're talking about.
So I mean, if you're someone who's like predisposed to computer science
in general, just program.
But if you're like afraid of it, I think like having visual scripting
stuff is a good kind of like first step to just like.
Get something done.
I think the most important thing is to get something shipped and out of the door.
And like when you make like your first little baby like pawn game
that might just be like dragging a couple blocks in and it works like it goes
from something you can't do to something you can do.
And I think that's a huge, big, important first step.
Did you did you do any like math in college?
No, no, no, maybe maybe that's the difference.
Because I mean, I didn't even do like like advanced high school math.
Like I was so dumb at math.
Oh, you're just not you're just not a math guy at all.
Not at all.
I mean, maybe that's the difference because like I, you know, I got my physics degree
and I had to take a bunch of like I had to take a bunch of like semi advanced math
and stuff, maybe, you know, I mean, writing in GML is just it's a lot of like
it's not math, but it's, you know, you you put a you take a function
and you put the operand in the fucking brackets and then the operator operates
on it and then it, you know, iterates on it in a sort of math like way.
And I don't know, maybe I just find that maybe I'm just kind of practiced
at the at the sort of thinking that, you know, writing code in that way demands.
Yeah, I mean, now that I've done like a lot of visual scripting stuff,
like I can look at code and understand much better what it's doing.
Because it's just like it's just being able to translate.
It's like any other language being able to understand like what the basic kind
of linguistic functions of it are for lack of a better term.
You know, like once you know what an FL statement is, you can look at code
and be like, oh, I understand what's going on there.
Whereas before you'd be like, what the fuck does this mean?
Yeah, it's all good.
It's all about finding the right tool for your skill set.
Sure. I mean, whatever, whatever.
At the end of the day, it's whatever works.
I just I just found that I went in to Game Aper being like make her being like,
oh, I'm so glad I don't need to learn code
because I have these drag and drop functions.
And I and I left thinking like, why not even bother with the drag and drop functions?
The code is like not significantly more difficult to understand.
At least that was that was my experience with it.
Sure. But I guess I guess my point is just that, like,
if the drag and drop thing wasn't there,
which you've ever made a game in the first place, you know,
it's it's that breaking down to the barrier that's really helpful.
You know, you know, I turn my nose about it now.
But at the same time, yeah, there there must have been a period
where I was dragging and dropping.
And then I was because like you can take a drag and drop function
and then you can say like, OK, actually, just show me the code.
Just convert this drag and drop block into raw code.
And it will just turn it into code into a block of code for you.
And you can look at it and edit it as you want.
And you can like see what's in it that made it do the thing.
So, yeah, actually, I probably did go through a bit of like
a transitionary period where and I come to understand what is going on
inside the blocks, open them up and look around inside them and go, Oh, I see.
Well, all I really need is this.
So I could just take this and put this over here and instead,
and instead of all this other stuff that's in here or whatever.
And yeah. And then I'm like, OK, so now I know how to do it
without the blocks, but like I built it with the blocks in the first place
that kind of got me there. That's probably true.
Yeah. And now that you mentioned it.
Yep. Make it.
Hey, there are my headphones dead again.
Oh, OK, hello.
Charge the fucking battery, Ben.
I. You're right.
You're absolutely right.
Or just use wired headphones.
You're on your desktop.
What do you need wireless for?
Um, I just my wireless are my best ones.
They don't have like a oxport you just plug a cable into.
They not I am not like a signal cable.
They have a plug that they can charge with.
Oof. No, they don't.
They don't have a signal cable.
Brutal.
I forgot to mention I want I mentioned that this week I had.
I had the run in Noida and I just want to mention
that I had my nukes.
I had all my immunities.
I was a complete God.
I was running around nuking entire biomes,
raining gold, so much gold on me that it crashed the game.
And I just died fucking around with wands.
I just died fucking around with my wands
and like shot myself with a bullet that killed me by accident.
It was I will I will try not to go too much into detail about it
because I could explain it all day.
But the short version is I was using modifiers
that add extra damage at the cost of making the bullet deadly to you.
But I was further modifying them with a
another thing that makes they the bullet the projectiles lifetime equal to zero.
So it doesn't travel at all and it can't hit you.
Long story short, I took off that
no no lifetime thing that makes the projectiles disappear.
So the projectiles were, in fact, flying around and I fired a shot
and the bullets whizzed all around and I was like, oh, wow,
those are like incredibly deadly.
If any of those had hit me, I'd have been fucking dead.
Ha ha. And then I shot it again and they killed me.
And I was like, why didn't I just not do that?
Why didn't I simply not do it?
I was fate telling you to start working on your game again.
You know, honestly, that's how it is now.
I'll get on.
If I boot up Noida and I have a good run, a good run takes a long time.
I'll be playing it for like several hours and I'll be like, yes, this is the run.
This is the run.
And then I die in a stupid way.
But I'm just like, you know what?
Good, I shouldn't play anymore, Noida.
I'm free now.
You've said that multiple times, though, and you keep dragging yourself back to Noida.
Please forgive me, baby.
I'm sorry. I just shout on you in the procrastinators podcast.
Just one more run.
It'll be different this time.
But it's never. But it's never different.
No, this no, no, no, baby.
This time, I promise you'll get explosion immunity and fire resistance
and glass cannon and nukes this time.
This will be the run. This will be the run.
But it's never the run.
That one could have been the run.
Whatever, I I I I met the goal.
I met the goal that I wanted, which was seeing what it's like to fire a nuke
with glass cannon and survive.
And it was I mean, I I already told you about the gold.
I don't need to explain.
I don't need to explain how glorious it was.
What more can you what more can you ask for?
I guess it's finally time to move on to another game.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You know, it's a little thing about Noida is that like
as a run goes on, I always eventually find myself
gravitating towards the same kind of bill in the same way that like all life
forms will eventually evolve to resemble a crab.
Every every Noida game eventually evolves so that I have my main damage
wand, which shoots one bullet, which then explodes into lots of tiny bullets
that have huge damage modifiers on.
That's my damage dealer.
And then I have a teleport wand that shoots little short teleport bolts
that go so I can go really fast across the map.
And then I have a third one that shoots a bunch of black holes
infinitely that can dig me through any terrain I want to go.
And then the third one is just whatever else I fucking feel like carrying
because it's just those three.
Those are the three things.
Huge damage, teleport really fast, dig through anything with infinite black holes.
And that's all you need.
So, you know, in a long enough time frame, every Noida game kind of ends up
looking the same, if I'm being perfectly honest with myself, which I always am.
It's good. Yeah, sad, but true.
People were trying to get me to play Isaac.
I don't know.
I don't know. I want to go back to classic.
I mean, I used to be really into it.
I played a lot of it back in like twenty fifteen or so, fourteen.
They were just like an updated version, didn't they?
Yeah, people were telling I think pretty recently they did.
And apparently like people really like it and it's got a lot of stuff in it and like.
But I mean, I feel like I had my fun with Isaac years ago.
I don't know if I want to do it again.
Well, it's always there. Time to I know it's I know it's a good game.
It's a fun game. I like it.
But do I do I need it, though?
What will it do when needs video games?
Nobody needs video games, except for our video games.
Those ones you need pre-order now.
People need Phantom's Revenge.
Yes, the the Brony community needs the shot in the arm.
That will will be the Phantom's Revenge.
Just going to split the fan between between Gen five and Phantom's Revenge.
The two camps.
I maybe I'll it would be really funny to like.
Phantom's Revenge comes out.
It's a huge hit.
It shatters the glass ceiling.
It transcends the boundaries between YouTube and My Little Pony
and and whatever the fuck else.
And it's like it's it's a smash hit.
It makes me a million dollars.
And then I'm like, damn, got to make a sequel.
So I just take the engine and I just kind of build a sequel.
That's like the same game.
But I don't know.
I'll just set it and I'll just set it in the world of Gen five.
I'll just have Phantom killing a bunch of like the Gen five ponies or something.
You know, that'd be good idea.
Can you imagine that actually happens and then the peak,
the procrastinators podcast comments section just full of bronies
and like we come full circle.
Could you?
We have to go back.
We've been saying it for years.
We have to. This is it.
This is our ticket, our ticket back into the limelight.
If G five does well.
Horace return, we have to go to Brony Con again.
God, I wonder.
Right.
Somebody, somebody must own the rights to the name.
Brony Con, right?
Like somebody would have to either the owner of that IP.
But do you think someone owns that name?
They have to, right?
There's no way they just let that lapse.
Because if not, Radcon six, Brony Con is happening.
I.
Well, I don't know.
Do you think maybe it's too generic a name to be copyrighted?
I don't know.
If no, if nobody owns that name, I would say that, like,
probably a gen five will see a return of Brony Con.
If it is like a trademark name, then I still think it's pretty likely.
We'll return in spirit, if nothing else.
There will be another big convention.
I would think that at that point, whoever owns the copyright
could just sell it to somebody who wants to make do another one.
That would be a good move.
I don't see why you wouldn't do that.
But yeah, even if it's called something else, honestly.
Yeah, I bet it will.
I bet it will, because it's looking at little shy F.I.M.
and Dr. Wolfe, like the audience is still there.
I'm sure it's not what it was at the height of the Brony craze.
But there's still an audience for my little pony content.
Look, and a lot of it is the old audience.
We need to get in on the ground floor if Gen five starts doing well.
We don't have to change anything.
We just have to have every week we're talking about the new episode
and the PCP becomes the the the pony consuming podcast.
And we just kind of just don't even mention anything.
It just it just kind of happens.
God, you know what?
I'm fucking I'm fucking ready.
I'm fucking ready to just be a fucking pony tuber again.
Just take me back.
Just take me back to the simpler time.
I'm not kidding.
You laugh, but I'm totally serious.
I'm better times.
It was fun.
I there are times when I do miss it.
I was all it was all it was all fun and games back then.
Oh, I didn't get my closure.
I didn't even get to go to the last Brony con.
It's a it's a hole in my heart that will never heal.
Why didn't you go to the last bro?
Oh, because you were sick.
Or are you not sick?
You had him.
He had mobility issues.
Yeah, I was still waiting to get my surgery back then.
Right.
No pun intended.
No, you know what?
I think there will be another Brony con.
I think I think it'll and I'll be I'll be curious if it's like
half the size of the old ones or if it's like really small,
like not even like enough to be in like a con.
Or I mean, or maybe it would just be.
I guess the alternative is that it just becomes subsumed by furry conventions.
Yeah, maybe, I guess.
It might just might just become a facet of furry.
The fandom's still alive.
There are people who like I still follow some pony artists
and they're making their shit.
Yeah, but I mean, I don't know.
I guess I could just see like if it doesn't.
Unless there's like a real resurgence of the Brony culture, like it depends
on how well Gen five does, I guess, unless there's a real deal.
Yeah, if it's not a big deal, I feel like the natural thing
for bronies is just to become a subset of furries.
Yeah, become the diet furries.
They were always accused of being.
Yeah, exact.
Exactly.
I didn't learn anything.
Oh, I got to.
I have something funny happen.
So did you have you heard me talk about the the Cato anthology that is seen?
Mentioned, but I don't know anything about it.
Well, yeah, they were they were a comics anthology that's going to they're
going to do a Kickstarter in this pretty soon.
Actually, shit, the Kickstarter might even be running by the time
this episode comes out or like pretty close.
Yeah, and they last month, they were looking for submissions.
I think submissions are closed now, but they they they asked me if they could
publish The White Lion, which is like, you know, that'll that'll
chestnut. And I was like, sure, yeah, we can put that in if you want that.
And I they they asked me like, you know, for the files.
And I was like, OK, sure, I'll get you the the image files.
And I was looking through my computer and I could only find the ones
that I have that are saved at website size.
So like 900 pixels across as in like completely inadequate for print.
And so I'm like, well, fuck.
So I had to dig up the originals, which I happened to have in my closet here.
I dug up the original like drawn versions, the inked pages of White Lion.
And I am going to rescan them at high res.
And so I will be giving the Cato anthology the like
I guess the the the the HD remasters.
It'll be the HD remasters of the White Lion.
It'll be never never before printed, never before seen anywhere.
They will be making their their debut in one point five remix.
Yes. Three three eighty six over two pages.
Key key blade, whatever.
Yeah, yeah, like that.
Yeah, the the White Lion remaster.
I should I should make a new like title page.
Just says White Lion remastered just because it's funny.
I don't know, maybe.
But yes, that's going to be that's going to be in that book.
And they're going to do.
Yeah, I think they said they're starting the the Kickstarter on the 14th,
which is only five days from recording this.
And I got to fucking draw a cover for them.
I told they asked me to draw the cover for the that, which I said I would do.
And so I must do it soon.
This is just that's just another I didn't even get to do any of that.
This week, but that was just like the other stuff that I had to do for that
was just another thing like this this week went by.
Faster than usual, I really feel like only like.
I feel like we just recorded the last episode.
It actually really freaked me out.
Well, like yesterday when I was I'm like, oh my god, it's Sunday tomorrow already.
We just recorded.
We just recorded an episode.
What the hell?
It like it actually kind of upset me because it's like it's a very strange
feeling when it felt just like what did I even do?
And you start having like a minor kind of like freak out.
You're just like, so what would happen yesterday?
What I do the day before that?
And what about the day before that?
What where did it all go?
Yeah, I got it real bad this week.
I got it particularly bad.
Mm, mm, yeah.
But what can you do?
That's life.
And they say, you know, every time the older you get, the older you get,
the smaller a fraction of your like your total experienced time is like.
Yeah, you're like relative perception of time gets faster because like every day
your your total life being alive is longer.
So each day is like a fraction smaller.
When you're when you're 10 a year is 10% of your entire life.
And when you when you're 50 a year is 2% of your entire life.
So there you go.
I don't know the worst, the worst, terrible, terrible, awful nightmare.
Nightmare world we live in.
Yeah.
What do you think about voicemails?
It's the part I've been dreading this entire hour and 20 minutes.
We last episode, we did two hours of voicemails.
I don't want to hear that.
There's no way.
I don't know how much of a penalty do I take if I leave early?
We we have a formula.
Oh, God, no, we can't surely surely we won't do that again.
Surely because last time we scolded everyone and we told them, hey,
script your voicemails.
Don't just ramble like, like, I just kind of think like,
so surely these will all be succinct and to the point and not annoying.
Our audience always listens to us.
They are.
Cherubs, absolute cherubs, every single one.
We have a page and a half, a page and a half, which is about that's normal.
OK, let's do it.
No, no, bullet, bullet time of bullet round.
First one is called Dead Leaves.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben, you should check out Dead Leaves, if you haven't already.
It's a 2004 anime by Hiroyuki Yamaishi.
It is 45 minutes of constant frenetic action and they shoot a ton of cops.
You probably enjoy it.
I think I've seen it.
It sounds cool.
It's not a big ask.
It's the one with the guy with the TV head, right?
The one guy's got a TV head.
I think I've seen it.
Uh, and I think it was cool.
I don't honestly don't remember.
Thanks for the recommendation.
Sounds cool.
I'm going to check it out.
If you if you Google it, you'll you'll recognize what it looks like.
It's the guy with the TV head.
That's that's what I think of.
It doesn't look that it doesn't look like it should be called Dead Leaves.
I don't know why it's called.
I searched dead leaves and I just got dead leaves like leaves on the ground.
No, you got to go dead leaves anime.
Yeah, now I'm seeing it.
Yeah, yeah, there it is.
This is a trigger thing.
It looks very trigger.
I don't think it is trigger, but it does look very.
They're definitely trigger inspired.
Yeah.
OK, next voicemail is called The Digital Indra three two one go.
Hello, I just wanted to say I've been a long time listener of the podcast.
And by a long time listener, I mean, I've listened to probably about 10 episodes
and figured so many.
That's like 30 hours.
I'm in on all the jokes now.
Anywho just wanted to let you know I'm seizing the means of production
and producing my own podcast.
No, you can't do that.
And hookers.
You can't do that.
You're not allowed to do that.
So that's basically a keep on keeping on.
Return the scrolls, Ben, and Tom will never die.
Keep it sleazy, bitches.
What was the point of this voicemail
that we've inspired him to create content?
I don't care.
Well, I'm happy.
I was I was I was going to be annoyed
because I thought he was just going to plug his own podcast.
But then he didn't plug his own podcast.
So I'm like, OK, well, I guess I shouldn't be mad.
But then well, if he's not going to shamelessly plug himself,
then what was the point?
It was it was a point.
Thirty nine seconds.
I'll never get back. Oh, God.
Do you think I'm proud?
Do you think I'm proud to think that there are more podcasts
out there in the world because of me? No.
No, I'm ashamed.
I do. I've done harm.
You're not making pony fan games.
You're not using your time correctly.
No, no, you do as I do, not as I say.
Next next voicemail is called.
Oh, God, it's a minute, thirteen.
It better be worth it.
It's called Super Volteca. Three, two, one, go.
So, guys, how would you feel of all the kick
starters that the PCP made over the years?
Ended up being featured on an episode of Six Gamers.
Now, for those who don't know, Six Gamers,
this is a great series on YouTube posted by this guy named DJ Slope.
He's also like a frequent collaborator with Guru Larry.
I feel like I've already gotten the gist of the question now.
Well, you see, Six Gamers is a show where he covers some of the oddest,
stupidest and most dreadful, crowdfunding campaigns to ever grace
this invisible hellscape that we're forced to call Earth.
I ask this because, you know, the shit that Tritsey has done
is about you and the fans, whether it be the BronyCon lecture
or those curses that you leave in the V-blue rays.
You know, that would be something for Perfect for either an episode
about like five terrible podcasts or like a kickstarter.
Hell, you know, Tritsey herself would be an ideal subject alone
when it comes to like, I don't know, five shitty anime related kickstarters.
You know, I bet Slope would get a fucking kick out of her
messed up history and all the drama shit.
So, yeah, what do you guys think?
All the OK, he starts the voicemail by saying,
how would you feel if all the kickstarters that the PCP made over the years
went on this, whatever, this like kick scammers thing or whatever?
Um, well, uh, none.
First of all, none of none of the PCP kickstarters
have failed to deliver on anything, except for unless you count Radcon four.
But we are still delivering on that.
So that one is that one is incoming.
So none of those none of those qualify.
The Tritsey stuff.
I mean, yeah, Tritsey did kind of fail to deliver on some kickstarter promises.
I don't know if it rises to the level of like a like a like a hilarious
scandal or anything. Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, I don't know if it, yeah, I mean, yeah, yeah.
And then, I mean, I mean,
and then he goes off on a tangent about, I mean, would be funny
because Tritsey is weird in other ways and like, yeah, true, but not
the kickstarters are not because the kickstarters.
The kickstarters are a small footnote in that history of I would, I would agree.
Yeah, I would agree.
So yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Next voicemail, Alaskan Weeb, three, two, one, go.
Ben St.
You pawns, you fool, you rude, you simple capitalist overloads.
The whole reason that you can fire somebody for failing to prevent a shop
lifter while also allowing them from preventing shoplifting in the first place
is so that you can discriminate against people who otherwise are perfectly
acceptable employees. You can't fire someone for being gay.
You can't fire someone for being trans.
You can't fire someone for being non-binary, but you can fire them
for failing to prevent someone from shoplifting.
And that's how you fire people, how you discriminate against those people.
That's why that loss still remains.
Well, I.
I feel like you could fire someone.
You could make up any fucking reason you want to fire someone if they're gay
and you just don't like them.
Yeah, you can't say I'm firing because you're gay, but you can say like,
you know, you're you're I don't know, you're lazy.
You were you were five minutes late today and you're late.
You don't do your duties, you know, the you don't get along with it.
You could you could make up whatever fucking reason you want.
And like, yeah, sure, failed to prevent a shoplifter is could be one of them, I guess.
Uh.
Yeah, maybe it's I'm sure in some places it would be a perfectly reasonable.
I mean, you don't always even have to give a reason why you're firing someone, right?
Like, that's I think that's state by state.
And I don't think every state requires that an employer like specifically tell you why
maybe they do fucked up, but it would be it's kind of fucked up.
Yeah.
Do the next voicemail.
Oh, God, I'm going to have to hear my own voice on the episode three, two, one, go.
OK, I go to make a shitpost, like take take the garbage yelling thing
and pretend it's about the egg.
But no, no, OK, I go on to Trixie's Twitter and she posted tech talk where it's
it's literally her just just reviewing rest stops.
Why isn't Riley stopping her?
Doesn't Riley want want to make sure that nobody gets
they don't get docs and no one calls the police whenever,
whenever they're straight up saying what rest carriers they're at.
Why post them later?
She posted why they're already gone.
I thought you didn't want to show the RV so people could call it.
Why?
OK, this is what's passed to me later after they've already left.
So it's not it's not docs worthy.
I I just want to say funny, funny thing, funny thing that happened this week.
Just got to mention it is I actually caught Riley in the comments
of the video claiming to have an RV when they don't have an RV.
He straight up said or someone said RV and he said, oh, no,
this video was before the RV.
This was before we got the RV when they don't have an RV.
He's straight up just lying about it and it's so fucking funny.
OK, I'm sorry.
It's tangent. It's not important.
It says whatever. It's just that's for me.
Next voicemail is called Apologies, Benjamin and Gibb for two in a row.
This one's short.
Thank you. Three, two, one, go.
Also, in one of them, she's in a car.
She might just be taking the car and then sleep in the RV.
But there's no RV.
That would mean the RV exists and it doesn't.
Just so there's no RV.
It's the same car.
It's the same car that they've used in all the previous road trips.
You can tell because it has a telltale crack in the windshield.
And it's been there the whole time.
So that's fun fact.
There's some deep lord of this already.
I've been I've been away for a few weeks and there's all sorts of layers
that I didn't even know.
Internet, internet, internet sleuths,
internet sleuths have cracked this case wide open.
Much like the windshield.
Got up, got a plug, got a plug.
And, you know, if there were any doubt about whether the RV exists,
all you have to do is go to isthereanrv.com and you can have it answered.
And you will always you will be up to date on the answer to that question
at all times.
We've got you covered.
Next voicemail is called Frost Drive.
Three, two, one, go.
Gip and Ben and Tom, you guys really like video game commentators.
YouTubers that talk about video games.
I do. I'm ashamed of it, but I do.
There's a YouTuber I know who's virtually unknown.
His name is Ray R. Reviewing and his videos are really insane.
I think you guys would like him.
He even has puppets in his show and everything.
And it's oh, it's so good.
Some videos are an hour plus long and it's amazing.
If you like video game commentators, check out Ray R.
Reviewing, maybe talk about him on the show because that'd be pretty cool.
But if not, I mean, at least check him out.
Ray R. Reviewing.
Let's see.
All like all one word Ray R.
Like the word R.
Do you think this is his YouTube channel?
No, I don't think so.
Frost Drive has his own YouTube channel.
That'd be pretty funny.
It'd be a good bit.
It'd be a good joke.
Ray.
Let's see.
A filter by channel.
When I search Ray R.
OK, I'm searching Ray and the space, the letter R, space,
reviewing and the first result is Dame Drops.
Is it supposed to be like Ray R as an A R E reviewing?
I'm searching that I tried searching for that, too.
And I didn't get it.
Now, let's see filters channel.
I get one called Ray reviews and it's a puppet.
Ray reviews now.
That's not it.
Maybe maybe no spaces.
Yeah, I'm doing those spaces right now.
Maybe.
OK, I think I found it.
I think I found it.
And it's like a guy with like a purple mask.
And it's all one word, R A Y A R E reviewing 837 subscribers.
I don't know.
Fuck it.
I'll give I'll give one of these videos a watch later.
Why not?
I'm watching a bullshit.
Oh, he's got a real mask.
He's got a mask in real.
Oh, he's costumed.
Oh, he does costumes.
Oh, that's nice.
Oh, that's good.
It's gonna be really cool when it's in my other tab,
not being viewed as I just listened to it.
But I appreciate the production value regardless.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
Next voicemail is called YoyyTuber.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, sorry, I'm not that YouTuber girl.
Sorry.
Also, please, please, please watch.
Also, please watch.
Odd Taxi, please, please, please, please, please.
I am watching Odd Taxi last last week.
Someone I think the same person told us to watch Odd Taxi.
You've seen it.
I think I'm tweeting about it.
Right. I am watching Odd Taxi.
It's very good.
I like it.
Oh, wait, someone.
They said. OK.
They said like, oh, yeah.
Odd Taxi is about like a world of animals
and there's like a bear or a hippopotamus
or something who drives a taxi and there's a murder mystery.
And I was like, Snore sounds shit.
Sounds dumb.
Sounds bad. It's pretty good.
It's pretty good.
It's it's like a it's kind of like a slice of life thing,
but it's like kind of esoteric in that like the guy drives a taxi.
So like he's just doing his job driving his taxi
and people get in the cab and like have conversation with them
and then they go back out.
But all these characters that are coming in and out of his cab
are called part of this like bigger interconnected kind of murder mystery thing.
And it's some of the storytelling kind of synchronous.
So characters who come into the cab in one episode,
you'll get their backstory later and see what brought them to getting into the cab
and having that conversation.
And there's like some bigger
meta narrative with a lot of other characters.
And like everything's kind of like coalescing
and like all these characters that seem unrelated to each other
kind of cross paths with each other.
And like there's a bigger interconnected story
that's slowly coming into focus as each episode continues.
It's really cool.
It feels it feels like there's like a world happening
because all these characters are doing things and following their own goals.
But it's happenstance that brings them together rather than like
a kind of like more blatant kind of like schlocky plot.
It's just like they're just doing their own lives.
And and they're just getting into this cab and talking to this one guy
is like the thread that like starts connecting them
and like bringing them close together.
It's pretty cool. I recommend it.
Hmm. OK.
All right.
Listen, I'm here.
Yeah, I feel you down with this.
I'm down with picking up what you're throwing down, dog.
OK. It makes sense. Sounds good.
All right.
Prize. I probably won't watch it.
But I don't know.
I'll watch the two hour YouTube man,
but not a twenty three minute episode.
Absolutely, because I can fucking draw sprites.
I can draw sprites while I listen to YouTube puppet man.
Only we knew Japanese.
I mean, well, I mean, you got to watch a show.
I don't know. I can't like some some bullshit on YouTube.
Some guy talking about video games.
I can just listen and I don't have to look at it.
A guy, a show, though, like a cartoon, like you got to you got to watch that.
OK, then if you have to watch it, what's the problem with it?
Not being you're not going to watch another tab anyway.
So just like put aside 20 minutes and watch it.
But I don't want to put those 20 minutes aside.
I want to make sprites.
I want to play Noida for 600 hours.
Yes, I want to if.
And that's that's my Noida time.
That's my Noida time.
And I can't it can't sacrifice any of it.
Well, I can argue with that.
I can and I do listen to YouTube video game man while I play Noida.
That's like my favorite thing to do is those two things at the same time.
That's that's it for me.
That's that's that's all I need.
Playing video games while listening to something.
Yeah, I'm not into that.
You don't want to get absorbed into the experience.
Dog.
Dog. No, that's so fucked up.
No, that's what I do.
I put on I put on a fucking two and a half hour.
I two and a half hour retrospective on why
on why Platinum, Pokemon Platinum is better than Pokemon Crystal.
And and then I and then I played Noida for that long.
And then I just said I guess I guess something like more roguelike
like like Noida works in that.
But I usually play like linear games that are a bit more active thinking.
Yeah, I guess it probably wouldn't work well with like a story driven.
Active thinking is not the right word, because obviously there's a lot of active
thinking going on moment to moment in Noida.
But like something that's more narratively engaging, I guess.
Yeah, if I'm going to be engaged by a narrative, I don't want some fucking
white guy telling me how nostalgic he is for, I don't know, Banjo-Kazooie.
Like that's yeah.
Next voicemail is called Bleach Fan 17 3 2 1 Go.
OK, 15 seconds in.
Those who do not know what love is liking it to beauty.
Those who claim to know what love is liking it to ugliness.
Bleach volume 20 and a hypnosis.
Beautiful.
More piano.
This would be better if you played the piano yourself.
But, you know, we all have to work within our limitations.
Yeah, well, you know, the struggle.
But thanks. Thanks, Kubo.
Thanks for the thanks for the wisdom.
It's it's Tite Kubo does Bleach, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, I saw.
Oh, God, I watched a pretty funny video.
Hold on. Let me let me let me check.
Let me check my subscriptions.
Oh, who was this fucking?
Who was it?
I.
It was a video about.
Pixie Pixie Terry.
Is that her name?
No, I don't know.
You know, this this cosplay lol cow.
Oh, God, no, I have to I have to figure out what the name was.
You're definitely more.
You do. Why won't you just fucking?
Why won't you just fucking show me?
OK, OK, the channel was Cecil McFly.
Yes. OK, the channel is Cecil McFly.
The video was the a Pixie Terry story.
And this is the story of I had heard of this person before.
But this is basically like an in depth, like her whole story on the Internet.
And she's she's she's basically like, like, you know, I was going to say female
AFAB Chris Chan, who wanted to be like a cosplay,
wanted to be a gravure model.
Basically, it was like trans Asian like claim to be Japanese,
even though she wasn't like what else what else.
Um, oh, but the I guess she had there was a time when she had kind of like
a breakdown and she like closed all her accounts and went offline for a while
because Tite Kubo got married and like she had always wanted to like be with Tite
Kubo, he was her husband.
Oh, yeah, but he got married and she couldn't take it.
Good, good stuff.
She's just perfect.
Yeah. Um, OK, next voicemail is I think
the next one is called Jade, right? Yes. Yes.
OK, three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP, how are you doing?
Great. That's it.
Doing how are you doing?
Thanks for the voicemail.
If only there were all that simple.
Yeah, right.
The next one is called a message from your gaping ass.
Three, two, one, go.
Are you actually kidding me, Ben?
You've made me sit here for over a year,
waiting on the Sonichu 102 lecture so you could sit around making a shitty game.
Yes, I can't believe this.
That's exactly right.
I put all of my faith into you and you betrayed me.
I'm so shit. This will not stand.
I will fucking fly out there and I will hunt you down.
And I swear I'll destroy your kneecaps.
Have fun making a video game from a fucking wheelchair.
A loser. That's like the optimal position to be.
Then he can't get up and do other things.
All he can do is sit his computer and finish the game making a video game
from a wheelchair. Who am I? Tom Oliver.
Yeah, seriously.
God forbid.
OK. Yeah, I fucking did it.
Yeah, I fucking made you wait a year so I could make a shit.
He's going to do it again. Good job.
I will if I so if I please.
Next one, a message from your gaping ass.
Two, three, two, one, go.
And another thing, you stupid piece of shit.
I want to hear another thing.
I hope you go to hell.
By the way, Gib, I think you're really cool.
OK, she didn't hear you stupid.
I'll take that compliment for myself, though.
No. Fuck.
All right. Next one is called Conky Kong.
Three, two, one, go.
No more voicemails.
And while we're at it, you're right.
No more P. C. P.
Agreed. Oh, God, if only we could be free from this curse.
Agreed on all counts.
Anyway, on to the next voicemail here on the pro
procrastinators podcast, it's a message
from your gaping ass. Three, three, two, one, go.
So turns out I was wrong.
I just played the game.
It's actually kind of fucking based.
Yeah. Sorry, Ben.
This will never happen again.
I apologize. Better not.
Stay in your fucking lane.
Thank you. I'm glad you like the video game.
Stay tuned for the full release.
Stay tuned for the full version soon.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
You know, no, no.
You will.
Next voicemail based Joker seven.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, some people find themselves
waiting for the other shoe to drop.
I was really happy I was waiting for the shoe to drop.
But she no one's ever waiting for the other poo to plop.
Why did he echo me?
I mean, just to remind me that I said that one time, you know,
you've got to have it's like that grayscale, you know, flashback sequence.
Oh, I saw. Oh, I saw it in grayscale.
Oh, absolutely. Of course. Absolutely.
In slow motion. Yeah.
Blurry. Blurry.
It's like grainy, you know, kind of like superimposed over the over
the negative space of the image.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's a cinematic painting, a picture.
It's beautiful. Textbook.
It's textbook. Next voicemail.
A message from your gaping ass.
Four, three, two, one, go.
God damn it, Ben.
You and your fucking shitty roundabout ways and loopholes.
You just fucking took away all the power I had.
OK, rape you.
If you give me consent, dumb piece of shit.
Oh, yeah. Great.
Now, what am I supposed to do?
Just jack off thinking about raping you?
That's no fun. I wanted to actually do it.
Now I can't. Can't do it.
I did it. I cracked the code.
I cracked the code. No more rape.
No more rape. Universal consent.
You know, if Andrew Yang gets elected mayor of New York,
I hope he does away with his stupid universal basic income
and implements the policy of universal basic consent.
And that's where we can abolish rape.
You know what? This joke is played out.
You get it. You get it. Ha ha. Funny stuff.
Next one. Audio borked a bit.
But anyway, video games. Three, two, one, go.
Then talking about his game got me thinking
that it would be real cool to do like a PCP game jam or something.
It's real easy to set one up on itch.io.
You can just set the dates and tweet it out.
You could have a theme or restrictions or it could just be free form.
And then you can do a little stream to play through the games
or a special podcast episode where you discuss them
and it would be a fun community event, even outside of games.
I think comic jams or other things like that
would be a neat way to engage with the community
and help foster people's creativity.
Because making and discussing art is way more cool
than talking about Twitter drama.
You know, you know. It's got a point.
You know, actually.
My server, some people in there made a channel.
One of my mods, Spork, made a channel for doing game jam stuff.
And three of them.
And also one other person who I think is not in my discord,
who I don't know, but three of them, Sporktown,
Heroin, Tio and Roxanne Kaiser,
they have been making a game.
And you know what? I will I will link a tweet
because like they're actually making it and it's actually like turning into.
I'm like watching it turning into an actual video game on Twitter,
you know, smugly snickering to myself that, you know,
it started from like a jam sesh or an arrangement agreed upon
in my discord server, which means that I get partial ownership.
I get residuals. That's the deal.
You signed it when you joined my server.
Let's see here.
Tio was tweeting it.
Yes, I found it.
There it is.
Well, as you can see, if you if you follow the link.
Yeah, they got this game that they're making where you're like some kind of bat girl
and you like skate around on rooftops and you glide on your bat wings.
And you I don't know, you do stuff.
And it's looking it's looking good.
It's looking cool.
So, you know, you might you might call that a sort of PCP game
jam of sorts, they just they just did it on their own.
They just fucking did it.
I just realized I posted my picture from like two
hours ago on the wrong chat because I'm an idiot.
Wait, where'd you post yours in the main?
I'll just put it in the the place it should be.
Oh, oh, the cookie cutters.
Yeah, you did.
Well, true, dumb, dumb.
Eleazar can't see that shit.
He's not allowed in the real server.
Forgot.
Keep in this wild garden.
Next voicemail is where is it?
It's Jackass.
Yes, yes, Jackass.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, guys, you want to know what I just realized?
It's called self-abuse because if you beat your beat hard enough,
your dick starts to cry tears of life.
And unlike a battered woman, it can't call the cops on you.
Said.
I mean.
OK, duh.
You think you tell me that?
Oh, you just figured that out.
Oh, yeah, yeah, bad, bad.
Great. Thanks for the voicemail, sucker.
Next one is called Munky needs a hug.
Three, two, one, go.
You know what, Ben, I heard you saying you don't know why
Munky would want to be back on the podcast if not to talk about Trixie.
Have you ever considered that maybe he just wants to talk to some god damn friends?
You know, like the PCP was mentioned, originally meant to be
excuse for some friends to come together every week and talk to each other
to help keep the friendship together.
That may not have worked for the vast majority of you guys, but fuck.
I'm just sad you don't even seem to consider that angle.
Oh, well, would Munky ever want to hang out with me if not to
shit talk someone who used to be friends with?
I mean, I believe in the power of friendship, man.
I mean, we haven't.
What are you talking about?
We haven't talked.
I haven't talked to him in like in like two years.
I don't know. I'm not.
I hope it. I hope it's not.
I hope it's not the I hope it's not inflammatory to say.
I don't really think we're friends.
We don't like talk, so I don't I don't know, man.
Whatever, who knows what the future holds.
But yeah, I just I just thought.
I just thought it just seemed obvious that if we were going to talk,
that what else that just seems like something that would naturally talk about.
What? But for for content, anyone that doesn't know, I asked.
I asked Munky if he wanted to because because nobody else wanted him to be on the show.
But I was like, well, I mean, maybe I'll just could record something with him
and just talk about Trixie on our own.
And he was like, no, I don't want to talk about her.
I just want to be back on the show.
And I'm like, well, I mean, I get.
But no, I was the only one that wanted to do that.
And I got out of voted.
So I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know if I don't know if that's going to happen.
And like, why and why?
Why would we do it?
If we weren't going to talk about Trixie, it just seems obvious.
It would be it would be just seems natural.
It would be strange.
That's the thing I want to talk about.
That's the thing I would want to talk with him about.
That would be like the obvious launching point, I guess. Right.
Yeah. Yeah, that's what I thought.
That's what I thought. And that was my plan.
I don't know.
Um, anyway, next voicemail is called
Sanity check at the silent rave. Joker socks optional.
Three, two, one, go.
Bear and I are locked up now
at the clusterfunk hell sanatorium.
Nothing to do but sing and dance.
Sing and dance and misbehave
at the clusterfunk asylum, silent rave.
Oh, that ended suddenly.
I wasn't expecting it.
Feels like it's a transition piece.
The next like emotional high point of the arc.
Yeah, yeah, I feel like the next one starts right where this one cuts off.
Yeah.
Silent, a silent rave.
That's the thing where like that's a real thing, right?
It's when it's a rave, but like instead of them playing the music,
everyone's got their headphones in, right?
I believe so.
And they're all they're all raving to the music.
But like, if you don't have your headphones in, you can't hear anything.
Yeah. And everyone's dancing.
Just look like freaks.
Yeah. Yeah.
I went to a rave once in Poland.
It was pretty cool.
OK, next voice is called Ben.
Read one piece, please.
Still trying, huh?
Really, it took forty seven seconds for you to deliver this voicemail.
Let's let's see what you let's see what you did with the with that time.
Three, two, one, go.
OK.
Ben, real quick question about the Sanju one or two, not like,
when is it coming out?
Yeah, this time.
But I don't really follow all the pony shit.
I don't care about it.
I am I'm never going to care.
Why would you need to?
I mean, you guys are so into it, but I don't give a fuck.
But what does that have to do with Sanju one or two?
Can you explain that a little bit?
What was it just like you wanted to get one project done before you do another one?
No, it's not like you had one or two done.
And that was content related reasons before.
I feel like I explained this already, but I'll explain.
Also, go to the dentist like your mommy told you it's good for you.
I have. Oh, God.
Oh, God, this freaks me out.
Speaking of the dentist, I think I have a.
I was looking at my teeth the other day and I think I have a spot on one of my
teeth that I think I think is something called a root carry,
which if you Google that, you will find horrifying pictures.
Mine is not like that bad, but I think it is like a very early like root carry
that I was I was reading about like treatments for it.
And I don't know, maybe I'm hope I'm hoping it's not as bad, but like,
you know, if they get bad, they can like destroy your tooth.
You got to just fucking lose that you got a fucking root canal that shit.
And I'm so I'm so fucking scared.
Yeah, I've been ignoring my teeth for like a year.
And I'm pretty sure I got like I went to the dentist.
Like maybe a year and a half ago and because I went there because I thought
I had a really bad cavity and like, yeah, you have cavities,
but you have so many we can only do half your mouth right now.
We'll have to do another one later.
And so they did like all these fillings.
And then ever since then for like a year and a half,
my mouth's been bleeding almost constantly on the side that they did
the fillings and the other side that they didn't is fine.
So I didn't go back because it's like clear, you just made the problem worse.
I don't have.
But I've just been ignoring that.
It was probably a bad idea.
Nothing in my mouth like causes me discomfort or anything.
Like I don't have any like pain or irritation or anything like that.
So I feel like probably nothing is like super advanced to the point
that it's like awful.
But I don't know.
I googled.
I googling, googling about root carry has really made it sound like a dire
any medical issue.
It always makes it 10 million times worse.
And then I'm hoping I'm hoping that that's was the effect that was going on
with that because it was it made it sound like if you've got one of these,
your tooth is fucking done.
You are going under the knife.
You got to cut your whole fucking job.
I mean, at that point, I just like just pull the fucking tooth.
I don't give a shit.
Oh, God, it'd be cheaper, easier.
Fuck it must must just must just suck to get your tooth pulled, though.
Right. Oh, I've never had a.
Sure, it's a bitch, but Jesus.
But about Sonichu.
Yeah, the reason why it's not it's not just pony shit.
My comic Slime and Punishment is Sonichu Canon.
It is official Sonichu Canon.
It is technically Sonichu special number.
Hold on.
It is Sonichu special number seven or eight, I think.
Let me let me find that out for sure.
Sonichu, Sonichu comic.
Go down to the chapter listings, Sonichu special number.
Yeah, Slime and Punishment is Sonichu special number seven.
So in covering the lore of Sonichu, I had to talk about
Slime and Punishment.
And so I wanted Slime and Punishment to be done before I released that video.
And the game is the end of Slime and Punishment.
So that is why I waited.
I wanted to wait to release Sonichu 102
so that all the canon could be out when I talk about it.
And that's it.
Next voicemail is called a simple misunderstanding.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben, just wanted to clarify some things.
When I said that you would stop being a dumb leftist,
I did not mean that you would stop being a leftist altogether.
You mean I would stop being dumb.
I just meant you would start being a based and history
pillow leftist because my bastard is very good and very funny.
Well, and you would get a better understanding of why your beliefs are based.
That was all.
Fair enough. I apologize if that I wasn't specific about that.
Don't apologize to me.
Apologize to that guy.
Anticipate the misunderstanding.
Sorry about that.
It's fine.
My bad. It's fine.
Have a great one.
You too, buddy.
Yeah, OK.
All right. Love you.
I understand.
I get you.
Cool. I mean, yeah, it's always more based to know more than to know less.
True.
I should be more history pilled.
I don't I don't once in a while
I will listen to like a history podcast or something and like I like it.
And it's cool, but I don't do it that often.
And so I often am like, I just don't know as much about some things as maybe I ought to.
Yeah, next voicemail is called Autism 101.
And oh, my God, it's a minute 26.
This is better be good. Three, two, one, go.
Hey, guys, just wanted to explain some things about autism that you guys seem to have had difficulty last week's talk
because that's kind of frustrating.
You guys don't know about that, but that's OK.
I'm going to try and explain.
I got a lot of things to talk about, so I'll be quick.
So autism, it is, in fact, two spectrums because it affects two areas of behavior in humans.
And to be autistic, you just have to land somewhere on those two spectrums.
It can be very high on one and very low on the other, et cetera, et cetera.
Those two areas of human development and behavior are the interpersonal communication and ability to socially communicate.
And it is the repetitive behavior and limited interest areas of human behavior.
So, in essence, autistic people will generally have some inflexibility, be very attached to their routines to various degrees,
and they will also have a varying degree of difficulties with interpersonal communication or communication in general.
And that's pretty much the basics of what autism is.
Hope that was helpful.
I see you.
Love you, Deb.
Love you, Ben.
Fuck you.
I'm out.
With all due respect, no, that wasn't very helpful because I already said all that.
I literally said all those things last week.
I don't get it.
What are you trying to clarify here?
What about that did I get wrong?
I mean, I'm not trying to antagonize you, but I don't get it.
I don't get it.
What are you correcting me on?
What's the problem?
I don't know.
Thanks for the voicemail.
Next one is called Riley is bad at his job part two.
Three, two, one, go.
All right.
So I want to make some clarifications on my voicemail segment.
Riley is bad at his job from last week.
So I know that he calls himself a producer and not a promoter.
I also wanted to argue that he's a bad at promotion.
So that's why I said promoter.
He's also a terrible producer because he fucking can't produce an RV.
He can't produce sound because his audio sounds like garbage.
He can't produce fucking fans because he drives them away every time the smug little
dipshit opens his mouth.
So he's also bad at that part of his job.
That's true.
Ethan Ralph bit.
So what had happened there was after the fight, both parties agreed to go on the Dick
show and like talk about it.
Yeah.
Fucking Ethan Ralph called in and he was comparing himself to the Joker and it was really cringe.
People on the Dick show also hate Ethan Ralph.
So you know, really anybody could have taken it, but Riley chose not to call in.
He said he was busy on the discord thing, even though he was there the entire time.
What?
He just looked like an absolute bitch.
Why?
You'd think that as a hip hop guy, he'd know that beefing is good for business, but that
would imply that he's good at his job, which is I mean, they made that whole video to
make beef out of PCP forever.
Tom will never die.
Call me back.
Okay.
That actually, I didn't know that that actually does really baffle me.
Like it's like the whole thing cloud chasing.
Like why would you not chase that?
Yeah.
If you're making the video, like you're make the video.
It's all about the beef you have.
And I mean, those the the Yig people, like they love Dick, they love the Dick show.
Like they want to be on it.
They they they'll go, I don't understand that and there's like a perfectly good opportunity
to go.
I that actually really throws me and I don't know what to make of it.
It's very good.
If someone can explain why I, I mean, I, I mean, I, I don't agree with a lot of their
choices, but if you make the choices that they made, you know, you get in that situation,
you make that video about it.
Why then?
No, I don't want to talk about it.
Why would you do that?
I don't get it.
But yeah, just another reason he's bad at his job.
Why next voicemail is called why you got to assume three, two, one, go.
Why you gotta assume every color's gender been always like, thank you, sir.
Okay.
Mr. I think he said, just say they make it, you ain't gotta assume.
You're probably right.
I have a bad habit of just kind of assuming male by default, which is our analytics.
You're probably right more often than not.
Probably.
But I also, you know, I feel like it's becoming, I think I'm becoming less and less probably
right with each passing day.
Everyone's getting, everyone's getting pink pilled and you know, it's, it's, it's starting
to cause an inconvenience for me personally.
So I don't like trans people anymore is what I'm saying.
Oh no.
Pink pilled.
It's funny you say pink pilled because I, I misheard the colors as colors and I was
like, did I miss something last week?
Yeah.
I thought that's, yeah.
I thought so too.
But then I got the context.
I was like, oh, callers.
Yeah.
No, this, this color is right.
I probably should just default to they more, I, I advocate for everyone to do that.
But I don't, I don't always put my money where my mouth is.
They is just the perfect pronoun.
More people, more people should use it more often and I should, I should be the change
that I want to see in the world.
I wish all pronouns, they for everything.
Yeah.
Well, all pronouns except that one because that one's good.
I guess, I guess you can stay and I, I can stay.
No, they, only they for all those.
Yeah.
We is right out.
Next, next voicemail is called perpetually two weeks behind three, two, one, go.
Hey, I wanted to ask.
What's the ideal fame to money ratio?
Because if you have a lot of fame, you can get a lot of money and people will recognize
you on the streets in like your entire life is now a public figure.
But if you have no fame, chances are you're not going to get much money.
And I think it's very interesting how the different members of the PCP and previous
PCP all had like different levels of fame and what they wanted from fame.
Like Ben, he, he is pretty famous, but he's not so famous that most people would recognize
him on the street.
I wish I was more famous.
Even less famous.
Like I, I'm a fan of the PCP and I don't even think I'd be able to identify him if I saw
him outside.
Wait, who?
I was assuming you who were very famous.
You know, I'm sure they got a lot of money.
I think it kind of went to their head, you know, so I'm just curious.
I wouldn't even call Trixie very famous, optimal level of fame, I mean, Trixie is Trixie at
her peak was like approaching like baseline internet at her, at her peak.
I mean, she, she did rarely get recognized in public.
Like not often, but it happened.
Actually, I mean, I got recognized by something by a stranger just completely at random, at
least like once or twice.
Same.
So did you?
Always the most.
Yeah, twice.
It was very awkward.
Um, mine was, mine was fine.
It was just like, it was awkward on my part because I was not prepared.
It's like, bye.
I thought it was awesome.
I was like, oh my God, holy shit.
Uh, million views, baby.
Um, the, the, uh, I mean, I just, I don't know, I don't like this question because
I feel like more of both is always better.
Oh, like the optimal mix of the two is just as much of both as I can get, please.
I mean, there's definitely a limit for me.
I don't want to be like so famous that like I, when I go outside, like I get recognized
left and right.
But I think like in the sphere that we're involved in, that's not even an option.
Like I think like, yeah, you can be, you can have like 10, 15, 20 million subscribers
or something and still not get recognized when you go outside because like the internet's
just like not big enough, you know, so, yeah.
I mean, yeah, fame, fame on the level that it would like interfere with my daily life
is like so far away that like doesn't happen in our pursuits at all.
Yeah.
So I mean, I mean, just if I, um, I mean, I guess it would be bad.
I guess I would lean a little more towards money just because if you are very famous,
but you have no money, like you're still, you're still poor.
You're still fucked.
Yeah.
Whereas if you, if you're not famous at all, but you have tons of money, then like you
can become famous.
This guy implied, sorry, this person implied, I shouldn't assume gender.
It's true.
I say that like it's a joke, but I actually mean it sincerely.
This person implied that like having more fame implies that you have more money.
No, no, no, no, they said having more money implies that you have more fame and like that's
not true at all.
You can just like.
Chris Chan's pretty famous, doesn't have a ton of money.
That's true.
Also like in the verse, you could just inherit a bunch of money or maybe you just fucking
invested like a thousand dollars in Bitcoin in 2008 or whenever it started.
And now you are, now you have fucking 500,000 is lying around somewhere and like you don't
have to be famous at all to do that.
And once you've got a bunch of money, it's easy to turn that money into more money and
like.
Yeah.
Or turn it into fame.
You can buy attention.
So yeah, I would probably say money.
I would lean towards money because like having no fame, having tons of money can solve all
your problems.
Having tons of fame, having tons of fame doesn't necessarily solve every problem that you will
face as a result of having no money.
Yeah.
So that yeah, okay, satisfactorily answered.
Next one is called it's all downhill from six.
She her three, two, one, go.
I recently rewatched the final fantasy lecture.
Still a pretty good watch, even though it's mainly just Wikipedia plot summaries of all
the games and that's my least favorite one really and gotta be honest, like my least
favorite one.
But Ben, you had mentioned that Final Fantasy six is your favorite, which is based as fucking
I agree.
It is the best one.
Yes.
And it seems to generally stand seven, but you know where it's at.
Who's your favorite party member?
Cool.
My favorite.
My favorite party member.
God, I don't fucking know.
I don't know.
I feel like maybe my I'm drawn to six.
Honestly, maybe a little bit out of a contrarian urge to be like, to be like, seven's not
that great.
Six is where it's really at.
But at the same time, I genuinely had moments in six that like were really good.
And I mean, seven's got great moments too.
But you know, like the part where you catch the fish for Sid, it's like that part's great.
You know, the opera house, the opera house is so like cheesy.
It's a little it's a little like goofy.
But like, you know, whatever, if you just if you just let yourself enjoy it, it's like
it's fun.
It's a fun.
It's a fun time.
I don't know.
I don't know if I, I mean, it's been a while since I played.
I like Saban.
I like Saban's like fighting commands for his his special moves.
I think that's pretty cool.
The I don't know.
I don't know.
They're all they're all kind of they're like mechanically all pretty similar to each other
story wise.
I guess I like.
Oh my god.
Is it Cyrus?
Is Cyrus the knight that you pick up like late, late, later in the game?
I think he's pretty.
He's a pretty cool guy.
I don't know.
Oh, none of the none of the characters really have like a ton of.
None of the characters in six have like a ton of like development, like they don't have
as much as they get in seven.
Like in that level, I think like seven's got better characters.
Whatever. Sorry.
I feel like.
This is this is a six.
This is a six aficionado.
He might be disappointed with my inability to articulate like my my preferences about
it, but it's been a long time.
Fucking up your brain.
I'm I'm fucking up my brand right now, my my six loving brand next next voicemail is
called our pal Doug three two one go.
Just to give you guys an excuse to talk about nostalgia critic again.
I have the weird distinction of having seen Doug Walker in person twice before ever having
seen his content, both of the same Walgreens, so he must live near me.
The third time I saw him, I'd actually seen some of his videos and it was the Gallup and
Ghost Arcade.
And I remember like, I fucking, it was so interesting because the first time I was
like, oh, it's like, oh, it's all exciting.
It was like, it was the internet man out.
Look at that.
He's like internet famous.
I'd never seen one of his videos.
So I was all like, oh, interesting.
The third time I met him, I had seen his videos and I fucking hate them.
And it was a completely different experience where I was like, oh, there he is.
Look at him.
Look at that goblin.
I just think it's fucking funny.
How.
How do you remember that you saw him twice before you knew who he was?
I would assume he knew his face, but didn't see his content.
Like just like, oh, I know that someone from the internet I've seen like screenshots or
people talk about them on social media or whatever.
But I've just never watched the content.
Oh, like he knew who Doug Walker was.
Just hadn't seen his videos.
Right.
Oh, yeah, that could be it.
I was thinking that maybe this was just like a person that like you knew from
around town to maybe like, why is this guy walking around with like a loose
fitting tie and like a weird hat?
And that was that was what keyed him in to getting interest in him.
It's like, I got it.
I got this guy's there.
What this guy must have a story.
I got a I got to hire a private eye to figure this guy out.
And you find out he's a he's the head of a of a fucking global
monolith of internet criticism.
He started a revolution.
He's that guy with the glasses.
He's he's that guy.
He's the he's the guy with the glasses.
We have one brand.
We have one more voicemail and it is called Autism 102.
Oh, no, I hope it's better than the last one.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, gang, just wanted to explain a couple more things about autism
before I left you guys alone.
It's very hard for autistic people and non-autistic people to empathize
with each other because our brains work in very, very different ways,
like fundamentally.
And since, you know, when you try to like discern motivations or
intentions, but I thought it was a spectrum, two spectrums, it's very hard
because you don't have the same framework that led them to those decisions.
I don't know.
I'm not trying to defend tricks here or anything.
I'm just, you know, it's hard.
It's hard. I've done with this.
She's not autistic life.
She's not fucking autistic.
Like I make a decision.
I think about something and people look at me like, why the fuck are you doing?
That's a logical step.
Oh, OK.
What?
And so it's kind of hard to really know if when someone's autistic,
what's going on in their head.
She does or she's not even it's not even clear what she thinks.
So, yeah, try not to, you know, scribe intentions and shit.
It's kind of kind of leads to bad stuff.
What the fuck is this?
All right, that's what I want to say.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Am I speaking out of turn, but I'm annoyed.
I this is annoying.
I don't have a contact.
So what are you talking about?
Like, what the fuck are you talking about?
Don't ascribe intentions to things that someone with autism has because
non-autistic people and autistic people just can't empathize with each other.
So I don't know.
I get OK.
I think the point is like an autistic person
operates with a different mental framework.
So like you partially actions is not necessarily what they were coming at it from.
But like that extends to people in general, right?
Like everybody kind of processes things in their own way.
And like it's easy to misunderstand intention.
The the.
Oh, God, like, OK, autism is two spectrums.
So are you I mean, two people can be at different points on the spectrum,
but still like share some things in common, right?
Because they both they both two people exist on, you know,
on points along this well-defined spectrum.
They're they're not polar opposites of one another.
They are all arranged along this linear continuum.
So it's not like it's not like there's nothing in common.
It's not like there's no understanding that can be.
I don't I don't really know to what extent.
I don't.
First of all, first of all, OK,
assuming we're talking about someone who is like really profoundly autistic
to the point that I like a non-autistic person just can't empathize with them,
can't understand the way they think their motivations.
Sure, fair enough.
Is Trixie that? No.
Is Trixie autistic? No.
Uh, I know I'm not a doctor.
I know maybe she maybe she should get a diagnosed by a doctor
or something before we say that for sure.
But that's the point.
She hasn't been diagnosed with anything.
I mean, even if even if Trixie was to get diagnosed,
like it would be a mild case, like because I mean, like, right,
it's not it's not like there's like any sort of like communication barrier there.
Like, yeah, on a fundamental level, like we've collaborated,
worked on projects for years, like we've it's there's definitely
you know, enough of a common barrier there that I think I think I'm comfortable
saying that to some extent, the likes of you and I can ascribe
some kind of motivation behind Trixie's actions.
I'm pretty sure that we're capable of empathizing at least a little bit
with what she with her brain.
Right. I don't think the barrier there is impassable.
I'm sure I'm a little annoyed.
I'm a little pissed off.
I would just argue the entire like basis of our friendship going back
to like the pony days is that we were all kind of doing similar things
and coming at things from a similar angle.
That was kind of how our friendship was forged to begin with.
So, yeah, I don't know, like.
I'm being hard on this guy.
I mean, I don't think there's anything wrong with making this case.
I just don't know if it applies in this particular situation.
Well, that's the point I I feel like it nakedly doesn't apply.
Like to the point that I'm like confused about what is even trying to say.
Well, again, I'm operating without context for prior episodes.
But like, obviously, we know much more about how Trixie acts and is in person
than this person. The short version is that I guess at some point
or at one or two points in the past, Trixie has talked about being autistic
or behaving as though she's she's like alluded to it.
And people were saying and I said like,
you know, actually, it's kind of I said, like, you know, that should be diagnosed.
You can't self diagnose that.
And some people were like, well, I don't know, it's like.
And I know that like it's it's it is it's diagnosed through like a series of questions.
So it's not like I mean, like in theory, in theory, if you really understood autism,
you wouldn't necessarily have to be a doctor to make like a credible case
that like, oh, yeah, this person is, you know, far enough along with whatever these spectrums.
Like, yeah, you could probably like maybe that you would need some you would need
at least some level of expertise, you need to be some level of expertise.
Right. I would I would say if nothing for no other reason,
like you can't objectively give yourself an examination
because like your own biases are going to be clouding your own right that that too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you know, yeah, I said, like, you know, you should at least
have some level of expertise.
You should be to diagnose yourself.
But yeah, it's probably even if you are an expert, you shouldn't be able to diagnose yourself
because obviously you're going to be biased about when the subject believe it.
And you can say like I resonate a lot with these symptoms and like I probably have it.
But like until you get diagnosed, you can't really say for sure.
It's like for a while, I thought that I had mild ADHD.
But I didn't like say I had ADHD until I got diagnosed by a psychiatrist.
And they were like, yeah, like here's medication.
I made the argument last time that like being autistic since it's a spectrum,
it's kind of like being tall, where like, OK, maybe if you like if you're
in the middle of the spectrum and you go to a professional and you they do a test
and the result is like, well, you kind of display some autistic traits.
It's like, well, OK, so are you autistic then?
Maybe like there's not really an answer.
But like it's just like any other human made category where like the category
doesn't actually exist.
It's just a way of categorizing a sequence of traits and things like that.
So like, right.
It's all it's all fucking dicey if you really start like hacking away at it.
It's a good well, well put, well put, it's it's it's a category.
It's it's a line.
It's a line that we draw around a certain cluster of traits.
And we say these are we call we call these traits this thing.
If you're like this, you're autistic.
But it's like, well, I'm kind of like that.
But like, I'm not all the way like that.
And like, I have a little bit like that, but I'm kind of on the edge.
That's the whole point of saying it's a spectrum in the first place.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
True, true.
But like, I don't know where.
What are we even talking about?
What was the question?
I'm I'm, you know, damn, I don't like this note.
I don't like this as a note to go out on.
Shit.
Somebody quick, somebody send in the new voice.
Five at five.
Maybe someone left a voicemail.
No, no, no, I'm refreshing, but there's nothing.
What are you doing there?
Ah, fuck it, whatever.
You know what? We so what this episode sucks.
We make these every week.
They'll come back to the trough for more slop next time.
And then we can make up for it.
This is what happens when there's no give.
The episode just sucks.
And everyone hates it.
Apps in the chat for give.
She wasn't feeling good.
Oh, yeah, she said she was feeling sicker than usual today,
which is very unfortunate because like, damn,
she's been sick for like a
kind of like almost a month now, right?
Yeah, Jesus.
That sucks.
Hope it's not her liver, pancreas or whatever the fuck.
Gulp, she's coming down with a case of the autism.
Yeah, it's it's it's contagious.
Actually, I hear.
Oh, no, we're all infected then.
Trixie got it.
She's spanked.
See, more contagious than covid.
What were we thinking?
And deadly or two.
There's no vaccine for that.
There's no vaccine for that, baby.
Are you vexed? Did you get vexed?
Not yet.
Did you see I got vexed?
I got did I did I mention on the last episode?
Did I get my shot?
I was in here.
I don't I don't remember.
Whatever, if I didn't mention it last time.
Yeah, I got my first shot and I'm getting another one in three
at two, two, two to three weeks, going to be going to be cool.
I saw the dev of that game.
What game?
Clarence is Clarence's big chance.
You know that they talk about that is familiar.
It's the game where you play as like a fat, middle age,
disgusting slob who has who has like who has like fucking
tricked his way into getting a date with a hot girl tonight.
And he's got to like he's got to do his day perfectly so that he can be
all set up to have like the perfect date and impress the girl.
And he's got to like he's got to like find computers to like find her files
so he can find out like what she likes and like buy her all the right gifts
and like answer all of her questions in the way that will please her the most
so that he can find his true love.
Anyway, I saw the dev of that game saying that like the covid vaccine was
really fucking with him and I said, damn, dude, sorry to hear that.
Gone by and he liked it.
He liked my reply to his tweet.
So I thought that was pretty cool.
Tobias Cornwall, the guy who got his fucking pineal gland removed
because he had brain cancer or something.
Oh, God.
I know, right?
I'm only thinking about any of these things.
No, it's scary as hell.
But he fucking did it and he's he's good.
He's good now.
I kind of hope that we're young enough that maybe by like 2050,
when we're like getting old, we'll finally have like artificial organ cloning.
So maybe our bodies won't completely break down.
But I feel like God, I hope so thinking.
I feel like even if they have that, that'll just be reserved for the rich
because we'll be in hardcore neo feudalism by then.
Yeah, I mean, thanks for tuning in everybody.
Have a good week.
Pete, patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Speak pipe.com slash bzb voicemail to send us your thoughts on neo feudalism, baby.
If you want to save us from neo feudalism, $5 a month gets you access to the bonus episodes.
We can start pinching our pennies to get our artificial organs.
We can keep making these podcasts for decades to come.
$5 a month for more artificial organs for your old pals.
Ben and Tom.
Tom will never die.
Make Tom never die at the patreon.
Okay.
Thank you.
And good night.
Cool.
Good, good stuff.