This is for PCP. They say it's the worst podcast on the internet. F-f-correct.
Okay, it's another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's started. We just started hitting
the start button. We're going. We're live. Hi, everybody. Oh, my fucking god. It's me, Ben Saint.
I'm here. We've got guests. We've got more guests than hosts. It's fucked up.
It's real fucked. Okay, we got Oblivionfall is back, of course.
Yes, I'm here, and I'm editing this episode probably.
And we've also got a C-Toll and Four Eyes are here. Do you want to introduce yourselves?
No. I mean, hello.
It's me. Four Eyes, you know me. I'll introduce C-Toll. I'll mansplain. A C-Toll runs the drawcast
with me, and we've had cool guests on, like Ben Saint and Gibbontake and Teleperte,
and we'll get Tom one day, too. The drawcast. The drawcast, your own original creation. Do
not steal a YouTube show where you draw. It's a podcast where you draw. It's like a portmanteau.
Yeah. It's a good show with good people and Ben Saint. Good people and Ben Saint.
It's a good show. It's a good show. Yeah. C-Toll, you gave me a gift.
You gave me a priceless gift that could never be replaced. And you know what? Okay, I'm going to
say it. It could say if it was not functioning. Right. This week, it's time. It's been long enough.
By the end of this week, by the time this episode comes out, I'm going to have announced it. I'm
putting the time limit on myself. So I'm just going to say what it is. You gave me the funny
a DVD, a Blu-ray burner. You gave me the Blu-ray burner for me to create the plebe and the wee
Blu-rays, which I have made and which do exist and which you can buy from me now. Oh, shit.
After Trixie stole everyone's money and didn't deliver on them. And then you gave Trixie the
Blu-ray burner. Yeah. And then she just took it and was like, okay, and didn't make them and didn't
give it back when you asked for it back. Yeah. LaMalle. She was like, she was like, if someone
got me the Blu-ray burner, I would make them. I have the Blu-rays. I have the cases, but I don't
have the burner. It's not, it's even worse. It's even worse. It wasn't like if someone, it's not
like, oh, well, if someone gets it for me, then I'll make them. Which like, there was the bit where
she said, where she said, like, what am I supposed to do? Just pick myself up on my bootstraps and
buy a Blu-ray burner. Yes. As though that isn't a perfectly reasonable thing to do. Right.
You said you were going to make Blu-rays, ma'am. You were supposed to make Blu-rays.
Yes. And people paid me, what am I supposed, with what money? The money people gave me to do exactly
that? What are you, stupid? Yes. That was, that was tricksy. Then I'm like, oh man. Yes. So anyway,
anyway, okay, I'll show a picture on screen because I have gone above and beyond. I have,
they have Blu-ray cases. They have the boxes. They have a cover art. They have a cover sleeve.
They have a back of the box. They have reviews, rave reviews of the, of the product. They have,
they're, they're the printed on disc. They have a disc design on them. They have DVD menus and stuff.
Navigate them with your remote control and your Blu-ray player. They are a professional product
that I have spent months making just out of spite. Anyway, anyway. I'm proud of you. I'm proud of
you, Ben. Thank you. Thank you. Buy one. Everyone, if you think that's funny, if you, listener,
if you think it's funny, go to my Twitter, go to my Twitter or go into the description
and follow the instructions listed there and buy a copy because I did have to buy all the
raw materials for it. So it didn't cost me a little bit. Please don't let me come out at a loss
for this funny project, my funny secret project. You had to buy literally everything
Trixie already had except the Blu-ray burner. Right. I did. I did. Only, only it's better
because she was not going to make a, put them in a real, but she was going to put them in a shitty
jewel case and they were just going to have like a generic like no label disc. They were going to
look blank. She was just going to mail them in the mail. She was not going to make a professional
looking product. I have done, I have done that. My version is way better than hers would have been.
For the low, low price of $30, which is what was listed on the,
which is what was listed on the, on the, the Kickstarter page said they would be $30.
If you backed the, believe in the weed Kickstarter, I don't have, I'm, I obviously,
I didn't get any money. So like, I didn't get any of the Blu-ray money that would have paid,
that you would have paid for the product if you pledged to that. But because I'm a nice guy,
if you did pledge to the Pleeve and the Weeb Kickstarter, I will give, I can't give, I can't
give them for free because I had to buy all the materials, but I will give, I will steeply discount
the product. I'll give you like $20 off if you can show me proof that you are a, a $40 Kickstarter
backer, which was the reward which entitled you to the, to the Blu-ray if you pledged it. So I
don't know. Get, let me know about that. Yeah, we'll get to figure it out. Okay. Well, that's
my big announcement for this week. What do you guys got going on? Oh boy. The second episode with
Cheesy will have come out by now, I think, or will be coming out soon. You mean of the draw cast?
Yeah. Well, the second episode of the draw cast with Cheesy will come out, but it was actually
the one that was recorded first. Yeah. Because Cetol, the genius Cetol deleted their recording.
The genius smart man. What happened? The recording got deleted. Yeah. So was it destroyed? Was it,
was it ruined? Yeah, my laptop, I work on a laptop and it has fuck all memory. And it was
standard of the year. And I was, we'd done like three comics jams, like basically in a row. And
my recordings were getting corrupted because I didn't have enough space on the computer. I'm
like, oh, that's kind of shit. Yeah, that's kind of shit. I should start deleting some of these old
comics jams because they're kind of old. And I deleted the one Cheesy was on. I deleted the
one Cheesy was on accidentally. So, so you had to rerecord it? Oh, no, no, we did something else.
We did something ridiculous. The episode will be out probably the day after people see this,
so I don't mind spoiling it a bit. We kept the episode, at least the free other people's
audios, we kept me, Cheesy, and Gibb. Yeah, we give was on it too. Yeah. Yes. Gibb was on it.
Okay. And C.T.A.L. recorded commentary over the parts that were quiet during all the parts
where C.T.A.L. was talking. And I created a little pony vector like pack of C.T.A.L.
to do a little, a little brony analysis style commentary, you know, all the different faces.
And that's your answer. That's your answer to everything, Oblivion. Just make it. Why don't
you just make a pony vector about it? When all you've got, when all you've got is a pony vector,
everything looks like an analysis video. That's funny. He didn't make the vector for the video.
I paid him to make the vector because he lost his job. And so I wanted to never money. Then I'm
like, I don't know what I'm going to use this vector for. And then this happened. I'm like,
well now I know what I'm going to use this vector for. It's very silly. It's very good.
It's absolutely at least the quality of her brony analysis video. Yes. At least.
That amazing. Yeah. Can we, can we, can we clear that far? We did.
My horse moves. I think it's a bit too low. I don't think you can go lower than that. I don't
think you can really limbo that. My horse moves. Therefore, it's at least as good if not better
than some brony analysis videos. Four eyes. Yes. Why don't you explain what your deal is?
Oh yeah. I've just kind of been here. I'm an artist. I draw things. Oblivion.
That's me. I'm oblivion. I'm sorry. I'm not very good at explaining myself.
All right. Four eyes has relevance. I met oblivion a while ago and I do pictures for him.
Yeah. I have some, I have some relevance. Me and four eyes met on one fateful 9 11.
When he has paid money to join my Patreon server and we got talking. He was crazy. He was just
a fucking cool guy. And then he found out all this funny stuff about him that was good and funny.
Excuse me. I'm sick. Several years later. And I drew women with big tits for him.
Yes. Oh no. Didn't you say that four eyes was the voice of some iconic voicemail characters?
I wonder if you can recognize me. Well, that's what, well, I didn't know that,
but oblivion told me so and I believe him. Well, I mean, we can have a whole discussion of
about that after we go to the voicemail segment and we play the first voicemail,
which is a very spicy one. Oh, okay. There's a reason I'm here. I see.
Yeah. But like four eyes to regular PCP viewers. I mean, aside from designing my character for
the ComeZone videos, which I've talked about a few times before. You mean, you mean what's her
name? Thalia. Thalia. Yeah. The big booby demon girl. Yeah. Four eyes designed her. Yeah. We both
like worked together on the design and he did the art that was used in that video.
He gave me pointers and I did the design. The actual art that you see in the
ComeZone video is my art with his direction. Yeah. It's really good. And any old school
PCP fans who remember Roddy Fuckers, cop killers, frog fractions, all the drama with the analysis
and the big arc with Ms. Anfropony. I believe that Ms. Anfropony's icon that they were using
during all those videos was one drawn by four eyes. Back when I used to watch
Brony analysis videos as a wee teen, I was very absorbed into a lot of the pity stories that
a lot of people were bringing about. And I was like, oh, I feel bad for this guy. He has such a
oh man. I'm going to draw a picture of his pony. I gave it to him. Don't feel bad for Ms.
Anfropony. He's thriving. He is thriving. And he's not using it anymore. I've looked.
This image, I think. Let's see. Yeah, that's really old. The era of the pony avatar has
it's rare to see a pony avatar in the wild anymore. Yeah, he no longer uses this,
but he did for a long time. I was very surprised.
I love Ms. Anfropony. See him in the comments once in a while, which is nice.
He's around. Yeah, I see him around. He's around. Shout outs to Ms. Anfropony.
Okay. Yeah, good. Well, understandable. What else? I didn't do anything this week,
because I had coronavirus. I had coronavirus just long enough to ruin my Christmas and my New
Years. Because I was still. Me too. Congratulations. Yeah. Thanks. I was sick on Christmas. I felt
sick. I had a fever and I felt awful. Just terrible. And I thought I was over. I haven't
had any symptoms since basically since the last PCP, so basically a week now. I've had no symptoms,
but I tested myself yesterday, or no, day before yesterday, thinking I was over it for New Years.
And no, I was still positive. Sad times. So I'm just like, I got to get another test and I'm just
waiting until, well, when will I be? When will I be negative? When can I return to society?
Yeah, I got sick with. So I haven't just been at home. Just been working on the game. Just been
working really hard every day, all day, 24 hours a day, adding totally frivolous features to
slime and punishment, Phantom's Revenge. How dare you, Ben. Completely pointless, huge waste of
time. But I mean, aren't video games just a big waste of time anyway? So that's probably good,
actually. That's how I know I'm ready to do it. How dare Ben saying, make progress on his game,
thus driving up his Patreon dollars further away from me? I wouldn't call it progress,
exactly. I would call it wheel spinning. I would call it, I'm adding, basically what it is, is I'm
adding a bunch of frivolous features to the game that I didn't need, but that I keep thinking,
oh, this would be funny. Oh, that would, oh, that would be cute. And then I'll spend three days
doing it. And then that's three days that I don't have to spend doing the boring work of
making the itch page or figuring out how to upload on new grounds or et cetera, et cetera.
What else can you do? He already dabs. He already plays for it. He already dabs. I won't say,
I won't say exactly, but I will say that it, I feel exactly, I'm adding stuff that you can do in
Endless War. I'm adding stuff, that stuff as commands in a fandom's revenge. And it feels
just like it did when I was making Endless War in the first place, because I remember thinking,
like, the, what if you could do this stupid thing, lol, okay. And then I spent like two days just
being like, um, take a, take a, take a, take a, put that. Okay, now it works. Only this time,
I don't have to send it off to crack. So he can be like, this doesn't work at all. Here,
I redid it. And now it works. Now it just, now it just works because I'm doing it in Game Maker.
So nice. Phantom Horn can fish and dig through garbage and grow crops.
I'm speakable. Listen, stop spoiling it. Stop spoiling it.
It sounds like, it sounds like you're just remaking Stardew Valley, but with Phantom
Horn. I'm all for it. I'm not, I'm not going to say anything else.
Oh, that's great. For as you've been doing some game making.
Me? Yeah, you have some game. Oh yeah, I have. Wait, what? I mean, yes. I've, that was like,
that was like the beginning of the year though. It is the beginning of the year.
Oh, you're right. It was the beginning of last year. I did it a year ago. Yeah, no. Jesus.
A long time ago, I was doing game development. I was helping a friend with an RPG maker game.
And it, it's like a niche of a niche thing. So it's, I don't think it's worth plugging too much.
You know, if you know, like any RPG maker games that got popular back in the early
2010s, then, then you know what kind of game it's like. It's a fangame all for a game like that.
I have been helping somebody else recently, but I'm not directly helping. They just want
artwork and I'm good at providing artwork. I, I would hope I am at least. Yeah, so.
Before you said you were, you tell me you were like learning how to like make a game engine or
something. Oh, oh, that's a whole side thing. That's like, I'm learning to, I'm learning to
program and I want to build my own game engine because fuck learning how to use something like
Unity or RPG maker. There's so many limitations with those engines that make me go, why can't I just
do that? And that's a whole thing. I barely even started. I think I've got like some logic.
And why couldn't you? I mean, for RPG maker, especially there's a huge restriction with
what you can do there. But it's like, it's one of the easiest engines to learn because it,
it uses a, I think it's called low coding, where instead of actually typing out code,
you just put in commands and it just plays them in a sequence. It's, it's just a bunch of presets
that you play off. I know that a game maker has its own, like dedicated programming language,
right? Probably. It does. Yeah, GML. Yeah. I've been told that's pretty good, but it has its own
restrictions as well that make people go, why can't I just have an actual programming language?
GML Gay Mer Life. Oh, no. I, you know, I was, I was originally, my initial
thought was I was going to make Phantom's Revenge in RPG maker. But I found I,
I'm sure there would have been ways to do it, but it was, I was, I found it like impossible to do
like really basic things that I, like all, like I just wanted to rename the fucking health bar.
And I, I don't know. I couldn't figure out how to do it. I believe there is a way to do that,
but I think it only does it for certain things. I know in 2003, there's like a thing in the database
that lets you change a whole bunch of terms that the game uses. You can change like HP to
Googity Boogity and a new game to this closes the game, but secretly actually makes a new game.
There's just, I mean, those are like very basic restrictions that's like, why can't I just rename
it? Right? Yeah, because like, I don't know. I guess maybe if I had learned, what is it,
it runs on like Ruby, right? Is the scripting? Oh yeah, the old ones do. Anything, anything
before RPG maker MV uses Ruby. Once it reaches MV though, it uses, I think, I forget it's a Java
or JavaScript, but it's one of those two. Yeah. Well, I knew, I didn't know any Ruby. I knew,
I knew some GML. So I don't know. I was just, I was just like, I was struggling with that.
And then I was like, well, shit, if I can't, if I can't, I'm having, if I'm having so much
trouble figuring out something as basic as just changing the name of like a function in the game,
it's like, well, I feel like I'm going to be like struggling against this system the whole time.
And I should probably just like, yeah, that's the problem with the, I'm just going to use GML.
That's the problem with RPG maker, like development in general, when a lot of people go
into it because it's an easy engine to learn. It seems like it really, really is set up with the
idea that it is, it is to make it as easy as possible to make a like the most generic RPG.
Yeah. You can imagine. And, and like, you can deviate from that, but like,
you have to do a lot of juggling around. You have to like, you have to work for it. Yeah.
I, I fucking had to do so much shit in RP, or like in 2003 alone, it's actually the most versatile
one as far as I'm concerned, but that might just be because I'm very knowledgeable in it.
But like, if you ever want to do anything in a, in that engine, you have, you can't really
rely on the engine itself. So you want like a character to be like half a half a tile across,
like if you really want to have this very specific thing happen, then you can't actually
use them to walk half a tile, you need to have like, you need to make the illusion of someone
walking, AKA like put a picture on screen and have it move. And in that case, you're basically
just building an engine on top of RPG maker as you start building more and more things that you
don't want from the game. And that's the limitation that RPG maker developers really have. They want
to do something more. But the problem is the engine is optimized in such a way to only do
you know, this one thing. Yeah, it's a, you gotta work within the restrictions. And if
you're knowledgeable, maybe you can make something impressive. RPG maker seems like it's set up so
that like basically a child can like turn it on and make something that is technically an RPG.
Yes, that's pretty much it. Yeah, it's yeah, you just see so many of these. Oh yeah, cool. My guy
has HP and he's got a little bar and he can do spells and it's technically it's a video game.
Yeah, that's why you see so much, you know, just free, very trashy RPG maker games. It's why,
in fact, the RPG aspect of RPG maker is often so confusing for people that they don't even make it
for RPGs. The most popular RPG maker games come to think of it are all like top down survival
horror type things where you don't fight things, you just walk around and try to run away from
other creatures because it's easier to just deal with the overworld than it is the combat balance
because I've tried messing with it is so confusing. They do things in like, I guess if you understand
it, it makes sense. But like, you just think, why can't I have like a character do this action on
this turn? You can't tell what you can't force like anything to happen cinematically in a battle.
And it's really, it's really annoying. Yeah. Yeah. I know that didn't didn't
undertale start development and RPG maker and then get ported to a game maker at some point.
I think I read that somewhere. I don't remember that. But I do know that Delta Rune was originally
going to be done on a different engine. But eventually, Toby Fox was just like, yeah, no,
learning this new engine isn't really going to help. I've got like years of experience in
game maker already. So I'll just stick with that. Yeah, I feel like I've reached I feel like I've
reached a point where I am just like, I just kind of like know how to do a thing. And I just am not
I'm no longer like, how do I do this? How do you know, because when I started out, you have to like
look shit up. Oh, yeah, tell you learn to code. You just fucking open up the wiki or whatever,
and you just open up like a guy and you got to look shit up. And now I'm kind of just like,
I mostly know. I mostly know what I'm doing. Yeah, I mean, it's just a matter of cranking out the
functions that I know and need to be in there. Programming does become a little bit easier when
you finally just kind of accept it as a combination of problem solving and abstract thinking,
because you're not really dealing with a cup being filled with water. Make an object,
make an object, set up, set a flag, you know, have one object, you know, turn its flat set state
to weight, you know, change sprite, speak in timer, set timer flags, object instance destroy,
you know, create a different object, literally just got to take all the information of like an
object and just put it into a bunch of numbers and booleans and other buzzwords that I hate.
Boolean. Boolean. That's right. That's right. Booleans, more Booleans, please.
Yeah. Maybe a child Boolean. Yeah. Fucked up that RPG maker doesn't actually like make a
differentiation. It doesn't really make a difference. Oh my god, differentiate the
the difference between a variable and a switch because technically there is none.
Because a switch is just a Boolean and a Boolean is a variable. Whereas a variable in RPG maker
is an integer and that it makes it so confusing when translating it to actual programming.
Oh god. Yeah. Oh my god. Oh my god. What the fuck. All to make it hip and sick for the people who
don't understand. Like me. I can follow well enough. I know you sat excited to be talking about it,
so that's good enough for me. I love it. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah, so that's what I've been
that's what I've been doing. I've been making video games and waiting until COVID goes away
so I can go take promo pictures of the Blu-rays. Bleeming the wee Blu-rays. They're real. I actually
made them for years. For years. People be where's the Blu-rays? Trixie, where's the Blu-rays?
I paid you money for the Blu-rays. I gave $40 so I could buy the Blu-ray. I did it. I did it. I
made them. I made them. I made them real. I brought them out of the void into reality.
I have a big box of them. Wouldn't it be kind of funny if Trixie bought them all from you to give
to the people who paid her money? No. That's stupid. She would never do such a thing.
She would never do such a thing. That's what she ought to do. She ought to pay me. She ought to pay
me for satisfying her demand. If she gave me the plebe and the weeb money, then I would give the
copies for free to the people that already paid for the Kickstarter. But since I don't have that
money, I can't do that. I can't honor those people's purchases, even though I would like to,
because it would put me at a net loss. That's just not acceptable. You can't operate a business
in the negatives. That's true. Unless you have a name in some Jeffrey Bezos.
Sure. Or any number of tech startup geniuses.
Uber runs at a loss. YouTube is still running at a loss. That's pretty crazy.
Hasn't YouTube always run at a loss? It has. Not even all the YouTube red
subscriptions and stuff could salvage it. But it just keeps going.
And it needs storage. And it always will.
For all the weird stuff people put on YouTube.
It needs to exist, so it must. It simply has to exist, no matter of the cost.
I have a story. I have a funny story from the My Little Pony days. I'm a horror story, if you
will. So in 2014, I used to be a part of a bunch of... Back when everyone had their Skype groups
that everyone was adding each other to for projects, like, oh, we're going to read a fan
fiction and we need voice actors. We're going to make a little My Little Pony fan animation,
whatever. And they just get your friends to make you join or whatever the fuck.
Like you do. Like you do.
Yeah. There was one project called Journey of the Spark that had a bit of traction.
These guys were like, hey, let's make an entire movie. An entire movie made by the fans.
And they had this trailer. And the animation was sort of half okay.
Have I heard about this?
Possibly. Journey of the Spark, maybe.
Sounds familiar.
Journey of the Spark. It sort of rings a bell.
They got panels at conventions several times. I can post some of the posters and promo images.
Maybe you'll recognize one. Let's see. There's that one.
Oh, I do remember this. Let me see here. Oh, wow. Look at that background.
So this was a project I'd heard of for a while. I got invited onto it when
the director of the project auditioned for one of my projects I was running with my partner.
And them, sorry, they've transitioned since. So like all my memories are with male pronouns.
So I'm going to try my best to use female pronouns. I apologize in advance if I mess up.
She was talking to my partner. I guess my partner's also transitioned since then.
And like opposite directions. Whoa. Anyways.
Wait, somebody else did too?
All right. My partner was identified as female back then and is now male.
And for this person, it's the other way around. And I just find that funny.
It's the nature of my little party.
Wait, one of the producers?
Yeah. The person whose last name was right now or something.
So anyway, they were like the person.
What's their name now?
The name now is a spoiler. It's funny and you'll find out why later.
ContraPoints.
Natalie Win, producer of Journey of the Spark.
That would be fucking funny as fuck dude.
No.
So Journey of the Spark had, like I'd heard of it. I'd seen the trailers.
They got a lot of views. I knew they had panels at conventions.
And the director, the person in charge of the whole project,
auditioned for our projects. We spoke to them and they invited us on.
And when we joined the Skype group, immediately there's a red flag.
Because as we're joining, we're seeing like 20 people leave
and a couple of them are being like, hey, just warning you,
you're going to have a bad time. Get out where you can.
And then like dropping out of the chat.
Wow. So this is you like basically like asking, like,
can I be involved in this project? And a bunch of people involved in the project
are like, don't make the same mistake I did.
You're walking into a burning building.
Yeah. Like, and the second we got in the server,
like half the people were like in the process of leaving,
like within like that hour, pretty much.
And we didn't really find out what happened.
The old head of animation was a guy called Jan.
I don't know if it was Jan animations.
I was going to say as in Jan animations.
I mean, possibly I never got it confirmed.
Someone said that it was, but I don't know if they were correct.
Reena Chan, also Kara Buckland, was also involved in the project at a time.
Who's Reena Chan?
She was fat.
The voice actor, right?
She was a voice actor.
She voiced in a lot of old Newgrounds animations.
Did you say she was fat?
Is that the first thing that comes to mind?
She's not fat. I don't think I said that.
Sorry, my voice.
I am having a...
He said that I said PHH as in sick.
We swear.
I thought that was what you said, but I may have misheard.
I don't even know what I said.
I can't raise my voice because my voice like literally goes on mute like in a real life.
If I shout, my voice just goes...
But that's a voice actress, right?
Yeah, Reena Chan.
Oh, oh, oh, Reena Chan is Kara Buckland.
Is Kara Buckland, yeah.
She's popular now because she voiced to be in the English dub of Nier,
which is trash, play the game in Japanese.
But yeah, what was I saying?
So, you know, the project had some notable names in it.
Some of these people, like bigger names, hadn't left.
So we had some faith in the project.
And the director was very friendly with my partner.
And they had a lot of calls together.
And we quickly found out that the lead voice actress for Twilight Sparkle,
I believe her name was Meredith Sims.
I think she voiced some characters for Silly Philly Studios.
I think she was the voice of Snowdrop maybe in the Snowdrop animation.
I don't remember too clearly.
Who could forget Snowdrop?
Legendary, legendary short.
Snow Blind.
Snow, Snow Blind, yeah.
Oh, shit, what was I saying?
So apparently the director had been having some issues with Meredith's, I guess, acting ability.
Because they were recording some lines for a trailer.
They wanted to debut at a convention.
And there were some scenes where Twilight had to be crying.
And just didn't feel the emotion was coming across.
She couldn't do it.
Like, obviously she could do it.
But just didn't think the emotions felt genuine enough, you know?
Which is always like the biggest thing the voice acting is.
Everyone thinks they can do a good impression.
I guess that's the director's job is to get the right performance out of their actors.
They brought my partner on to be the voice director specifically.
So they're like the head of project.
And my partner was going to be working with them as the voice director,
giving direction to the voice actors and working with them.
Oh.
So that was what my partner's job was going to be.
Was this a paid gig, by the way?
No.
Or was it just a fan?
Nothing, nothing.
It's cost, cost, okay, okay.
This was a pony community.
No one got paid for anything back then.
Okay, okay, I understand.
Which every time people make fun of KP for not paying people,
I'm like, dude, it's a fucking pony community.
No one gets paid ever.
Yeah, nobody, nobody, nobody got paid.
Yeah.
But anyway, so that's fair.
So yeah, the director was to my partner.
Oh, hey, why don't you record some sample lines for them to reference?
So my partner did.
And my partner also had a pretty decent Twilight Sparkle impression.
My partner was pretty decent at acting.
So they did that.
And the director was like, oh, oh my God, your Twilight voice is actually really good.
It's actually really good.
Like, ah.
Oh no.
You know, originally when we started the project, I got Meredith on board,
you know, back before I really had, before I really had a team.
She was just a friend I had.
And, you know, I brought her on board because, you know.
And now she's just, now she's just a dead weight anchor around my ankle,
weighing us down, dragging us down.
This project is done.
But now, now this project has scope and we're gonna make this.
And now that this project has scope and potential and, you know,
we can make this first fan animated movie, something that's never been achieved before.
You know, it was two hour feature length like Disney quality film that us unpaid
Bronies are totally going to be able to make.
Totally.
It'll definitely happen.
That's right.
All it takes is grit and gumption and elbow grease and a lot of, and love of the, of the
source material.
You know, maybe exactly.
All it takes is passion.
Yeah.
Maybe it'll be worth like having you takeovers when you twilight,
you know, sparkle voice actor for this project.
And my partner's like, oh, me?
This is a, this is a, this is a what's not, not a, not a my fair lady moment.
It's like a, like a, like a, I don't know.
What's a movie where it's like a Cinderella moment.
Like, oh, the shoe fits, the shoe fits better.
Right.
So the, the funny undertone of this is like the surface reading is, oh,
they just thought the voice was better.
And they had also hinted a lot that they had a crush on the old Twilight voice actor at the time.
And they at some point confessed that they were crushing on my partner as well.
And like, they just have a thing for any, anyone who happens to be voicing Twilight.
That's the impression I get.
So like, it's, it's funny.
All right. So this is a very, I'm glad, I'm glad everyone's a professional in this.
I'm glad everyone's a professional.
Stupid scenario.
So it's like, they, they, they, they like confess a lot of things.
They, they told my partner about the inflation porn.
They're like, they really liked a blueberry inflation porn.
Um, that was like a big thing for them.
What is it?
What is it with these people and inflation?
You know, they just watched Willy Wonka and it just had an effect on them.
You know, they got, they got to have that blueberry inflation.
It's, it's, it's part of the balanced breakfast.
Everyone has a moment in their childhood where they see some weird shit that they really like.
And that was theirs, you know.
Wait, what the fuck?
There's a fucking blueberry inflation Funko Pop.
Hold on.
What?
What the fuck?
Oh no.
Yeah, that sounds, that sounds about right.
That's fucking stupid.
That's hilarious.
Why is that?
What was that shit?
I, I, I am, hold on.
Hostessly.
It's slight distraction.
We got to see it.
There you go.
Oh my God.
Violet Beauregard.
Amazing.
It's how tragic that this is the Violet Beauregard Funko Pop.
Like this isn't what she normally looks like.
This is her with like a medical condition.
And it's, we caught a shiny, we caught a shiny variant.
Yeah.
Well.
Anyways, so this was going on.
And eventually the director went to Meredith and,
and told them that they wanted to replace her.
And when they did, they suddenly were like,
yeah, this new voice directors, they're really pushy
and they're manipulating me and they said they don't like you
and they want you off the project.
And I just have no choice.
Like they just made up all this bullshit
because they didn't want to hurt their friends feelings.
They wanted to shift blame.
And I know this is a case because they immediately messaged my partner and said,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I said all these things that weren't true.
If you're going to lie, if you're going to lie,
why not just stick to your fucking story?
Why not just lie then?
Just, I don't know.
And then Meredith, who had a lot of connections, told everyone,
oh, yeah, watch out for oblivion's partner,
very manipulator and all this shit.
And I had a bunch of like big people.
That's true.
Including Rob Bob, who.
I heard, I heard from a guy that that's true.
Yeah, I had.
I heard from the director.
The director of Journey of the Spark, the famous director.
My friend, my friend, E ride an hour.
Careful.
A.K.A. Natalie Wynn.
I was going to say, don't be dead naming now.
So anyway, I don't close enough, a dead initialing, maybe.
Their new name is not E.
Actually, no, it was for a while.
They were Erica and then they changed to something else
that I'll get to.
So they said that and we were really upset.
Like, why are you doing this?
Like, now my partner's reputation is in trouble
and I had to try and do damage control.
The guy Rob Bob I mentioned was like,
he had huge industry connections.
He got Gray Delisle to voice in an animation project
that we were working on once.
Gray Delisle?
Gray Delisle.
She's voiced about as many or more characters
than Tara Strong, including like Frankie Foster
from Foster's Imaginary, whatever the fuck.
Azula from Avatar.
She's the voice of Azula.
Oh, wait.
Okay.
What's what's your name?
Gray Delisle.
The Azula Jeth.
Yeah.
Great.
Gray Delisle is like super legit.
I'll just link her wiki page.
Oh, sure.
Okay.
But yeah, so the guy who had connections to like her
was even like caring about it.
And so that was like, that really bothered me.
I was really like, okay.
So I was having to do damage control on that level.
And so I was really pissed at the director at this point.
And then we realized that like we found out
from other people who left the project
that this is like a repeating cycle
and that that was actually the second way if you left.
There was one even before that.
And so we were like, oh, and then things were
really sour with the director from then on.
And after like a few weeks, I was supposed to help
with the trailer, but I was just like,
I don't want to work for this person anymore.
I mean, my partner at a certain point
was just like, yeah, now we're leaving and we dropped out.
And then the project kept going.
Half the team dropped out with us.
And then a new team was brought on,
including a friend of mine, my friend Phoenix.
And then they kept going around to conventions
for about a year afterwards.
And at a certain point I was realizing like,
Hasbro's got to send them a cease and desist at some point.
For one, like after a year,
if I couldn't even get a trailer done,
they think they can get like an over two hour long like a movie.
Oh, that's bad.
That's bad.
Yeah.
And they think animators,
including people who I'm friends with,
I believe in this project and are throwing away their like labor
for someone who isn't paying them
for a project that'll never even come out.
Because it's guaranteed to never be finished.
Or I mean, if it gets close enough to being finished,
Hasbro's not going to let you make a fucking movie.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
So I was like, I am going to message Hasbro.
I still had access to all the drop boxes.
I still had access to all the information.
I downloaded a lot of it, checked over the script,
checked over some of the details.
And I sent Hasbro, I found their contact,
their legal contact.
And I sent them a message because in my mind,
I'm like, this project is doomed anyway.
I am just freeing these animators early
so that they can actually focus on things
that'll actually come to fruition.
I'm doing the right thing.
Yeah.
I'm the good guy.
I'm the oblivion full breaker of chains.
Breaker of chains.
Wait, what so what information?
What information did you have access to in the drop boxes?
Basically just like the script and storyboard,
basically certain plot details,
including like Celestia dying and stuff,
which I messaged Hasbro.
I said, hey, just letting you know
there's this project being worked on.
Here's like some conventions where they showed it off.
You're a whistleblower.
I was a whistleblower.
And I explained some of its plot details
and in the story like Celestia dies
and there's all this dark stuff.
And I don't think that'll fit with your brand image
and all this, this and that.
And I left like a few paragraphs
and I linked to some videos and some things
so that they could have evidence
that this project was legit
or at least it was taking itself pretty legit.
Who did you contact at Hasbro?
I just contacted, I just Googled Hasbro legal or something.
Like customer service?
Or customer service or something.
I don't remember what, this was like mid 2014 at this point.
So this was like seven years ago.
And I got an email back like that day
and I wish I still had it.
Oh my God, I wish I fucking had this email.
It was amazing.
If I can paraphrase, it was something to be effect of,
hi, thank you for giving us this information.
We take this very seriously.
Intellectual property theft is no joke.
And we will take swift legal action at the appropriate time.
Have a smiley day.
So what you're saying is that the director
was absolutely correct.
You are a backstabber.
Yes, well, at this point, I mean they said I was in the back.
We're a back re-stabber.
We're just putting, we're just giving the knife actor
it's rightful owner.
Hey, it's like you stab my back.
I stab yours, buddy.
You know, we can help each other out.
We help each other to die.
Yes.
Two weeks later on their Tumblr.
Hey guys, we got a cease and desist,
but we're not giving up hope.
And I'm like, okay, okay.
Oh boy.
But the project basically never had legs after that ever again.
And the animator friends I had on there did leave
and did go on to better things and good for them.
How much, so how much was, okay, how long had it been going on
and how much was done by that point?
I think like, from what they told us,
they had started working on it like early 2012,
like maybe like in the scripting stage,
like very beginning of 2012, they had the idea.
So it had been going for a year plus, maybe almost two years.
Well, this is like mid 2014.
So it was a bit over two years at this point,
maybe two and a half years of production and like going for
like three or four different teams worth of people.
But so the project never really had legs again,
but the director sort of stuck around and sort of like,
I posted about it for a while and that's,
and like checking up on their Tumblr to see like how it was going.
That's when we learned about the transition.
They changed her name to Erica at first.
And then a little while later, if you change her name to something else,
your name now is Violet.
I'm just looking at that Funko Pop.
That explains a lot.
That's funny.
She's just really exiting guys, I swear.
She just really likes your name.
That's pretty humorous.
The name just speaks to me, you know?
Like it's a chuckle out of me.
Yeah.
Yeah, fascinating.
Well, that was a journey of the spark.
You were taking me on that journey with you.
That journey of the spark, yeah.
Of the spark, all right, all right, yeah, of course.
That fan of had a lot of shit going about it.
Oh yeah, there's a number one that's pretty good actually,
that Faye can comment on.
So I don't know, actually, no, of course you remember,
you were a fucking My Little Pony analyst.
You probably talked about this character on T-Bap.
Do you remember this wheelchair pony from Tradia?
Yes, the purple and brown guy, yeah.
The Make-A-Wish guy.
Yeah, with the steampunk wheels.
Yeah, I remember this guy standing out to me
when I first saw the episode.
I'm like, this guy's weird and some YouTube comments were like,
oh, it's a Make-A-Wish kid.
He got a Make-A-Wish to be in the show.
And I'm like, oh, that's cool or whatever.
A few months afterwards, I got messaged by a friend on Facebook,
someone who is not a brony.
So in no relation to it, he'd sent me a Tumblr post saying,
oh my God, these bronies are sick.
Did you know that there was a Make-A-Wish kid in My Little Pony?
And they drew porn.
They drew hundreds of porn images of this child in My Little Pony.
Bronies, oh, they're so sick and twisted.
How dare they do this?
They're all fucked up.
And I was like, oh, let me check Derpy Breeru,
see how many images there actually are.
And there was less than 20 after many months.
And I'm like, that's nothing.
I told my friend, there's not really that many images.
And it looks like it's just two artists.
So I don't think it's that widespread of a problem.
So it seems like a valid reason to be concerned.
What I didn't know at the time, because I didn't know him yet,
the artist responsible was Four Eyes.
Well, Four Eyes, what do you have to say for yourself?
I'd do it again.
And I did.
What's your, well, officer, he says he'd do it again.
And we can't arrest him if he's not sorry.
I'm guilty, but it's fine.
It's fine, he wasn't actually a minor.
The kid wasn't actually a minor.
It's fine.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, is that true?
Yeah, this Make-A-Wish kid was 18, first of all.
Faye, you tell the story to me or you actually talk to him.
Yeah, the whole scandal happened.
And as far as I know, nobody even knew that it was me that did it.
People just kind of saw that like me and like one other person
like did some vaguely not-safe work images and just labeled it all as bronies.
And I think during the whole scandal, the person was not present.
The guy behind the OC was not present at all.
But his mother was commenting on Derpy Boo, sending
asks to people on Tumblr saying, this is destroying my son's life.
He's ruining his reputation.
He's crying.
He's dying.
He's from Make-A-Wish, he's dying.
He literally was dying, right?
Sort of.
Is he alive?
He's still alive.
Yes, because about a few months after the whole thing settled down,
the guy specifically came to me on DeviantArt.
He gave me a private message on DeviantArt saying,
hey, I'm sorry for the way my mother was acting.
I'm actually over 18.
I really actually enjoy all the fan art that I've been getting of my character.
And I'm horny as fuck.
They apparently are completely fine with it
and have commissioned plenty of artworks off their character in NSFW situations.
Getting fucked in the ass by Discord.
No, that was just me.
They paid people to draw him fucking fore-eyes.
Yeah, that was what he paid one artist to draw as a gift back like,
hey, here's my character having sex with your character.
It's like, oh, thanks.
I'm glad there was a happy ending forever.
Happy ending.
He was okay with it and he didn't even die.
He didn't even die.
I don't know how much I can share.
I don't know how much I can share his illness.
I hope he's not listening.
This is going to sound...
I mean, it's fine.
Wait, what?
I think he's fine with it.
You don't know if he can share his illness?
I can't really share the details of it,
because one, I haven't really asked him much about it,
but he's talked about it sometimes.
I don't know.
I just thought that if you're a make-a-wish kid, it means you're going to die soon.
It's a...
So, you know, I was expecting...
I was, you know, I was hoping for a death.
They ripped me off.
My little pony told me that kid was going to die, damn it.
Well, I mean, he still has something.
I mean, it's been like years.
It's been years since that episode.
Like, guy, come on, like, clock's ticking.
Like, how many...
Like, are you going to keep us waiting for, like, how much longer here?
I can at least say it's not...
It is life-threatening, just not immediately.
It's something about how he'll only get worse and worse with age,
until he's basically incapable of handling himself.
So, while he is still capable of handling himself, he got a make-a-wish.
I'm...
I'm sorry to be so grim about it.
It's absolutely fine.
I'm pretty sure he's fine with it.
I don't actually want...
I don't actually want this kid to die.
I mean, he's happy.
He's like...
He's still making art.
He actually makes his own art.
Well, good.
Oh, good for him.
Very funny.
Yeah, I remember people commenting on the...
You know, the character is just...
It's just a little bit OC-looking, even before the kind of notable steampunk wheelchair,
which is a bit funny.
The colors are just a bit too dark, you know?
People make fun of...
The what?
The colors of his...
The color palette of his OC is just a little bit too not pastel, basically.
Yeah, yeah, a little bit too...
It looks like a fan character.
Yeah.
You know, I guess the steampunk wheelchair, you know, maybe that's like...
Maybe that's not fair.
Like, I mean, I guess it does kind of look like...
What do you call it?
I mean, they're more like training wheels.
A little bit, yeah.
Right, it's like the thing that you give like a dog that legs don't work, right?
Well, he is a horse.
Maybe it's supposed to resemble like a cantorlot, you know,
cantorlot architecture, which it kind of does.
I mean, in plenty of the images I've seen of his character that he's commissioned,
he's always in pretty fancy bedrooms, so maybe.
Well...
This is my game theory.
Thanks, Matt Pat.
Where would we be without you and your porn theories?
My knowledge of the dark side.
I'm barely even there anymore.
I'm a pretty shallow consumer of this stuff nowadays.
All right, all right.
That's fine, you know, whatever.
Very wax, very weird.
I'm actually kind of glad to know that the kid didn't die.
Yeah.
Yet.
That's kind of nice.
That's a bit heartwarming.
He's still doing good.
We'll all die eventually, Ben.
It's okay.
Yeah, we'll get him.
We all say to get your blood less yet.
So...
Yeah, I don't know.
Tell me more.
Tell me more stories.
I got nothing else to talk about.
Uneventful week.
Uneventful week for me.
I mean, I've just been fucking sick too.
I would have had my animation that I've been working on for months out by the end of the year,
except that I got sick.
Don't know if it's COVID.
We can't seem to find a test where we're at.
Yeah.
I mean, even before that work was...
I was amazed that I could find some in CVS.
I was shocked that they had some available.
But they're out now.
I went the other day and I asked again and they're like,
nope, we're out.
And so I'm...
Yeah, all the places around here seem to be out.
But it kind of ruined all my plans.
Like, I was fine on Christmas, but like by...
No kidding.
That night, like when I woke up the day after Christmas,
I was just, there was a boulder in my throat.
I felt like it was...
Oh, so you definitely, so you definitely spread it.
You definitely were being a super spreader.
No, I wasn't leaving the house.
Our roommate who works at a movie theater brought it home
and gave it to all of us who sit indoors all day.
Oh, okay.
It was his Christmas present to you.
Yeah, I didn't go out for Christmas.
Okay.
But yeah, and that kind of...
I was bedridden for a while and my voice is all fucked up.
If I try to raise my voice, it just cuts out.
And I'm really worried that people aren't going to understand
what I'm saying sometimes because my voice just keeps going.
When I speak.
But um, oh God.
That was a hard cut off.
Yeah, I...
When I was able to at least not be in absolute pain and agony,
I've been drawing a bit, I've been working on music,
but not my main project because I already realized
I'm not a misfit deadline.
Did you have a fever?
I had a fucking bad fever.
I couldn't even sleep.
I was so, it was so hot.
I was all around six hours one night.
That was my experience.
That was the only thing that really was bad.
I didn't cough that much.
Didn't have much of a runny nose or anything.
Not my first.
There was a fever and the chills and I couldn't lay down.
I didn't get headaches, but I couldn't lie down
without sweating profusely.
And then I'd sit up and I'd feel cold and I'd be shivering.
And I'd be like, I can't tell how hot it is.
I can't tell what temperature it is in this room.
Am I just imagining the cold or is it real?
Yeah, that's what my partner's been going through.
They have it really bad.
I'll feel them.
I feel like he's blasting off their skin like a fucking oven
and they tell me that they're freezing cold.
And I'm like, no, you're not getting the extra blanket.
I'm sorry.
Even though they think they're shivering.
I experienced that a little bit.
My partner's immune system's a lot worse than mine though.
I've been taking care of them because
they caught it slightly later than me.
But yeah, we think it's COVID.
Like we've spoken to our other friends who caught it recently
and they've all described pretty much the same thing.
And yeah, that's probably what's happened.
We don't have our booster.
We're not eligible for a couple more weeks
because it hasn't been six months yet.
I don't think, I don't know if it makes that much of a difference.
Maybe it does.
Omicron though.
Omicron doesn't give a fuck.
I mean, it does a little bit.
It might be Omicron for all I know.
I caught regular COVID in early like 2020
and it was a little bit different.
I guess it depends.
Omicron might not be dominant everywhere yet,
but it probably will be soon.
If it is, I will have had COVID twice in my life.
So, woof.
Iki, icky, icky, icky sticky.
Iki, icky, no, thank you.
I mean, I guess if we don't have a lot of things to talk about,
we could go to that voicemail thing
because there's going to be a lot of discussion
to happen afterwards.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I mean, yeah, why not?
Why not just get the ball rolling on that, I guess.
Oh, yeah.
Do you want to post it?
All right.
Dropping voicemail finale in...
Oh, it's taken a bit.
It's a bit long.
It's like horseshoe finale.
We're going to be here for several hours.
There's a lot of loose threads.
Horseshoe finale.
Jesse Wood, plebe and the weeb.
Plebe and the weeb blue rays available now.
Send me money.
Send me PayPal, me $30 plus shipping.
Get a fucking DVD.
Wow, can you fucking believe physical media still exists?
I can't.
Fred, how much will shipping be?
You're in Australia or some shit, right?
I am in Australia.
Or some shit.
Okay, now maybe something's changed.
After Christmas, the shipping has changed.
I know because my friend's sending me a computer part.
So it might be viable again.
America will...
The US post office will not ship just fucking ship to Australia.
Although it might have gone back to that.
But for a while there, it simply would not do it.
Shipping is $5 inside America.
$15 to other countries.
But Australia, New Zealand, I can't do it.
It's like $90.
It's like $90 to ship some...
What's a communist for America?
It's because...
Yeah, it's like the COVID lockdown something was like,
well, first class mail just doesn't go to Australia anymore.
You have to send it some other fucking way.
And it costs like a hundred bucks.
Yeah, maybe check a game soon, see if it's...
If someone...
Yeah, so I'm gonna...
Since you gave me that burner.
So I'll just give you one.
I'll just have to wait until that is no longer the case.
Yeah, it's okay.
I'm fine to pay for shipping.
That's like shipping to drag.
Yeah, I don't want to...
Yeah, but that's too much.
So if you're a listener and you're in Australia...
Sorry, but if you buy one, it will be $15.
And I will just wait until the shipping is normal.
And then I'll send it after it becomes normal.
Like whenever that happens.
Yeah.
And then we have $5 or $15 if you're out of the country.
Was it...
Wait, $5 shipping in America.
$15 to other countries.
Base price is $30, but if you are a Patreon...
If you are a Kickstarter...
$40 pleadingly Kickstarter backer, I will.
Purely out of the goodness of my heart, by the way.
Purely, this is pure charity.
I'll give you $20 off, right?
So if you were a backer in America,
it would cost you $15, including shipping.
Right?
That's how it works.
PayPal me at IASUcomic is my PayPal email address.
Send me the money.
Include your shipping address.
Patreon.com.
That's...
Oh, shit.
I've been hijacked.
All right, sorry.
Anyway, voicemail finale.
Oh god, it's four minutes.
There's no such thing as a voicemail
that could possibly justify it being four minutes long.
Look, no, it's fine, Ben.
That's what you think, Ben.
Just wait.
All right.
All right, let's do it.
Three, two, one, go.
I've done it.
I finally made it all the way back to this
miserable cum sock of a planet.
Earth.
Home of the PCP.
The elite cabal who banished me to the Twilight Realm.
Voice limbo.
I toppled the king from his throne
and bore this tape from his bone.
This is the final tape.
My swan song to you.
All right.
This tape will self-destruct.
What?
Oh boy.
It's happening now.
Oh.
Take a sip, babes.
Delicious.
First voicemail of the day in heck.
Ben St. didn't even bother to check.
Just how many of these voicemail suckers
want to be, want to be, league of nate fuckers?
Cook up a carb-filled savory plan.
Don't do keto or you'll be in strife.
Just take a bite and change your life.
Voice grail for life.
I'm a fucking pile of snakes.
Oh well, nothing until I wipe cough,
wipe my grit and pull out my quark.
Aim for Michelle as I start to suck.
Oh my god, she's such a croc.
Voice grail for life.
I am Ben St's worst nightmare.
I sure gave him quite a scare.
He wants to put me in the brig.
Cause I'm a fat, interrupting, non-specific farm animal.
Yeah.
Voice grail for life.
This podcast has gone too long.
I will now complain in song.
If no nate, then I won't watch.
I'll just torture Ben St's crotch.
Voice grail for life.
I've got a question here for Nate.
I'm sorry if this comes in late.
I just-
I hate this podcast.
I fucking hate it.
I can't do a single point
without literally every single host
constantly like vultures
trying to jump on me
and cannibalize my point.
Clear words unrecognized.
Okay, stopping.
And with that, my work is done.
Finally, my inner peace.
Oh god, it hurts.
Why do I put these things in my fucking face?
Pound of beef in the pan.
What seems to be the problem, man?
My tape.
No, so sad.
He got shot.
The gun, a recipe for death.
But there are more recipes to share in part two.
Oh god, there's more.
The second part's shorter, don't worry.
I feel like this is actually the finale
of all voicemails
and we can't have any more voicemails after this.
Like it's over.
It's almost over.
There's a few characters
who have yet to have conclusions.
But rest in peace, tapekeeper.
You will be missed.
Yeah, that's the tapekeeper.
Wait, from lesbian horse RPG.
Yeah.
Right?
Is this always, has this been the lore the whole time?
Yes.
Okay.
Literally the best character in that game.
Well, yeah, I remember voicing this character
in TBAP plays.
I talked inward.
I did an inward voice breathing in voice like this.
Dude, I fucking love that let's play so much.
Oh god, my COVID.
Oh, that really activates my,
that really activates my,
that really activates my antigens.
That really gets my spike proteins.
Jocelyn, yeah, vibrating.
Oh boy.
Vibrating with motion.
Oh my god.
Well, Mal.
I recently watched like several reviews of that fucking game.
It's so fun to watch people rip into that.
Have you seen to Snaker's review?
I have not actually.
He was on the PCP a few weeks ago.
He has one of, I think his and his and Running Shine's
are my two favorite yick reviews.
Oh yeah.
In the crowded genre of YouTube yick reviews,
those two are head and shoulders.
In general, Running Shine is very entertaining.
I rewatch his stuff every now and then.
Pretty fun guy.
Sure, yeah, I like Running Shine.
I need to look up to Snaker's now.
I will absolutely watch him.
That's a good one.
Yes.
All right, voicemail finale revelations.
This is part two, I guess.
Are we ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Are you ready?
Eleazar, cut that part out where I got, where it stopped.
We could just pretend that didn't happen.
Just, I'll be cutting it because I'll edit this episode.
Okay.
Yeah.
Pre Eleazar.
Oh wait, that's right.
You're editing this episode because Eleazar is gone.
He's on a trip for like a week, yeah.
He's on holiday.
Eleazar, beta.
Oh, good for him.
Anyway, that's the side of the point.
Voicemail finale.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Apple seeds, buy the pound.
Crush them all the way.
Blend it well.
Almond smell.
Cheeseless.
Cyanine, sense you to hell.
Press for paste into a pill.
That's good kill.
I put the pill between my teeth.
Take a bite and you're live.
Rest in peace.
Press F.
Tito Kitchen.
What a fucking moron.
Imagine killing yourself.
Quinn.
Classic.
It appears I have a snake confession to make.
For four years I have slivered this planet.
Yet none know my true nature.
I have always identified as 28,980 snakes.
But in reality, I am simply one very lonely snake.
With 28,979 snitch-shaped tumors.
This begins.
The then snakes cancer arc.
Make a wish.
It's finally time that I unplug my voice filter.
My voice filter, which just so happens to be connected to my life's support system.
I will die.
But at least I can gaze upon Ben St.
with my lone eyes.
This ends.
The then snakes cancer arc.
Short but sweet.
Them snakes.
Oh, oh, there they are.
It would seem that I'm not dead yet.
Hello, hello.
Snakes, are you are you feeling all right after unplugging your life's support?
You do.
I may have been overdramatic.
This voice is really fucking hard to do when I have COVID.
What the fuck?
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, and cancer and damn COVID and cancer.
That's brutal.
I'm so sorry.
It's COVID.
Must be rough.
Three of your, well, one of you and two tumors, I guess, are here in the hall.
We're here for moral support.
Where the dearest, roundest, floppiest turn is a snake could ask for.
Oh boy.
I call them keto kitchen.
I'm in Cluster Punk Kitchen.
Yeah.
Cluster Punk Kitchen, yeah.
I was the keto man in Cluster Punk Kitchen.
Everyone's dead.
Everywhere at the end of the PCP, all the voicemailers have all been, they're all dead.
They're all gone.
They've all gone to the great comet in the sky.
It's lonely.
So lonely at the top.
Tumbling down, tumbling down, tumbling down.
So, oh my god, them snakes, it was me all along.
It was me, Austin.
I know some people were very suspicious.
How could it be?
How could it be me?
Well, I fought.
I don't believe it.
I'm sorry.
This is an op.
Bandsynch.
This is me.
I believe it on the file.
I just, God, it's hard to do.
He doesn't have the voice filter.
I can't convince him.
Aha, them snakes would never cough.
Or have COVID.
Why did I have to be sick visually?
You imposter.
God.
Dude, recording that last of them snakes a bit was actually a nightmare.
So, when the voicemail's first fucking started, the first character I made was crunchy,
which was terrible and I had no ideas.
I don't even remember that.
The first voicemail, and it was on the very first episode.
I mean, that was their name or you're describing like their audio quality was crunchy.
Their name was crunchy.
They were like munchies dark side or whatever the fuck.
And the first voicemail, it's so bad.
It's just me going.
Like with like.
What a memorable character.
And the second time crunchy appeared, I did my impression of the undertayler
with again with voice filters and shit.
And I thought crunchy was a shit character and then I thought of them snakes.
Oh, Ben St. Vem snakes.
What if it's just a bunch of snakes and Ben doesn't like things that are
unoriginal or that are like sequels or whatever the fuck.
That was like a meme back then.
So.
Right.
Yeah.
Ha, Ben's the copycat.
That one episode with Jeff, where I was like, iteration is bad.
Yeah.
And Ben Ben St. V iteration of snakes, clearly.
Right.
So Ben bad.
That was that was the joke.
I was going to go all the way around.
I was going to do like analog woman, you know, for Digi bro.
I was going to do a bunch and then I just kind of was like, no, let's not do that.
And then I then I actually before the PCP editor contest even happened.
I got to go on as Vem snakes.
I fooled everyone managed to get myself in that was live.
That was before remember, remember the rap?
Remember that time I did the little animation for the rap?
Yeah.
That was fun.
Oh, yeah.
That was beautiful.
That was a beautiful moment.
I'm still proud of that.
I thought it was great.
It was really fucking great.
The editing on that episode was fucking crazy.
It being on there was surreal.
Yeah.
I worked really hard on it.
What?
So so I have two discords, obviously.
And I even have two Minecraft accounts.
I have a Minecraft account called Vem snakes.
I had I made a YouTube channel did all this stuff to keep up the deception.
The Vem snakes, Patreon page, all this shit to keep the deception running.
Wait, is there a Vem snakes?
Yeah.
Like in the very first voicemail is characterpatreon.com slash Vem snakes.
And then it says like, like, you know, like they Vem his pronouns, the plural they,
you know, the rare plural they, of course, of course.
Yeah.
It was and then fucking Gibbs suggested making it the black and red snakes from the game,
from the pump game.
And that was a great idea.
Right.
And I think there was fan art of that episode.
And four eyes.
Oh, yeah.
Do some Vem snakes fan art and even created Vem snakes mall.
There was actually a thing with that.
Oh, I remember.
I remember that.
I do remember that fan art.
That's specific one.
Yeah.
For sure.
I remember specifically I brought out that fan art and then somebody else who was also cold
four eyes also did fan art at Vem snakes.
Yeah.
Yes.
That was great.
There is another person named four eyes on Twitter who, yeah.
They are also like coincidence.
Pretty horny from what I've seen.
I thought you two were the same person for a while because like.
No, it's just fucking big coincidence.
I think it's a reasonable assumption.
But oh, yeah.
No, I just look in the shadows.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Where is that fan art though?
I want to put it in chat so we can show the screen.
Oh, let me.
Let me.
I think it was this one with the funny.
That was during that was during an era that was during an era in which I was putting in high
effort, high effort editing on the PCP.
That was the era of the Vem snakes rap battle and also that bonus episode with where we played
the Baron Munchausen.
Oh my God.
And I animated the battles.
Oh man.
That was a fun episode.
That one was way fun.
I thought that was great.
I never saw the video for Valley only.
I only saw I only got the audio frivos.
I just downloaded the audio for bonus episodes foolishly.
I should have grabbed the videos.
I don't even know where the playlist is.
Yeah.
The audio component or the video component, like the character, like their mouths are
animated in that style of like, you know, black background and like, you know, the colored outline.
And like they like draw their weapons and they like clash in the screen and they like shoot
past each other and like flash red and take damage and stuff.
It's a whole, it was a whole production.
Yeah.
That was that.
Before we fucking were like, why don't we just pay someone to make these episodes for us?
Nobody even watches them.
They just download the audio.
LaMalle.
That's what happened.
I have this image.
This image.
Excuse me.
Oh yeah.
I wanted to, that was a scrapped idea, but it's still cool.
Where was the VemSnakes mom with the snake boobs made out of snakes?
With the vagina.
Not sure I remember.
I don't know if you would have seen it.
This is like a completely separate thing.
Like, back when I was getting like way into like, when you were introducing me to VemSnakes and
showed me like the episode and stuff, I was, I just became a bit of a big fan.
So I need to find it for sure.
Yeah.
I did.
I went on 4chan at the time.
VemSnakes is, he's sexy, but also at the time also getting into
Choose Your Own Adventures, which is apparently just a thing that is on the MLP board for 4chan.
And I thought, I would love to do something like that.
And there's a whole thing where like, you're playing as underwater fish ponies and stuff like that.
And there's a weird plot about a bunch of.
On the sea ponies.
True they do.
Yeah.
When you're in distress.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Should be due, should be due.
And there were a bunch of black snakes underwater for some reason that could just breathe, I guess.
And they were taking it over the whole land and terrorizing people.
And they were led by a gigantic milk snake that had giant, that had giant tits made out of snakes.
That's crazy shit.
Here we go.
Crazy shit, my dude.
Very, very old stuff, very, very old stuff.
Very good, very good.
I was a big fan of this.
I was starting to get really into, that is the best compliment you can give that, very good.
Yeah, I mean it's great, I love it.
It ended very quickly, but that is a thing that exists.
It's cute and good and I like it.
That is cute.
It has lesbians.
I guess when there was Lost Tapes Archive, which...
How that started was, Forai's had a really kind of funny psychic pebbles impression he was doing.
And calls a lot.
I thought, that's a funny voice.
What if we like make a voicemail character out of that?
And so we came up with the idea of this guy who just like finds all your dirty secrets and shit.
And I really wanted to do the Ben St. Licious meme.
And my partner, back then, this was before they started Pormones.
So they were able to do their Twilight voice still.
I remember you guys were like, wait, did they get Tara Strong?
And I was like, that was a compliment.
That was epic.
Oh, amazing, amazing.
I also remember Nate being like, huh, we're getting a lot of voicemails for Ben.
What about the rest of us, huh?
I remember that also being a thing.
Shut up.
Which is also my doing.
Where are you now, Ben?
Where are you now?
Yeah, exactly, exactly.
Ben's the most reliable person to pick on because he's always here.
Yeah.
And then from there, for Tom's tape, the one with the train,
like the Thomas Votan engine parody, we got Will Ryan.
He's a YouTuber with life.
I'd like me to go back and listen to all these again.
Now that all this is out in the open, the Vem Snake channel will be used to
archive compilations of every complete series of Clusters 1 Kitchen,
Vem Snake, Sloth's Tape Archive.
It's all going up there probably in February.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Well, I guess we'll have to link that in the description.
I don't know if it probably won't be archived that soon.
You can just link the Vem Snake's channel and it'll be up there in a few weeks probably.
Yeah, okay.
That'll work just as well.
That's pretty funny.
All right.
Yeah.
Vem Snake's channel.
I'll subscribe.
You weren't already subscribed?
Ooh, shameful.
I don't think so.
Maybe I was.
You know, we should have Vem Snake's on the draw cast.
No, he's dead.
Bring him back.
He's fucked up.
He's dead.
No.
See, there's a thing.
That's my secret.
Yeah, just bring him back.
Vem Snake's has been on so many draw casts.
He's been on the rest of the world.
Just make him not dead.
Yeah, but as I was saying about the Tom Tape,
Will Ryan voiced some of the Thomas characters?
He's a YouTuber with over a million subscribers.
Did you say Will Ryan?
Yeah, Will Ryan of DA Games, that channel I work for.
Challenge everything.
Yeah.
So, it all got.
And then there was the DeVoo rap.
Oh, that was so great.
That's my ringtone.
That's ironically my ringtone.
I love it.
Yeah.
I like the goo.
I don't know.
Lost Tapes is my favorite series before I had the most effort put in.
There's a lot.
I had a lot of voicemails.
I had a lot of voicemails over the years.
Yeah.
And then there was Cluster Punk Kitchen.
I was editing the PCP during that.
I liked your book, Kiki.
Keto Delito.
Right, yeah.
That was good.
Yes.
Keto Delito.
That's why I was saying Keto for Cluster Punk Kitchen.
Yeah, Keto Delito.
I was Ben St. in that voicemail.
Oh, yeah.
You were the little Ben St. standing.
Well, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry for you.
It's tough.
It's okay.
I survived.
I've only lost an arm.
Then there's a whole bunch of minor.
There's a whole bunch of minor characters.
Right wing Richard.
Left wing Larry.
That was us.
Okay.
Center Sam.
Politics.
What are they?
Oh, yeah.
That was just a...
That literally came about as me just saying something random
and you just thought it was so funny that I just said that.
That was weird.
There was a double, double Satan.
Satan.
That was also me.
There's fucking hundreds.
I've done so many characters and so many voices.
Oh, yeah.
The big thing this year was the League of Nightfuckers,
which I created.
That was my brainchild.
I gathered Seatull and Four Eyes.
And I just have a funny idea.
I did it.
Okay.
It didn't actually start when Michelle thought
Sean was going to spicy salt.
And we were talking about that situation.
And that gave you the idea.
I heard that Michelle thought
that Sean was going to sex Nate or something.
And I'm like, and...
Sean...
Wait, who's Sean?
Sean Dawn.
He made the...
Oh, right.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
That's Sean.
Sorry.
I was thinking of the Skull YouTuber.
Yeah.
You drew him a thing recently.
Oh, yeah.
He wants to fuck Nate.
Yes, I know.
I drew his sword.
Sorry.
I was just thinking of a different show.
So anyways, I heard Michelle thought
that Sean wanted to fuck Nate.
And I'm like, that's not true.
But that's also really funny.
You know what?
Everyone wants to fuck Nate now.
And so I sat down and like,
this is like two weeks in advance.
I'm like, we need to make like a bunch of voicemails
and like submit them all back to back.
Just all of them.
And then we thought of like the Thousand Lung Man
who's just like, like fucking breathing.
We did one from Lost Tapes Archive.
I did one as Van Snakes.
A bunch, just a bunch of fucking freaks.
That's where the William came from.
My favorite one was the Freddy Freaker parody.
Yeah, the Freddy Freaker song was so good.
And you and Gib also were like fucking dying during that.
Yes.
And then we just kept going.
Ben, do you remember the Lord of the Rings, Smeagol?
Oh, yes.
Nate fucker.
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember Smeagol.
Don't do Smeagol.
That was for us.
Yes.
Okay.
This feels like this feels like the end of an era.
Yes.
The human guitar.
Oh God, human guitar.
Poor Alie Azar.
Every time I submitted a human guitar voicemail,
he would message me being like oblivion.
Please my ears.
I'm like, I'm sorry, I have to punish Ben St.
It's the only way.
True.
You're an unfortunate side effect.
The Legendary.
You too.
Yeah, he's a collateral damage.
He's collateral damage.
It's all about just messing with Ben St's head
that's been in the game for like three years,
four years almost, probably.
What am I supposed to do?
Not do that?
Exactly.
Sorry.
Yeah.
It is an unhealthy, genuinely,
it's an unhealthy addiction I've had,
just making voicemails is a dumb idea.
And then I spend like three or four hours.
New year's resolution is get clean,
get clean off voicemails.
No more voicemails.
This is like, I'm blowing my little all white joke.
That's what that was.
This man has been in the middle of work,
get an idea for a voicemail,
and then spend like two to three hours not doing work
so he can get this idea perfectly out.
And he's just like, please do this voice for me.
I know that feeling.
Not for the PCP.
I would never like do work for the PCP.
For other things.
Gotcha.
Okay.
Well, this really is voicemails revelations.
It's all coming out in the watch.
It's all coming out.
Third impact, baby.
And the third impact.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
So now we know.
The pig saga was so good.
The terrible truth.
Turns out there was a voicemail cinematic universe.
The voicemail cinematic universe created by me
and my friends who I roped into it.
Yes.
And it's been going on even since before I was the editor.
I even managed to fucking get on as VemSnakes,
which was so funny.
There's so many points.
Like when the first time I came on the PCP
as the believe in fall, I'm sitting here like,
I've been here before and they don't even fucking know.
Yeah.
I mean, I had some inkling, but I'm sure there were suspicions.
Do you really think all of these people were oblivion fall?
I knew that some of them were oblivion fall.
I didn't exactly know who, but I think it was pretty obvious.
I knew that.
No, I knew that.
I knew that ClusterPunk kitchen.
Yeah.
For sure.
Oh, yeah.
That's just my regular voice.
Just slowed down.
Yeah.
Human guitar, I think, is also pretty clearly your voice
if you can listen past the filter.
I also just spilled the beans on that one immediately.
So.
Oh, yeah.
I thought it was a surprise.
Well, I guess we'll just never have another good voicemail ever again.
Exactly.
You're all these shit from now on.
We've peaked.
This is it.
I think so.
So, I mean, should we listen to some bad voicemails?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, let's go for it.
All right.
I guess let's let's let's do some and just see what just see what remains.
Let's see what the kingdom of ashes is left for us to to reign over.
Let's see what the nuclear apocalypse looks like.
I think so.
I think that's right.
All right.
First one of today is it's called Keckfest 2020.
Okay.
Sorry.
My folder computer.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
Never mind.
It's a three second voicemail.
I think there's a.
Okay.
Yeah.
Listen to that.
But the actual voicemail is here.
It's a YouTube link here is the link.
Okay.
What the?
Simeon Jimmy's treehouse procrastinators podcast versus Simeon Jimmy.
What?
This is just monkey.
What is this?
The fuck is this?
This is a 46 minute monkey video.
Is this new?
This came out.
Oh, yeah.
This came out at the end of last year.
Whoa.
Like two days ago.
What?
What the fuck is this?
Okay.
This came up two days ago.
Yeah.
I guess I better give this a watch.
That's I'm concerned.
Yeah.
I'll wash that later.
I guess.
Oh, God.
How embarrassing.
I, uh, uh, this is, uh.
It's been so long since I heard monkey's voice.
I'm like, I'm like concerned.
I'm like afraid to listen to this.
I don't even want to know what he's going to say.
Treksy's under digital brain.
Oh, my gosh.
This calm, this comment.
Comment on this video.
Wait, what does this say?
Um, holy shit.
I woke up from a four year coma.
I've missed so many uploads from the PCP.
I can't wait to see all the crazy content
they made together in the PCP house.
And what the bleep in the weave.
Can't wait for those bleep and weave
Blu-rays baby.
Yeah.
Get with the bleep and weave video
that I spent $500 crowdfunding look like.
And I sure hope that Digi is living successfully
with his wife and hasn't become
a literal homeless drug addict.
Getting less than 200 views for video.
Oh boy.
I'm so excited.
Uh, the bleep, Blu-rays baby.
The Blu-rays are real.
What a time.
What a time to be alive.
Men saying to the rescue.
Yeah.
At least, at least,
chap McBloake making from his coma
love something to look forward to.
And that's those Blu-rays.
I see, I see a comment from Project FM.
Imagine forgetting both mother's basement
and the DeVoo, but not Si.
Yeah, like Si is listed as a member here.
I mentioned that I asked Si
if he wanted to come on the show
and he was just like, nah,
he's just too good.
He's too good for the PCP now.
Tragic, tragic.
Mother's basement would absolutely come on though.
Mother's basement would never turn down the PCP.
This is a fact.
No, there's a guy with integrity.
There's a guy who would never turn his back
on his old pals at the Procrastinators podcast.
Okay, that's very funny.
Obviously, we're not going to watch it
because it's 40 minutes long.
Link in the description to
Simi and Jimmy's Treehouse Procrastinators podcast.
If there's a Simi...
I'm like, ugh.
I don't want to know what he has to say.
Apparently, he replaced DeVoo with Si last minute for some reason.
Sure, whatever.
Okay, so that's very funny, probably.
Next voicemail is here.
I'll put it in chat.
It is called...
What's it called?
It's called a concerned viewer.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP.
You ever wonder what happened to that one fellow
who was just always really thirsty?
At least, I don't think we've heard from him in a while.
But then, I remember, it's dry dump December.
He's not thirsty anymore.
He's absorbing back all the moisture from the poo he's been holding in.
We've done so much good.
He's really changed someone's life for the better.
Yeah.
And thank you for that.
You're the best PCP.
Hell yeah.
You're doing good.
You know, a couple of days ago was dried up December for me
during the height of my fever.
I guess all the moisture in my body was just being like
sucked out into sweat.
And I had to...
You needed it.
My butt was glued shut.
God.
It was awful.
Wow, that's nasty.
That's just fucked up.
Dried up December.
It's just fucked up.
Delicious.
That's just beyond the pale.
Eleazar, edit that out, please.
I'll edit that out, Eleazar.
Thanks, Ele.
Thanks, Eleazar.
Oblivion, edit Eleazar.
Oblivion, edit Eleazar back in.
He's good.
Oblivion Fall.
Eddie at...
Yeah, put it...
Oblivion Fall, fuck you.
Get out of here.
Put Eleazar back in the episode in the editing bay.
Thank you.
God bless.
Next episode is called...
TheFAG is on Twitter.
This is at FAG Penridge, all one word.
You remember, this was that club that was
doing a counter turning point USA
campaign at their school.
Oh, yes.
Yes, I remember this.
I remember this.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP.
I called in a little bit ago, maybe two weeks ago,
about the FAG, the Fellowship of Atheist Gamers.
And I just wanted to call back in to say
that the FAG has a Twitter account now.
Who, boy?
Because I know that Instagram's kind of for Zoomers
and there's more for Boomers.
So I'm just trying to diversify our platforms.
And now we have a Twitter.
It is at FAG Penridge, at Fag Penridge.
And it's just going to be the uploading
what's already on the Instagram account.
But it turns out that Turning Point Penridge
also has a Twitter account.
So, yeah, I get it.
Now we're taking a full frontal assault.
Everywhere.
Oh, boy.
You got to take it to the streets.
Well, we are liberal.
Hashtag love is love.
Hashtag FAG.
The official page for the Penridge chapter
of the Fellowship of Atheist Gamers.
Take the blue pill.
I don't know.
I don't know anything about these people.
But every single tweet that they make,
I fully endorse and 100% believe in.
100, agreed.
Agreed.
I'm doing it.
I'm giving them a follow.
They're tweeting little pamphlets.
That's neat.
And that's an endorsement.
Yeah, a little Jimmy Carter, Grover Cleveland,
a little historical section search.
Here are three reasons why capitalism
is an optimized and fair system.
I like their reasons.
Damn it, he's right.
Yeah, look at them.
What are their reasons?
See them?
Good one.
Got them.
That'll show capitalism.
Is epic.
Endorse.
It is epic.
It is a little epic.
I support it.
Okay, next voicemail is just who chooses
the episode titles and usually Eleazar.
Usually Eleazar just picks them
unless I say I want it to be called something else.
But usually I don't do that.
Yeah, Eleazar.
Okay, next one is just called E,
the lowercase letter E.
It's uploading.
Okay, there it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Eleazar always makes good thumbnails,
but the last one let me down.
Why isn't the thumbnail Ben Sainte with huge tits?
We have that, don't we?
Yeah.
Don't we have Ben Sainte with huge tits
taking the blue pill somewhere?
Blue tits.
Oh no, blueberry inflation.
It's all coming full circle.
One though.
Right, because last week me and Gibb talked
about how oppressed big booby women are
and how they're all gate kept out of Hollywood.
And there aren't enough leading women in Hollywood
with huge knockers.
It's true.
It's fucked up.
And so in solidarity, I've given myself huge tits.
With enough synthetic plastic, we can fix that.
Yeah, we can fix that.
Even Ben Sainte can have huge tits.
Technology sure is incredible.
Even Ben Sainte.
Even, even, yeah.
The greatest technology of all, Ben Sainte.
Next voicemail is called X5321GO.
He is coming for you, Ben Sainte.
Oh no.
He's still coming.
For me to see.
You know, it's kind of, we haven't really
shared that sort of information.
You got big fills to shoot.
We got another arc, baby.
We got another character.
We got some new characters in the voicemails.
These are the people picking up them snakes mantle.
Picking up the slack, yeah.
Picking up the skin.
Season 12 of the Ben Sainte arc.
There's an arc.
There's an arc here.
This is, we're in the midst of it.
We're at the top of it.
We're hanging suspended in midair before the fall.
The second half we come plummeting down to the ground.
Next voicemail is another YouTube link.
And it asks what to make of this at gmail.com.
Oh, it's the same link.
It's another one.
The procrastinators podcast for two people.
Okay, fair.
Big news.
Tell you next week, maybe.
I don't know.
I don't think I'm going to watch it.
It makes me a little uncomfortable.
I'll tell you in the comment section.
I'll tell you in the comment section what to make of it.
I think it's funny and concept,
but I don't know if I actually want to sit through it.
Just for my personal comfort, Lamal.
Next voicemail is called Talking Pirates in a Nutshell.
Parentheses, it's good.
It's good.
All right, three, two, one, go.
So, Jimbe bad, hockey bad, law bad.
Yes.
Oda make mistake, law bad, pre-timeskip, good.
Booba.
All good.
New bad.
But booba is eternal.
Booba is timeless.
I think I agree.
I've seen that before and after.
That sounds about right.
I've seen the exaggeration of Oda's work with One Piece,
and it's amazing how much every woman in that
has just become more of a bimbo.
That's good.
One Piece is the real binification poll.
These do sound like Nate's opinions,
as far as I'm aware of them.
So, I mean, it's just, yeah.
Oh, I found it.
It's like you never left.
I found the picture of you with big boobs, Ben.
I found it.
Here you go.
Oh boy.
Oh, shit, nice.
Oh, wow.
Oh, yeah, I remember this one.
Yeah.
Good shit.
Hey, I'm getting the beard back.
Again, I'm getting beardy again.
Those are some guitar pick-shaped boobs.
Yeah, they're not big enough.
That size would get me cast in Hollywood.
I'll give them the weight and the sag desired.
I'll make you a true busty boy, Ben,
yet you'll see.
Just make sure he's also still taking the pills.
You know, but change the pills to something else.
Just booby pills, maybe.
It's a good change to make them blue.
You gave me the pink hair.
We need a rule 60 free, Ben saying, to be honest.
You gave me pink hair, blue pills, tits.
All I need is pronouns, and then I'd be good to go.
Do you not already have pronouns?
Oh, Simon drew this?
Yeah, Simon drew this.
I have, sorry, my pronoun game is just...
I think Simon's still any old, but I default to she-they.
Well, that's fine.
I'm talking about me, though.
Can we keep the focus on me, where it belongs?
Thank you.
No.
I'm sorry.
Next voice, they, yeah, yep, you are.
Next voicemail is called My Favorite PCP Member.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, I was thinking about my favorite PCP member,
and I went back to watch the old episodes,
and it always used to be Digi, Best Guy Ever,
and Jesse, and guys like them.
Now, my favorites are obviously Tom, Ben Benzane,
that you give, and honestly, fuck everybody else.
Well, you gotta go back, watch those old episodes,
just everyone else is a fucking idiot,
and then there's Ben, Tom, and give the legends.
So, you're saying your opinion has changed in hindsight,
which is fair.
Yes, clearly.
I mean, I agree.
I hate those fucking guys, and that's not true.
Well, I hate Digi, obviously.
Trixie, Beatrice, Blu-rays, even we Blu-rays.
Trixie, Blue Horse, Blu-rays.
Blue Pill?
Blue Berries?
Blue Berry, Violet Beauregard, Blu-rays, Blu-Pills.
Time is a flat circle.
Time is a flat circle, it's true.
Buy my fucking shit.
Hey, buy a Blu-ray.
While you're buying a Blu-ray, why not buy a copy of Rotoradcon?
I got those, I got like 50 more of those.
Please, please sell me out.
I don't want 50 of them.
I got mine.
That's good to know.
You know, I had kind of hoped to have the Radcon dogen ready by now too,
so I could maybe have, I could sell it all.
I will give like a bulk discount if you buy the dogen and the Rotoradcon,
but the dogen has seen unforeseen delays whose nature I will not elaborate upon here.
Because you're not a messy bitch.
I do get angry about it.
I do get upset.
I do get upset in the, in some bonus content and some behind the scenes bonus content.
I did, I did rave a little bit about it to Gibb last week,
but that's whatever.
That's not, that's not main show talk.
Yeah.
Anyway, what the fuck was I talking about?
Oh, next episode is called Digimon Lecture 321 Go.
On episode 274, Ben was floating the idea of doing a lecture on the real Digimon forums
where most of it is stuff from the something awful third or from memory
and Jack went, that sounds kind of bad lol.
No, it doesn't.
It sounds amazing.
Who gives a single solitary shit about proof?
All of the lectures are just people talking about their memory of the interesting topic at hand.
That's not entirely true.
There's been times in lectures where an audience member asked a question
and the lecturer didn't know the answer.
These aren't encyclopedic 100% accurate records of the topic at hand.
They're engaging retellings.
The real Digimon believers shit sounds great.
Do it.
Fuck the haters.
The real, yeah, the real Digimon believers shit is, it was great.
It was awesome.
It's just that, I don't know.
It's just that simply like not much of the record of it exists.
And like, I'd be the, I can, all I can really do with the Digimon believer stuff at this point
is explain what it was and then like, there's not, it doesn't really take that long to explain.
Yeah.
Take a page out of Trixie's book.
Do the mini lectures.
You can make a 10 minute video essay on it.
Oh, the, the little, the little lecture.
Yeah, that are just like small videos.
About like, about like why like you should diagnose yourself with autism or whatever.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, just do one of those, but about something good.
You know, you've been stealing all of Trixie's ideas and making them good.
Why not just do it again?
That's true.
I hope she gets mad.
I hope she gets upset about the, the Blu-rays.
Ah, that'd be funny.
That would be really funny.
It would be.
It would be funny.
I could see her thinking that she could be like, oh, that's my intellectual property though,
which would be very funny.
I mean, I don't know if that'll happen.
She's probably to check that.
She'd have to get-
She's probably to checked out to even, to even notice.
Yeah.
To do anything with that, she'd have to also get Jess on board.
And I think, I don't know the guy.
I feel like he just be happy it's all over.
Like it's done.
It's off his back.
That's the impression I get too.
I think Jesse would just not want to even have anything to do with it,
which is what he has been doing for years.
Okay.
Next voicemail, it was, next, this is the last voicemail.
Oh, fuck yeah.
Well, it's a second long.
Wait.
Sorry, no.
Anyway, listen, three, two, one, go.
Formation in this.
What?
It's so quiet.
It's very quiet.
Formation boost, what the fuck does that even mean?
I don't know.
Well, there's a YouTube link attached to it.
Oh, I knew it.
I knew it.
Yeah.
I mentioned last week, I thought I said, I asked like,
was there an endless just fuck football video?
And I thought it was no, but yeah, I guess there was.
Okay.
I was right.
I knew it.
Okay.
Well, that's good to know.
You weren't wrong after all, Ben.
You weren't wrong after all.
I was right.
I do remember the, maybe COVID didn't shrink my brain that much
after all.
I remember stuff.
I was wrong.
There's one more voicemail, but here it is.
It's three seconds long.
It's called, in my opinion.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
In my opinion, all pro and on should die.
Yeah.
Iceborg.
Well, hello.
Wow.
Iceborg.
Hard agree.
Thoughts.
Is the pro and on still occurring?
Does that still exist?
Yeah.
We did a New Year's episode.
It's mostly just a friend group where we hang out and vibe.
Die.
No.
I mean, soon I'm going to be streaming Disco Elysium on the pro and on channel
if you're interested in that.
It's Pog.
And there's also my Stardew streams.
You're Stardew?
Yeah.
Stardew.
I play as Garfield.
I roll play as Garfield.
I had a Stardew Valley game that I like complete.
I was going to I was going to pave the entire world.
That was my plan for Stardew Valley.
By making like pavement tiles and just placing there.
I paved a lot of it, but not enough.
We go back to it then.
It was pretty funny.
You can always pick it back up.
You know, I had a world where I like I it was like islands.
Like my farm was like had like an island layout and I paved all the islands and I built bridges
and I put like I had slime farms.
I had slime slime hatcheries and I like I organized all the slimes by color on different
little islands and I paved everything and it was all nice and nice and industrial look.
It was spent like really long time because it's really tedious to do to make the the paved
I think there's a shortcut now to like make a bunch of them at once, which is pretty base.
Oh, that's pretty good.
Yeah, I would have been helpful.
I have a very little experience with Stardew, but I did play multiplayer once.
Someone on Twitter, GabaNinja1 on Twitter just coincidentally added me and asked
where's the announcement.
I'm pretty sure they're talking about because I said I was going to announce
the secret project on New Year's.
The reason I haven't announced it on Twitter.
I will have announced it by the time this episode comes out.
The reason I haven't announced it on Twitter is because literally because I had COVID,
I have not been able to go to Munchie's house and take a picture of myself holding
the Blu-ray in my hand while it's like playing on the television.
I want to take that picture and be like the Blu-ray is real.
Here's what it looks like.
It actually has like a menu system and stuff.
I just need to get that picture and then I can announce it.
And just because I'm still COVID positive, I have not been able to go over there and do that.
So there's a reason why I put me behind schedule because I said I was going to
announce it on New Year's, but I was set back slightly.
2021.
You wouldn't risk Munchie's home.
No. I have to go to the printer and pick up the DVD sleeves, like the cover jacket.
I have one.
I have one box that has a sleeve that I'm going to use for the picture.
And then I have 48.
I have 50 more in a box that I need to pick up and put on the other 50 boxes
because I made a batch of 50 of them.
They are sitting in my closet.
They have been quarantined from myself.
I have not gone in my closet and fucked with them since I got COVID.
Because I want to keep them uncontaminated.
I'm pretty sure it's fine.
Even if I had breathed on them, COVID doesn't live on surfaces forever.
It dies after a few days, I think.
So it would be fine anyway, but I'm trying to keep them away from myself just in case.
Something like on plastics, it lasts three days and on cardboard,
it lasts two days or one day or something.
Okay.
So it should be fine.
Maybe I'll just wait a couple of days after my...
I'll wait a couple of days after my I'm negative before I actually send any.
Just be super, super safe.
Spray some Windex on it.
Yeah.
I guess I could do that.
Yeah, just a little bit of disinfecting.
Spray it directly onto the surface of the disc.
And then scour and scrub it really hard.
Yeah.
I'm just saying I'm absolutely sure it gets any contaminants off of there.
Just leave the disinfectant on for like five minutes.
That'll get rid of any like germs and stuff.
And then you wipe it away and you're done.
I gotta complain about this.
It was so hard finding...
It was easy to order Blu-ray discs that had a printable surface so that I could like print
an image onto the disc.
Getting discs like that was easy, but finding a way to actually print the image onto those discs
was unbelievably hard.
And I called like so many different printing services and like local print shops and was
like, can you print on this disc?
And they were all like, no, we won't do it.
We simply won't do it.
But you can buy a printer that does it.
And ultimately this is what I had to do.
I literally...
Oh, I didn't buy it.
I asked my parents if they would get me one as like a Christmas present and they were like,
sure, whatever.
So they got me a printer for Christmas that has a disc.
It's a Canon printer.
It's only like a $200 printer.
Like it's not an incredibly expensive piece of equipment, but it has a tray that you can
put a disc in and it will print on the disc.
It's just a thing you can buy for not that much money on a home printer.
And yet commercial printers, they just like, no, we can't do it.
We simply don't have the technology.
We just don't have a machine that does it.
Sorry.
I tried.
I really tried.
I didn't want to buy a whole printer over it, but I had to.
I was like, okay.
So that was my...
This was like a month-long struggle that I went through trying to find a method of printing
images onto discs when it worked out.
Damn.
That was by far the hardest part of the whole process.
I got a Serbian guy named Slobodan to actually do the...
To do the...
Slobodan, that's great.
Like the data, like to build the actual like DVD file and like menus and stuff.
I got a guy on Fiverr to do it.
Slobodan, he's my guy.
Give me an incredible deal.
Other people were asking for like $500 for this job.
This guy was like, I'll do it for 100.
He did it perfectly.
He did it exactly what I could have wanted for.
I was like, this guy saved me so much money.
I tipped him 50%.
Did you put him in the credits?
Credit to Slobodan?
No.
No, I didn't.
I should have put it on the back.
I should have put it on the back of the box.
Label, I should have been like, uh, credits to Slobodan.
Shout outs to Slobodan.
Just pull paper inserts.
Just a little piece of paper that says credits to Slobodan.
It's, it's great.
It's like you put, you put it in the fucking Blu-ray player.
There's a menu screen and it plays the jingle by Sick Rick.
The little, the like the background song for the season two, Plebe and the Weeb theme song.
I added bonus features.
There are bonus features, including a special message from Ben St.
That's an exclusive, exclusive content on there.
I went all out.
I think it's like the funniest fucking thing ever.
I can't wait for people to have them.
So I'm very, I'm very excited.
I'm very excited about these.
Yeah, you can tell.
That's good.
Anyway, I'm glad it's finally out.
Yeah, sorry.
And that other people don't know about it.
Don't apologize.
Stop that.
Yeah.
It's fine.
You're fine.
I got, yeah, the Blu-ray, the Blu-ray burner you bought me broke.
I know.
I was there when you were complaining and I couldn't get ahold of them.
I was so mad.
I burned, I burned one disc and then it fucking broke.
And I was just like, but, so I had to, again, I got the, also, also as a Christmas present.
I asked my, my parents, they were like, what do you want for Christmas?
And I was like, well, I need a Blu-ray burner.
And then later I knew it was like, also I need a printer.
Ben, I told you I was just buying you a new one.
I didn't want you to buy me another one.
That, that sucks.
It was only like a hundred bucks.
Yeah.
It was like 90.
So whatever.
I just got one, one disc, one disc and the thing fucking breaks.
That thing is trash.
That thing was so,
has maybe made me really mad.
This is a safe space.
You can be mad.
You can be mad here.
Modern technology.
There's fucking Chinese swindlers, the shysters that sold that thing.
And they didn't even get, you should get a refund.
You should get a refund on that thing.
Oh, you want that?
Just yell at them.
Be like, hey, you, you sold the thing you sold me fucking broke.
I'll kill you.
Instantly.
It like didn't work.
I'll show up to your house and I'll kill you.
Anyway, I have a question for you, Ben Singh.
There seems to be rumors about the pro and on going on, like how we're dead.
What's up with that?
Wait, what?
There's rumors about what?
About us being dead.
You like just ask, like, hey, are we even alive?
Like, I keep hearing that people say we're dead.
Haven't been paying attention.
I just haven't heard anything about it in a while.
I just haven't heard about it.
Like I know that like you and Sean and Simon,
is Simon a pro and on?
He is, right?
Simon's like dead.
Simon's in our D&D game.
Okay.
Like I know, and like Dune Koon and like I know all these people,
or no, she's not called Dune Koon anymore.
She's, I don't know her name.
She's, I know, I know.
Every time I say anything about Dune, she gets embarrassed that,
her YouTube is still doing Dune Koon.
Actually, she's just got monetization on our YouTube channel.
Nice.
Oh, wow.
I mean, I know you guys are still around.
I just haven't heard anyone mention the pro and on cast in a while.
So I don't know.
Yeah, we just, we're just a friend group now.
That's fair.
Talking about the PCP, nearly tore our friendship apart.
And we're like, we don't want to be that much like the PCP.
Yeah.
We don't want to.
Being the procrastinators tore our friendship apart as well.
Yeah.
So we're like, let's just stop reviewing the PCP.
Let's just make things when we have something to say.
Don't want to go the way, you don't want to go the way of the PCP.
You don't want to follow us over that, over that cliff.
Yeah.
So instead we just hang out.
We play D&D.
We play video games.
We're going to be playing Magic soon, I hope.
I'm trying to coerce them into playing Magic with me.
It's going to be great.
Yeah.
We're just having fun.
We're just a group of funny little guys having a good time.
Yeah.
It's great to be a funny little guy.
It's a great world to be a funny little guy.
And we're just having fun.
We're just having a good time.
Well, what's up?
Are we done?
Do you want to wrap up?
I guess so.
I'm winding down mentally.
I think we have a draw cast today, the Femboy episode.
Yeah, we do.
I have to go run and see my uncles.
So I have like-
Make a message gothic to see if she's still ready for that
and then find out who the other artist is going to be on that one.
Right.
Yeah.
Check out the draw cast.
Hey, Daniel, spend more time with us.
Then you want to spend more time with us.
Trying for Femboy.
Not today.
I'm busy.
I'm looking forward to another week of furiously typing away in GML
to add features that nobody asked for and are not necessary.
But they fill out the menu and they make the game ha ha funnier.
We could have all drawn Ben St. with tits.
It could have happened.
Oh.
I just want to be left alone.
I just want to be left alone to my own devices to do that.
You want Ben St. with tits, you say?
Here.
Here, let me give you up Ben St. with tits.
We already got one.
Oh, no, this is a new one that I made while we were talking about it
because I thought it'd be funny.
Oh, no.
Demand is sky high.
Production is infinitely low.
I just thought it'd be funny.
You know what?
It was funny.
Let me get it.
Wait.
Okay, I was going to say I don't see anything.
No, you don't.
Get it.
Because I haven't put it up yet.
Because I forgot what you looked like.
Don't stop. Get it, get it.
It's all your captaincy in here.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Just constantly shoveling them into the mouth.
Incredible.
The boobs, these boobs are way better.
These boobs are way better.
Yeah, those are closer to ideal.
They're chunkier.
They're getting bigger by the moment.
Yeah, closer to ideal.
You're getting the Oda treatment.
Closer, we're 5% better.
You're being bimbified as we speak.
You know, this is what we need.
This is the prejudice that we face,
that we big booby women face in Hollywood.
Just because our breasts are big doesn't mean we're slutty.
Doesn't mean we're bimbos.
Doesn't mean we're not intelligent or talented.
Doesn't mean we can't be leading ladies
in major motion pictures.
And it definitely doesn't mean that you can talk to me that way.
You fucking scoundrel.
It is a very, very real prejudice.
I follow some very, very big breasted women on Twitter.
And all of them have made poise at various points about,
like, they can't ever wear a low-cut top
or without, like, mothers covering their children's eyes
when they walk past.
Even if they just wear normal clothing,
like, have to wear excessively baggy clothing
that disguises their form.
Otherwise, they'll get dirty looks from everyone.
Like, oh, how dare you be out in public
with your obscene body, that sort of thing.
And I think that's really disgusting
that people don't like that.
Them saying shit like, how dare you come out there
with that, that erotic body is like,
that's porn dialogue.
What the fuck?
So lewd, so lewd.
I know, like, oh, look at your obscene body.
Like, that is porn dialogue.
But like, that's actually how these people are being tweeted
and it's not a good thing.
It's, they're being judged.
What they don't know is what they're saying
is even more obscene.
Exactly, they're falling into the trap.
I see.
We have to end the oppression of big booby women.
By becoming big booby women.
By becoming big booby women, it's true.
We got a tran- transition.
Bam, we're all big booby women now.
All the gravestones have tits.
That's the Anthony Fantano strategy.
You're actually going to put tits on all the gravestones.
That'd be fun.
No.
Just put them on my mind, that's fine.
I already have too many ambitious ideas
for how the episode's going to look visually.
Yeah, this is why you had to stop being our editor,
because you've worked too hard and you put too much effort in.
And it was unsustainable.
Oh, Ben, like over two weeks ago,
when Eleazar told me who has gone away,
I'm like, hold on, Eleazar.
And I fucking created an After Effects template.
I did some crazy shit.
When you see this episode, when you see what it looks like,
you're going to be like, oh, god, what the fuck did he do?
You're going to be, the audience has already seen it.
They've been watching this whole time.
Yeah, I guess I probably will say that.
That sounds about right.
I saw you prepping.
It's kind of insane.
It's kind of just very funny.
Okay, well, I can't wait.
I can't wait to go back two hours into the past
and start this episode and see what that looks like and be shocked.
Eleazar, Eleazar, edit my reaction to what the episode looks like.
Wait, no, no, I can't see it.
Never mind.
No, it's fine, it's fine.
We haven't been called.
I can't do that until after.
Okay, all right.
What does that mean?
Do you have the technology?
Well, that's going to, well, that'll be pretty fucking stupid, I guess.
All right.
Yeah, let's let's wrap it up.
Let's let's let's put a little bow on it.
Check out the draw casts.
Check out OblivionFall, follow.
Yeah, patreon.com slash oblivionfall, twitter at oblivionfall underscore d.
Me and Dune are making a comic, so go read that maybe.
Link in description, maybe.
Where?
Where ever we post it.
Where ever we post it when it comes out, I'll send it to Oblivion and Oblivion
can put it in the description.
It's fine.
No matter what, Eleazar is our friend and we will sneak the comic link in one of the
episodes at the PCP somewhere.
It'll be great.
Okay.
Oh yeah, you'll need to give me whatever template you use for the video descriptions these days.
Oh god.
Or I'll just copy it from a recent video and just figure it out.
Yeah, that's what I will do is I will simply go to the latest episode and copy paste the
description and then just give you that.
Yeah, all right.
If you want me to do that for you, I can't just do it.
I can't.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, Benny, Wanny, I did so hard.
I can't do it by myself.
I know, I know, I know.
You're so useless.
More porn dialogue.
That's it.
My boobs are too big.
I can't reach the keyboard to control C.
Everyone, everyone watching the episode, draw Ben with big boobs and you'll be featured on
the next episode of the PCP.
Yeah.
Heck, heck, why not?
And then I'll, and then I'll meticulous, all right, I'll draw me with big boobs and then I'll
go up through every submission and I will meticulously critique, I will critique every
boob drawing.
I will, I will cruelly point out what I do and don't like about them.
I will dehumanize them and pick them apart and, and objectify them for the sake of, I
don't know, big booby liberation.
I'm going to de-sexualize them.
It's self-objectification.
By overanalyzing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm going to, I'm going to dehumanize myself in solidarity.
What a true ally.
Solidarity with big booby women all over the world.
Four eyes, plug your Twitter.
You love you.
Four eyes on a score of T.
Underscore T.
Nice.
Yeah, underscore T, like an actual underscore, because I don't know if I'm, I don't know if
I'm following you.
You should.
You definitely not.
I went through a Twitter purge at one point.
Four eyes.
Oh yeah, underscore T.
I will give you a file.
I don't, I don't follow you.
I follow the other four eyes, but you know what?
I got a, well, there we go.
Give you follow.
Hell yeah.
Thank you very much.
Now you're going to see lots of titties.
Okay.
Just remember to retweet that smaller artist then.
Oh yeah.
Wait.
Four eyes is bigger than me.
Four eyes has more Twitter followers than I do.
Oh snap.
Never retweet that smaller artist, Four Eyes.
So he'd better retweet me actually.
Yeah.
Uh-oh.
I've never been in this position before.
Whoops.
You've been caught in it.
How do I, how do I, how do I walk away?
Too late.
One foot behind the other.
Oh no.
Yeah.
Okay.
Anything else, anything else before we wrap?
Uh, twitter.com forward slash cicada underscore God.
No matter what, there I will pin the comic.
If you want to read it, it'll be a comic.
Hopefully it'll be good.
My goal is to one day destroy Ben St.
So if you want to support me in destroying Ben St.
By making comics more regularly than him.
And then laughing.
Go to patreon.com forward slash cicada.
S-E-E-C-A-D-A.
Watch the draw cast because it's good and fun.
And Ben's also on there.
You guys like Ben.
He's there.
He's been there.
I've been on one or two.
Yeah.
He's been there.
Rest in peace, them snakes.
Yeah, that's it.
That's all you got.
Rest in peace.
Rest in peace, everybody.
Rest in peace, them snakes.
Rest in peace, Cluster Punk Kitchen.
Right.
Tapekeeper.
Right, right, right.
A whole, a whole mass grave of voicemail characters.
That's why we are.
This is a good thing that PCP is a graveyard.
We can just, we can just like add them.
Like to add like gravestones for them as the episode goes on.
Yeah.
Oh, hell yeah.
This episode was a voicemail Holocaust.
A voicemail Holocaust.
So I would describe it.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry, Harold Henry.
You're being replaced.
Not, not left wing Larry.
Oh, no, centrist Sam.
Harold Henry of the gravestone in the background, that.
Oh, oh, right, oh, right.
Right.
That guy who's dead.
That literal dead guy.
That real guy.
He's dead.
Right.
Sorry about that, everybody.
All right.
Let's wrap it up.
That's the end of the episode.
Patreon, whatever.
Pledge.
Epic.
Buy a, buy a, buy a Blu-ray.
Don't pledge the PCP patron this week.
This week buy a Blu-ray instead.
Yeah.
Nice.
Epic.
Okay.
Good, good bye.
The end.
Good bye.
Bye.
Okay.
stopping can I stop being a snake now yeah we can yeah oh yeah that's right three
two one go sink I meant to say I meant to say sink sorry okay three two one
sink sink sink sink oh boy that was bad is horrible the delay is way worse than
usual today