Listen, listen, I'm not out there every day, you know, put on my heart,
hard hat, I'm not out there, you know, getting a jack hammer to the roadside to install
some more plumbing. I'm just out there rubbing lotion on old people, rubbing lotion on dead
people, just trying to get them all lubed up for the afterlife, you know what I'm trying
to say? God, you know, you know when you're a kid and you don't know better and you don't
know what's rude, and you have a grandma, and you just want to touch her flabby little
elbows and her arms and her forearm, you just want to fucking get your all grubby hands
all up in there with some lotion. Well, you know, she's got flabby skin, you know, she's
got skin hanging off her and you just want to go rub all around. Why? Why? Alright, alright,
guys, here's the intro. Guys, I've been working on an intro, I've been waiting for the day
when Nate would finally leave us alone for once, and I've got the intro. Here, let me
know what you think. I hope you're recording all this. Oh, oh, oh, I am. Slippity slap,
put on a hat. Slippity slap, put on a hat. It's time for an episode of the PCP, guys.
Wow. I'm so upset, I'm such a virgin, no one will have sex with me, you know, I'm going
to die alone, I'm so upset about it, and I think I might just have to resort to some
sort of outward acts of violence. What do you guys think? Do you guys think that I should
do something brash and reckless due to the fact that I have so much inward self-loving
based on my fact that I'm a virgin? Talking about weapons of mass destruction? No, I'm
talking about like AK-47s, I'm talking about like tech nines. I think we didn't sync our
audios yet. We didn't, we can do another show. Yeah, like we said, like we were just talking,
we're bringing the A content today, like syncing the audio on the show. Alright, on the count
of three, let's say good podcast. One, two, three, good podcast. Okay, let's just say
good next time. One, two, three, good. I want you to know that I made air quotes around
a good podcast. Yeah, that's fair. Yeah, listen. Hello everybody and welcome to the
Procrastinator's podcast, none of that is in the podcast, this is the podcast now. I
hope not. No, why? Because look, how does it look? Okay, we all know that we're having
a good time, we're having a great time and we want to bring it to the people, but you
know, you know that Nate comes, but Nate listens to the episode, and what's his takeaway? Oh
yeah, right. These guys can't run a podcast without me. Oh, without me, it just descends
into chaos, unprofessionalism, and we can't, we can't have him tighten his iron grip any
further, will strangle us. The hallmark, the poster child of sheer madness and chaos is
us doing a cold open laughing. That's what you can easily use no hand wave away, that's
pure unorganization. He'll hear that and he'll take off his headset and he'll put it down
and he'll look out the window sadly and he'll shake his head and he'll say things have really
gone downhill around here. The ideal PCP intro for Nate is all this like solemn in change
wearing, you know, prison jumpsuits, looking down on your keyboard, not even looking up
at the audacity recording, and him just blathering away for 35 minutes while we just whimper out
affirmative yeses and mm-hmms. I think we should start with a liturgy. I think we should
start with prayers. Oh yes, yeah. Well, let's start with like saying who's on the podcast,
and then we can start by starting about the, we can start, I'm, hello, it's me, Hippocrite.
Oh, they know us. I'm ready, yeah. There's Mage, there's Tom, there's Ben, there's Munchy,
and there's also a secret guest. No, don't tell them about me. You know what's going
on? Is every time Nate's away, we destroy the podcast and make a fool of our own self.
I don't want to make a fool of myself. I want to, whoa.
Look, let's dismantle more PCP's. We want to make Nate feel like shit, and the only
way to make him feel like shit is to make him feel smugly superior. It's going to feel
smugly superior. He's going to be secondhand embarrassed for associating with such degenerates.
Guys, guys, you're talking about him? He already won.
No.
Oh gosh.
That's true.
Welcome to the Procrastinate's Podcast, everybody. This is the new Procrastinate's Podcast.
Merry Christmas. This is the beginning of the episode, and nothing has been in the previous.
We sure have been talking for two hours prior to this recording.
We haven't been talking at all about no one in particular. It's me, Hippocrite. Today,
we have with us, Mage.
I am alive.
We have Tom Oliver.
And we have Hippo.
We did it. We did it, guys. We did it. We did it without he who shone off me name.
Hey, it's me, Munchy, doing also the Procrastinate's Podcast intro while Hippo's doing it. Next,
we have Hippo.
Next, we have Ben St. Hi.
Hi, I'm Hippo.
Next, we have Ben St.
Even when he's not here.
Next, we have Mage.
We're wrapped up. He's our abusive boyfriend. He leaves his mark on us.
Dude, I have the ultimate in shitty podcast audio quality right in front of me. I ordered
food, and it came just before we started to record, and I'm hungry, so I'm going to take
a big old bite of this chicken burger.
Oh.
All right, get ready.
Chicken burger.
I'm going to eat through the entirety of the podcast to make it really bad.
We already did that. That was a bonus episode.
Remember everyone's favorite bonus episode, talking while eating?
Can you believe this terrible thing that Hippo did? Wouldn't it be so funny if I would
do this thing in the entire podcast? We already have done that and charged for it.
This is a teaser trailer. Go to the bonus PCP to see that for real.
Wait, Hippo, you got to say the line. We remember we used to advertise the bonus episodes,
and you would be the one to make the trailer for it.
You know, talking with your mouth full every single time.
Hey, you know what I want to talk about? I want to talk about how this is not well-munchy.
It's so cool that you fucking hate the PCP, even though it's not even true, but it's easy
for people to take that away, even though that's not what I mean ever.
We all hate the PCP, man, but not real.
It's cool.
I want to talk about how the PCP's views are stagnant and how I want everyone to not have
that happen anymore. So let's discuss how it's the fans fault for that.
Okay. If we do that, we'll drive away, we'll drive away, if our views are stagnant, it
just means that we've got our dedicated fan base.
Right, we have our cult.
Yeah, we're not gaining new ones, but we've got the old ones that are on lock. We've given
them Stockholm Syndrome, and now they can't escape. We've got the sunk cost fallacy, and
now they've invested too much time listening to us, and now it would be a waste to stop.
You know, I'm not trying to gain YouTube here, I'm not trying to get the PCP to launch
into PewDiePie, Tobuscus level. I just like seeing numbers go up, that's my one and only
goal here.
Literally, why are you talking like you're up at four in the morning looking at pornography
on your 1998 AOL internet connection, and you don't want your parents to wake up?
Listen, some people, they jack it to Fuda, some people jack it to Femdom, I jack it to
the Procrastinaires podcast.
Oh, every time?
Every single time, yeah.
Alright, unironically, the PCP to me feels like the niche content that is like lesser
than all of the small other projects that we do. Like the PCP is the offshoot from the
podcast, I Am Games, and like everything. Like it feels like this is the least viewed
out of all of the smaller projects that we do.
I don't even think it's true though.
It's not the least viewed, but I know what you mean. Like, Tom, I think when we were
talking about this, you brought this up, and I wholeheartedly agree that the PCP is not
really an enterprise in and of itself. It's sort of a well or a cistern, or like a sewer,
if you will, like a sewage drainage pipe where like our other projects will garner attention,
and then people that are interested in that will follow us down the drain and end up here.
Yeah, this is like the end of the funnel. Except the end of the funnel is usually how
you get the money, so.
But okay, but consider this, we did have smaller numbers before, and then we got big numbers,
and then those big numbers turned into normal numbers, and now we have those now. Do you
think that that's purely just from people finding our individual content? Because there
were a lot of people back in late A, saying like, oh, I'm a big PCP fan. Dude, I showed
my friends the PCP, and they were like, holy shit, I didn't know people could be this funny.
And then they turned three years old the next year, and they stopped watching. But the point
is, is that people used to watch the show, like, not independently from our own stuff,
but they thought it was like, you know, the main content. And who thinks the main content
is the PCP anymore?
Let me pause it an actual theory about this. I think I might have the answer. Like, these
days, what are we all doing these days? Like, we're doing, like, I'm chugging away on vapors,
which I want to talk about that in a minute. But like, you know, mostly lately we've been
working on Endless War, which is so niche. You know, like, Hippo, you've stopped making
like, mainstream YouTube stuff. Tom, you've pretty much, you've stopped making YouTube
stuff and you're working on a Zoomy game now. Maid, you've been dead for a while. I think,
I think maybe back in the day, when we were growing, it was when we were doing like, you
know, mainstream consumable products, you know, like Hippo was making Hippocrite video
game reviews and stuff. Tom was doing like tech reviews, you know?
True. I don't know, though, because like...
Just for the record, I am working on something, but it might not come into fruition anytime
soon, so I'd like to keep it for the most part a secret, but I'm not just sitting on
my hands for the most part. Don't worry.
Maid, you've never heard of a thing that takes a while to do.
Maid, you gotta follow Maid on Twitter for those amazing androgynous, confused characters.
Boys who don't know what a boy is. Yeah, they're going to be...
Excuse you.
I don't know, because like, we weren't like, super big in those fields. Do you think it's
the idea that we were making stuff, like, created an environment where it seems like
we're cool, and now we're not cool because they don't see stuff?
Well, all I was suggesting was just that, you know, we as a collective were getting
more views through that more mainstream digestible content. However, I think there's something
to be said, yeah, for the perception that, you know, we are all YouTubers, which was
never really true, but it was maybe truer at some point in the past than it is now,
that we were all YouTubers, and we were all embarking on this YouTube adventure together,
you know? We were like a guild of some kind on this unified quest, and like, we've all
diversified our shit, and like, we've all gone in all these crazy fucking individual
directions now, and it's maybe a little less like that.
I thought of a counterpoint that scares me. Yeah.
I was going to say, sure, we were making more mainstream content.
I hate quiet munchies so much.
Raise your fucking voice.
Listen, I'm in a high-rise apartment in downtown Boston. I'm making Mad Bank. I'm the vice
president of TripAdvisor, and I don't need this sort of this rabble rousing and all these
screams and these maims coming from you lower class. I'm just trying here to make a quick
buck.
Why don't you get Munchie off? Let's get the rowdy fucker on here instead.
Oh, I hate that guy.
Me too, man.
I thought for a moment, like, you know, oh, sure, we were making more mainstream stuff
before, but you know, people like niche stuff. People surely like our stuff now, because it's
more interesting. But then I thought for a second, maybe they don't. Maybe they don't want to get
you dumb, dumb, because a lot of people don't like it.
Well, sure. But I'm saying, you know, you would think that maybe your core audience would appreciate
what you're doing now, but I would think there's probably a lot of, like, for instance,
hippo fans who don't really, maybe not dislike his comics, but don't really like, oh, he's not
doing game reviews. Okay, bye. Sure, yeah, with Munchie fans who are like, oh, you know, I don't
like, you know, he's not doing an arm retrieval or, you know, whatever. I mean, think about it,
like, go way, way back. Like, the foundation of the PCP was the horseshoe crew, and everyone,
it was all YouTube. Like, everyone, you know, everyone who found us in the horseshoe days found
us through YouTube, maybe not everyone, but almost everyone, you know, everyone that found us once
the PCP became a thing, you know, in the postponement, they all found us through the PCP on YouTube.
Like, most of us were on YouTube making YouTube stuff, you know, people have found me through the
the Sonichu lecture, and come come here through that, and that's YouTube. So, you know, and it's
I mean, it makes sense. It's obvious when you lay down like that, but it's just kind of, I don't know,
startling in a way to think, to maybe some people, we've just completely abandoned what made us good,
and we're going to be the stars of YouTube videos, I mean, like, like, how how they lost their spark,
or, you know, like, fall straight. Yeah, yeah. Like, like, Ben St. Stop doing My Little Pony
Reviews, and he became a pokey tuber. Like, that is just great. It's scary. It's scary and a little,
almost like, nauseating. Not not in the sense that like, oh, you make me sick, but it's just kind
of like a sickening thought. Like, yeah, there's probably a lot of people, maybe, you know, people
that have like seen my, say, the Sonichu video, and think that that's what I'm about. And like,
the fact that I'm not doing that means that to them, I'm effectively dead. It's like, I've effectively
quit doing anything as far as they're concerned. I really, I really dislike, like, I don't mind
the fact that people do that, but like, it annoys me, just conceptually. This idea that on the
internet, it's, it's like, if you're not creating a constant stream of something, if you're not
maintaining a presence, then people immediately forget about you. And you'd need to be like,
the best of the best of all time for people to actually care. And even then, they'll just get
mad that you're not uploading frequently enough. Well, I understand, because if like, you know,
I'm watching a YouTube creator or YouTube channel, and he's making one type of content,
I'm going to subscribe to him because I like that content. And if he totally shifts gears,
it's not that I'm thinking, oh, this guy is terrible. This guy's lost all his creative
inspiration. She's like, well, I didn't sign up for this. I hate having the mentality applied
to me, but I absolutely apply it to everyone else. I'm just as guilty of this as anybody else.
And it's interesting. Well, I don't expect the people to suddenly like my comics. I expect that
to be a completely different thing. I just, when it was like what I was doing, if you stay away from
the internet for even a week, people are like, what the fuck? And I'm like, shut up. You don't
know how long it takes to do anything. Yeah. Right. Right. Well, I mean, how could they?
A little kid, John Tron made like a post like back on normal booths like way a long time ago,
talking about his like upload schedule. We can't talk about John Tron anymore.
I heard he said some bad things. When PewDiePie way back on normal booth, oh,
wait, shit, went to a buskets, oh, wait, shit, when, um, when, um, when Harvey Weinstein,
oh, wait, shit, non-descript internet YouTuber celebrity. Yeah.
He was discussing his upload schedule and he was talking about how like, yeah, I'm sorry,
guys, like I fucked up. I shouldn't have said I would have a bi-weekly schedule. It's, you know,
that's bi-weekly. Yeah, bi-weekly schedule. It's way too short of time to make a good video. And
I'm like, bi-weekly, I can, that's like two weeks, dude. You could do anything in two weeks.
That's what you're talking about. This just makes me think of, uh, like, like the new T-Bap,
like Tom, you said it, like the, like the old T-Baps, we made them in a weekend. We, we rushed
them out. We had deadlines and we stuck to them religiously. The new one has no hard deadline.
And for that reason, it's taken us like, like for the better part of a year. I mean, we haven't,
we weren't working on it for a long time after, right, but you know, it's been a long fucking time.
And it's like shit, man. We, we all need, we all need the deadlines of a weekly children's
cartoon to whip us all back into shape, I think is what we're getting to here. There's definitely
something to be said about a deadline. Please, please, please rescue yourself from my scorn.
Surely this P-Bap is more intensive. Well, I mean, obviously. Yeah, okay. But however, you know,
counter to that. I somehow doubt that like, it will be, you know, a more of a hit. Like, I don't,
like, even though more work has gone, like this, this, this T-Bap is not going to get like, you
know, insane views or anything proportional to the amount of work that was put into it. Not,
not even, not by a long shot. I mean, that's just because you dropped off the map of pony reviews
and people wouldn't be expecting it, except the small amount of people who that played
the Frog Frashions fans. I imagine if it does blow up and all the Pony people are just like,
oh my god, these guys are great. I wish they were T-Baps back and Phantomore can finally make his big
cameo revisit on analysis anarchy. Oh, no. Do we have to go back? Do we say something, mage?
Yeah, I wouldn't, because I feel like there will not be a good time to remind you this,
because we'll always be talking about something. You are going to put me on blast and I'm just,
I'm really scared and I want to get that band-aid off. Don't, we don't have to do that right now.
We don't have to, I have written down here. I will, I will, stop hurting me. I will get to it.
All right, mage. Stop hurting me and hurt me already. I'll tell you how you broke, I'll tell
you how you broke my heart. Oh no. Yeah. I was in, we were in, you know, we were in, I was in
New Los Angeles City for Slimer Nailia, right? The, the, the, the week of Slimer Nailia.
And who do I see? Who do I see in the RFCK Discord, but none other than mage,
Uwu. And I get so happy, I'm so happy. I'm like, mage finally joined the Discord.
She finally took my advice, joined the Discord and listed killers, became purple, like, like,
it was always her destiny. And then I see that, no, it's just a troll. It's just Shawnee. It's
just Shawnee, that wily trickster god putting on one of his many hats, one of his many disguises.
And I was crestfallen, crestfallen, mage. So, so, so that's what I didn't do.
That's right. That's right. And now I'm putting you on blast for it.
Well, I, I don't understand. I'm not sure if I should be apologizing.
I guarantee you should. If, if only you had joined the, the thing already,
then there would be no confusion. I, I made it clear I have no interest
in fighting people over slime things. You can farm. You can farm.
She's already lifted in real life, Ben. A Discord server just doesn't satisfy the urge for mage
anymore. Instead of slime, mage, you should join my server, the, the mud puddle, and become a mud,
mud knight. No, no, no, no, no, there's no fighting. There's no fighting. The mud puddle is all about
just wallowing in, in, in the swamps and doing nothing on Discord. Mage needs to start her own
purple server where everybody fights with Pokemon skeletons. You gotta, you gotta start a gang that
just fights with the bones of Pokemon that you dig up. The, the, the, the violent violets,
they'll be the gang. Oh shit, yeah. Here's, like the other day, because like last PCP we talked about,
the Discord's going to war. I riled up my boys and, and I created some lore for my server,
the mud puddle. And then we're like, we're like the Abyss. We're like the, the, the downtrodden,
like, dregs of human society covered in filth and muck, swallowing in the dirt. And we're here to
drag you all down and drown you and make you into a, into a bunch of gross shit. And that's us,
and that's what we're here to do. And you have to be a mudblood. You can't be like special or
anything. You have to be a freaking loser. And mud is better than slime and mud cannot be defeated
by slime because mud is endless. And it's a lot of it. And I like, I want every Discord in the
world to have like a cool lore and fighting style, not, not necessarily because we're going to make
every server a bot server where you can do stuff, but just as like a cool aesthetic thing. So you
can wave your flag. My server has some of that, has some like some, some vague role lore going on,
but it could be codified. It could be codified a lot better. We've got the rank and file soldiers
of the Wastoid's in Ben Stelfire. Are like Protestant Christians and Catholic Christians,
where, you know, we can fight a lot, you know, we can have some hard times, the rising killers
can kill each other mercilessly in the street over and over ad nauseam forever. But then we just,
we look a little bit to the, to the east and we see some Muslims and we just, like we just
on cue both simultaneously. And we just, we can't have that. No, sorry. Yeah, no, no, you know,
we may hate each other, but you know, we hate other people even more. So we have to kill them.
We have to team up to be able to destroy them. It's game of, it's game of Discord communities.
We like, we will, killers and rowdies will come together to protect their fair city from a mutual
threat. Disgusting though. What happens when the hippos invade? What happens when the mud envelops
in the swamp? Talk about niche content. What the fuck are we talking about right now?
This is the real shit. This is the raw shit. This is what we care about deeply. We want to,
viewer, listen, we invite you to join us on this quest of inner beauty and self-discovery.
You know, we invite, invite, we're inviting you into our world, into our private world
of, of whatever the fuck we're talking about right now. Come along. Come along. It's just,
it's just way more interesting. Like YouTube, I see like is 100% explanations about something or
other. And I'm like, I don't want to explain. I want to create. That's why I like all this Discord
shit because it's, it's very creative and it's very silly. And it's very on the fly. And it's like,
you're interacting with people. It's like having a comment section, but like a real time comment
section, but you don't even have to stream to do it. You just talk to people live. It's great.
Was it, was it, you always talking to Munchie about how like Discord has changed how, how people
like talk to each other on the internet? It was me who told that to you. Yes. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Well,
it was a conversation we were having. You and I. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know. We're partners in this,
I guess. Whatever. It was, whatever. I was in, well, if it wasn't you, then I was going to bring
it as my own idea, but whatever. Yeah. It's interesting. I never thought about it before.
Like I had, I mean, has everyone on the internet migrated to Discord? Has everyone given up on
Skype? I'm super big. My original point was back in like Skype and stuff like that.
You know, you had group chats, but you had to be friend, someone in order to get into those chats.
And there were more like friend groups. There were some like big, you know, 100 people groups,
but those were few and far in between. And again, you had to be friend, so maybe an admin or a
member or something like that to even get into them. With Discord, it shifted away from like
friend groups to like capital S servers that are borderline independent communities and
completely communities, completely revolving around one aspect, you know, maybe a game or
a show or something like that, or even just, you know, common interests or, you know,
something niche like endless war. But the point is that they aren't friend groups per se. They can
become friend groups. And sometimes they are friend groups. I have some, you know, IRL friend
group Discord servers, but most of the time they are like independent communities. Yeah, that you
join and you can partake in, you know, in whatever you want. They're like forms interpersonal
connections. They're like, yeah, they're sort of like forms. They just move super fucking fast.
Exactly. It's weird. It's very strange. It's a very strange world we live in now.
I don't know. I don't know what's so strange about it. It's just sort of chatting with,
it's a way to communicate with like a large amount of people very easily.
It's not that easy, though, because like, it does kind of feel like Discord servers and things
like that have replaced internet forums to a certain extent, but it's a totally different
experience. It doesn't feel the same at all. Because a Discord server goes by and like,
you pretty much have to be there, or you miss it. Whereas like a forum, it's like people are
posting and it's all archived and you read through the backlog. I don't really read through
backlogs on Discord very much because there's just too fucking much. And it shows Ben. It shows.
What do you? What do you? Yeah, I do. I do all the time. Who's got fucking time for that?
Who's got time for any of you freaks? Yeah, true. Apparently you do, since you're here.
I'm only here for that moolah, baby. Destroyed. I'm only here for that cassola.
Why does everyone sound like dead and or dying physically and or mentally? Well, you're talking
quiet. I thought I always sounded dead or down. Let me tell you a story, Hifo. I went to Canada.
I returned from Canada and then I got ill and almost died and my fever was very high.
What a story. What a cool story, dude. Why were you in Canada? Just another day in the life of
the violent violence. Was this on a podcast that I wasn't on? Did I miss the story of why you were
in Canada? No, that's the thing though. Like, I haven't been in an apartment. Like, this is my
first podcast after I've returned from Canada. Yeah, Mage has been gone for a while. Mage was
in my time zone and didn't even say hi to me. Discussing. Making a mistake, viewers. I'm not
bored or uninterested or sleepy. I just am quiet today. You're getting quiet much. It feels like
there's a different person. Yeah, it does feel, you know, like I'd seen in Men in Black. It feels
uncanny. Where the bug just like wears the guy's skin. I feel like that's happening with you right
now. I think, I don't know if it was you, Tom, who described this to me, but I think it was at
your house, at DigiHouse last trip to Boston, where I was just talking, I don't know, pretty
seriously about college or something. Or maybe it was on an episode and everyone was aghast.
Everyone didn't know how to react to me. That happened on like six different episodes.
No one just can't. Everyone just can't. It's still doesn't sink in though.
Yeah. It will never sink in. Hey, hey, did we, did it, is it, is it kosher if I bring up the whole
Vic thing? Because people told me, people told me that Vic like criticized me on the college thing,
but I listened to what he said. And like, it was so, it didn't even feel like criticism. I don't
know. People, people told me like, man, Vic put the PCP on blast. And like, I was, he was pretty
anti-Ben with it. And I listened to it. And he's like, it's totally not. He disagrees with us not,
like, you know, with us, like discouraging college and stuff, you know,
I'm so mutual on that, by the way. I, you know, I mean, I don't know. I've thought about it in my,
my position. Like, I was never like totally against. I'm just, you know, hesitant. I'm
hesitant and, and, and concerned about the merits of it. But I'm not like totally, I don't know.
I guess I just wanted to say that people told me some people, people hyped that up like it was a
big dramatic thing. And then I listened to it and it wasn't, you know, just like everything else in
life. That I have not seen any of those videos besides hippos. And I assume due to the fact that
they're the college topic that are all revolving around me. And it's more fucking noise on that
front, which I don't really care for the other way to hear more affirmation or, or negativity.
Yeah. Doesn't really, I don't need that. So I've seen that, that they can help you to come out.
Then I've seen Digi's rebuttal. And I thought no fucking thanks. I didn't see Digi's rebuttal.
Digi's video was just a apology, general. Okay. I saw hippo's video. And his description is like,
he really replies to Digi and his description events sound so strange that I had no, I have no idea
what I had stumbled onto. It was so different than what I had thought. So how often do gangsters come
up in the discussion? It was, it was just once. It was, they were, they were talking. That was,
that was the dumbest thing by far. Well, but, but hippo, you agreed with it. You like, you were
like defending the argument. I was, I was defending, which again, I didn't hear his original argument,
but I heard your rebuttal to it. The basic gist was they were talking about college and
what a college degree can get you. And it like is a good reason for college. The doctors were
brought up, lawyers were brought up. And then Digi brought up like illegal doctors could only go
into the gangsters. And like Mae was like, what the fuck are you talking about? And Digi had been
like smoking weed like during the episode. And it was very funny. But I thought he had a point
and he was getting shut down because he was smoking weed. And I decided to defend him.
PCP or is this on? No, this was on Digi and Mae Pokemon Colosseum. Let's play.
Right, right, right. Okay, okay. Well, I, well, I, we probably don't need to go any further into
all that. You know, there's already like a, there's already a constellation of minor
videos, reaction videos about it. I just want to, I just, I just want to know if there's anything
I'm missing out. Is there any sort of like a knowledge bomb that Victor or did you have dropped
that changed the conversation? Digi, Vicks is very, Vicks is very pro college and thinks college
is a good idea. I mean, did the only thing that was definitely there are arguments for that.
Victor's video was that like college can be good. And he goes on to basically say that like,
the PCP in general is kind of on the downswing. And like, we're not doing enough. And a lot of
like, like no one would want our lives lifestyle is basically what the gist was.
In so many words.
Well, I mean, the statement college can be good is the most
That's pretty uncontroversial.
Right. I guess the only thing, because like, Digi made a response video and he tried not to
include Munchy in it at all, because it was just supposed to be his thesis on college,
which is just everything we've already heard, but said for everyone can hear it now,
not in his own house when it was like Halloween or whatever.
And he was just, you know, just went over the same fucking points, whatever.
Okay, but there were some things that Victor said in his video that like,
weren't 100% accurate to like what we've been saying and stuff, I guess, and she was trying
to clarify that. I don't mean the reason the Victor thing was a big deal is because he went
into all of us for like, not producing content. And the fact that some of us that was saying
college is bad. And like, you're not successful. So how can you say that you idiot?
And it was like a bit like, incendiary. I thought it was funny, because like Victor is
too chuckly to seem like an actual dangerous man. Like if he had a knife, he'd be laughing,
I'd be laughing along with him. So like, it was, you know, it was just a little,
like slight drama bump, like brony style drama. It's not even actually a thing.
It's not, yeah, it's not, if you watch a video, like, at first I was like, I don't know, like the
only thing that felt weird is that it's some of the stuff Victor had say at the time felt like he
was just like, because I haven't talked to him since Radcon. So it was like, between Radcon and
now, did he suddenly like get on a different wavelength or something? But it was fine. It was
not a big deal. It's not even worth talking about right now. That's how unimportant it is.
It's so hard to keep up tabs with Victor. Granted, I haven't tried that hard. I mean,
I guess if I wanted to do that, I would be watching the, you know,
Vic and Hope, the Vic and Hope channel, but I haven't been watching any, any such like,
Let's Play videos. I've recently outlawed Let's Plays for my life. I've made a restriction
where I can no longer watch them as a mental health. Yeah, I jumped back into them. I like Vic
and Hope. I don't watch it because it's breath in the wild and it sucks to look at. But yeah,
and the Digi and Main stuff. I like a bit of Let's Play talking about shit,
because it is kind of like, it's a weird format because they're friends and they know you.
And when they talk about you, it's kind of like you're listening in on a conversation,
but they're making it public. It's such a weird, you would never get that in a formal podcast,
necessarily. It feels more like a conversation that you, you, you just have like the key to, to,
to snoop around in the back and listen to them. I'm actually going to rescind. I'm going to rescind
my last statement that it's so hard to keep up with the Victor. It's actually, I assume,
I assume it wouldn't be that hard if I tried at all. 100% my fault. I used to fucking watch a Digi
bro every single day it came out. I was the most religious team Victor fan of all time. Victor's
my spicy bro. Victor is an official spicy bro. But what have I done to keep him tabs with them?
I haven't fucking messaged him and probably literally a year, if not more. I have not been
listening to his podcast. I've not even been attempting to keep up with him. I've just assumed,
you know, haha, he's not on discord or at least I don't think he's in the server,
right now. No, no, I, I know he has a discord account, but I think he made one specifically to
join the, the PCP discord, correct me if I'm wrong, but I'm, that's probably true. Yeah, I don't think
that he's on it. He's, he's notoriously like not on the net. Yeah. So I think if I were to text him
or something, it would be a gale of time, but this is just, I don't know. This is another example of
just, I assume things are hard so I don't do them and therefore my life is terrible. Yeah,
yeah. Radical. I rescind everything that I said. Victor is an angel. Let's start the podcast over.
Yeah. Hey guys, welcome to the PCP. Here we've got Ben. Bye. This is sketchy later.
Just Ben, just, just Ben. Ben is the only one here. I don't, I, no, I'm not trying, I'm not trying
to make this all about the discord. I'm not trying to make this an rfck thing or anything,
but I do really want to talk about the fact that I was up all night last night making slimeoid
battles and this past week we really slimeoids and I'm just so fucking excited. I'm just so
fucking enthused. Ben, hold on. I'm gonna let you finish. I'm gonna let you finish. Yeah. We do have
our own show, you know. What are you, what are you talking about? We can just talk about this on
rfck. There's no reason. Why can't I talk about it here? I wanna fucking share what I'm passionate
about with my fucking friends, you piece of shit. Okay, no problem. Okay. What I'm saying
is that it's basically the entire topic so far has been like rfck. No it fucking hasn't. What the
fucking talking about. It's been, it's been prevalent. It's been prevalent. No, it has not. It has been
ancillary and best. Continue.
Quite Munchy is like such a, like a psychopath. He's such a piece of shit. You know what happened?
Munchy has stolen so many dads. He just is a dad now. That's what we're experiencing.
What are you talking about? Listen guys, I'm not trying to be stern right now. I know you're not
trying to but like the fact that- I can be fun too. I'm just one of the boys. You know I'm just
one of the boys. Guys, what are you playing now? It's Mario still playing. Listen to this
wolf in sheep's clothing. Oh, it's funny. It's weird that Munchy being the youngest one is
currently doing the hello fellow kids. I know. I think so. Ben, do you know if there's a
discord server that I can join and play in browser for free and that might be text based
based on old mud type games? Do you know- I might have heard of- Oh yeah, the mud puddle. Go to
discord.com.com. Splash. Ben, what are you talking about? Slymoids. I just- I don't know. I just-
Someone ask me something about them. I just want to gush about them. Dude, what the fuck?
Dude, what the fuck? Sweet Mouse messaged me like two hours ago being like,
hey, so I want to make the best Slymoid I can make for when Slymoid battling becomes a thing.
Let me ask you some questions about Slymoid Brains. How does Slymoid Brains work? And I was
like, oh my god, I'm so fucking enthused to tell you all about how Slymoid Brains work, dude.
I was like, man, this- this brain does this and that. This one sucks. This brain is pretty good
if you want to do this kind of thing. And I don't know how this is going to work yet, but probably
this brain will be- This brain's like nature's-
Basic, more or less. You can- you can- you can choose all the different parts. You can- you
assemble your- your Slymoid from all these different parts and you get to choose what kind of brain
it has. And depending on what kind of brain you give it, it will have- well, it has different like
personality behaviors when you interact with it and it like behaves- it's gonna like behave
differently and it's gonna have like a different AI sort of- sort of controlling it. Um, it's so
so fucking cool. I'm just so fucking jazzed about it 24 hours a day.
It's good that you actually finished the thing you were trying to do because you've got a lot of
stuff to- to- to get done and you're always like- you've been like stressing out about Slymoids for a
while. So yeah, that's good to be done. The end of season one was when I started working on Slymoids
and then- It's been a while. Yeah, it was like a long- and then like season two came out and the
code was all different and I got frustrated and then I took another crack at it and I realized
that like it needed to interact with the database and the way I didn't understand so I got my friend
John to fucking show me how the database works and then I went back to it and I realized that nothing
I had written would work with how I now understand the database to work so I had just fucking redo
it all from scratch and then the other like a week ago or two weeks ago now maybe or something
like that I finally finished it and then- and then it comes out and everyone loves it. Everyone's
making their slime but it's not like okay now it's time for the most arduous task of all taking
everything I've done and build- and building upon it to create Slymoid battle system. Okay,
I'm gonna have to throw out everything I did before and start from scratch and then I tested it
and like everything that I made from battle system actually worked fine and it just needed
minor tweaks and it was done in like a day and a half so that's coming out really soon. Ben and I
hung out a week ago when you're listening to this and I can confirm that every 30 minutes
when there was like a slight lowland conversation like a two second gap here you just sigh and say
oh when Slymoid battling comes out like you'll all see you'll all rue the day you picked on little old
Ben at the same. Yeah. You'll all realize the fool you know yourselves returning me down for
for junior prom. Yeah exactly. When I just showed up with my new Slymoid wife. The whole motivation
for this was that when Jenny shot you down that was the moment you decided someday I'm gonna have a
discord server. Jenny I miss you you bitch! Ben I just want to know when are you doing your sabbatical
you've been talking about sabbatical for like three fucking months and I have not I have not
seen you turn hide nor tail. You know the truth okay so when we recorded when we recorded that
17 hour nightmare horror show rfck episode. We're gonna do that again I hope you know.
No we're not I'm never playing sprawl ever again. No we're not we don't we don't do
brawls. Okay well when we recorded that yeah I talked in the conversation about how I wanted to
take a sabbatical from the internet and the truth is that I kind of have been like I haven't been
like on my discord very much I haven't really been like doing much on the internet so I just
I don't know I just didn't like at the time I thought maybe I would announce like okay I'm
unplugging from the internet and I'm going away for like you know a month or two until
shit's done but then like I don't know just something clicked in my head like maybe a week
or two ago and like suddenly I fucking buckled down and I got slymoids done and I like I did like
two new vapors pages in like three days and that was like you know a recent record that was I couldn't
believe how long it had been I had let that shit lie fallow for so long it was I can't
fucking believe how long it went without drawing a new page I hate it I fucking hate it but I'm
but it's okay but it's okay because I'm back so I'm fucking back and slymoids are done and it's
all about the vapors now you know what you know it's slightly also too bad which is also almost
done you know it's like you're disturbing bin yeah for for our relationship as humans is that you
can like log off from the internet from the internet softcore and I view no change in the
amount of time that like we interact in fact it almost goes up in a way I haven't been logged off
I just have not been engaging with like I haven't really been on Twitter you haven't really been
in my discord I've just been like there was a lot of wasting of time on the internet and now
you're using the internet for the constructive purpose I didn't view it as wasting of time
I just I viewed it as like you know arranging of time I well at that like like being on Twitter
and being in discord like that's how I like interact with people but yeah I think maybe
it was cutting in it was I was doing it at the expense of like you know working on shit
and I mean you're I mean you're supposed to interact with people right you're not supposed
to just work and not talk to anyone right no yes I think yeah that's something very important
and yet at this moment I feel so much better about things since I've stopped doing anything
since I've stopped communicating with people and just been working instead well I mean I feel if
you if it's been so long I was I was in balance yeah you were I was in balance I was in balance
and I've tilted the other way now and and it'll feel good for a while until you start feeling
the longing for social interaction I mean you know you gotta balance the back out
moderation in all things as I'm sure you know like no I don't know moderation I can't do it I can't
do anything but not like I can't I can't do anything without throwing myself into it completely
and being like this is what I am now then there are huge and the same goes for the everything I can't
like I can't like tape or something back I just if I if I if I tape or something back at all if I
push something even slight if if something goes behind anything else in my mind's eye it's gone
it's gone and I don't touch it I'm a hundred percent on board with this horrible mentality
it's horrible it's it's ruined everything there's a huge difference between talking to people in
your discord fan server and talking to your friends there's I would say that like what is
important for you to do sure like networking and and you know like community management quote
unquote is important but I would say what most people mean when they say you guys talk to people
you can't just focus on your art is just talk to your friends and get more input even just for
your art it's important to have second opinions and stuff like that it's not so much people are
thinking oh yeah go post on forums you got you gotta you gotta go post on some forums uh you know
you meet your form post quota for every comic page you make it's more like you gotta have
more fucking human action genuine ones watching a presentation uh some guy was making this point
that like artists are terrible at like networking or like making time in person to like talk about
their craft um he was this thing was specifically talking about like actors he was presenting
something like actors thing but he just like it said applied to artists in general because he was
saying like you know the most of the time that like when you're an actor and you see other actors
is when you're like going for a role and you all want to kill each other because we're all fighting
like there's never a time when you can just talk about your craft in a like normal kind of friendly
way and like artists in general are bad right if you're if you're an actor and you're doing like
some performative art or something you know your art and your job means you're interacting with people
like right now you know i'm talking to other humans right now i'm talking to hippo ben tom and mage
like i can like trick myself and they're thinking all right that's that's good enough human interaction
you know i've got my fill for today no more please and just go back to working on you know endless
work code or whatever it is that i do but i mean i'm not trying to say that this podcast isn't you
know good or that we shouldn't do and it's not good for our friendship or anything i'm just saying
like this is not really you know this is way different than when me and ben were hanging right
this isn't shooting the shit we're all putting on a subtle performance right now we're all exaggerating
and regressing parts of our personality in order to be more entertaining this is not the way we
talk to each other off camera i don't want to glorify shooting the shit or anything like it's
not like i think it's like a super productive thing to do i just think your mind sort of
cag lugs it differently i think it's i think it's healthy to shoot the shit every once in a while
at the very least i think human interaction is important in person iRL for real i mean i would
say that even though we were you know shooting the shit and talking casually we weren't trying to fill
every you know silence gap with with you know content for people to drown in we did talk about
you know art and work stuff yesterday ben we did talk about stuff to do it was i wouldn't say maybe
productive but i mean that's how all ideas are made right you know two friends are talking
and they think huh maybe we should do this you know maybe they made a joke and they're like you
know that could turn into a real projects and boom bada bing bada boom you've got a t-bap or
something like that you know i've talked about this on the show before um it doesn't feel that
different being on here than it does just talking to someone in a normal setting because like
you're always performing right even if you're just talking to a person in real life like
you're still on it to a degree it's not like oh now i'm on but when it's my friends in real life
i'm not no i'm still like trying to be i'm still like i'm still like trying to be cool and trying
to make people like me through the way that i interact with them like that that doesn't turn
off no i think you turn it up or down though depending on the the context of the situation
well i don't think i don't think i don't think i don't think maybe aside from munchie i don't
think we really put on that much of a show um individually on the pcp because it ends up being
you know just us talking about stuff generally like i've seen in in radcons like we would make
jokes that we would make in a podcast in real life we would do funny things all the time and
then we would have quieter moments where somebody's just talking about something and it's like it
feels pretty much the same i mean anyway the difference is the conversation itself the conversation
topics where i would probably talk about and ask about way different things on a podcast and i would
ask someone else you know one-on-one in person or you know in a group in person just hanging out
talking casually when i'm talking here the sort of topics they bring up are usually meant to be
you know entertaining in one way or another either i guess i guess that's why the podcast
sucks is i don't think about what could be entertaining for the audience enough um i think
i whereas i would probably ask more i don't know personal things that i would usually want to talk
about more you know i would bring up wouldn't be necessarily be good podcast material it would
just be something i want to know about you what you've been doing and you know what you want to
continue to do i would be happy and talk about you know maybe some some taboo drama that's come
up recently with ben that you know we can't talk about on the show because there's none of there's
none of that by the way that's there is no i was i was wondering what it really sounded like you
were hinting at something no i just want to like no there's no that that's a hypothetical yeah
oh but you know what i mean right you get you get what i'm trying to yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah it's a different sort of air it's a different i mean i mean it's not exactly i don't think i'm
putting on a character right now like i don't think that like munchie is separated from how i am in
real life i don't even think that he's particularly like some sort of like on staroids hidden version
of how i am it's just i get nervous when i get nervous i say kooky things and scream in parentheses
usually but you know when i'm off air i don't have to work i don't have to be nervous because i'm
just with my friends and i don't think they'll hate me if i say something wrong i mean they might
but i don't operate under the fact that they will i'm not i don't ever like i would never
consider talking with one of you guys like just off air like performing anything that's just how i am
when i'm talking to you guys that's just i don't know everything's like everything you do in life
is a performance even yourself sometimes if you want to be fucking if you want to wax philosophical
pseudo philosophically then okay maybe but i think there's a very clear at least in my you know in my
worldview very very distinct and clear difference recording a podcast and talking to someone else
it's not for me it's the lines the lines very blurry the lines very wide
gradient for me i mean i want to talk about just like the physical stuff i'm looking at my computer
screen i'm looking at a microphone right now i'm not looking at someone else's face but i'm but
i'm talking to you guys the same way that i would if i wasn't being recorded is what i'm getting at
sure i don't really think i'm i think there's still a bit of a difference just even if you don't
mean it it's still it's still maybe well maybe i can't maybe i can't accurately self assess that
it's it's a difference that nobody would ever like it's so um unique to you what you literally
actually acts like when nobody's watching right that nobody would ever know unless they spy on you
and i don't want to do that or do i what do you know now i'm interested to see if this comes across
at all in the way i speak when you guys like we're talking to me at during the non-recording
moments of icon three or even just when we were out you know doing something whatever when we were
talking casually do you sense much of a difference in the way that i am or is it all the only thing
that seems different is that sometimes on a podcast you'll have like an actual script in front of
you that you wrote and you read it but outside of that not really no i i do i don't like i haven't
the the things that are like recorded are like more memorable because i've seen them more than once
but like i do remember times when munchie is just sort of there and it's he's not like doing
boring you know yeah like like for a lack of a better term like not being haha it's me munchie
like how dare he not entertain the masses well i mean you're not doing that right now
like you're not you're not like that all the time not that he's not like being like a core
jester i mean like um he wouldn't necessarily have a thing on his mind to say next it would just be
like wherever the conversation is going um you know if he has something to say he'll say it if he
doesn't and he doesn't but like in a in a podcast there's this constant pressure to think of the
next thing that has to be said about this or like what you want what you want the the the public to
know you think about certain topics recording a podcast is like killing a vampire you're trying
to reload your shotgun while the vampire is making his moves and and and because of that you're not
looking at the vampire you're not trying to see where he's circle strafing or where he's moving
this lens you're just focused on reloading your own shotgun just shoot him with am i the vampire
we're all the vampire bin we're all the vampire no one's the shotgun the viewers of the shotgun
i i have a thing about like working and stuff you have to raise your hand before you can start
squeezing i did i've been raising it this whole time but you can't see because you're just looking at
the screen oh wow just another shotgun that's why you can't see your hand just another failure of the
medium of podcast not delivering me my raw friendship i couldn't see him raise his hand that
was crucial to my appreciation of him as a person uh my little brother who uh you may know as the
master kota who created uh runaway from snakes the video game buy it now on itchio.com slash
charlie batten uh cool guy obviously because he's my brother i like him he's making a new game which
is like oh wretched and clank-esque whoa what uh yeah he's got like a weapon wheel and he's figuring
out how to do like water ripple effects and stuff and he's got jumping it's really cute it's really
good and i'm really proud of him he needs to get in the iam games discord and get into the devlog
channel because we all circle jerk about our games and that and it's great motivation this
is gonna have a thousand fucking discord invite links yeah yeah yeah but uh he's doing all that
stuff and i'm like okay this is good this this means he is like still a like this is he hasn't
done a shade and like stopped making uh what he makes he hasn't done a shade and like stopped making
music he i i mean i haven't kept up the shade makes pizzas right he makes pizzas now he does make
pizzas yeah so like surely those aren't mutually exclusive well he's a manager so he's not like
making them deliberately i don't know maybe managers do maybe when it gets really busy the
the manager has to step out of his office he's got to like take off his suit and tie and put on
one of those blue shirts i'm like get some like flour on his hands like all right pizza it's time
fucking year i'm getting real pissed about it when is he gonna upload that 3d printed image
dude i want to 3d print the pizza myself i want to go to shade and be like shade i want a custom
pizza i want to request like down to the millimeter the amount of the thickness of the crust if you
if you pledge to shade on patreon to get a custom pizza
shade is making sick custom pizzas every month every month over you gonna say yeah yeah yeah um
so he's making a new game and he's intercoding stills which is this good thing for me because
i want to make another game um with his skills well i mean yeah it's like oh i'm not i'm not a
part of the creative process because whatever but like he is like my contractor or i'm the other
the other way around he is like the the muscle and i am the brains and i have to think of all
the cool shit but who's the heart and i'm just um it's it's a very it's annoying because i have
this idea for this game and i have an idea for a comic that will be you know like run away from
snakes was part of the bell jpeg comic my next comic i'm thinking oh i could make a game for that as
well and it'll be like a thing i do and and so i've got a new comic idea that is swirling around
in my head i've got a new game idea i've got this idea that i could like model the main character
in 3d and i'll be really cool do it i've got all these things going on and i can't do any of them
because i'm supposed to be doing something else with a deadline that is like eating up into my entire
december i haven't been doing anything other than working on this this one thing it sucks because
all these new cool ideas fresh and unique that i just can't spend any time working with
we gotta do this is what you gotta do you gotta you gotta write everything down every time you
have a cool idea write it down so you can get back to it when when you have i mean i have been writing
them down i got like google docs all the time for not writing them down and it is the most
retarded thing ever hit hippo before i respond to your actual point i just want to say whenever
you come to radcon or just after the pcp when we're recording you just splay your teeth out wide
and i just want to suckle it so badly but it's so hard i can never get it in one clean pump
it always leaves me so unsatisfied whenever i go pee so i have to hear this i get so fucking mad
whenever you're like um yeah you know i'm just like we're gonna move you like it's no big deal
i hate elk Baldwin you know you know what i mean uh and and then you know i approach you i corner you
to get some of that tid in my mouth and you're just like um well you know it's not really a big
deal so i'm not even really gonna talk about you know like whatever i'm just making the movies just
a script you know whatever i don't even care it is just a script i mean there's looks to it but
like i don't i don't know how to talk about it like i'm not a screenwriting analyst i didn't i
didn't cut my teeth on reviewing scripts or your shows all i know is that when you know occasionally
you'll post some work from from your or you know just talking about on the pcp chat it'll be like
a whole new world and and you'll post like some animated trailer that i'm not even supposed to
talk about don't worry haha uh and i'll just like lose my fucking mind because i like i don't
recognize my mind that it's like real because i don't know anything about it so i just think ah
hippo he he code it scripts that's just code word for gay sex he's just a gay person now that's what
he means because i haven't i don't know anything about it i actually see proof of it it just i
fucking go insane it's it's something i don't know how to upsell well i don't want to i don't
want like i don't want you to like fucking i don't know like like trying no no i i'll i'm okay with
talking about it a little bit it's just i don't really know how to to explain like what is it about
like i've been doing it for a while now so certain things i've learned and i've just come to accept
and i'm not sure which is like the most interesting part the most interesting part to me is that you
are in the industry and that is cool all this yes the pcp has built up a culture of anti-industry
for good reasons and i'm not trying to say that it's squeaky clean or anything but uh when it's
when did cartoons and movies stop being cool when did you know working in bank groups and having
you know a budget that stopped being cool it's nice to be in the industry you know who was in the
industry fucking don bluthy you know who was in the industry ariel from my little mermaid
i'm just trying to say some good things can happen when you got two people together fun and
in fact i uh one of the times i went to a thing for like pitching an animation show
i met an old dane danish man and he said he used to work with don bluth i was like oh
did you say yeah i know that guy it's not really a big deal like you're not really that special
because like you know like i played dragon lace too so yeah and i would be the shit out of him
and left him in the in the in the sewer yeah what if um no it was just cool it was just like
we talked about stuff um but i'm like such as idiot that i didn't think to make a connection
with him and i don't know anything about like how to contact him but you know it's one of those
things just one of those industry things when you're a fucking idiot and you don't have an
imdb that you look at you know it's not really a big deal you want to go and shave my balls
what's the thing what's the thing where like all the business people have an account and
linkedin yeah i should i should be looking at a linkedin i should be doing that
hippo are you gonna you have you're gonna have an imdb you're gonna have an imdb
and it's gonna be your writing credits oh you're gonna be a real human
oh the show you're gonna be on is hippocrit show like deceased
yes oh god please don't do that if it comes out don't add hippocrit to it just please don't do
that it will be funny but don't oh i cannot wait for you to get james gunned i cannot wait for you
to get james gunned down where you uh are you successful screenwriter and you make and you
make gardens galaxy three and uh then then then the the the uppers at disney see the hippocrit
show and see like i hate mud that's a terror that's a terrible substance and texture deleted
they're gonna fire you it's gonna have to happen to all of us none of us are clean we're all
gonna go a little bit of mud on us because i want to get into like major specifics and i don't want to
like like spoil or also like break contract or whatever i don't want to i don't want to deal
in trouble with it's not about like breaking contracts it's just like the more i talk about it
the more it becomes a thing in people's minds and if it just falls through at some point i will
have nothing and people will be like oh so i don't want i you know i i'm just being cautious about
it i understand that makes sense however fuck off and i want more but after so your your brother's
making video games and he's a coder yes he is a coder he is a unity uh 3d man uh he's very very
smart always has been smart for his age probably because he hung around with me who was years
older and therefore like when he went to school this is this has always been funny to me where he
would like talk to me about like philosophical things that i was having when i was whatever age
i was he brought those like thoughts into his younger class and nobody fucking got it and
everyone was stupid and he said guys my people in my class suck and it's been like that forever
like he's just smarter than everyone around him so he's calling munchie is that what you're trying
to say yeah he's basically my munchie that i have created he's just been giving him some
intellectual rare candies all his life you know you know that that's really cool you know brothers
are coder hey tom do you know if there's a free podcast on the internet so that someone could
listen to an original like i don't know uh learn code let me let me let me just think
i think there's one called uh uh killing code i think i think that's what's called
that that might be one i hate one of the on the host on there he just streams and doesn't
actually have any insight it's really funny i like that podcast it's pretty it's pretty good
there's only one episode right i listened to the first one there's two there's two i haven't
know some of the second one yet uh can i be on sometime and brag about slime oids that's not
no you can't and just talk about all the coding i did that's that's very that's a very talk about
all the things that i talk about all the things that i learned you have to buy the book that we're
going through and you have to talk about what we're doing in the book uh yeah but i look i look
look it's an educational buy the book i don't go buy the book okay i'm i'm i'm a cowboy i'm in the
wild west of coding python i mean i understand that's what i was doing with gd scripts and then
munchie like corralled me into being uh uh uh educated he's he's sinking his college bound
teeth into my brain and getting me to like buy a book and use curriculum it's crazy i don't even
know what's going on it's totally different it's almost like being taught you know is is less painful
and more engaging and educational than just trying bullshit and just making hackneyed code
i don't know if i agree though i had i think i i i the reason i wanted to do this podcast
is because there were fundamentals that i did ignore and it was going to bite me in the ass
but i will say it is way more fun to just open up g'dow and like all right how do i make this
character move and just start googling until he starts moving then to uh do a plus b in parentheses
and finish yeah it's uh worth mentioning my brother went to like coding uh university course
and he passed and is is good um but he's still like regularly when he needs specific information
will google a tutorial about how to do something i mean like that's what a lot of our comment section
on the podcast so far has been is like you have to as soon as possible abandon your your uh book
and just go out into the wild because that's the way you're actually going to learn how to code
sure i'm not saying that you don't learn by experience i'm just saying it's good to know
where to start it's good to have both yeah you gotta have the fundamentals i would not know
what the fuck to google if i didn't have this book and just like all right like how to code
python there would be like an there would be like an hour long youtube video about it
and that would just be some fucking schmuck explain things there is yeah there's um when i was
when i tried to learn i go like the like the first time when i when i tried to um
when i was when when endless war was just a twinkle in my eye and i went and tried to learn
the right way i found yeah these these youtube videos called uh automate the boring stuff with
python which turns out i actually found that book lying around my house like later yeah
turns out that like those youtube lessons were like the guy who wrote the book sort of delivering
the first couple chapters of his book via youtube video um but i didn't get anywhere very fast with
that it was too basic and it was too slow um i probably if i had not been in a hurry i maybe
could have stuck with it i do i like i like just sort of googling shit and just like learning
like that's kind of how i do most things i just google shit and i just whatever i want to do i just
look around and try and figure out just how to do this one thing and it's all very willy nilly
and nonsense and it's it's pretty fun but i definitely have gaps i definitely have gaps in
my knowledge like um i don't know i i was talking to you earlier we were looking at the um we're
looking at the database and like he he like knew all the like for me to debug something i just have
to like make a change to the code run the program see what it does and then try and like figure out
why did it do that he had like strats he like typed something in so that like the the the fucking
my sql thing would spit out like a result explaining like what happened when the code is run
which is like i don't know what how'd you do that um would probably be helpful for me to know
right and i don't that that's that's the that's why i wanted to start that's why i stopped doing gd
script and decided to do the podcast of munchies because like there i got to the point where the
my lack of the fundamentals were compounding upon themselves and causing more issues and
like i had to go back like i could have kept going forward and like fucking like just like duct taped
all my code together and it would have worked but i could see like the scope of my project was like
if i keep going this way it will eventually jenga all over my my ui and destroy my code forever so
i had to go back i had to turn around i had to abandon all the cool stuff about like getting
attack animations and physics calculations and all this cool shit i had to go back and i had to do
a plus b in brackets uh declare variables and be like i guess i gotta learn how this basic
baby stuff works so i can go build the real shit and that's where we are right now yeah to me it's
it's like i don't even know how i could possibly like just start i mean i guess that's how he started
doing drawing right like i didn't have a good book to teach me how to draw i just started putting
pencil paper and eventually i got good but i don't think it's a stretch to say maybe if not i had a
book but you know if there was an art class at my school probably would have got better
way faster and way less hardship in the beginning it's interesting you say that much because i can
explain exactly what would happen if you had just done what i did because i did it um the part we're
at in the book right now where we're talking about uh functions and arguments you know uh i was just
following tutorials on how to make a platformer in godot and they would just tell you to type
these functions and i had no idea what a function is uh i just typed it out and i didn't understand
what arguments were because they they just assume in these videos i was watching that you know what
an argument is because you know how to program right wink wink and i was like no i'm just copying
what you did wink wink so like i would just get to the point they'd be like you gotta put these
arguments in i'm like why what is the point of an argument why is this happening here i don't
understand i'm just copying what you're saying and i understand what it does but i don't understand
why it does it and i was getting to the point where i would like stop following the tutorials
because the tutorial i was following the dude had a kid and just abandoned the thing mid mid like
thing so like there's no more band in the kid yeah he just abandoned the kid and kept making
coding videos for me specifically because i PMed him and he decided to keep going no so the the
series ended i was like well now what i do so then i like started watching another tutorial that was
like how to make a zelda clone i was trying to reverse engineer like the code from that to put
it into a platformer and i did figure out like wall collisions and stuff and i felt like a god
but eventually it was just like i still don't know what a function is i just know yeah so it's like i
gotta go back i gotta go back so like you just understand what and not why and uh it becomes a
problem i remember like coding coding like little games on multimedia fusion 2 and there was like
easy code for babies where um they spoke in in plain english like if character touches side of
screen stop movement so like they can't go off the screens like okay now i understand code um of
course i didn't but like they have these these other things which were like completely alien to me
and i didn't google them because i didn't know what google was because i didn't care enough to try
um like and gates and or gates and x or gates and things that are like the basic fundamentals of
like uh computer chips and like electronic pulses going around uh computer chips to just determine
whether something should go on or off and that's like that's uh it's hard that's that's hard to do
that's too fundamental i mean yeah but like i i i really enjoy understanding the fundamentals
because like watching my brother code he's doing all this fancy stuff and i ask him uh how like what
he's doing uh affects the thing and he'll give me some sort of explanation and i was like okay so
and then i like translate what he's doing into english that i can understand he's like yes that's
how it works i'm like sick like i love i love translating code um speak into uh like human
words like when this happens that happens oh i get it that's cool see man i am straight up telling you
miracles it's like all right computers right what the fuck miracles is what
that's how i feel every day in coding miracle in a box exactly it's magic
that's all needs to be said dude we're gonna be wizards that's the whole point of learning code
mage do you have like uh tuberculosis what is wrong with your car
uh i i don't know what's wrong with my car uh it's i have phlegm in my lungs i guess gross
how much are you selling that for oh that's not an ooh that's good that's good stuff right there
but it's like that's like that's slime adjacent that's slime adjacent that's slime adjacent that
that would go for like twelve dollars per pint oh my god no don't make this weird
weird time i just talked about your phlegm on the podcast look i'll DM you after the podcast
we can just we can discuss rates uh fucking getting colds during the the winter times it
always happens always i don't think i'm quite over mine it's my yearly tradition i step outside for
one second and i catch a cold and i die every single year oh no i did not get a cold this
season but something happened to me my one night i just slept on my head weird or something
and like the next day my neck hurt and it has not and it's just my neck hurt for like a week
it's kind of going away now it's kind of it's i can kind of i don't know i've had that but for
like two years it's the white thing i'm trying to imagine like a like a neck thing like you know
you'd folded your neck like forwards onto your chest and you were sleeping for a chest down
and your head was completely folded in on itself was like i just don't know what happened i think
i just like slept with my head like turned a little too far to the side and pulled a muscle
or something yeah i think that happened to me as well i i had to change pillows honestly because
apparently my pillow was too hard so i had to buy a new one it just kept i just kept the muscles in
my head kept getting sore and i just couldn't sleep and it was just awful it was awful i used to i
used to have a bed that was way too fucking soft and every day i my back hurt i would wake up in
my fucking back hurt and i was like i you'd think that a soft bed is like good for you like it's like
gentle it's like gentle it's like gentle on your body you know it's like oh i just like like laying
on a cloud no it fucking killed me it killed me and it ruined my life um oh no and now i sleep on
fucking stone slab you know now i sleep in a coffin and it's red you sleep on a stone slab
and then i stab you through the heart and you ascend to god tier yeah this sleep discussion
being dangerously close to dream discussion oh if i like the way mage did this on purpose
no no you were the one who brought it up i wasn't gonna mention any dreams you you heck heck all of
you were trying to you were trying to whoa whoa foul language she's bringing the hex hex
hex on upon you the heckles the shekels for the heckles and the shekels for the heck i need to be
on that show again i came up with the name of the show i need to i need to be i need to take
my you know i've only been on the first one i keep missing all the other ones i've been on two uh
do we do them like every sunday i don't know when we do them that's why i keep missing like we started
doing them every sunday but i think we've like gotten bad no it wasn't every sunday it was like
every other sunday oh okay then i guess it's not as bad as i thought yeah that's all within industry
guidelines then if people want to see me play dark souls with restrictions that was the last one that
was pretty fun i want to i want to continue that one i really really want to be on the shekels for
heckles but i'm never i never it's it's always poor timing for me aren't you like up all night
aren't you like a nocturnal vampire sometimes but sometimes i i have to do things and i cannot
part time vampire i don't know if i buy that i'm pretty sure i've been on every shekels for
heckles and let me just tell you you're not really missing out on anything it's like it's just like
that's because i'm not there to make it good uh i i think it's pretty fun i like it i just i just
want to hang out with you guys and maybe heckle someone for the game no no well you would have to
get in the chat okay so that the concept of the show mage is that people pay in super chats to
insult us that's where the shekels for heckles come from they give us money to insult us so you
want to be in the chat and pay us money to insult them oh no i mean someone has to read out the
heckles right you can't you can't you can't heckle for free but we're not obligated to feel bad about
yeah yeah yeah we're only obligated to feel bad about the ones people pay for i i will say that
yeah i also have people who have to read out the heckles right so that's true if you want to be
the heckle announcer all right you could you could be that yeah that's true yeah you could do that
stream is definitely feel closer to talking to like a normal person in real life they definitely
feel like less performative than a podcast right so being on a being on a stream feels exactly
like being on a pcp to me oh it feels way less responsibility to me because streams are just
by definition terrible just that's just part of the whole kid in caboodle of streaming is that i don't
there's like a terrible as in like like name a good like okay give me a stream that you were like
wow fucking great stream dude i want to name me a fucking podcast where you felt the same i wanted
to say i have games but i am games is a bad stream uh so there is the last there are some
pcp episodes and i'm like wow fucking home run great job keep it up there are moments in streams
that are just like yeah but they're fucking seven hours of bullshit and you get i think hippos
are totally on the money that a podcast is has the same problem in that it's just long content
and it's long content and sometimes there's something really funny and sometimes people get
ziggiegles completely disagree i mean i mean and the same thing can happen on a stream it just feels
a little less like you know i mean even i feel like the the lack of responsibility is what causes a
lot of the funniest moments in a stream sure but i if you want to like to get the good much
well streams have streams have a big like cut it out from there streams have a big leg up on
podcasts and that streams have the jar streams have the fucking jar all right which is a miracle
did you did you turned off the jar because he thought it looked bad and i'm just like you're
doing everything he thought we thought what he thought the aesthetic of the jar looked bad and
i'm like you're missing the point here's here's a thing i don't understand i see like every now
and then i pop on twitch and like i'm following maybe like you know i'm following a bunch of
like artists and stuff that i just followed in a way i'm like hey this person looks all right i'll
follow him maybe you'll check out a stream once in a while and everyone's got the jar
and like tiny like tiny in a corner that you can barely see it it has it looks like a little tip jar
like my streams like i said like my screen does not fill up my my my twitch stream generally so
i'll usually have like a big black space on the sides so i use that black space that's there
anyway and i put the giant fucking jar there and it's so fucking cool because people will like pour
in like you know one cent bits they'll fill up the jar with ones and bits and then someone will
subscribe and it's like an event like the stream like everyone is like focus it's like a it's like
an event when someone drops like a a sub or like a like a thousand bit you know bit piece in there
and it all just like crashes into it and sends it all like spewing out because it's like squirting
it out because of how heavy it is just squishing it down and sending it all flying it's it's a it's
a it's a tree man what what if you you made like like it's gotta be big which was like the goblet
of fire from harry potter but it was just the jar in the middle of the screen with like some some
like a pedestal wait and people would put their name into the jar of fire i've i've got it i just
had i just had you've given me a wonderful idea because i have been pushing for it i'm almost at
a thousand subscribers on uh you know twitch.tv slash thousand subscribers or not subscribers
i was gonna say holy shit dude you're loaded as fuck yeah that'd be a lot of money that'd be a
lot of money i'm almost a five grand a month easy and i've been um well twitch takes a cut but
whatever um so they would be and i and i've been and i've said like when i hit a thousand i'm gonna
do a 24 hour you know stream to celebrate and i don't but i don't know what i'm gonna do on it
i've been thinking i thought it'd be funny if i did like a 24 hour maple story stream or like i
did it i did a really long stream of hollow knight and i've got lots of hollow on it maybe
because you do 24 hours of hollow knight and i haven't decided i don't exactly know what
but what if i just did a 24 hour jar stream where it's just the jar and we just watch the jar and
comment on the various comings and goings that occur in the jar case in point that podcasts are
objectively superior to streams no find me one fucking person who prefers rck streams the episodes
one person um anyone well leave a comment literally one person
you know what i'll bet there will be oh but there's actually plenty i mean we don't get
as many views on the streams uh all all the feedback it's funny like thousands of people
watch the rfck videos but like 50 to like 70 tops show up to watch the streams and i don't know if
it's just like a timing thing right like it just seems like viewer numbers like the numbers are just
lower on twitch across the board and that's like i mean the the obvious like uh advantage of a video
rather than a live broadcast is that you can watch it at your leisure you can pause it you can come
back to it that's why i mean you can you can watch that you can watch the twitch vod is no one does
you like they're all why you put no one does that i know no one does it but like you can do it just
as easily it's i just like the site isn't set up to like funnel people into doing that the site is
set up to get people to watch people live and like the archive videos are sort of an afterthought
that's there but like the twitch doesn't want to acknowledge them the only feedback we ever get
on streams is either wow pretty good for a stream or wow wish you would record more in episodes
those are like the that's not we get four like the streams themselves we know i i mean yeah
nobody ever says that on a stream nobody ever says wow wish you would record more episodes people
are there there's not as many of them but there's but they're super engaged and they're super
they're fucking like interacting with like the community like yeah it's it's it's i mean it's
got its own it's its own thing like we couldn't rfck as it exists now would not exist if it was
if there were no streams so so there i think i don't how i guess okay we we we review the contest
on stream that's that's pretty connected but like and and you know we we talk about the game
on stream but like i don't think that's really anyone's major source of like a gaming news
or anything based on in the swore i think that's anyone's like main way to interact with the
discord server i don't think besides we would have to find a new way to review the contest
or and you need to you know like spotlight slam times but i don't think that would like if streams
were to just like disappear like the fanno gets fanno snapped i don't think there would be like
maybe there might be a handful of people who drop off you know the the bandwagon but i think it would
continue chugging along just as fine as it did before i don't think there's a lot of people
maybe it wouldn't i mean it wouldn't it wouldn't like die it wouldn't like die without i'm not saying
that it would die without oh my god it's christmas i forgot i was gonna talk about christmas in a
few days it will be christmas day i always i think that i love christmas you'll be watching this after
christmas day you don't get to do this you don't get to just cut in here and in the stream conversation
i'm actually i'm actually i'm actually done i'm actually very grateful you guys have talked about
rowdy focus cop killers a lot no yeah we have no yeah the thing that you said before was not true
when you said it munchie but it has become no this is not an rck thing this is not like an rck like
like like specific problem i just hate streams i think they're meandering i think they're all bad
and i hate them i don't know how you can possibly say that podcasts are just as bad when like
overwhelmingly podcasts are shorter and they are besides ours usually edited and usually more
entertaining i don't know i podcast who edits the podcasts what do you mean what do you mean by
this why why would you edit a game why would you edit a game there's always not paying attention
it's all it's just reading chat chats are a fucking curse i hate the chats on streams no no
no you that's not i'm asking why would why do people edit podcasts isn't the point of podcasts
to make the audio look or sound all right no no not like oh my fucking god they edit it
so they can edit out topics that weren't that interesting i imagine much better the pcb if
we did that there would be no pcb if we did that there wouldn't be any videos the the problem with
that specifically is that we're a rotating cast and um everybody will have different things to say
and a lot of the time running jokes come go from topic to topic so like cutting out a topic is not
as easy as it would be on a two-person show well i'm not which is why i'm not trying to advocate
my point is not to get the pcb to edit a podcast i'm not that's not what i meant i'm just saying
there's all right almost universally more effort put in well i love podcasts but i think streams
are cool i don't know what you're talking about i want to talk about they're all they're always
they're always born in meandering there's never i want to talk about i want to talk about i want
to talk about christmas now fine and how much i hate it and how much i think i like christmas
until it happens and then we get close to christmas and i'm like oh yeah lights snow i like the
aesthetic and then actual christmas then it comes for your wallet you're like this is the worst
and it's like tomorrow and i'm like oh god damn it fuck i don't want to fucking go like don't make
me go don't make me go jesus why did you do this to me listen i don't want to like you know be that
guy who's like oh fuck my family you know it's so annoying at them you know i like my family but i
just want to say you know what we all know is the case if we didn't have family obligations we would
never hang out with our family on christmas never agreed agreed of course um no i don't
agree with that yeah but like that's because uh your family sounds pretty good it sounds it is
you got a programming brother and a cool dad that's what i know about the one the one good thing
that's gonna happen this christmas is that my mom is gonna trade me her shiny swab blue
i'm gonna have a lucky shiny swab blue i'm gonna evolve it into ulteria and i've decided i thought
long and hard i thought long and hard i considered many names for a shiny a shiny ulteria and i almost
went with dawn but i think i'm gonna go with glory i'm gonna call it glory it's gonna be the coolest
thing ever and that's it that's what i'm gonna call my one pearly gates i i like my family don't
get me wrong i'm not saying this is like a like i'm so annoyed by my family that i have to spend
time with them like oh mom i just want to play my nintendo switch i just this is the reason
why halloween is great is because you could it's a holiday which is fun in and of itself it's fun
to be festive every once in a while and you can hang there's no you know you're not gonna go to
your fucking parents for halloween it's not the type of holiday you can just hang out with your friends
and you know eat black eyes while while watching an iam game stream or being online that's all
you have to do in halloween what's a black guy uh what we were fed by digi and me it's a meatball
with olive on it oh those are weird but for christmas i okay you know i don't mind going over to my
families you know you know have christmas day you know open presents or whatever but i really just
want to i i what i want to do they just want to hang out with ben and tom at digi's house
well digi's not there and just make a muck out of the place that's what i wanted that's what i'm
looking forward to you know yeah it's gonna be fun to be with old people you know it'll be nice to
catch up but like that's not what i'm about that's not what i want to do on the lord's day well i think
part of that might be because you also have thanksgiving which is exactly the same thing
hey and that and that's kind of close by we don't have that so like this is the family time of the
year i look forward to i already did i already did think i already did thanksgiving a month ago
i'm sick of it i'm fucking sick of it i want to i want to i want to state my opinion as to why
i like christmas do you understand there i want to complain about something well you can go on
first yeah i like i like i like christmas a lot because um i am not a fan of winter i snow
is aesthetically pleasing but there's not a lot of snow in the uk uh regardless it's like it's
damp it's dark it's cold it's windy it's not my kind of season and it's absolutely dreary and sad
and christmas when christmas comes around everyone decorates with shiny bright lights
and then there's happy holiday music playing as annoying and obnoxious as it is like i can't say
i hate it um and it's just like the whole place everywhere i go it's all just like bright and
shiny and happy and all lit up everyone's in the mood and it's just i like how christmas looks i
like i like being outside on christmas i like that whole part of it 100 what always hits me though
it's like straight after the new year is at least in the fainia and i guess in uk as well straight
after a new year is like all the festivities and everyone takes down their decorations and
be back to the mundane and then i realize how absolutely sad and quiet and dreary the rest of
the winter is because like nothing nothing of importance or significance or festive happens
up until like i don't know spring and i mean you got valentine's day that's everybody loves valentine's
to heck with it it's still in all i guess it's february so now that's not spring but you know it's
still like a whole a whole month of nothing and except for sadness and sockiness and it's just
it's really sad and and and i miss christmas during that month see mage the interesting thing that
is like you're missing the american perspective right because in america what happens is that uh
there's there's nothing like that we've we've all realized that this is a problem and we did
what we always do to solve problems in america which is throw consumerism at it so and in america
as soon as halloween's over it's instantly christmas the next day until christmas and then once
christmas over it's valentine's day but the post the post the post christmas the post christmas
time is still a doldrum yeah exactly yeah i was talking about as soon as but like we also have like
the halloween christ christmas like overlap yeah i don't mind i think it's funny um i don't mind
winter i don't mind cold that much most of the time it's the worst i love it it makes me really
happy i i'm i'm i'm down with it being cold oh god never you know 75 of the time if you want to
know my exact unaltered raw opinions on winter turn on the scott pilgrim the game track another
winter and that's exactly how i feel every single moment i'm out in the cold which is to say
it's astounding and i love it god i wish i being in new england i wish i could be you because every
time it's not i'm i'm i'm fucking like three miles from you right now that's why i said because
i'm also in new england i wish i could be you okay yeah yeah yeah i wanted i want to be on your
wavelength we're trapped in the same house together now tom you and me are just some
fucking brown hairs yeah oh ben i'm so glad you've adopted it yeah yeah tom you're just a
fucking brown hair jeez brown-haired white people we can't can't deal with that guys yeah do you
do you do you like smell like seasons yes i i smell season i like the smell which seasons um no i don't
um i don't go outside enough the weather seasons like you go outside and after it's rained it has
this very specific smell that's true yeah yeah but that's like a little bit different i can like
seasons have their own specific smells like i go outside and i can smell winter and it's like
this crisp fresh air and it's it's so good well i don't smell that but i do feel that
like like i can feel it on my skin like ah yes that's that's like sharp but not quite sharp enough
to cut me and draw blood i think i know what you're talking about i have a terrible sense of smell
and my nose is constantly plugged up and my life is terrible we don't want to know why i have a high
pitched voice it's not because i'm naturally gay though that it does play into it just my nose
is constantly stuffed and that's the reason why munchie sounds like munchie hey guys welcome to
the pro crass natives podcast today we have mage hello we got tom gay we got munchie and then
together yep we're together anyway so that album creating should be out any day now so just look
forward for the munchie out the munchie solo album uh you know any any fucking moment here like tomorrow
you're gonna bring out the the the nice fucking munchie jam you're gonna play in your car in your
carpool and you're gonna sing along karaoke style there's gonna be a karaoke version of all the
tracks in case you want to sing along uh it'll be great so just look forward to that that is definitely
coming tomorrow from when this is released the munchie album munchie.bandcap.com check it out
and i'd appreciate if you share this with all your friends and uh listen you know if something goes
awry you know all the files are deleted on my computer please you know take this as a betrayal
take this as a disappointment because i am promising you that tomorrow there will be a munchie album
at least one track so please you know uh you know just delete me out the face of this kick me from
the pcp let me join let let me start a scorned trilogy of outlaws and outcasts that is the
the band from the pcp members and uh you know this is going really long i'm bored uh should we
just go to questions it's been like two hours wait i have a really important announcement
that everyone is relevant to absolutely everyone i'm gonna i'm gonna hold you to this
is that i'm quit i'm quitting keto for christmas oh i ate i ate croissants today
croissants you're so so for croissants i'm getting well they were they had no they had chocolate
in them they had chocolate in them so you see you might think you might think that me the ultimate
human core artisan that i am the the ultimate anti-keto anti-utilitarian uh of food choices
might applaud you and be like wow i'm so happy for you but no i'm just disgusted that you do this
perverse degenerative lifestyle and then don't even stick to it you haven't even just fully converted
to being a cherry for like two days you're now just so goosey goosey what am i gonna what am i
gonna show up to family christmas and be like uh no i can't eat a fucking eggnog because it's got
sugar in it did i tell you about my metabolism the vegans would do what does eggnog taste like
i wonder oh i love eggnog you don't you don't know egg we don't have eggnog over here we don't
what i understand is that you you put an egg in a nog and you drink it it's a nog here's the thing
i have never i've never had like homemade eggnog or if i have i don't remember it i just you know
you can buy it in like hood fucking like like court in the hood yeah you can buy it and you
can buy it in like courts in the supermarket and it's fucking great man i love apple cider tea he
i'm doing what ben says he hates and that's talking about food even though he brought it up initially
look man my the status of my metabolism is everybody's business but my um ben just comes
up here with his sunglasses on and his dick out and his collar pops saying hey guys did you know
that i'm abandoning my ideals just thought you should know and he expects us to just get on all
fours and just beg for it but i'm not gonna do it ben i'm gonna say you you either you either die
heroes live long enough to yourself stop keto that's what you're doing this is a slippery slope
and you're about to abandon all that you care for just to get a fucking croissant he already did he
had the croissant they were delicious yeah it's not only that it's done it's done if you recall he
already abandoned keto on halloween when he had the pizza so this isn't like a new i ate so many
i ate so many airheads on halloween he abandoned keto yesterday he had some he had some sugar
i ate like one fucking starburst yeah we're some artisan some artisan candy you handed
guys guys speaking of candy at one point like in aziz store like they were stocking like those huge
actual marshmallows that you like put on a stick and over a fireplace and i bought them and they
were delicious and they don't sell them anymore and i was like this was my one chance and thankfully
i took this chance and i had those marshmallows and they were great how how big are we talking
really big like a like a like a like a like i don't know like a tennis bowl i guess someone like a
tennis huh okay these are huge the the hugest marshmallows you say that really say that again
say that again huge no i didn't have the magic you're exhaling at the time it was once in a lifetime
it's one we've got to move on yeah you cut it on tape though so you can read it's true we can
relive that on at our leisure yeah yeah are we doing questions are we doing voicemails voicemail
time yeah it's voicemail right now all right all right all right speaking of being a shit person
we've got some fucking asshole doing something terrible he's trying to make his cat vegan let's
listen to this no i call to get your input on a grave moral quandary you see i'm shifting into
veganism because i feel uncomfortable making the moral distinction between animals we keep as pets
and those who are born into factory farms loser you say that i love animals but among the animals
that i love is the house cat an obligate carnivore whose nutritional needs are only supplemented by
animal products additionally according to the 10 seconds of research i've put into the subject
most commercially available vegan cat foods do a horrible job of fulfilling their dietary needs
and are very unhealthy and harmful for the cat in 100 years when the revolutionaries overthrow
the meat industry and the world is tossed into utter vegan chaos will probably create an appropriate
substitute but for now i'm reminded of the vilification of goblins as a race that can only
how long is this voicemail making them an objectively evil force and forced to grapple
with the question do i deny my convictions and therefore justify any act that goes against
my moral convictions including murder or do i embrace my utilitarian doing and strangle my
sister's cat for the greater good all right here's the deal if animals can't be vegan
if you're if you have a pet if you own a pet and it needs to eat human flesh and you're not okay
with giving it human flesh then you shouldn't have that pet don't kill it obviously just give it to
someone else wait who said it needs to eat human flesh well i'm just making a metaphor comparison
like like other people can relate to the idea of not feeding their pet human flesh if it needs
that here here's the fucking deal dude cats again as you said are carnivores you you cannot get them
fucking some kitschy quirky vegan cat food that will kill them and fuck them up don't do it you
absolute idiot so the only choices are to get rid of that cat through either murder or through
trading bartering but but or to just kill yourself if you if which is if you if you own a cat and you
feed it meat you are contributing to the meat industry that's what he said like he has to
choose between his ideals and his cat he's really he's really struck on something important here
give the cat to a good loving home that they won't that will actually care about them yeah exactly
or just or just put it outside and close but here's but here's the thing if you can if you give the
cat and close the door if you give the cat to somebody else you're also contributing to the
meat industry because you're enabling the sales of meat products to continue well why don't you
just shoot everybody in the fucking so that's what i'm saying vegans need to just kill everybody
or kill themselves stop thinking about it this but if you own the cat but if you own the cat you're
and and you don't want to help the meat industry you are you are being complicit by your cat ownership
in in all right perpetuate this wasn't even a real question why are we giving it an answer
this guy was obviously trolling all of us and we're following okay here's the real i think it's
a real i have more i foolishly have more faith in our audience than that okay i don't know like i'm
trying to say made a goblin slayer google vegan cat food and give it to your cat because it's a bad
idea and don't do it and also yeah i think i think the takeaway here that i believe is probably true
is that if you don't believe in the meat industry and you're not willing to support it i don't think
you can own a cat yeah i mean you have to find unless you're gonna like unless you're gonna
like be catching mice for it or whatever and feeding it to you so unless you're gonna do like
grass roots cat but that's like that seems like even worse let's let it be an out there just let
it be an outdoor cat and hunt for itself cats do that true yeah that's true hey just invite rats
into your house i'll be the first thing to do is is that one of the reasons i don't think it's
there's probably not the only reason but one of the reason he stayed for being a vegan so he doesn't
like that there's no difference between the animals that are like house pets and the ones that are
being killed on mass and i don't know i guess i don't understand like why that's weird for some
animals we just like more like i don't think humans like like cows that much you think they're cute
it's like dogs are smarter than dogs generally we kill pigs and we don't kill dogs the the biggest
problem i have with this line of thinking is the idea that animals are a group that have
anything to do with one another like we group them together as animals uh for convenience and
we invented that group to say that all animals deserve rights is like all like all animals
deserve the same treatment is like saying all things like you could you could extrapolate it
further and further to late to two other things some people actually do it to like plants as well
and then they die instantly because there's nothing they can eat right i mean that is the
closer to meat than plants i heard that interesting is that that must be why they're so delicious
i'm saying okay listen i'm doing i'm i'm i'm on tape being pro animal however i'll maybe that
weird if you ate a dog i mean you know people know i would eat a dog if you offered me if you
offered me some dog i would eat it it that's why why is that weird mage i'm not trying to be edgy
here why is that why is that i know i know it's it's kind of like a i know when you think about
it it's a bit of a double standard yada yada i don't know i don't like thinking about eating dogs
though it's like it's i once saw like a show that like i think it's like an extreme factor and like
all you had to do was like eat an egg but then the egg was an unborn little baby duck or something
and it's a delicacy somewhere and i just i couldn't stomach it it's just well the like i said it before
like pigs pigs pigs are smarter than dogs and they're like they're they're like more
fucking emotional and like until intellectual and are just like cerebrally better and more
complete as beings than dogs are just but because they're ugly you know we think it's
we think it's gross to kill a dog and eat it but we just fucking have a lot of dogs doing
i think it's just because it's not fair it's bullshit it is not fair um i i support dog
treating animals well before like it's even i mean i don't you know the reason dogs are like
weird to eat uh like generally is because for millennia they were useful for us for like hunting
and and being like a you know a friendly associate to help uh to do stuff around the
tribal camps it's like why are you eating your gun yeah it's like it's like eating your gun
and they don't have a lot of meat on them and they're more lean it's like why would you eat that
when you can have this big fat fuck who's full of meat it just makes so much more sense to eat that
guy so we do that because it's sensible we we bred pigs and cows to be well yes we are meaty
and delicious and we bred dogs to be you know useful no yeah i mean they or whatever we'll
start it off pretty useful in terms of like running around and stuff but like this we did all that
stuff because it was like handy and like efficient for for everyone and then as soon as we like didn't
need to survive we started thinking like you know like things were said in their ways dogs were now
things that were our friends and pigs and cows we eat but now that we don't need to survive we
don't think about like the efficiency in the we're too emotional because we can afford to be emotional
we can afford to not live a meat eating lifestyle even though in the past that we would probably
just starve to death this all all i'm saying is i eat pig i don't care dogs and cats dumber than
pigs qed if i would eat a dog or a cat because it would be a hypocrite not to he here's my here's
my deal i'm you know it's unfortunate that we are we are being so mean to these animals you know
mean but as a human i can eat meat my ancestor ate me it's pretty human core to eat me and there's
one thing i care about most in this world it's about being a human so you want me to stop being a human
i'll kill you so don't ever bring me this vegan shit ever again in my fucking face if you want me
to stop eating me and roasting over a fire kill yourself humans humans don't need me they can get
by without it sure they can they can they can be fine are you are you are would you say it's not
human core go out and hunt a big wilder beast are you saying that's not human core that's pretty
human core okay it's pretty human but you know there's there's probably lots of ways to be human
core you know like uh uh uh raising a cornfield and plowing it with your with your uh domesticated
ox munchy and making millet out of it is pretty human core also to play devil's advocate munchy
what's what's more human core than going out of rate to specifically not eat you could what other
species does that but a human you would say being vegans the most human core thing you can be
that's fair i'm saying you know this this discussion ties right back in to my two
essential factors of being a human it's you have to eat bread and own a dog and you know
the two worst decisions you could make in your entire life agreed if you don't have those and
you're not a human uh and and you know if you eat your dog you'll still be a human but you know
what you should have owned it instead that's my feelings we're gonna play the next one no this
guy is a little bit hard to understand but just brace yourself attention all right you know what
you should do you should ask the fans which topics are our favorites and maybe one or twice a year
you should do an episode we'll just talk about that a continuation of that for example i just
love you guys rambling about how your fitness life is going what's dieting taking how i can
improve my life for example i love that fucking nate recipe for the cereal sometimes i do this
and i love it i just love getting fitness shit from you guys are you also really listening to the
wrong podcast about video game experiences that you had and stuff like that so yeah just
do a continuation of some things some things we love them guys want to hear more oh we'll be the
best oh please do that i would love you forever i i is this ironic i can't tell no i well i mean
i assume it isn't because uh people do like um things i i feel like this is something we could
try and implement which is not necessarily having a hard line topic of discussion um but to have
like little corners like in hello internet like a regular reoccurring thing that they can bring up
we can bring up every so often relating to a specific uh topic such as fitness like ben you
just do it um anyway you bring up keto a lot but like if people like that it could be like that's
this will be like oh it's the food out like not the hour but like the food call like segments
like we have played little jingles at the beginning of our segment like doing is the fuck why don't we
do that why don't we do that why don't i have that queued up why don't i have a little keto jingle
that i play when i fucking mention keto i can't believe i'm so fucking dumb that i haven't done
that already i can't i can't believe either that you have never thought about having segments like
ben how we never listened to it before it's just that there's nothing like we can talk about
consistently about it is your only experience with podcasts this podcast that you record
no okay well well but not every in fact most podcasts i listen to don't have segments
most of the podcasts i listen to have segments so it seems weird to have someone not be familiar
with the idea i mean i am familiar with the idea as i think should be clear okay um um
but yeah i think i think that could be be pretty cool something we should probably
maybe we should run like a poll maybe we should i don't know have like what is your favorite
procrastinator recurring topic or i don't know i don't like ask for that right now the number one
result would be monchi going to college i guarantee you for the meme well no no i think nobody i think
people are against people hate hearing about that or no maybe that's just us that hate talking
i hate talking about it i hate that i just brought it up right now i hate talking about it
people tell me people would ask for comment or rules three is what is what we've had people
already asked about okay let's do that again so i can completely not have the same opinion that i
did last time because i completely disagree with how i thought before i mean i think i think that
would be interesting now that the dust is settled i don't think i have anything else to say about
it i think two is stretching it she too was stretching i think the problem with two is that
comment or rules i talked to digi about this at one point i said comment or rules one no i think
was monchi i said this comment or rules one was ironic and funny and we were having a good like
joke about it i like we were like we're kind of serious but not really taha he he this is funny
comment or rules two everyone was angry and we were like being like legit about it and i was very
confused being on that episode because i thought it was gonna be more taha he he but it was not it
was very much like comment or rules two was like we're drawing the lines in the sand and i was like
i thought we were supposed to really want what do they want to drink monsters for oh
shit monsters for baby sign me the fuck up that's a segment we got to have the monsters for a
segment for now on every episode for ever for a segment monster ever we got we got we got to
get we got to get we got to get six tin to make a little jingle for it or something we could have
like a whole jingle episode or we have so many different jingles and and topic things we could
we could have like uh the 60 second dream time when mage has to say her dream within 60 seconds
you have yes you have 60 seconds every episode to talk your dreams and you have to cram into 60
seconds we cut you off we ring the buzzer and and if you don't if you don't cram it and we
boot you off the episode hey everyone it's like it's like a death rate i haven't been on the last
couple episodes is there like a overarching like voicemail story arc of some guy going to hit on
a girl and like he's like asking for advice something is that is that something that that
happened a while back by one guy i mean one spark one spark so i don't know if i had a weekly thing
going for a while okay well this is no but there was there was a guy there was a guy asking about
like advice about how to hit on the girl or like he really wanted to date this girl and i think he
called back because i was on the episode that he called in first and i think he called in through
a later episode but i wasn't on it so i don't know well but i think that was a here's the thrilling
finale oh oh yo what up dogs i'm just being cool here okay so i asked him yeah he gave me some
advice and it was pretty good you know i'm just being cool here and like i was you know i asked her
i was like hey you know uh you want to do the whole voicemail girlfriend he's just being cool
and she said no sorry guys you don't get any money but okay thanks i'm just being cool
hey hey man you know he's just being cool yeah you know i can't even be mad because he was being
pretty cool about it you know the part of being cool though part of being cool is learning to accept
rejection man and that's the that's the coolness lesson for today brought to you by the pro craft
podcast patreon.com slash the procrastinators podcast where you can learn all about how to be cool
take it away munchie right it's it's really funny to imagine like the idea of him like doing i'm
just trying to be cool i'm just being cool like like actually saying that hey i'm like hey what do
you think about the girlfriend boyfriend thing you know i'm just being cool and like if she actually
reacted to him actually literally saying that guys that would be very funny should should i take like
two minutes out of my life out tonight and like make because i make because i made that spread that
teespring site uh should i just make an i'm just being cool share yeah we can't no a fan made that
we can't sell it we can't sell everything that's submitted to this podcast is our property a fan
did a fan did not make up i'm just being cool jesse jesse was like riffing on it it was like a jesse
riff oh did he okay then yeah we we we spun it out of a call well then that's a pcp i that's a pcp ip
um all right well i should all right all right the next one fucking click the link in the description
buy a fucking i'm just being cool shirt the the next uh voicemail is a call out post for tom
so get ready to be viciously attacked all right juicy let's do it
well are we gonna make a copyright strike yes
pcp this is me ranger t and i'm here to cut a promo that's been coming for a long time brother
because let me tell you me gene i'm the next number one fan and defender of the character of
tommy oliver from the mighty morpher power rangers jen and it's recently come to my attention dude
that's one of your members not only runs a channel under the name of tommy oliver but it's its legal
name brother and he's not even a power ranger fan creator meaning toom if you are listening to this
this is your one and only warning brother you need to delete that channel and legally change
your name dude or start making some power ranger videos man i'm gonna body slam you and put you
in the act so hard your freaking head will pop off dude and then i'll spear you through a table
brother i mean serious business here mean gene i've already taken one youtuber down brother
oh which one you got one month to get your act together jack a lot of times
as that the gauntlet's been i mean that was definitely a challenge but like i gotta say first
of all thank you for the gracious window of opportunity you know most people go with like a 24
hour did you make a power rangers video at some point i did i did do like a half-assed halloween
episode where i was reviewing the power rangers halloween episode which was just a wrapping
pumping guy which was funny uh so i guess technically i have made power rangers content
and i do already win the bet or the win the challenge beforehand you've gone away from
your your power tuber yeah yeah you've won you've already won the only question is is
tommy oliver aka macho man randy savage aka the green ranger going to kick your ass anyway um
that's the only question left i guess so i guess we're just i could have to wait an entire month
now to find out i don't even have to like do anything i just have it's already happened
yeah the we have the gears that have been set in motion yeah so it's time to watch them back
lean back and that's the easiest challenge i've ever participated in i just be like but by the
way it's done this is this is unrelated but but it factors into you yesterday when me been in kazi
we're all hanging out in boston kazi brought up a very interesting thing that you do on instagram
which which me and ben left really hard at wait what i never knew about i didn't even know you
were on instagram because i don't use it yeah uh we really enjoy the hey what's up guys just go
back from the gym right for another q and a sesh just you know post your comments and we are just
okay okay uh kazi made it sound like like to hear her tell it like every day you go to the gym
whoa and then you get home from the gym and you pop on instagram and say sup guys just home from
the gym for a little q and a well that that is literally only i mean i only do the q and a's
on friday that's why it's called q and a friday and and i've only ever done it back from the gym
that one day so i mean if by every day you mean one day the day that happened to be brought up
then yes i do it every day tom it was hard to believe so we had to pull up one and like the
very first video we saw on your instagram stories you saying ah i just got back from the gym guys
q and a i don't know it just left me scratched in my head like what is it wait how many questions
are there when he goes to the gym and that is a q and a every day oh god i i i wish i had the
self-confidence to think i was worth having a q and a every day i'd probably be so much
further in life if i cared about myself that much i thought it was some sort of like marketing the
community management thing where every day after the gym you're just so pumped up you're like yeah
i just can't wait to answer some questions like you're on the treadmill and you're just going
fast and fast like i gotta get home so i can read my fucking q and a question i like this fictional
facsimile of me that exists now and i want to become closer to it i've you've given me a goal to
aspire to it's legendary that's linking the description to tom yeah q and a
um all right okay so we were talking a lot about discord wars and i have no idea what the genesis
of these discord wars were but there were a lot of voicemail so i picked two here for you to uh
some some both sides of a of a hunggoing war so this is like keyblade how do you do i'm here as
a representative of the market how do fan discord i've been hearing a lot about this pcp discord
war that's brewing and i'm here as the market mod to officially declare our neutrality in this
conflict all right i agree remember what the markets can do for you well what you can do to
market yourself all right that is all the whole problem with market how do being a part of this
is that market how do is not technically a pcp product right because i do it with my friend
mad who has nothing to do with the pcp so it's pcp adjacent but i mean you're on it and you're on
the pcp so it's pcp it's pcp adjacent yeah you know it's totally pcp adjacent but it's not pcp
itself is arm retrieval pcp adjacent or is it a pcp spinoff i would have is it a pcp is it a
pc property that's a good term copyright you know that's a good question i guess i wouldn't consider
it i want it because it doesn't i would call it's adjacent but it's about as adjacent as you can
possibly fucking get yeah without being incorporated yeah it's like it's arm retrieval is like on the
level of adjacency of like the give and take streams i was like i don't think that's really a pcp
thing but it is arm retrieval is not pcp adjacent it's like a pcp spinoff it's like it's evolved as
a product as a result of it whereas market how do wasn't entirely separately uh you conceived
endeavor market how do is yeah it's like a totally separate thing that just sort of got entangled it
was caught in the orbit yeah while they're not a huge section of the viewer base there are there is
a considerable amount of people on the arm retrieval fandom who have not are not like pcp heads
and they just are homestuckers and they just found it through you know like you know i'm stuck
yeah yeah real jealous yeah that's what you gotta do well about this discord war
i hadn't heard about this discord war but i guess they better whip the hellfire hamlet up into a
frenzy there's killers what are you talking about there are well there are killers and there are
people and there are like people that were there before rfck that have no that are sort of killers
in spirit but have no like real gang affiliation ben how are there people in your discord server
that you have not bullied into playing the game i don't understand because i'm a fucking nice guy
man yeah i'm gonna finish last as always yeah and that's why what are you like you're slightly
shit you're slightly ahead of the leaderboard there is because i'm a nice guy i really want to
like draw up like a map of where all these discord countries reside spatially so that we can have
like a game of thrones that would be sick and i want you to do it well well i mean we have like
like a bubble infographic can we have like a bubble infographic of discord servers
you know what i'm talking about like an interconnecting web of them oh yes perfect
would we need like to actually get dated for that or uh you just just make it up you just make it
look convincing and i'll be happy all right we've heard from some neutral now to see someone on like
in the front fucking line all right these guys in the trenches he's deep in this shit and hippo
please close your ears and close your eyes and leave the call and close your heart and close your
heart okay so so you don't know the secrets about to unveil here this is paradox crocs
i'm behind enemy lines in the mud puddle discord server i don't think they've realized that i'm not
a syrian german immigrant yet i'm gonna keep laying low and try to give as much information as i can
to the rfck discord i can't promise that i'll be able to make another transmission but i'll do my
best good luck godspeed and semper fidelis to all our armed forces god bless all right hippo you
can unfold your ears now i'm i had my ears unplugged the whole time oh my god oh my god this is a
this is a security breach we gotta fucking close down close down all the airlocks we've got a
quarantine ourselves i'm throwing many tridents he's captured he's in circles no this isn't true
the consort the consort paradox crocs is captured and and and is now we're gonna we're gonna dip him
in the mud we're gonna push him real down in a muddy prison in in a ditch in africa in a stinky
swamp guarded over by shrek the the biggest mud knight of them all no fuck listen i don't think
there's anyone that can match the brawl brawn and paradox crocs this is a hostage situation yeah we're
we're gonna have to get him out we're gonna have to do something what a fucking nightmare we got a
fuck we two armed we got a fucking do a call to arms we got a rally all right we got a fucking
rally and invade all right the we got a fucking raid his stream on twitch listen listen killers
ratty's like an all agree that we need paradox trucks in case the trend towers ever get erected
again we need him on standby so we can do 9 11 3 we need to make sure that those things do not come
back i like the idea the idea that they're constantly trying to build the two times again
we gotta be vigilant we gotta be looking vigilant against urban development that threatens to bring
back the twin towers we're gonna fucking gentrify it and i'm scared what a toy of what are you
returning to don't worry just none other than three soon to be four all right all right well
we'll get out of there just stay calm and don't get killed mage what you missed was more a discord
war stuff in your server i do you have like a i remember you having a discord bot of some
kind the dude that says uwu and stuff is that weaponizable can you weaponize that in your purple
army uh you're gonna be on the front lines whether you like it or not we're coming through
bring mage sounds like she's about to get poland pretty quick yeah this war bring bring your
bring your purple army to the but you don't have to fight just bring it there so that when people
think they're attacking the killers they'll actually be firing their guns into your crowd by
accidents i mean i'm not gonna participate you won't force me into it you just sit on the sidelines
no just just no no just die just die once you all kill yourselves then i'll prevail
first they came for the killers and mage did nothing then they came for the bud nights and
mage did nothing and then they came for mage and there was no one left to defend her no there's no
one left to come for me because you're just gonna murder each other she's counting she's counting
on us all killing ourselves she's counting on b she wants she wants to be queen over the ashes
gentlemen you heard it here but by the way the iam games discord needs to get mobilized real
fast because me and ben are playing a sneak attack aka a fully like like telegraph i'm telling you
right now yeah i was gonna say it's a shitty sneak attack just a heads up time we're playing
by the time it is it will still be in the works uh so get ready for that all right this is the last
voicemail of the day and this is the worst one yet like i just like they were like so wow really
this is there was so many shit voicemails this episode i don't even know why i don't even know how
so i just saved i just saved like a good sample of like the like terrible questions and voicemail
so we get for this show so get ready for this all right unbelievable hey pcp this is uh the
goodest boy of all time i just had a quick question for you and your readers so i'm on the island of
oahu in hawaii right now it's the most beautiful place in the world what i want to ask real quick
is uh how do you all not kill yourselves for living such an enchanted fucking charmed life as me
to be out here in the best place in the world how do you live day to day knowing how inferior your
life is compared to mine that's my question for everybody this has been the goodest boy
of all time or whatever see you soon he's gone he's gone he's fucking gone he's fucking gone
yeah god doesn't even know what is this guy on yeah this guy's hopped up on he doesn't know
shit all right he doesn't know shit about anything he listen listen every single day
the goodest boy ever burns me right every single day i wake up and i look out my window and i'm
snowed in and and the electricity is out in the air and that's out and i wake up and i see some
lepers on my dick giving me some is some enchanted you know herpes i just think thank god think i'm
god i'm not in paradise i'm i'm not living in 80 degree weather in the winter and i'm not on the
beautiful island of oahu or mawai or or hawaii and i'm not there with with some big fucking
chi chi'd hawaiian sluts giving me coconut giving me shaved ice out of the fucking cup thank god
i'm not there because i you know i'm out here i'm getting work done every day i log on and i start
pressing some keyboards then i somehow wind up on youtube and spend three hours watching buzz
feed videos i fucking thank and pray to god every single day god please don't allow me to relax on
hawaii i enjoy it it's my favorite thing in the world not relax on hawaii so please i'm so happy
about it i'm glad that i've never been to hawaii because i can turn my nose up at this and say
it probably is not that's not can't be that good it can't be that good it can't be what's what could
possibly be good about i can't think of a single thing i don't well i've already said that i don't
like living living in hawaii sounds like living with your face pressed against the barrel of a gun
because it's only a matter of time it's only it's only a matter of time for that fucking volcano
goes off and kills everybody including you and your paradise is reduced to ashes
it'd be queen over the ashes
listen when you want when you want to imagine hawaii imagine a boot stamping on a human face
forever okay enjoy yourself you fuck living in hawaii is like going up to mother nature herself
whipping your dick i would be like come on bitch bring it on that fucking volcano this is a personal
message personal message to the goodest boy ever don't you ever fucking call this show ever again
don't you ever fucking darken our doorstep again you piece of shit i don't ever want to hear your
voice again oh hawaii isn't be the only gun you're pressed against i fucking hate that guy
hey fuck him podcast over it's the end um go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators
no that's in the episode oh no it's over remember to buy fucking merchandise for Christmas that has
already happened for you because it's like the 30th or something speak pipe speak pipe speak
speak pipe dot com slash uh link's are in the description pcb voicemail
uh guys hello welcome to the pcp where we've got mage here we got tom we got bang we got munchie
hey guys make sure to go to hgtps colon slash slash discord dot gg slash mtr
s k e k that was wrong that was wrong all of that was wrong goodbye
you