Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I am the best
guy ever, and today we've got a full box of chocolates, including Hippocrit.
Hello, I am a parrot with a cowboy hat. That's what I am.
Thank y'all for coming. Ben Saint is here.
Hello, I also am a parrot with a cowboy hat.
Thank y'all for coming. Munchy's here.
They finally did. The government wranglers that have made me, the government scientists have put a shock on me, and if I raise my voice above one decimal, they will shock me and kill me. So get ready for quiet Munchy this episode.
Thank y'all for coming, and Mage is here as well.
Are you a parrot with a cowboy hat, Munchy?
Yes.
Good.
Thank all y'all for coming today.
I cannot believe you guys. Oh my God.
Yeah, there it is. We stole this hilarious joke from Mage. We got things to say. Let's just jump into it. Who wants to start off? We've got enough business to attend to.
I want to start with a light topic. Disabled people. I want to go jumpin' right in the deep end.
Okay.
Disabled people. I'm talking about down syndrome. I'm talking about heavily autistic and physical. They can't move their legs. They can't move their head. They can't move their eyeballs.
Can't move their brains.
Can't move their brains. Can't move those cogs in those gears. And that's what I have as a topic, because I guess two weeks ago now, I was at the camp, which I briefly mentioned, and the camp was a goonery, which you can look up.
It was a goonery? Like a place where goons caught?
No, no, no, no, no.
That's what it sounds like.
It wouldn't sound like a concentration camp.
Yes. It is spelled with an A at the beginning, which is why it sounds like a goonery, but it's just one word. A goonery.
You can look it up. It's a thing. They do it in Australia. They do it in Indonesia. It's a scout camp.
It is a scout camp for disabled people, usually like children and young adults.
A-G-O-O-N-O-R-E-E?
Yes.
Just Google it. I think that's right.
Yeah, yeah, I found it. I don't know Wikipedia.
And we do one in the London area, and I was at it. And the idea is that I am a volunteer at that camp, and I help people in the patrol who are disabled get along and have fun and have fun because it's a thing.
It's basically a respite for the parents of the people who like a whole week camp where they get to have fun and do activities and stuff, but obviously they're disabled, they need a lot of volunteer help to come and wrangle them.
Can I wrangle them? Can I read the bizarre history of the name?
Yeah.
Down in Wikipedia, in 1949, Netherlands scouts organized an international camp at Lunteren for scouts with disabilities called agoon.
After the Greek language word agon, meaning a gathering or competition, and then the success of those events prompted the establishment of the agoonery, which is a compound of agoon plus jamboree.
Yes.
It's so weird.
It's got all those things.
Yeah.
Which a jamboree is already a gathering, so it's like a gathering gathering.
A classically educated, like soccer.
But you know, I mean, I'm sure that jamboree doesn't have a Greek root, so they're mixing their minerals, which is animalogically frowned upon.
I imagine like with the little, how do you call those little string instruments that like...
Banjo?
Yes. It has to have a banjo, and otherwise it's not a jamboree.
There was a campfire song thing where we sang old scouty campfire songs, and I was there playing the guitar because I can do that.
Cool.
But the point is not scouting, because I don't really know anything about scouting.
My experience of scouting is exclusively this, and we don't really do all the rigid like badge things.
We have like a scarf and a woggle.
I got my Hitler Youth badge.
We got a scout scarf and a woggle and a logo and a style and a flag, and we have like inspections of the tents.
What's a woggle?
It's the little plastic or leather thing you put around your scout scarf to keep it in place.
I thought a woggle was like what roosters have, right?
No, this is a woggle.
W-O-G-G-L-E, I think.
Woggle.
Anyway.
I was pretty into the ceremony aspect, like the honors and the badges and all the Nazi shit.
That was the way, and that was what I was in it for.
The cultist enterprising, all the cult shit, killing lambs in the forest.
The summoning of spirits, the entities.
We don't do much of all that ceremony stuff, because it's hard to keep some of their attention, because they're like, you gotta dangle things in front of their face.
But that's the topic, disabilities, not scouting.
What do you all think about disabilities?
Well, I like them. I'm in favor of them.
As many as possible, please.
I'm making more every single day of my life. I'm going out with my bat, and I'm making as many disabled as I can.
I know I've talked about this before. Ben and I, our mom, was actually just retired.
That's right.
Permanently.
So she's all done.
Congrats, mom.
Yeah, congrats to her.
So she was a special education teacher for like 20, 30 years or something.
That's what she studied in college and all that stuff.
And like, the way she described it was like, these are just kids.
Because she worked with middle schoolers mostly in a little bit of like high schoolers and some elementary school stuff.
But mostly like middle school age.
She'd be like, yeah, these are kids. They need a little extra help.
They're trying to just get by day to day. They're just like anybody else with their wants and needs.
They just need extra help to get stuff done.
And so she just tried to describe it in very normalizing terms.
This was never effective on me.
And every time she told me about her students,
I was engulfed with a massive crippling depression at just the injustice of people who were born with disabilities of any kind.
And this is a problem with me that I have known for a long time.
I need to get over that and be like my mom and just accept the fact that some people are differently able.
Mom was never judgmental about it, obviously.
But like it's so hard. It was so hard to hear her talk about her kids, her school kids.
And like these are kids who they got no chance. They got no fucking chance, right?
That's the problem, right? It's because my whole worldview is so based on like productivity and what you'll be able to achieve with your life.
And like needless to say, these people are quite limited in much of what they're going to be able to do through no fault of their own.
And so I'm left with no recourse but to conclude that these are subhumans who need to be purged.
Okay, I'm just kidding. That's not exaggeration.
My angle on this is that I went to that camp and sometimes I don't like it.
But the part that I do like in the end is like the being helpful and the helping them and being like a person that they enjoy being around.
Because I'm good at keeping them entertained and being like a good boy for them.
And you know, for some of them...
Those good boy points.
Yeah.
Sometimes it's a bit more like...
Thanks, Lord. Love that wisdom.
Sometimes it's a bit more hands-on than some others.
Like changing diapers hands-on, that sort of thing.
Wait, really?
Christ.
In my patrol this year, there was only one who needed like a toilet assistance.
Okay.
And usually have to go with two people for health and safety reasons.
So I never actually did the wiping, thank fuck for that.
But I did have to put on the rubber gloves and to like help him get showered a couple times.
There's like, there's all that stuff.
But...
I'm just curious, what was the nature of his disability in this?
Oh, he was...
I don't really know the names of the disabilities, but he could, you know, he was engaged by a lot of things.
He could walk if he wanted to, but he had like weak legs.
Okay.
And he enjoyed coloring.
He's sort of mentally disabled in that he can't really talk.
And he's...
He learned like an...
He made up sign language.
This is one of those guys who...
You can't really teach him things and he just sort of knows what he likes and he gets excited when he's excited.
Okay.
But he won't be able to really tell you except for a few basic things like toilet or food.
Like, I'm hungry.
Juice, please.
Like, you'll point to things if you want some.
I feel it right now.
I feel the sadness welling up inside me.
I can feel it.
Yeah.
But like, it's...
Like, I feel good being helpful.
And I don't know whether that's a good thing.
Because obviously...
Why did that be a bad thing?
It's...
Well, it's...
I mean...
There is a reason.
It's the...
It's the, you know, I'm gaining like happy points from the misfortune of others.
Not like I'm like...
You're happy because you can be abuse of help and you make the life of him easier.
Yeah.
But here's the thing.
I only do that once a year for one week.
And then they go back to their parents and their parents have to deal with them for the rest of their lives.
Right.
Like these parents.
You're being like a helper tourist here.
I'm just sort of like dipping my toe in and being like, yeah, it feels great to help people.
But if I had to look after like...
Leaves immediately afterward.
Yeah.
Like if I had to look after a person like properly, like if I had a son and he had a disability,
I wouldn't be able to like, you know, bring him out behind the shed and get rid of him.
I would have to keep him alive because I'm human.
I can't do that.
I can't murder people.
Oh, geez.
So I'm gonna have to deal with it for the rest of my life.
And I don't know whether I'd actually be able to do that.
Well, think about it.
It's like this...
It's a moral quandary.
You give those parents a break.
It is.
I mean, I know that it is a good thing.
But like morally, like I think of myself as like, yes, I like disabled people or like,
I like helping them and I like the feeling of doing the volunteer work, but like...
Do you feel...
Such a small amount.
Do you feel overly privileged to not have to do it all the time like these parents do?
Like you don't...
Yeah, like an actual care worker.
Yeah.
It's unbelievable.
I mean, it's not as though you are happy every moment of the day.
Think about how you have helped these kids once during the year.
I assume that you feel the happiest when you are actively doing it.
I feel like what's the harm in that?
If you're actually doing something presently, then you should feel good about it.
Well, you know...
If you think about it like biologically, it's...
I think it's more like you have accomplished a task and now you're getting rewarded by
your body by getting like, you know, the happy hormones or whatever being sent to your head.
It's okay, but isn't your clan or group...
I didn't really mean to say like, my enjoyment is a bad thing.
It just...
Like every so often I feel...
You feel...
I feel like I am not like thinking of it correctly.
That's normal, but I understand you as well.
That's normal.
Famously, Christopher Hitchens was a big critic of Mother Teresa specifically.
And the reason for this was because he believed that Mother Teresa was actually a bad person
who loved going down and dwelling in the shit.
And that she actually went out of her way to kind of create more suffering in the world
so that she would be able to go there and feel like a saint who was fixing it or whatever.
I've read quotes from her that suggest that she thinks that human suffering is a good thing
in the grand scheme of things.
I have not looked into this in any great extent, but that's the sentiment behind it, which is interesting.
But Hippo's not going around like me with his baseball bat full of nails cracking these people's skulls down.
Wait, on the subject of quotes...
It's a different kind of sin.
On the subject of quotes, I learned not too long ago from a channel called Knowing Better.
I know that guy. I subscribed to that guy.
I subscribed to him too, just recently.
Oh my god, on youtube.com? Wow, I've been there.
I had heard the quote from Winston Churchill saying something about using gas weapons on native tribes
and saying that he was in favor of it because it would spread a lively terror.
And it's supposed to pain him as a terrible person.
Well, that's war for you.
But the full quote, he's saying we should use them on native peoples because they would spread a lively terror
which would have psychological effects, which would make physically harming them less necessary
and would probably prevent more of them from dying, is what that quote is actually saying.
Well, that's just the fucked up thing about how you can manipulate quotes.
People misquote that to pain him like he loved hurting native people.
It's like the exact opposite was the point.
People hear what they want to hear with that stuff.
I guess I was inspired by the wrong thing.
I was inspired by the wrong part of that quote.
I thought I should kill native people.
No, no. He just wanted you to gas them and make them afraid.
This one is already half dead, so I'll just finish him off right now.
I'll do better next time.
A little gas thing goes a long way, as the saying goes.
Exactly.
I don't fully understand where...
Frankly, Hitler would have been the good guy if he just gassed a couple of Jews.
We would have been like, yeah, this makes sense.
Just spread a lively terror. He wouldn't have had to do the rest.
I don't fully understand where the sadness comes from, Hippo.
If it's not from you enjoying it, are you feel guilty that you are not doing more
and you are getting any pleasure from it whatsoever?
In a way, I am because I used to be a bit high and mighty.
I remember Nate saying, oh, yeah, disabilities make me feel sad.
That doesn't make me feel sad because I help them and I know more about it than you.
I wasn't lauding it over him, but it was that sort of like...
I live in England, it's true.
We had a whole PCP talk about...
I live in Sin.
Yeah, we did.
What do you call it? Something...
Was it crying?
No, no, no.
The one where you go around telling people you're so great, but you're not actually...
Was that when it was like childhood?
No, there was a topic about the concept of doing good things just for the sake of being a positive outlook.
Having a good reputation.
Philanthropy or something like that?
I don't know. It's the one that had the second thumbnail of a guy up in the mounds with his arm spread.
Oh, Virtue Signaling.
Virtue Signaling.
Virtue, that's the one.
That was one that triggered you guys.
Well, because I made that thumbnail so I remembered it.
I was looking at the thumbnails just...
I was looking at the thumbnails because the other day I made a playlist of every video I've ever been in.
There were like 450 of them.
I noticed, Ben, this was actually funny to me. This is a total aside.
But I noticed that you included all the T-Bap videos in that.
What I did strategically was I put...
And like Digi's is every video Digi's ever been in.
I put a every video best guy ever has ever been in.
And of course, Keg's standard was in T-Bap.
I don't know who that guy is.
Best guy ever over here.
He started with, you know, video one best guy ever.
A hundred fangirls just realized that you are Keg and Phantom.
A hundred fangirls just realized that just now.
Oh, no!
A new wave.
Every time you mention it.
I'll never do that.
Keep it under wraps, listeners.
Yeah, please. Don't let our enemies find out.
Hippo, I mean, all I can say is that you are helping these people.
You may not be doing it as much as the parents,
but like, it doesn't mean you aren't doing it at all.
And I'm sure that this camp is a rigorous thing that is not just like a normal day at, you know, the house.
Not saying that you're better than the parents,
but it's not like you should torture yourself and think that you aren't cool
for helping these people even a little bit out of their life.
I suppose. It's just, I'm wary of like, maybe unnecessarily so.
I'm wary of like, giving myself points, like life points.
Like, yeah, I do that.
And I've done it for like, I think eight years now in a row, which is pretty cool.
I mean, it's an objectively good thing to do, to just volunteer your time to help people.
I don't think it's a bad thing. I don't think I am a bad person for liking that I do it.
If you went out and poisoned women's babies, like in the womb,
so they would have disabilities, such that you can take care of them,
then we'd be having a different conversation.
But like, I just like to intellectually...
And once you've been going about it all wrong, your way is inefficient.
Yeah, that's true.
I just like to intellectually, like, criticize a lot.
It reminds me of...
Shit, I was just thinking of somebody...
Reminds me of this one-piece character, dot, dot, dot.
Yes. Yes.
I don't think there's, I'm trying to think of there's a one-piece character who exists.
Was there any one-piece characters who were like, were virtue signalers?
I can't think of any. No, it's not that kind of series.
Wait, wait, well, what about Full Body?
It was kind of...
I don't know, like, he was just trying to impress some bitch.
No, surely there were some...
I mean, what about Crocodile?
Crocodile, like, pretended was like a hero of the people, right?
You know, that is a different sort of thing, but he did pretend to be a hero,
but was actually attempting to, like...
He was the criminal trying to overthrow the entire government
and make the king look bad, who was not bad, who was good.
I think he could probably make a strong case that Crocodile was a heavy virtue signaler.
Okay, fair enough.
You knew when you said that, that it would actually turn into a conversation.
Yeah.
Hippo.
Were you a teacher of some sort, or were you just a general, like, counselor?
Like, what was your position within this camp?
Oh, okay, well, there's...
Master of Executions.
Master at Arms.
Madam Legality at Wrangler.
In charge of the weaponry.
Yes, surgeon.
There's a patrol...
There's, like, a number of patrols.
There's, like, the kitchen, and the staff that do the entertainment.
Also known as the Ents.
And I am...
Big tree guys.
Yeah, there's patrol leaders, two of them, and then there's patrol helpers.
And I'm just a patrol helper.
If I had, like, more scouting experience, or just experience in general,
I would be picked randomly one year for patrol leader,
and then I would be, like, in charge of the thing.
So you're, like, a brown shirt, hoping to break into the SS.
Well, I'm not really hoping to break into a patrol leader,
because that sounds like, oh, God, I gotta be responsible.
Like, all I'd really do is that I keep them entertained as best I can.
Like, I hang around the places.
Like, when there's downtime, they're in the patrol tent,
or they're just walking off wherever they like in the area, in the field.
And, like, when there's an event, like, there was, like, a zombie day
where there was, like, a dressing up box, and we had to go get the dressing up stuff.
And I, you know, helped them pick things and tried it on,
and they were all happy and stuff.
And it was, you know, nothing big.
Whenever there's food, I go with one of them.
Like, they enjoy helping as well.
They see how fun, like, how cool it is to be a helper,
and they want to help, and it's quite key.
So, you know, I get the food.
You feed them sometimes with a spoon,
but in mice, in this case, all of the scouts could feed themselves.
So, I just needed to give them the plates.
Yeah, it was really quite chill this year.
Some years, it's, like, there's one guy or two guys that are, like, a real handful.
You constantly have to be keeping track of them.
There was this one kid who, like, sometimes, like, his first year,
like, would run off-site, and we had to, like...
Shit.
He just ran away, and we had to try and find him.
And from then on, he, like, he wears, like, a high-visis jacket at all times.
And there's, like, photos of him given to all patrol leaders at the beginning of the week,
just in case that he runs away again.
It's funny.
That's high risk.
I ask, because friend of the show, Kazzie, is actually a similar position.
She works at a disabled camp during the summer.
She's an arts and crafts teacher.
So, I've heard a little bit about what you're describing from her.
Oh, yeah.
She was, her and her brother both do that, right?
We were talking about that on Squirtle Day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's cool.
And from what I can tell, it's fucking sick.
It's really fun.
Yeah.
It sounds like a real race.
If any of you would like to, like, come down for one week of the summer
and camp and do that with me, that would be great.
No, because we would get right in.
We'd just check in our mental illnesses.
We'll get in, you know, no problem.
Yeah, that's true.
I would, but I spend all of my summers taking care of my grandma, who is disabled.
So, I already do that kind of.
Makes sense.
What, here, here, maybe.
So, it's like, like, whip out our trading cards.
What does your grandma have?
Because my grandma's got a ton of shit.
Right, she's not mentally disabled.
She's just physically.
She's old and infirm.
It's having trouble movement.
So, I have to help her.
How old is she?
I'm curious.
She turned 88.
So, that doesn't seem battled, but.
Whoa.
Vriska.
There she is.
Oh, no.
Oh, yes.
My grandmother has broken both of her hips.
And each time she's broken them, she has fallen on me.
That's not a joke.
She has fallen on to me both times she's broken her hips.
Well, maybe she should stop breaking her hips,
and she wouldn't fall on you.
You're a cursed child.
Yeah.
You mean that she broke her hips on you?
Yes.
That is exactly what I'm trying to say.
She was doing the peach side B from Smash Brothers.
Yeah, yeah.
That goes to the hip.
I can't remember the first time.
I can only remember it vaguely.
But the second time, I remember excruciatingly in detail and vividly.
Because we were at the hospital already to Vris, my grandfather,
who had broken his hip as well.
So, he was at the hospital because he had broken his hip.
And so, we were just sitting there, and you know, I'm like a kid.
I'm like eight or something.
I'm like, I don't care about anyone's well-being or safety.
I am really hungry, mom.
Can we go do something to eat?
Mom, mom, mom.
I'm hungry, mom, mom.
And she's like.
And so, then we walk outside.
And we're taking the whole family.
We're going to a nearby pizzeria.
Then we walk in the door, and I'm like, Salvation, finally.
My taste buds are vibrating.
I can taste the pizza party marinara sauce right now.
I take one step, and then my grandmother crashes into me.
She's tripped on the carpet.
She crashes into me with like a thousand tons.
I fall onto the fucking floor.
And I just know, above all of the pain, above all of the cream,
I know I'm not going to be able to eat a pizza.
And that's what hurts the worst.
This is real, Bailey.
This is not a joke.
This is actually true.
This has happened to me.
Yeah, I believe you.
And then she was impossible.
It was even longer until I got to eight.
What a bitch.
Yeah, I know.
We're an asshole.
Seriously.
My grandmother's 90, and she's holding on by a thread.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
She got both of her hips.
She's holding up for a hero till the morning light.
You know that one comic of Apple Bloom talking to Granny Smith
and I think Granny Smith is like, hey, Apple Bloom's friend,
can you, where's Apple Bloom?
And Apple Bloom's like, I'm Apple Bloom.
Granny Smith's like, huh?
That's what's happening in real life for me.
Yeah.
It's dementia or whatever it is.
Grandma mistakes me for my mom sometimes.
Not like she thinks I'm her mom,
but like she calls out my mom's name towards me a lot.
Oh, well, my entire film does that regardless of age.
They confuse you with your mom?
Yeah.
Well, me with other cousins or something.
Oh, yeah.
I call my uncle's name a lot.
Is there a crew of people who look like you,
like in your family?
They're just so distinct.
You know what?
No.
I'm kind of the only person that looks like me.
Okay, I have the neck of my family.
All my family has this neck.
That short stout head connected to torso neck going on.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, you're close to not connect to the torso.
As opposed to not connected.
These other families with their head not connected to torso.
Yeah.
My four-chain uncle that I'm always talking about looks exactly like nothing like me.
He looks aptly nothing like me besides the throat.
He looks like a square, not like an insult,
but he is like a rhombus.
He is a geometric.
Yeah.
Okay.
My grandmother's gonna die soon.
Gotcha.
That's the ultimate disability.
We're all future disabled.
When you die, all your other disabilities go away.
So in a sense, it's kind of the best possible outcome.
We're all just nascent disabled people.
We're nascent handicaps just waiting to be birthed.
We're like pupa awaiting our transformation into butterflies.
That's true.
As J.H.W. Connors would always describe himself,
he is a future retired United States Marine.
He should be treated with respect.
Oh, it's true.
It's true.
We're all cursed with a disability called being alive for a thing of the day.
I have one other angle on disability, which is sometimes,
I don't know who else does this,
I imagine what would happen if I had a catastrophic accident
and I had like, oh, I lost either control of all of my body,
most of my body or my mind or something,
and how people would talk to me and react to me
and what they would say and how I would continue to live
and what skills hopefully I would still have
and I imagine futures where I have disabilities.
Having seen a lot of them, it's sort of like,
does anyone else do that?
I prefer not to.
I sometimes do that because it makes me sad.
Sometimes I wake up and I feel,
you know, you get that brain fog when you first wake up,
you don't know what's going on,
and I wonder if, and I might think for a moment
that I might be disabled, I don't know,
or I think that maybe I might have had an accident
that I didn't remember or maybe I'm paralyzed now
or I'm sick or something.
I feel that mostly when I wake up.
And then I feel grateful and then I realize,
I think I was just a mad, but it takes a while.
It takes a while for that feeling that like I am,
there is something wrong with me,
but it goes away after a while and I'm just like,
oh, thank God, but then I'm afraid
because I'm like, what if one day in the future
I wake up and have that thought and it's not fake?
It's true.
Very understandable.
I get that physically sometimes,
mostly with like, if I fall asleep and my arm is numb
and it is asleep and it will not move,
that freaks me out, but even worse,
is I have in fact experienced weird sleep paralysis
a couple of times and that is,
like you wake up and you, I cannot move
and it's like, well,
I will die now.
I've only gotten that once or twice
and usually when people talk about sleep paralysis,
they talk about like seeing ghosts and shit.
Yeah, I know what the fuck that's about.
Which has never, I mean, I have had,
I mean, there have been moments when like I've looked,
like when I'm just about to go to sleep
or just woken up or something,
I have like looked at something
and thought I'd seen like a terrifying face,
but it's like, it's only just been like a flash split second thing
where like, you know, your brain sees something
and recognizes it as a face,
even though it's not.
Yeah, yeah.
I haven't had the sustained,
like there's a demon sitting on my chest thing.
Yeah, I've had sleep paralysis a few times in my life.
I usually keep my eyes closed
because I am fearing to see something
that there's not in my room
because I would be probably be scared
to go back to my room.
You know that opening of Bloodborne
where you're lying on the table
and all the demons start to crawl over you?
No, I do not.
It's like that, it's like that.
But like, a funny thing about sleep paralysis
that I had like, this happened to me twice.
Like I never had sleep paralysis before.
Then it happened once
and then like a few months later,
it happened like twice in a row.
So it was very weird.
So like what happened was like,
I couldn't move and I was sort of still half asleep
and I kept having like a repeat to dream
where I kept dreaming that I kept waking up
and like that I wasn't waking up
and I couldn't wake myself up and I couldn't move.
And I realized that this is, you know,
this is on repeat.
Now I realized that I'm sort of like half asleep
and I can't wake up.
So what I tried to do was to scream my boyfriend's name
and it came out as a very soft menacing whisper.
So it's like, like it's the middle of the night
and like, so me and my boyfriend are asleep, right?
And like, then he hears suddenly like,
brighter, brighter.
It's like.
Oh, it's like, it's like at the end of Titanic
when she's like blowing that whistle
and like crying for those guys to come help her
because she's freezing to death
and the Pacific Ocean or whatever.
She's like, help, help.
I'm gonna die.
Fuck you.
Yeah.
I don't remember.
And he, I freaked him out.
The next day.
And you haven't seen Titanic
the greatest film of the generation.
I've seen Titanic when I was little.
Yeah, I've seen him.
I've seen Titanic.
That guy.
Somebody post fan art of the Titanic guy,
Guy Jinka or whatever.
Wait, wait.
You know that, you know that?
Titanic, Titanic Chan.
You know that?
Yeah, I was gonna say.
You know that shitty concolle or whatever it is
where like the battleships in Japan
like our hot anime girls make a Titanic one.
Make a Titanic girl.
Wait, I don't know what you're talking about.
I mean, I guess I can imagine.
Well, yeah, there's like a Japanese mobile game
slash like anime or something where it's like
Japanese battleships.
It's like, it's short for something.
It's Japanese battleships anthropomorphized.
Ethan showed me one episode of that
in hopes that I would think that it's cool.
And I'm putting you on fucking Blast right now publicly.
Ethan, what were you thinking?
I'm gonna fucking shame you right now.
It was the worst experience of my entire life.
And I can't believe you made me do that.
Oh yeah, concolle.
Conti collection better known as concolle.
That's the one.
Better known as so many dojins.
Like so many.
Well, I mean, yeah.
I mean, it's built for dojins.
And there's that one.
The only time I've ever had sleep paralysis
is I was like real young.
I was like 10 or so.
And looking back on it, the guy, like, like,
I, you know, it was like I couldn't.
Oh my God, they got little masks over their head.
Yeah, and the guy, there was like this guy
standing in my doorway that started to walk over me.
And looking at him back on it,
he kind of looked like Matthew Matosis.
So I'm gonna just want to assume that it was Matthew Matosis.
Wait, you know what Matthew Matosis looks like?
Isn't he like not showing his face?
No, his avatar.
Oh, oh, like that.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, he looked like that, but like a real...
I know he's an Irish fuck who wears Hawaiian shirts.
Some red-haired trash.
Yeah, he wears Hawaiian shirts to work like a...
Like a very funny man.
Did you know that Hawaiian shirts are formal wear in Hawaii?
Did you know that?
That's, what?
That's cool.
That's true.
Is it just because it's a hot transition?
No, because they're like, they're like old school,
like they are formal fancy clothes
to like wear a nice Hawaiian shirt.
It must be because...
Like you'd wear it like to a business meeting,
like the mayor would wear, like on TV,
like a Hawaiian shirt.
I mean, wearing a suit must have not taken off there
because of how hot it is.
That's my guess.
That's maybe?
Is that actually that hot there?
Nate.
Yeah, well, much is, by the way, reporting from Hawaii right now.
Yeah, Nate, at your request,
you have sent me on a PCP scouting mission
down to Hawaii to survey the land for demolition
all the mountains and all the towns people shall be eradicated
at your behest.
So I'm here.
I'm here currently reporting from Maui.
From Maui.
There you go.
Yeah, from Maui.
I'm down in Kihei.
So look, that docks me right now.
Keyblade?
Wait, is that Keyblade or was that Keyblade?
Yeah, he's in Kihei.
Right, okay, okay.
Appreciate that.
Nate, actually, I meant to tweet about this
and I probably still will,
but so I got your letter.
Oh, you got my package.
I got your package.
Oh, yeah.
Should I say what it was?
Yeah, tell everybody.
Tell everybody.
So yeah, you sent me this wooden,
this carved wooden idol of the god of...
It was a tiki, it's a tiki.
...of the god of money.
The god of money.
And Nate, I swear to god, no lie,
the day that I opened this package,
I got like three new patrons for no discernible reason.
There you fucking go.
The god of money.
Patreon.com.
But it did.
There it is.
Yeah.
Patreon.com.
The fucking tiki god commands you.
I'm glad you liked it.
I got a tiki idol for my aunt one time,
just out of the blue sheet.
She had gone to like Florida,
not even near Hawaii,
but she just brought in back some tiki statue.
And what I would,
you can hear this on the PCP actually,
is when this incident I'm about to describe happened.
Oh.
Well, I'd like to like,
I like to slam him against things.
We just, it just made a great vibrating noise
and I just love to listen to it.
So one day on the PCP,
I was just, you know.
I do that with children skulls.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, go on.
I was just doing that.
I was just slamming him.
And then he snapped in half
and he like broke.
His like feet fell off of his body.
And then he fucking disintegrated before me.
And I think that starting like the mid 50s
or something, PCP,
if you can find a timestamp anyone,
I will reward you with absolutely nothing.
Is there a distinctive snapping sound
in the mix?
Yeah, yeah.
There is, okay.
It happens, right?
And I think I also,
I also see something in the effect of like,
oh no, like something has happened,
but everyone just like stampede's over me.
Like you don't only hear pain in the background,
like something has occurred.
So if you can find that, let me know.
Also, Hawaii, just,
this is the best place on earth.
I understand what you mean.
It is the best place on earth.
There's no debate.
Munch is there right now.
This is two of us who have now confirmed.
It is the best.
PCPHQ.
PCPHA as in Hawaii.
That's what we need.
This, I said this to you in DM's Nate.
This is like, off the back of Italy,
Italy was great and beautiful and stuff,
but it's like all foreign countries,
a huge hassle.
It is such a hassle to get around,
to learn the language,
to exchange all of your money
and do all of these things you have to do
in order to exist in a foreign country.
And Hawaii has all of the beautiful architecture
and all of the cool scenery
and the beaches and all that kind of stuff,
but it is America.
It just is America.
It's so convenient.
I don't like beaches.
Ben, go to Hawaii and tell me that you fat motherfucker.
You just don't want anyone to see your pasty-ass body.
That's your problem.
You need to get over it.
Well, that's true.
I mean, I'm not going to deny any of what you just said,
but I don't know.
I like looking at beaches
and I like maybe like spending like,
I don't know, an hour walking there,
but like just staying there, laying there
and like having and getting a tan
or going to the water.
Okay, but Mages, think about it like this.
What if...
Okay, this is how it is to live in Hawaii.
I know because Michelle lived there for many years
and is a Hawaiian.
It's like you go to work,
you go to school or whatever you want to do,
you go do some work,
and then you take the two-minute walk
to the most beautiful beach in the world
and you swim there for as long as you fucking feel like.
You watch the most beautiful sunset in the world
for as little or as long as you want,
and then you go home, you shower,
and you continue the rest of your day.
It's just in the middle of the day
is the best things in the world.
Okay, I'm sorry, what's up?
I can't swim.
Did you splash the shallows, dawg?
It's all good.
Oh my God, it's because you live in ice place.
That's the reason.
There is no water there.
There's only ice.
Not even in the bath.
I mean, the infrastructure is so fraught
by the urban warfare going on in the streets.
I don't understand people who can't swim
because swimming isn't really anything.
You can just exit in the water.
You think that makes swimming real.
Swimming requires a strong will to live
and age lacks that, so that's why, you know,
it's understandable.
I mean, trending water is a skill
you can learn in like 10 minutes.
I've been trying, like when I was younger,
my parents and stuff, like baby tried
to teach me how to swim, but I don't know why.
I just, I just, I never picked up on it.
I'm good at like diving.
Maybe it's just your colossal body.
Yeah, you dive, but then what do you do after birth?
You didn't teach me how to come back up.
You just stay at the bottom.
I just sink like a rock.
Let me just throw this at you guys real quick.
I looked into this after going to Hawaii.
You can just live in Hawaii for approximately like,
it's like for three grand, for three grand a month.
If you make three grand a month,
that you can put aside for like rent and stuff.
And other things cost more in Hawaii too.
You've got to import stuff.
But if you basically make three grand a month
that you can spend on housing,
you can live in a great place in Hawaii.
I looked into it and that's what it costs,
which is that's like three times what like I pay to live out here.
That's significantly more than what I make.
It is more.
Sure, sure.
I'm just, but there is a number.
And if you can achieve that number,
you can live in Hawaii and it's a great place.
What if you can only achieve that number outside of Hawaii?
Also, you can live in Hawaii for less than that
if you are just like willing to live in a shitty,
very shitty place.
Well, I am.
All right.
I want to give a shout out to Michelle
because I've seen at least six of her here.
I've seen at least six of you.
Which is a Hawaiian girl taking a selfie?
I've seen at least six.
We were at Michaels today picking up supplies
so she could take selfies.
Wait, what do you need to take a selfie, a stick?
No, I mean like background implements
and sparkles and glitter and things
that one uses to beautify.
They got apps for that, dude.
They got filters for that.
Yeah, that's true.
This is a new PCP meme slash vocabulary term.
A Michelle is a Hawaiian girl taking a selfie.
Taking a selfie.
Yeah, that sounds good.
That sounds good.
Works for me.
Oh, I was also harassed.
Well, I'll get to this later
because there's actually a far more pressing issue.
If you guys remember the nature episode
in which I describe a scenario.
I want to dub nature light or diet nature
in which it's not like real off-road experience.
You're not in a real forest.
It is a paved, Disneyland-esque romp
through a human-civilized section of a rainforest.
I'm here to report that in Hawaii this exists and is real.
Shout out to the I-A-O-I-O, I-O Valley.
It is great.
It's just a small little section
and there's paved roads and everyone.
But you go into a real, actual, historically significant
and beautiful rainforest.
I was described as the second wettest place on Earth.
Except for your mom's vagina when I am around.
There you go.
It was great.
I just had to walk up like paved pavement.
I just walked through some rainforest.
I could touch a rock and it was great.
The Heinz got it figured out.
So the rest of the world?
Yeah, they do.
I was also well in Lahaina, harassed by a dirty, disgusting,
indie artist.
I walked into like some...
Like a street artist?
Talking to shit?
No, no, no.
An indoor artist, even worse.
A proper bed artist.
So he could flex his whores.
So I walked in this art gallery
and then around the corner, I'm entering the door,
he said, some skinny white Ben St. Fox says,
I've been waiting for you.
I turn around and I say, oh, hello.
And then he's like...
He's something in effect of like,
hey, have you heard of Sacred Geometry?
And I'm like, yeah, dude, I love it.
Oh, yeah.
Hell yeah.
Hell yeah, I have.
He quickly reveals that this is not a joke
and he actually has many Sacred Geometry tattoos
all over his body.
Word.
Yeah.
And so he's like, do you know what dirty poor is?
Do you know what dirty poor of painting is?
It's like cut scene flashback smash cut
to literally fit like 30 minutes ago.
Kazine telling me about what dirty poor is
and about how it is the most fucking sinful low effort.
You are a hack thing that you can do as an artist.
I don't know what this is.
I have no idea what this is.
Here's what dirty poor is.
It's you get a cup.
You need a cup and a canvas and some paint.
You get a cup and you just pour some paint into a cup
and you don't mix them together.
You just pour them so it's just, you know, in the cup
it's like a kaleidoscope.
Yeah.
Just is some grains and some yellows.
Then you pour that onto a canvas.
That's it?
Yeah, that's it.
Well, that sounds lame.
Yeah, it's retarded.
And so he leads me into this little hut he's got working.
This fucking skinny white asshole.
This twain.
When I heard you say dirty poor,
I thought you were describing my economic situation.
Yeah.
But that is true.
It's like a hygiene thing to me.
So he leaves me in this room and just wall to wall
the exact same image, but just the color palettes are different.
It just all is just what you can imagine.
It's just like a splotch of like water,
like a splotch of water that is some different colors.
And a single fan art of crying sands in the back in the back of the shop.
I Google dirty poor.
Yeah, I mean some of this imagery is kind of nice.
Some of it kind of looks like a, like a geode, you know,
like you cut open a rock and it's got all these like crystal layers.
Sometimes it kind of looks like that a little bit.
Yeah.
I've seen worse, I guess.
I mean, I'm sure the ones I'm seeing,
I'm sure the top results on Google are the best of the best.
And he's like, oh, what do you think?
And of course that's the situation you have to be like,
oh, you know, it's really good, dude.
And so I'm like, oh, I like this one a lot and the colors are nice.
And he's like, oh yeah, normally it's $500,
but I can get it to you for only a hundred if you want to buy it right now.
Why does he think that like, well, okay,
you do look like a 45 year old man,
but you know, still it's, he's just, he's just, he's just cold Colin.
He's just a cold approach in people.
I respect the hustle.
You gotta get people in there, you gotta do your routine.
You gotta get, you gotta, what's the word?
You gotta escalate the interaction up until the sale.
You gotta throw some nags in there.
Do you call you a chubster?
You'd be like, oh, you look like a big guy,
but you could afford some of these.
You gotta bring them to the point,
you gotta push the choice, you gotta make them make the choice
right there and now.
And you gotta have established the groundwork that they like this painting.
Right, right.
Don't forget the 90s title rule.
He's gotta bring the painting 90% of the way to you
and make you come the 10% of him at the end.
That's, yeah.
One time in my life, I would love to have the courage
to just say to someone, no, it looks like shit.
I would love the opportunity to do that.
But nobody really asks me.
Then hit him with a dab.
Bam.
That was not all, by the way.
He said to me, and I was like,
well, I don't know, like I am underage
and I don't have that amount of money in cash in my wallet right now.
And he was like, ah, ah, ah.
So how about you go back to your mom
and how about you get some more money from her from, you know,
big mom and you come back here tomorrow night.
He's just pushing it.
Yeah, yeah, just pushing it.
Tempting proposition.
Yeah, yeah.
She just goes siphon off my mom to buy this stupid dirty pour
that he said that he makes every single night in 30 minutes.
He has claimed that to me.
Yeah.
No, no, you twink.
I'm not going to come back to your art festival.
I'm not going to buy your dirty pour.
Leave me alone.
Dirty pour.
Munchy.
Totally.
The first of those two stories you told, I just wanted to say,
that is fabulous.
But when you were talking about the cool rainforest stuff,
I wasn't on Maui when I was in Hawaii.
I was on Oahu, the one with Honolulu and stuff.
The Apple City and shit.
Were you there too?
No, no, no, I said I wish I was there.
Oh.
Because there's no ramen over here.
There's no ramen over here.
Yeah, that's the most developed place.
It's the most hippin' and hoppin' and scene.
But there's a highway.
I-3.
There's like three main highways, I-1, 2, and 3.
And I-3 goes through the middle of the island,
and it cuts through these valleys,
which is just literally where they film Jurassic Park.
And so every time we drove through,
and you'd see these big old,
Jurassic, big old fucking hills,
and Michelle's dad would be like,
hey, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
I'd be like, right.
I'm sure he did that like six times by the six times,
and you're like, okay.
Well, actually, he did it the first time.
I did it subsequently every time after.
That's how it went.
That's how much he liked it.
I loved it.
It was great.
It was adorable.
Everybody had a great time.
This dirty pour, it reminds me.
I hate the meat.
I hate that.
It reminded me.
It's really gross.
I Googled dirty pour,
and I had the displeasure to see
both dirty and poor people before me,
which was very unfortunate.
I didn't like that one bit.
It's P-O-U-R, you know.
Oh, I spelled it wrong.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Now I see.
Yes, that was the source of my confusion.
Fuck, wait.
What was I going to say?
Something about our...
Oh, it reminded me of this movie.
Maybe you've seen it.
It's like a...
It's called Titanic.
So documentary.
It's called...
No, it's not Titanic.
20%.
It's like a movie of a little parkie.
Oh, God, it's called Exit Through the Gift Shop.
Anyone seen Exit Through the Gift Shop?
That's a great one.
That's by Banksy, I think.
Yeah, I think it was probably made by Banksy secretly.
It's kind of debated, whether
or not about Banksy.
how much of Banksy is staged.
It's not specifically about Banksy.
It's about this guy who gets involved
with the street art community,
even though he has no skill or talent, and rises through the ranks, he manages to get
some good PR through various shady ways, and then he gets Banksy's endorsement, and then
so, based on that endorsement alone, he throws an art show, and is a huge overnight success,
and everyone loves his shit, and then like, but the scene that it reminded me of is a
scene where he's trying to sell all these, like he's promised all this original art
to people, people who bought it from him, so what he'll do for that is he just lines
up posters, and will just take cans of spray paint, and just sprays all these posters at
once to put an individual mark on them to make it personal custom art, right?
So that's what this dirty poor reminds me, you mix up some shit, you pour it on a canvas,
you swirl it around a little bit, you throw out the ones that look like crap, and if some
of them look kind of okay, you keep them, and then you sell them for $500 to some kid
in your Hawaiian bungalow.
Quick theory, greetings everyone, soyboy here, here's my theory, Banksy, Shadman, they are
the same guy, prove me wrong, you can't.
I never agree with the political stance of yours until now, now I'm in agreement with
this ideological theory right now.
I build my whole moral system on this foundation.
Have you ever seen Banksy and Shadman in the same place at the same time?
Here's my hot take, Banksy is good, shut up.
What are you saying about Shadman?
Have you not seen the comic that's taking the world by storm of the cute comic that
Shadman just did, where Waluigi finally gets invited to smash, and Daisy's crying, so he
gives Daisy his invitation.
It's the real reason Waluigi's not in smash, because he gave it to Daisy.
Also, can I just say, if I give you Ben an invitation to my birthday party and you just
give it to some dumb cryin' bitch who I didn't invite on purpose, I'm not gonna be thrilled
when she shows up with your invitation, I'm just saying.
People are mad that the world would have been better served if Waluigi had gone and not
given Daisy that invitation.
He has done a harm.
No, see, Waluigi can't be Waluigi if he wins, though.
What's that?
What was that?
Like, Waluigi can't be Waluigi if he wins, he has to be the underdog.
You're saying that Waluigi is defined by his perpetual, like, underdog status and loss
continuously.
Yes.
That's like people love him.
People love him because of that one image of him, like the plushie of him in the in-ray.
He is the revenant, IRL, only in video games.
Like, imagine, I mean, if Waluigi was in Smash, people were like, yeah, but they immediately
not care because then there's no guy to make memes about anymore.
He is the meme.
Like, Ridley was the biggest meme.
That one's gone.
We need a new meme.
Okay, Waluigi, I guess.
Yeah.
I mean, and let's say Waluigi got confirmed immediately, immediately the meme focus would
shift to, oh, how about Isaac from Golden Sun or, you know, Gino, like, these are the
big people they're talking about these days or whoever else.
I'd rather see Gino than Waluigi personally.
I mean, so would I, but I'd like both of them, you know.
I wanted as many as possible.
I want as many as possible.
Okay, can I just say, I've been wanting to say, Bandana Waddle D is the worst possible
to who?
Why?
No, no, literally, zero, no, Z-E-R-O, not any character.
He is a void of character.
He's got a spear, you idiot.
Yeah.
He's a spear fighter from Fire Emblem.
Anyone who wants, like, the weird thing is, I was looking at the polls, he's actually doing
quite well in the polls for people wanting him.
Yeah, those polls.
He is not, not a character.
There is nothing.
He is.
Hold on.
Is he from that game that we played at Radcom, the, like, four person?
No, he's not.
Well, he does.
You can unlock him.
He's appeared basically every game after that.
Like, he's the main series character now.
What do you mean?
Okay.
His first appearance, as I recall, was there was a Bandana wearing a Waddle D in Meta Knight's
Revenge.
I think that's where it first showed up.
Well, it appears in, like, Revenge of the King and stuff like that, a lot of mini-games
in a...
Isn't he one of Meta Knight's, like, henchmen?
No, no, no, no, you're thinking of Sam's Waddle D, which is a completely distinct
character.
Sailor Cap Waddle D is not Bandana Waddle D.
Right.
Oh, okay, yeah.
My mistake.
I forgot these totally distinguishable characters from each other.
Yeah.
They're nothing alike.
There's no similarity.
It's, it's like having Toad in, like, nobody cares.
Let me ask you this.
Well, yeah, I mean, I would like, yeah, Toad is kind of similar, only Toad has a thousand
times more personality and history than, than fucking Bandana Waddle D.
Why do you think, why are you dissing Bandana Waddle D right now?
I actively hate the idea that Bandana Waddle D would get in.
Okay.
Like, if he gets in, I'll be like, okay, cool, another character.
But he, he does not deserve it.
He does not, he has not paid his dues in the video game landscape.
Yeah, I think, I know what you're saying.
It's like, there's so many characters that are cool, that are getting the snob, and then,
like, there's like some, at some point, it feels like you're just sort of, they're sort
of putting characters in, like, reaching, like, we can put this one in, I guess.
When there are so many actually good ones that are just not being noticed at all.
That's a variation of the classic slots arguments, like, so-and-so is taking up a slot that could
go to someone else.
And I, there is something to that, absolutely, because they only have so much, so much manpower
to put in and make new characters.
But beyond that, I'm making a further point that, like, just imagine for me, for a second
here, what would Bandana Waddle D's final smash be?
Like, what magical, like, character-defining epic thing has he done that would be turned
into a final smash?
First of all, you're making the mistake that final smashes have anything to do with the
actual character, because most final smashes are just literally nothing.
But he has literally nothing to him!
What would it be?
Tell them what you, what would it be?
He has a match made in heaven, man.
He could have King Deity's, like, before final smash, he could have the one where he calls
a bunch of his brethren, some wildies to come down, he could have that, he could have, you
know, so lame.
So lame.
I don't hate the idea of Bandana Waddle D, but I feel like we've got Kirby, DDD and
Meta Knight.
I feel like Kirby's pretty well represented in the series.
I don't know if we need another one.
Fair.
I generally agree.
Also, put Galacta Knight in as a skin for Meta Knight.
Do it now.
Galacta Knight is a skin.
I can't believe you think that Galacta Knight is a skin.
No, as a skin.
As a skin, god damn it.
As a skin.
Okay, okay.
No, no, I'm not saying that he shouldn't get it.
I'm just saying that he is gay in concept.
Well, he is pink and gay, but you know, that's fine.
I saw a video about this, that in, god, what is the one, the one that we played at Radcon
that none of us liked?
Kirby, whatever, the new one, yeah, Star Allies.
Kirby, Star Allies.
Okay, there is a secret boss in Star Allies where Galacta Knight shows up.
I saw this, yeah.
Yeah, and then none other than the butterfly that rests on Kirby's face in the intro cut
scenes to like many, many games, shows up and merges with Galacta Knight and becomes
Morpho Knight, the ultimate warrior.
That's uh, yeah, that's accurate.
I don't know what was being implied by that in any way.
I actually watched many, I watched many YouTube like lore videos on that character because
I actually do pay attention to like Kirby lore and I'm kind of interested in it.
Uh, I, yeah.
I just happened to catch, I happened to catch this yesterday because I was watching Arlo's
review of Kirby, Star Allies and the, the, okay.
Let's talk about Arlo once we're done with this because I want to get into that.
Please.
Okay, we can talk about Arlo, but I just want to say that, okay, I thought like Star
Allies was so boring and terrible and I hated it.
I hated every second of playing it, but I, but apparently it's really short, which is
also bad.
However, I kind of wish we had gotten to the end because I saw the ending and the ending
is like super epic.
It's like, the final, the final battle is this, it's awesome.
Oh, I think I actually beat that game and just forgot.
Kirby games have fallen into this rut basically from day one, but like every single game after
a, like return to dreamland and it's like, it has to, Kirby has to go to space, Kirby
has to go to space and fight over designed monster like, like, he always has to do that
now.
He didn't always have to do that.
It could just, I mean, Kirby's always fought nightmare fuel at the end, but he doesn't
have to be this specific brand of nightmare fuel.
It can be, it can be something different guys.
I'm actually playing through because despite me being a Kirby fan, I haven't played a couple
of the newer ones.
So I'm just now going through triple deluxe.
I want to play Robobot and return to dreamland.
And they aren't, okay, return to dreamland is fun because it's co-op and it's not like
completely mind numbing like star allies.
I enjoyed, I enjoyed return to dreamland.
It's a good game.
It's, it's good.
It's not as good as I remember and also triple deluxe so far seems pretty fucking nothing.
It seems like, okay, it seems that like it's, I'm glad you're telling me that because I've
been wondering.
Return to dreamland seems like it is literally the same game.
Well guys, Munchy real quick, I just, I loaded up Kirby because I wanted to see if I'd beat
in the game, which I'm pretty sure I have.
I just unlocked just by starting the game.
I can now summon a dark metanite.
Dark metanite.
Yeah, from, from, from the amazing mirror, from the amazing mirror.
He's from the dark side of the mirror and it's in the shadow.
Oh, well, okay.
That's cool.
That's a real character.
All right.
I like it.
Never mind.
The amazing mirror is great, but like I don't think it's the best Kirby game.
It's the best one.
Yeah.
The amazing mirror with the four players because that's the way it's meant to be, but I don't
know if I can literally do that anymore.
I don't know if that's like, it was, I mean, if you have two people with a GBA, they can
connect, you know, Wi-Fi or whatever cable though, we're having a cable for like four
people.
Oh shit.
There is.
I forgot about the cable.
But Star Allies was shit, right?
Like playing Star Allies was terrible, right?
I actually, I did go, I beat Star Allies on my own.
I thought it was okay, not great.
That's really all I have to say about it.
I think it would have been better alone.
Having four people.
It is better alone.
It is such a clusterfuck.
I didn't even know what was happening most of the time, just everything just died before
I even knew what I was doing.
That's exactly.
There was zero challenge.
It was not fun.
It's way more fun alone.
I cannot get over that choo-choo shit.
Oh yeah.
It's not even that it was too easy.
My problem was not that it was too easy.
It was that, it was just that, there was, yeah, I had no clue what was going on.
I didn't need to do anything.
Yeah.
For a multiplayer game, that was kind of the biggest problem with it.
Like it was all about playing together and by playing together, you don't do anything
yourself.
You're just alone for the ride.
I'm becoming increasingly aware of an epidemic of in you, new Kirby.
We are definitely in the era of new Kirby, where Kirby is just this perfectly spherical,
like no personality happy face as opposed to like being fat like he's supposed to in
the old days.
Yeah, a little blob.
And that transcends to all ways.
He used to have some weight to him.
Yeah, he used to have some weight to him.
And that transcends to like gameplay, to aesthetic, to like music, to everything, where it's just
like it's become way too clean and way too new Super Mario Bros.
And also D.D.
looks disgusting in the new games.
This is, this is unironically why this, this like hasn't made any difference yet.
But I still hope to this day that, that asshole, elitist video game playing 100% completionist
assholes like me and like us are the way that we save companies like Square Enix and Nintendo
for making increasingly shit products that are just like, like, like these Kirby games
are the perfect example.
Amazing Mirror is the best Kirby game.
It like, it doesn't have all this fucking online connectivity, all this shit.
But you know what?
On the other hand, I'm completely wrong because the people, the people who games are made
for like 99% of people don't beat a game when they buy it.
They just play it for like two hours and they never play it again because they just felt
like doing something with some money.
So the, the actual completionists are such a small minority that they don't even matter.
You know, the thing about that is that it used to be the case that games, like, like,
I know there was, there was only so many games and they were all kind of expensive.
I mean, they're still expensive, but like, I think people have more money to throw at
them, I guess.
I mean, there's like steam sales and stuff, but like, games do not, games are more about
playing it for a bit and not beating it necessarily.
People get new games all the time and it's not really a big deal because they can't afford
it.
But when I was younger, I got so used to having the game and playing the game until I beat
it completely.
And it just, it feels wrong to me, but it's not necessarily wrong in real life.
Achieving mastery in a game is what I play for and the rest is a waste of time.
Playing the new Kirby game for an hour sucks.
Don't care.
I want to master it.
Can we, can we talk about that?
Man, I was, I was streaming nuclear thrones with it.
We will.
And I felt so shitty.
I was doing so bad at it.
Oh, I watched that.
I watched that.
You were fucking up bad, dude.
Well, that's not there to carry you.
The only times you've ever done this, we used to play multiplayer and I carry you hardcore.
That's the only time you've done good.
No, the last time I played on my own, like, I managed to loop and this time I only, I
only, well, shut up.
Okay.
Well, usually I, looping is not out of the realm of possibility for me, but this time
it just was not happening until the very end.
And then I got almost close and it was a big letdown when I died against the throne.
Oh man.
Hey, we need to stream more and we all need to fucking raid each other's streams.
We need to do that more.
We should do that more.
That little raid button.
But before we leave Kirby, before we leave Kirby, I, much, much like Digibro famously
has said that the A is the best era for anime and that's how, and that's what he believes.
I am now coming to the conclusion that the DS was the best era for Nintendo games and
the DS is home to the best installments of each Nintendo series.
So Kirby, you got Squeeze Squad, you got, you got, you got, you got, you got Canvas
Curse, you got, you got a Superstar Ultra, the best.
Wait, Canvas Curse?
Yes.
Canvas Curse is great.
That, that's the best Kirby spinoff, even better than the sequel, which came later,
which actually is really terrible and I hate it.
I never played it.
Was very good.
And, and for Pokemon, Pokemon especially, you got Black, Two, and White Two, which just
are the best Pokemon games.
You got Heart, Gold, and, and, and Steel Soul Silver.
Black, Two, White Two are my favorite Pokemon games.
No, Heart, Gold, and White Two are best mechanically.
Heart, Gold, and Soul Silver are my favorite though.
They're my favorite.
Heart, Gold, and Soul Silver are, like, it's really close between Heart, Gold, Soul Silver
and Black and White Two.
You know, I, real quick, I never played Black and White Two.
Why, why are they so good?
Why are they so good?
Because it's, it's, it's all the best Pokemon.
Because I played some of them and then I was like, well this is just Black and White One,
so why would I play this?
It's so fast.
It was everything good about Pokemon until, and that was the last one before the switch
to 3D.
Okay.
All right, fair enough.
When it suddenly got worse.
If you want to hear a five hour analysis, talk to Steve about this, but Black and White
Two is good for the fallen reasons.
It's so fucking fast, it's lightning fast.
There's absolutely no bullshit.
You just pick up and play and go.
All the sprites are, it's before Gen Six, all of the sprites aren't, like, washed out
and awful.
They're all bright and vivid colors and it's, it's the best Pokemon has ever looked to
this day.
They move so good.
It is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And, and the gameplay is modern enough to have all the conveniences that you like, you
know, like, repel.
You, you can just, would you like to use another repel?
Yes.
As all the convenience like that, teams aren't disposable, but also it's not new enough
to have all of the baby pissy patty bullshit that you don't like.
Yeah, okay.
The legendaries in Gen Five were kind of disappointing, I don't like them very much, but I don't
give a shit about legendaries at any point ever.
I just ignore them, but whatever.
All right, all right, right, right, fucking Arlo, YouTuber Arlo.
I have an opinion, I have a strong opinion about Arlo and, and like game reviewers in
general, and I will explain it now, there's two types of game reviewers on YouTube.
There's people who try way too hard to be John Tron, aka me, yeah, and to varying levels
of success.
And then there are people who are trying way too hard to be Mathematosus, which is like
all of the analysis sect of like, like game reviews, I think of like as reviews and analysis
as like the same group.
Yeah.
So like there's people who like just talk about something.
I don't think that Arlo is either of those.
No, he's, he's, he's kind of like the most frustrating one I've ever seen.
Mostly because he looks, he talks like normal, you know, he's just like a decent reviewer.
He's pretty good, you know, you go to him for like a, you know, quite a chill review about
some things like, yeah, I'm just talking about thing and this is what a game is and I like
games and yeah, yeah, yeah, this is me, Arlo, but he has the best like resource at his disposal
for being the funniest game reviewer in the world.
He is a puppeteer and a very good puppeteer and he has a really cool looking puppet and
he's the most like, it's the most squandered potential of any YouTube channel I've ever
seen and it makes me sad just to see it.
He could do a lot more with the character if he, because what he actually does is just
like he doesn't really do like Jon Tron style comedy and he doesn't really do like deep
analysis.
He really just does like consumer reviews, like he just does like, should you buy this
product?
Like how good is this game of things, which is fine and for that, I think it's great that
stuff.
But yeah, you know, now that you mention it, if he did more, God, I mean, I'm such a fucking
idiot.
I'm such a fucking Rube for lore, but if he did like more in character stuff and skits
and stuff, he does them like very rarely and they're kind of funny, but he doesn't, yeah,
if he focused more on that, I'd like it.
Here's an extension of this point.
It's that because that is the case, I actually find watching Arlo's content kind of off-putting
because I'm like, why is there a puppet?
Like what is the point of this puppet here?
It's true that there is no point.
I know the man, the man has a passion for the puppet.
He has a passion for the puppet and I can respect that.
But I don't think the other receiving end here.
It's akin to like a person talking about video games in a normal way while wearing full clown
makeup and a clown costume.
But also not as funny as that.
It's like, well, it's like, I mean, traditionally, you would use a, you would get some idiot
on Tumblr, you would pay him a hundred dollars to draw you a couple poses that you would
swap out and you would use a cartoon avatar.
And this is that only it doesn't piss me off from overuse and being boring and a cliche.
I salute his industry.
I absolutely do for all the effort that he clearly puts into puppeting that guy.
But okay, here's another thing.
Okay, this is a, this is a, this is my biggest problem with Arlo across the board.
He uses a green screen and he has those little dangly hairs at the top of his head and you
can see the shitty effect of the green screen on those very thin hairs and that always annoys
me.
Every single time I'm like, that's where my eyes go.
I'm like, I can see the green screen effect happening on those, like it's, it's bad puppet
design for using a green screen.
Well, it's actually quite good design because of how very, but with the green screen specifically,
that's always annoyed me right now.
Like if it's, if something like you can make hair, like really, like, I think he's just
doing the green screen kind of badly.
I agree.
If he lived up to his green screen game in some way, this would probably fix that problem,
but it does exist.
I'm never going to be able to stop seeing it now.
Right.
So I got a, I got a screenshot on the chat.
So we got to link this so people can see this.
I should reiterate or iterate for the first time.
I don't hate Arlo, but he just, he just makes me sad to see, to see such talent for such,
for a YouTube channel.
Like make a real TV show with that, please.
I mean, he probably doesn't have the resources.
How do you do that?
Join Sesame Street.
I don't know.
Like they'd still do those YouTube or, or what do you call it, the Muppet Show.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
For whatever fucking reason, for whatever fucking weird twist of fate has led us into
this darkest timeline that we all reside in, reviewing video games on YouTube is how you
get your name out there and you get the ability to, to be known and do things.
Then that's what he's doing.
Also, look at the edge.
Look at the edge of all of Arlo's edge.
You can see it is tinged green because he is using a green screen that has always annoyed
me.
I mean, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but he should be using a blue screen because of the medium
he's chosen.
I have to give this technical, this a technical criticism.
He needs to either get a better camera, use better software or stop using a green screen.
Some combination of those said this particular issue stops annoying me.
That is my personal opinion as a viewer of your content Arlo.
Please help.
There you go.
Yeah.
All right.
Yep.
I don't hate him though.
I've enjoyed his content though.
Yeah.
Speaking of Puppet guys on YouTube, how about that guy who uses like that old man, you know
that old man puppet that the guy uses?
There are like two people who use that old man puppet.
Oh.
Is that true?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Why?
I think like Digi was saying that he really liked him the other day and I've watched
him for years.
God damn it.
What's it called?
Uh, Old Man Puppet Game Review.
Um, I, like I've seen it before, uh, well, the point is I've watched a bunch.
That guy is fine.
He also uses a puppet and like he, he like is a character of the old man, whatever it
is.
I'll put a link because I'll find a sapper if I can.
Mr. Plankett?
No, it's not Mr. Plankett.
God damn it.
Oh.
Vox's Productions.
Found it.
SmackTalk.
That's the one.
I like that.
Have you screen shot the puppet?
I have linked it.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
That's the puppet I've seen, uh, used in Honey Badger Radio, but that's not a game related
for watching.
Nothing more, more dangerous than a Last Jedi review.
There's nothing I want to click on less than something that's on Star Wars.
Well, it was just the first one that came up.
Uh, do you say he's like Honey Badger related?
No, no, no.
Not him.
Like there is a person on Honey Badger Radio, uh, which is a podcast, um, and he uses the
same puppet, but they're not the same person.
It just confused me one time.
It's probably like a commercially available puppet or something that they both use or
something.
Like, I would like if, if, you know, it's the Last Jedi review with an old man puppet,
but it's like, it's always like a skit comedy, like clickbait, not actually a review.
It's just a fucking silly old man doing, I fucking hate Star Wars.
I'm a puppet.
Like, I just want it to be a comedy thing because it's a comedy puppet.
It's so funny and cute and silly.
And it's just like saying like, yes, I think the game design here is very good.
I mean, this guy give credit because he is playing an old man character and he is not
I haven't seen this.
So I don't know.
Wait, wait.
Yeah.
If we're talking about Arlo, um, he does, he does come across as a Muppet reviewing
video games.
Like he made, like he doesn't swear and he maintains the, he has the right tone for it.
So it doesn't feel like it's completely arbitrary that it's, that it's a puppet doing the talking.
Yeah.
Um, but it is, it is, I do.
It's a, it's a concept that I really like and enjoy and am behind.
And yeah, I guess it is kind of a missed opportunity that more is, he doesn't do more with it.
Well, here's his invitation to step up his game, right?
You know, there's nothing stopping him.
Arlo.
Take it and run to Arlo.
If you want to be the 10th member, you gotta remove that green screen, dude.
That reminds me.
I got to get back to Laserbot.
Yeah, you do.
Laserbot messaged me back.
I think he might be, because he said before that he was interested in being on an episode
and he got back to me the other day, uh, but I was not logged into my Facebook, so I didn't
see the notification.
Okay.
I got to see.
Facebook lol.
Yeah.
I know.
Well, that's, I could, that's how I got in contact with him was I branded him on Facebook.
I mock your form of communication of choice.
I do not use, I do not use Facebook, uh, except in dire circumstances.
Oh no, no, no guys.
It was just my wife's son Facebook.
I swear.
It wasn't me at all.
Yeah.
This is you.
I hate Facebook as much as anyone else.
I swear.
Um, anyway, that's, so yeah, we will, I will let you know how that goes.
Well, good.
Yes.
Let me get back.
By the way, yeah.
If anyone forgets.
I'll let you know if, if Laserbot senpai notices me.
Please do.
That's the tales gets trolled guys.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Laserbot is the tales gets trolled guy.
Um, do we want to do another topic or should we, should we move on to our next topic?
I have this one little bit.
I have some more.
Okay.
I had this one thing that I couldn't say, uh, cause it turned into a Hawaii talk during
the disability thing.
I can't say it.
Oh no.
Uh, the, um, when I was talking about like dreaming of like the possibility of like me
being disabled, it's actually quite a positive thing for me because what I do, serious.
It's like, I, I think of like, like the, like I think of like the perfect disability to
get.
And it's kind of like a, a lazy stupid like thing like, oh, when you're disabled, people
do things for you.
So if I was disabled in this specific way, but I could still like, you know, uh, like,
uh, play guitar or something, but I had no speech abilities, then people wouldn't like
make, wouldn't blame me for not talking.
They'll be like, oh, we can't talk.
So that's fine.
But then you wouldn't be able to be on the podcast though.
That's true.
Yeah.
Like, like the more overtly disabled you are, the more, uh, I can get away.
I can get away with, uh, that I wouldn't normally just do.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Speaking about that sort of like disabilities, I saw, I saw like, um, this channel just randomly
got recommended like a video, uh, of this, like, um, I think she's British and she is
deaf.
And but like, she speaks very eloquently and she, in that video, she explained how it's
kind of tough when people don't believe her that she's deaf because she speaks so well
and she doesn't have that sort of, uh, deaf person's, the way they speak.
Yeah.
The, the being deaf is the worst because you can't, if you're blind, you have the sunglasses
and people like, oh, let me help you.
But like if you're deaf, people say, Hey, I'm, you're not, you're not hear me, motherfucker.
I'll push you.
And then you do wrecked.
Hippo.
I want to do Chibi Bakas Khan, like our machine will come, but Chibi Bakas Khan, we should
do that.
We'll get to London.
And we'll throw an anime convention.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I'll just call the London.
I'll sort it out.
We'll take over the city of London and not to be fused with London.
We'll take over all that and we'll turn into the city of animals.
I'm so glad that Manchi knows the difference.
Yeah.
Well, we've all seen that incredibly popular CGP creative video.
I don't actually have any real knowledge.
I've just been, I'm just encouraging when I've seen the YouTube videos.
I just want to go on record saying I only just figured out that CGP Kray, CGP Kray is
not one of the green brothers, that he is not like those guys.
Oh my God.
Whoa.
And now I understand why you thought he was gay.
Now I understand.
I just, I thought that was like the main channel of like one of the green brothers or something.
You're insane.
I don't know why you don't.
They have, they have made, they have their own main channels.
I know.
I don't, I don't know.
I just thought they were the same guy or something.
Well, that's, that's pretty unbelievable.
The good news is now my opinion of the green brothers has tanked in my opinion of this
new entity that is CGP Kray has surged sky high.
Because neither of, neither of them is like, doesn't he, well, CGP Kray doesn't show his
face at all.
So like, no, no, they're all American.
I remember when the green brothers were like harmless and made like some wholesome content
and now they go into this.
What do they do now?
Well, they're just kind of like corporate titans.
No, no, yeah.
They haven't done anything wrong.
They're just shills and hacks.
Well, they're, they're, they, they make antifa vlogs now.
When you get to a certain level, you know what you say?
When you get to a certain level of like notoriety or power or social influence, which they have
socially okay to hate you for some reason.
I mean, that's basically true.
That's true.
Back when I actually watched them, which was like forever ago, all they did, the only
content they sort of produced were like these little sort of vlog things.
And like the each, each video, they would start as like, Hey, Hank, today's, this is
the date.
And yeah, it was really cute.
I watched.
It was really cute.
I fell down that rabbit hole.
I remember the vlog.
I bet they, I bet they, I bet they got into that habit when they woke up in the same bed
looking at each other lovingly, gazing into each other's eyes, say, good morning, Hank.
Today I blah, blah, blah.
Good morning.
I need to see a video from you every day.
Yeah, exactly.
I'll miss you forever.
Gay.
Very gay.
The only, only content of theirs I've actually watched was Crash Course when I was like
11.
And I was too stupid to realize that it was literally extra credits to you and not actually
to you.
Uh, sure.
I, I like, I like Crash Course literature.
Some of it's not bad.
I've seen a couple of those, but, but, but I've just opposed the idea of brothers staying
in contact.
It's very gay.
It's extremely problematic.
I hate that shit.
I'm opposed to it.
I am kind of surprised.
I'm kind of surprised to feel this, uh, this anti-vlogbrothers sentiment bubbling under
the surface in this conversation because I, I, I, I've never seen a, a, a frog brother.
I've never seen a single one of those videos.
I don't, don't, don't forget to be awesome gamers, but I don't care for them anymore.
I have fond memories of Crash Course.
I remember liking it a lot, but, but, but it wasn't very, you know, I have fond memories
of the, of the Kids WB show Crash Test Dummies, if you recall that.
But there in lies the quandary.
When you're a little kid, it's hard to pick out to tell, like when people want you to
believe something that's hard to tell when you're being brainwashed.
So I couldn't, I couldn't tell that I was being brainwashed when, when I watched Crash
Course, but now, but now when I'm a big boy, I can.
There's a little bit of that, I guess.
I don't know.
Well, I mean, they, they're saying things they want you to believe, which are, may or
may not be 100% true.
They have their own skew.
Well, that's just, well, that's just education.
And I'm suspicious of all educators as I am of everyone.
And like everyone has an agenda in the world, but it's people with power who have the ability
to, to exercise.
Uh, not Asian people.
They also, during, during a later one, during a thing that I was like past nine, I went
like after I got off the boat, they, they did an entire series or on the foundation
that, uh, guns, germs and steel was racist because it specifically, um, yeah, yeah.
When, when, when gun germs and steel is the opposite of racist and is proving that racism
is.
See, that's the thing.
What is guns, germs and steel?
A book.
Have you ever heard of chug guns, germs and steel?
It's an extremely famous and influential book.
Like on, yeah, yeah, book.
I literally never heard of it.
It is the most famous book of all time.
Well, not to me.
So fuck you.
Summarize it, Monchi.
What's it about?
Just in summary.
It's the, uh, the CGP gravy on the, uh, uh, America pop.
The spread of disease.
Yes.
It is that.
Okay.
It's talking about, it's talking about how the, the map, uh, matters more than the players.
I see.
Oh, right.
Okay.
Right.
I'm with you.
Well, I mean, let's, I mean, people were pretty racist in the time when America was
like settled.
I mean, I'm sure that's true.
No, no.
That seems reasonable.
They were talking about how saying that the map matters is racist when that is the
same.
That's extremely retarded.
What?
That's the way to be not racist.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
I mean, any, any of this stuff that's like equipped, like this SJWS kind of like, uh,
you know, he's never apologized.
Okay.
This idea that like every human being is like exactly the same in every way, except for
like the environment you're born into is pretty ridiculous.
Like there's cultural differences.
There are genetic differences.
No.
There's all this shit.
So their ability to create things, to have large scale civilizations is dependent upon
the animals and the geography in which you are looking.
Which seems reasonable.
Yeah.
That seems reasonable.
Uh, okay.
To be completely transparent here, it was John Green who was writing for one of the teachers
who delivered this and John Green, the writer has later apologized for this because it
was factually inaccurate.
Oh, wait.
He did apologize for saying.
Yeah, he did.
He did.
So.
Oh.
He's not a bad guy.
Those are the sorts of things I think that have piled up to give them something of a
negative aura, at least in my sphere.
I honestly, I know very little about them.
I know they run VidCon.
And I'm glad that, you know, I'm glad even though I'll make fun of extra credits, I'll
make fun of them.
They started VidCon.
They're being literally retarded.
Um, I'm happy that kids in any way are getting, you know, into history and stuff like that.
So I'm happy that they have.
That is a good thing.
Even like popcorn renditions and stuff.
I'm happy.
Popcorn short renditions and stuff.
Gotta call them out though.
The Green Brothers did not chastise Anita Sarkeesian when she called out Sargon in her audience
for being, what was it, a garbage human, for lambasting a member of her crowd.
And that's like the last update I remember.
Calling out the Green Brothers for not actually being green aliens.
They're shitty gray aliens, way more boring.
I cannot fucking believe how important Anita Sarkeesian is.
She's a totem.
She's a totem of feminism is what she is.
She is a totem.
She's this weird symbol and like how you feel about Anita Sarkeesian determines what tribe
you belong to.
It's all in reference to Anita Sarkeesian.
Do you like Anita Sarkeesian or do you hate Anita Sarkeesian?
Fucking red or blue motherfucker.
What if I like the first half of her name and the second half I'm not so fond of?
Wait, what if I spit right down in my mouth?
Yeah, that's the only solution.
The boy shall be cut in half and each pundit side will receive the part.
You know that contest we did like a month or two ago, whatever happened with that?
Shall we get into it, team?
Yay!
Is it time?
Wait, wait, but I have things I want to talk about.
What the boy speak?
Yeah, let's let Ben say his thing.
Well, don't worry.
Say your piece.
Well, I had two topics I wanted to bring up.
The first is the keto is going good and I'm 10 pounds down from what I was at my heaviest
a couple months ago.
And I just, but I'm upset because I don't see enough keto representation in media.
Speaking of Anita.
Yeah.
And I'm just wondering, like, when is Marvel going to have a keto superhero?
Damn it, you're right.
And I'm really hoping that by 2028 we can have it for our first keto president.
Because keto kids growing up today need role models just like anyone else, you know?
The only role model that is worth anything is the president.
That's true.
If you're not the president, you can't influence anything.
And Marvel superheroes, not DC, because DC makes bad movies and movies are what's important
now.
I agree.
I have been told this.
I am a sheep.
Listen to my YouTube reviews.
Keto.
I'm trying to think.
Who's a superhero who might be like closet keto?
You know, like, who is keto, but doesn't make a big stink?
Popeye.
Deadpool.
No, he's eating spinach.
That's got carbs.
I don't know what keto is.
No, spinach is totally keto safe.
Oh, really?
Okay.
Yeah.
It is.
Luffy is definitely keto.
That's definitely true.
Yeah.
Oh, hell yeah.
Someone's trying to get my attention.
Someone's trying to stop me.
No?
No.
Can I imagine it?
No, it's just funny.
Deadpool.
And if you're Deadpool, then we might have to have a discussion behind the stage here.
Okay.
So I guess Luffy is a pretty good keto hero.
All right.
That's not bad.
And let us know in the comments if there's any more great keto heroes out there so that
I can have my kids have role models.
Finally.
What's that diet that you eat?
A paleo.
Luffy is also probably paleo representation.
Oh, he's definitely paleo.
Yeah.
Steno.
Shout out to you.
Paleo, it's like the caveman diet, literally.
Oh, yeah.
Paleo is Steno.
Luffy just kills animals and then roast them over fires and eats them.
Is this what you're talking about here, keto?
Keto?
Oh, this is the Shinigami magic used for binding off attack.
Keto demon magic spells used in the bleach universe by Shinigami.
Yes.
Related.
Pretty good.
The other, okay.
And the other thing, I want to talk about, okay, I don't want to say whose video it was
because this is not a person that I have any ill will towards or want to shit on in specific.
Uh-huh.
But do you remember that video?
It was by a certain Brony analyst and it was the Me Too video calling out a tune critic?
Yes.
I mean, I remember the idea in general.
Okay, okay.
To give context for this, this was amazing.
To give context, there was this guy tune critic who was kind of a sort of respected member
of the Brony analysis community.
Me and Munchy, we talked about him a little bit in The Rowdy Fuckers.
That was before this news story broke.
He was involved in some shady, some pervy stuff.
It was a huge bit of pedophile stuff.
He was being a pedophile, that's, I don't want to talk about the specifics of that because
I will get the details wrong.
Right.
I don't know what the exact...
I think it was that he was grooming somebody, but that's...
He got in trouble.
And now everyone hates, everyone denounced him, everyone was like, oh god, we gotta, everyone
made videos being like the truth about tune critic, like, you know, no more tune critic,
tune critic's out of here, we don't want anything to do with him anymore, fair enough.
And then not to, a couple, it was a couple months ago, this one guy, he makes a video
that's like, it's like a, he unironically calls it like a Me Too, like a hashtag Me
Too video.
Was this Deadpool?
Yeah.
I wasn't going to fucking say it.
God damn it.
We'll cut that out.
Because it's embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
Whatever.
I mean, I don't actually care that much.
I mean, you're the bad guy now, not me.
Well, whoops.
Okay.
We will cut that out.
Right.
Whatever.
Yeah.
Okay.
So the video was, he introduces it that like, okay, so tune critic abused my girlfriend
and then he's like, and now I'm going to let her tell the story and she comes on and
she tells the story about what happened and I'm going to condense it here.
But what happened with her is that while she was with so-and-so, this person making the
video.
And these are from her own words.
These are her important.
Yes.
While she was with him.
Okay.
Tune critic hits on her online.
She goes along with it.
They, they like have, she, I think he like shows him her dick or something online.
She lets him do it.
She says, yes.
Let's her do that.
Okay.
Feels guilty about it later, tells him to tell the guy whose video this is and he doesn't
do it and she doesn't do it either until much, much later.
And this apparently is, is the me too that like, oh, my girlfriend was also victimized.
Oh my God.
Like, no.
He, he propositioned her and she accepted.
You motherfucker.
Like, I'm sorry.
This conflation of completely consensual, like willing sexual acts with like sexual
abuse, this, this is what they mean when they say me too going too far.
Tune, yeah.
Tune critic might be a pedophile and a rapist and tune critic might be the worst abuser in
the world, but this is not, that's not what this is.
Okay.
No.
Yeah.
I was just throwing that out as something he might, he could have done any number of
things.
Indeed.
He could be the worst person in the world, but this is not, this is not that.
And it's like, I don't know.
I think I got upset, I got kind of upset watching this video and then, and I finished it up
and I was like, okay.
So clearly the guy released in this video, he's doing what he wants.
He wants to believe.
He wants to blame what happened on tune critic being a monster.
He does not want to hold his girlfriend accountable.
I mean, because that would be something that he would probably have to deal with.
And I'm sure he wants to put the blame externally to her, everyone was in support of her and
saying, we're sorry this happened to you, we're so sorry you had to deal with that.
He's a terrible, yes, everyone, everyone.
Am I, am I confused here?
Cause I've heard a little bit of this up to this point, but it's, am I wrong to say
that this girl clearly cheated on her boyfriend and is now using some sort of me to defense
to say it was not her fault.
Sounds good.
What's going on here?
I feel like what it was, is that she cheated like by like, uh, acquiescing to tune critics
like sexual like advances and just like, okay, I'll show you me and you show you, you
like, she was into that, but then she felt guilty, but didn't do anything about it until
it was okay to shit on tune critic publicly.
That's how it feels.
How long ago was this?
That's curious.
I don't know the timeline.
I don't think she was specific enough about the timeline, but how it feels to me is that
she admitted to this after tune critic was a bad guy and it was okay.
I don't know if that's true, but that'd be damning.
That'd be quite damning.
I mean, this already sounds quite damning.
I mean, what is there even a debate here?
Like, is the argument, is the argument here?
Other than maybe going behind his friend's back, like going behind his friend's back
and hitting on his girlfriend, not cool.
No, not at all.
Other than that, in this situation, he did nothing wrong.
I don't understand.
I don't understand what is being implied here, uh, because this person, and that's not me
saying tune critic did nothing wrong in general in this situation.
I mean, I don't understand this.
This is very strange.
He has not done any, like, malicious action, but you're right, it is not cool of him to
have done this.
It is not good.
No, it wasn't cool.
It's just so fucked up to...
But it's less cool on her part.
Like, she was the one who was, you know...
He did ask her, like, from the sound of it.
He did ask her first.
Yeah.
He shouldn't have.
Yeah, like, this was consensual.
If she wasn't comfortable, that was her chance.
By her own words.
Say no.
I'm not saying that there's...
I don't even want to assign the amount, because I say there's equal or no blame.
I'm just trying to say that he should not have asked in the first place, and that in
itself is a bad action that should have been.
Well, no.
Sure, yeah.
And that wasn't cool.
It was a bad thing to do, to go behind your friend's back and proposition their girlfriend,
obviously.
It is a totally separate, also bad thing...
But it's not abuse.
No, it's not abuse at all.
Not even a little bit.
It's not abuse.
Which is what is being claimed in the video.
And it is a totally separate bad thing.
Is that she was abused and victimized by them.
Okay, these people are children and they can't be trusted to reliably relay facts or anything.
Look, is the argument here, is this the argument going on here, that TuneCriticY2K had so much
power in this situation?
He was such a villain.
TuneCritic fucking Y2K was the most powerful force who has ever sexually propositioned
her, and she couldn't say no.
Because what, it threatened her livelihood?
No.
Harvey Weinstein would come up to you and either forcibly rape you or be like, look,
you gotta fuck me, or like, you ain't moving up in this world, I control Hollywood, you
gotta do what I say.
And like, that's evil and fucked up.
What could he even possibly hold over her?
I don't understand.
I don't think so.
Nothing.
Literally nothing.
There was no solution at all.
Look, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You made the decision to cheat on your boyfriend and you felt bad about it, but maybe don't
do that next time.
If you spend all your fucking time rationalizing how it wasn't your fault that you made this
choice, what happened to actual feminism?
Taking responsibility for your own life choices?
Why are you now saying that men are the ones who dictate how you act every second of every
fucking day?
Be a goddamn adult, you fucking coward.
This pisses me off so much.
God, stop hiding behind a movement that has nothing to do with you.
I feel, God.
I understood the motivations of the guy making the video and the girl.
I understood why they would both want to believe this.
Indeed.
But seeing the comments coming out in full support, it was just that brony hug box bullshit
mentality.
There's nothing worse.
This is where the brony hug box turns malignant.
Yeah, yeah.
Turns a little scary, honestly.
The fact that, I don't know, let's say it was a guy who-
That someone can come out with a me too story and then tell it and it's clearly bullshit.
Yeah.
Not even someone claiming, oh, I bet you're lying.
It's not even that I bet you're lying.
It's that she is clearly wrong.
She's telling the story and it is not lining up.
What if this same story was just told about some guy who just had also not been accused
of being a pedophile and then this equally flippant story that has obviously no validity
to it is just made up about someone who had, yeah, maybe he consensually tried to hook
up with his friend's girlfriend that is not the same as sexual assault.
This is not a me too moment.
Any of this shit.
In this case, I mean, I'm sure that in this, the hashtag me too is just, it makes it like
so farcical.
Yeah.
The whole thing.
Yeah, farcical is the word.
I mean, in this case, you know, everyone was really eager.
Everyone's really eager to shit on Toon.
That's what it is.
To dump on Toon to show that they too hate him and what he has done.
Yeah.
That they too are on the right side of history.
This is just an extension.
Even though it really does nothing to do with them.
No.
They want to, they want to, they want to perform that, that action.
This is an extension of our fucked up political landscape and how like we just, people are
not being, people are not having integrity with the way they address with the stuff.
Imagine you go into those comments section and you say your story kind of sounds dumb.
You're going to be called like a rape enabler or something.
You're going to be, you're going to be your rape apologist because you're defending Toon
critic.
This is where we're at.
It's so fucked up.
How do we selectively pick and choose like what we like about what like our political
opponents are saying and then like, and like, like with, like with James Gunn and like his
political shit recently about, he made like some really fucked up jokes in the past or
whatever.
That's so terrible.
It's so scary.
I mean, I don't give any fucks that he did that.
And I mean, I don't care.
I'm, I'm not on either side of this fight, but like the left was just like trying to
excuse it.
Like imagine it was like any right wing guy, like you just know they would use this to
like destroy their career even more vociferously than was done by the opposite side of James
Gunn.
We just have to have integrity here.
And I know like literally no one can because we all have massive biases and everything,
but it's an ideal to strive for.
It's a whatever it's a platonic ideal to work towards.
I don't know if you guys were aware of this, but that whole scandal happened before the
episode that we recorded that was recorded earlier, in which I talk about like, like
writing for office and about how like, oh, I'm a friend, like, like, like stuff that
I've said, like when I was like a baby or like now will be dug up like three years down
the line.
And it was like, oh, that's ridiculous.
Like what you're saying right now at this very moment.
Yeah.
And then like, and then meanwhile, James Gunn, there he goes.
I mean, in a different sort of way.
I mean, Alex Jones is doing the stuff that they don't like right now.
You know, I saw a tweet that was like, okay, oh God, I'm going to forget the details.
They don't really matter.
I think it was like the Washington Post or someone hired this woman.
Oh, yeah, I know this one.
This agent.
Sarah Jong or something.
Yeah.
And she had made tweets like, yeah, like, like, you know, saying really shitty things
about like white men and men in general and white people and like really being a,
you know, kind of saying some racist shit about white people and like fuck white people.
And she defended herself as saying like, like she was saying all these things in response
to, you know, in response to abuse from other people that were being racist to her, which
I'm just might be true that I can believe that.
But yeah, I think, I don't know, like, I understand that like obviously the Washington
Post and Disney are not the same entity and we can't call it hypocrisy for one to fire
James Gunn while the other hires whatever.
Are you aware of the, the extension of that story about what happened later on based on
those tweets?
No.
Okay.
Most people, I bet people have heard of this, but, but like a couple people specifically
Candace Owens, what Candace Owens, who is, she is a conservative, she's a black lady
and she, she was like, she took the exact tweets of Sarah Jong and she replaced white
with like Jew and she got banned on Twitter for like intentionally replacing the exact
words with like anti-Semitic shit.
And by the way, and her tweet included like, it's like, it literally replaced her quotes
with racist shit against Jews and it said at the bottom like, this is what it looks
like if you like do this at Sarah Jong or whatever, it like, this is why you shouldn't
do that.
And for that tweet, like she got banned for like, and they restored it later once the
outcry happened.
But like, wow.
Wow, guys.
Yeah.
I mean, like, like, this is the problem, man.
Can they move on?
It's, I mean, you shouldn't say things like that, but you, I don't know, it's not, I feel
like we should be forgiving.
Yeah.
Like James Gunn and probably of her to the problem is you just don't think you should
say anything like that.
Who wants to be forgiving of their enemies, though?
You know, nobody does.
It's a problem.
Like I know she might have said those things out of frustration or anger or, or ingest
or whatever.
I forgive her, I forgive her, but I forgive everybody else who makes like racist kind
of stuff.
I just don't care.
It's fine.
Whatever.
I can kind of understand why like a corporation wouldn't want to tie their wagon to yours
if you are, if you've known, known to have said, you know, things that alienated them.
What's the problem then?
James Gunn making Gardens of the Galaxy like an incredibly successful movie franchise.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
100%.
And guys like Digi.
And like, literally who has read those tweets?
Literally who?
So like, what do they stand to lose?
No one.
They were dug up, they were actually dug up by people on the right wing to like make
him look bad because they wanted to use the, the left's like political execution squad
against the left itself.
So that was kind of what went down.
Yeah.
And it worked.
It's fucked up.
It's bullshit.
It's really fucked up.
Yeah.
Well, it's fucked up, man.
I don't know.
I don't like it.
Yeah.
I think the main problem with all that is like, I just want to one point is that, Munchie,
why are you trying to shut me down?
I was trying to shut you down.
I just want to go out and get to that beach, you know?
I'm, I'm actually, I'm actually done.
Okay.
Is that, is that, um, forgiving people doesn't get you any points, but condemning people
does.
Oh, it does.
That's true.
Yeah.
Like, like these people, like, condemning tune critic for what he did to this poor girl.
Um, that's, that's condemning him for that.
I mean, it's just no currency condemning someone for what they actually did and is confirmed
is great.
And like, if anyone in the world has ever called tune critic a rapist, for example, they
are fucking up bad because that is totally not true.
And the, and the, the conflation and the loose language, I shouldn't have tossed out the
R.
I don't even blame you.
You were doing it.
Casually.
I guess so.
But you know, I guess that, that is part of the larger problem.
I suppose those sorts of things, but you know, I don't know, man, it's all, it's all
fucked up.
We're all going to hell.
Yeah.
And on that note, let's go to the funny fucking.
On that note, let's, let's, let's guys, it's time you've been waiting and we've finally
done it.
What's it been like two months?
Some longer than that.
I think two months in the making.
Yeah.
Around there, around there.
It's time to answer the question of what the hashtag PCP theme is going to be in the
future.
What the hashtag hell is up?
Oh, well guys, I've, I've, I've done it.
I've gone over the numbers.
We've listened to them all.
We reviewed them.
We have all voted and I'll just break it down for you real quick.
How we did it.
We each voted for our top three picks.
The top one got three points.
Our second choice, each of us got two points and the third choice got one point.
Some people only wanted to vote for their number one.
So the numbers aren't exactly, they're not, you know, up to all the numbers being added.
But like that was how it worked.
So given that point system, we're going to run through it here.
And real quick.
We're going to go from top to from bottom to top.
I think what we do is the top three will do separately, but I just want to shout out
like the guys who didn't get in the top three, but still got voted in the thing and went
and were selections.
So let's see what we got here.
We got Felix Box was, was Munchies number one pick.
Did not win tragically, but that, that's in the right.
These are, these are like the honorable mentions.
Alex, A-A-A-L-E-X-X.
That one was beloved by DeVoo, specifically that was the vaporwave one was pretty dope.
The vaporwave cover.
The vaporwave cover of the PCB theme.
Yeah.
That's right.
Both of these are covers of the song that we have right now and that's why I want, that's
why I like them.
They're the one that we have now.
That's why I didn't vote for them.
Because they were, they just were the old song.
Some of them were good.
I didn't, I didn't want it.
I didn't want just a new version of this old song.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Exactly what I did want.
Fair enough.
Our tour, our tour got some votes.
He made a PCB theme as well.
Accelular was voted by a couple of people.
Congrats dog.
Which one was Accelular?
Accelular was, let me see real quick, that was, let me see, I don't want to say who
picks that was.
I hear, let me link it real quick.
It was a fucking, hang on, getting the stupid link.
Come on.
Okay, here we go.
You say you didn't want to say who, it was the voter for him, but.
Ah, right, right, right.
Oh, the voter for the PCB dimension.
That's right, the dimension one.
Yeah, that one.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm going to refrain right now from saying who voted for what.
You mentioned the other ones.
The other ones.
Well, he said, oh, like this one.
No, I did it once and I won't do it again.
You did it like twice.
I said like, I said that Munchie's top pick was the feelings box.
And then you said like someone, they will, they will like the thing as well.
Okay, well, whatever.
I won't do it again.
All right, whatever.
My bad.
Don't do it.
Fine.
Well, okay, whatever.
There was that dope ass rap by Akazi.
Remember that, that rap with all that shit?
Yes.
One of many.
That was dope.
That, yeah, that trap beat, that fucking heavy ass death grips rap.
Yeah.
I really liked that one, but tragically not the winner.
Wings of Strife got a shout out.
That was good.
That one was solid.
That was enjoying.
That was a solid one.
And in our last fucking honorable mention was Oblivion with his meme theme.
Oblivion ball with his meme theme.
Oh, I'm so ready for that to win, god damn it.
The meme theme was good.
The meme theme was really good.
But it was, but it was just a, it was essentially a cover of, through the fire in the flame.
It was like a sick cover with like dope shit.
I guess it is fun.
The only thing that could have been better with that entire theme was to pick a few,
a few more choice memes for me, but you know.
I agree.
But I did really like that one a lot.
That being said, we're actually going to, we're going to play these.
So, so here we go, everybody.
Time to have a listen.
Wait, what are we playing?
I'm going to play for everybody.
Our top three picks.
These are our top three picks.
So are we going from third to first?
Of course.
You always end with the, with the hypest moment.
So our, our, let me get the actual fucking play thing here.
Okay.
So our, our number three, top three with a total of six points, which for, for this contest
was pretty good.
Let me, let me, let me get ready to play it.
All right.
This was Oblivion Falls dream theme.
There it is.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
Yeah.
But I love working.
Sorry, buddy.
You didn't win.
You worked really hard on this.
I think we all loved it.
But it was really good.
It was really good.
I love the cover.
I love the vocals, the audio, the background.
And like he got instruments.
He like worked with artists like sing it and shit.
Yeah.
Again.
Sick as fuck.
Yeah.
But I did not want just a cover of the old song.
You know what?
Let's make me think, oh man, the PCP theme is so great.
Let me go listen to the Procrastinator's theme song that we already have.
Let me go listen to that because that's iconic.
I mean, yeah, but you know, I mean, so was slavery, but we got rid of that too.
You know?
It was truly iconic.
We didn't replace slavery with a different flavor of slavery.
What?
Corporate slavery?
Is that?
Oh.
I said it.
So that was number three.
Okay.
I said it.
All right.
So that was number three.
So oblivion fall.
I don't want you to think that I hope you don't feel slighted.
You worked really hard.
We appreciate your entries.
They were great.
But you get, you get the bronze medal here, buddy.
All right.
Second place.
Moving on.
This one, this one got 10 points across the board.
This one was quite well liked.
I guess there's nothing else to do, but just to say congratulations on your silver medal.
Arkin with the PCP theme entry.
There it is.
Oh, remember this?
Yeah.
I really like this one too.
Oh, there you go.
No.
I wouldn't spoil it today.
That sentencing.
Cooper.
There you go.
Blaming his near moral perception.
This one is really good.
I would have been, I would have been happy to have this one as the theme.
Me too.
Oh, let's see.
Here it comes.
PCP.
Oh man.
This one's cool.
PCP.
This drug is not a play thing.
It's not a beer.
It's not a marijuana cigarette.
This is something so mind-altering that it will make you accountable or base.
Man, that's so good.
Oh, it was really, really good.
I love it so much.
I'm just going to use that when I edit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can't blame you.
You should use it for stuff.
I mean, we've got the rights to all of them.
They sold off their souls.
We've got them now, baby.
Arkin, congrats on the silver medal.
That was great.
I already know what that next one's going to be.
I already know.
Well, smarty pants.
Maybe you don't know.
Maybe it's going to be, shut up.
So anyway, here's guys.
Here it is.
The moment we've all been waiting for.
The number one winner with a total of 17 points.
Jesus Christ.
17.
This one really took the cake.
This one really surged ahead.
It was a lot of people's top pick.
Jesus.
Sasuke Zero Pro.
Congratulations, buddy.
Yeah.
The new PCP theme.
Here it is.
Oh, yeah.
What is this?
You're supposed to be working right now.
I'm sorry, darling.
I'm listening to the PCP right now.
It's so interesting.
Oh, there it is.
Guys, play this for your wife when she comes home from a hard day of work.
Forgot to pick up the laundry.
Forgot to do the taxes.
Forgot to pleasure you for the last 10 months of your relationship.
But she did remember to listen to the PCP.
And you know what?
God bless her for that.
And that's why I'm a feminist.
That's good dinner conversation right there, boy.
Damn right it is.
Sasuke Zero Pro or Sasuke Pro.
Congratulations, buddy.
Congratulations.
You are the gold medal winner.
I'm happy.
Hold on.
Congratulations to the guy.
It's awesome.
But I just realized sort of like, I'm not sure if you mentioned the honorable mentions
of, or I might have missed someone, Eric C. Bass?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I totally did miss him.
I missed him.
Eric C. Bass or Bass or whatever.
Yes, you were not able to mention two.
Really sorry I forgot you, buddy.
We liked your multiple versions.
Can I shout out a couple of the other ones?
Absolutely.
Guys, go nuts.
If you want to shout out stuff you like, now's the time.
I want to particularly shout out Zero Alias' Chip Tune.
It had a really great beat that I think would have made a great theme song.
It gives me the chills when it gets that drop.
That one, yeah, I feel like that's one of the ones that I'm sad that we had to pick
one.
And the Garbage Burners' Hypus theme was fucking sick.
I did like that one, yeah.
Yeah, that was another one.
I only voted for ones that had lyrics, right?
And that was one that had good lyrics.
I really like this one that I feel has gotten unmentioned by all of you guys.
I feel it's this really underground theme.
This name guy, this guy called Endless Jest, and he's made this really nice mellow
edition of the theme that I really enjoy.
I'm really sad that didn't get picked.
Well, you know, he's dead now.
That's how it goes.
I kind of like-
How old and with the new?
I got to say, I like the winner here by Sasuke Pro here.
I like that it incorporates the old.
Yeah, I feel like it's like that plus.
It's not a cover, but it's got-
It's not a marijuana, it's not a cigarette, it's not a beer.
Oh, man, that's good stuff.
That was a different song.
Well, yeah, that's Arkin's.
That's Arkin's.
The silver Midwest.
Smash up the two of them.
Am I allowed to critique the winner?
If you feel to ruin his good day, absolutely.
Because I didn't like it the whole time, and I-
What?
There was something about the female voice.
No, okay, I like that part.
It's funny.
Yeah, it sounds weird, but it's funny.
I mean, yeah, he sounds like he's got a shitty non-English voice or something,
and he's trying to do it.
A shitty non-English voice.
He's got an accent or something.
No, it doesn't sound like an accent.
It just kind of sounds like he's half-assing a female voice.
I'm listening to the BCB right now.
But it's funny.
I like it.
Yeah, I like it.
I mean, kick and scream all you want, but...
I mean, the majority of us voted for this one.
I'm surprised that I didn't vote for it at all.
No, you didn't.
That's true.
Yeah, because I didn't mean that I voted on it.
I mean, if you guys won, I'll break down the demographics of the winner here.
That was my top pick.
I'll put it out there.
Everyone picked this as their top pick.
Davoo put it as a second choice, and then Gib, Mage, and Munchy just didn't vote for it at all.
So there's a pretty harsh divide here on liking this or not.
My picks were...
Yeah, that was my top pick.
Arkin was my number two, and then...
Oh, God, it was the Wings of Strike was my number three.
Gib, I don't...
If you just fucking use the song you want when you edit, I don't care.
It's fine.
That's true.
We can't force you.
Nope.
Can't do it.
I guess we could.
Don't be my calling card using the other one.
Yeah.
I mean, that sounds fine.
No offense.
I actually do, like, enjoy everything aside from the female voice in that intro.
So I'm not, like, aghast.
I think that we should use the other songs as outros.
I mean, I like that idea personally.
We'll talk about that.
Yeah, we talked about this yesterday.
At the real one.
We're going to literally get rid of it.
Is that what you're saying?
Why not?
Who cares?
But I mean, that's been incorporated into the new winner.
Look, it doesn't matter.
We'll talk about exactly how we're going to work this out later.
We have a winner, guys.
Let your voice be known, people, because I know that you won't want this.
Let your voice be known.
If you say so, buddy.
I mean, it won't be gone.
It won't be gone.
But, like, whatever.
I-
Guys, it's in the new song.
You guys are pissing off a little bit.
I'll be straight with you.
I'm getting a little annoyed.
Look, we've got over 100 episodes where we use the old theme.
It's not going anywhere.
We've got it.
It's in the annals of history.
It's here.
It's even in the goddamn new theme song.
Get excited.
This is good.
I like it.
I'm happy.
I love it.
Can't you hear the happiness in my voice?
We've got all these-
We've got, like, the arcan one and zero alias.
And we've got all these other ones that, like, we could use as outros.
And they're all great, and they're fan works, and they're made, you know, for the glory of
the PCP.
And we have thusly been glorified.
Indeed.
And I love it.
Bitch.
By the way, I do love arcans a lot.
Like, the thing is for me, like, arcans was my second choice.
And I'm-
Like, I would have been happy with either one, frankly.
But, uh, yeah.
Whatever.
There's a few I would have been.
Probably like five or six that I would have been happy with.
Yeah, me too.
Me too.
But guys, let me just say.
Let me just say, this has been a tremendously positive experience.
Doing the PCB theme contest.
It's been awesome.
Yeah.
I'm so happy that everybody came out and made dope shit and gave us it for free to use
however we want.
Love that.
Just love that fact.
I love the contest.
I've been going over a great and RFCK world, and I love them.
Dude, contests are the future.
Wow.
The contest stat, because people love getting involved, and let's do them the favor and
let them get involved.
Yeah.
Feature film.
Somebody make a feature film of the progress news.
It has to be feature length.
Oh my god.
You know what?
This is-
It has to be released in theaters.
Yes.
Don't call, don't, don't add us until it's in theaters.
This is, this is a bit of an aside.
This is no longer about the theme.
Guys, www.speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail is now live.
It is active, and you can leave us voicemails at that.
We'll put a link in the description.
Speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail.
We'll take your goddamn audio and listen to it.
And we will listen to it on, I mean not all of them, right?
We'll know.
We'll weed out the shit ones, and we'll get the good ones.
We'll listen to it on the show, and we will respond to it if you, if we feel like.
Yeah.
That's how it's going to be.
So leave them, and hopefully when you hear this they'll be like a day or two.
I'm sure we'll get a bunch.
Like when this episode goes up.
So probably by like next Sunday when we record, we'll have like a couple to look through.
Yeah.
Do it guys.
Fucking give us the voicemails.
You've been asking for it.
We live to serve.
And here we are giving you what you want.
Now head on over to www.patreon.com slash the procrastinators to show your support.
Yeah.
That's what you need to do, friends.
All right.
Well that being said, I think it's time to remember that I forgot to ask for questions
on Twitter before we started recording.
Everybody quick, quick, quick.
Somebody go to the goddamn thing, the patron lounge.
It's okay.
I'm going to get old questions.
Everyone stall for time.
Stall for time.
Uh-oh.
We don't have a charismatic thing to say.
We have no charisma at all.
We have no personality.
We're going to get questions real quick.
I got the...let me talk about...I got really drunk last night.
Oh yeah?
How'd that go?
I went out to a party.
Crack came too.
And I went out and I bought...they were drinking Yingling, which is not keto, because they
were a bunch of filthy glucose brands.
Oh, God.
So I went and I got Michalab Ultra, just 2.6 grams of carbs per bottle, drank the entire
pack, passed out on the sofa.
And it was, you know, it was fine.
That's good.
Whatever.
That's my story.
Not bad.
And I'm sticking to it.
What was the nature of this party?
Was this a friends party?
It was a bunch...it was a guy...a guy who I knew in college, who was like friends of
a bunch of my other friends from college that I'm still on good terms with.
He was at his place and it was...oh, it was our other friend who we hadn't seen...he
was in town.
So we were just like, why don't we all get together because this other guy who we haven't
seen for years is coming to visit.
And we did and we played Clankers and, you know, you know how that goes.
I want to give a shout out right now to Mazele Finneken and C. Geddesi, or I've pronounced
that, for being the worst PCP fans of all time.
Wait, what?
What's going on?
Who?
And going out for being late and asking questions.
I want...you now have the official title of the worst PCP fans.
How dare they ask questions.
And they were asked to ask questions.
You're not asking questions, they're just saying, come on guys, come on, several people.
Yeah, oh, several people are typing, but they're all like, oh, why are you so late?
Haha.
Yeah, that is bad.
I hate it.
He's got to be destroyed.
Oh, here's something that's relevant to earlier discussions.
For those of you planning on having children one day, what are your biggest fears when
thinking about being a parent, that they are disabled?
Being a parent.
Being disabled and I have to live with them.
How I'm going to be able to teach them effectively, because there's no way to guarantee the ways
I have been taught will be effective on the people that I produce.
So there's no way of knowing how I'll be able to affect my child and I'll just have to do
my best and inevitably fail.
I can't stand being around another person to the extent that I would need to if I had
a child, to the extent that I would need to be around them.
I'm still on the fence and wondering how I want to have a child, so I don't know.
It's understandable.
It will also be trying to regulate the internet in a non-obtrusive way and in a fair and balanced
way that my child will be able to understand and appreciate and not just hate before, which
will be impossible.
Yeah.
I feel like I think I've said this before, but there's only so much you can do when it
comes to the new generation being weird and doesn't make any sense.
All these things I was thinking my whole life, I'm going to teach my kids the ways of the
world, but the world changed by the time I was having kids, so now I don't have any information
on it.
You'll never understand your kids.
You'll never understand the things they like.
All you can do is be generically cool in things that are always good, just being someone that
is playing guitar and cooking.
Yeah.
Or social interaction, being a good party host.
If you're a good party host, you bring people around.
Yes, be my dad.
By the way, I want to shout out Hippo's dad and Kaz's dad for being the best two dads
I've ever seen.
They're actually quite similar.
They are like reg universe from Steven Universe, and that's why I like them.
Have you seen my dad?
No.
But I know him.
I know him.
I know all day, intrinsically.
I just lower my head.
I put my ear to the ground.
Did you steal my dad as if it was easy?
No.
My biggest fear about having kids is that my dad would always say when I was growing up.
He would always say that I don't really care what you do, but I want you to be successful
and content doing it, whatever it is.
I don't really care what my kids do, but it torments me every day and night that they
will just be lazy and stupid and not be willing to put an effort to achieve whatever their
goals are.
And then they will become whiny bitches about how it's everyone else's fault when, meanwhile,
I'm staying on the side observing them continually fuck up everything by not putting in enough
work.
That is my biggest fear.
I feel like if you show this attitude towards them, I need you to be not lazy.
Don't be lazy.
Then they're just going to do that because that's what they do.
Those are the pitfalls I'm interested in avoiding.
Whatever the mechanics are involved in making sure that my children are not lazy sacks of
shit, that's what I want to do.
If that includes me never bringing it up, then I will do so.
Whatever that is, I want to do it because I don't want my kids to be fat waste of space.
Here's the thing.
There's a gang you don't want your child to be in.
There's just a generic street gang.
You're fucked no matter what you do.
You can't say, don't join this gang because your kid will be like, huh?
Yeah, you're just fucked.
And you can't say nothing because then your kid will be like, I like this gang.
I'm going to join it.
So literally, no matter what you do, you just have to be transparent with your kid.
The main thing with children is you just have to explain why you have rules.
Explain why you are limiting them in whatever way.
And try and be open and understanding of their wants and needs.
And it's really hard.
And it's hard when your kid wants to play with knives.
They just got to let them stab himself and he'll learn.
Though, you know, I've watched a lot of anime that has taught me that, like,
just putting rules in place and making broad statements
without explaining the motivation or why I'm saying them always works out well
and does not cause any misunderstandings or problems.
So that's what I'm going to do, probably.
Yeah.
Fucking...
You also don't want a child to just be obedient because then they have no drive.
Yeah.
They have no personality.
If they just do what you want, like, that's the worst scenario.
Yeah.
Where, like, you're not rebellious enough.
Like, I feel like I was never rebellious enough.
And I'm like, ah, that's why I'm a piece of shit.
That's why I make game reviews on YouTube.
The only reason, the only reason I would want to censor the internet in any way
is not to, like, limit my kid's options so that he's like how I am.
I just want...
I've made mistakes in my past and so I don't want to inflict the pain that I felt onto my child.
And so I want to be able to, like, warp zone, like, one, two, skip that pain of life.
But I think at the end, like, you can't avoid it.
Like, no matter what you do, even if you, like, hide for infinity or anything,
your kid will still turn out to be a sexual degenerate no matter what you do.
So why even try?
No, no.
Why even try and make him hate you?
Why would you make him hate you if you don't?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to...
Speaking of that, I've got a question here.
Which fandom, by Rusty, which fandom has the best quality porn?
And I asked this because...
Oh.
But, like...
Is that true?
UCP.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Fucking...
I've always been annoyed that the things that I was a fan of when I was a kid
don't have any good porn because they're so old that all the artists didn't exist.
And now if, like, if anything exists, if a game is released,
there is, like, 10 trillion...
Yeah.
...terabytes of porn, like, in seconds by really good artists.
Dude.
And it makes me sad.
Oh, do you guys remember Queen Chrysalis?
It makes me annoyed that they're just, like...
I have, like, five images of Florina from Fire Emblem.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's all.
And they're, like, pencil drawings scanned in, like, terrible drawings.
But that's all I have.
Do you guys remember Queen Chrysalis and how there was...
There was, like, a porn of her before the episode was over?
No.
But I could believe it.
I can believe it.
I always remember that.
Before the episode was over.
That's dope.
I do love that about, like, that's, like, what Twitter is great for.
What was the question?
I totally forgot.
What fandom has this stupid question?
Oh, that's right.
I just wanted to say that thing related to it.
Okay, yeah.
Let's just move on.
I don't think anybody cares.
Here's a question from...
This is a pity question from the Twitter.
From atitsyaboy2 asks,
I'm a male on the prowl for some female action.
While my personality is obviously a 10, I still look 14.
What should I do?
Meet women who also look young for their age, date an actual 14-year-old JK,
or stick to my 2D girls?
Any other suggestions are appreciated.
Wait, what were the three options presented?
Okay, well, most of those were jokes.
He's like, should I date a girl who also looks young?
I don't know.
That's not a solution.
I don't know what he's talking about.
That's really bizarre.
I don't understand what the problem is.
It's like he's framing this like, guys, there's this societal impetus
to date people who look your age.
This is such a problem for me, but no.
I would assume that he's saying that he's 14
because 14-year-old guys are not particularly attractive.
I would assume that's the issue.
You just gotta do what everyone else does,
which is cast your net around for a girl who is into what you look like.
Indeed.
That's really all there is to say.
There you go.
That's it.
I want to give hope now to all those freaks out there.
Chat them up.
Because no matter how disgusting or generous you are,
I guarantee you there are a ton of women or gay guys
if you want to turn gay who will be into you,
no matter how gross and disgusting you are.
I know none of you are gay now,
but if you're thinking about it, it's always an option.
That is too real.
Yeah.
Because I've only ever gotten attention from gay men.
And it annoys me quite a bit.
It'd be so easy.
Yeah, it's annoying.
It's annoying to get, for a beta male like me,
desperate for the affections of women,
it's very irritating when a man likes you
because it's like, well, this isn't what I wanted.
It means I'm attractive, but the wrong kind.
I'm like, well, what am I going to do now?
Do I have to shave my head off?
Do I have to do that?
Oh, wait.
Here's a meme question.
Not really, but it's at Imperial Denasty asks,
are you guys ever going to make a cover of the PCP theme?
Oh, well, we outsourced that project.
That didn't be Dana.
All right, just saying.
What else we got?
Here's a question.
What's one bad purchase decision that still haunts you still?
When I was like 11, I spent all of my $100 I got for my birthday.
I spent it all on webkits, and I got four webkits.
I'll never forget myself.
I remember you talking about that.
A terrible purchasing decision that haunts me is one that I made recently
because my Oculus Rift was not working.
And I assumed that it seemed like it was a port issue or a cord issue,
so I got a replacement cord, but that didn't fix the issue either.
So the problem is in the headset or at least in the port on the headset.
So I'm going to try and get the port fixed.
And if that doesn't work, I'll just have to replace the headset,
which is like $300, which I probably won't do.
I'm going to fix the port.
How do you do that?
I don't know.
I'll take it to a mechanic and be like,
Guys, the port seems not to work.
Replace it or do something about it.
I'll give you money for this.
So quickly answer the question on my card.
I once bought a microphone and it was expensive as hell,
and it worked terribly, so wasted money there.
I bought a mouse from Amazon for $10.
Oh, you smashed it.
Within a couple of weeks, yes, with Leopold the Mace,
the flanged Mace that I bought at King Richard's Fair for $90.
Which is a purchase you don't regret.
That was always as expensive as my $100 Vampire Hunter D Leather Hat.
Your Leather Hat.
Your wide room leather hat.
I can't believe my Mace costs less than that.
I know, right?
I could have bought a suit Katana, dude, but...
Well, I don't know about that.
Okay, maybe not.
I could have bought probably a hammer of some kind.
You could have bought a blunt weapon like mine,
which is what the cool kids wheeled.
No, that thing's paid for itself many times over,
in the form of revenge against Amazon.
I tweeted the video of me smashing it, which was awesome.
That was great.
SambaMan64 asks,
what's your go-to interesting fact about yourself?
I'm gay.
Oh, guys.
We got to stay on the same person.
But you just complied about not liking attention from gay guys,
and yet your first thing out of your mouth is I'm gay.
I'm a self-hating gay.
Aren't we all?
I hate myself in all those places.
He streams to high heaven,
I'm gay, I'm gay,
and then when the gay guys come to him like a scarecrow,
he bats them away.
Like, what's the deal?
Come on.
Yeah, why the mixed messages, friend?
What?
Yeah.
When you insist like you're gay like us,
you're going to get gay people who want to be gay with you,
if it's true or not.
Oh, that's the secret I now know.
Maybe, yeah, maybe we should stop pretending we're gay.
No, no, that can't be it.
Yeah, yeah.
Go-to interesting fact about myself.
I mean, what I do for a living is fucking weird and bizarre.
I was pretty much thinking of that as well.
For most people, yeah.
When I have a little, I enjoy being at work,
and there are several people who I'm relatively
kind of buddies with at work
who I distinctly have not told them anything.
And one of them is actually a guy who I'm,
I'd say I'm friends with him,
and we talk about One Piece every week when it comes out,
but I have not told him that I do a podcast about it.
That I do a podcast,
that I have a YouTube channel I talk about.
It's fun for me to just not talk about it,
and so I get to giggle myself.
Okay, so yeah, I get it.
At that party I was at last night,
the topic of me and my comics and the Kickstarter
and get it, you know, all that came up
and the lectures and YouTube,
and it was so awkward and embarrassing,
and I was like,
it's not that I'm embarrassed of it,
but talking about it was really uncomfortable,
and I just wanted it to be over.
There was no, it doesn't even matter what people,
some people thought it was cool.
Someone said, oh, they were jealous.
Someone made a joke and thought it was funny,
and it's like, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter what the reaction is.
I feel weird and uncomfortable talking about it.
No matter how positive the reaction is.
I've always felt that way.
I don't know,
Michelle's talked to her coworkers about my online stuff,
and I don't go and see her there,
and they'll see a coworker and they'll be like,
oh, hey dude, the guy who makes the YouTube videos.
I was always like, oh, blush, how's Kashi Sensei?
You know, that.
It has not reached a point of like, I'm not embarrassed.
I am embarrassed, why am I embarrassed?
I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know why either,
because in my heart, I like it about myself,
and I think that it's cool and I'm glad.
And yet, having it come up at a party,
it's like, oh god, no.
Let's talk about anything else.
I think we just got to rebrand it.
We got to rebrand it as saying, I'm not a YouTuber, I'm a Tuber.
I'm a Tuber.
I'm on the tube.
That's far worse.
No, no, because it goes so far into like,
stupid that it is like something you can laugh about.
Like, yeah, yeah, I'm a Tuber.
I should circle around.
I should circle all the way around
and go so far into being an internet weirdo
that I have to start wearing a tie everywhere that I go
and disguising myself as a normie.
Yes.
And like, you know,
just dressing like a witch.
And just performing the character.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whenever someone comes up to me and asks me where I go,
I say, I'm a digital influencer.
Oh.
You don't get your eyes with outside people enough.
That title, while accurate,
that title is deeply dystopian to me.
Yeah, it definitely is.
Digital influencer.
More, more, yeah, that's a little dystopian.
Just the fact that the word content
is something that people bandy about
to just mean like anything that anyone makes
is pretty dystopian.
I mean, I suppose that's true.
I think I might have seen a tweet about this.
But it's like content.
It's just like anything anyone makes
is just like material.
It's just raw material to be fed through the grinder
of your brain, of the masses.
I absolutely hate the phrase content creator.
Yeah.
It's the most disgusting way.
It's pretty convenient just because it is so vague.
It is convenient, but it's weird.
It reduces all art to the same base matter.
Yeah, one of those is that if you're a painter,
you don't say you're a content creator.
You say you're a profession.
Everybody on the internet considers what they do content
rather than the art that they make
in whatever form it is.
They should just say I'm an artist.
Don't say you're a digital artist.
Don't say you're an internet artist.
You're an artist. You do a thing.
You just happen to be on the internet.
Here's a quick newsflash.
Ben, did you by any chance just attempt to log into
the t-bap account on Google or anything?
I assume not.
I did, actually.
Oh, you did.
Oh, okay.
Because I was going to say,
someone is attempting to hack our mainframe
Oh, okay. Okay.
Well, never mind that.
Well, I mean, I'm done.
I've ceased.
Are there any more good questions?
I'm not looking at the...
Well, I guess I'll open up the Discord.
Fair enough.
I mean, I'm looking.
I'm looking. I don't see much.
What is this?
This is from Dazz Biggles.
One.
Why?
Oh, yes.
Wow.
Band.
Seconds two.
You're in a dangerous woods.
Which is...
Which...
Okay, wait.
You're in a dangerous woods.
Which escaped felon do you partner up with?
A serial killer?
A mass shooter?
Or a tax evader?
Tax evader.
He's spry.
He knows how to evade the jungle animals.
I'm going to go with serial killer
because I imagine he would be rugged.
That's what I imagine, too.
Mass shooters are like pussy incels.
And probably...
I mean, serial killers, you know,
they have a certain type that they kill
and odds are I'm not his type, right?
Yeah.
They usually kill women or, you know...
Probably women or, you know, something.
Like, there's something about the people that they kill
that is like, this is the kind of person that I like to kill.
And what are the odds that I fit that...
Oh, no, Ben.
Oh, no.
You've been partnered with the Alternative Lifestyle Killer.
Oh, no, it's the Keto Killer.
It's the Keto Killer.
I remember reading about him in the newspaper.
Oh, what a coincidence.
Well, if only I had thought that this might have happened.
I would go with the villain, King Dedede.
Oh, yeah, I would, too.
I like that guy.
He's got that hammer.
No, just escaped convict.
I think his jet-powered hammer would be very useful in this situation.
I think that would really help escape this mood.
Tadpo asks...
Sorry, was anyone else going to answer that one?
No.
It's dead.
It's over.
Tadpo asks a question that I just happened to have an answer for right now.
When have you guys attempted blah, blah, blah, blah.
Cheaper Jerry Rig Solutions.
Well, okay.
I have a Jerry Rig solution going on right now.
So I had a coffee table and then...
I had a coffee table and no desk, right?
And then someone...
Oh, God, who was it?
It was...
Okay.
Someone in my Discord, I won't say who it was, bought me a chair.
They bought me a desk chair.
Nice.
It was very...
Oh, wait, it was Ash.
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, he bought me a desk chair and I appreciated that a lot.
Thank you.
But now I have this coffee table that was too low.
So I literally just stacked books and just random objects and boxes under each of the four legs.
And the fourth leg is resting on top of a jar of protein powder.
God, that makes me nervous.
I'm already nervous.
I'm shaking and my boots here.
So, yeah, my desk is just kind of on top of stacks of things now, elevated up to more or less desk height.
It shifts around...
Well, the table is actually very stable and I do not see it tipping over.
The one potentially weak link is the jar of the protein powder moves around a little bit.
Sometimes it kind of goes close to the edge where the leg of the table might go over there.
But the lid just kind of happens to have this ridged left-around edge.
Oh, thank God.
We've done it.
So, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, like, it's not...
Full proof.
I would basically have to deliberately kick it out from under.
And also, the final thing is that the weight of the things on the table are mostly at the back.
So if this one were to be kicked out, it would not even tip over because the weight is at the back.
So I would have to kick it out from under it and then apply weight to the front of the table to tip it over, which is not...
So I feel like it's pretty safe.
Do I want a real desk?
Yes.
But do I think that this one is going to fall over and wreck all my shit?
Probably not.
I don't know about you guys, but my fears are assuaged as hell right now.
Yeah, it's probably going to be fine.
God, what a nightmare.
I can't see if Ben dies.
If he doesn't die, then it worked out well.
And if he does, well, you know what I mean.
Well, it wouldn't be me that died.
It would be my sentie.
You could die at any moment, Ben.
Let's not pretend you could.
I've got a Jerry Wrig solution.
I'm tearing.
This is kind of...
I mean, it's nothing amazing.
But, like, forever we Agua, I've filmed.
What I've done is...
Did I do this for me in MAFA II?
I can't remember.
Like, I do this thing where, like...
You're not supposed to do this, but, like, you know the microphone arm?
You know, the fucking road one?
What I do is I...
Because that's my mic I record everything with.
I screw it...
I screw, like, the clamp to the arm of a swivel chair.
And I move it out to, like, the center of the floor.
And I kind of just, like, position it so it's not in the shot.
And it kind of is just, like, floating, like, a couple feet below me so it's out of the shot.
But the thing is, that chair swivels extremely easily.
So, it just, like...
For the lightest gust of wind, if a fucking butterfly beats its wings anywhere in the vicinity,
the chair swivels at mock speed violently out of orbit.
And just results in a whole cavalcade of comedy, if you will.
Nate, do you know that office chairs can explode?
I'm sorry?
What do you mean?
Office chairs can explode because there's pressurized air in there.
Very, very rarely, office chairs can explode and it has killed office workers before.
God, I hope that's me.
Please let it be me next time.
I'll do anything.
It'd be a shame if that were to happen to you, says the creeper.
Yeah, he says, he says, exposing his bare neck to the compressed air chamber.
Please let me continue a little.
Wait, where is there compressed air in an office chair?
It's gotta be, like, the swivel thing, I guess?
I mean, I don't know.
This sounds kind of made up, TBH.
No, no, no, no.
Sounds like bullshit.
They put nitrogen in there.
If you shake it too much, kaboom.
I want some fan art of Nate dying via explosion caused by an office chair.
I like to imagine that you just sit down on it too hard and then a rocket propels you through your butt,
up your spine, out your head.
It reminds me of a similar sort of thing.
There is a real thing that, like, sometimes office chairs will break
and they have the center column that swivels.
People have broken the chair, it sat down fast, impaled their own asshole
on the center thing of their chair.
A lot.
Yeah, it's truly the worst case scenario.
Let me die instead, just kill me.
I don't want to deal with all that.
It's the beginning of letting me die.
Let this episode die, we're done.
Congratulations again to Sasuke Zero Pro or whatever.
Let me know if you want to be called something else or whatever.
Everybody, he's a big boy.
He did it.
I don't want to be mean.
I do like it.
I'm sorry for being critical.
That's fine.
I want to say thank you for everyone who entered though.
It was amazing.
It was an amazing experience.
Absolutely.
It absolutely was.
It was a joy and we got to do more stuff like this.
The next PCP contest coming at you soon, we'll come up with something.
We should start, we should do the race.
We should do a PCP race.
We should do a race, but it's not really a community thing.
I guess that's not the same kind of thing.
We could challenge the viewers to do a race.
We could have a community race and then we could laugh at them.
Oh, like everyone has to upload their own best time.
Yeah, like people did when people were speedrunning sheepovers game.
That was cool.
Oh, dude.
Right.
The biggest annoyance with the PCP race is getting people organized to do it.
If the fans do it, then it's much easier.
That's true.
And we just commentate like, haha, that guy sucks.
Yeah, that's not as fun.
Remember my breakdown in the Pokemon race?
That was pretty good.
All right, we'll come up with something everybody.
We'll get back to you.
Thanks for listening.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
$5 tier.
Get the bonus episodes.
Monsters 2.
It's the greatest single form of media ever produced by man.
Listen to it.
$1 at least.
And you're in the chat.
You get the questions.
You get all the fun stuff.
And you're hanging out with the cool lads.
So go do all those things.
There's some links.
Oh, buy the gum road stuff if you want the backers content stuff.
It should be linked below for the...
Oh, man, we're at almost 300 patrons.
Yeah, we are.
We're right about that.
We are at 297.
We are about to break that 300.
The Patreon, the PCB Patreon has been an incredible success over the years.
It's doing absolutely magnificently.
Truly suckers.
It only knew about the Syrian refugees that we were funding to do acts of terrorism with
all the 100% proceeds of the PC on Patreon.
Maybe they wouldn't be so able to give it to them.
Just imagine how it would surge if we revealed that fact.
How much support would flood in if they knew?
Oh, well, I guess they'll never know.
They'll never know.
All right, thanks for listening, everybody.
Rest in peace, everyone.
Go rest your ears and eyes and brain.
Thanks for being here.
Rest in peace.
And we'll see you next week with another one.
Goodbye.
Yeah.
Oh.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.
What the hell is wrong with me?
I'm supposed to be making money.
I'm supposed to be creating funny things that the people
gladly will pay for.
Artistic genius.
That's what they came for.
Instead, I'm tweeting.
That's why there's no heat and holes in the ceiling.
Yeah.
It's quite the burden.
It's a hard knock life.
Being a genius.