Hello everyone and welcome, oh god I hit the mic. To another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast, die Mike, die.
I'm the bestest boy with the most microphone skills. And we've got Ben Saint is here.
Nate, why did our sister not show up on the show?
Grace! Grace, come here!
I know, it's too late.
Wait, okay introduce yourselves. Let me see if I can get her.
I'm Hippocrit, who cares.
Yeah? What's your deal?
Oh you know, I'm just one of those people who don't do anything.
Oh, my favorite.
Alright, grand debut. Here's Grace, say some words.
You're a dog, you're a dog and I'm sick of it.
There's my sister guys, it's Grace.
You hit mine too, idiot.
Don't appropriate Ben's sister.
Yeah.
Well, that's a meme now.
How nice. Yeah, that is good. Way to go, Grace.
I assume the rest of you introduced yourself. You're all the same shit.
I'm just glad there's only four of us because it means I make more money.
No, don't talk inside baseball. Don't pull the curtain back and kill the magic.
Inside baseball, inside basketball.
The only people that information is relevant to, that I do in fact try not to mention is the other members of this podcast
so as to not overly encourage them to show up on the off chance I can make more money.
Our system of distributing our assets is fundamentally broken.
I think it's perfectly reasonable. What's wrong with that?
Isn't it weird that you get more for being on an episode if there's less people on it?
Well, you have to do more work. You have to assert yourself more.
It doesn't feel like more work.
Well, you know, if somebody shows up to every show it means they were dedicated to making that dash, you know?
Yeah, like the real thing that you have to do is just get there and start recording.
This is why capitalism doesn't work. That's all I'm saying.
That's a silly point. I will grant you though, Ben.
I mean, simply having the profit motive, like that alone, totally changes the dynamic of like any given relationship.
So that's very true.
I gotta imagine that there's somebody who listens to this show at the stop clock that says on it like minutes till Ben mentions capitalism.
Well, guess what?
They slapped it just now and went, God damn, new record.
Your job is done. You can go on.
You can rest now, we're each other.
Speaking of capitalism just a little bit, I have been watching videos of the left or whatever direction.
Oh my God, let's fucking chat about it.
I've been watching a lot of Thought Slime. I've been watching a bit of ContraPoints as well.
And I like them because they're funny and also the things, well, you know, they have a humorous spin on the things they're saying,
which makes it more palatable and easy for me to get into it.
ContraPoints is very theatrical, which is, you know, it's fine.
If you're a drama kid, I'm sure it appeals.
I am fine with it. I wouldn't say that it's like, I mean, it's a little much, I get feeling like it's a little over theatrical.
This is kind of how I feel about Philosophy Tube and how the way that he mugs the camera is like a little weird sometimes.
You said like the incredible sensuality of the videos can be a little much.
He will sometimes get really sensual in the way that he makes direct eye contact with the viewer and licks his lips and stuff.
Yeah, that sort of stuff. I'm not so much, like I think I've seen one of his videos and he seemed, I just looked it in.
I was like, yeah, I don't watch all of, okay, well he has a goatee and I hate goatees.
That's like, that's the worst thing about him by far.
Fair enough. Fair enough. I hear he's like a real philosopher or something.
He has like actual credentials, Philosophy Tube. Is that true?
Is there such thing as credentials and philosophy?
Well, like a PhD and like is like a doctor or something. I don't know.
There's no way he has a PhD.
Okay, I could be wrong. I could be wrong.
He probably has some kind of qualifications. I don't know what they are.
But he's got, my favorite Philosophy Tube is a little series he's got called What Was Liberalism and it's very informative.
That's a really good one.
I feel very informed. Just about things in general, seeing it from the other side.
I grew up kind of grew up on things like The Amazing Atheist, who is still not that bad.
He's just sort of obnoxious in the way he approaches things.
But he's very more thoughtful than you would imagine if you don't really watch him that much.
But then there's like all that whole crowd of amazing atheists like copycat people who are the same video every time.
The skeptic community.
Yeah, and I was just like, ah, geez, this is all really boring and who cares?
Ah, geez, Rick, there's a lot of atheists on YouTube and it's upsetting me.
Morty, don't you know God isn't real, Morty? What are you fucking stupid, Morty?
Yeah, but then actual dialogue from season four.
And I don't think women should be in video games.
But then there's thought slime.
It's just sort of like he's just talking about things that they wouldn't talk about, like what anarchism actually means.
I mean, I know like words mean things to different people, but it's just interesting to see from different perspectives.
There's nothing wrong with being in a perspective totally agree.
It is. It is, right? I mean, can I ask, okay, where did you jump in?
Did you jump in with thought slime?
Or did you jump in with contra points and migrate to thought slime?
I watched a contra points video when it was recommended to me like months ago.
And I was sort of taken aback by the whole, the way it looked.
I was like, what? I don't get it.
Like, what's going on here?
It's a little too much for me. It's a little too much for my little brain, P-brain here.
That's my favorite thing about contra points.
It was. It was just sort of like, wow, this is like the big trap.
Like, my first thought was, this is a trans woman.
And therefore, I don't know whether the content will be good.
Just because I-
What does that mean?
No, no. Yeah, I mean-
Relax.
I got me some-
No, I want to know what that means.
I got like prejudices because like, oh, social justice for a trans community.
They're the same thing.
And so, if there's somebody popular, it's probably just because they're trans
and not because they have interesting things to say.
But I stuck out the video because I was so, I guess, enthralled by like what was going on
that I was like, oh wait, they're sensible and they're like, they're not,
they're not like preaching to the choir.
They are talking about things that I don't hear people talk about
and they're just really good.
I don't know if I would say they're not preaching to the choir.
Well, I mean, not every video is the same video.
Everyone who does commentary, you know, by virtue of the fact that they have,
you know, gained an audience through the things they say is,
you know, like obviously they're preaching to the people that have subscribed to them
and are therefore sort of self identifying them as the choir.
Only because I used to be a fan of Contra points.
And in the early days, she was a lot edgier and a lot more willing to sort of go
against the grain of like what's popular in that movement.
And I think it kind of became that as she became like a bigger voice,
more and more people were looking to her as like, oh, you are like our representative
spokesperson.
So you have to be more careful about what you say.
And you have to, you know, like basically play by the book a little bit more.
And it seems like she very much like internalized that and kind of took it like,
okay, you know, I do have to be, I do have to take more responsibility and be more like that.
And that just ruined it for me.
It's a very typical phenomenon for people.
I mean, what do you, what do you mean?
Not that I know.
Like what changed?
I'm curious because I haven't watched all of Contra points.
So like, I might not know.
It would be easy to understand if you watch a lot of the earlier videos because
yeah, in the early days, like Contra points is just a lot more.
I guess I would say nihilistic about it all or just like she didn't care so much
about being politically correct with the ideas.
It was like presenting the arguments in a way that was charitable to the,
to people who don't see, like, don't think you have to communicate this particular way
that you have to like watch your words and really like walk on eggshells through your explanation.
I know she used to go on 4chan.
I don't know if that stopped or if she's changed her approach.
But I mean, anyone who does that, I remember when, whatever one video she said,
she used to go there to hear, like,
I forget which video this was.
She would go to like the LGBTQ board, I think, and would like post her like,
you know, how's my transition going specifically to receive the kind of incredibly harsh feedback
you'll never get from like your friends and allies.
You'll only get from people who just don't give a shit about you.
Contra points is kind of like a hard ass and kind of like,
which is what I like about those early videos is that they come off as somebody
who's very critical of themselves and their own side, you know, like somebody who...
I always enjoy that.
I mean, I think she's, I think like, she seems pretty willing to like,
she doesn't really seem to be that like towing the party line.
Like, I think, I feel like she's pretty willing to come out,
to come out with like an unpopular take on like, you know, something like,
like what is, what does it mean to be trans, for example.
I mean, I'm sure she is and I haven't been keeping up with her content for a long time
because what bogged it down for me was just the sheer amount of like,
over-explaining the language or like trying to basically compromise,
what's the word I'm looking for?
It's like she babies you through the videos in a way that she didn't used to.
Do you think that's like a sort of a, like, as her videos got viewed by more and more people,
she had to like, simplify them, like make them more accessible?
Yes, and make them more accessible and also less, like less potentially triggering, we'll say.
Like that she might have made an edgy joke before and not explained it.
And now she feels like I have to explain every single thing I say on the off chance
that somebody is going to be offended by the way I've chosen to phrase it,
which is exactly what my problem with that community is in the first place.
That like, people are in, are just so soft that they need to have everything broken down and explained in depth.
And it's like, you can just offend people sometimes, like, it's okay.
Just if they can't handle it, they shouldn't watch the videos, you know.
There's always going to be a pressure to avoid that when you are trying to reach more people.
I was watching, I watched the R-Traps gay video, have you seen that?
I think I've seen that one.
Well, like that one, she says like, I think maybe this might speak to what's going on there.
She says like, this is like a bad question in like, the question itself is sort of like inflammatory
and like derogatory, just in the way that it's phrased.
But like, she said that she wants, you know, she wants, she's making a video so that like,
some kid who hears the question and maybe goes home and Googles it,
she wants his first exposure to the answer to be like, her video versus like, some fucking idiot,
some meme or unfortunate or whatever, who is just, you know.
It's just kind of like, in the early days.
In that way, I think if you're looking at it that way, she probably just wants to like, control her language in a way that like,
you know, gives like, people who aren't being newly exposed to these ideas like,
absolutely.
She wants to guide the conversation in a certain like, more productive way.
That's just the opposite of what I want to watch.
Like, it's that ContraPoints in the early days, because when I was watching her,
she had like 50,000 subscribers or something, less than that.
Like, this is years ago, you know.
682k.
Yeah, way, way bigger.
She had like 45,000 when I was watching her.
And like, again, the content was a lot edgier.
And like, part of the appeal was that she called herself like, the right whisperer or something like that,
because her appeals reached across the aisle to both camps and were capable of, you know,
basically being nuanced enough in their approach that people from the other side would also be able to appreciate it.
And now it just, when you watch the videos, it is so indebted to the community that she's speaking for at this point,
that it could no longer reach across the aisle that way.
Like, people on the right are not going to watch these videos because they're going to see it as excessively SJW pandering.
I think that, I don't know.
I think that they are still intended to reach across the aisle.
I mean, I don't know how.
Hence the Trap's Gay. Hence the Our Trap's Gay thing.
I don't know how long ago this change started, but the one I watched recently was the two part,
What's Wrong with Capitalism video, which, I mean, the reason I liked these videos,
I haven't been watching them in order or anything, just like what's recommended to me,
is that she would bring up things like the alt-right perspective,
and she wouldn't attack it in the same way that the armored skeptic would attack a left idea,
just make fun of it and make names out of it.
She would bring it up and honestly talk about it in a sort of neutral fashion,
before going on to her explanation of how whatever she's talking about.
Now, it's just sort of like, I mean, I don't know whether that aspect still,
I mean, her most recent video, Transtrenders, I watched and I felt like that was the same sort of thing.
It was a bit, like, difficult to follow because I didn't know a lot of the terminology at first,
but I got the gist by the end about, I don't know.
I don't know whether she's too pandering.
It's not that I don't think that she still thinks the same way as before.
It's that the videos are boring now because of the fact that they have to softball so much,
explain all the jokes, you know, like make sure everybody knows that she's not saying this or I'm not saying that.
Like I said, I mean, if you just go watch some of the earlier videos,
they are just a lot more like dense and edgy and they don't come from somebody
who seems like they were trying to appeal to everyone, you know?
It just felt much more personal and raw and like what I see now is like somebody who is trying to take responsibility
for their level of celebrity and present things and like be the spokesperson for trans people,
you know, because people are taking her that way because of the fact that she is more reasonable than most people.
She's the one who everyone's going to link you their videos, you know?
Like everyone's going to say, oh, you want to talk about this issue?
You got to watch the ContraPoints video and like I think she's internalized that and taken that into account
and I totally respect that, but it doesn't work for me because I already understand all this shit
and I don't need it to be re-explained.
I don't need to be babied through the video.
I don't want to have to listen to you correct yourself and like make, you know, apologize for everything you say.
You know, obviously my own content, I make a point to not do any of that because I find it annoying.
And I would rather...
Well, there you go. You're not the target audience.
You know, I would rather just offend you and then have a conversation about it than, you know, to make my content boring.
I doubt she hopes for the same.
Oh, sure.
Sure.
Hippo, what got you on Thought Slime?
Because I love Thought Slime.
I think it was just that you had mentioned you were watching him and something about Slime and getting him on IRFCK and that was funny.
Yeah.
So I saw a video of his and I was like, oh, okay.
I didn't like his cartoon face and his more recent videos with his actual human face.
He's not a great artist.
We can all agree on that.
Yeah.
He also has the misfortune of looking like a giant baby man, which, you know, I don't hold against him, but is true.
Professional soft boy.
See?
Yes.
Indeed.
Oh, he's like, who's that guy from Dark Souls 3 who just consumed like human flesh until he softened and turned to ooze and just started spreading everywhere.
Saint Aldrich of the Deep or whatever.
That's him.
That's Thought Slime.
I got nothing against that guy.
It's just funny.
When I found Thought Slime, I was just like, oh, wow.
Here's a guy who's just outright saying like he's not, there's no, there's no pretense.
He's outright saying, hey, I'm a fucking anarcho-communist and I want to fucking end capitalism.
And here's why.
And you know what?
It's just refreshing, right?
It's not like he's the only one like that, but he was like the first one that I found and he was just like bald-faced like capitalism sucks and I want to dismantle it.
And here's the problems with that.
I was like, oh my God, sick.
It's like a relief.
Well, that's understandable.
Hey, hey, I've got a higher, let me go one step up on the conversation tree here because I experienced a truly euphoric piece of content recently that is very relevant to what we're talking about right now.
You may be, of course, you know, of the world-famous podcast known only as Grimp, episode two.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The title, Should Grimp Do Politics, was the question.
Yes.
And now let me just cut through all the, let's do it.
You know, you and Duobo, is that what is first be known as online?
Well, I mean, we just call him John.
Okay, I just didn't want to.
Yeah, Duobo, AKA John.
Okay, so John, I'm going to call him John because that's how I think of him.
Discussion, you guys both very left leaning, no problem, that's fine.
But you get to the end and the summary is, should Grimp discuss politics?
I would like to quote, I wrote down, when Ben, quote, insanely transphobic Ben St., with the words, Ben, should Grimp do politics?
Definitely not no, end quote.
That's the exact words used by one Benjamin Eleanor St.
And I would just like to present that to the group.
As in, definitely not colon, no, definitely not semicolon, no.
Correct, correct.
Not a negation of the previous statement being made, but a continuation of these-
Yes, got it.
Negatory expression, yes.
Got it, got it.
So I would say, and you know, that conversation was interesting, everyone should go listen to World Famous Podcast, Grimp.
World Famous Anarcho-Communist.
Indeed.
Well-
Advocate, Grimp.
Sure, but the consensus of that show was like, there are times when politics should be discussed and fleshed out and dived into,
but politics is a fraught subject, can cause stress, inevitably causes much conflict.
And there are times and places where it's appropriate, not appropriate, and one needs to just partition your life
in the appropriate way, probably, to decide when you want to get into it and when not.
And I submit to the group that I think the PCP, my vision of the PCP, is one of these places.
It is a fun place, not designed to cause- there are times when it'll inevitably come up,
but to make it like a staple of the thing, I would think is not probably the optimal solution.
I agree.
And I think I could probably dial it back.
And I've been thinking, yeah, I don't need to- but I'm not going to dial it back down to zero.
Because sometimes, sometimes things are said, and I feel the need to comment on them.
And I mean, sometimes I feel like I'm not the one bringing in the politics.
The politics are coming in accidentally, and I'm merely reacting to them.
Do you know what I mean?
You know, I am sympathetic to that point.
I would say that, however, there's a way to look at the world where anything could happen
and one can view it through a political lens.
I would say that it kind of depends on the observer.
So I wouldn't exempt any particular person who views an event and chooses to view it through the political lens,
as opposed to someone who doesn't do that.
You could look at- I mean, kind of like Anita Sarkeesian.
She says everything is sexist, and you need to look for these things and point them out.
And I have no problem with her life, whatever, do whatever you want.
But she's choosing to view the world in that way, so as to identify-
It's a little bit of a caricature.
But I don't think so.
I mean, I think that's a very rational reading of the ideology being put forward.
I think there is a clip of her saying everything is sexist, everything is racist, and you have to point it all out.
Yes, and it's taken out of context.
I am not trying to say that Anita Sarkeesian thinks that everything is sexist.
I'm merely positing what I think is a reasonable point that it seems to me that her and people of a similar persuasion
choose to view the world through the lens of their particular ideology, which in their case is feminism.
Well, I mean, everybody does that.
Everybody views the world through the lens of their particular ideology.
But not everyone's ideology is to lean towards politics, so there is a difference between people.
Well, I think the thing here is that Anita Sarkeesian does-
She talks about feminism things as sort of a job at this point, so of course she's going to comment on them more than someone who isn't doing it for a job.
This is just kind of an evolution of the, like, keep your politics out of my video games,
which is like a wrong-headed argument in the first place because, like, everything is inherently political.
I want to pause it first of all.
That's not true.
It is.
I don't think this is a new thing for our podcast.
I think we just have been using more political terms.
Like, when I think back to the early days of this show, like, almost every fucking episode ended up in some kind of anti-SJW rant
where we would go down the road of language politics or political correctness or something, like,
it's not unusual for us to spiral into political rants.
It's just that with Ben consuming all this political content all the time, it is more, like, direct.
Like, the terminology is there.
The argument is more, like, directly in reference to political terms.
But, like, I mean, it inevitably happens if that's what's on your mind when you discuss things.
I'm just going to say it.
I'm just going to come right out.
Guy, are you ready?
Are you ready for my bombshell?
Are you ready to get triggered?
Okay.
Well, here's what I think.
I think that as I have developed as a human being, right, as I have evolved, as I have opened my third eye and, you know,
ascended to the anarcho-communist utopia,
I feel like there's, I've just had, I've moved a little away from what the rest of you guys might think.
I've moved away from the centrist bullshit that dominates our society.
I know.
It's not real.
It is.
But anyway, the point is that I, I don't know, that I have disagreements now.
That's it.
I think that's a crux of it, is now I have disagreements.
We didn't used to have disagreements and now I have disagreements.
I've changed my position on a bunch of things.
I mean, I'm, I'm like pretty casually political.
So like, I'm not like so overt, like I don't have a set goal in my political like ideology or what I want out of the world.
So like you having like this different, you know, this, this change in politics a little, it's really just made me curious and I'm going to look.
That makes me so happy.
That makes me so joyous.
I mean, I don't know what centrism really is, but I'd like to be able to understand both Nate and Ben at the same time.
If you know what I mean.
By the way, I want to be fair to our audience here for a second because the argument is not really from them that they don't want us to talk about politics.
They're split.
No, it's that they don't want us to talk about politics.
It's not that they have a problem with listening to people talk about politics.
They just think we are retarded and they don't like us talking about politics.
That's the biggest, that's by far the biggest complaint.
You know, I see it.
I'm not unsympathetic to it.
I'm trying to get less retarded.
It's hard.
It's also hard because I'm not there yet.
I don't trust the people who are criticizing me always to actually be, to actually know.
Because a lot of the time the argument is just you should shut up about politics because you don't know about it.
And then I say, well, what do I not know?
Are you capable of explaining this?
Because as far as I know, you're retarded about politics and I'm right unless you can put up an argument.
But, you know, I mean, there's, I'm just being charitable to what their actual feelings are, you know, not that I think they're correct.
On the one, on the one hand, there's like, you know, there's lots of books out there to read.
There's lots of stuff out there to consume, right, to get educated.
On the other hand, you can, you can never have read it all.
You can never know enough, right?
You'll never be done learning.
How do you vet which ones are like, there's always people who they've read a few books and now they think they know it all,
but they haven't read the counterbooks.
And it's like, you have to have read all the books and all the counterbooks and all the everybody's perspective before you can really look at it all and make a judgment for yourself.
Like, it's always going to come down to not what is correct, but what you agree with.
I mean, even then there's infinite knowledge that humanity doesn't know yet.
So any of that amount could be the, look, the problem with this whole discussion is that let's say we, let's say we literally,
we as the PCP found literally the perfect political ideology.
We knew it.
We had done this in some way.
Okay, let's say we did that.
I already did it.
Okay, great.
So you've got it.
And now our mission is to convert the audience to thinking this in whatever way we choose.
There is like, okay, you just have to think that the audience does not immediately like agree with you and the process of making it like converting a show that's like a comedy show.
Are we a comedy show?
I have always stood by that and I believe it to this day.
Well, we're funny people.
So therefore we're a comedy show, I think is generally like we didn't get, we don't sit out to make jokes.
I don't think there have been no laughs on this particular episode.
I know.
And I consider it a tragedy.
Do I look like no laughs?
And there have been laughs.
There have been laughs.
But the point is, look at the laugh, Nate, show me the laugh.
Even if we, you're laughing right now.
Even if we had a perfect political ideology and we were attempting to like teach it to the audience, I would like that process will be fraught and contentious.
And you're making it like a political thing that just will be divisive.
Could not everyone will agree with you.
And that the question is, is that the kind of atmosphere you want for your show?
Some shows are political.
Some shows are not.
And you can say that everything is political.
I know, I understand the point and that's kind of true.
But there are shows where they talk about things where the point is not to be political or to make any kind of major point.
I couch everything I say in, I'm an idiot.
I don't know anything.
This is just my life experience.
Could be wrong.
Don't trust me on anything.
Believe what you want to believe.
What I want the PCP and any content I'm involved with to be is a place where people don't get hung up on this.
Like you have the strength of mind that you can listen to us talk about anything.
Like that's what I would hope is that like we could talk about politics.
We could talk about anything else.
The point of it is that it's us and our perspective and just being ourselves.
And if you are interested in us, that's the appeal.
Like I don't think the PCP really has like we could say it's a comedy podcast, but obviously you don't listen to this podcast for comedy.
You listen to it because you're interested in us.
And so whatever we have to talk about, you know, again, I understand the people whose argument is I don't want to hear you guys talk about politics because you don't know what you're talking about and they find it infuriating.
I would encourage those people to consider the possibility that we do know what we're talking about unless you can prove that we don't know what we're talking about.
But you know, I just think it's not fun.
I just think it's and my goal is to make it fun to listen to.
This is my priority.
Yeah, I would say just we should we should always just if we think a conversation is not going anywhere, we should move.
I want to keep the conversation upstream at like ideas and culture.
I do not want to bring it down to downstream to politics.
That's my that's I don't know what the fuck that means.
But the trend that I notice in the last like two episodes is that like the episode would come out and then there'd be kind of a bunch of comments and, you know, sprinkled in there would be a bunch that were like, I love the political discussion.
And then later on, like more would trickle in that are like, I hate the political and in the end, it would kind of even out.
But it was like the people who are like watching it right when it comes out, they seem to like it more.
And then the people that like watch it later or something.
It seemed it seemed like more than like lessons like does this mean that like maybe the people that are like more engaged like it.
And like the people who are more casual listeners are annoyed by it.
Man, we don't have an analytics on that.
No, I think it's possible people literally just jump into the comments leave that comment because they want to get ahead of the other comments that they haven't even listened to the episode yet.
Who knows who knows.
Well, I think inevitably as always, the funny thing about the PCB has always been there is no thought leader.
There is no one whipping the ship.
It's just whatever any of us want to talk about.
And there are inevitably going to be disagreements and differences of vision as to what is to be done.
The emphasis where it should be put.
So I think all we can do is just state our case, write it out and see what inevitably wins out long term.
Well, this conversation has been boring for like 20 minutes.
Exactly.
I can say, well, you want to go?
Well, yeah, I got I got a thing.
It was just sort of like an idea I came up with and I want to see who else feels this way.
It is copycat anxiety.
And this is the the anxiety that when you are about to do or say something and then someone else does or says that exact thing.
You find yourself unable to do the thing you wanted to do for the fear that somebody will think you're copying the first person.
Absolutely.
Right.
I mean, I've thrown away video concepts many times because somebody else has already done it.
Somebody made a Banjo-Kazooie kind of stylized like my Smash confirmed series.
And when I first saw that, I was like, oh, shit, someone just did this and perhaps I have some idea to make something like it.
We'll see.
I was like, well, shit, I guess that's out.
But then I watched it and it wasn't that good.
And I was like, oh, OK, that's fine then.
Yeah, it's always easy to justify doing it again if you think that their version sucked in your version.
There's many differences, but when I saw that, they used the same kind of thumbnail template I used.
They used the same font that I used for it and I was like, ah, shit.
But then it did seem to have a different kind of intention.
I mean, in that case, if it's somebody who's doing your style, I would see them as the copycat.
Yeah, but it's still kind of like, let's just say that he literally ripped off my formula, which is fine, including like thumbnail, title, everything.
It's very deliberate and like you could instantly know if it's like copying me, which it kind of was.
Let's just say that he made like the full thing in the way that I would have.
Like, is that bad?
Should I be like mad?
Should I not make my own if it already exists, basically?
I would think you would do, I would definitely say you should do your own because it's your series.
Yeah, I mean, the thing about that is like, those videos were so big and they were so shareable,
but they weren't like Nate videos.
No, they're not about me.
They're copyable.
It's a style that people can copy.
But the problem is with that is that people won't realize if they're like casual watches, they just saw these smash videos.
They won't notice that a different person has made them.
Like some people probably don't even realize it's not as good.
I think it would be evident when you watch it and it sucks.
Well, I mean, I'm not even saying this was like horrible, but it was not at my level.
That's true.
It went on for like 20 minutes doing the intro before I got to the music or something.
But a lot of people are dumb.
They'd see like the black background with the smash ball.
They'll see Banjo.
They'll be like, oh good, another one.
They'll see like the font.
And they'll be like, wow, this guy really dropped off.
Like what happened here?
I don't know.
Nothing I'm really worried about.
But like the point just to get back to Gibbs point because I do find that interesting.
And like it did kind of dampen my spirits a little bit like, ah, shit.
But then I got over when I saw that like, okay, this didn't really like do what I've done.
But like if you want to like do a review of an anime because you've got something interesting to say
and it's an original idea you thought or something.
Then you like happen to click around and you see, oh shit.
This guy talked about the exact thing I was going to talk about and his video is like nice and stuff.
I mean, what the fuck am I going to do?
This is not like you.
I mean, in a small enough community, this is more powerful and more potent,
especially when it comes to each us in the PCP because I came up with this idea like a few weeks ago
when Digi had been paid to rant about the quick draw not being advertised enough.
Up until that point, I'd been thinking I really got to get around to making a video
and then Digi says it in the rant and then people like, yeah, what the fuck?
Where's the quick draw ads?
And I'm like, damn it.
Now people are going to think I wouldn't have had the idea if not Digi had said it.
They think I'm cocking Digi's advice and that it's all his reason that, god damn it, I got so mad.
Then I made that like sort of passive-aggressive ad.
It was very passive-aggressive.
Like, yeah, it's your fucking...
Because I knew immediately people in the comments would think, oh, Digi saved the day and I was like, it wasn't Digi.
I was thinking about it.
I already knew.
I'm the smart boy.
I know how to do things.
I know I hadn't done it.
I know.
That's why, I mean, it's not even that I was angry at you, obviously.
It was that I was angry that I took so long and now people are going to think I'm a copycat freak with no brain.
Yeah.
You know, this is...
I can't really speak to that situation.
But just like two things like I was saying before about like other ideas.
This is why for anything that like I want to even like tangentially relate to things I want to make videos on,
I just like don't consume other people's media about it.
Unless I like do...
I expect to like quote it in the video or whatever.
That's a funny thing, Nate, because like I know a lot of reviewers do that.
Like Yahtzee has always said like, yeah, I don't watch anybody's reviews until I do my own.
And it's because they usually say they don't want to have like anybody else's opinions color theirs.
And like, I feel the total opposite because...
And this is wrong of me to feel this way because like most people view creators individually.
It's like I follow you.
I follow this guy.
Those are the people I consume.
I always think of it as like this overarching discourse that like anything that's been said already.
I don't have to say that again.
You know, like if somebody else has said it, I don't have to say it.
And so I always am trying to find the one thing nobody said.
So like rather than, you know, just like not consume anything else.
Which at this point, I don't because I don't like any anime reviewers at all.
So I don't watch anybody's shit just for that reason.
But like for instance with Mob Psycho.
Like I would have made a video about Mob Psycho season 2, but you had already gotten out your Viagoa before I got to it.
And in my video, I literally am like, hey, Nate already talked about the show in broad terms.
I'm just going to fixate on this one detail he didn't bring up because like I don't want to just repeat everything you said when you already did a good job.
I'd rather just send people to your video, you know?
See, that is a perfectly reasonable thing to do.
To see what other people are talking about and kind of like avoid it.
Or even maybe in general terms, recap it like to a degree, that seems fine to me.
But I very much worry personally about the guilt of either consciously or unconsciously like ripping off other people's ideas in any way.
So I don't know.
When it comes to like an anime or a video game video that hasn't been covered to death, then I think it's fine to make your own video because people will think of it as your take.
Even if it's very similar to some other video, there's a lower chance that they have seen all those other videos of the same thing.
When it comes to something like a review of The Last Jedi, nobody could do that anymore.
Like that has been done or like the last episode of Game of Thrones or something like overwhelmingly like, what's the word, cluttered, stodged.
It's just too many. It's too many saturated.
You know what's funny about that though?
Unbelievably saturated about that one aspect.
The funny thing about it though is that the audience by and large will just watch all of them.
They don't care if they repeat themselves. They don't care if they hear the same information.
I'm sure some people can.
I must have watched 20 videos about that Game of Thrones finale just because they were out there and I was like, alright.
I watched one.
Eventually people will stop.
A certain person will only be able to consume so many last Jedi reviews, but the audience doesn't disappear.
It tapers off over a long period.
For me, it's always difficult for me to understand other people's viewing habits because I only watch my subscriptions.
I really do not adventure out of that.
I'm not the type of person who watches a movie and then searches for what people are saying about it.
I don't care.
I really don't care what anybody has to say.
I only watch people because I like those people and I don't care what they're talking about.
I'll watch anything they talk about.
But that's not how most people are.
They watch everything pertaining to their interests.
I'll talk to Victor, for instance, who will do that.
He'll go and watch every video that's about something he cares about.
He just thinks all the videos are shit.
He'll tell me, you have to talk about this show because I watched 10 videos and they were all garbage and you have to make a video about it.
I'll just be like, okay, is there anything I can say that they didn't say?
Is it just a problem with the presentation or what did they talk about?
I want to know what he's unhappy about in a situation.
Did they not discuss the ideas he was interested in or is it that the presentation was terrible?
I think it's usually that he thinks they're wrong about it.
That they have the wrong take.
I think he was positive about-
Every girl log in review before I made mine and my great rage at that.
I think Victor was actually more positive about the final season at Game of Thrones, for instance.
I think he was upset that everybody had the same negative take.
But I think he watched them all.
Every single one, he just gets madder and madder as he watches them.
I watched them all in a quest for additional details that most people weren't aware.
For nuggets of information.
Maybe there was-
This was said, Daenerys' thing was set up in a really cool way.
We weren't aware of it.
That's not what happened.
But maybe someone knows something that I wasn't aware of.
I'm on a quest for people who did actual research and looked behind the scenes info
and are going to present it to me in a way where I don't have to do any work.
I feel like that's what I'm doing when I scour video after video.
I'm looking for the more things than just the whatever.
Women are gay.
I suppose if it is down to everybody's covering something and if it is Game of Thrones,
I would react a certain way after watching it.
I wouldn't watch reviews first.
And then based on my reaction, I didn't like it.
So I wanted to see all the ways in which it sucked because I'm not going to watch it again.
So I would find somebody detailing everything.
But then I'd also want to know how they fucked up.
Alt-Shift-X got us covered.
No, no, fuck Alt-Shift-X.
You got to go with Preston Jacobs.
Alt-Shift-X is fucking...
He's the fucking bargain bin.
Fucking watered down Preston Jacobs for the dirty degenerate masses.
Yeah, like me.
Like me.
I've never watched any of those books.
So it's perfect for me.
No, Alt-Shift-X, he only talks about the show.
I spit on him.
That's not even true.
He made a fascinating video about the extended lands.
That video fucking ruled.
You know what?
You're right.
It actually does rule.
All right, there we go.
I have a vlog that's going to come out soon where I talk about this.
But one of the most important things that's extremely difficult for you as a content creator
to put yourself in the mindset of is the fact that the audience has not seen your video yet.
When you title it, I have this problem where I always try to give my videos a title that
makes the most sense for the video, which doesn't matter to the audience because they haven't
seen it yet.
When they read the title, they will not know what the video is.
So I can make the title basically anything and then once you click the video, then you'll
understand what it is and you'll go, oh, okay, now I see how the title pertains to this.
But like, you know, and so I think that with people are looking for information on a show,
they don't know before they click if your video has any original or unique information.
They're going to watch it to find that out.
And so even if it has no original or unique information, it's going to get watched because
people are looking for that and they can't know if you have it or not until they watch
the video, which is why you end up watching 25 fucking videos and you think half of them
suck because there's so many people who are just spamming every single, everything that
is popular, anything that their SEO manager tells them this is the thing to talk about.
They're going to make a video regardless of what information they have and you just have
to be the guy who had the most unique take or just the best made video so that people
will actually say, wow, this guy was actually good.
I'm going to subscribe to him.
But like, if you concern yourself about it, like if you're too hung up on everything I
say has to be unique, you're missing out that there's only two kinds of audience members
who are going to see your video.
It's either somebody who's watching everything that has to do with the show you're talking
about, or they only watch you anyways, which means that they're not going to hear any of
that other shit.
So if you only have like the most unique take and you don't focus on any of the outer details,
then maybe those people who are watching absolutely every review will watch yours and
think, okay, this one had something unique to say, but they would have watched it anyways.
And if they're not that person, then they only are watching your channel and they don't
hear any of that other shit.
So what's your suggestion?
What's the way to operate then to capture that?
Just say whatever you want to say and don't worry about what anybody else is saying.
You mean in like the title and thumbnail?
No, in your video, just don't think about what anybody else is saying because it won't
affect you.
It won't matter to your audience at all.
It only matters to you because you want to feel original and you want to feel like they're
not copying people.
But your audience won't perceive it at all.
They're only going to perceive like what the video is in and of itself.
And if the video is good, regardless of if it repeats points from other people, then
that will be what's recognized.
I suppose the most important audience to capture on YouTube, as sad as it may be, is specifically
that demographic that isn't just watching everything about the show nor your own core audience
because you've already got those people just by making the video.
It's that other demographic that like you just aren't reaching that you need to in some
way like clickbait into the video or I don't know, like convinced to watch where they otherwise
wouldn't have.
That's through making the video really good or like clickbait-y stuff or whatever.
I suppose thinking cynically from like a business perspective, that's like the most important
demographic to appeal to however you can.
The funniest thing to me is like my brother Vic, he watches Jeff, mother's basement, pretty
regularly and hates it.
But he watches it because Jeff talks about every relevant cultural thing.
That's his gig and Victor just wants to hear about those things so anytime Jeff talks about
anything Victor's consumed, he's going to watch it and just get mad.
Like that's what people-
But he wants to know what's going on.
People don't care if the video is even good, they watch it just because it's about the
thing.
Like who's the, I don't know, like a guy's like Tim Poole or whatever who I'm actually
pretty bored with because I'm sick of news, fuck news, news is shit.
But he'll make a video about any event that happens politically speaking, like in the
world and he'll give his take, I mean who cares?
I'm over it.
Like who's doing that for anime?
Jeff?
And I guess that's it.
Like just Jeff.
Maybe gig a little bit with his like wrap up things he does.
I mean Jeff, even beyond anime.
The anime man?
He covers everything that's relevant at the moment.
Yeah, that's true.
Because that's what, I mean what SEO is, search engine optimization is essentially you just
look at whatever everybody's talking about and you talk about that and it always works.
It will always be the most successful thing you can do.
That's the nature of it.
Is just talk about the thing we're all talking about and I think that Jeff is somebody who's
really good at getting interested in that thing.
I mean you could just say he has basic bitch taste, but like anything that everybody's
talking about he will legitimately form an interest and find something to say about it
because that is what he's passionate about, is being on the money, you know?
And I think for you and I, we have a much stronger like I have to really legitimately give a shit
and I don't about most things, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
So it's like.
Oh dude.
It's like the.
Paul this, this Tim Pool guy.
Seems like he really sucks.
Let's not get into it because my point was I don't care so let's just keep it at that level.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
Well, anyway, I guess I was just going to say that when, when something I care about is
also popular, it feels like the planets are aligning.
It's like the most beautiful sensation.
It's like, oh my God, everyone's talking about it and I have something to say about it.
Yes.
I'm going to ride this all the way.
Like I have to put all of my focus onto this because nothing else is going to be my meal
ticket for the next however many months this is relevant for or.
Indeed.
In some cases.
I mean, not to, not to make a cynical transition, but there was a tragedy recently that happens
to appeal to you.
Oh, not appeal, obviously, but in your wheelhouse of, of interest things, which is of course
the Keohani nightmare.
Yeah, but that's not a good thing.
I'm not saying it's good.
I'm saying it's relevant to Digi because he's a big Keohani fan and.
Well, in the, in the sense that like being relevant is like good for money, but like.
Well, it literally is.
It literally is.
But I mean, yeah, I can't, I can't really deny what Nate's saying because like as much
as it, it really is like, I don't want to say an opportunity, but like I have gotten
a lot of views from talking about it.
Like, I mean, my initial one was just kind of breaking the news story, which I'm like,
I made international news.
Did you guys see that?
I was on the news in like, some Mexican or Latin American country or something.
Yeah.
What?
Why?
Because I broke because of my video on a, oh yeah, I should get the link.
It's on Twitter.
I was like the first person on YouTube to report on the Keohani fire and my video.
Yes.
My there's a clip of my video in a news report from some other country.
So it's like.
That is so crazy that like, I mean, I guess it makes sense.
It's just, it's just funny that like they'd make a, I don't know, be like a news report
and like they would include footage of like a YouTuber talking about it.
Just like a news person talking about the thing, basically.
Yeah.
I mean, isn't that sort of like them like including a clip of like another news network
talking about it?
I mean, I know it's not.
Yeah.
They don't like play a clip.
It's just like, like running in the background as this guy's talking, like he's basically
talking about the fan reaction on the internet, like how people are, you know, how people
are reacting to it and I come up in that, but it's like, so yeah, I can't deny that
like even if my goal is just to, you know, break the news to as many, like the only reason
my point is of course not to call you out or anybody.
I understand.
This is.
Absolutely.
Like, yeah.
The fact that I feel something about something that everybody else is feeling something about
and I'm able to put it into words is, is to my benefit in the long run.
I mean, like, yeah, you know, there were some people who criticized me for the, because
the second video I did the, the one you will experience hurt or whatever.
Yeah.
The damage is coming.
Right.
I monetized, which I had not done for the original news breaking because I thought,
you know, obviously this is, this is not, this is not about me, but the second video
is a creation I made.
It is, it is in the vein of every other video I've done.
It is my creative output and my ability to connect with your emotions is my job.
So it's like on the one hand it is, there were some people who said like, I can't believe
if you monetize this video, you know, when it's about this tragedy and it's like, well,
this is, this is like me writing a book about a tragedy that happened, you know, like you
would pay for a book about 9-11.
You know what I mean?
Like.
We have complicated relationships with tragedies as a society, I think.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't blame you.
It's whatever.
I mean, I don't know.
I mean, you know, just my take on it was like, I considered even tweeting about it.
I was like, you know, I, like after I did, I was like, I don't know what to say.
Frankly, I was like, I don't know what charity to trust.
Maybe they're literally embezzling.
Like, I don't know any of these people.
What am I going to do?
I just don't want to get involved because it seems weird to like a tweet about Edeca
and I kind of felt bad because I'm like, I don't even want to be part of the conversation.
All energy should go to focus on like Edeca and other people.
I, this is like, like, maybe I could amplify like helpful voices in some way.
I don't know.
It just made me a little uncomfortable.
And then like this happens.
It's funny, because ordinarily I wouldn't, and like in a case like Edeca, I mean, I
didn't know about him, but I wouldn't have probably said anything other than maybe just
like, oh, I missed the guy because there's nothing you can do.
He's dead.
There's nothing you can do for him.
In the case of KyoAnnie, it was like, this is an ongoing scenario where there's not
only is there going to be the families affected, but like the studio is going to have to rebuild
a bunch of people are out of jobs, you know, like it's not just about the people who died.
It's everybody surrounding it who's going to need help.
So like, that was why I felt like I had to do, I had to say something like, oh, if there's,
I wasn't going to say anything until there was some kind of action that could be taken,
you know, right?
Like there's no sense in me just making a video to cry about it.
It's like, okay, well, there's, there's a GoFundMe.
It's being done by Sentai Filmworks, who basically licenses all of KyoAnnie's shit.
So I would trust them to, you know, have the right intentions and it seems pretty fair.
Yeah.
It was just kind of like, yeah.
Is there been any, any new information on like the person who did it?
Do we know why he did it yet?
I mean, I'd rather not.
You know, I pulled up an article from the AP, well, I just like, I think his motivation
is relevant just in terms of like why he did it so we can understand.
Well, he seems to think that they had plagiarized his book or something.
Yeah.
Stole his novel or something.
Just some insane shit.
I mean, that's the only thing that people have.
It doesn't sound legit.
I mean, I'd be, I would, I would like someone to investigate this to some extent to find
out if there's any truth.
Obviously, even if it's 100% accurate, disproportionate backlash, obviously, but, you know.
I'm just curious.
Whatever the case is, the guy clearly had meditated this for a long time because the
amount of, like it just so happens that that day, because the studio only has one fire exit
because it's like an older building and they had unlocked it that day because the news was
coming to do interviews with them.
So he would have had to have known that.
Yeah.
So like, he was definitely like stalking them, trying, like he was planning for it, you know.
And I mean, he's fucking insanely ruthless.
He was dumping fire on people as they ran out of the building and shit.
Like, it's fucking crazy, but the reason for something like that could only be something
insane.
Can you fucking believe this happened to Kyoto animation of all fucking studios?
Like, Jesus Christ.
What the fuck?
I mean, okay.
It seems like they were like the least bad one.
They're like the one studio that like really takes care of their employees and like, like
has good hours, good management.
Everyone there is extremely talented.
And this doesn't really matter, but it's like mostly women too.
And it's like, what the fuck?
Mostly women.
They had a daycare in that building.
Oh, God.
I don't think any children were there that day.
Yeah, I heard.
Yeah.
Well, all right.
It keeps getting brought up, but it's still like to walk through that.
You know, even in this moment, I feel a little guilty about even expressing any sentiment
because I feel like I might be playing it up for an audience and it makes me feel uncomfortable
that I'm doing that.
You don't have to worry about feeling that way because everybody is feeling something,
you know?
I guess.
Yeah.
So early into this happening, because I was following everybody who was tweeting about
it.
Director, is there any news on that guy?
Have we heard anything?
Jesus Christ.
I mean, if they're labeled, the reason that they're considered missing is that they haven't
There's like a weird Japanese thing.
They don't pronounce somebody dead until a doctor is pronounced dead.
So missing.
Were they working on season two like right now?
Yes.
I think that's probably why he was in the studio is that they were working on it.
Yeah.
I mean, it's fucked, but there was people saying everybody grieves in their own way
and I was like, yeah, it's always important to keep that in mind because a lot of the
ways that people react to it, I look at and I think, what the fuck?
Why is that what you're focusing on?
Why are you reacting like this?
Right, right.
And then I just have to stop and say, okay, well, look, not everybody thinks like I do.
Everybody's emotional.
Just let them
Let them do whatever they think they have to do.
I saw a great interaction, which was just Demo tweeted like, this is horrible.
And then his follow-up was like something, something, this would a horrific event and
like, what a blow to the industry.
And then someone said like, really bro, you're going to focus on like the industry instead
of the people.
And of course, this is him following his first tweet about like, what a nightmare for the
people.
And Demo's like, we really going to nitpick my specific word choices, bro.
And like not
He responded in such a calm way and was like, come on, bro, we really going to do this.
And the guy's like, oh shit, you're right.
Sorry.
Like it's fine.
I mean, it's been
Way to keep it cool, calm and collected.
You should have been invited by Discord yesterday with 13-year-old Annie Fred, newest member
of the TNCP was running around screaming about how he doesn't actually think that we, that
like everyone's emotions are legitimate because they're worried about  you only care because
it's Kyoto Animation, not because it's people and it's just like, yeah, all right.
I mean, yeah, literally kind of true, I'm not really overly  I should be, but as
a flawed human machine
I don't think you should.
I think that people should only be concerned about things that concern you because if you
try to concern yourself with every single human life on earth, you will just be depressed
all the time.
True.
If it had been like the building next door that was burned down and the people in that
building had died, like none of us would have heard about it.
We have a personal  I mean, many of us do.
I've seen many of  obviously, many of us are big fans.
People take this line about like, yeah, you only care because you're personally involved,
like other things.
No shit.
That's not even a real argument.
That's not like  I mean, I guess you're correct, but what should I not care because
I don't know.
You're only sad because you care specifically about people.
By the way, nobody  nobody attacked Annie Fred.
He's like 13.
He's young.
He doesn't know what's up.
Well, we had a long  there was a long discussion.
Right.
Okay.
He's not admitted to being wrong or anything.
He's 13 in the time, people.
Anyway, the thing is that like, yes, obviously, it would be nice if we cared about every human
life, but there are billions of people and you cannot do something for everyone.
You can't.
You have a limited amount of self.
The first priority of everybody should be taking care of yourself.
Make sure you are in the right place.
You are mentally okay.
You're physically okay.
Take care of yourself.
If something's wrong with yourself, don't worry about other people unless it helps you
to take care of yourself.
Hence the  hence the put your mask on in the airport before helping those next to you.
Exactly.
You just gotta
And then once you are taken care of, you should worry about other people, but like think
about like how much can I give?
If I have to give money, for instance, how much money do I have, who needs it, and what
causes am I  what do I care about?
Fix the stuff that you care about because nobody else is gonna fix it.
Everybody should be fixing the problems that are relevant to them, and that way, every
problem's getting worked on at the same time by the people who should be working on it.
Yeah.
Like if Kill Andy burns down, like I was on Twitter, and there's a lot of people who
weren't talking about it, who don't know anything about it, who don't care.
You know, I follow plenty of people who aren't anime people, and like I just kind of  I
didn't want to read those tweets.
I was like, I only really care about this thing that's happening, so I'm not reading
all these other tweets by other people, and I don't blame them at all.
Why would I  why would they care that 33 people they've never heard of died?
Like that happens all the time.
That's true.
You care when you heard of it and when it's relevant to you.
I almost worry even more about  I mean, I know, whatever, there's no point in comparing,
but like imagine being like not one of the people who died.
One of the employees there who's now permanently burned and scarred for life, you watched your
co-workers burn and die around you, and you  and now you're like your job is gone,
your life is for  and maybe you're like permanently crippled as a result of this one
guy who you saw shouting, die, die in the building and killing people.
What a fucking piece of shit.
I mean, obviously, but  you know, this makes me think though.
I'm sorry, did that happen in
Yes.
That's  what?
Yeah, that's what happened.
Wait, the arsonist was in there shouting, dying.
He was in there screaming, die at the people in there, yeah.
He was not  this was like a very active arson.
He was like in there dumping gas on people.
He lit the exit on fire and then was throwing gas on people as they left the building.
Like
Makes me feel legitimately sick to think about it.
Ridiculous.
It's nuts.
Oh my god.
That's why I'm saying like the reason can only be something insane.
Okay, you know what though?
This is the heaviest episode of the PCP ever by the way.
It is terrific.
Okay, I was just going to say, you know what, on this subject it kind of even relates to
politics as we were talking before, and it's just that like  I mean, the  specifically
I heard about Q&A, fucked me up, then  it's fucked up to even think about it this way,
when I heard about like the director of Dragon Maid, like that he probably dead, like that's
when it was like  that's when it kind of became real, and I'm like something that
I was looking forward to, was really excited about.
I'm like, I will  like I'll probably never get it, and even if I get it, like it
won't be what it was, everything that was in the building, all their work gone, even
if they rebuild it, they're starting from scratch.
And it was like  I thought to myself like, oh, I want a tweet.
I want to like share the information.
But you know, when I ultimately decided for various reasons I already talked about, I
was like, you know what, I think I want my online presence to be like, other people can
talk about politics, totally understandable, totally fair, other people can talk about
tragedies, I get it.
I kind of want my little bubble to be like an oasis of just like positivity and like
a little bit of like, you know, just lighthearted, like talking about video games, talking about
anime, things that we like.
I was like, there's a time and a place for these things.
I think I will kind of craft my online experience to just be a place where people can like
chill and like get away from like stress stuff.
Current broadcast not with standing eyes.
Not counting this, you know, I don't know.
This is a shared group.
This isn't just my stuff.
I don't  like this is  maybe that's me being like a coward.
I mean that we talked about  No, I think that's totally  I think we need stuff
like that.
There needs to be a place for them to  I agree.
That was like why I put out  because I almost didn't put out the newest whirling
dervish episode because like I personally  like that episode was done before the
fire happened.
Right.
I felt really weird about like saying anything other than about it.
I was like, this is the only thing I can talk about right now and it wasn't until I had
out my tribute video that I felt I could post anything else.
It was like, this has to come out first, then we can do  but I was like  there was
a part of me that was like, all right, do I want to post this podcast because it's
still on my mind.
But then I was like, well, what about all the people who would like rather think about
anything else right now, you know, like
I posted my We Agua like the next day and people were like, oh, I was really hoping
he'd like make a video about, you know, the Kill Annie.
First of all, I don't have time to get that out before this.
Right.
But I mean, that's just the sentiment.
I get it.
That's what's on everybody's mind.
I think I saw one person like criticizing you for like talking about something else.
Who me?
Yeah, like they wouldn't have imagined that you could have  you would have recorded
this before you heard that news or something.
Yeah.
Well
I don't remember where I saw that.
It was a comment in a discord.
It's another case of like everybody grieving differently.
Like there are some people who I totally get why you are just going to be upset that anybody
cares about anything else because that's always how it feels.
It's like when your like parent dies, like you are not going to be interested in hearing
about anything that anyone has to say because you're going to be completely focused on
this thing that nobody but you has a reason to really care about, you know?
Right.
And it's just like you have to face the fact that we all have to reserve our grief for
when we need it, you know?
Like I don't
Sometimes I think about
There was a mass shooting 10 minutes from my house a month ago.
And when I heard about it, my reaction was like, wow, that sucks.
The world's a shitty place.
Even though it happened right near my house because I don't know the people involved,
mass shootings happen all the time.
If I'm just depressed every time there's a mass shooting, I'll never not be depressed.
But like when something that's really relevant to me, like this happens, it's like, okay,
the walls are coming down.
Like I can't control this emotion.
This is  that's kind of the point of my video.
It's like sometimes it's going to happen directly to you and that's when you're going
to feel it.
And you know, a fascinating thing happened to me recently, which was just me and Michelle
went to Kings Island, a big roller coaster water park place in Ohio.
Pretty fun.
Pretty good time.
Did you make a vlog?
I should have.
No.
I took the pictures.
I don't know.
I didn't post them on Instagram.
Maybe I will at some point.
But it was just that like the first thing that we did was Michelle and I went on like the
first  it was like a wooden roller coaster.
And it was  I don't know.
The first one to go on or something, Thunder  that might be the wrong name.
But like as we're getting on it, like Michelle hates roller coasters.
And I'm saying to her, oh, this is a wooden roller coaster.
Like these aren't as bad.
Like we can see a diamond bag.
Oh no, no, no, no.
Wooden ones are the worst.
Well, okay, at the time I wasn't  the shaking you get on a wooden roller coaster
feels far worse than the sleek experience of a metal.
At the time I was not thinking about that, have not been in a while.
So we're in line.
Michelle's very nervous.
I'm like, no, it's fine.
Like this isn't that big of a roller.
It's going to be fine.
We get up in the front of the line.
Michelle's still nervous.
We ask the guy there.
It's like  we ask the guy like in the line, hey dude, is this  like she's a little
nervous.
Is this roller coaster bad?
Of course, we aren't thinking this is a jaded man who works at an amusement park.
And he says to us like
If I were you, I'd have done that specifically because like, yeah, I'm going to ask this
guy.
Obviously, this guy doesn't give a shit.
He's just going to be like  he's going to be like, yeah, it's fine, don't worry
about it.
Don't be a pussy.
I was kind of thinking that at the time.
Yeah.
And then, you know, it's going to put her mind at ease.
That's what happened, yeah.
And then she's going to do the thing.
I'm like, it'll be fine.
Well, okay.
It's going to be fine.
Ultimately, it was fine.
But when we get on, there's a moment where as we're on the ride, the guy said like,
yeah, this is the first roller coaster you're supposed to do.
That's what he said.
Now he meant of the serious roller coasters there because there are kitty ones that you
can do too.
But anyway, we're going on it.
We're going up and up and up on the thing for the first drop.
And as we're like halfway, Michelle just leans over and she's like, wow, we're really
still going up, huh?
And the answer was, yep, we're still going up.
And it just feels like an eternity as we climb.
And the realization dawns on both of our faces as we look at each other that this was more
than we had bargained for.
And as we go down that first hill and I see any anticipation, any, you know, feelings
of possible trepidation, turn into sheer pain, sheer agony, any feelings of possible reconciliation
out the window, well, that the screams, you know, and at first I'm like, yeah, this is
fun.
My stomach was, was like holding it together at first for the first dip or two.
But then I turn over and I see just the, the actual agony, the actual not a joke pain,
pure pain.
This is not a joke, like wanting anything but to be doing what's doing there on Michelle's
face.
And my first, I lost my nerve and then I felt sick and I was like, this is not fun.
This is not fun anymore.
And and then I actually felt deeply emasculated that my girl is in such pain and there's nothing
I can do to help her and we just have to endure until we get to the end of this ride.
It was a very negative experience for that, like 30 seconds at the end of that ride and
we get off.
What a bunch of pussy shit I'm hearing.
I just, all right, we get off and Michelle was very unhappy about, look, she recovered
like real fast, but in that moment of being on that ride, it was like the, if you could
crystallize her emotion, you have pure crystallize anti fun in, in some sort of gem and that
I would sell it to the highest bidder.
Somebody hates roller coasters as much as I do.
Clear that she is, she is, she's your girl.
She's your girl.
Now I went on to go on the metal roller coaster and had a grand time.
I was too scared to go on the biggest one, Diamondback or whatever it is.
But the other, like the loop to loop, it was easy.
What difference does it make to go on the not as bad one versus the super bad one?
Like they all are the same.
It's always going to be the same.
I disagree.
I think a wooden one is a bad choice.
It was a bad choice because you'll get waist, you'll get waist sicker.
I think Michelle would have actually been much better on like the metal one I went on.
Like it was even bigger because the shaking on a wooden one is so much worse.
Okay.
But this was my point.
Like the helpless feeling I felt looking at Michelle was like similar to how I felt
when I heard the news about Kew Annie.
I just felt like such, I kind of forget the point I was making it first, but I think this
was it.
What a strange, what a strange comparison.
You think so?
I, you know, I forget exactly what I was trying to link up, which two ideas I was trying to
connect here because that story was too long, but, uh, oh, you know what?
I've got, I've got another story.
I wanted to report here to the ladies and gentlemen on the PCP, which this one's shorter
and much more fun.
So me and Michelle are just, we're going into the, we're by a university of Cincinnati.
I forget what we're doing there, picking up some stuff or whatever.
We park next to a famous landmark in Cincinnati, Toppers Pizza, where, uh, you know, Grace
was here.
Uh, we ordered some yesterday just for a little snack.
It was fun.
It's, it's.
You're a dog.
I tracked my calories.
I was a little bit over, but it's fine.
Uh, uh, but it, um, it's like the staple of drunk college kids at four AM.
You go to Toppers Pizza and you get their breadsticks and you dunk that shit in marinara
sauce.
That's what you do in Cincinnati.
If you're a college kid.
So that's the, that's the vibe.
So we happen to be parked.
I just, I just got a break in and say that yesterday I made my best, I made my masterpiece
keto pizza.
Oh really?
I made the ultimate keto pizza.
The secret was I use Arlo's recipe, less egg, more xanthan gum, ultimate crust.
Shit was crispy.
It was legitimately crispy and I couldn't be more pleased with Arlo Keto.
No, but one time he posted a, he posted like a low car.
He was doing like, he was dabbling in low carb and he was like, Hey guys, hey guys,
you know, like store bought like cauliflower pizza crust, they just don't do it for me
anymore.
You know, I just can't get off to that shit.
I need the hard stuff.
Yeah, right.
I got my own.
So here's the best recipe I found, yeah, almond flour and fucking coconut and whatever.
And he was right.
It was base Arlo knocks out of the park once again.
Base Arlo.
All right.
Thanks man.
Listen, this is what happened.
So we pull up, we're parked in front of Toppers.
We're getting in the car to leave.
We went and we didn't go to Toppers.
We just have to be in front of it.
However, next to us, a car pulls up and blocks us in so we can't leave at the moment.
We're like, okay, we got to wait for this guy to go.
He gets out of his car, walks into Toppers.
He's wearing a hat and sunglasses and we're like, well, dude, I mean, we're like, what
the hell?
We're trying to leave here.
Um, well, you know, a few seconds past, we're like, hopefully he'll be back soon.
Looks like his car is still running out of the store.
He comes back.
He's kind of hustling.
He gets in his car and he drives off and we're like, okay, we can go.
Okay.
Out of the Toppers bursts a woman who comes running looking back and forth and is like,
where did he go?
Where did he go?
Well, I lean out of the car window and I say, uh, ma'am, he drove off.
What?
Like, what happened?
What's the deal?
She says that man robbed the store last week and just came back now and threw a roll of
toilet paper at us and then ran away and sped off in his fucking car.
This man had robbed this store the week before and came back a week later specifically to
throw a roll of toilet paper and prank them in some way before speeding off to adventures
unknown at Toppers fucking pizza and Cincinnati.
What's the deal with that?
Why did he do that?
That's what he, um, any, any thoughts?
He robbed them.
Well, maybe he thought they were unsporting about it.
I think that's probably true.
Um, just one of the strangest things I've seen, then we just drove off.
And that was the end of that, but, uh, fascinating event.
I don't know, just like a tall, well, I don't know, middle-aged white guy hat, like looking
to be incognito, uh, just came back and pranked her story had arrived the week before and
off he went.
I wonder about his motivation.
I wonder about what he did later that day.
Uh, he probably put it on his YouTube channel.
He was probably streaming the whole time.
He probably was.
He occupies a lot of my thoughts these days.
Um, but that's it.
I have a, I have a story, I have a story, something that happened to me this week.
All right.
So, um, this is going to be stupid.
Okay.
Um, so I'm, so I'm going to Aldi, right?
Cause they got the best deals, right?
They got the best fucking deals at Aldi heavy, heavy, nowhere can you buy heavy cream for
less per quart, uh, than an Aldi.
And you know, that's where you get, uh, that's where you get, uh, my, the ultimate energy
drink, uh, gridlock extreme red, um, 99 cents a can can't, you can't beat it.
You just can't beat it.
So, so, you know, uh, I'm like, okay.
So I leave the house, right?
I'm all right.
I'm going to go catch the bus.
There's like, I take a bus and I catch another bus and it brings me there and then I take
it back.
That's the route.
Right.
So I get, so I get on the first bus and I realize as I'm going like, oh shit, I didn't
charge my phone, my phone's dead.
So I want to have Google maps, whatever.
I know how to get there, right?
So I'm like, okay, but I know how to get to Aldi.
So I take the first bus to, you know, the place and I stop and I'm waiting and I'm
waiting for like half an hour.
It's taken forever.
It's bullshit.
And then finally I'm waiting for one bus, but another bus comes.
I'm like, this bus has gone the same way and it's not that far.
I bet it'll take me to like the same place, right?
So I get on that and I go for a while and it drops me off at, uh, Sullivan square or whatever
there's some, uh, mart, mart, whatever, the, the, the stop, let's say Sullivan square.
And so I'm there and I'm like, shit, this isn't where I was supposed to go.
And so I'm just like, but you know what, I, I have a keen sense of direction.
I know generally where I am.
This has worked out for me before.
This strategy has, has yield, has borne fruit.
So I'm just like, I'm just going to start walking in the general direction that I'm
pretty sure Aldi is in and I'll probably recognize some landmarks on the way there.
So he did a full magta.
I mean, yeah, I mean this, you know, I'm prone to this kind of thing.
So I just start walking and I just start going, Vapors 3 available now, StComics.com.
Um, so, and I just start walking and, and I'm going for probably like, I'm going for
a while and I'm like, I don't recognize anything.
So we duck into a vape shop, right?
Of all places.
A haven from the heat of the, of the cool world.
Right.
It's like a, it's like a pocus, a Pokemon, no a fucking Pokemon center.
You dive in and recharge your batteries.
Yeah.
Right.
All right.
And I asked the guy like, the guy behind the counter, I'm like, Hey, do you know where
the Aldi is?
And he does not know what I'm talking about.
And I'm like, you know, the grocery store and he's like, Oh, stop and shop.
And I'm like, uh, yeah.
So I, so I pretend to be interested in him telling me the directions to the stop and
shop.
Of course.
I pretend that I'm going to take any of this and use it.
The right thing to do.
So I, so I, I humor him for a minute and I'm like, okay, thanks.
And I'm like, I turn around and I walk back to the station.
I'm just going to go back and wait for the bus.
I'm going to wait for that bus to go the other way.
I'm just going to go back to the first stop.
Um, so I get on, I wait for a while.
I get on what I think is that bus.
Turns out it's going the other way.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm actually going the wrong way, but I'm like, okay, whatever.
It'll turn around, right?
I'll get back to where I started eventually.
So it's going, and then I think that, wait, I do recognize this landmark.
I have seen that Bank of America kiosk.
I have seen that CVS before.
I know where I am.
So I'm like, I hit the fucking strip on the side, right?
So I get off the bus and I'm like, sweet.
And then I walk to where I think the bus stop is at this place.
And then I realized, no, I have no idea what this place is.
This is not what I thought it is.
I'm lost and my phone is dead.
Oh no.
So I'm like, okay, cool.
So I just, I'm just like, you know what, I'm just going to start walking.
So I just, I just start walking and wonder, right?
I'm like, I'll find another bus stop eventually.
Um, I go like, I go up and down like a couple of times.
Uh, I pass the bus stop.
I'm like, no, that, that bus stop looks bad.
Look, it's, it doesn't look like it's, what is it?
Stop for an express line.
I don't want that.
But then I finally settle on it.
So wait, and the express line comes and I'm like, Hey, are you going to such and
such square?
And he's like, no, you're going to want that bus.
And he points to a bus that is one stop down.
It is there.
Like I must run to the stop across the street.
I must beat the bus to it.
I barely do.
I jump on that.
And I'm like, are you going to such and such square?
This is the bus that I just got off, right?
It's the same one that I just jumped off thinking.
So I'm back on the original bus, which is whatever.
Anyway, turns out somehow this does in fact get me back to where I started.
And then I wait at the original place.
I wait for the first bus that I was supposed to take in the first place.
I get there.
It takes me to sort of near the Aldi kind of, I get off in like, I'm
within like a couple blocks of it.
I have to like go through a chain link fence.
There's the, luckily someone tore a hole in it.
So I'm able to, so I'm able to dive through.
This is like the fucking odyssey.
When does it end?
I have to ask a guy, like a mailman.
I'm like, hey, do you know where the Aldi is?
And he like looks up on his phone.
He's like, yeah, it's that way.
So then I'm like, okay.
So I go and, and, and I find the Aldi.
Okay, great.
It's closed.
It doesn't, it's temporary closed for repairs.
So I have to go to the stop and shop instead.
You should have looked for that wise man.
Which turns out is the stop and shop that this guy was telling me
about, which is right next to the Aldi I was trying to get to.
I should have just taken his advice and followed his directions.
It would have got me there.
So I fucked it all up.
Um, so I do my shopping, right?
I buy my heavy cream, cheapest you can find anywhere.
Except Aldi.
Mushrooms.
Oh, that's right.
No, it was a terrible deal.
It actually was a terrible deal because I got from stop and shop.
So I get my shit and I go and I walk and I feel like again, I
missed the bus stop and I have to walk around several blocks to
find the place I was looking for.
I sit down, I'm waiting for the bus.
And then, and, and who do I see?
Right?
Who do I see coming down the street, but some, but some young thug, right?
Some like criminal, some thought criminal, wearing a Trump make America
great again shirt.
So I pull out my stiletto, my blade and I slip it between his ribs and I
make like a quick sideways cut.
No.
So I have, I'm, I'm wearing my, I'm wearing my yang shirt.
I just have, I'm wearing, I'm wearing my yang shirt.
And I'm like, I'm going to kill this guy.
I'm going to kill this guy with, with facts and logic.
So he's walking by this is he, he gets close and he's like, um, he's like a
teenager, he's like an Asian kid.
He might have been like, could have been 18, could have been like 15.
I don't know, high school college.
And I'm just, so I just kind of turn to him and I just kind of grab my shirt at
the corner and I just kind of like sort of like, you know, you know, you can
kind of like tug it up a little, just sort of like, I basically just kind of
like make a gesture that it like draw his eyes to like the logo on my shirt.
And I just look at it and I like, uh, uh, uh, and he looks at me.
He's on his phone.
He looks at me and he says like something in Chinese and I'm like, um,
uh, I sent all you people back.
What's going on here?
And now I don't know what to say.
I'm like, uh, uh, Yang, like, cause like you're, you're wearing a, and he's
like, cause like you're, you're wearing, and then, and then the bus that I'm
waiting for starts to pull up and, and he's like just staring at me and I'm
like left, I have like a moment, I have but a moment to explain what I was
trying to do.
And I'm like, and I'm just like, cause you know, our shirts got two different
guys and he's like in like a super thick accent.
He's like, oh, oh, and I'm like, all right.
What, what, I got, I got to take this.
He was like, oh, okay.
Or something and I'm like, and I'm like, I got to take this bus.
I'll see you later.
See you at the ballot.
And I made a great friend that day, an ally for life.
Right.
So having, having owned the Cuck servitors jumped on the bus and headed home.
Victoria.
I don't, I wonder if he even knew like, I mean, surely he knew.
And this is like exactly the story of the like, that meme of like the two guys
walking by each other.
Once is like, howdy.
The other guy like cries to himself and then he like goes back home and blogs
about how he owned the libtard or whatever, uh, you know, in that, in that exchange.
He's just like, just be muddled by your attempted communication.
And then here you are claiming victory, the moral victory, if nothing else.
I, I, I, he went home.
Yeah, I'm sure he had a long hard think that night about what he really
believes and what his priorities are.
I've no doubt.
And what really makes a great nation when you really get right down to it.
Yeah.
So that was my adventure.
Fascinating.
Um, yeah, uh, anyone else, you know, I'm just, I'm just going to say, I've
heard that Chinese people, uh, uh, have a hive mind.
And I think that your attempt to convert one of the drones was unsuccessful in
this particular exchange, but also explains, you know, why, why he was
unable to communicate.
The queen wasn't there.
This is my, this is my understanding.
I mean, I wonder, I mean, I wonder what, just, you know, I wondered like, why
was he wearing that Trump shirt?
Does he know what it is?
He probably knows that it's a Trump shirt.
Like he's probably knows like, here's the theory.
Here's just a theory.
Maybe he's wearing it not because he like loves Trump, but because like, maybe
he just acquired it in some way and that is just like the president.
And so maybe, maybe he, maybe he just, maybe he just had the shirt, right?
Maybe his parents like Trump or something and he just had this shirt.
Maybe he does know what it is and he sincerely likes him.
Maybe he like thinks it's funny.
Maybe it's hard to say.
Maybe he's like a big memester.
Um, but I think it's highly likely that he probably didn't recognize my
vaporwave Yang logo.
Probably, probably.
Um, cause I, you know, it's that, it's that sunset, not pulling too
well these days, uh, I mean, this is a kid.
He's probably not that politically engaged as well as like, his English,
his, I mean, maybe his English is better than I, he would have led up.
Then he led on in his like one and a half words that he said to me.
Right.
Um, but you know, just really, really makes you think, really makes you think
about what's going on in the world.
This is a power of political discourse.
Ladies and gentlemen, there's always, you know, I just think that there's a
lot of things going on in the world.
Like there's always something going on and like, you know, world leaders are
real, they're, they're keyed into it.
Like they're always paying attention to like what's going on in the world.
And this is something that went on in the world.
Certainly went on.
It qualifies for that.
And not much else, but yeah.
That's right.
Ben, uh, there is an Aldi near my, my house, uh, that Munchie visited.
Yeah.
Um, and he was bemused to find a, an Aldi specific, uh, energy drink called Dark
Thunder.
Oh, was that it?
Was that at your place?
Was that a, he was an, okay.
He told me about that.
He told me about Dark Thunder.
And okay.
So I wonder, right?
Cause the thing about Aldi is that Aldi is one company that branched off of a,
a parent company that split into two.
And in Europe, they're like Aldi East and Aldi West.
But in America, like I, I might be getting this little messed up, but like in Europe,
they're like Aldi East, Aldi West in America, like Aldi East is just Aldi and
Aldi West is drum roll, Trader Joe's.
What?
Like, like, yes, that's true.
Trader Joe's related to Aldi?
They, yeah, they are split off from the same parent company.
But they're nothing alike at all.
That's why they split.
They had a fundamental philosophical difference and they couldn't reconcile it.
They couldn't reconcile.
I think it's like two brothers that founded the company and like,
that's interesting.
Yeah.
And, um, yeah.
So, you know, and like one of them, you know, one of them, one of them,
one brother leaned left and the other leaned right and they couldn't reconcile
the differences, which is what I don't know the difference and ended in a boy.
Sound familiar Nate.
Sound like a tail is all this time.
Indeed.
Only my, yeah, fair enough.
Yeah.
So, you know, which one, which one of you is Trader Joe's left or I don't know
the difference between the, like, which is which, I don't know.
But okay, fine.
I don't know the difference.
More like Trader Joe, more like, yes.
Okay.
But now I wonder, okay.
This is your story has some holes in it.
According to wikipedia, I was thinking, okay, my details don't matter.
Right.
Um, so I was, so I was going, if, if the Aldi had been open, I would have gone
in there and immediately looked for dark thunder, but it didn't get the chance.
But now I wonder, hmm, if this was at a European Aldi, maybe then, if this
Aldi doesn't have it, maybe if I went to a Trader Joe's, they would have dark
thunder.
So that'll be my next intricate web.
Yeah.
It might be.
Keep us posted.
I mean, I'm in it.
I'm in it.
What are the holes in my story?
Uh, well, that Trader Joe's was originally a Californian grocery store that
opened in 1967 in 79.
It was bought by Theo Albrecht, who owns Aldi North until his death in 2010 when
the ownership passed to his heirs.
Um, maybe those heirs were the two brothers that like split us.
There are two, the two brothers do own the two different Aldi's.
Like it was founded by a pair of brothers and they did split it into Aldi
Nord and Aldi Sood, but the guy who owns Aldi Nord just happens to also have
owned Trader Joe's, but it's not that it's the same.
That's enough of that.
Okay.
You guys have little, uh, little in America, little LIDL.
It's a very similar Europe.
No, no.
Wait, it's, it's basically the same as Aldi, but, uh, spelled slightly differently.
We have BJs.
We have BJs and that's sick.
I walked by.
Okay.
So as I was, as I went after I went under the chain link fence, uh, to get to Aldi
or Sopin Shop or whatever, I walked by none other than an ocean state job lot.
Oh yeah.
Right.
But the thing about this ocean state job, it was completely boarded up and I
shit you not, right?
Okay.
Imagine an open state job lot.
Like, you know what they look like?
Like they got a big front wall and there's like a big, like sort of opening with
like what I probably like some fucking, uh, automatic doors, right?
Some sliding automatic doors.
You can imagine the entrance way to an open ocean state job lot.
This one, it was like, it was a brick wall.
Like there was no, there was no recession, just the entire thing that would have
been like the entrance way leading to the sliding automatic doors that would
enter into the store had been entirely covered.
Someone had just brick and mortared over them into a solid brick wall.
Dude, that is a basic bitch Minecraft build.
You have to switch up your blocks.
You can't just be using bricks like that.
I mean, it would have been, probably would have been more energy efficient.
Just use crap.
Indeed.
Well, cobblestone.
Ben, I'm reading about Aldi and I want to know how you feel about the fact that
while Aldi is the cheapest grocery store with the best prices, the guy, Carl
Albrecht, who, who owns, uh, Aldi sued is the richest man in Germany and the 21st
richest man in the world while the brother was the 31st richest man before he died.
Um, well, hey, what can you do?
I mean, we all use Amazon.
Yeah.
You know, it's, it's bad, but there's no such thing.
There's no such thing as ethical consumption under capitalism.
So, you know, it's damned if you do, damned if you don't.
Fair enough.
Um, and they're just, I mean, that had the deals on the heavy cream.
Forget about it.
It's like, it's like, it's like a dime less per tablespoon.
That's not true.
That's an exaggeration.
Um, one might say that the low, low prices are able to be so low because of the
strengths of the competitive market.
Any thoughts?
Um, I mean, it's a little reductive.
I mean, probably, how can you, I mean, you could say that, I mean, but this,
this is a, this company was formed in the, the, you know, the market.
Yeah.
So like, it's the way it, yeah, it's the way it is.
I mean, you, you could say that about any company, like any company, however good
or bad, whatever strengths or weaknesses it has, you could attribute those things
to, you know, the competitive market.
Remember when Nate was like, I don't want to do politics on the show.
I get to say, I say, I say one thing, I just make one mild point.
Give me a fucking break.
One wild point that is a question that has huge ramifications.
It could lead to a massive discussion.
I know, I know.
But then I wonder, is it best to just, you know, let everything go unchallenged?
I guess.
What do you mean unchallenged?
That's what I do.
I mean, I fundamentally disagree with much of what you just said, but I guess I
just won't say anything because I, I don't want to argue about it.
Well, well, Nate, well, if your goal is to not talk about politics, then I would
say that that is the only thing you can do, um, in pursuit of that goal.
I guess.
I mean, what are your, what are your priorities?
Well, but what's to be done when one hears political discussion that they
disagree with, but they also don't want to talk about politics.
Do what I do.
There's no way to win.
I just ignore it.
If I, if I contended every single thing I disagreed with on this podcast, there
would be nothing, but that it would, you know, do your right.
You're better than that.
You're better than me at that.
Absolutely true.
I need to get on your level.
Well, I also just feel that way all the time about every interaction I have with
anybody.
It's like, if I stopped this to nitpick everything they said, I would, there
would be no end.
This is all that we would be doing.
I do that a lot.
And I want to stop.
I want to not do it anymore.
This is a personal issue.
I'll work on it.
You're right, guys.
You're right.
Do we want, do we want to transition topics?
How about to voice mail?
Well, I have one.
Okay.
Well, kind of, I don't know how much we want to talk about this, but
speaking of politics, kind of, not really.
I was just going to say that I fell down the, the destiny well and I watched
like a million destiny debates.
Oh no.
I, I really, he's, he's good.
I think he's really good.
And I don't agree with him on a lot of things, but boy, I sure do hate a lot
more people now.
I've got, I've got a juicy one.
This isn't really, this isn't political.
This is, I suppose, a cultural issue, but it's one thing I see destiny get
attacked for all the time and I could not be more with him on this subject.
And it is that everyone shits on destiny for being ostensibly in the
sense that he has no moral objection to the consensual adult incest.
And I listen to the video, I listen to the video where he debates that the guy
he's debating it with is so stupid.
Nobody, no one has ever raised to me why it's like morally, like, yeah, okay.
This is not, okay.
If you're looking for like a really robust argument for why it's not wrong,
you're not going to find it here because the guy he's debating, it's incapable.
He's barely even capable of stringing a sentence.
He will literally say a thing.
Destiny will quote it back to him word for word and say, is that what you're
saying?
And he'll say, no, I didn't say that.
And he does it over and over and over.
I don't know about any specific, I don't even, I don't think I watch
any specific video, but I see this come up a lot.
That specific video is really frustrating, but it's also really just okay.
People cannot understand the concept of like, of like, he can't, he cannot understand
like the, the process by which an argument is made people have so much trouble with
this issue and they, whatever they get all mixed up.
Let me just state my case because I think, I mean, Destiny, we're totally in
agreement on this does involving yourself in incest in my humble opinion.
Like pretty much fuck up your family life in a major way permanently.
Absolutely.
That being said, does a person who's an adult have a right to fuck whoever they
want or not?
I say yes.
Therefore it's not my business.
Whether people choose to engage in consensual adult insight.
I have no moral objection to it and I cannot find any reason to what people
who say, but people get so on his case about this, like it makes him like a fucking
idiot.
Is this a contentious issue?
I feel like probably people are just trying to mess with.
Yeah, it seems like it to me.
I see people use this like it's kind of like the way people just throw it.
Pito, they say that like, Oh, Destiny is like pro incest for, you know, I could
imagine, I could imagine that people are just scorned by the fact that Destiny is
really annoying and so anything they could potentially do to attack him.
Destiny, extremely annoying, much of the time, nonetheless.
I don't understand why people find him annoying.
I really, I really don't get it.
Yeah, I really don't get it.
The, the reason they find him annoying is that, Hey, the constant just barrage of
insults that he throws at people, he doesn't really really, he will, he will slip
some in like if someone, if the person he's arguing with slipping them in is being
like really, really, I find him very patronizing to listen to.
To the people he's to be extremely patronizing.
He also constantly recontextualize what you're saying and, and like just changes
it.
He changes what you're saying into something else on the fly constantly.
I don't, I don't agree with that.
Did you watch our debate?
Yeah.
You didn't feel that he was literally proving my point as we were arguing.
You're retarded.
You are fucking retarded.
I'm sorry.
Did you?
Not that I don't already think so, but you're fucking retarded.
I don't think most people think that you came out on top in that particular debate.
And you know what?
Most people are stupid and they didn't understand the point of the debate because
he changed it to be about something else.
The thing, the thing.
Well, yeah, I thought that the whole point of the debate and what it turned
into was like, it was sort of, I didn't understand why it needed, like, I know you
like, you went on there to talk about dick.
No, I did not.
That's the whole point.
He made it that way.
It was not about dick at all.
The, okay.
Hang on.
What can you, can you state the point of the debate then?
Yes.
So I understand.
Okay.
What happened was that I had made a video criticizing the debate he had with dick
where I said that I thought dick was correct in, cause dick's argument had been
you put words in people's mouths and you argue like an asshole.
Destiny continually deflected this and made the conversation about all this other shit.
And he put dick in a position where he's arguing with him about like stuff that
destiny has clearly done a lot of research and has very particular points
about and forcing him into an argument he wasn't prepared for cause he's not
showing up to argue about this, which is proving the point.
Dick had no fucking idea what he was talking about.
It doesn't matter because that's not what the point was.
The point of the argument was just that destiny argues like an asshole and
makes it about other things, which is what he did.
What kind of an argument, what kind of an argument is that?
Do you even have like, what do you mean?
The argument is that he argues like an asshole and that's the whole fucking point.
What's the point of going on his show to debate him about whether or not
who cares what the point is?
Who cares what the point is?
That's what the argument was.
The argument is you argue like an ass and you make the conversation about other
things, you constantly divert what the person's saying and you put words
in people's mouths and that's exactly what he did.
So I accused him of the same thing and then on Twitter, he, he wanted to
bring me on the show and he wanted to argue with me about Dick.
I told him, I'm not interested in having that argument.
However, I will argue with you that you put words in people's mouths on
the basis of this tweet where you did exactly that, where he took what I had
said and he reframed it in a way that was not at all what I was trying to say.
And so I said, let's argue about this tweet.
So I went on his show to argue about that tweet.
What was the tweet?
I don't fucking remember.
This is ages ago, but it was that I had said something where I chose my
words very carefully and he found an interpretation of it that was not what I meant.
Look, I do think that as a man who debates a lot, my biggest criticism, and
this is a common thread for me, I say it all the time, is I find Destiny, he
engages in the kind of debate that is kind of like, who can win with
the information that you bring to the table and look, that's fine.
I don't, I don't care.
But I do wait, wait, wait, wait, it's the kind of, it's the kind of debate.
Yes.
Where like he's trying to triumph over the other person in that particular debate.
And like, I get it.
What I like is when people try to be as charitable as possible to the other
person, and he definitely does not do that.
No, he tries to opposite.
He tries to find.
He makes your argument into the worst version of it that it could be.
And most people don't catch it.
Like he'll say, you say something, he doesn't mean he's factually wrong.
It's just the particular lens.
Well, it can mean that he's factually wrong.
Like when in the case of my tweets, he literally reframed it as something that
was not what I was saying.
Like I said one particular thing and I only meant what I was saying.
He responded by extrapolating from that something that he wants me to be saying
and said it back.
And I said, that's not what I said.
That's just literally not what I was saying.
You have just reframed it into something else.
And so I went on the show to argue just that point.
And in service of arguing that point, he was trying to break down the exact
semantics of what the words I said could potentially mean, what
interpretations there could possibly be of those words.
And to say that, oh, it's, it's, I'm not misrepresenting you if it could
potentially mean this.
And in order to do that, we had to get down to the bedrock of what each of us
thinks winning a debate means.
And because we had a disagreement about that, then, you know, basically
in order for me to prove that he was misrepresenting me, I had to present
that winning a debate can mean more than one thing.
And he disagreed with that.
And a lot of people disagreed with my idea of what winning a debate could
mean, but that had nothing to do with the argument I came there for.
I came there just to say that he's putting words in my mouth, which he was
doing demonstrably, but the debate becomes about something else because of
him using exactly the tactics I'm talking about, which is to divert the
conversation to be about something else.
Ever watch Thank You for Smoking, because the whole point of Thank You
for Smoking is that the idea is to win debates by framing things the way
that you want them to be presented.
Because when people are right about the facts, you've got to change the
conversation to something that you can win.
And I think that's basically pro-debate, and it's so obvious what he's doing
because he will constantly drill down through anything you say until you
call him out on something he can't respond to, and he immediately changes
the subject, like he'll instantly make it about something else.
He'll ask you a different question.
He won't, he'll divert.
And it's like, when you see it happening, you just go, Oh, okay.
So you're a piece of shit and you're not worth talking to.
Like that's, Oh, I get it.
Like you just want to, you just want to be able to say you want an argument.
You don't actually care about having a conversation.
I mean, that seems to be the currency he travels in.
I find, I mean, all right, I'm going to, I'm going to open myself up to criticism.
I don't know.
I don't know what the like popular take on destiny is.
Um, my, uh, I like him.
I think his arguments are generally pretty good.
And I feel like what he's mostly doing is taking another person's argument
and just like poking holes in it and like dismantling it and like showing
how it doesn't, a lot of the people who destiny argues with are retarded.
And so yes, he's going to come off as just being right most of the time
because he's arguing with fucking retarded people.
Like he's arguing with people who are just wrong about, who don't have
any facts whose, whose position is completely unsubstantiated, who really
don't know how to argue and he's blowing those people out of the water.
And that's obviously going to happen.
And the reason he's got popularity is because of when he blew out John
Tron, who I was going to say sounded like a fucking idiot because he didn't
know what he was talking about.
And like, um, people want, I mean, people want, they want it from destiny
because they want to be able to talk about how he bodied this celebrity, how
he's, oh, he's, he's fucking taken names.
He's, you know, he's taken people to task and like, yes, if you agree
with his politics in general, it's going to be gratifying to watch him
make a bunch of dumb people look even dumber.
But like the tactics he's using for that are just inherently obnoxious and
faulty.
And it's like, I don't care to watch somebody beat up on dumb people.
Like I probably agree with destiny on most things he believes because
he's pretty well researched, like he's trying to be correct.
But like he also says things like, um, you know, I think conservatives
are such a problem that I would endorse violence against them.
And it's just like, okay, well, now you're, now you're fucking crazy.
You know, that's, that's really not, that's really un-nuanced.
I mean, when he literally said that, he said, I would support political or
actual violence.
Well, there are, yeah.
Well, there are arguments for violence sometimes.
I disagree.
Ever.
Not, well, not necessarily never, but he was literally just talking about, I
think that conservatives are just such a problem that we should have violence
against them.
Like there was no, there was no circumstance he was describing it under.
He just said, I mean, if you, yeah, there are some, sometimes it's appropriate.
That's ridiculous to, to make, that's ridiculous to frame as what he was saying.
Well, I, all right.
Well, I mean, I'd have to hear the quote.
It's pretty damning the way he said it.
I mean, look, even if he literally said that he is a live streamer who streams
24, like would he today, like agree even with the words that he said at that time?
I mean, that's the sort of thing that, you know, sure, at the time, maybe he
said something bad, but does he even to, like, that's why you should ask people.
Okay.
You said this.
Do you still agree with this personality is toxic.
It's that he himself is about being an asshole to people.
I mean, he would agree with that.
I think it's pretty funny because like he's, it's funny to listen to people who
knew about him before he became like a famous debater, because apparently he
was basically driven out of the Starcraft community for just being a piece of
shit, like people just I can see why he would have trouble in like team sports
and whatnot, because he was like, he was like a pro Starcraft player.
But he didn't last long.
He wasn't wasn't very good.
And also everybody hated him.
But, but I was I was going to say this this morning, I did finally get around
to listening to the John Tron one.
I'd never I'd never heard it before.
Have you guys heard it?
Oh, I heard a bit that I was like, it is fucking rough.
It is a fucking sh yikes.
It is.
It is kind of a dude is fucking.
It kind of comes off as a white nationalist.
Yeah, a bit.
I mean, he had, I mean, look, if someone presented you facts that you thought
advocate or that, you know, that that showed the racial demographic skew in a
certain way and like, and you just thought they were true.
I haven't listened to the whole thing.
So I don't really know what else you said.
Well, I mean, yeah, I mean, there's there's the facts, right?
And then there's the the way you argue them, right?
Like, like, I mean, some things he said are just factually untrue, like that he
said that, you know, like rich black people commit more crime than poor white
people. That's the one thing that I know, he said in the in the discussion.
There's that there's if that was true, then like fair enough, but if it's not
true, OK, I mean, if that were a fact, it would be a remarkable thing.
That would be really be cause for like what's going on here.
Absolutely. It's made up.
And then and then there's a part there's a part where he draws.
He's like, oh, yeah, crime rates among black people are really high in America.
Oh, you're you're trying to say that's just because of socioeconomic reasons.
Well, look at the crime in Africa.
And it's like, I mean, what's what's that supposed to make a racial point there?
Right. I mean, I don't what is that is the crime rate bad in Africa?
I don't actually know what the what that is implying.
I mean, I don't know either.
But like, even if it were high, yeah, what would be what would be the take?
I don't think there's anything there that would be more of like a poverty thing.
There's there are a couple other things.
But like, oh, there's OK.
There's one part where he talks about global elites, but like I'm going to give
him that I'm going to give him the benefit of the doubt on that and assume
that he wasn't thinking like Jews.
He was just thinking like super rich people.
Although he brings it he just kind of throws this like global elites term
out there at like a weird moment as he says.
And this one I'm going to kind of just assume is weird wording, too.
There's a part where he talks about like, like it wouldn't.
He said, like he just asked him, like, would it be what do you be OK
with like a hundred million, like Mexicans, like suddenly emigrating
to the United States all at once, assuming they all like perfectly integrated
into our culture, like perfectly.
And John Tron has he goes like, yeah, I guess that would be OK.
Just it doesn't usually happen like that.
Usually they have to like they come in slowly over a long period of time
and integrate into the gene pool.
And it's like I'm sorry.
It was like just kind of they'll they'll mix in with the white people
and like they'll they'll become white.
I don't know. That was I don't know.
I mean, I don't know. People people are weird about this.
But like a Mexican culture is not identical to American culture.
If you like American culture and don't want it to just disappear,
it's not crazy to be like, no, I like things about it's just a phrasing of gene pool
that is like, hmm, you know, like, are we concerned about their genes
or just their culture?
I don't I don't necessarily want to have a destiny versus John Tron debate
right now, but like me, maybe American American culture, right?
Like people that move to the United States, they become Americans.
Like, I mean, are we going to act like
American culture is just purely, you know, doesn't because it does exist.
It's definitely real and it's not identical to outside countries.
Well, sure. But like no culture nowhere is culture
identical to culture anywhere else and cultures shift.
And you know, America culture has been I don't see it's whole existence.
I I generally don't.
I don't I mean, I I understand the the emotional reasoning
for like caring about the culture you can't you grew up in or whatever.
But like preserving culture is not that important.
Like in Mayan culture is completely gone.
We just have a bunch of ruins.
It's and if Mayans were around today, they might be bummed about that.
The introduction of the introduction of like new people into an area
doesn't like erase the culture that exists. But it changes it.
Well, all right, I'm just going to take the culture always changes.
That doesn't make an extreme example.
It doesn't matter if you like the way something is.
Why would you want it to change?
Well, it will change no matter what for white add to that.
If you like how it is now.
Well, you can't avoid it.
But you cannot do it as fast as possible.
You can do it slower than that.
Well, but why?
Because you like how things are. That's it.
No, no, Nate, like people who like the way things are don't decide to change it.
It's just that things change around them and they have to change with it.
Otherwise, they have to cordon themselves off and build wars and all that
and and and segregate themselves from from everyone else.
But I mean, but this is this is the question.
It's this idea of magically adding a hundred million Mexicans to the American population.
Like if I don't know, like, what would happen in this example?
If like, are am I going to genocide those people if they don't come in?
I mean, maybe then that'd be different.
But wait, what are you talking about?
The example that you said, like in the discussion where they said, like,
would you just like assuming that they integrated perfectly?
Would you accept, you know, a hundred million Mexican immigrants just into American culture?
I mean, that would affect so many different things that who can say, like, let's say.
Well, no, well, no, because like the the question is like,
what if they just integrated perfectly into existence?
So they're not like a Mexican culture, they're American culture
just with the genes of Mexican people.
Is that the question? Well, yeah.
That's what he was trying to say.
Like that there will be a lot more.
So it's a purely racial question, not about culture.
Right. That's why John Sean Spencer came off as so weird
that he's talking about the entering the gene pool as if that matters.
Like, it's like he's he's not saying, oh, it's the culture.
That's the problem.
He's implying that just having the genetics is the problem,
which is what makes it racist, you know?
Yeah, I don't know.
Do we know everything about every racial group?
They're not identical.
They're pretty close.
I agree.
Nate, just because they're not identical, it's it's if you are not
OK with one of them, that is what racism is.
Like it doesn't matter that it like the fact that you're not accepting
something that is different from you is what you're saying.
The word not OK in a in a pretty loaded way.
I mean, to I don't know, like nobody wants to be have like the environment
around them like be radically different.
No, no, no, we're not talking about the environment.
We're talking about the genes.
He specifically said they're entering the gene pool.
So his concern is that like the like the white race, like your blood,
like your lineage will be polluted by other races, like integrating in and marrying.
Like he's not talking about culturally.
He's talking about literally the genes of non-white people.
He's he's talking.
He's talking about like genetic.
He's talking about like genetic, like like intermarriage and intermix intermix.
Implication there is that genes like non-white genes are inferior to white
genes, and to believe that is what racism is.
You're you're adding the word inferior that I don't think is necessarily
necessarily implied if you like that you're even if you don't think it's inferior.
He didn't say.
Just to think that that you, for any reason, do not want other races,
genes to be mixed in with the white people in your country.
No, no, no, I don't think that's I don't think that's not even true.
I mean, he would he was saying it's not true.
Look, if it takes take Sicily, Sicily has an identity.
Let's say that we add the population of Sicily only in Chinese people to Sicily,
that we just do that.
OK, Sicily is now changed.
Is it OK to be like, damn, you know, I mean, I thought the people of Sicily
like they were pretty cool the way they were.
I mean, no, Nate, Nate, Nate, I'm talking about genes.
I'm talking about genetically.
That's what I'm discussing right now.
Even though these Chinese people act the exact same way as the people in Sicily.
Yeah.
The only difference is that they now have Chinese genes.
If you're not OK with that, that is what racism is the idea that you're
you're adding this not OK as in like think they're inferior or one
can prefer a racial group.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
OK, OK, to prefer one race over another is what racism is.
That's what I'm doing.
I'm doing I'm doing a TV commercial.
I'm filming in front of, like, a very dark oak-paneled wood panel.
A person with black skin would be muddled into there, so it's not for a white person in this context.
That's not the same thing as what we're talking about.
Yeah, in one specific context is different from, like...
Yeah, in that context, a white person will just pop off the background better.
That's an aesthetic consideration. It's nothing to do with them as a human being.
As is the population of Sicily looking like Sicilians as opposed to half Chinese half Sicilians.
How is that a pragmatic consideration at all?
It's not pragmatic at all. It's purely aesthetic.
Well, the example you were giving there was a pragmatic consideration.
There's a difference between aesthetic...
Okay, in the case...
Yeah, I mean, the pragmatism is the only difference.
You don't think models are chosen for aesthetic reasons when they're doing different shoots?
Nate, what the fuck? That's not even relevant.
The difference is between the pragmatism and the non-pragmatism of the aesthetic consideration in this case.
In the case of the wooden door, it's not your fault that a black person would blend in with the door.
That's just the way that nature is, and you can't help it.
There's nothing racist about not doing something that doesn't make sense.
In the case of wanting the population to look a certain way,
if you want them to look like a certain race, that is what racism is.
If there was a button I could push to convert the race of every Chinese person to Mexican,
I just wouldn't push it because they seem to be doing fine.
I mean, why would you push it?
Exactly.
That would be game.
That makes no sense.
But if you did push it, like...
This seems pretty steeped in the sense of you've grown up knowing that Chinese people from China look like Chinese people.
If they were to change and then a plague hit China, all the Chinese people did,
and then Mexicans came in and now Mexicans are Chinese people.
That loads back in cultural issues.
It's weird and strange and different.
You don't have a preference for one or the other,
but there's no need to get into this.
I'm not making a case that any race is better than any other.
I don't know, I'm just saying there are visual differences
and there's probably some genetic differences on some level too.
To care about that is what racism is.
I'm not saying I want you to understand, Nate,
because I know that when we say racism,
it sounds like I'm basically accusing you of baby murder.
I don't think racism is as bad as people make it out to be
if it's not something you're actioning on,
if it's just your feelings are racist.
If you can keep that to yourself,
go ahead and have racist thoughts.
Just don't act on them.
That is a racist thought to think like,
oh, I liked it better when everyone around me was white.
Now that there's a bunch of brown people,
I don't like it as much.
That is racist.
Regardless of what the consequences of that may be,
whether you really think of that as a heinous thing to think,
it is racist.
I was trying to say earlier, this question.
Nothing about that necessarily implies inferiority.
It doesn't have to imply inferiority.
All it implies is that you prefer one over the other.
You just prefer it.
And if you have a preference, that is racism.
I think what you're describing is the experience of every human being
who's grown up in a particular community.
Yes, most people are racist.
Everyone's a little bit racist.
Haven't you seen Avenue Q?
Okay, so we're just taking the word racism,
and we're just expanding it to just the average human
feels that their particular group that you're up with.
Almost everybody has some racism, yes.
Everybody has some preference of race.
If that's the definition you're using, fair enough.
It's not like racism doesn't mean to be hate crimes.
When you use the word racism, that's a very loaded word.
That doesn't mean that it's not bad, though.
I think it's neither necessarily bad nor good.
It simply is.
Well, it is bad.
If somebody moves into a neighborhood
where everybody else is a different race,
they're going to feel a little naturally
and understandably unsure about stuff.
It doesn't matter what race it is in any situation.
And the people who live there who are having,
they see this new person, different race,
they're going to think, hmm, I don't know about this.
Then it's unusual.
That is just what it is.
I agree.
So over time, both of them will get used to one another
and he will just be a different race in a place
and it will be fine.
I agree.
The thing that I was trying to pose a question is,
if a lot of people in the UK are very, very scared
of Muslims taking over the entire country
and it's going to be a big old brown land
and it's going to suck.
There's been some terror attacks related to Muslim immigration, though.
Nate, you've got to get off the fucking intellectual dark web.
It's fucking you up.
But I mean, that's literally true, though.
Yeah.
Nate, it's way overblown.
It's way overblown.
But I mean, if you could have a demographic
that didn't have any of that.
It's not that it doesn't happen.
It's just that it, I mean, immigration,
immigrant status is not that highly correlated with crime.
It's not really.
That is probably true.
So the immigration is not necessarily the problem.
I mean, well, if you could, if you had snapped your fingers
and every person who had immigrated was Christian instead of Muslim,
does that mean those attacks wouldn't have happened?
Well, I mean, maybe not like the specific things,
the specific things that happened might not have happened specifically in that way.
Maybe other bad things would have happened or something.
Maybe, I don't know.
Well, fair enough.
I lost my train of thought and I'm really annoyed.
I haven't been able to say anything, so fuck it, let's move on.
Shit, I want to hear your take.
Well, I can't remember what my take is.
It's just sort of like, I think deep down, people is the same.
This is my world view.
What a hot take.
This is my world view philosophy.
People is the same.
And like, stripped away from like,
the unsureness of like, mixing with a culture that you don't understand.
Given enough time, everybody can get along.
And it's just, it seems, well, everybody who wants certain races to be not coming into like,
yeah, it's just, I don't know.
No, yeah.
I don't know from what angle I'm supposed to be going at this from.
I just think that things stupid.
I mean, I think my take is that, all right, so you got like immigration,
you got like, I think this is the thing.
You got like immigration from a lot of like Middle Eastern and Muslim countries,
you know, into America, but especially into Europe, into parts of Europe.
I think that like, there have been, there's been crime, like there's been crime committed by immigrants and refugees.
But I think that like, by and large, immigrants and refugees are like the victim of a lot more crime
than they are the perpetrators of, like per capita.
Well, that's not really, I mean, to the citizen who lives there currently,
that's not, you know, particularly relevant to their interests.
It's worth considering from a humanitarian perspective, of course,
but that doesn't really impact the question of like, should they, you know,
immigrate more people or whatever.
Um, what do you, well, I mean, what, what are you saying?
I'm saying that from the perspective, if you've got a country,
if they're deciding to like, allow more people into the country,
the question of like, the suffering of those people when they get there,
isn't the concern of those people deciding whether immigration should happen or not.
Their concern is, does this make the country better or worse for me?
Well, that's, I mean, that's, I mean, that's like the whole,
that's kind of the whole point of like, allowing refugees into your country, right,
is that you want to alleviate their suffering.
Um, well, that's the debate.
Yeah, that's true.
The debate is whether you care about that more.
I mean, Destiny would also, Destiny also argues it from an economic perspective.
Like, he's, he, I don't think he was always like this,
but I think like, at some point he became like, fully like,
full open borders guy on the basis that like, immigration is just like,
immigration is like, just increasing the labor resource that's available to like, industry.
And it's like an, like, immigration is like an economic boom.
I mean, frankly, I think that the, I think most problems would be solved
with changes in the education system, because like,
the biggest thing that people fear with immigrants is that they're coming in
and taking the jobs of people who are already here because they'll do it for cheaper.
And the bottom line is like, that's, that should be a good thing.
It just should be that you can do jobs that they can't.
Like you should be, if you are a naturalized citizen who's gone through the education system,
you should be trained for something that an illegal immigrant wouldn't be able to do
because they haven't gone through that training, you know?
Or else, why wouldn't the corporations just use their labor if it's cheaper
and they can do it just as well?
Well, here's the thing.
That's like all those, these like low skill jobs, they're all going to get automated away soon.
That too.
And that's why, that's why we're going to need that yang gang universal basic income dog.
But that's not right now though.
It's not right now, but like, it's coming sooner or later.
At some point, you know, whether it's like 10 years or 50 years or 100 years down the line.
I mean, even a small change makes a huge difference, you know?
Like even just automating one thing is going to have millions of people do that thing.
And like the first ones to go are going to be like the unskilled, you know,
kind of jobs that like, you know, less educated immigrants,
the kind of people they're like, oh, they're taking our jobs.
Those kind of people, the kind of jobs that they're supposedly taking are going to get taken by the robots.
This is this is true.
Hence the bag McDonald's, automizing and whatnot doing the, you know, all that business.
Yeah.
And like self-driving car.
Okay.
Uber, Uber, right?
Uber is a nightmare, right?
Uber is like, is like the Uber is like the capitalist boogeyman.
It is, it is like, it is like, there's no better example of a company that like simply exists
off the back of exploitation of labor.
Like that's all it is.
It's like, they don't do anything.
They just have a fucking app and then they have this whole fucking network of people that work for like
bullshit rates.
They make shit money.
Why do they do it if it's so bad?
Because fucking the economy sucks, Nate.
And people are poor because we have a huge wealth gap in America.
Well, okay.
So, you know, they do that.
Well, I mean, it's also just ignorance to how bad it is.
Like, I don't think the average, I think most people are just viewing it as, oh, I can make some extra
money without realizing the actual toll it takes.
Cause like the real problems with doing Uber is that like it will destroy your car and like
the amount you pay in gas and mileage and shit is going to, you know, it's going to counterbalance what you pay.
Just wait.
Like, like Uber is bad now, but just wait until self-driving cars show up and then suddenly,
suddenly they won't have to pay anyone.
They won't even have employees, right?
They won't, or not even employees, contractors, right?
Independent contractors, like they're currently considered.
So they don't have to give benefits to any of the people that make their money for them.
They'll just, they'll just like, no, they won't have it.
They won't have any fucking costs.
I mean, I guess they'll still have to pay for gas.
They'll have to buy their cars.
This automation revolution, and if UBI was included, would probably solve illegal immigration
as a problem if you couldn't get that universal basic income without being documented.
Cause there would be no reason to come to America if there's no unskilled work.
I mean, there's no way you could get it if you were undocked.
There's no way you could get it if you were undocked.
Right.
So it would just be like, hey, if you come to this country, you really don't have any
opportunities except unless you are like able to, you know, either become a naturalized
citizen or have a more skilled job.
I think that in itself would probably be a huge fix.
Maybe.
Well, they might still, I mean, they might still want to come just because like, yeah,
maybe they're not getting the bag, but there would just, you know, people would just have
like so much disposable income that maybe, I mean, there'd still just be a lot more money
to be paid.
There'd probably be more charity going around, like probably more people who could take care
of it.
I mean, I'm, you know, I'm, I believe in the whole, I believe in the trickle up economics
thing.
Right.
So I think like if people had more, no, people have more money to spend, there's going to
be more spending.
Therefore, there's more money to be made by, by, by like an enterprising person who is
the opposite of trickle down is pump up.
That's how I learned it in middle school anyway, but I lately I've heard it called trickle
up.
Whatever.
Like pumping the tire up.
Yeah.
Like you pumping up the jams.
I have to piss and shit.
We should go to voicemails.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm down.
All right.
So I can piss and shit while listening.
Okay.
Well, I've got it right here.
Let me see.
Okay.
This one is from, I swear this message will give Ben a boner.
That's the, that's the one.
Okay.
Let's see what he's got to say.
Go.
So my mother told me something that she was going to be doing with her current boyfriend
that really made me think of Ben.
The both of them are going to do what I would say is the peak boomer thing this Wednesday.
They're going to go to a new Costco that's opening to celebrate it like opening, but
they're going to go the day before it is actually possible to purchase anything.
Like they're literally going to browse the store and celebrate Jesus.
Jesus.
Opening.
Like why?
I don't know.
It just made me really think like, wow.
We truly do live in a society.
I guess it just kind of made me think of like traditionalists and the plight that they're
in, given the like, I don't know what that's about.
That we're in like they don't have any, what do you call it?
Any rituals or anything to particularly hold on to?
Oh, okay.
So I don't know.
I just found that interesting.
This guy's, this kid's a fucking, this kid's a fucking psycho in the ass.
This kid's got fucking brain problems.
All right.
Forget everything.
Digi, right?
You and me, we're talking, I think yesterday, about how kids these days don't understand,
they think that we're the boomers.
We're only the meme boomers.
This people he's talking about, these are the real enemy.
These are the real boomer.
We have to keep, like you got it guys.
You got to stay focused.
Stay focused on the real boomers.
Don't let them fucking smoke screen into thinking it's us.
We're not your enemies.
They are your enemy.
They'll make fun of us millennials once the boomers are dead and gone.
But for now, we have to focus on the fact that the actual boomers are still around
and are still the problem.
In spite of everything, they're still here.
Don't lose sight of the real enemy.
We're your allies.
You can tell we're your allies because you just made an undertale reference on the slide
in the middle of this thing.
What could be more zoomer than an undertale reference?
Come on guys, we're pandering to the kids.
We're Pokemon going to the polls.
Did you watch the Teen CP episode where the baby boomers, they just read this news article,
this tweet where baby boomers were being given like university courses for like five bucks.
Yeah.
I've seen that going around.
They could just wander around campus and learn and then die immediately afterwards.
Yeah.
The purpose of this for like new jobs?
No, no.
It's just like, oh, wouldn't it be nice if these old people could have the thing that
all the young people actually need?
Could just fucking occupy themselves with some shit.
I see.
That's pretty much what it is.
So, okay.
So I'm assuming that on the Teen CP, they read this article and thought they were like
talking about us, talking about like 30-year-olds.
No, they did not.
There was a little video and they were like very old, very sleepy men.
Well, that's how zoomers view us, the boomers to that.
I wouldn't be surprised if they didn't make the distinction.
I can imagine them reading that and like maybe if they weren't watching the video,
maybe if they just read it in text form, like they would picture me.
It would be me on that campus.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'd imagine so.
On death, on death's door.
All right.
Well, all right.
Let's go to our next one here.
We've only got three, by the way, because there were actually very few submissions
and most of them were bad, but there's a couple that are funny.
Oh, and I'll just say now, before I forget, that we got one voicemail from Quality Women.
Quality Women called in.
Buddy, you rambled too long.
Some of the details were interesting, but like you bored me to tears, so work on it.
But the gist was that he did fuck the milf, but he deeply regretted it.
And it got like weirdly relationship-y, I think, and it was like...
Wait, how old did he say she was?
I think he said she was...
40, I think?
Oh, okay.
Or maybe 50.
I don't know.
Might have been older than that.
I think I remember feeling like that was like a little too old to be cool anymore.
He said that she was a very weird person to be around, and she would just like stare off into the distance.
It makes me like...
Oh my God, did she have fucking dementia?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Fucking boomers.
Oh, fucking boomers.
Dude, he's literally fucking boomers.
Literally.
Yeah.
I feel like she...
I'm not trying to judge anybody, but like if you're like 40 to 50, you're on like an app.
You should just die.
You should just fucking die.
Like a 20-year-old or a 25-year-old, I'm not trying to say you're bad, you can't do that.
It's just like, I think that speaks to like what you've been able to accomplish with your life.
Like fucking like some young stud, if you're like a milf, I get it.
That's fine.
Hey man, who can judge?
Do whatever you want.
Like is this...
Like it sounds like she's pursuing a relationship with this guy.
Shouldn't you be pursuing like some like, you know, self-made millionaire who's like spinning
all these plates and has his shit together and will, you know...
Well no, because that's a capitalist dog and who would want...
He's a dog.
Yeah, a damn dog, whatever it was.
A damn dog.
Thanks Grace.
Thanks.
Okay, well whatever.
Rip.
There's these guys who call in who think that we're like so fascinated with their story
that will definitely play their voicemail.
Oh.
It still has to be entertaining or I'm not going to play it.
Can I...
Alright, this is fucking stupid but I want to do it anyway.
That's just fine.
Okay, there was one...
There's one destiny debate.
It is...
Debate with a female Trump supporter, right?
Okay.
And it is so incredible.
It's like, it's like three hours long and she...
Again, she...
What if he grabs you by the pussy?
Got him.
Yeah, no.
Good one, Destiny.
That's right.
So, but like, okay, she's like a junior professor or something.
She has a PhD in some kind of social psychology or something and she doesn't understand the
difference between anecdotal evidence and statistical evidence despite supposedly doing this for a living.
Whatever.
I see, I see.
So she's really dumb.
Like, she...
She...
For all kinds of reasons.
I won't go into it.
But she comes in and like, she's looking at the chat.
She's getting real nervous at the chat.
She's saying like, oh, oh no.
Like, oh, your chat says they're going to dox me.
Oh, I knew this was going to happen.
I knew I was going to get doxed.
Your chat says she's going to dox me.
But she keeps going and then over the course of the whole thing, she keeps fucking vol...
She says what state she's from.
She says like what school she teaches at.
She says like, yeah, she says like...
She's like, oh yeah, when I was a kid, you know, I knew a girl.
I won't say her name.
Right.
But she raped a boy.
The boy's name was Trevor.
The girl's name was Marianne.
Right.
She raped this boy and then he had to pay for her kid or something.
Like, this is her anecdote story that's supposed to prove that like, that like men aren't...
Like females aren't oppressed in society or something.
And it's just really fucking great.
It's really great and she's awful.
Okay.
That's all.
That's it.
I just wanted to tell her.
I guess we really did make Donald Trumpf again.
Okay.
Let's move on.
Oh God.
I'm mad.
I'm mad thinking about this person.
Okay.
Well, let's calm that with a nice soothing voice from our friend.
I'm English.
Okay.
Go.
Oh, hello.
I'm an Englishman.
And I attended the RSCK London event.
I love the taste of cock in my mouth.
Sick.
Oh, yes.
Damn.
I'm dressing the chaps and buddies and my pals over in London the other week.
Yes.
I can't believe it.
It was such a good time.
Yes.
I'm blue.
Okay.
Dude.
I bet that guys suck the dick in London and France.
So I don't know if this is a hot take or not, but like, is this what we've come to?
This is the quality of the voicemail that makes it onto the show.
I thought that was hilarious.
Do we not live in a society?
I guess we don't.
I guess fucking, oh God, what was his name?
Hey, I like that guy.
Who said that we live in a society?
He doesn't afraid of anything.
Agree.
Who was the guy who said we live in a society just a minute ago?
Like five minutes ago?
That was his long name.
I swear this message will give Ben a bow.
Yeah.
Well, I guess he was wrong.
I guess his thesis was wrong.
Okay.
All right.
Well, the good news is we've only got one more.
Bottom of the barrel cast.
This is from Koji Sama, apparently.
Okay.
46 seconds.
Maybe I'll let people know the time so they know how long they have to endure it.
But okay.
Here you go.
Go Koji.
What do you got?
I'm a pretty hydrated guy.
So about every night around three a.m. as I'm sleeping, I wake up.
I have to go pee.
And the other night I did so.
I went down and I went to the restroom.
I didn't turn the light on because my eyes wouldn't be disturbed by it.
And my dad, you know, the doorknob to the bathroom, you can pick it with a clothes hanger.
So he did that and he got in there.
Okay.
He turned the light on and he saw me.
The light was on?
Because, you know, it's three a.m. right?
Right guy.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
So the next day he bullied me for it.
And I just wanted to know, do you guys think that's an important part of being a man, being
standing up?
You know, I still do it, but sometimes I'm just in the mood to sit down.
What do you guys think?
That is a vital part of being a man and you are not a man for sitting down.
As a man you ever sit down to pee, I would advise you to once you're done, turn around,
dunk your head into the pee toilet and hold it there until you don't breathe anymore.
I mean, I feel like it generates a certain imagery of what he's like if the sitting down
is worth the time that it takes to pee because you never pee for that long.
Like sitting down would feel like a hassle.
See, he was in there with the light.
The light was off.
The dad came in, picked the lock and turned on the light.
He was peeing in the dark because he feels shame.
He feels shame for what he's done.
The reason that he was sitting down is because the light was off because he wouldn't be able
to aim, so he's thinking, oh, I'll just turn on the light.
Why didn't you turn on the light?
Because he said it would disturb his eyes.
I understand the logic of what this guy's doing, but I wouldn't do it.
It's way funnier to just stumble around in the dark and pee on something.
You know, just turn the fucking light on and just through my bleary damaged eyes try to
aim my fucking flaccid tiny cop.
Getting blinded with light when you're used to the dark is a unique feeling.
I don't feel that often.
But when I have an opportunity, I may as well blind myself.
Put a fucking nightlight in your bathroom.
That's a good idea.
Well, that would have taken pre-planning.
The ship has sailed on that.
We've got to deal with the world as we live in it.
You'll never have to sit to pee in the future if you just put a nightlight in your bathroom.
Maybe he can take something valuable away from his experience.
True.
But the real question is, is it a vital part of being a man to stand while you pee?
What's the answer to that question?
Absolutely.
I wouldn't say that one of the advantages is that you get the option.
You don't necessarily have to close yourself off to either one.
However, I do think it is a vital part of being a man that you do get to stand while you pee.
I just can't imagine wanting to sit because it's so much more convenient and cool to stand
and make all that noise.
You can aim your piss at the edge of the sea so you don't make noise if you want.
I think you have just insulted.
It would just feel weird.
You have insulted and alienated our diverse and expansive female to male trans audience
by making this a male necessity.
They can stand to pee if they want.
Yeah, they can let it flow.
They can let it flow, guys.
They can have a funnel.
I've seen illustrations of girls standing to pee, I think, and I can extrapolate from
that that it can be done.
Probably there's some technique involved.
I mean, the girls literally can just stand and pee.
Well, it's about controlling the stream.
You're going to have a trouble with the urinal.
They go straight down.
I would think it would be easier for them, actually, because all they have to do is just
spread their legs over the toilet and go.
As a guy, the stream goes up.
Does it go straight down?
Just go straight down.
What if?
All right.
Let me just hypothetical.
Look, I'm not trying to trigger anyone here.
I'm just thinking out.
I'm just asking questions.
What if?
They reach down to their pubis mons and apply some pressure onto the skin and just pull
up so that all the skin in that area is pulled up.
Would that direct the stream forward?
No, that's what I mean.
That's what I mean.
You can you pull the skin up to direct the stream forward so you can pee forward into
the toilet.
Surely one can simply angle their pelvis.
From your girl urethra, a.k.a. the girl urethra.
I'm just saying you don't even need to angle it forward because you can just spread your
legs a little farther and go around.
You're going to tell me that you're going to stand with your legs fucking spread eagled
standing directly over the bowl.
Yeah.
You might as well just say that.
Yeah, that's right.
In fact, I'm going to do that personally.
I'm going to do that.
I'm going to do that stand over the toilet and pee directly on the wall.
Here's why.
No, you'd have to fucking.
Okay.
To do this.
Digi, I'm going to tell you why you're a fucking moron.
All right.
To do this.
You would have to.
You would have to pull your pants all the way down, right, like to your ankles to do
this.
Okay.
And then you couldn't move over the toilet because the pants stretch between your ankles
would catch on the toilet and you would have to take your pants completely off.
Wait, wait.
Okay.
You could do some sort of squatting position where you angle your butt back while standing
in front of the toilet.
But then you can't see.
What would you be?
What would you be looking?
Looking through your legs behind you.
You have to take off your shoe though.
You have to take off the shoe for this.
Looking through your legs behind you.
Like, come on.
That's just not realistic.
Okay.
We're never going to get to a conclusion here.
We need evidence.
We need people in the PCP viewer base.
We need photographic evidence.
Women, please try this, document the results and get back to us.
Leave a comment.
And then give us a voice mail.
Am I the only one who when I take a shit.
Send us a voicemail of you peeing unless you're underage.
In which case, just make sure you don't say it and then we won't.
Am I the.
And then we're not legally liable.
Am I the only one who when I take a shit removes all of my clothes completely.
Yes.
Well, I do that.
I do that.
On some occasions.
I will.
I will if it's like hot and like I'm sweaty or something, but not just like as a matter
of course, like as part of the shitting process.
Okay.
If it's hot, like usually I like to squat on the toilet ball.
I need to take my pants, my trousers, shoes, socks off, but also I definitely do not do
this in public because the floor in a public bathroom is just gross and I don't want any
of my clothes on it.
Or the nightmare of someone opening the stall somehow while you're in there in public.
I mean, that's a, you know, it'd be over for you.
Here's a question.
I've been called out on this like people have bullied me for this lately and I need validation.
Right.
So you're taking a shit.
You're done.
And it's time.
It's time to wipe.
Right.
If the time, the time has come.
Do you wipe still sitting on the bowl?
Like are you still on the boat or do you like?
No, you stand up.
You stand up.
Yeah.
I've heard that it's literally 50 50.
It's like one of those things that people are all of us.
I like, I don't stand all the way up, but like I stand up like enough.
Like I'm off the bull.
Like my knees are still bent.
Like I'm not like fully.
Yeah.
I stand.
Okay.
How could you?
What are you going to reach into the fucking bowl next to you?
Apparently half of everybody does that.
Literally.
People have.
I don't.
That's insane.
People have been telling me that I'm weird because I stand.
And like, I think that's insane.
Well, look, we all seem to be in agreement on this, right?
Is it like fat people who can't be bothered?
I have no idea.
I just heard statistic that it's maybe there's a physiological difference.
I don't know.
Personally, I'm a standard.
All right.
Let's go full dick show now and ask you the other question.
Over the waistband or through the fly for pissing?
Depends on the trousers I'm wearing.
Mostly through the fly.
Through the fly.
Mostly.
Yeah.
No matter what.
Well, I think, isn't that because you wear pajama pants and you don't have a fly?
That contributes a lot.
Well, they do.
That's the issue.
All my pants have a fly.
I won't wear pants with no fly.
Except for these ninja pants I'm wearing right now.
But no.
I mean, yeah, going over the waistband is definitely easier in pajama pants.
But even in just regular shorts, I'll just undo the top button and go over the waist.
If you undo the top button, well, I mean, do you unzip?
No.
You have to.
Yeah, like surely you're undoing the top button.
Wait, what about with jeans?
Wait, so you're saying that you undo the top button and then you don't unzip the fly.
You just pull it down.
What?
On jeans?
I don't wear jeans.
We're talking about shorts.
Well, if the fabric is stretchy, then it doesn't matter, I guess.
I mean, I would do this on any because to me, if you go through the fly, you have to hold
your cock while you pee.
If you go over the waistband, you just let it rest on the waistband and you don't have
to touch your cock.
I mean, if-
I suppose.
I mean, I hold my dick.
I hold it every time just to make sure I'm, you know, getting everything going the right
direction.
It's like the waistband of the underwear to like prop up my dick so that it, like, you
know, shoots out.
Okay.
Like none of the pants or shorts that I own would be comfortable to like pull down and
go over the waistband.
Yeah.
I basically don't have a choice.
And then, so even if I'm wearing like pajama pants, like I still go through the fly, maybe
that's just out of habit because I do it in every other pants that I wear.
I never really like going through the fly, mostly because when I do, it's because there's
a, well, a lot of pants have zips and the zips usually get me and I just, I just rather
would avoid that.
I'm first of all terrified of the zipper getting in my cock.
And second of all, I don't want to have to like reach through the fucking steamy jungle
of my salty nuts to fucking get my dick out.
You know?
Why do you have to reach through your nuts to get to your dick, Gigi?
What the fuck does that mean?
You have to open up the fly in your underwear where it's like the multiple doors.
I mean, I don't wear boxers.
I wear boxer briefs.
Multiple doors?
Oh, wait.
I see.
Like you got to go through the first fly and then the boxers.
Yeah.
The boxers have like the double fucking, you know, it's like two layers over your cock
and like that area is fucking sweaty, all right?
And maybe, and maybe your boxers have kind of twisted.
So like if you got to go through like a fucking zigzag, right?
Like you got to go through the fly and then like reach over and get to find the other
one and then pull it over to the whole fly.
You wear pajama pants a lot.
Okay.
You wear boxer briefs.
You probably don't have this.
I wear boxers mostly.
There have been incidents where I like I rarely go out wearing like pajama pants, but I have
done it before and they have like the open fly, like without even a button.
There have been incidents when I'm out in public, my dick finds its way through both
my boxers.
That's another reason I don't wear boxers because of the fact that yes, I wear that's
fair.
I wear pajama pants.
And yeah, if I was wearing boxers, my dick would slip out all the fucking time.
Like it would be constant.
It's happening.
Like if you wear pajama pants without underwear underneath your dick will just be out.
There is.
100%.
Okay.
Wait.
That's fair.
What is the difference between boxes and then like boxers that are not as big as other?
Is it like boxer briefs?
Boxer briefs are they they have they don't have like a button up fly like boxers have
a button up fly just like regular like like pajama pants.
True.
Okay.
And they're much more loose.
Obviously.
Oh, I have legs.
Yeah.
Okay.
I have I don't have those.
I don't have like an in-between of briefs and boxes or whatever they're called.
Boxer briefs are impossible to get your dick through the flat.
That's exactly why I go over the waistband.
It's impossible.
It can't be done.
I think we've cracked the code off.
I like it.
It's never been done in the history of humanity.
I like to be snug.
That's fair.
I don't know.
I've always worn boxers and I just feel like I always will.
Yeah.
I mean, I think it really just goes down to what you grew up wearing like my dad wore boxer
briefs.
Yeah, I think so.
You know, like I share in my family, like every all the boys just kind of shared like
a pool of boxer briefs.
Like, you know, that was not like to nominate it like who's our which.
It's just like everybody's wearing them because we're all the same size.
You know, at some point I was doing a load of laundry.
I don't know if they were mine or like I don't bend somehow it absorbed into my collection
or if it's just someone else's.
My box is my life.
My box is just like quantum tunneled over.
Oh, we know this one.
We lived at parents house.
Well, I don't even remember when it at some point.
My history and I feel like it could have been from a complete stranger.
One pair of boxer briefs entered my rotation of underwear and I do occasionally wear that
after I came from, but it was like freshly from a laundry.
I don't think so.
I don't think it was before that.
So I have one pair of boxer briefs.
I will wear on occasion and I'm not a fan.
Not a fan.
Speed.
Digi.
Do you have my slime corp tea by any chance because okay, I don't know.
It's like gone and I can't find it.
I have no idea where it could have been and I thought like maybe did I wear it to your
house one time and leave it there?
I probably would have found it when we were packing.
So I would say no.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, this discussion has run its course and we are out of things to say clearly.
So let's wrap it up lads.
PCP.
Thanks for the money.
Patreon.com.
Slash the procrastinators.
$1.
Patreon discord.
$5.
Bonus episodes.
I think bonus episode 28 will be out shortly after you hear this.
We need to record it soon.
We also got at tbcrastinators, fucking twitter, follow us, speakpipe, leave us more voicemails.
We need more voicemails.
Keep them coming people.
There were slim pickings this week.
Link below to the speakpipe.
Very soon, the most of us will be at BronyCon August 1st to August 4th.
A couple days after you hear this, we'll be at BronyCon before the next PCB episode comes
out.
I mean, when this episode comes out, I will be at Otacon.
So if you're hearing this at Otacon for some reason, I'm there too.
Hey, quick question.
How fun.
Wait a minute.
Most of us will be...
Wait, is this...
Yeah.
Is it like this Thursday?
What?
No, no, no.
No, it's the next Thursday.
Next Thursday.
Oh, okay.
Oh, God, few.
Okay.
Yeah, you're good.
All right, okay.
The PCP, we're all going to be at BronyCon, except Digi.
Well, a couple of people won't, but a bunch of us will be there.
A lot of the regulars here will be at BronyCon.
How do we do a PCP episode if we're all at BronyCon?
I'm not going to have my computer.
You could live stream it from a phone.
Like on Friday?
Well, but that's the next...
Because it happens as a delay, so we have to live stream it the following Friday.
Surely one of you is bringing a laptop, right?
I mean, I wasn't planning on it.
I don't know.
I mean, we'll have to think about this at least a little bit.
We could just live stream it from a phone.
But that doesn't work, because we film on Sunday.
Hold on.
We just saved that episode and released that the next...
Are you bringing a laptop give and take?
I should be.
I probably will have space.
I don't know whether I'm going to use it that much, but yeah.
Sounds like we need to lock this down in some capacity.
I just can't imagine traveling without a laptop.
I don't know why anybody will not have a laptop.
I got my phone.
What do I need?
Well, is anyone...
I mean, nobody's going to be bringing like a digital camera, right?
Like the only camera we're going to have available is a phone camera.
Unless you have a laptop with a built-in camera or just like a webcam.
I don't know.
Every time I went to BronyCon, I had all of my mic equipment, my computer, like the full
setup, like I would come with everything and never use any of it because we never had
time.
Yeah.
I remember that.
All right.
Let's...
Meeting place, the BronyCon Orgy.
We'll livestream from there.
We'll livestream the BronyCon Orgy.
Yes.
That'll be...
Wait, are none of you all bringing like cameras for vlogging?
Like couldn't you just film it on that?
I'm bringing a camera for vlogging.
The small one.
Oh, wait.
We've got the GoPros.
Dude.
We could wear GoPros on our heads during the Orgy.
I mean, true.
I'm bringing my phone.
What do I need a GoPro for?
Dude.
It's all the video camera.
I got a fucking...
Dude, we should...
Okay.
We all got to bring our fucking GoPro.
I mean, I'm going to bring mine.
I mean, look.
Okay.
We can talk about this and discuss things or whatever.
I forgot I even...
I forgot I even have that.
Okay.
I got mine kicking around.
All right.
But that's it, everybody.
Thanks for being here.
We'll see you later.
Speak Pipe.
Patreon.
Appreciate it.
Twitter.
You know what to do.
Links below.
Thanks for being here.
See you next week.
Bye.
Yeah.
What the hell is wrong with me?