Today is my graduation, I've done my dissertation. Even got a hat I can't bow.
Today is my graduation, I'm on the education. Doesn't learn a thing anyway.
I am the best guy ever. And we're here, I'm here with these guys to talk about stuff again.
Here is Ben Saint. Hello everybody. And here is The Hippocrit. Hello everybody.
And here is The Mumkey Man. Hello everybody. What? You all owe me a dollar.
That's a copyrighted phrase. That's the meme that made Ben Saint the man he is today on the internet.
So today's theme is, today's topic is exclusion. That's the real topic.
There's bits of news, there's some exciting news people, which is kind of why I want to do this today.
And it is that both me and Mr. Mumkey Jones have both finished our college experiences.
We have gotten our degrees, mine's coming on like Monday or something, but we're done.
We have just finished our secondary education. Round of applause please.
My graduation was actually earlier today, this morning.
Oh really? It was a shit show.
I'm going full Kanye West and not going to my graduation.
I wish I had that option. My parents made me go.
You know, if I was, I'm sure if I was like a reasonable human being like you I'm sure, and had like completed it within the relevant time frame and done it.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, he just said he wouldn't go unless it's, except that he has to for obligations.
That's right. I've risen, I'm beyond obligations related to school at this point. I've transcended.
But nonetheless, so the reason why Ben and Gibbon here are because they too have gotten their secondary education degrees.
And we tried to get in everybody who had actually finished, who had finished college.
So that'd be, I believe Tom and Jeff.
Where is Tom by the way?
Tom is busy and didn't want to get his mic.
He and him were just having a real shitty Twitter argument that went on forever and was a complete nightmare for everyone.
Tom has time to tweet endlessly at work, but he doesn't want to like go get his microphone because it's at home or something.
Because he orders at work or something.
It was about, it was about art and whether it's the artists, it got out of my control really fast.
But it was intended to be, it was the point was that at work of art, if it has to be explained to get its message across, then that's a failure.
It's the whole, the joker says, if I have to explain the joke, there is no joke.
And I think that, and how I think it's the artist's responsibility to convey with their work.
And that if they, if you can't, you can't blame the audience if they don't get it.
The thing that everybody's getting confused about in that argument is that failure is not necessarily a bad thing.
Yeah, everyone thinks that what I'm saying is, oh, if, if you, the artist, don't make your work 100% accessible to 100% of the audience, if you don't dumb down your work, then you're a failure as an artist, which is just so not what I'm saying.
Well, well, I mean, okay, it sounds like this.
We don't need to talk about this at length.
Right, there's, there's some nuance there.
I'm not, I'm not sure where I'd land without thinking about some more, but this is not Ben's Twitter drama podcast.
I'm just saying the procrastinator's podcast.
We're trying to, trying to talk about how we ruined our lives through various things.
Now we're rising from the ashes like a beautiful Phoenix now.
So, um, let's, uh,
Yeah, that's right.
I've been, I don't know whether Ben has been to like a ceremony with a hat and stuff.
Ben has. I was there. I was at Ben's.
Yeah, I did. I had a very traditional college experience.
Nate, please tell me you have pictures of Ben in the full wardrobe.
Oh, I'm sure we do somewhere.
Yeah, I'm sure they're around.
I'll have to talk to my parents and, uh,
Hell yeah.
Well, I mean, I actually know what, I don't care. Share whatever.
Yeah.
Show me in my goddamn, um, mortarboard.
The, the one thing I, I bet you're sexy as hell wearing that hat.
Yeah, the mortarboard, motorboard, mortarboard.
Yeah, that's what, motorboard.
The one thing I liked about the, the ceremony is that, I mean, it was boring and whatever.
I didn't care.
Yeah.
It was expensive because you had to rent the things to, to wear.
But while I walked across the stage, I was confident and I tipped my hat to the audience
and people said, oh.
And it was all, it was all cool and I was,
Did you fit that hat on your hair hippo?
The hat looked absolutely terrible with my hair.
Sure.
Was it kind of floating like a foot above where it's supposed to be?
No, I bet he just squished down the top.
And it was all squished down the top.
Well, yeah, I have picture.
I mean, I got, you have to, you had to take a, you had to pay for like a professional photographer
to take the picture with you standing in front of a pretend bookcase, holding a pretend thing.
And it was really fake and I really didn't like it and it was really expensive,
but my parents paid for it so I don't give a shit.
But the photo itself is absolutely awful.
I want to see that.
Nate, can I pitch an idea to you right now?
Sure.
I want a picture of hippo in his graduation shit and a picture of Ben
and I want the audience to vote for who looks more dapper.
That sounds good.
It might be tough to get those, but...
I look good.
My crazy hair just does not work with a classical school aesthetic.
That's what makes you dapper.
It makes you a distinguished gentleman.
When you get older, you're probably going to look just like Claudio from Cohen and Camry.
You know what the biggest hair in the game?
You know what I'm talking about? That guy?
That guy is the coolest.
I always think you look like Danny from Game Grumps.
Yeah, yeah, maybe that.
Only...
More small.
SMOL, as Mage would say.
Small.
So okay, who's got feelings about having graduated?
I'd like to put out how there's a...
I mean, in my case, it might be a little different because I found my job and did all my shit
before I finished my degree and so now that I have it, my only goal in life is to leave that job
because it was kind of backwards for me.
I got my job and part of that was saying that I'd get the degree
because you're worth more to your company once you have your degree.
It was also something I promised my parents and it's sort of like an insurance policy or whatever.
But my goal is only to leave, to no longer be doing these things and to do this shit.
I assume that's not the case for you guys and most of the people.
Well, I did get a bunch of jobs directly related to my degree after I got it for like a couple of weeks.
Should we all say what degrees we got?
Oh, good idea. Let's do those real quick. Let's run down.
Monkey, you go first.
I wish I didn't introduce it because I'm ashamed, but I...
Originally, I wanted to be an English teacher, either high school or middle school,
so I was going English major with a minor in education.
And then when I was signing up for student teaching, I realized that it was terrifying and I hated it.
So now I am graduating with just an English degree and nothing else.
So it's terrible.
It's a nightmare.
Wait, what were you originally going for?
I was going to be a teacher.
Oh, so you were going to get like a teaching certification or something.
My buddy John was also an English major and he's done some like copywriting work,
but it's basically worthless.
He's really just thinking about going back now to get like a computer science degree or something.
Oh, fuck that. I'm not going back for shit.
My buddy Scotty was...
He finished his degree as a...
Fuck, what was it?
Music, like a music guy.
He just did like a music major at TCNJ where we went.
And then he just...
He was like half a semester away from finishing that degree and just decided this was a waste of time.
I'm just going back, taking all the computer science classes like my buddy Nate did
and everybody else and just did it and just didn't even finish the first one.
But it was smart. I mean, he ended up...
He did save money by doing it that way, but...
Poor guy.
Anyway, I'm sorry, didn't mean to interrupt.
So let's go, Gib, could you tell us what your degree was?
I got a degree in animation.
I think...
Yeah, that's just what it was called.
It was just animation.
I did three films over three years.
Yeah.
Can we watch these films anywhere?
You can go to give and take...
youtube.com slash give and take and they're on the front page.
Oh, hell yeah.
They're all great by the way.
Those were done for your school in or whatever, I forget.
Spiders are people too.
The tallest man and what's the other one?
The fish at the door.
Oh yeah, that's right.
I love them all.
I'm going to go comment on them right now so then everybody will go there from this podcast
and give me a bunch of upvotes on my comment.
Good idea.
It's a currency that really matters these days.
Hell yeah, fucking upvotes.
Ben, could you tell us your degree please?
Well, yes sir.
I got a Bachelor of Arts with a major in physics and a minor in philosophy.
Oh, I thought you double majored.
I did not, wait.
Oh shit, you're right, I did double major.
Fuck.
Four years of your life and you forgot.
The philosophy major is like the most requirements light.
It had like half the credits requirements of the physics part.
Most of it is just answering the question, what is a philosophy major?
I took like one or two classes in it each semester so it felt like a minor
because I was doing so much less work for it.
That's cool.
But you mean you fished in four years and you were done.
I did finish four years.
Yep, I had a very traditional, got in, spent four years and got out when I was supposed to.
And, Mumki, did you also just do it in four years?
I did it in three and a half years.
It's okay, so you, alright.
Because I was supposed to spend my last semester student teaching but I dropped that so I had enough credits to graduate early.
I've never understood what the fuck is a semester?
It's half a year.
Okay, it's real simple.
Every school year, I mean summers are, you know, exempt and there's like a short winter break,
but there's two semesters a year from around September to around the start of December
and then I believe sometime in January, at the end of January, until May.
And those are just two semesters and within those you take usually around four classes,
so you take like 80 years and you do that for four years basically and you get your degree for the most part.
See, it feels kind of weird, I mean the semester is like just a term that you know, you use.
But the idea that you take multiple classes or you get majors and minor things,
like I don't know whether that's a thing over here, maybe it is.
It's because you went to like a technical school basically, right, where you did like one thing.
It was a creative school and I just did animation and that's it.
Well see, that sounds, I mean, I wasn't talking about my experience.
It's like a typical liberal arts degree program.
I know it's just different in different countries, but I think that like the way it works in America,
at least in my experience, is that you go to college and you only declare a major like later.
Sometimes you can declare right away, but you don't have to.
You can spend time not knowing what your degree is for and then like after a year or two you decide what your degree major is.
Alright, let me tell you my degree real quick.
And that's what your degree is in.
Yeah, well did you have another question about that, Gib?
I don't know, it just seems weird because like the only reason you'd go to university is to do a specific thing it feels like.
Oh no Gib, no no no, you don't know how America works now.
You go to college just to go to college.
Yeah, that's right.
Ask backwards as you would say.
It's backwards, alright.
Okay, well let me just tell you mine.
So I'll be getting a bachelor's of science with a major in computer science and minors in interactive multimedia and of course Japanese.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Do you speak any Japanese?
Yeah, yeah.
I always sounded like English to me.
Why'd you say something like that?
People would know English.
He's the only one.
I can speak bad Japanese, you know, so I kind of get it.
So Nate went into the STEM field and the three of us wasted our degrees.
I went into the STEM field, I was fucking physics major.
Oh, I just heard the philosophy part.
It's easy to forget because Ben has no redeeming qualities.
That's true.
I majored in physics and then I went and I immediately after college I went and I was a counselor at Astro Camp which required a science degree.
And then I was like a lab technician at a company that made fucking mirror coatings and I ran tests on samples and shit for like six months.
Yeah.
Yes indeed.
By the way, we're talking about stuff that I got after like job wise.
There was, due to my animations on my channel, somebody came up to me and said, these are funny.
I would like you to write a few scripts for animations that we're working on and I've done those and I've been paid for them.
But I don't really know, like I haven't got any animation work and it's sort of just, that was just a sort of one time thing.
Did those scripts ever become animations?
They pitched them to the things, like they're trying to get pitches together so they can get to a studio say.
Yeah, I was wondering what was going on.
The latest one is Nick Jr.
Oh cool.
Yeah, it's a thing that they're pitching and it's my scripts.
That would be pretty fucking neat if the show got picked up and you got writing credits, wouldn't it?
Yeah, it was funny. When you were talking about that, like I remember I think me and Digi were like, dude this is the coolest, you have to like do this shit, this is the coolest thing.
This could be like legit professional animation cartoons that you did.
It would, but you know, it's kind of a long shot.
Yeah, it is quite a long shot. I felt like everyone blew it out of proportion and was saying, oh look, you got a real job now, you're a real boy and I'm like, I don't know.
Well, but you know, it's just like, okay, let's say that you did that as your job, like you just prepared these scripts for pitches for things.
One of those would probably eventually become a show and then it's just like whatever one that happens to be, that would be the one that was like the big breakout success, even if they were all equally good.
What do you mean one of them would eventually become a show?
Well, I mean, if you're a guy writing pitches for shows, you would think that at some point.
Well, if you're writing for like a dozen different shows, but yeah, I mean, isn't that...
Right, but that's not, we're talking about a particular company came and was like, write us a few scripts and we will pitch them with our show or something.
Yeah, they had ideas for shows and they just brought me on to help write because they saw that I could do comedy.
Well, all I know about it is, is that if Hippo did get a show on Nick Jr., then maybe did you would do an 18 episode series dissecting it?
Yes.
Hippocrates show sucks. Part one.
It's gay.
We gotta check out this new children's show. It looks pretty deep.
Yeah, children's shows are deep, dude.
Well, that's a good question. Hippo, did they pitch it to the hub?
Yeah, the hub is dead, Ben. The hub is dead. It's something else now. It's like Disney.
Disney XD.
I'm trying to think. There was other ones when, I think, there was a bunch of things that they were pitching to that rejected them.
Can I say the name of the company? Is that cool?
I don't think...
Well, I'm asking Hippo.
Well, I can't remember the name of the company is...
Well, the one that I remember, can I say it? Is that okay?
Yeah, sure.
Wasn't it like Dragon Bee or something? Like Bee Dragon?
That's the name of the animation studio that hired me for that.
And they were trying to pitch it to big studios that would help fund and produce it and publish it and all that.
But they're just a small-ish studio that are making stuff.
You did not get that as a result of education. You got that because your work was out there on YouTube and these people liked your stuff.
I mean, that is true, but I wouldn't have made those animations had I not gone to university.
Yeah, that's fair.
I like the time I spent there. I learned a lot of things, which has helped my YouTube as well as just, you know, animating.
Can I tell a little of my story?
Wait, I just want to say that in addition to those real jobs that I had, sort of real jobs, I've also done a lot of work tutoring physics, mostly online, which is a field that there's always demand for.
So, yeah, and I may continue to do that at some point in the future. Hopefully not. Hopefully I'll never need to do it again.
When was the last time that you were doing that?
I haven't done it in quite a while, although maybe a couple months ago I was popping in here and there and like just doing like one or two lessons, just, I don't know, make a couple bucks.
Ben, do you feel like your study of philosophy has helped you a lot with your comics?
With my comics?
Yeah, like trying to, you know, having a deep thing to say with them and all that. I'm being serious.
I think, this is going to sound so pretentious.
Well, it's coming from Ben, so.
Yeah, so of course. I think that your studying philosophy helped me understand just shit in general better and I think it informs my worldview a bunch in a lot of ways.
And so I don't think, well, I wouldn't say that it's had a direct influence on any of my work. It did make me a different person and that has influenced things.
That doesn't sound that pretentious. That seems pretty reasonable.
I feel like philosophy is one of those subjects where people can go through it and they can get a passing grade, but there will be some people who understand what they, you know, will take on what the whole thing has taught them and use it in their normal life.
And then there will be other people who will just, they will pass, but they will not understand what the hell they just did.
I think you could come away from like a formal philosophy education with like wildly different understandings of what it is you just learned.
Yeah.
It's probably a good thing though, right? You wouldn't want everybody, like the whole point of philosophy is to think for yourself, right? You don't want everybody thinking the same way.
It is true, but I don't like pretentious people and there's a lot of philosophy people that seem really pretentious and I like them.
I mean, I know it's not everyone.
I got into it because of totally pretentious reasons. I just thought it seemed like a thing that smart people would know about.
I was like, I want to be a smart guy.
I think philosophy is really cool and I would have, my entered in it if I was thinking that far ahead.
I don't really know what would be involved in that kind of, I mean, I think about philosophical stuff kind of a lot, I guess.
It's one of the things like I hear about like degrees in philosophy and I'm like, well, I can be philosophical, you know, just thinking about stuff without having a degree, but you could do that with any degree.
Yeah, I was just going to say, you can learn anything that they teach you in college. You can learn it elsewhere, but yeah.
Yeah, the intro class I took for philosophy was just reading, you know, things by Plato, things about Socrates, that kind of stuff, stuff that you can just buy yourself and read.
Yeah, totally.
Well, you know, higher level classes in that were stuff like, they got into more like specific things like the philosophy of mind or the philosophy of language.
And, you know, there would be a lot of readings from like, you know, contemporary philosophers on, and it was all like, it's all discussion with no conclusion, really.
Right.
I mean, there are conclusions. Some people have come to their own conclusions, but like it's all debatable, you know, like you can form your own theories about these things if you want to.
It's not like science where like, you know, you learn what it is, and then there it is. And maybe this is all obvious, I don't know.
Well, it certainly makes sense, but it does sound like there were things that were gained from your education here, and Gibbs seemed to be expressing the same sentiment.
How about you, Mumpke, what do you feel like you gained from your experience at university?
Well, I learned a lot about what it takes to be a good author, and that's been a passion of mine since I was like 11, was to write things.
So even though I didn't really get...
Did you do a lot of creative writing?
I did. My senior project, I decided to do a creative project, and it ended up being like 55 pages.
But what's cool about the senior project is that all of the professors in that area read it.
So all of the English professors had to read it, and then I went into a defense where I had to defend my project and explain...
That's like some PhD shit, like our dad had to be on.
Yeah, yeah, pretty much. And they would ask me questions, and I'd have to defend my project, and I did very well, and I'm happy about it, and I'm hoping I can turn it into a full novel.
So I guess that's what I'll get out of my degree.
Like, what was the project? Are you comfortable?
Yeah, yeah. Well, you guys know me. It's inspired by Elliot Rodger, of course, because it's the only thing I ever talk about.
But it was a portion of another work that I've... like a novel that I've been working on.
Was it a 55-page suicide note? They're like, wow, this is pretty well thought out.
You really made it so that the people that you left behind are gonna be okay with your suicide. That's good.
I thought you were gonna say like, oh, you've really painted a portrait of a madman here, and you're just like, yeah, yeah, that's right, painted a portrait.
You guys are joking, but it's almost completely true, everything that you're saying.
It was a manifesto of a school shooter.
A fictional one, though.
Well, sure, I mean.
But borrowing from Elliot Rodger.
Right now it's fiction, but I've got big plans, people, big plans.
I'm just saying it was like a character piece, right?
Exactly.
But yeah, I'm hoping to publish it soon, even if I just have to publish it myself and let everybody check it out.
Okay, but now question.
Sure.
How much did that cost? How much was your education? I mean, you don't have to tell me the exact number, but I'm just wondering, so was it worth the investment, do you feel?
Well, you guys might get mad at me, but I got the presidential scholarship at my college, so I had to pay almost nothing.
Oh, shit.
What do you have to do to get that?
It was based off of my high school GPA and other things I did in high school.
That's a pretty good deal.
I mean, I can't be mad, I can just be pissed off.
Yeah, people get worked up over college debt, and I feel you, even though I don't have that much.
That's why I was voting for Bernie, you know, a little beneath that fucking college debt.
Yeah.
That's Jill Stein.
Okay, well, that's interesting.
So you've got like almost no debt now? You're pretty much good?
Yeah, pretty much. My biggest debt is my fucking rent.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I wish I had picked a cheaper college. I don't know why. I had like, I don't know, the college that I picked to go to, I guess it just fit my vision for what a college should look like, and that's why I wanted to go to it, even though it was way more expensive.
I could have gone to a state college and paid like a fraction of what I did.
Picking out a college is such a fucking trap for the kid doing it, because it's always going to go the same way.
You're going to see a college, and you're going to say, wow, this looks nice, and then you're going to think of like your future there, and like, oh, I'm going to spend four years.
And then when it gets to the price, and it's going to be huge, and it's going to say, well, you know what, I can just take out fucking loans, because this is where my future lies.
This is like where my life's going to be. I'm going to build a future, and I don't have to worry about that debt for like fucking 50 years when I die.
So it's just, there's no way you can make like a thorough, well thought out decision about like what your money is going to get you.
When you're fucking 18, I mean, if we were fucking, you know, like World War II era guys, like we just came back, and we're trying to pick a college.
At that point, you know, like you're probably mature enough to make a good decision about this shit, but we're all, you know, fucking rich white kids basically.
Fucking sheltered millennial 18-year-olds.
Yeah, that's right.
And it's all lies. When you go on a tour, it's all lies. They treat you like you're going to be the most special snowflake at that school, and everything's going to be great.
And then the first fucking day that you're a real student, it goes to shit, and they don't care.
I mean, those girls wouldn't even date me. They just date those fucking chads.
I thought it was part of my fucking degree audit.
Even though I'm so beautiful, and I'm such a distinguished gentleman, they just don't, they don't come.
Oh, no.
Did you just say Santa Barbara, dude? You gotta use the USB.
Yeah, you know, I don't want to talk about my specific history here.
I guess this is a good segue into, like, what, like, the life of being a college boy is like for everyone.
It's a big change from high school.
You, monkey, you mentioned it being worse than high school, almost, or maybe.
Yeah, he did.
That is totally not my experience.
Yeah.
When I'm all fucking sexy like you, Ben, getting laid every night, fuck.
I mean, I can respect that. I have to give you that one.
There's a reason why midway through college I started making mumkey anime reviews instead of going to parties.
Yeah.
You know what, my experience was that there were no parties, because I didn't know the kind of people who had them and hung out an anime club instead.
That sounds way better.
College was a pretty lonely time for me.
I had my good buddies, but I did, and like, well, this was like the first three years.
My last year was a totally different experience than my first three years, which were hanging out with my buddies who were, to this day, some of my best friends.
You talking about anime, playing video games, some of the happiest times of my life where we're just hanging out with those guys.
But was not having the kind of life that I felt I expected to have, you know, like meeting lots of new people and doing those things.
A lot of it, I'm sure, was my fault.
And then, the summer of my, after a third year, I went to Japan.
Oh fuck.
I just went completely insane and just became a hedonistic monster doing things that would definitely get me arrested in America.
And then when I came back, I was a self-described fuck machine.
I just wanted to do these things and I achieved those goals.
And I'm a little sad that I've lost some of that fire just because I've been focusing.
I've diverted my sex passion from that stuff into making anime videos on the internet.
Nate, I'm empathizing so hard right now.
Yeah.
How so?
Well, my college experience was I got there and I was lucky enough, I found, I got a girlfriend in the first month there.
Fuck you.
I know.
I don't know how it happened.
I had a girlfriend for like three years and it was very nice and lovely.
And then I ended that relationship my senior year.
And my senior year was just, my senior year was just this crazy time, this crazy time of just being a, like, just a complete slob.
Just not giving a fuck about anything.
That's when you became the king of fives, right?
It was just a wild fucking orgy every day.
No, it's not true, but it is true.
I fucked random girls all the time.
God damn it, turn them off.
It was beautiful.
And now I'm like, yeah, now I'm like mad.
Now it makes me mad because I'm not in a position to live like that anymore.
And like, I would.
I don't know.
I feel like, I don't know, I just don't, I don't have like a social, there's not that atmosphere in my life right now where like I can be out like mingling with people.
That's all I want.
I want to move to a city so that I can have a lifestyle where I'm going out and meeting people and socializing with people.
So that I can be fucking doing things with my life.
That's why I hate it here in Virginia Beach.
Because it's not, I don't know.
I understand.
I know it's kind of pathetic.
I know it's kind of pathetic to look back, you know, with fondness on your younger years and be like, ah, those were the days.
But yeah, senior year of college was probably the good old days for me.
And I'd like to get back there sometime.
Same, same for me.
Well, it was in the sense that I was, in terms of socializing, was definitely the peak of my whole life.
But in other ways, obviously it was worse.
I didn't even make videos about anime.
I mean, come on, what the fuck?
That's the killer.
Well, my college uni experience was, I mean, my whole school experience has kind of been like a steady,
very slow incline of getting better.
Mostly because I just, over time, got better at talking to people.
Like I had one or two friends in primary school, as a little boy.
In secondary school, I had one or two friends early on.
But as Facebook and mobile phones became a thing, I didn't really catch onto that.
And I sort of drifted away because I wasn't keeping, you know, contact with people.
So by the end of secondary school, I had no friends.
And then I was really depressed and I didn't know what I wanted to do with my life.
Wait, what age is this we're talking about?
It's like 13.
This would be the end of high school age.
So 18, 17.
Yeah.
I took a year off because I was too scared to go into university.
Because I thought it was just going to be the same bullshit school that doesn't actually teach you anything and whatever.
But that was worse because my parents got mad at me for just not doing anything, not looking for work.
And I didn't want to work.
So I went to college for a year and I met some arty people.
And it was kind of cool, but it was, you know, it was different because it was like people who just did art.
And it was a foundation thing.
And I was friends with a couple of those people, but it was, they were sort of not really my people.
They were normie-ish and they were into different sort of things, but it was nice.
I was making friends on my own, starting from scratch.
So after that year, I went on to university for an animation degree.
And since it was animation, there are a lot of people there who liked Egoraptor, John Tron, Game Grumps, Total Biscuit,
all the sort of internet things that I liked and I gravitated towards those people.
And those are like my best friends that I've ever had in a school setting.
Really, like my best real life friends I've ever made.
And I'm still talking to them because it was over time where I was, technology was like,
I was all up in that shit with Skype.
So I could actually stay contacting with them and it's just been, it's just got better and better.
So for me, college, university, that was the best time and it's just continuing to be the best time.
Even though it's finished, we're still talking, we're still playing games.
Are those the guys you play Minecraft with and World of Woe Craft?
Yes and yes.
I hate them.
Well, we don't play Minecraft because we're Minecrafters.
I know that you're a 12-year-old kid, fucking logging on a mom's PC to go play Minecraft with your friends from school.
I probably would if I was a 12-year-old when Minecraft was big.
Yeah, me too.
But the idea that anything has gotten worse after I left is not true at all.
I mean, during the school years, it was like in that one year where I was doing nothing, where I started making pony videos.
And from there, I made the analysis videos and then I met you guys and then that's just gone.
And it's all downhill from there.
It's all uphill.
I like being a video guy and an animator and having lots of friends.
It's all great.
Everything's great.
I'm glad.
Yeah, on the subject of friends from school, I would just like to say that almost all the friends that I had,
literally all the friends that I had in high school and almost all of them from college, I have nothing to do with anymore.
Interesting.
I just haven't held on to any of those except for two.
There's two friends that I hung out with a lot in college that I used to room with them for a while.
Oh, yeah.
I had that weird experience of talking to my oldest friends from primary school when we were little kids.
And I was friends with him the whole way through primary school.
And then on Facebook, I was like, I'm friends with him.
I haven't said anything to him for a decade.
And then I just said something to him.
And he was like, oh, hi.
And it was good that I did it, but we never talked after that.
And I guess it's just not going to happen anymore.
Dude, there was this girl that I was sort of involved in in a very kiddie way.
We were sort of dating, I guess, when we were like, we were like 10 or something and Amelia.
And so I messaged her on Facebook, I think.
This was like two years ago or something.
But at that time, she had moved to Arizona like 10 years before that.
So we hadn't talked at all.
And we had the most, actually it was kind of a lovely conversation, but it was like, God, I don't know.
If you guys have read that manga, Oyasumi Poon Poon, there's like, when Poon Poon was a kid and there was that girl, Aiko, who he was like madly in love with him.
It was like his whole world.
Like they were like so tight.
But then years and years later, he sees Aiko again and she's just like some normie girl.
But like she had just fallen away from what he thought.
And actually, as they talk and get to know each other, they kind of break through that and they kind of rekindle like what they had known of each other before.
But if you just stopped that experience when he first met her and thought she was a disgusting normie, that's where I got to.
That's the point that I reached.
Oh, what a joy.
And then she went on a flight around the world and was never heard from again.
That's right.
Oh, Amelia.
Yeah.
The saddest.
The way that's easiest to make you depressed about school is looking at people's Facebook feeds.
Lucky I never go on Facebook, so it's perfect.
Yeah, neither do I.
But it's like I friended them all at the time.
I'm like, I can't be bothered to delete them.
But then I see that some of them were married, pregnant, graduating.
Dude, my friends are starting to get married now.
It's really weird.
It's really strange.
Like one of my buddy Michelle has always intended to get married and did and that's perfectly expected.
Nothing weird there.
But now my friend Doug, who has been my friend for a long time, is getting married next year.
And he's like, he's one of my brothers.
I can't believe Doug's getting married.
Doug's getting married like next, I don't know, September or something?
Yeah.
It's fucking weird.
But I mean, I like his fiance.
She's a great person.
So it's nothing against her.
I'll be there.
Are you going to object like Shrek?
Stop it!
Don't kick!
Wait, what is, what is, oh god, I'm so ashamed that I forget the actor's name.
But in the graduate, what does he yell?
Mike Myers.
No, at the end of the graduate.
Eddie Murphy who plays donkey.
When he rushes into the wedding.
Doesn't he like bang on the glass and he's yelling something?
Oh, I don't know his name.
Stella!
They parroted it in the Simpsons when Grandpa Simpson wants to marry Marge's mom.
He's like, he's Mrs. Bouvier and he's like banging on the glass in the church.
It doesn't matter.
Dustin Hoffman was yelling the lady's name.
Dustin Hoffman, that's it.
Oh, okay, that's your, yeah.
Anyway, the graduate's 10 to 10 movie.
It was probably Mike Myers.
I thought it was.
Michael Myers, the killer.
He's just like, through the fucking mask.
Hey, okay, so let me tell, I wanted to talk about my experience of going through college,
just kind of in general.
Because things, as everybody knows, things did not end with that fourth year of college.
That was a very good time for me.
Things continued on for years until this very week and they'll be over on Monday.
So you weren't there for like seven and a half years or something?
The grand total was eight and a half years.
Eight and a half years.
I am, I am 20.
Oh God, 26.
Yeah, I'm 26.
That's right.
But yeah, but okay, it was not like I went there the entire full time for eight years.
Okay, so, so I spent four years in the school doing undergraduate stuff and I changed my major a couple times up until sophomore year.
I started out, I wanted to be a doctor when I was a kid, you know, and because I'd watched a lot of blackjack cool anime about a doctor man.
I wanted to do that.
But then like in freshman year of college, I realized that that was too much work.
Ironically, I said, I don't want to be in school for eight years.
That's ridiculous.
I thought there's no way I'd want to waste my life that way.
Jesus.
Yeah, I know.
But anyway, it's not quite that bad as I'll explain.
That was a bad Dick Masterson impression.
I understood it.
Thank you.
Oh, okay, four years later.
I'm not as smart as I think I am.
So four years later after that.
You jackass!
Is that one?
I got to the end, right?
That's from the guy's mom, Angelo's mom.
What? Who are you gay?
Come on.
I'm sorry to talk over you.
I love you, Maddox.
Yeah, I'm sure you do.
Okay.
Four years later, and I reached a point where all my friends were graduating
because they had done things right,
and I had failed like maybe just like two classes,
but really the bigger issue was that I still had like eight left,
which was like two semesters worth.
And so I thought to myself,
okay, how do I do this?
This was followed by several years of me thinking like,
oh, I've only got a couple left and I'll be done.
So I'll just take like one this semester and one next semester.
And of course that did.
I took like one per semester.
Over the next eight and a half years it's been,
and some of them didn't even get counted because I fucked up the paperwork in various ways.
I remember a time when it seemed like you were on the cusp of graduating.
Yeah.
Okay, here's the thing about me.
When I'm not interested in something,
and I'm sure a lot of people are like this,
when I'm not interested in something,
I will put like the minimum amount of brain effort into like figuring it out
and like making sure that everything's on track.
So I continually fucked myself up repeatedly thinking like,
okay, I've only got this, I've only got that.
Okay, I'm done.
That's enough thinking about that and it'll be fine.
It was not in fact fine.
And I ruined everything for myself for many years.
But so my actual life during this time was just working like part-time jobs
as close to full-time as possible, like shitty ones, like stocking shelves.
And I worked at a peer one just like building things
and working behind the counter doing retail and stuff.
It was terrible. It was terrible.
But I believe a year after I had been out of school
and was doing that shitty stuff,
I was taking like one class at a time at various schools in Massachusetts.
That's when Ben suggested that we do a fucking My Little Pony video
and I thought, ah, this is crazy, no one's going to want to see it.
It's all downhill from there.
Yeah, yeah.
And it was just because I was in this shitty position,
because I hadn't finished my degree on time
and was just wasting my life doing this bullshit.
You know, me and Ben were in the same place
and were able to do this, you know, video thing together
because Ben happened to be home and I was there and we did that.
And just ever since then, I've been, you know, finishing my degree,
just taking one class at a time and it's been like three years now since then.
And finally, at long last, have reached all the things that were necessary to finish it.
At that time when we started making videos, wait,
you were still working on that, you had that first internship, right?
Or was it after that?
I think it was, I don't know, I think it was after that.
Oh, I forgot, the other fucking physics job I had
was when I was a physics teacher in Poland.
I completely forgot about that whole year of my life.
Oh yeah, that's true, that's true.
Yeah, and then I had just come back, I had come back from that
and was living with parents because I had no fucking idea what to do with myself.
Right, right.
Yes, and then we made a pony video.
And just ever since that point, I have been saddled with a whole bunch of shit I had to do personally.
Just having to work because I had to pay rent and I had to go to school at the same time
and also wanted to make YouTube videos.
And man, that was a glorious time when we would bust those videos out in one week
and they were due as soon as possible and we became the guys who got them out first every week.
I remember that very fondly.
It was a glorious time.
I'm sorry for asking because I'm not as enriched on my Ben and Nate histories.
It's cool.
So when you guys made your first video, did you already have an audience or did you guys just, you grew it from scratch?
Yeah, it was totally from scratch, yeah.
It was just because you put out videos so consistently and on time that people came and then you grew the audience.
Well, the pony thing was big, so there was an audience waiting.
Anything that was about ponies was guaranteed a few thousand subscribers.
A certain level of viewership.
Yeah, that's true, that's true.
I don't want to go too deep into people's past or whatever because I know you guys are whatever the fuck.
But I know Hippo, I know that your Gibbentake channel has a lot more subs than the Hippo.
So, Nate and Ben, did you guys have a lot more subs on a different channel or just the most you've ever had?
We did.
Actually, it was just about 17,000 by the end.
We had, I think we slightly passed Hippo's channel.
We were always ahead of Hippo once we got ahead.
We guys, like competing against each other or what you guys had?
That was a short period where I was very jealous of the fact that they were all taking me.
But I was jealous because I respected them and I didn't want to feel jealousy, but I did.
Did you already on the scene at this point or were you guys...
Oh yes, he was around before us.
He started that whole scene.
He gave us all the ideas.
Oh, okay. You guys all ripped off Digi.
We ripped off the idea of ripping off Digi.
It was already well-worn ground when we got away.
That's true.
But we distinguished ourselves amid the thronging mass.
The teaming throng.
Yes.
Anyway, that was a whole history thing.
I didn't really want to spend that much time on, but...
Sorry, I didn't want to...
No, that's cool.
I think he's talking about his personal history.
Maybe not.
I just wanted to kind of explain all that so that I could say, when you look at it,
the things that I'm doing now that I want to do, it's true.
I do have a good job that is based on my education and I'm thankful for that.
But really, I'm also just kind of not liking that because, I mean, if you look at my situation now,
I have this job, it's fine.
But the thing that I really care about doing and that I'm by far the best at in life
is making these videos and things.
Okay, do you think you would be doing what you're doing now if you had not gone to college?
Well, I mean, you have to think about it in the full context,
because we've been making videos for like three years,
but I mean, I spent eight of those years, you know, it's been a total of eight doing the school stuff.
I mean, if I just hadn't done school, I first of all wouldn't be in massive amounts of debt.
That'll take me a long time to pay off.
And I wouldn't have had to, you know, kind of waste my time doing this.
I do consider it a waste of time for the most part.
But that's not my question.
I probably wouldn't be doing videos, but who knows what I'd be doing.
It could have been anything.
And the work I'm doing now is totally, I just learned it all myself.
It has nothing to do with any education stuff.
It was totally a separate thing.
So I don't want to say like school is always bad because it's definitely not.
There are definitely good things you can do and use it for.
But for me, it was a pretty huge waste of time, especially for what I wanted to do.
I heard this school sucks podcast, and I was pretty sure the message was don't go to school.
I was the only one playing defense for school at all.
A lot of those guys, unlike us educated folks, didn't even finish school.
Yeah, yes.
But what I wanted to express was the feeling that you need a plan.
If you're going to go to school, for God's sake, the thing I really object to
is the idea of defaulting to going to school and just figuring it out at the time.
Because I really feel like that did me wrong.
Unless you can go free.
If it's free, go for it.
Definitely do that.
The thing is that it's just everyone who has to make those decisions is too young to make them.
Yeah, that's the problem.
Parents, I think we're at a time right now where parents have had such great success.
A lot of our parents have had such success going to school.
It's worked out fantastic for them, and they assume that things are exactly the same.
We'll work out the same way for their kids, and it really is not the case.
Because there are so many more degrees now.
School is so much more expensive now than it ever was when our parents went to school.
The way and the job market is much like, because there's so many people with degrees,
the jobs that are available require more and more expertise in whatever fields
and more and more degrees and shit.
It's a different landscape, and I think it is a reckless thing to do to throw your kids in
and say, it'll be fine, don't worry about it, figure it out as you go.
I think it's way smarter to have a plan and do what Mumkey did basically.
Get your shit done as fast as possible.
If you can do it early, all the better.
It would be better if your degree was worth anything.
That would be a plus.
On the subject of student loan debt, I have a lot of it.
And let me tell you what I've been doing.
Patreon.com slash Benson.
That's right.
Well, so I have a ton of student loan debt, but when I was doing real jobs,
I was paying back some of it.
So I have repaid a certain portion of it.
But since I've been doing internet stuff, since I've been being an artist,
well, here's the beautiful.
I make so little money, and I'm so fucking poor.
I'm so far below the poverty line that it's not even funny.
Not at all.
It's kind of funny.
I'm low enough that I qualify for deferrals, so I haven't actually had to pay back any.
I'm just putting it all off until I'm making more money, and then I'll start paying it back again.
And am I accruing some interest debt?
Yes, it's not a huge amount, but yeah, the amount I owe is going up slowly as this time goes by.
But I can't do it right now.
I mean, thank God, thank God that I've, I don't know, maybe in the future I'll regret deferring,
but I think it's the only option.
It's the only option that'll allow you to keep doing what you want to do.
If I had to pay back my student loans, I would probably have to get a real job to do it.
Patreon.com.
Well, speaking of having a plan, I'll go ahead.
If you had to, like, well, say you stayed at this sort of level of money,
where you were below the threshold or where you needed to pay back any money at all,
would you keep that up forever?
Or would you strive to get more money and then pay it off eventually?
Well, one of the things is Ben and I both owe our parents a big chunk
because they paid for a bunch with the expectations that we would pay it back at some point.
Some of my debt is to our parents, some of it is to the government.
I mean, I want to, if I had money to pay back the loans, I would pay back the government first.
Yeah, me too, because parents won't charge interest, so.
And I mean, not like the debt's not valid or anything,
but to a certain degree, their money is our money, because eventually we'll just inherit it, you know?
That's fair, that's fair.
So you're just waiting for your parents to die so you can pay off your college debt?
I mean, in the grand scheme of things.
In the grand scheme of things, you know?
Yeah, their money, we all have the same pool of money, in a sense.
I don't know. I guess that's kind of how I see it.
Can I ask everybody on the subject of, you know, having a plan, and this might go...
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry to bring you up.
But what you said, that's what makes me feel better about the fact that, you know, like, parents sent me to college.
I picked my college, but like, they let me make the choice.
And I could be upset, like, I could be mad that they let me choose this expensive school and put myself into all this debt.
On the other hand, since their money is my money to a certain extent, I kind of feel like it's both of our problems, like they fuck themselves over just as much as me.
So that's why I try not to sweat it too much, I guess.
Well, I don't spite them for that, but I do think it's not an optimal choice.
I could spite them for that if I wanted, but I try not to.
Anyway, Momke, what were you saying?
Well, now that we're all graduated, I'm curious what your guys' plans are.
Hippo and Ben, or Hippo and Nate, you both want to do YouTube videos as your career, right?
That's right, that's right, up to a, yeah.
As long as, I mean, if there's some way to do that, like, that's what I want to do.
I want to tell my own stories through videos, you know, and YouTube appears to be the best way to do that, so, yeah.
Because right now, oh, yeah, go ahead, Hippo.
Right now, it seems like a good idea, because I know that I'm pretty good at it,
and if I get the right, you know, big breakout video, I could get quite a lot of money from being a big old gay guy on YouTube.
Make a review of roast things.
I do like creating things like writing and animating, so eventually, I'll probably try to make, you know, create stuff.
If not either instead of, or, you know, if not in tandem with YouTube, so.
Create stuff, yeah, I want to fund myself by converting energy into matter.
I want to create stuff, that's where I see my career going.
I mean, I get a lot of money if I could make a machine that creates energy.
Yeah, that's true.
The reason why I'm asking is because I'm now in the position where I need to find a job,
but I have a useless degree, and I'm also, you know, all three of us pretty much have the same sub count at this point,
like we're all about the same on YouTube.
So I'm thinking like, am I going to be as crazy as these guys and pursue this as a career,
or do I be more of a boring guy and get a real job and do this shit like in my free time?
I don't know.
I've been a bit of a bitch, and I have, you know, been working this whole time, full time,
and I sort of had to, but really, I mean, it was my choice ultimately to work a full time job while making videos,
and that's something I did because I'm not the same exactly as Ben here or Digi,
where they're willing to kind of just fucking say fuck it and just like quit their job and just do it immediately.
I don't have exactly as much, I would say, carelessness.
That's a good word.
I'm a little more conservative in my financial risk-taking abilities.
I felt like all the time I was spending doing a real job was...
Miserable? Because I feel pretty miserable doing it.
It's not just that it was miserable, it's that, I mean, some people might see it as more responsible in the long term,
but I'm not convinced that's the case because you can be laid off for no reason from your job that you've sunk countless years
into, and I feel like the possibility exists that you could end up, you know, really regretting your decision to work a regular job just as much.
When you get laid off, they don't take back the money you made, Ben, you still make money, it's responsible.
That's true, but you still end up at square one.
You end up with money.
Well, you have job experience and stuff.
Well, okay, because I actually do feel pretty strongly about that subject, and all the time I find myself looking at guys like Digi,
and this is the negative side of the kind of cautiousness I have with my financial situation.
I think about the last year and a half that I've spent at this current job, and in the last two years, Digi has blown up in a big way,
and it's because he has devoted his life wholeheartedly to making this content, and my current channel has existed for about a year
and has gotten way less content, but again, that's the kind of style of video I do, so obviously I know it's not complete apples to apples,
but all the time that you devote towards doing stuff on YouTube grows your viewership base,
and that leads to more likelihood of financial success, and so it can be a snowball effect where the better you do,
the more content you make, the more money you can make, the more economically viable it is.
So to actually divert yourself to work a full-time job and try to do that at the same time is probably the least efficient way to do it
as opposed to maybe saving up some money and then just going for it, and just going as hard as you can to try to grow to get that base that will support you.
Especially if you want to do, it makes sense to go as hard as you can, because even if you fail, you've got to spend that time doing what you love,
so there's no downside.
But then you're living in poverty, that's a pretty big downside.
Well, I mean, it depends how you do it.
Hey man, take it from me, living in poverty can be a pretty great time if you know how to approach it, you know what I'm saying?
It depends what your needs are, you know?
It's easy to wave it off and say, oh, it's poverty, but why does poverty have to be a dirty word, you know?
Why can't we all just accept it and stop being so fucking classist, you know?
It depends on the situation.
I just want to be able to pay for my rent and for my internet and for my gas.
Okay, but see, if you do the calculations for that, which I have, those numbers aren't necessarily that high, like I could get away,
and this is actually something I did on my Patreon recently, where I tried to calculate how much I would need based on my output of content,
like what the Patreon number I would need to be for me to be pretty sure that I'd be okay.
And I found that $750 per video, because I do it per video,
and I'd post like twice a month.
Well, I know it's high, but that's what it would take for it to be a livable wage and I could do the things I do.
Why is it that high?
For me, $600 a month, and I would be in the black.
Yeah, but do you guys even pay rent at Digi's house?
Of course I pay rent at Digi's house.
I thought he just got the fucking house for free.
He did not get the house for free.
My rent is not particularly high, but I do have to pay rent.
It's about what I was paying at my last place.
I mean, let's just say that rent is like $500, and you'll need, I don't know, like $300 left for various expenses throughout a month,
and then on top of that, there's being able to invest in things that you need and pay off student loans, because that's a lot for me.
So, I mean, we're looking at $1,500 is not a lot of money.
I guess that's true.
If I ever want to start paying back my student loans, which I do, a big priority for me is paying off my student loans.
As soon as possible.
I mean, my student loans, they want me to pay like $350 a month, so that's, I know I could negotiate that down.
Just make less money, just make less money, and then you have to pay less, and there you go.
Well, that's one way to go.
I don't know.
Well, that's the thing, 750 was the target, and even if I don't reach that, then that's, you know, I could probably still live with, you know, some amount less than that.
But that's the goal for like a comfortable way to be.
Hippo, I've always been curious about your plan on living and surviving off of YouTube.
Well, right now, I have a pretty good deal, because my rent at my parents' house is very low compared to anywhere else I could possibly be.
And also, they cook food for me.
So, I really don't have to worry about as much as many expenses as other people.
So, doing the YouTube is very easy, a decision for me to make.
I don't have any work at the moment, and I could spend time doing, you know, looking for animation work.
But it's more fun at the moment to just be doing YouTube with the hopes that it gets bigger.
And if it does, then it'll just work out.
I don't really have a bad situation going on unless my parents start asking for a lot more rent.
Let me briefly return to what I was saying before about, like, if you get laid off from a job and, like, all you've got is you've got work experience left.
And, like, yeah, when you work a regular job, you get work experience, which helps you get another similar job.
And I guess the thought process for me was, I don't want work experience in a field that is not something I want to do.
You know, like, I didn't want to be a lab technician or a physics teacher or whatever.
So, like, getting that work experience is only going to help me continue to be a lab technician or a physics teacher.
That's how I feel about my programming, which I don't care about.
Yeah, so I feel like bailing at the first, bailing as soon as possible was the smartest decision.
It's not a bad idea.
Ultimately, striving to do the stuff that you want to do will be just better for yourself.
You may have, like, financial trouble, and eventually if it gets so bad, you might have to take a normal job.
But I think if your goal is to do stuff that you want to do...
I know that it's going to sound shitty.
I know I could be making more if I spent that time, you know, climbing the corporate ladder or whatever.
But my end goal is not to end up at the top of the corporate ladder.
Well, I mean, obviously not.
That's all I'm saying.
I hear you, and that's fair, but this is going to sound, I don't know, maybe hypocritical or something.
Despite me choosing the safer road and to, like, do a job that will kind of allow me to live okay while, you know, trying to do my other shit sort of in my spare time,
I also feel kind of resentment for people who do it full time because they have so much free time.
And I sort of feel like my way is sort of like the way that I've been trained is the right way to do things.
So, you know, it's shitty, but I'm kind of pissed off at people who have the kind of personality that will allow them to just be like,
yeah, fuck it, I'll just go do what I want.
Whereas I'm over here like, guys, that's irresponsible. What are you doing? That's not the smartest way. What if you fuck up?
Yeah, I'm not sure that I would be doing YouTube if I wasn't so financially stable.
Like if I was on the edge, I'm not sure I would just say, fuck it, I'll do whatever I want.
Although Digi was never that on the edge, was he?
Well, at the beginning Digi was very, you know, up in the air.
He just didn't have much of his own money.
Yeah. And he lived with his parents, so he had kind of, you know, he wasn't going to get thrown out if he didn't make any money,
so he had some stability when he was able to start, which was definitely a good thing for him.
And I'm just bringing up Digi because he's the guy who's made it, you know, he's doing great doing what he's doing.
We're not talking about school anymore.
We have gone off the rails, but school is related to a lot of other things in life, so I still think we're kind of sort of related.
The podcast about being graduated smart boys is all, you know, very civil conversation with smart topics.
I agree. We're all very intelligent, and that's the lesson.
I mean, if some of those other guys are fucking dumb.
If those other guys were here, I really think that the conversation will be dragged down a lot.
So I'm glad that only the brightest of boys can be.
Thank God we're here.
Sivilly discussing just how civil our conversation has managed to be riveting.
That's right. Well, I mean, if you guys don't have anything particularly relevant to say on the topic,
we could address, we could get to the final portion of our podcast.
Wait, how long have we been going? An hour?
About an hour.
Okay, so yeah, so we're people, as you know, at TP Crastinators on Twitter.
At the start of our recording, we put out a little message that's like, hey, tweet us here if you want us to answer questions,
and we will grab a couple of them and see what the fuck is going on with them.
Have we been getting tweets?
That's right. So when I just checked now, after tweeting, we had like 48 notifications here, so that's a good amount of shit here.
So let's see what we got.
Maybe I'll go check those out too.
Do they know who's on the episode?
No, they have no way of knowing.
So it's a surprise. It's like those Wonder Balls with a surprise in every chocolate coated thing, you know.
Can I say one quick thing about this episode in particular, though?
This is the third time I've been on, guys, and I thank you so much for inviting me back again.
I hope to come back many more times.
But like every time I come on, there's always like six or seven guys and it's a cluster fuck.
So it's been really nice this time to have four people, two of which are my favorite PCP and one of which is my least favorite.
So it's been a great mix.
Oh no.
I think I know.
That's all I have to say.
Oh, I think I know.
Yes.
It's been.
It's been, of course.
Okay, so you're gonna like me a lot less after our next battle month.
Oh shit.
I forgot that there's sworn enemies trying to kill each other's best friends.
Yeah, we've tried to keep it civil this whole time.
That's good.
But I fucking hate this game.
The rage barely contained.
Okay, here we go.
Bubbling just under the surface.
Yup.
I'm about to break everything used.
Okay, here we go.
Here's a question for you.
I want to stand closer to the edge and I'm about to break.
All right shut the fuck up.
You won't do what you tell me.
Here's one that's going to be relevant to your interest, Ben, by at Steel Viper 77.
Hey, Steel Viper.
Sure, I know that guy.
Oh, I know that guy too.
Is it the audience's fault if they do not understand a piece of art?
Oh.
I don't know if that one's been addressed.
Yeah, okay.
That's a good question.
Clearly he saw me and Tom arguing about it.
Yes.
No, I mean no.
It's the artist's fault and the artist is not obligated to make his work accessible,
but if the work is not accessible to someone, there's no one else to blame.
There's no one else to blame but the artist.
Who at what?
Is it the audience's fault?
Some people think it's...
What if the audience is too stupid to understand it?
Then if you wanted stupid people to understand your work of art,
you should have made a stupid work of art, you know?
It's your fault.
So then it's just the fault of the stupid people according to that logic?
No, no, you have to make your own...
The argument was flawed from the beginning because it's implying that the artist,
like, failing with their art to reach a certain person is like their goal
and they fail at their goal, which means they're bad.
That's not necessarily the case.
It just means that if somebody doesn't like something,
it's not their fault.
They didn't do something wrong.
Yeah, maybe that's a better way to phrase it.
Well, you know, there are ways to do things wrong actively and sort of passively.
Like, if you don't understand English and someone asks you a question in English,
it's not like you did anything wrong by not getting it, but...
That was my example.
It was like...
Yeah, if a work...
If the artist writes their work in English,
then people that don't speak...
It's not people that don't speak English as fault
if they don't get anything out of the work.
It's because the artist made that choice to write it in a way
that would include some people and exclude others.
And like, everything about making a work is like that.
And it's not a bad thing.
It's just the way it is.
You think you can find that as a failure?
Well, no, not in the sense that...
If I like something in English, it's a failure.
Yeah, this is where it comes in because people have interpreted that word failure in different ways.
It's not a failure in that the artist has not failed in doing what they set out to do,
but in terms of conveying something of value to the audience
or to a particular audience member,
yeah, I would say that the artist has failed in that because of the choices they made,
which is fine.
By writing something in English, they failed?
Yeah, they've failed to convey anything of value to non-English-speaking people.
And like, a certain amount of failure.
A certain amount of failure.
Let me fucking finish this point.
A certain amount of failure is always unavoidable.
So it's not like I'm saying that an artist sucks
or is a failure as an artist for doing that.
Wait, but hang on, Ben.
It's such simple shit to me.
If I intend it, if I only intend for English-speaking audiences to get it
and it is not my intent for French-speaking,
haven't I not failed in my goal?
No, you've succeeded completely.
That's exactly the point that I just made,
is that that's not how I'm defining failure here.
Do we have better questions, Nate?
Yeah, I thought that was going to be a joke and he wasn't going to respond seriously,
but he's fucked up.
I'm just going to do a couple here. These are small ones.
Okay, at GTR Santiago.
Yeah, okay, there we go.
What's your alcohol of preference?
Gin and tonic.
Just like our grandpappy used to drink, right?
Did he?
Yeah, I know he was a big gin fan.
I didn't even remember that.
Well, I'm pretty sure that's what he drank.
Yeah, good.
Apple cider is nice.
That is nice.
Monkey.
I've been drinking a lot of vodka and lemonade.
Are you drinking that now?
I did like two hours ago.
That actually sounds really good.
I wonder if I have any of that.
And I don't know.
I'm not picky, but I like Guinness.
So I like Guinness.
Okay, here's two short ones more.
What's the most extreme measure?
Oh, I forgot. This is by at 69...
Wait, is that 89?
At 89, taqueso.
What's the most extreme measure any of you
have had to take because of the stupidity of others?
No, they're 14 meters.
What does that mean?
The stupidity of others.
You know, I actually, when I read this,
I thought he meant the stupidity of the other procrastinators.
I didn't realize it was so general.
I didn't actually listen to the question.
But yours is the best answer.
I don't even have an answer for that.
I don't have an answer either.
Ben, are you still thinking?
Oh, this is Santiago asking.
Yeah, I see that all the time.
I don't know.
The stupidity of others.
What's the most...
That's such a broad question.
You see, I was going to say something like,
well, there was this one time when Jesse got real upset
about the color of his films,
and we had to talk him down for a while.
I wasn't going to say anything,
but his videos are kind of yellow.
Have you guys seen them?
Oh, no.
Okay, let's move on.
Here's the last real question.
I feel like I can think of an example,
but what's something someone did to me that was really stupid?
I said a mean thing.
People just don't understand that you can fail to convey meanings
as an artist.
It's a real big problem.
Yeah, I had to get in a fucking argument on Twitter,
because Tom didn't agree with me
that the artist's responsibility, whatever.
Yeah, that was gay.
I'm still with Ben on that.
Thank you.
Okay, great.
All right, anyway, here's our real question.
This is the last one by at magos underscore sigma.
What's the real meaning of Christmas?
Because it is Christmas coming up in a couple of days.
And behold, there were three kings,
Martin Luther, Don and Rodney.
Martin Luther was the smartest of the three.
He preached equality, peace, and self-respect.
He was the good king.
Don was a hoopty who got hoopty from a hoopty
while brass and diarrhea all over his crib.
He was a bad king.
I don't know the whole quote.
I'm quoting Charlie Brown's Christmas.
And that's the real meaning of Christmas, Charlie Brown.
It's like the black, like, really racist version.
Yeah, it is.
Oh, Charlie Brown, Kwanzaa.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, the true meaning of Kwanzaa.
Fuck, I was going to say something.
Oh, right.
But forget Christ's birthday.
Actually, do you guys want to answer that?
Any other meaning Christmas?
Is that all you have to say?
Just forget Christ's birthday and that's the meaning of Christmas.
I was going to go on to another point that relates to that.
Okay, we're done with that question.
Okay, right.
There is a more important birthday three days before Christmas
and it is that on December 22nd is the one-year anniversary birthday
of the Procrastinator's Channel.
Right.
Of the release of our first week.
Our first podcast.
It's also my mom's birthday.
Is it?
It really is.
Well, is she the Procrastinator's podcast?
She might be.
I'll ask her.
I'll call her on to the podcast.
Yeah, she really is.
The Procrastinator's podcast.
Monkey is a virgin birth created by the Holy Spirit
of the Procrastinator's podcast.
Yeah, find out.
Get back to us on that.
Like half of my subs are because of this shit.
Oh, really?
That's great.
They mostly came from Digi, but I'll give you guys all credit.
All right.
All right, that's good.
And also shout out to my new microphone arm, which is wonderful,
and I can move my microphone everywhere and it stays in front of my face,
which I'm doing right now.
I love it when you say shout out to inanimate objects.
Yeah, that's what I do.
Shout out to my microphone arm.
It's not like you put a microphone on the end of your arm like Barrett Wallace.
No, you fool.
I'm not Mega Man who just killed microphone man and I got a microphone guy on my arm.
This is a, it's like a metal thing that you kind of screw it as it clamps to your desk,
and then it can kind of swivel and extend the microphone out.
I see.
And it's wonderful.
I can't recommend it highly enough.
I've been using a stand and it was bullshit and I hate it.
This is a thousand times better.
It was like a hundred bucks, but everyone should get one.
It's fucking wonderful.
It was great.
Great.
I think that's enough of that shit.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
Yeah.
We'll tune in next week.
Oh, next week's going to be a very special episode, actually.
We've been cooking up something for a little while and it's going to be a big fucking thing.
Oh, is it that thing?
Oh, it's that.
Oh, man.
We're going to show them that.
It's going to be a crazy time.
I'm really, really excited for that.
What are you guys talking about?
Oh, you'll find out next week.
Everyone here is going to be on that.
We're all involved and it's a couple other people in the procrastiners will be there, too.
And it's going to be fucking dope.
So stick around and we'll see you then.
Wait, can I give a hint?
Can I give a hint?
Oh, you can give a little hint.
Sure.
If you're a fan of Retro, if you're a fan of Gen 1, if you're a Gen 1er for life.
Oh, boy.
Oh, shit.
I am part of this, ain't I?
Yeah.
Yes, you are.
Oh, I forgot I was.
Okay, people.
So go speculate.
Yeah, go be hype.
That's insane.
Go to YouTube slash MomKeyJones.
Go sub to my channel.
Go to Hippo and give them a thumbs up.
And don't go to Nate's channel.
Okay, thanks everybody.
Okay, we'll see you next time, everybody.
Thanks for watching.
Bye.
Yeah.
Hooray.
Yeah, everyone.
I'm supposed to be working right now.
But I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing.
My dick, I'm jerking.
Myself, I'm sucking.
I am an asshole.
I am a stupid.
I've got a deadline.
Don't want to do it.
What the hell is wrong with me?
I'm supposed to be making money.
I'm supposed to be creating money.
Think that the people gladly will pay for artistic genius.
That's what they came for.
Instead, I'm tweeting.
Hashtag repeating.
That's why there's no heat and holes in the ceiling.
Yeah, it's quite the burden.
It's a hard knock life.
Being a genius.