Oh my fucking god, you're still listening to The Pro Crastinators Podcast in 2018.
It's me Digibro, and I'm joined by good ol' boy's best guy ever.
Microphone Jones is over, so please excuse the noise in the background.
We've got The Davoo.
I recently watched FLCL Progressive, and in one part someone says, you need to become
a pro, and he was like, what kind of pro?
I don't know, you gotta decide what kind of pro you wanna be.
And I thought, a crastinator pro?
And then the song started playing in my head.
I wanted to yell to him over the screen, become a pro crastinator.
We've got Tom Oliver.
I am here, and I am queer.
And you are games.
And we've got Munchy.
Wait, you're telling me it's not 2015, and we have Oliver and integrity intact still,
and the PCP hasn't just started a couple months ago, and it's so still gone?
What?
Wait, is this show starting 2015?
I don't think that's accurate.
That can't be right.
We can't be doing this for three fucking years.
The first episode was the very end of 2015, so it will soon become three years.
Oh my god.
Well, it's now an unstructured clusterfuck, like it was always meant to be.
Does anybody have a subject that is burning through their mind, or should I just start
us right off?
Start us right off.
Pop culture is bad.
Go for it.
Yeah, I'm going to talk about, let's talk about how pop culture is bad.
And I don't mean anything, like any individual piece of media is bad, or that people's tastes
are bad.
In fact, I think that people's tastes are a lot better than pop culture.
But what I think pop culture is, is like a filtration system that just puts everybody
to the same things.
But I don't think it's inherent to people that they like that stuff.
What do you guys think?
Yeah.
Well, what's inherent to people, I think, is that they gravitate to the most popular
thing, because it's the most discussed.
Right.
So I think it's just a natural process of people's interaction, and discussing media
and stuff.
The thing is that it's so easy to control.
Like, for instance, with music, I was just watching some analysis video called, When
Soundtracks Repeat Themselves, and it wasn't saying anything I hadn't already known, but
just hearing it reaffirmed by quoting a science book made it like, man, it really made me
think about it.
In fact, people literally, literally like something more, like a song more, because
they hear it multiple times.
Like the more times you hear something.
You're saying this piece of information was more impactful because you heard it again,
A.K.A. multiple times.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, and it wasn't even that I'd heard it before, it's more that I just implicitly
knew this, but like, just knowing that a scientist person had put it in science words
in an academic book somewhere, like she literally was like, yeah, if you hear something again,
you just like it more, because you'll internalize it more, you'll think about it more.
And this is why when a new song comes out that the radio stations think could be a number
one hit, they just play it all day and hope that it works.
They're just like, here, listen to this song every hour on the hour, and you just are going
to end up liking it because you hear it so many times.
Is this applied to everything or just songs?
I mean, I think that anything you hear it probably applies to.
If we watch Sword Art Online enough, will it be good?
I've argued that before.
You'll probably develop a familiarity and thus like a comfort with it.
What about FLCL Progressive?
Can that become good?
Oh, God.
You have to put yourself in the process of watching it again.
I was a pop culture.
Do you mean just art?
Do you mean movies and video games and songs by pop culture?
I mean anything popular.
I think that popularity is an engine that perpetuates itself not on the basis of what
people like, but on the basis of what someone wants people to like.
Bludgeoning yourself with it over the head till you like it.
Just last night, I was having a conversation at the round table about Fairy Tale, to which
one of my conversants said, oh yeah, I didn't like it until around 50 episodes in, to which
the wife came up and said, see, even if that's true, I have to watch 50 episodes to get to
that point.
And I just sort of mumbled Stockholm Syndrome under my breath.
I don't know, man.
I hear that shit all the time about those long running shounens.
People will say, oh, once you get 40 episodes in, it gets really good.
The fact that you even made it 40 episodes in means that your thought process is so fundamentally
different from mine.
I'll tell you that I can't believe that it actually gets good.
The shonen that I watched that totally changed my perspective on all of fiction was called
The Pretender from 1998 to 2002.
It's one of those shounens that are from America and are live action.
And it's about a guy who's super autistic and has genius capacity.
He was locked up his whole life, but he has the ability to, in the first episode, he just
reads a medical book and then can just go and be a fucking doctor now.
That's how good he is at simulation, which is a cool premise, just like any good shonen.
And it's got some very archetypical but likable characters, just like any good shonen.
But it was written terribly.
The same shit happens all the time.
It does things where it'll build up like, oh, his long lost brother for half a season
and then he dies immediately, and then the next season they build up, oh, he's actually
returning, he's not dead, then he actually dies for real.
So it's like, it's horrible, it's tedious, it wasted four seasons of watching, and at
the end of it all I was like, I didn't gain anything from this.
I like the character, I don't need to know what happens to him, he's not fucking real!
Stories aren't real, and if they're frustrating you, fuck them.
Fuck those sympathetic characters you like for the sin of being in a shitty story.
Dump the story.
I was probably like 13, and ever since then my mentality has been, fuck a story!
I feel like I had a recent example of this thing, which is, just the other day, me and
I was, I don't know why, but I thought about Cromartie High School, and I'm like, Michelle,
do you want to watch Cromartie High School?
And she was like, okay, sure.
In my mind I was going through all these loop-de-loops about thinking about how this is the best
show ever.
I'm telling you, this is the funniest show ever, it's the best comedy, it's one of those
anime that reminds you why anime is worth existing, and then we proceeded to watch it.
We watched like four episodes, and I loved it because I love all the characters and I
know everybody there, and there were some great jokes, like in the very first couple
minutes when the guy just eats the pencils, like that's hilarious.
But I got a distinct depression that like, huh, these episodes are not as funny as I
remember them being.
I'm enjoying them, but I can sense that this isn't going over as like literally the funniest
thing of all time.
That's so bad when you show something to someone, and they're just kinda like, they're
watching it, they aren't seeing anything, but you know, the aura is changed.
The aura, the aura is there, and like, I felt like, okay, I think that there are better
episodes later or something, but I was still thinking like, this is so far not exactly
lived up to what I thought.
It's really funny, Nate, because Chromarty High School was a show that was pitched to
me kinda like that, and when I watched it, I really thought of it as like a 50-50 kind
of show.
Like, half of it is unbelievably hilarious, the other half is just okay, and like, but
there's this amazing line-
I still buy it though, it's still the best show ever made.
It's still, I mean, it's really memorable because it's so different, because there's
not another comedy show that feels like it, and so if you just like that feel, and like
you remember the great scenes, then it's like, that's enough.
There's a fucking phenomenal quote from the Watchmen that I love bringing up, towards
the very end, where throughout the whole story, Silk Spector, I think that was the younger,
the girl, right?
Yeah, the lady.
That was the young lady.
She's like, she's, you know, always been like traumatized by the fact that her mom
was like, raped by the comedian, and in the end, her mom is like, kind of like, she's
kind of nostalgic about him, and kind of like forgiving, and Silk Spector's like, what the
fuck?
Like, he raped you.
Like, how could you feel this way?
And she says, like, you know, as you get older, and you know, everything's changing,
and all the people who you care about start dying, like, you just look back, and you don't
really fixate on the bad stuff, all the bad memories are replaced with bright lights, as
she says it.
And I see this in people all the time, especially if your life is, if you're going through something
rough, if your life feels worse than it once felt, then like, you will over glamorize the
past.
You'll remember all the best things that happened, and you'll be like, oh man, I was so much
happier when I was this, in this state, like, if only I could get back there, but then you
remember like, oh wait, that's right, there was tons of bullshit, you know, and I think
people feel that way about media too, where you just, and I think because I've kind of
known about this, I've always tried to avoid it.
Like, I always try to remember exactly how I felt at a time and preserve the memory of
how I felt rather than my memory of the thing itself.
So like, with Chromarty, I remember exactly the fact that it was like, I thought it was
50, 50, half the funniest thing ever, half not, and that's the memory I've preserved
above everything else.
And then if I watch it again, I can be surprised or reaffirmed, but like, yeah, I do think
that it's why we, it's why nostalgia is so powerful, you know, like nobody remembers
the bad episodes of the stuff that they watched, and especially this is why people will always
think that modern media is worse than older media, because when you think back, you're
only going to remember the shows you actually finished or the ones that stuck out, like
all the dumb generic bullshit just goes by the wayside and nobody talks about it anymore,
so it doesn't stay alive in your memory.
But there was always just as much dumb generic bullshit as there is, you know?
Yeah, more or less.
Percentages-wise, anyway.
I mean, people will sometimes look at certain mediums and like run up stats of what people
are enjoying, and it does come in peaks and troughs.
I think generally people would say the turn of the last decade from 08 to 12 or so, you
know, that was the club shit era, and people tend to be more favorable of pop music right
now in comparison.
But also, people talk about-
I mean, it really depends on who you ask, because when you look at Todd in the shadows
and like, he really thought that last year was like the worst year of pop music.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Because that's why I found your series, Digi, legitimately fascinating.
And you, like, when you like, you tried to basically mathematically prove that I think
it was that like 2007 was like the best year of anime, like based on like reviews and stuff.
And that's like a useful thing.
I mean, by really analyzing daily, you can be like, are things actually getting better
or not or, you know, whatever?
The thing about that video, though, is that I may have empirically proved that 2007 is
the best- what I really proved is that four like Western anime fans' consensus 2007 is
the best year.
But the reason why that's the case is that 2007 is the year that speed subbing really
took off.
So for most people, that was the first year they were watching anime while it came out
in Japan.
Myself included.
Like, that was the first year where I was watching seasonal shows.
And like, at the time, a lot of shows were, you know, still getting subbed really slowly.
Like it wasn't like everything got subtitled back then.
What caused that?
Did Haruhi cause that?
Or was it Lucky Star?
It was Naruto.
Naruto caused speed subbing.
Throughout the 2000s, there were sub groups who were basically competing with each other
to see who could sub it as fast as possible.
So Naruto was the first show, I think, that ever had fansubs like day one of an episode
coming out.
And then the fact that Torrenting got popular and Torrenting was by far the safest and easiest
way to download stuff.
So it was like, between that and also streaming sites were getting bigger.
You had sites like Crunchyroll that were taking in, like they had- Crunchyroll used
to have fucking everything.
Like, anything that had been subtitled was on there.
YouTube had a lot of shows at the time.
Back when they were good old pirate boys and didn't have their squeaky clean image.
What did For Never World say about them?
They're a clean company.
That's hilarious.
I love that.
They were literally the dirtiest of all those fucking streaming sites because you had to
pay for a subscription to full screen your video.
How come we can shit on- It's okay to run James Gunn out of the business for saying
some fucked up jokes about baby rape.
But it's not okay to shit on Crunchyroll for being the worst actual pirates in the game
back in the day.
I went to Disneyland recently on every single roller coaster at the height of the coast
before it dropped.
I said hire James Gunn as loud as I could.
It was the most effective marketing campaign of all time.
On the Matterhorn, I had the abominable snowman that was going to come out and get you.
I kept going over to my friend Kyle behind me and I'm like, dude, that's James Gunn.
He's going to try and swipe you up.
He's really mad.
He wants to contract that Kyle.
He's going to make the contract.
It's the only job that had left.
He gets into the abominable snowman costume, runs around.
That's where Disney puts all their rejects so they can stop the abominable snowman costume.
They force him to characterize people.
This is what your tweets have done to people.
Now they act it act physically and now you can see the damage you've done.
Oh boy.
Yeah, I think it was a combination of Naruto and Torrance making speed something possible
and then yes, the hype around Haruhi, but early 2007 Gurren Lagann came out and that
was subbed within the week every episode and Code Geass was also really huge at that time.
So I'm thinking it was those two where I think Code Geass probably even more because Gurren
Lagann was like a slow burn before it got popular.
That's true.
Geass before Gurren Lagann.
Yeah, Geass was a huge meme on A and everything so I think it was that and so yeah, I think
a lot of people are really nostalgic for that era and also it depends on genre because
most anime fans in the West get into it or at least they used to get into it because
of action shows and the mid-2000s was when action shows were the most prominent genre
in anime and then as it sort of drifted over into cute girl shit and comedies and isekai
and light novel adaptations, it's like people who really miss that certain style are kind
of ass out now and so that's kind of how it was with Gigak with his whole golden year
of anime which was what inspired me to make that video was that he was reminiscing on
this certain era that he considered the best but it's entirely because of what was popular
during that era just happening to resonate with him.
But anyway, my real problem with pop culture is that it's not even so much that the wrong
things get promoted or that they get promoted for the wrong reasons, it's that it hampers
people's ability to find what they will like because I think that the average consumer
actually has a much broader taste than they probably give themselves credit for and like
if you talk to almost anybody, they probably have something they really love that you wouldn't
expect because maybe it just came on one night when they were watching TV and flipping through
channels or like a friend showed it to them or there's just something particular that
this person is way into that's not on the radio and it's not like a best seller or anything,
they just found it and loved it and I think most average people have that but like most
people don't go out of their way to look for media to consume, it's not really something
that is encouraged by our culture because most of us are just going to go see the things
that everyone's talking about so we can be in the conversation.
When you're trying to fuck Stacy Rottencroch down the lane, you only need to know about
the latest season of Game of Thrones, you don't need to know about Psycho Pass season
two and why it's shitty compared to season one or whatever.
The most fucked part is that literally seeing, I think that going beyond music, going beyond
anything, I think that people will respond more to something just because they have seen
the name before.
Not even that they've seen the show, just the name because like so many things that
Shenmue is the perfect fucking example because Shenmue was like this fucking obscure Dreamcast
title, people treat it like it's this beloved classic.
Only when the revival became a thing did I suddenly hear everybody really excited about
Shenmue which very much surprised me.
Because Shenmue 1 and 2 not only, they didn't really review all that well at the time, they're
not like important classic games, they just introduced new things that hadn't been seen
before.
Is it the same way as like God Hand was like hated when it came out but has like become
a classic since then?
Is that what happened to Shenmue?
I think that, well with God Hand it was a case of if you love platinum games, people
have gone back and played God Hand because it's all mechanics and that actually brings
me to part of this because part of what inspired me to bring up this topic was Shinobi which
Tom did a playthrough of that we live streamed and then we did a video about it.
Shinobi is a game that got like 7 out of 10 reviews across the board and like generally
was not praised as like this amazing game but when you play it it's clear that the game
is like it's borderline perfect at what it's supposed to be like if you're somebody who
likes like hardcore arcade style games this game is for you and you will love it.
But because of the fact that magazines would not see that as for everybody they're not
going to give it a super high score they're going to give it a 7 because they're like
oh well people most people are going to be disappointed with this game so if we give
it a 10 and everybody rushes out and buys it they're going to complain that it was too
hard.
I know I talk about this all the time but this is exactly the issue I always bring up
about how like super bunny hops reviews like 100% Metal Gear Solid 5 that's for a specific
audience somebody else could review the same game being like I played 10 hours it was really
fun then threw it away that's the right review for somebody else.
Everybody needs to be clear what their review is for like if you're going to review something
be like look here's who I am here's how I feel about games in general here's what this
game means to me because anytime you try to make it for a general audience you kind of
fuck over everybody because the only games that get 10s are the ones where they're like
oh we think everyone will love this game and the only reason you would think that is that
other games that are popular are similar and this is why every game that gets like high
review scores is the same fucking game.
I know if it's a fool's errand if it's literally impossible I feel like we could make a change
here.
Well I think so.
I think the problem is that like traditionally like to talk about game reviews in particular
because that's what I'm most familiar with like growing up reading EGM and GamePro and
all that shit like those were just magazines designed for anybody who's into games no matter
their taste to pick up so they had to just like write them for everyone because they
had no control over it the interesting thing about YouTube and like us doing reviews like
a singular person is you're not a big media company so you can be like I'm going to make
reviews for X kind of person who shares my particular taste you know that gives us the
freedom to really craft a review with a specific focus as opposed to like a game magazine.
I think that those game magazines were wrong headed to do that in the first place though
because they're trying to predict what they think people like and care about and like
I think that you just need to be honest about it because for instance a great example of
something where I think that this that it got saved by reviews taking the opposite stance
is the Souls series because when Demon Souls came out obviously that's a pretty hardcore
game not everybody was going to love it but GameSpot gave that their game of the year
they were like Demon Souls is fucking perfect if this is your type of game this is exactly
what you need go get this and the the like groundswell of recognition surrounding that
that game because everybody who played it was like this is the fucking sick of shit
ever so then when Dark Souls came out all of those people were like really talking about
and they wouldn't shut up about it and like that made it able to be successful and it's
like now the Souls games are like millions selling you know it's a it's a huge game
franchise even though like nobody would tell you oh this will appeal to everyone but guess
what most people are willing to bend their tastes a little bit if they hear that it's
supposed to be good then they will try to engage a little harder so if you give Shinobi
a 7 out of 10 and you're like you know it's too hard for most people they're gonna play
it and they're gonna go oh it's too hard I can't get into it but if you give it a 10
out of 10 and then someone picks it up and they're like this game is really fucking hard
but I know it's supposed to be a masterpiece which means that it's probably my fault I'm
not understanding it I'm gonna try harder basically we're all sheep and we need to be
led like cattle I was just gonna say Tom I think the problem here is the allure of the
just x out of 10 generic rating scale and the simplicity of it is so powerful that and
it's so to like a useful metric for people to not have to like look any further than
just that that you're you're really fighting an uphill battle trying to get people to like
think as a teenager I always felt bad for okay come on read the review this time read
the review this time be literary god damn it ah numbers numbers numbers numbers numbers
fuck again why am I paying for this but looking back as someone who's written reviews
other reviews were shitty and boring I was averting my eyes from literary filth from wasted
brain cells still to this day I mostly look at review scores with those magazines because when
I try to read them like I get game informer sent to my house and like I just give them the scores
and what I'm looking for is what got under a seven because anything that gets under a seven a
game informer is like unplayable I was like recently nothing gets under a seven if I became
like if I if my career I switched it to making documentaries I would make like my magnum opus
a documentary called the IGN seven about and it would start by just talking about IGN and its
culture of you know the whole cultural idea of anything less than the seven is bad but that
just means that it's this weird way of looking at the world and I very slowly start to pan out to
the rest of media and how we think of us out of a seven and then I slowly spiral out to seven out
of ten being the mindset that holds back all of human progress this idea that we need to chase
what we see as good but what is good is actually just mediocre I'm gonna finally break it down
right now what the IGN seven actually means because I think that the reality is when IGN
gives something a 10 or a nine it's because they think everyone in their audience will enjoy it
when they give it a seven it's because they know someone in their audience this is their favorite
game but not enough and when they give something less than a seven it means it's actually a bad
game so like the seven out of ten it's such a it's such a weird milk toast middle rating because
like for instance jrpg's they if you look at review scores in any major publication you will
never see a jrpg get a 10 no matter what the absolute the ones that are considered like the
greatest of all time might get like a nine to a nine point two five and the ones that are like
really good will get like an eight to an eight point five and the ones that are like jrpg
fans will like it will get a seven and it would have to be like broken and unplayable to get below
a seven but like that's all the mindset is it's just like seven out of ten means play it if you're
into this genre eight out of ten means like you know definitely play it if you're into this genre
nine out of ten means if you care about rpg's this will be your your new magnum opus but like it
will never get a 10 even if it is legitimately one of the best games ever made just because it's a
jrpg and like they know that most people won't play it um but i just think it's wrongheaded
because i think there was a time when jrpg's could be the greatest game of all time and there's no
reason we couldn't get back there so like for for magazines to try to instead of just saying like
this game's a 10 out of 10 let's make a cultural shift and and go back to appreciating jrpg's
instead they just say well we can't give it a 10 because this is not a popular genre it doesn't
matter if persona five sells as well as a you know major title i think for for game informer in
particular they also have like another reason for never giving below a seven and i think it's just
because like they're owned by game stop and like games off they want to sell games so if they give
the more games they give seven or higher the more like titles they have to sell at their stores
the conversation shifted a little bit but that's why i look sorry i just want to say that's why i
like looking at the ones that get under a seven because it's when it's like so bad they won't
even shill it they're like because they know that if you go buy this game it's gonna make
game stop look bad for selling it to you you know to go back to the the idea of like like top 40 and
you know popular movies and stuff like that are we being cynical or are the people who are flocking
into these things just genuine fans because i have a i have a friend who i didn't know could exist until
i met him and this person is just a diehard honest to god like he loves marvel movies he just
wants to see them with all of his life and he has a ton of friends who are the same i i i've
sort of cracked into the the norm a lot of my friends are like that yeah so who are we to say
that they are not enjoying them and they're just kind of being i'm not saying that at all i i think
those movies are legitimately good for the most part and i definitely think the reason that like
the avengers movies get such like absolutely insane ratings is partly this it's that it keeps
coming back up so people get used to it and and they want to be a part of it because it's like an
ongoing narrative but it's not that i don't think people would naturally watch those movies it's
the problem is that it takes them away from everything else it's that it's that we're siphoning
people into just a few places and like sort of being like hey you know this is a thing you recognize
go look at it again and again and again and it's like there's no attempt to make people
go to something they don't aren't already comfortable with you know but i think most
people would you know most people would like something that they're not comfortable with
they just need to be showing it and like you know co-recently went out i didn't go but she went
with like i think her mom or her friend or whatever and watched crazy rich asians don't
think it's a movie i would like but she came home and she was like almost a different person
for about 36 hours she was so happy she was just she was simply filled with energy and vigor
more than she usually is and i was like damn man and that's what people out what i don't know it was
just a movie that she liked a lot you know i think that i think a lot of people um like the stuff
that people tend to say is their favorite is rarely the one that is the super big popular
tentpole media because everyone likes that thing but it's made you know it's made to appeal to
everyone and like most people whatever is their number one favorite is something that is more
you know true to their their them personally but like most people aren't like me where they've
gone out and like watched everything in the effort of finding that one thing that appeals to them most
most people it's like they happened upon one thing like yeah and you see this a lot with newer anime
fans where it's like whatever is their favorite is usually something they saw in like the first
10 shows they watched and it like blew them away and it could be something that like they're like oh
my god like it's online a good example like because even though it's huge like you know on a world
scale when you think about it as an individual person living it in the world like most people
haven't heard of sword art online so like like average joe so like when someone finds out about it
from their friend who's like dude you gotta watch this show sword art online and then they watch it
never having seen anime before never having seen a show about being trapped in an mmo never having
seen a show about like a death game never having seen a show with you know with this or that element
maybe even just a fan service that they're very young and they're sexually you know like they're
just starting to feel you know sexually like awakened and then they see this like really
raunchy shit and they're like whoa my dick is exploding like that's the kind of shit that will
make people say like oh my god this is my favorite show i can't believe it and then like someone like
me who's literally watched 10 000 of the same exact thing but better is like oh boy you know but i
totally understand why people like it it's just a matter of like when i see those people i just want
to say well let me entreat you to to to some more let me show you there's an endless world of things
out there that might appeal to you even more specifically because everybody's a little bit
different and so there's probably something that appeals to every individual person a little
differently from everybody else around them you know that's true it's just that most people don't
give a shit right not like not even close and for most people i think about my dad for example
my dad watches and i know that he's not the typical yet but like this will be like when our
generation becomes dads like that'll be us then and then it'll be you know the next year blah blah
like he couldn't give less of a shit about like like what would my dad ends up watching is like
like fox 24 style shows like crime dramas you know and like like real world stuff that he can
he like he like gets it he's like ah yes i understand what this is and like he'll watch the
stuff that falls into his lap and now that there's like Netflix and the on-demand stuff like it's
easier for him to like to find those things and watch more but like he is not i mean he's not
going on youtube this will change slightly as as youtube like takes over more and like i think that
like tom was saying more personal tastes we'll be able to permeate just as like it's not one monolith
now that controls everything but more smaller voices that reach more people let me let me expand
this beyond just media because it supplies to everything in culture a huge one is food and it's
really funny to me that they're like nobody comes out the pussy with a specific preference for food
like probably not if you're american and all you eat is american food it's because all you've eaten
is american food you grew up with it you're used to people who only want to eat hamburgers that that
marvel movie friend is just like that all i want to do is eat hamburgers and just have the meat
the the cheese the bun interesting to use like that yeah like and i i know a lot of people like
that who who won't even go to like a restaurant from like you know you say oh let's try out this
tie place and they're like oh like what is a i don't know about that and it's like it's the same
fucking thing they first of all there's only like six animals we actually eat on this goddamn planet
they eat the same shit everywhere they just cook it slightly differently with a with a few extra
peppers like you'll be fine go to the fucking tie place i okay i i i am a picky eater i was a picky
eater ever since i was a kid so i sympathize with but ever like like recently i was okay much i was
a picky eater too it's not it's not hard i'm gonna pick up new cultures of food it's not it's not
dude right okay or these good restaurants and figure out if you do like Thai food or whatever
right i grew up as a super fucking picky eater as a kid all i ate was like macaroni and kid
cuisines and like i was raised on garbage like outright garbage food and it wasn't until like
my late teens when i just because of the fact that i was applying this logic to anime that like
in my early days watching anime all i liked was action shows and shit like that and then
when i got introduced to like cute girls shows because that was kind of the zeitgeist in the
late 2000 and i started liking that it made me able to start exploring and like the first time i
watched like princess tutu for instance i was like this is way too girly i can't sit do something this
girly and then like gradually i got into girly or shows through like hard catch pre-care because it
has cool action scenes in it and then it acclimates you and then at some point you're like it made me
realize oh like all you have to do is just get used to it whatever part of it that that strikes
you is weird or you're not sure about just exposure expose yourself to it and eventually
you'll like it so i went through that process with anime and then i went well surely this applies
to everything else so i taught myself to like spicy food i couldn't even handle texas peat
i couldn't even handle like fucking fire sauce at at taco bell and i trained myself up to be able
to handle like really spicy thai food and it's just like i now i'm sure how high your spice
tolerance is i remember me you and ben at a vietnamese place i believe i was it was like a yeah i
think it was that and there's they have some sort of pepper or thing with jig in the middle of the
bowls and you pointed that it's a thai place oh it's a thai place okay you pointed that shit and said
okay so that thing right there that thing is hot af yeah but be careful guys all right and so ben
ate it and was like i'm gonna have to a little bit hot and i ate it i was like wait this is like
dangerous and we just sort of looked at you and you just sort of i think it was just that it was
the wrong one oh oh i'm weak no it i think it was that i had misjudged what pepper it was
because like i know for a fact ben spice tolerance is no better than mine so uh but like i mean at
the time that you guys were living with me my tolerance had already gone down because i was not
training myself anymore like well i literally spent a year like non-stop eating nothing but
spicy food until i had a high tolerance and then it completely went to shit when i stopped eating
spicy that makes sense as an explanation but that i it's still been in my um rotation of funny
things to make fun of my friends i told people all the time you're gonna have to like fill me with
evidence in triplicate signed for me to like take that out of my rotation sorry when i was in Rome
the worst i don't want to take that out of your rotation because that is so innocent the absolute
worst thing that i saw people do like the different tourists that would walk past all the anglo pieces
of shit i would walk past some tourist trap and i would see people in Rome in the capital of Italy
i see it's been saying for that like like like hundreds of thousands of years they walk they go
here and they order spaghetti at meatballs at some fucking irish persians tourist trap italian
restaurant they don't go out and actually try italian food why would you come here if you just
want to order the same things that you can order at home what is the point you spent hundreds of
dollars to get here why are you like this why i hear reviewer people talk about how oh you know
you need to have better taste games or movies or whatever what comes to my mind is the dentist
fallacy which is that dentists feel matter at all that they think that they have the right to talk
to you like children because you aren't taking care of your teeth and the thing is that oh hey you
know trained medical professional who's got your life vaguely together is able to like go to sleep
and wake up at the same time therefore have a time to brush your teeth right you know some people
have depression or anxiety or they just fall asleep randomly you know it's fucking hard it's not
it's good to brush your teeth yeah i brush my teeth every night did you guys know that it was harder
did you guys know that dentists have like an extremely high suicide rate ha ha ha yeah it's
because their practitioners fucking based on lies no it's because they always have lost to hang
let me tell you right now guys i i i talked about this on a recent um pub crawl but i want to hear
your thoughts you don't have to brush your teeth all you have to do all you have to do to make your
teeth okay is to not consume sugar sure if you consume i know people who brush their teeth every
day twice a day still get cavities because they drink soda but i know people who don't brush well
this happened to me for a while when i quit soda for there was like a good year span where my teeth
were perfectly fine in spite of not brushing just as i have always not done and um your no cavity of
like acceptable teeth though is like way off like a rows of normal for this movement like
acceptable teeth is teeth that don't get cavities i mean okay as british standards by the way
that's the thing like most like the main reason to brush your teeth is if you want them to be white
and like i do which most like it's very highly valued here in america just because it's a big
fucking cultural meme yeah that's true and uh here we are in america conditioning stop being gay
i'm just uh i'm not proud of my poor hygiene i have poor hygiene but i'm not proud of it i'm not
gonna start it's not poor hygiene to have non-white teeth like teeth are not natural brush your
teeth at all or clean a part of your body because it's i'm telling you like okay i'm not i'm not
saying my teeth are in a good state i'm not like proud of the of my teeth because of the fact that
i do drink lots of soda and and uh fucking sugar and so my teeth do have problems but like i'm just
saying that that brushing your teeth is not the solution to avoiding cavities because you will
get cavities anyways if you consume and most of the people i know consult a medical practitioner
before listening to digi bro there's no dentist that will tell you that you just have to brush your
teeth and no one no no dentist will not say you have to not drink soda they'll all say that yeah
but they're like okay the thing about dentistry is that it is mostly a cosmetic business like it's
not really a health care service they dress it up with that so that people will feel that they have
to go but like dentistry is primarily cosmetic it's mostly about having straight and white
teeth and that's why everything in the fucking place is about how straight and white your teeth
can be straight and white it sounds like pastry oh yeah exactly we gotta get that
exactly listen i hate dentists as much as the next person but i i don't i'm the clean your teeth
and not drinking soda thing it's not convincing me i don't even dislike i don't even dislike going
to the dentist by the way i'm like a freak who doesn't even hate going to the dentist because
i've been so many times that i'm okay with sure yeah uh i think that's proof of what you're saying
earlier the more you repeat something that i mean i'm happy i'm happy to be agnostic about
whether or not it's actually necessary to brush your teeth or like if you can just like that's all
fine but i and i'm also sympathetic to this thing that like yeah it is one like i've been to japan
i've seen the people there with their fucked up teeth uh and that's just normal and most of them
don't like in a lot of those places where people have they have teeth that look fucked up because
they're crooked and they're not white but they're not unhealthy because those people don't drink the
amount of soda that we do in america they are not like they're not putting tons of fucking sugar in
their mouth and like the sugar is what rots your teeth like it might as well be one it's it's most
convenient to think of it as one to one hey man i'm sure you encourage people to consume less
sugar hundred percent one like i look at someone's one cavity like i look at devu who has a lot of
pride in never having had cavities and he brushes his teeth all the time but he also almost doesn't
consume sugar so like you know what the fucked up thing the most fucked up thing in my entire life
was was i okay i was so terrible about drinking soda like my entire life like from like age one
to like like recently i was just drinking like two cans a day it was awful it was horrible
two and i never had i never had a single cavity until i stopped drinking soda and then i got a
fucking cavity out of nowhere it's it's it's fucking not fair it was like a maybe it was like
that thing that mr burns has were like all the diseases were like trying to push through all
at once but then it's like if you take away a bunch of them then a couple can actually get through
yeah because i don't know so i brought up the dentist thing because i call it the dentist
fallacy because it's the thing that this person chose to specialize in and they have tunnel vision
regarding its importance and so imagine you know some people are like what you don't uh know
which is sub sub sub genre of metal is on the radio right now how are you living a functional
life if you don't know uh eight late 80s thrash hardcore from 90s thrash hardcore bitch the thing
about that though is that if you spend a couple of years listening to people like digis let's play
part of genre well whatever it doesn't matter you're the i know i know i know i don't have a
dysfunctional life i have to come up with a fake metal sub genre so so uh if you listen to people
who have who are always persnickety about having good opinions like digi who who insists you you
think your opinions out really long the more you listen to his shit the more you find out that he
does in fact apply this process to everything his chairs his walls his ceilings his floors his
houses his mouses his food his life his everything so it's not hypocrisy apply to all these things
the same logic of like experiment with absolutely everything and find the best one and and the
reason i feel that way is just that i see so many people that like they most people live sub optimally
and i don't just mean in terms of efficiency i mean in terms of like just their own mental well-being
like most people they just kind of get a job and then they have the job and it's like shouldn't
you be looking for the job that you can do best that will have the best min max of you know energy
put forth to rewards taken shouldn't you be looking like if you're gonna spend all your time watching
watching shit shouldn't you try to watch it that will give you something well if you're gonna play
a lot of video games shouldn't you go find the video games you'll really love and like i think most
people they'll consume and like with those those broad pop cultural things most of them again are
not bad most of them appeal to almost everybody in a very shallow way and so people will always say
like oh yeah i've played the new assassins creed i played the new call of duty i played the new
whatever but then like when you ask what's your favorite game it's never one of those it's always
something unique that they played usually as a kid because when you're a kid you don't know the
pop culture zeitgeist is easily you just go to the store and pick something that looks cool
and like maybe you you've did that a lot and you got a lot of bullshit that wasn't good so you stopped
that method but there was that one time you got that thing that was like life-changingly awesome
and it's been your favorite ever since and it's like you can have that again well you know what
it is um people treat life like they've just arrived in an unexplored land and they've they've
got to find where they're going to live and so like there are people live here like there are
signposts as to where to go in this new con that they've just arrived on and so they go through
and you know they'll find like you know the cities which are like the popular things like ah there's
a lot of good here uh maybe i'll keep going and and keep looking elsewhere but a lot of people
are just going to be like like this city's got everything i need man like why am i gonna keep
going and then of course some people are gonna like go out and they're kind of forge their own
path and discover new places and and find new trails and stuff and you know they'll find cool
stuff that other people didn't know and then some of those people will establish a new city and then
people will flock to that and some of those people will keep going others will stay there and be like
i'm content here because and like and maybe someone will make it they're on a new trail
they're like they find like a nice little valley or something they're like it's all metaphor
obviously and they're like you know what this is a nice place i'm just gonna camp it right here
even though over the next hill is like i don't know like a gold mine is like something that would
be incredible but like it requires energy and effort to continue to seek these things and so
after a while people are just like you know i'm content right here the majority of people are
just lazy just in everything you know well you could call it lazy but like it's fine for people
to just be content uh it's what i was saying when i was talking about the i g and seven of life
um you guys i'm sure know the allegory of the cave like and i think that's what we're kind of
describing here is like i guess you're right i guess you're right yeah like you don't know what's
above what's on the surface till you get i mean the first episode of growing the gond is literally
the allegory of the cave made into a show so let's make it let's make it relevant to anime uh
yeah and growing the gond it's like nobody believes coming out the surface is real
and he's like look all of our fucking people just like die in landslides all the time like don't
you think it would be nice if we lived somewhere where that didn't happen like but most people are
just like well i mean yeah that's how life is that's just what life is and it's like every time there's
something if there's anything that bothers me in my life my first thought is always there must be a
better way like surely and uh and i'm not even amazing at it tom was uh was telling me that
this is why he knows so much about computers because like tom is great at this i run into
lots of issues with with my computer and like i i've taken to just anytime anything goes wrong i
just asked tom and he's always found a solution for it because the second something bothers him
he goes well i know that this this can't be the way you know like there has to be something we can
do to a lot of us yeah i that's i totally do that with tom too a lot of computer and like
software issues are like black boxes and because you don't know that there even is a fix uh like
i feel actually there i there's a there's a there's a voicemail today that describes like
kind of a solution to our like voicemail uh issues and like because i had no idea how to do it uh
none of this would have made sense i never would have thought to do things this way but uh and we'll
get to that um but yeah i mean tangentially related but i am really sick of safe movies and
not just because they they upset me in the moment and you know like like i'm upset i want a movie
with like a 10 to 20 chance that i'll just be eviscerated while watching the movie i'm sick of
these safe movies ironically i'm upset with them because the like safe movies have not been the
most popular movies of all time and they haven't been for like a long time
nay if you remember is that true though isn't marvel like by far the most popular right now
yeah i'm saying that's not always been the case oh it hasn't always been okay nay do you remember
in the final fantasy lecture how i was mildly unimpressed with your eye over final fantasy
because like what the last few games have been bad you know like whatever yes i don't care um and i
haven't uh i haven't forgiven you yet for feeling that way okay well well i forgive you because i
haven't spiritually felt that until i re-watch a lot of disney movies and i realized how good
renaissance disney is and it is unorally some of my favorite art of all time and i think about how
every single year from like 1989 to like 1990 or to however long the renaissance was
every single fucking year what he said 1989 to 1990 oh oh sorry sorry i'm sorry i'm sorry
well what's the one movie that was it like little mermaid and just little mermaid or something
yeah yeah uh but every single year they popped out like incredible movies with like unbelievable
projection values that are ironically like like la hunchback no chadam takes fucking risk sure it
has the shit gargles that everyone hates and is a huge fucking meme but it honestly takes
risk in a lot of different ways that's sanctuary scene we're causing more crimes no chadam and he
fucking screams sanctuary down the crowd and it's fucking beautiful by the way those are ground
baking pieces of media that came out every single year like the final original final fantasy games
and then it just like peered out for a while and like zootopia is good but like it's not trying to
be like the hunchback of no drum it's not trying to have these incredible set pieces or make any
broad like real statements it has all about that organizational momentum organizational momentum
and like belief in the project and just morale and the creative flow and when it's on it's fucking
on and then the white 2k disaster didn't fry computers but it fried many creative minds
so it would seem and by the way uh they didn't make one in 1993 but that's because they were
working on the lion king so that would make sense but talking about king is the best production
cycle of all time talking about the fucking gargoyles from from hunchback you know i thought you
were gonna complain about disney movies because i complained about them for things like the gargoyles
because that's a safety measure because literally they're like oh but this one has like you know
issues of image and looking ugly and also has like suggested rape and it criticizes christians
and it doesn't have like a whole lot of goofy scenes we need to inject some really uninspired
goofy characters so that people who don't like serious catholic shit will be able to at least
sit through the movie okay that okay that is the fucking word the gargoyles are the worst thing in
any disney movie ever because it's such a bizarre half measure that makes no sense if you think about
for more than two fucking seconds okay in a disney movie you would think if the writers have some
sort of dark tones they wanted to explore disney would say okay yeah don't explore those because
this is disney and we don't want to have that in a movie because you know our target audience is
children we don't want to have dark tones but they have dark tones and execute them beautifully i've
watched hunchback notion down extremely recently in the past month uh fucking literal nine i love
that movie uh and it executes its themes perfectly but then they're like well oh you know i'm getting
kind of scared like you know pull the call on my shirt sweat in a little bit this is a dark movie
time to add the gargoyles so you know like the kids will still be interested but here's the thing
there's still all of the dark shit there so if you're a baby and you're amused by jess now xana
saying pour the wine and cut the cheese then you're going to be scared by claud throw a little
fucking raping ismeralda on screen and burning her to death and likewise if you're an adult who
likes frollo trying to rape ismeralda you're gonna be like oh the fucking gargoyles oh my god
raises paw yeah yeah so no one's going to be happy no one's going to like like either of these
two things you're not appeasing the children you're making them sit through a boring movie they won't
like there's there comes a time i think with big productions where they where they say it's a sad
thing but companies have to do this a lot they say we know we're not going to please everyone
all the way so we're gonna try to please or you know like they said like okay throw out the united
collective possible 10 out of 10 vision for some people instead we will take like across the board
eights or like across the board nines that we can get which is sad it's a sad artistic compromise
but i guess that's just business the bizarre part is is that it comes so close the hunter
no shame comes so close to just being a great movie with no flaws and i just think if disney
just a fucking if michael eisner just allowed the things to continue the way that all the writers
and all the artists want to push it to and they allowed the creative produce to go to like like
up to 11 and they allowed to have all the crazy dark shit that they want to put in it and you know
this one movie in this fucking like 10 year run of great movies that all peer to children this
one movie oh i'm so sorry it's like an e10 plus rating oh you know heaven forbid that they would
have swept the fucking academy awards they would have won every single like academy that they could
it would be great and everyone would have looked back on extremely fond but the problem is now but
the gargles and all you know a couple other shit just makes it so that couldn't reach the heights
that it could have otherwise because they were so scared about not reaching their usual target
i just want to i want to corroborate all of munchie's opinions on hunchback
it's the only movie i actually like from that era though uh i think of almost every movie in that
is fucking key now i've i've been recently i've been i've been watching just movies a lot recently
i think they're all landmarks in cinema and animation they're beautiful to look at they all
have incredible colors and they all have incredible animation i just could talk about them forever i
love the meta story behind disney and era i love the story behind michael isner and how he came
to be all this sort of stuff everything about them is perfect and they bring such joy to my heart
they are the best movies of all time well it's the best common part of history of all time to swing
in with a big fat pseudo disagreement my problem with probably the entire company-wide creative
philosophy of the entire disney super conglomerate since the late 80s can be summed up in the
fact that they boast about how many times they rewrite and re-storyboard their shit during the
production process which they frame as a constant effort of evolution and bringing the story and
the film to a greater height of of optimal realization but when i walk away from their movies
i come away underwhelmed thinking i felt like i just watched a frankenstein together mishmash
pishposh of different ideas that kept getting edited and i felt like i was like this was not a
smooth ride because i kept bumping over a shitload of staples what i don't know what the gargoyles
are what movie are referring to specifically when you think all of them starting with the little
mermaid um most of them they're all like like hodgepodge frankenstein like has someone much
had to know it was obvious i feel like the gargoyle effect is similar to i mean i i've always hated
the hakuna matata sequence in like lion king i just thought it was really lame and boring and
like for babies wait but that progresses the plot and it's and it's a fun music no no i was
exaggeration i hate fun i was uh the progress is great the progress is great and it progresses the
plot and it's a montage so that i was exaggerating when i said all of the problem i specifically
mean dumb and boring frozen i don't see the appeal i prefer watching nala uh you know get
clearly wet during can you feel the love tonight that's that's the kino moment right there hey you
know all this talk of like i i think the lion king is a great movie and i think it's i think it's a
great movie and not boring yeah that's a that's a very that's pretty much the opinion of everyone
other than me munchie so munchie are you ready for the lion king to get totally ruined when they
redo it oh yeah oh okay the disney live action movies are so bad action or something yeah i think
it's a live action realistic cg oh are you what yeah i know it's gonna be fucking crazy dude okay okay
okay okay all right i read an article about the live action lad which is my favorite disney movie
except it's not because hulture james but you know i like a lad and always have a place in my heart
because i like this next game uh and shout out to robin williams get hang in yourself will give you
such a crick in the neck robin williams uh uh there was a live there's a live action
land coming out soon like in the next couple years and one of the articles was don't worry guys
we're going to make jasmine way more feminist like you know she was just she was just a you know
cool sexy lamp and i'm not no way no way i'm not against jasmine being feminist but here's the
thing she already fucking was and that was her entire character that she was a feminist so okay i'm
not upset that they're going to make her more feminist i'm upset that these people are framing
it like they've done justice to land like you know we've no we don't understand the story to make
jasmine more feminist but no it's already there monchi what they mean is they're going to put more
clothes on jasmine they're going to take this character who dresses light because she lives in
a desert and they're going to put her in more clothes okay so they're gonna watch so they're
gonna keep in the original lad you know she runs away from home she doesn't want to be treated like
a toy you know she she she doesn't want to be married someone who she doesn't love you know she
does all these proactive things in the plot oh that's not feminist slap a brick out of the oh
dude i'm gonna i'm gonna get up we've done now uh um because what would be more feminist than
being ashamed of the human body yeah pretty much i i mean i don't know i guess it's not about this
is why the the like birk or whatever is like a weird feminist thing because like okay true it does
cut off the that evil sinister male gaze but at the expense of like a woman being you know like
unable to kind of express us like is that worth it is this disclaimer monchi's opinions have stopped
when he stopped talking uh understood understood look whatever i don't care about this i was just
gonna say about this topic of corporate meddling and like uh i don't know like like a creative spark
being kind of like uh interfered with by by business necessity like i get why it happens
and it reminds me of what happened to elon musk recently uh which was just he he stepped down
from uh the board of directors at tesla he's still ceo but he stepped down from the board of directors
did he step down or was he forced out because i know he's not the chair well i mean there was
pressure he he stepped down is what i read um i mean you know he i'm sure this was in reaction
to pressure so how much of this was like volunteer i mean i don't know exactly i'm sure it was just
to control it apparently worked out a deal of some kind where this was like the thing he probably
like did that got to stay being ceo doesn't matter but like the point is um the reason why he had to
do it was because after his appearance on the joe rogan podcast where he smoked the weed um like
there was a lot of people were criticizing him and shit and in response to that he made a tweet
he made a tweet it's all about this one tweet which was um thinking about taking it was something
like thinking about taking tesla public at four twenty dollars per share or whatever it was um and
and then the further line was funding secured and the issue is with that funding secured line
because it turns out that was like not really true and like okay this was clearly like a joke
but you have to like because he's such a huge guy and like the court like he is the ceo and it was
chairman of the board of this giant company that does these big important things like i guess he
does have these responsibilities to be like completely truthful and not mislead people at all
because i don't know maybe somebody when they heard that news like invested their life saving
because i don't know what's going to do this this time to make no this is this is this is people
who who had it out for elon and this was a convenient excuse oh just need a god damn satire tag
what is saying is that he did this this is why slash s at the end of that post this is why saved
everything corporations are the worst everyone just needs to work by themselves in isolation
have a patreon doesn't matter how big your dreams are no one has twitter twitter rooms
everyone's careers i love elon and yes twitter definitely did fuck him up real bad here i don't
actually think that like this is such a like elon is kind of a weird unstable guy like he whatever
he's got like a crazy sense humor it's fine i like him a lot i think he's like the best human on the
planet basically but still the fact remains that he is a weirdo uh who like is like when you're
the CEO of a company like you kind of are held to just a way higher standard because people are
depending on you and i really do believe in the philosophy of like with great power comes great
responsibility and it sucks and you're gonna get fucked over real easily yeah but it's with great
power comes great responsibility not with great power comes no sense of humor like like okay i hear
you i hear you but the thing is i don't know how much of that was actually a joke and i haven't
looked into it for 20 a share yeah yeah what there's no way that was gonna be you know what
would uh what that reminds me of talking about when you ascend to some higher plane of status
people put responsibility on you now um chairman of a company statements you make about the company
you're the chairman of that makes sense but what to me is weird is most subscribed youtubers
responsibility to not say the n word because it'll fuck up our ad revenue how dare you do that
you gotta take the black you fucked this up for us pewdiepie i'm sure that if i through the
lottery of the algorithms had become the most subscribed youtuber i would have changed my
philosophy my self-serving desire to get on youtube and would have elected myself the fucking pope
bishop of youtube and changed my whole priority to be about supporting the youtube community and
not about supporting my own channel like every other goddamn youtuber pewdiepie you're the most
subscribed so you need to like look out for us right for some fucking reason the most eyes and i mean
i don't really blame youtube for what they did i just hate that the people whipped up the kind of
like uh fear mongering and what's the word uh like reactions that aren't deserved you know something
like that whatever it was do all of you guys know about the most popular fortnite streamer maybe just
straight up most popular twitch streamer i don't know shit about this i don't know shit about
twitch but i hear about this yeah yeah yeah how he has a mic pens policy to not stream with women
yes yes because so to catch everyone up uh if it be some people don't know because he is married
and if he streams with women people are going to go oh are they having an affair oh look at this
thought over here right i believe we briefly discussed this on a previous episode but i'm
i'm happy to excuse me i don't listen to the show whoops i'm like one of those early uh biggest
problem guests who don't know shit but so i haven't heard this episode either so i'm so sure yeah dad did
you do you know about this whole controversy i've never even heard this guy before i do right so he
doesn't stream with women and people have compared it to how mic pens he has a policy of never being
alone with a woman and surprisingly there's never been that much of a blowback for that because
people understand because i mean it's happening right now it's like oh there's you know i was
raped by this guy 45 years ago right and while we were alone in the room at one point so you
don't know for sure right yeah i understand that and and he has the same this this twitch streamer
guy has the same policy of i don't want to bring this kind of hammer down on my head and i did
read one of those articles you know modern day sjw is now they they have to like write things
really carefully because they know what all the fucking you know shit lord rebuttals are gonna be
so they they did but before before you say that i just want to specify for the audience uh of like
a big part of why he wants to not be seen with women is that the people like of like the people
themselves his fans don't spread rumors about them having an affair it's mostly consumed about fans
and like the online perception his audience think like spreading right about him indeed exactly
yeah yeah recognizing what's happened it sounds like what somebody who's cheating on his wife would
say it seems pretty guilty to me we're spreading this rumor around what no i'm not cheating on you
with her if i was cheating on you with her i would pretend to be going out with someone else and then
i would go with her in secret tom just reminded me i was uh no please oh well i don't know that
wasn't he done he was he was gonna read something oh oh i thought i was i'll get back to it in a
second but all i did you say is fucking anyway uh tom reminded me of i was reading this article
about um privacy and how the concept of privacy only really began in like the late 1800s because
like up until that point most societies were like you know like it was a tight-knit small group who
all needed and relied on each other and there wasn't really that much room for people to even
be doing like vastly different things from one another and because these groups were smaller
there also was not even like there was there was like not a conceit of your privacy being at risk
like so whatever you did in the privacy of your home like there wasn't really a concept of like a
public figure because you know everyone's everyone's in a small fucking town you can't be there's
no famous people you know right i mean like london existed and like you know there had been
a lot of stuff before i think that's strange to me london is not the one in your thing you know
it's a big city it's on commerce but it's nowhere near like people if you're thinking of like old
if you're thinking of old london you're thinking of like 1800s industrial revolution where everyone's
poked like packed into small houses london and that's not how it was and write an article the
ninja guy whatever his name is i don't remember names whenever i read articles i just remember
like the ideas right and the article made me realize that like the person who wrote it doesn't
really understand what it's like to be popular l right doesn't understand what it's like to have
people know you to be sort of a public figure because the way the article was written again it
was one of those ones that was really mincing words you could tell it wasn't to go full you know
social justice about it but she knew that you know that would look wrong so she really meant
her words basically saying imagine that being expected to not lie what a shock she was saying
basically saying you know the stream his his policy of not streaming with women is misguided
it's okay horribly misguided in fact but what does it say about twitch culture that even
the most famous twitch streamer is afraid of their backlash and their toxicity and i thought about
that joking my chin thinking you know this person she's she writes for a somewhat known
like online magazine the one who is the most afraid of the backlash like you would like
here's the thing right despite that this woman is obviously a writer or at least a part timer for
some website i think i heard of before she probably doesn't have like anyone who like
thinks about her work and judges it as like a person if you know what i mean and that despite
being like a like a like d-list internet personality myself i've experienced this
for the experienced when you've made enough of an impact or made enough of an impression good or bad
and you experience absolute strangers picking around at your shit and talking about you like
they know you when they when you feel like they don't and it feels like they're talking about you
without your permission and it feels fucking weird and i think unless you felt that you don't
understand how vulnerable being popular is it doesn't do anything to boost your confidence
necessarily it doesn't make you immune to feeling weirdly violated it doesn't make you immune to
rumors often people who can stand being a top-level celebrity are just the ones who were
bred through the system of just the ones who were able to deal with it in the first place it's not
like becoming a millionaire makes you able to deal with it it's just that the only people who can
deal with it are the only people who stick around in the first place and these rumors can be spread
around so easily and with so much hatred right they can be post on encyclopedia and all that
should just pass it all over there and do you want that to even like have the chance of impacting
your marriage and then and then these people like have this foregone conclusion this isn't even
something that's like discussed or analyzed it's just assumed that these people are popular and
they have to set a fucking good example for everyone else so top fortnite streamer you need
to risk the hurt of your family and your lifestyle and your job and your career because we need fair
representation on fortnite right like on fucking twitch right because you don't want to have you
know a woman get called thought all all up and down the corner and like all this sexist abuse
right you know that's going to happen that's part of why you don't want to do it but it's your
responsibility to like try and fight against it and to take the hate upon yourself because you're
the most popular i want to follow up on that but first i never actually got to the point of what
i was saying earlier uh that that privacy was this new concept from the late 1800s and that like as it
spread um like that as soon as like tabloids were a thing it was immediately like anybody in any
position of like being known at all was gonna have things said about them and anytime that somebody
was upset that things were being said about them the immediate backlash was well you wouldn't have
anything to hide if you weren't doing anything wrong that's the that's the one that's the one
that always gets to me and that's it's so fucked because it's like first of all like i the reason
i have to hide is because i'm doing something that you will consider wrong that's why i have to hide
because this world is a bunch of people who think that their way of life is the correct one
and therefore anything that goes against the grain of what they think is right
they're going to be upset with and i don't want to be in a position where i have to constantly
explain and justify every fucking thing that i do and it's funny because i have been in that position
for the most of the last like you know since becoming famous and a lot of it is because
i'm somebody who's obsessed with being understood so like every time i do something and people
don't understand it i go out of my way to explain it but eventually that just got so exhausting
because you're never gonna you know if you have a constantly evolving audience and they're not
going to consume absolutely every piece of media you you do especially not if you're just like
doing a corrections or like a further clarifications video people don't care they don't care that
much nobody cares enough to get intimately into your life so it's like your options are basically
either do things in public that others may find questionable and then spend every fucking waking
hour explaining yourself or just say fuck off give me my privacy you know so i can just live
my life without having to explain it to you because and i don't know why people don't
complete like i on some level i do but i don't understand why people don't just take the mindset
of like other people's lives are different from mine i should just accept that i won't understand
everything about what they do you know like it's just that people think that they're right as i think
really what it comes down to and and they further around they don't have a frame of reference or
even understand the different experience of other people which is why i think it's so easy for like
lots of poor people to have very little empathy for rich people even though rich people for example
just have they have very different problems than like poor people but they're still real problems i
would say uh i would understand why i think i think typically very very general here a lot of people
with financial struggles overestimate how much their problems are all because of their financial
struggles yeah they put way too much the blame on that and then conversely it's an easy scapegoat
and then conversely a lot of people who are well off and don't have financial struggles
underestimate how fucking swell it is and how much easier it makes their lives to not have those
financial problems if it's been a while since they've had any i completely agree if you do
i think that all those what what the big misunderstanding is is that the reason people
um like the real appeal of having money is simply freedom it's not that because because money does
not bring happiness as the the aidage goes and it's been scientifically proven this is a fact
money does not bring happiness but say the peak is seventy thousand dollars a year i believe like
what i think the the rich don't understand about the poor is that for a lot of them there is just
no way out like there's nothing they can do within their environment to change things and if there
were they probably don't know what it is and they have no concept of it like there's no way for them
to grasp it and rich people are just like well i've also got my you know i've got issues too but at
least you have the power to redirect your life at least if you think like oh my job is a huge problem
you can try to go get another job and granted it's still a huge risk it's still yeah it's not
like anybody has the power to just completely uproot all the time um and like i've worked to put myself
in a position like that like the reason that i like doing internet work and working from a
decentralized location based on fan donations is that i don't have to answer to anybody so every
time something's even slightly off about my life i can work on changing it and try to try to make
everything just right but like that would not be possible if not for at the very least my baseline
understanding that that is even conceivable like most people don't even conceive of that as something
that they could live is really the the the thing that makes it so appealing it makes it so powerful
because like when i had to go back to a job after making a ton of money online like everything changed
it's like oh well like i have to be here at a certain amount a certain amount of time so like i
stopped going to conventions i stopped seeing friends as often like all these things i just like
could do you just can't anymore and like it's obvious but it is a huge detriment and changes
the entire way you think the entire way you have to function because like a third of your life is
now taken this this is related to something that i want to talk about later uh while thinking rather
reflecting ruminating upon the capital g capital b great people in life i was i was i was interested
in how all of them are nobles all of them are people who come from the upper crust of
sight i'm talking like pre let's say like pre 19 or i'm sorry 1850 almost everyone that you're going
to have a strong emotional connection to and and have like a narrative and you know piece of history
dedicated to them all that not just like to say kings or any just you know the the popular political
and religious and you know figures of the day the capital g capital p great people are all going
to be nobles and it comes down to i think i think i've i've isolated one specific thing it's because
when you have that much power and influence and you know money you are able to get a good education
and i reflect after reflecting upon history i think education is probably the most important thing
that you can do to have a better life not to just say like you know the institutions of
uh depending on the type of education but yeah i mean it's just not even college is good specifically
i'm just saying that having the worldliness and having the ability to maybe go to a different
country and learn things about the people learn things like oh these people are different why
are they different learn about the you know underlying uh structure of society learn about
these things learn about math learn about science learn about you know history and stuff like that
it's so so vital to having a well-cultured well-mean and intelligent person to be able
to understand not just you know being able to recite math problems but being able to understand
the underlying course of history course of society and be able to like you know have your
influence directed onto that society it's so important that's the most important thing that's
why power and money is so much it's it's almost directly to education i have a like a like a
theory a life i have like a digi bro hypothesis level of like this is really grasping at
theoretical straws makes a whole lot of sense to me what i'm about to say is that it has that being
a noble is not a state of uh physical satiation of resources but a state of mind that people who
are living in some white trash by the way what what a digi bro hypothesis is is something that
you know for a fact is true you just have no idea what words you can say that will make other people
recognize yes so you could be living like a white trash like trailer park there's a fucking like
half broken toilet in the front yard kind of life right that level of resources and i think what really
gets you down if these people are so poor how come they have so many broken toilets yeah why do they
spend all their money on because they got a shit no matter if you're rich or poor you got a shit
if you're that poor you can't flush you can't afford it so you got to keep buying another toilet
every time you needed to shit no he's right no one who's actually no one who is actually poor
has a toilet like if you live my mind for that for you with the world's your toilet my my buddy
don son uh who's uh you know vietnamese um yeah lived in vietnam for a little while and they don't
do toilets over there what they do is that they'll have a little bridge over a ravine with a hole in
the middle of it no and just go up on this bridge and you squat over the hole and you sit down into
the ravine there's like a koi fish down there that eat all the shit up whoa and then uh and then you
wipe with leaves whoa okay all right right that's actually that's what the third world no pun intended
and that's what i mean when i say poor is a state of mind right uh and i'm not saying that the physical
realities of it aren't very limiting i get that right i don't want to be like oh don't act poor
no no no it's a state of mind and it's not one you necessarily that have that much control over
when you know you're in a disadvantaged part of the world in in a uh rung of the world of rung of
society that's less valued that has less freedom that is seen as lower you can't help but feel
more demoralized about it right but what we don't but like what can be done is at least a little bit
a little bit of progress on on the individual level every day is all the free time you still have
like even if you are packed at work you know you have you work really long hours and you work
full time you still have at least a couple of hours in the day to do whatever you want maybe in
the week yeah maybe in the week right but you can do something with that time and it doesn't
have to be wasted but what happens is that most people uh i remember there was a cracked article
it wasn't like a one of those five amazing facts it was one of those personal story kind of articles
and it was saying you know if you want to make it anywhere in life you have to start now because
the cycle i was in said the article for years he said the cycle i was in was i had
have to wake up i didn't want to go to work but i had to go to work so i went to work and all day
at work all i would think about is all the books i wanted to write how i want to be an author how i
want to be a writer and i would just think of it all day at work and then like get home i'd get home
from work and i'd be at home and i'd have like three hours to do whatever the fuck i wanted but i
was pissed off and tired and filed the rest of that under hashtag fuck this day and then went to
sleep to repeat the cycle all over it this is my life this is my life i think that's the most people
and i was in that i was in that mindset um for a while but like when i worked at target like
because it was it was a it was a physically strenuous job because i was on the the flow team
and i'm weak but uh like a lot of the days i'd come home and just be tired like so tired i just go
straight to bed but then like there were days where like i was physically tired and out of it
and just done but i was like i need to make two videos a week if i want this channel to succeed
you know so that's what i did it was like no matter what their hat like it didn't matter if
i was like falling asleep while editing there has to be two videos a week or this channel is not
gonna succeed but you have to look at it i think that the the thing that that was different about
my mindset and this is the hardest thing for me to teach other people is that it can happen fast
like if you do it you you just gotta think of it like i'm doing this so that it because like
let's say that you you barely chip away at the thing that you are working towards like over the
course of years like that's years of you just getting further and further beaten down but if
you are trying if you're like really cramming it into every single waking hour you have there's a
chance it'll happen really fast you know and like with my channel's growth it was like then again i
was putting out two videos a week every week no matter what it took to get them out and like it
only took a couple months for me to get successful because there was just so many chances there were
so many you know so many lightning rods being placed in the ground that eventually something
had to get hit by fucking lightning you know and even if they don't immediately take off in a huge
way i this i can definitely guarantee that it is easy to get some positive feedback loop going
quickly even if it's small success which like for me and ben for example it was like when gib put us
in his like pony review like compilation thing that was the first moment where like all right people
actually like this stuff and they care and this is dope and that was something but it was a big
forward to at work like you know there's someone looking forward to the stupid shitty art you're
going to make when you get home that can at least raise your spirits and i will say to anyone who's
trying to break this cycle especially people who are at the bottom of it but actually especially
especially the people who have been at it for a couple of years and are totally demoralized about
it my mistake and i i recognize this just the last couple of days is that i was focused entirely
on getting out of my regular job 100% as fast as possible and which is the which is two extremities
right you could plan any other getting out of your job partially or getting out of your job
completely i went for completely you can try getting out soon or later i went for soon which
actually just made things harder because i wasn't satisfied with any of the progress i was making
until i had everything i wanted but if you could figure out how to have a plan to like reduce your
hours yeah that is actually what will get you from point a to b in a more realistic manner and i
almost never planned for that i i was full time and then like the second that i like realized the
channel was going to be successful i i had them cut my hours to part time because it was i was
like it's too hard to continue doing this job when they're working me because during the holiday season
it was like it was brutal because we were going at 2 a.m and they would often have us working like
you know as much as humanly possible so like it was getting really hard to do the youtube videos
and i was just like this is this is on a roll like this has a chance and like if i my dad was
super pissed at me when i cut down to part time because he was like you're gonna lose all the
benefits like how could you and i'm like because i don't plan to be here long like the whole point
of this is to not be here as fast as possible so if cutting my hours means that the youtube channel
can grow faster then that means it's that much and obviously this isn't something everybody
can do unless there is revenue coming in but that's the other thing is that getting getting enough
revenue to to to leave your job is hard getting enough revenue to cut your hours is not as hard
because like say you make a hundred dollars a week on whatever you're doing then it's like well
shit now that's you know that's a pretty huge chunk of a of a minimum wage paycheck and i know a lot
of people aren't in such convenient positions like you know digi you did you were able to like
not have to pay that many expenses in my case it was like when people talk about privilege i always
want to say like i completely believe that uh that i am a privileged individual but the privileges i
had were that my family was very loving and nothing to do with how much money they had
or how much it was that my dad thought i could do this and therefore encouraged me to do it
and i think that's the most important thing that you can get is like a safe environment because
space is such a better place yeah and i know people who uh who don't who who have like a family like
a i have friends who who come from families that had a lot of money who tried to put them through
college who tried like who would have been on that track but because they ultimately decided to do
like internet art or something that's not a guarantee that family cut them off and those
people are struggling now because they don't have the opportunity to sit at home and work on their
art until they're able to leave they are now living in a shit apartment somewhere trying to you know
work shit jobs trying to struggle to get it done and they're not making enough off of the other
art in order to put it back in but also with those people there's always an element of like
davoo said like there's it's just hard to find the energy and it's hard to convince yourself but
like i would encourage anybody if you're in a position where you're like i i just don't have
the energy to do it you have to just tell yourself the energy it doesn't matter like it doesn't matter
if you're tired and it hurts you have to do it because it's not supposed to feel good until you've
earned it you know here's here and this is it most it's most applicable to our audience who are full
of people who you know i assume want to be some sort of like youtube content career you know only
kind of career but this applies to everything this applies to any sort of like you know arts and crafts
you might want to do outside or just any sort of general hobby you know go into the gym or anything
like that this applies to all of it all if you want to like leave your job and start your own small
business of anything yeah exactly exactly anything it requires effort i mean i i i
climbed a mountain one time i was physically very weak at the time i was not somebody who
you would think could hike a mountain and it hurt and it sucked but i wanted to climb the mountain
and at the end of the day a a phrase i'll give you is don't run from the pain run with the pain
just be in pain because if you let yourself suffer that little bit then that means it'll
pay off later you know because you won't have to suffer anymore once you're at the top of the
goddamn mountain then it's over and it's like you know you you can sit you can keep you can take
your time inching up the mountain and it's just like you're gonna be on this mountain for fucking ever
or you can just climb the goddamn thing through the pain grit your teeth you reach the top and
you're like now i don't have to climb a fucking mountain anymore now there was a good thing where
someone's like pain points true north this this whole like you know speed this whole like fucking
thing we're this whole vibe we're writing right now any point in the last five years up until a
couple months ago my reaction would have been yeah right now though my reaction is yeah but okay hold
the fuck on though because i have been starting to more value a life of quality work rather than
like manic exhausting quantity work and i think that if you temper your mind correctly you can get
more done with less energy you know hashtag works mark not heart right and i even think well i didn't
have the freedom to do that before when i had my regular job cleaning windows that was uh you know i
had to i had to go double time in order to make progress right is that is anyone still here everyone's
be dead silent yeah okay okay cool i guess i have everyone's attention who so i i'm thinking back
because at the time i think more so than like my hours were booked my hours were taken up what was
even more so is that my ability to sit reflect and plan was was dwindled it wasn't it was it was uh it
was crippled and i think back now with with the greater clarity of thought i have now and i think
you know what i could have done i could have uh worked a little bit longer for a bit saved up some
money and got my own work vehicle and if i have my own work vehicle then i could actually then get
involved with the actual scheduling of the business because you know family business and i could have
actually scheduled my own work and said oh dad i'll take that job and that job and that job and i
could have taken control of my own job and actually started setting my own hours on my own as it was
because working in a family business while you don't have to deal with like the pressures of
like a boss who doesn't love you as a human being you do have to deal with the fact that you're kind
of being owned like you're just sort of like you're kind of stuck you can't you don't really have like
employee rights you can't say something like hey reduce my hours boss it's more like hey could you
reduce my hours dad and he'll be like uh yeah when they get around to it right i mean to strain
to strain my metaphor as far as i possibly can because that's what i love to do like i think that
when when you go to climb a mountain you often you you're saddled with this big backpack and you're
like you got to climb the mountain with this big backpack it's got all your necessary provisions
in it and you're just like okay and you start climbing and it fucking sucks and at some point
if you're really smart what you should do is sit down open the backpack go through it and make sure
it's all shit you actually need to be in there because the climb doesn't have to be as hard as
you think it does it just comes if you're carrying a bunch of it's always more important to work
smart than work hard so make sure you're going in the right direction as efficiently as possible
first before you get manic and work really really hard and do all that that's the mistake i've made
time and time again is that i yeah i know a lot of like what is the smart way to work but there's
there's often another smart way like the way i always looked at it was like okay on youtube you
have to game the algorithm and do content that everybody likes and all that stuff and and like
i don't want to do that so i'm just gonna work super hard and bust out as many videos as possible
and constantly be flooding things and then like over time i've come to realize that there are other
ways to work smart it doesn't have to be like this this is not a dichotomy that has to exist
like um and i one of my catchphrases that i'm trying to get off the ground is uh if you haven't
found a paradigm that works you're not done looking because there is there always is a paradigm
that works but like if you stop the book anywhere you're never gonna find it you just got to always
be questioning what you're doing and if it could be better so so i'm gonna like quickly go through
the specific scenario that happened with me just to a model so you can model yourself right so i
started trying to do youtube in may of 2014 by the way before he does that just consider if you want
end up where divu is right now consider whether or not you're going to do this all right no no no
i'm talking about how i could have done better and been in a better situation by now okay that's
what i'm saying learn from my mistakes my shortcomings is actually what i'm saying so i started
trying to do youtube in may of 2014 and it was around july of 2015 that i finally had a hour
reduction arrangement with my dad which was instead of working full time you work two days a week
and you don't uh all the money that you make just go straight to expenses and 200 dollars of your
youtube money you just pay that to me in exchange for only having to work two days a week which is
you know even less than part-time i think so that was the arrangement i got and once i got to that
nirvana wait wait wait sorry sorry i'm confused all your earnings go from your job go to expenses
hold on i was getting money i was being paid money i could do whatever with right right okay the
idea was hey dad i want to have fewer hours and he's like okay so you know your expenses stay the
same but you're just sure you don't get your own spending money right the money just goes straight
to expenses but then you're making a few hundred bucks a month from youtube right so you give me
200 to cover the rest of the expenses in exchange you only have to do two up two days a week of work
i feel like you're are you paying more to work less this seems i don't understand right but basically
what i'm buying is time instead of having to work five why do you have to buy time from your dad this
seems very odd yeah you know maybe what that's the situation i was in right of like you know i'm an
adult i should be paying my own expenses right you might i mean i think i've been having conversations
with with col lately she's like you know i think the way your dad treated you was actually very
manipulative and uh almost abusive and i'm like uh you know well probably but whatever it was the
situation i was in lots people are in manipulated abused situations and you have to figure it out
right so i basically just spent a year my whole strategy was make videos that get popular enough
so that i can buy my way out of this job but what i could have done is made videos
that's always on the table well then it would have fucked over my family because they needed the
money that i was well that's their problem not yours and you wouldn't be able to eat yeah i mean
it's my problem it's me paying for my own expenses and i was already an adult i was 20 years old so
i don't know whatever this episode is just very strange to me and i don't understand i understand
no no no i understand but like so what i could have done is is worked on videos a bit here and
there but focused actually on working more cleaning more windows for a bit saved up some money got a
work vehicle by probably the end of summer a really good vehicle and use that to schedule my own
hours and then just through my own agency been able to reduce my hours on my own time right
and that would have made things so much more relaxed you know i would have been able to focus
and think because when i finally had the chance to focus and think a year after starting youtube
that's when i was able to start getting successful so it's like you know maybe don't think of of
like this job as something you have to just kill right away as fast as possible like think of
it as a beast that you can tame and live with for a while i mean this is what i have done i have you
know so yeah you're right and and for a long time i thought oh man nat you're not going full in on it
but i'm like you know what your videos are good what can i say you can't argue with results you
can't fucking argue with the results uh so as much as we say oh yeah you got it you know no pain no gain
at the same time you know at the same time pain like physical stress sleep loss eating sugary foods
that is taking years off the end of your life that you could also no pain no gain but also don't
go out of your way to get punched in the face right yeah so lately i've been like it's you know what
i remember there was one like workaholic guy who like created an incredible business and burned
himself out completely at 35 by then he had looked at the metabolism of an 80 something he was forced
to quit and he said you know what for workaholics like me burning the candle in both ends is actually
the easy option a work life balance is actually the true skill that's the truly difficult thing
that the true master dude that is some shit that i'm in the middle of middle of trying to figure
out because like i for me working was just like it was just a way to kill time a lot of the time
like it's it's that i was so lonely and bored for most of my life that like working is the just
like what i defaulted to and this is why like in 2016 i was making like this insane number of
after dark vlogs and like um it's funny because there's a lot of fans who miss that era that they
call like the losing your mind in your room era because they related to it but it's like you did
that for too long there'd be no mind left to lose exactly i was legitimately losing my mind
in this room because it was i had gotten to a point in my career where i was making enough money
to be completely set and satisfied and i didn't know what to spend the money on like if you hear
the song rotten i say i got six thousand bucks and don't know what i want to own and it was like
because i had saved up that much which was a lot for me at the time like i'd never had that much
money and it was like i had already bought all the equipment for my job i was living in a good
situation and like i you know i would have liked to eventually move out of my parents house but i
didn't really have a reason to do so because everything was fine so it was just like well
what do i fucking do like what do i do with all the time i have in life so i just started making
videos constantly because i had no better idea of how to spend my time other than just make
shit and make shit and like it was it was so strange because it was like i didn't really
have a plan it was just do this as much as possible because again working hard like
divu said is kind of the easy way it's easy to tell yourself well if i just work all the time
is there's an obvious benefit i'm gonna make money but like most of those videos were not
making me any money most of them were not creatively satisfying most of it like you know the the best
thing that came of it is that people got so much of my voice that they in they just anybody who
was watching all of it because they had that little free time is going to love me but that has
huge diminishing returns because as soon as though that audience finds something to do with
their lives they're not following me anymore exactly me included it's true just just straight
up flooding the world the world with as much of your voice as possible like it's it's not always
going to work unless you have like a huge number of people but even then they're going to cycle out
constantly and and it's unreliable and so like at the time i was really relying on like my hardcore
fans it's like this is my central money makers but like as those people started getting jobs
or leaving the house or some of them just weren't interested in what i had to say now because
eventually i ran out of like super unique things to say because i'm one guy how many ideas can i
fucking have you know um so like well eventually i started losing some of those people and and
what i mean by not having a ton of unique ideas like i think that i was giving people
like the the least creative version and there's some people who like when you just you just speak
to them because it feels like you're having a conversation it feels like friendly but like
those videos are never going to get the attention that a hui's law video would you know present
the same that video i just put out what is deep um it like i literally made this exact same video
as a vlog two years ago during that stint and it was because at the time i didn't know how to write
it as a as a video because i hadn't spent that time like thinking it through really considering
it it was like here's an idea let me turn on a camera and rant it as fast as possible and just
publish it and like maybe it's got like 10 000 views and like for those 10 000 people they're
like oh this video you just made on your main channel it's just the same thing i watched two
years ago but the one on the main channel has 70 000 views because it was written and edited
and has a catchy thumbnail and title and it was prepared for an audience because i used in it i
just was using it as an advertisement for the iam games channel but like difference right right
used to be like the whole vlog group made sense in 2016 when a lot of people said they liked the
vlogs more i think i did too because the vlogs included a lot more side notes things that weren't
really essential to the point but just made the point more humanly digestible and it was much
more naturalistic whereas your videos were still really stiff and that has pretty well evened out
now you're writing in your vo it's all very naturalistic now it's your videos basically are
finally as good as i've always wanted them to be since i first found out about you in 2013 doing
pony shit like why thank you like yeah like this this year your your videos finally got that sweet
spot of just casuality i've always wanted it's really funny just agree you've never been as good
as uh sword art sucks etc go back to that please do more of those what would you like the sword art
one more of the astrosquare oh astrosquare that's true that's the best one um well you just like it
because it's long uh i like it because there's lots of parts and there's a great narrative going
between it's like compelling it's really long but long is good i mean if you went back and watched
those videos you'd realize that like half of it could be cut easily okay but but the fact of the
matter is i remember it more fondly than any other content and i think that's a powerful thing
i think if i'm objective okay i'm gonna also armchair psychology you and like tell you what
you're really thinking as if i fucking know but it's my pet theory with a lot of people
what did you when people tell you to go back to the astrosquare i think what they're telling you is
go back to finishing plans to fruition like here's the plan okay the plan finish the plan
you know because like the only reason standalone videos that i think are quite good i just like
the astrosquare stuff the best the only reason the astrosquare sucks was a plan that got followed
through is that i wrote the whole thing before it was out you know well most of it but in any case
like the people like astrosquare because it's it's super long and they want me to write stuff that's
super long and that kind of that that's sort of flowing engagement where you're like apart it's
like a show it feels like a whole show because it's as long as a whole show um and and i know that like
if you want to make something short you have to make it very robust and tight and great for people
to really remember it if you make something longer you can be a little bit more lax and you can you
could be more free flowing and people will still appreciate it because they're involved with it
for so long and i also want to talk about that that thing with that i was saying earlier about how
everybody remembers the best parts and everybody forgets the the worst elements exactly this applies
heavily to my fans talking about my content because almost all of them have some period that
they remember as the best period those also do have the most views which is a pretty good metric
of success i mean it really depends like i get my views have always been kind of all over the place
it just depends on what what videos can you just recognize that one just was the best which it was
which which one what are you talking astrosquare like the whole series doesn't have the most views
it's got like millions of views every part or no one million views i think no it's getting the first
couple parts in the last part are like getting there they'll be there in like a year but they're
okay maybe i'm wrong yeah i mean the fucking how to recognize a terrible anime has over three
million views by far my most successful video dear crunchy roll stop has more than any particular
part of the astrosquare and that came out last month okay um anyway drama so like my point is
that people look back and they they see they they remember like all the best things about those
i cannot watch a lot of my own shit like even the astrosquare sucks there's parts of it i just skip
because they're not good like my writing has gotten so much better my vio my uh you know if
i edit it myself my editing most of my old videos are like weird because they were trying to like
get past youtube copyright shit and it's just like you know of course people are going to remember
the emotional resonance they had with the videos and not like the actual quality of them which you
can only really experience in the moment you know but i mean okay like let's say that's all true
that's fine but why not apply that to like a new project all your better skills and all
oh i would love to mate you give me a fucking idea for one well okay uh i mean if the issue
was just you don't have an idea for one i mean i'm not trying to tell you what to do i'm just
you know laying out a case here i think you know it's not like i it's not like i haven't done it
because i don't think it's a good idea of course i would love to do another astrosquare sucks i
don't have anything i could talk about for 13 videos okay fair enough fair enough this isn't
even really a criticism i was just pointing out yeah an observation uh but by the way though i will
say because uh a certain a certain show is coming back for an entire year sort out online season three
50 weeks in a row get ready that's gonna be uh that's gonna be something all right it's gonna be
something all right i'm gonna do it i'm gonna do a video for every episode if that wasn't clear
do it dude do it yeah see but then that brings up like i think your greatest enemy so far has been
your like very unreliable attention span for projects you know that like hey man i did i did
my little pony every single time an episode came out uh yeah i mean did you just done a couple of
those like complete you know who cares if it was years ago what difference does that make i was the
same person you aren't doing it anymore i don't know man i feel like i feel like once you didn't
have to be as desperate for the money you've had a harder time like keeping up on things no i mean
there was the me and digi show that we would go back to my anime blogger days and you will find
that every single season i attempted to cover a show weekly and every single season i failed
until uh until my little pony and you know why because it comes out at the same time every week
and i just thought said i have to get a video out within four hours of it coming out for me the
key word is uh you have to get the video out because like you were desperate for the money and i
just feel like once uh after work came out i'm desperate for the money again i am i am beyond
bankrupt so uh like i have no money right that's why i phrase that your greatest enemy has been
your ocd so uh no not ocd adhd for projects and i'm pretty sure like you know last month pretty
well convinced me that you are fucking on points once more just make sure to keep being borderline
poor and you'll definitely be good digi if you want to bring back uh best guy ever in digi
review something i'll i'll i'll give you a cheap rate i'll give you a cheap rate for my services
that's what i'll do i'll consider it people um people wanted me to do that with saos return
but i have better ideas fair enough hey i have a total complete left turn topic uh because this
is i don't know where we've been we've been around the world videos like 15 minutes what he okay here
here's the topic uh uh uh skateboarding i am now a skateboarder and it is a huge life upgrade
and i'm better than all of you why that's the topic of is it just because it's a funner way
to like navigate the level geometry of your neighborhood i don't even do it um to get anywhere
i do it purely for fun and also to do pokemon go uh it is the most fun and i mean if it was
a normal skateboard that'd be some pussy shit we're talking about that boosted board that's
that's what i thought i knew that i was like there's no way you're talking about a regular
fucking skateboard no no no certainly not i got it's michelle's skateboard i got it for a birthday
it's a longboard she lets me borrow it you know let the cuck i am uh it's uh just the most fun
thing i've done in a long time i was doing it for hours yesterday i was doing it immediately
before we started filming this episode and i can't wait to go back out immediately after we're done
it just is great and it feels good and it's a perfect temperature and time of year to do it
and also i'm hoping it'll just be somewhat of exercise every single day i shout out like i would
have really i would have gotten into skateboard to me as a kid skateboards were always just the
thing that you do to get tricks and i don't think i would ever use skateboard to do tricks because
i don't care i would just if i were to just get into skateboard as like you know it's a pokemon
go machine dude a part of like exercise and also you know you're out in the world and you're
going slightly faster so you have that joy of going a little bit faster so you're not too fast
i think i would really enjoy it but it was just always the tricks machine to me you also wouldn't
do well on a skateboard i think because uh what is it uh unicycles are rowdy and skateboards are
killer so right i thought you were gonna say that i would be which would also make sense oh that too
i guess that people do skateboard i um shout out to who to the commenter currently typing the
comment about how he got really excited when nate said he was skateboarding and then utterly
furious when he found out it was a boost boosted board oh did you think somebody did that i think
so i think that'll that's probably happen somebody in our audience has to be like a really devout
skateboarder that's probably true i don't know i've uh uh i wore a lot of skater i wore a lot of
jinko jeans as you see as a youth and now finally it's coming full circle as i am the cool guy i was
always destined to be uh yeah it's super fun imagine me uh my my on my boosted board
fucking the the fucking remote in one hand cruising at max speed uh with my pokemon go
app on catching so many fucking magikarp as i cruise by the river and in my other hand
a full tankard of hule just chugging what the hell is your millennial levels are at 12
please draw it everyone please imagine you're looking at everyone that's probably like they're
so jealous of you look at the expert they're so jealous of me and oh yeah devoo by the way we
don't say millennials anymore we're now doomers ah yes i love that doomers doomers it's a new
meme on fourchan uh where there's because there's the boomers and then there's the doomers and then
there's the zoomers you know let me read it to you i've actually got in front of me right now
because i'm going to johnson it to me all right the doomer are we back on urban dictionary right
now uh it's it's basically urban dictionary but it's just the image it's the image itself um so it's
the actual source uh insomnia tried nofap music reading fitness forgot how to lack how to cry or
laugh no you got to go outside is groceries or booze no you got to read the original that the 23
year old boomer image oh okay i guess i don't have there's ones for our doomer rather there's ones for
each different age of like in the 20s um okay this looks like a late 20s guy yeah the original
is the 23 year old doomer and it's pretty well i will post it actually um all right let me let me
post this we can put on screen or whatever i was like getting so excited like oh my god i've been
going for like over two hours oh yeah this is a little post i'm not gonna have to edit anything
in and then immediately immediately we have to we have to have something that's gonna be oh yeah
that's just disgusting i googled 23 year old doomer oh here we go here we go got it um let me
fucking link this shit did you know this would be a good time to announce that we we've jumped on
this bandwagon hardcore yes we have a doomer t-shirt we do you do you can buy it in the iam games uh
our newest our newest creation the doomer t-shirt uh i will get a link to that as well so everyone
can enjoy oh my god just this 23 year old doomer is so real thinks crypto will fix all his problems
that one that's a huge one oh my god oh my god i love him plus picks his meme collection knows how
knows he needs to quit weed won't yeah all right this is all good this is all good uh this isn't
even the original one i'm not going to endorse doomer i prefer millennial i'm sticking with
well they're both you know they they do different things tell me if you think that when you see the
t-shirt yeah where where tom has cleverly cleverly reinvented the doom logo as a doomer
oh that's good i don't know it looks like this whole digi tom t-shirt industry not really getting
me i don't like the iam game sure it's cool you don't like the iam game well your taste sucks and
you suck i'm into this doomer one i might get this one this is pretty sick i'm fine with like the
next generation being called doomers but i guess they're gonna be called no they're zoomers because
yeah they're zoomers dog generation c they're the zoomers what what is that but like what do they
do that like a kid with like shaved sides of his head uh doing the fortnite dance and i don't know
like at like a carly ray jeppson concert i guess yeah all right look here's here's how i think of it
all right if you if the the if your turning point in your childhood was pokemon you're a doomer if
your turning point your childhood was minecraft you're a zoomer yes that is on point i think we're
gonna be able i ruby and sapphire you're like you're a zoomer okay munchie you're like a you're
like a uh you're like a like a um like very early zoomer i would say you know that i think about
it the raddies and the killers are really just doomers versus zoomers uh at the end of the day
oh dude okay munchie i was actually just yesterday in a debate like where does millennial and and
gen z began and the thing is people are gonna keep debating about it people keep debating when
millennial even starts whether it's the mid or the late eighties but i think what's gonna happen is
it'll be a lot more clear once two parents who are definitively stereotypical millennials have a kid
and then that kid becomes a teenager and begins to express themselves once we see what the new
stereotype is we'll start to then reverse engineer you have to let the generation become old first
we're getting i know i know dude like i mean the zoomers are already like adults now
but like yeah they're getting but when we get to the late era zoomers that's when we'll truly
understand it's some of them are what i'm looking forward to it may not be the zoomers it may be
the kaboomers which will probably be the last one and and it all comes full circle back to boom
right no no it's gonna go back beyond that what i'm thinking is gonna happen is that there's gonna
be like the the generations will keep getting more and more lazy and privileged and entitled and then
there's going to be a reverse polarity when there's like this sudden huge increase of like
religiosity and like discipline for its own sake after like society collapses right and it'll be
the first generation like 200 years where like the children are more those would be the bloomers
the bloomers yeah and there is a generation defined by like our parents are fucking lazy
it's really funny you say that because there is an image of the bloomer that is exactly what
devu is describing what yeah no look up look up bloomer and like you'll get or um i found it in
the like well while searching doomer i found the bloomer it was like a guy with a big smile and
like everything he's like perfectly moral and like i got it i got it right here it's like i oh my god
this is me this is me i'm a bloomer for sure oh it's too fucking small hang on it's actually crazy
that face uh i disgusting i hate that i'm no longer the child soldier there is a person one of my
consorts in the ratty rough house here we paradox crocs the ancient stignitary of urban development
that guy he has a he has a deep voice and he's fucking like i think like 16 years old or he's
going to turn 60 he's a really young lad and it's kind of crazy to me that i have fans who are now
younger than me and i could not be happier and i could not be more thrilled to have paradox crocs
the youngin on my side it's just it's just okay you know what i turned 18 i am now technically
adult and all the reasons why people used to like me they now have no justification they're all god
yeah and and now why they hate and and and now that my middling skills have been exposed as
middling skills and not like oh you know like you're good as like you're good for a kid much you
know you have good art and you have good humor you know for a child now all that is gone and now
they just judge me as a normal person and now i'm when i have no more fans and so i just stay up
every night i just drink gourmet tea and i go to sleep at like 3 a.m and think about how i'm
going to kill myself which is a real yeah that that's the uh yeah really was literally once i turn
24 i rose oh shit i'm no longer young i'm definitely feeling old now it's it's the true uh it's the
real big lie about hunter hunter where because there's so many fucking hiatuses they get to be
wow you are good for a kid gone and killer would get to be for 20 fucking years because
their story progresses so slowly they get to be in that in that nice loop of you know you're not
as good as all of us but for a 14 year old you're pretty fucking good but that period of your life
dwindles away so fucking fast you can't relax i don't i don't consider mungy i have not considered
mungy a child for like three years now like i don't think of you as being good for your age
i just think you are like the best graphic designer i know right anyway so i read the
bloomer meme and i'm reversing direction i completely am okay with this boomer zoomer
doomer meme as long as i get to be a bloomer i endorse let's let listen to this i have to
read out some of the stuff from this 27 year old bloomer now i'm 28 but this is just literally me
listen yeah me too juice out black pills spits out white pills a living breathing moral booster
for all nearby unbreakable resolve love for his people far exceeds any hatred he has ever felt
doesn't smoke drug-free peak optics loved by our guys and normie's alike nostalgia motivates him
instead of depressing him sees the better world he wants to build superimposed on the dark world
around him this is literally me this is me i am the bloomer click and the prototypical alpha
and i have now made the image my desktop background it tiles four directions
oh god this is great i feel really happy we you know if you're like an arty since we know that
none of you are bloomers and you're all doomers go buy our doomer t-shirt instead yeah oh i should
like let me let me read because this this image you posted has the actual like original doomer
on it so okay here's the 23 year old doomer which is probably most of our audience
maybe plays ps1 sometimes no hope of career advancement alcoholism tried reading tried
fashion tried lifting a shame to speak with family another night in high risk for opioid addiction
hasn't made a friend since 2012 lost youth cares but knows there's nothing he can do
cloud wrap has a tinder but too disgusted to use it slash nightwalk there's so many of these out
there there's so many oh god it's called being 23 and 2018 i guess so we need to convert these
doomers into bloomers though we can do it guys follow the life advice i've given you get out
there start meeting people don't get the problem is people get locked up and they don't change their
lives they just get stuck in a rut you got to switch it up people think smart you know that
you're just a machine you are just a godless animal and it's your job to make your life good
that nobody gives a fuck about you except you who should care about your life with a burning
passion and be motivated by the stories of your heroes and live life the way they would
seize the opportunities that are in front of you god damn it and be a god damn fucking bloomer
buy a bloomer t-shirt on redbubble.com slash best guy ever which i'm going to go make after this
podcast guy you sometimes say things i think are 25 stupid but every 20 while you say shit that's
100 percent correct yes thank you it feels good it feels good this is not one of those times
though buy a doomer i like that the bloomer standing in like a wheat field just yes just i don't
know what that symbolizes but it's completely out of touch with reality i would consider myself
to be what happens when you fuse a bloomer and a doomer which is a devil man that's what that's
well okay okay he's the body of a devil but the heart of a man yeah well guys should we move on
to questions this is an excellent meme to end on i think shall we transition into a couple of these
old uh voice mails here old old voice mails hell yeah all right let's do it let me uh let me pull
one up all right we've got to do our contractually obligated one from one spar here let me uh what's
up with that what's what's what's what's going on there uh well let's let's find out last we
met him i think he was like under attack so let's let's see what happens he was locked in a mental
asylum i thought right oh that's right let's see if he's escaped all right let's check in
apcp good news made it out of that place okay planning a daring escape for the better part of
the week involved disguises and pyrotechnics and then i just realized actually that the
none of the doors were locked you see when you pass out of your computer bleeding on the eyes
like with a whole bunch of youtube tabs open and a big text document full of time stamps
they just they just send you to a normal hospital anyway i took that ipad i made it to a starbucks
and they might not let you use the bathroom without paying but at least there's free wi-fi oh that's
that's updated as far as the bounty goes listen it's really important that i get these timestamps
hey you don't know anything no no ma'am i'm waiting for an associate we're gonna have a business
no sir you've been here for three days you have to leave i know you don't have to call the cops
i and go get all the cops right okay look guys i'll take care of this i'll get back to you later
one spar got kicked out of starbucks hold on hold on you're talking like one spar weekly yeah
that's him hey one spar the number of google search results is not a data point
oh did he use that for something mr beatong used that as a joke once it's not a real statistic
okay i don't know what you're referring to but fair enough uh i suppose that's accurate um all right
well good luck one spar uh keep sending him those uh timestamps for the star fleet things i think
that's what he's doing correct uh yeah there you go all right moving on we got one from house of
claude well i think someone last week did somebody's gone i'm in middle of a pokemon go up and i just
started thinking subconsciously i've just stopped drinking pop oh good you guys and i didn't really
all that much let's see from michigan but i did that because he says pop yeah i just wanted to say
that um oh good i don't have 95 percent of a liter of water i have like half of it so i'm gonna
oh god he's doing it again oh the sound effects what is he drinking like half a cup of water or
something half a liter of water that was lit last week he drank 95 percent of a liter of water
and that was that him was that him i think it was the same guy right oh okay i couldn't tell
those it was the same guy or he had been inspired by that other guy oh you might be right i could be
wrong someone let me know the comments how right or wrong i am yeah please do um i won't look at it but
here's one from um uh them snakes them snakes send in this one uh all right let's see what he's got
greetings my name is them snakes i am a sentient pile of snakes
in the shape of a human and i take umbridge with the pcp member ben saint
good he's not here as ben knows the sequel is never as good as the original and as the original
i have no choice but to inject my venom into his ben saint veins his only hope for survival
is to convince all of his patrons to pledge to me patreon.com slash them snakes
that's patreon.com slash them snakes i'm checking right now i i i have is the basis of his content
ben saint sounds too much like them snakes is phonetically identical it's it's amazing
them snakes is a real patreon that was created in september of this year so it just got made
about them snakes for this bit his bio is i am literally snakes they them and his pronouns don't
don't by the way my my additional headcanon is that this pile of snakes is the pile of snakes
from a gibbs uh try to catch pump game oh right i'm talking about yes yeah that's my headcanon
okay they know each other that was an excellent one of them snakes um wait what do you want ben
to do like make him ever all his patrons go to him oh yeah that's right right um okay let's hope that
ben does that and survives another week all right here's another one um wait hang on saloni okay this
one is from wise to your ways uh we should probably hey here's it it's all about that search engine
optimization gotta upload friday three p.m eastern standard time gotta hit up those kids who could
just come out of school so that by the time their fellow friends on the on the west coast are out
of school it's already blown up on the trending charts you already know how it is you already know
how to maximize profits you already know how to get those books cooked oh it's good
it is pretty good wise to your ways uh i was gonna also we release at 2 p.m we should be on
eastern standard time suggestion if you're sending in one where you want like a specific member to
hear it you should probably put that in the title like play this on an episode with ben or something
i've been i've been starting to tag i've got it actually i have one that it was for gib and i'm
just not going to read that because that's like a gib one so i've been trying to do a little bit
better with that but um all right we'll we'll keep working on it all right yeah if you could put in
the in the in your name or title that would be helpful yeah but here's another one this one is
this one is simply called pcp theme 2018-09 uh let's see what we have here
perhaps an update i got a new pcp theme here it goes all right starting up get ready what is that
it sounds like some hit
is this the german national anthem
i gotta find out
the matching lyrics to the other lyrics is very nice
is this is this a song that can get us blocked in germany could this happen is this a hitler song
you know what it probably is um i apologize to all our german listeners who can't hear us
because this episode was just blocked because it's probably that's probably the nazi anthem and
or you're currently getting arrested for having listened to it all right yeah uh all right here
we go yeah that's germany's a kooky play saying it um here we go this one's from uh tomaso choco
oh i think we had a mess from today is the one-year anniversary of me starting my diet
i could help breads rice, potatoes, pastas, and sugar and lost about 150 pounds so i want to
ask you how much you're celebrating the town's probably gonna say go to cuckold's landing but
i don't really like the idea the boy's getting sprung when the southern bells are being rung
so i don't want to do that anyway okay there was a lot there digi and davu i think you missed it
but like i think it was our boy choco taco was like driving through like south caroline or something
and like he said like hey guys if you're still looking for a place to set up pcb hq i just found
a place called cuckold's landing in like south carolina um but anyway this guy lost 150 pounds
in one year since going on a diet it sounded like keto if that's not it was on keto if that's not a
a ringing endorsement for not eating bread ever again i don't know what is bread is just bad for
you it is it really is it's that's that is bread yes scott pilgrim bread and does indeed does make
you fat and it's not no that means truffle gar law from one piece is actually on to something
because he hates bread but fuck that guy uh all right oblivion fall another one let's do it up
mate you are doing this wrong your entire approach with playing these voicemails through soundcloud
is a complete farce and an inefficient solution if you actually cared about doing this right you
would install vb audio cables and voice meter so that way you could play the audio directly
through your microphone to discord with no loss in quality what you can actually do is split the
audio in your computer to different channels and you can toggle which channels come through your
microphone and discord and which channels go through to your headset it turns this is what i want
to hear beastly audio machine dream and you can do so much with it and the best part is you don't
have to waste time on soundcloud and you don't have to delay starfleet from happening with your
stupid inefficient bullshit if you need help setting it up you can contact me i'm on the discord my
username is green you've got to eat your greens god damn it get voice meter you little bitch
that is a super helpful suggestion uh i don't know like will cost money i assume that it will
but i should i should just go reach out to oblivion i i know he i know it's probably just
cuz it it's funny but i've never understood the mentality of people who frame some like incredibly
obscure technology knowledge that you don't have like it's your fault for not knowing it like
how could you possibly not know about vba split gx 17 fucking color arrangement you bitch like
i i appreciate his expertise but please my my fragile this goes back to what you were talking
about earlier about about uh what debu said with like thrash whatever if you don't know the specific
genre like you know this guy just is so into audio it's like yeah i mean he's a music fan so i mean
i'm sure he's doing it because it's funny and maybe he listens to his biggest problem and
is taken out of every voicemail they get that's true uh okay here's another one this is from
truth sayer truth sayer all right i'm ready for the truth lay some truth tick tock tick tock best
guy ever loves the cork well he said the truth i thought it was gonna be like some heavy existential
thing about how time is like fleeting yeah but uh he brought it back and brought it back i feel better
again um okay that was pretty good let's see if we can follow up here's one from iron beaver um
let's let's let's see nate since you want to create the star fleet and the federation and all of that
utility and bullshit i will assume you also want to start all the other things that
lead that will lead us towards the star fleet like a third world war of 2053 um it is true that in
in star trek universe there was a nuclear world war three uh before star fleet got created but
but actually they really could have just because there was like a bunch of history in star trek
where like a bunch of like horrific like dictatorial regimes took over and then world war three happened
and like society kind of collapsed but like what actually made star fleet finally happen
was just like after all that bullshit uh there's a movie one of the star trek movies about this
first contact i think it was just where um key for southerland's dad uh he just invented the warp
drive like just because he was a good science man he just did it and when he activated it during this
like test the volcans who were nearby found them and were like oh shit you guys have the warp drive
and then they made contact and then they became best buds and then they like changed the world
they got post scarcity and then star fleet happened so you actually could just skip all that stuff
probably so it'd be nice to avoid that how did we uh how did we in in mass effect how did
he manage yeah how did we discover the master he discovered prothean ruins on mars yeah they found
that's right that's right that's what they did um there's one more here come on digi it's like the
first thing in the codex yeah no i just couldn't remember off the top of my head i'm so sad like i
want to go back and play mass effects all the way through because like it really is just star trek
only better and for free um and it was just such a joy for me to like play through yeah that's true
it's it was such a joy to play through like the first like couple hours that game with like all the
lore and like like learning about like basically their version of star fleet and like how it all
happened and meeting all the races ah it's a good game good game i wish i was playing it
oh speaking of of mass effect i found out that mass effect and drama is 10 times worse than i ever
would have thought because uh someone in the comments of our iam game stream of it said there
are literally zero quarians in all of andromeda which is like disgusting because the quarians were
fucking sick and they just didn't include them at all i guess they just felt like they wanted to
like cut some of the races and maybe like the quarian story is like kind of over because like
they were like this nomadic guys who oh yeah why would you want to bring people who've been
nomadic forever to a completely unknown galaxy how fucking retarded are you you really don't want
entire race of scavengers and like people who salvage it to go to a completely unknown galaxy
where you have no foothold at all what use could that possibly be maybe they're really sick of it
and they don't want to do it right of course oh god wait a minute wait a minute you know what
i read about that you know i there was one line in that uh bloomer description that i read before
i started to bring this back up it's just i just noticed this as i still had my search for bloomer
i just noticed um like there's others like there was one line in the bloomer thing that was um
what was it love for his people far exceeds any hatred he has ever felt i thought that was a
little weird but didn't you know that was fine then i see another one does it say something about
like jews because these these all originate from pole i think there's a connection to the alt
right with bloomers that i didn't okay this whole meme comes from pole like the doomer
bloomer all that meme it's from pole so uh yeah look look at this bloomer link maybe we're trying
to make it we're trying to expand it beyond the realm of pole because it's going to stay there
i just said like i am a bloomer so many times i didn't anticipate this turn but look look at this
one bloomer's friday night a condom you're funny anon that's not going to secure a future for any
white oh no i didn't expect all all this time we should have known of course yeah i got i bet a
lot of people are going to be like lol he says he's a boomer shit i don't go on polling up to know
which are the good memes and which are the bad memes no this is this is fine it's that that's
what's so great about the doomer meme is that the initial one doesn't have any pole shit if you
read the other ones that other people expanded on it they all added more pole shit in there but like
you know i think this this meme has legs to go beyond it's also on x so it's not just on pole
it's also been we can salvage this one and like when it's like his people i thought i meant like
yo yo me and my people we're like hanging out we're going out tonight you know no no no no that's
how i interpreted it um all right here's one more voicemail from uh chung skingy chung skingy
all right all right be good quick question tell the uh pokemon gore is in the pcp how do i
stop from throwing rocks at me and call me autistic while i play pokemon go
he said how do i get people to stop throwing rocks and calling me autistic while i play pokemon go
that's just part of the game munchie they they they balance it it's a feature not a bug
embrace it those are free geodudes coming at you dude just catch them um okay that's enough
for now it's enough voicemails let's uh let's get to a couple of those pity ass weak ass text
questions and then fucking ship this bad boy out the first one got me right off the bat totesual
asks if you wanted to be any planet what would you be hmm oh sadder yeah i was gonna uh well yeah
yeah it's it's taken now i'll i'll be i'll be the sun uh yeah but i want to be the sun
well whoa dude if mario threw captain sun could he become sun mario and burn
oh wow if if you put the bow uh what is it the oh my god the sun oh dude you gotta be sexy the sun
would be so hot oh meme is dead we killed it finally it's over oh oh there's this one kind
the rck chat there just is fucking begging us to discuss bowserette i just want to say that
bowserette is the worst meme and i hate it it's about that my dude but okay i pardon you i have no
problem with it it is just a thing it is like it's just another thing whatever uh i prefer a lot of
the original you know i've looked for lots of great bowser porn have not found it but i have
found lots of just generally sexy images so people need to step up their game and make actual porn
not this bullshit but you can't you can't post actual porn on on reddit and i mean on a twitter
and get all the fucking free likes and retweet right yeah i guess that's true yeah i mean i went
to x hentai and looked for a dojin there was none there come on coming get to it um all right
here's here's one from at giga munch at giga munch says uh story line it's just if pinocchio said
my nose will grow now what would happen hmm i mean uh what uh this is a conundrum okay here's a
question from to is there any fan of the show just move past that one is there any fan of the show
that you know of whose original creative content you respect or are yourself a fan of yes oh man
everyone in the jolem child found you let's go down the list now there's steve of course uh there
there's there's zack one two three z c one uh he makes yeah he's good uh silvia gunner stuff
there's that hippo great guy oh there's ethanok which debu i know you have a long history with
there's uh erowitz who's making a video game right now can we get can we get down in the
golden child foundry no down in there uh there's six and he makes great music uh uh you know there's
other people too uh i like everybody who does great art i haven't memorized any of your names
but you all do great art um there's like a he's a consort fucking fucking you know jade morrow
she's a great artist i don't think she's made anything i was kind of pondering the pokey
conundrum what was the question actually that's the only one i could think of off the top of my head
uh oh i don't know nexus mania obviously i mean he's just a yeah nexus does really great artists
he's all around are we just listening off viewers of the show who we like no we have good art yeah
good art oh people who do art mm people who have who's originally creative content you respect or
yourself a fan of well i'm thinking about it says original creative content so not just their fan art
of pcp but people who's original well i'm just gonna give a shout out to silent k who's completely
saved my ass with getting started on programming and shit currently in the process of like
un fucking a major bug that i have or a major hurdle i have to climb nice that's fucking sick
dude more so than that do we have do we have any rough eta of of the new release date no more
eta's i i had only one very rough eta now that that one's gone it's like taking the half life
re-approach now it's like it's like 99.8% done so all right we've moved up like 0.6%
since the last update then right oh excellent anyway silent k right even more so than being
good at like you know helping out saving my ass on shit he's just uh he's a great person to have
conversations about fucking uh life hacking optimizing your time with so so probably don't
talk to him asking him for life advice because he'd probably be like oh i'm talking to too many people
this is non optimal for my life but he's been really cool with me and he recommended me some
fucking audiobooks which really got me on this whole work smart not hard mentality specifically
deep work by cal newport and why we sleep by i don't remember his name but at some point
i'm just gonna force digi to read or listen to this book because he's one of those like
anti-sleep people this book convinces you oh shit oh no i'm no longer sleep the shorter your life
i am no longer anti-sleep that is not a thing anymore i mean i'm i'm anti-sleep the same way
that i'm anti-death that it's like a biological thing i wish i could rid myself of i've come around
on sleep uh partly because i'm old now and it's okay and it makes me feel good i mean if i were
you i'd be even more angry which is kind of how i feel that my weak human body has these weaknesses
that are getting more and more i mean the thing is when he says anti-sleep it's not just a matter
of i hate sleep it's that i was actively trying to end it that like i was looking for a way out
and now i am right i still feel the ire i feel that i have to waste all this time sleeping sure
but i have i have completely given into it and acknowledge that i need it and that it's okay
we're getting we're getting close you want if you want to have a chance to quell your ire this
book will explain because yes people haven't really understood why we sleep but they're finally starting
to figure it out i understand it now because like uh it it helps me to i mean i know that when
you sleep it like it lets your thoughts reorganize themselves it's kind of like a book goes in
extensive detail exactly like what it does with different parts of your brain and it's
so fucking cool to learn how like like no no okay they did a they did a test and this is written
by a guy who's like a sleep scientist so this isn't like a whole lot of oh hey i read an article
that said this about a study it's i did this fucking study where they had people in a sleep
laboratory read a bunch of facts and they put in a green r for remember and a and a red f for
forget next to every fact that they learned right they told them that means remember that means
forget but you actually want you to remember all of them equally ignore the forget and remember
had them go to sleep woke up the next day and they overwhelmingly remembered the shit that had
the green r for remember more than the red f for forget so the brain is able to process memories
overnight and it actually operates intelligently we may not have conscious control over it but we
are actually able to control what our brain does at night even if not like consciously directly
yeah i uh i believe all that i'm sleep fascinates me because uh some recent things that happen in
my life were caused by lack of sleep and it's it's very similar to when a computer has like
when it sounds like a memory leak and everything just like is wrong that's exactly what happens
to your brain if you don't sleep for long enough it's like it's not that you're at risk of dying
because you're not like rested it's that your brain just is confused and doesn't know where to put
all the information into what holes you know and it's just like it fucking goes haywire and like
now that i've been sleeping more regularly it's like i can i can also like now that i know this
like ever since like kind of realizing the fact that because somebody told me i guess at some point
that like your dreams are like reorganization of your thoughts and so like in spite of the fact
that i complain about us talking about dreams on the show because i think that
dreams don't mean anything to other people unless they know what's going on in your life
very particularly but if if you look at your dreams interpretively like usually i can look
back on my dream and say okay i know exactly what this was about like this it's all metaphorical
but i know exactly why i had this dream because like this is something that was either stressing me
out or this is something that uh and like you know if i reverse engineer it it makes perfect sense
in in terms of a metaphor you know uh anyway enough for this i don't want to talk about this
anymore kajoro bitter thorn asks which one of you is the most games this is the most important
question it's either a better name i want to say tom i'm pretty games i'm pretty games i don't know
i think ben is the most games in the pcp ben's probably the most games does he play i mean
why well what's your justification that he is the best at games ben is not the best at games
i'm the best at games god damn it i'm definitely the best at games tell that to the pokemon race
i won the dark souls race destroy ben was in the curvy race too though he did win the thing is
like i've seen not only does ben play games that like i can't even conceive of how the rules work
like like dwarf fortress and in fucking dungeon crawl stone soup but like there was that time
that uh me him and davu did a let's play of downwell and he hadn't played it in like six months and
he got to like the final boss on his first fucking try that she does get in the record the game
sometimes and also he like did a pretty good job at toho on like his first or second like like he
did like one game over ever playing it yeah what difficulty was it on i think it was on normal but
like he got a few levels in on like his first time ever playing toho which is like that's not that's
like that's like main character of story level of skill if you know what i mean okay ben's pretty
good at games but i'm better at action games and i'll run circles around him in kingdom hearts too
what i have to say hey listen to this question multi-player games maybe i don't really know i think
i've been catching my virtue of none of you playing online yeah i don't play tf2 or anything
so i i bet i could beat all of you at smash uh i don't think maybe when when ultimate comes out
it's gonna be yeah we have a switch now so i guess we'll find out i'm talking about melee i'm talking
about actual smash i could beat all of you an actual smash hey they say that this one looks pretty
good we got we've got directional air dodges back that's cool that's cool uh you don't carry your
running momentum into jumps it's retarded that's in don't that's in the original super mario bros on
ness oh that's rough that's uh that's rough hey okay listen to this question i love this question
this is fascinating i think it is from a female zoomer i believe that you can i mean that's my
assumption but we'll we'll see it's from at infinity rise one and they ask uh is it extra
to buy my that's how i could tell it to zoomer asking a question like that is it extra to buy
my crush the smash edition switch we're good friends and he knows i like him so yeah too much
or just do it don't weigh too much why the fuck are you doing way over the top dude you are a girl
okay not you are a girl if he's not already into you that's weird um i would wonder why that's the
case um i we're talking about like a three hundred dollar console right yeah i would not like so
just clearly buy i would not buy my best friend or no i wouldn't buy anyone that unless they were
sucking my cock at that moment yeah that's what i get to that's what i get to what i'm not i'm not
trying to stay like he'll never like you or like it's a loss you shouldn't have to buy like material
wealth to get someone to like you that's not how you shouldn't have to buy someone's affection
buying anything for someone because you want that are like you yeah like like you just
here's my advice show them a little thigh you show them a little just do that with smash underneath
it's not it's not it's not an issue of it being extra it's an issue of if that does work then you're
in a bad relationship if you know he's right because you bought him a switch that's fucked dude
by the way i'm assuming it's a girl because she said it's a he i mean it could be a gay guy i'm
just assuming here but like by the way if it is a gay man then go for it because i mean it is
different if it's if it's a man and he is like on the fence about being gay buy that switch
and maybe maybe you'll convince him if you buy okay i know he's on twitter i can never know
give him smash the hill make the match girl so i'm just assuming that that yeah if you are a girl
like don't believe what nate said oh if a guy doesn't like a girl there's something wrong i think
there are a lot of guys who will like any girl who likes them but yeah i think it's like you know
there's sort of a mad toxic masculinity pressure to act like every guy is like that you know like
so i don't think all guys are like that i don't think i just mean like like what the real situation
is like if you're a girl you've got like a friend who's a guy and like you're into him
and like you want like to make it a romantic thing the solution is definitely not to like just buy
him presents and like hope that he makes the switch it's to in some more like court like like
full part full way you have to make yourself like clearly just show that you are romantically
interested but here's the part of the tweet that concerns me is that they said they already know
that they're interested right in which case i mean if if oh my god you're right i forgot about that
knows that you're interested and they don't like you then the only conceivable solution
is that you tell them more about yourself and maybe they like you based on that stuff but but
even then don't go too far down that road i just like if they already know about you like if they
already know enough about you to make a judgment on whether they like you or not then you're already
this has red flag written all over i'm sorry it's rough yeah that's just the way it is
buying them presents this sounds like a lost cause almost it will only make them feel weird
or if it doesn't then they might have sinister intentions they're gonna try and i i suspect
look guys are very simple i'll say this about guys like a guy knows at first glance with a girl
if he's willing to date her or not for the most part that's true and i don't know hey uh i haven't
the odds are he's not attracted to you buy smash buy a switch for yourself invite him over to play it
and see if he likes you you know that's the way don't do it only because you have this plan you
have to also want this way to the very least yeah it's just not it's not extra it's just retarded
that question was good that's what extra means well i mean kind of that question was good but
here's a way better one from at doom box two who i recommend buying the doomer shirt asks
best way to cook eggs fried i like fry fry keep that yoke runny as hell my dude runny as hell uh
that's okay i think it's like okay first uh fried egg second uh scrambled uh but if you
want to go the extra like what is the best egg dish carbonara hands down oh uh whatever it was
that me you uh and digi had at that breakfast place it's on an english muffin with the egg on top
with like a piece of ham eggs benedict is the best egg food in the world i'm convinced i'm convinced
i'm gonna show you carbonara i'm gonna show you you're gonna like it okay all right i guarantee it
you're not the way you look you're gonna get 50 pounds you're gonna like the way you just so
everyone knows i'm just gonna give you the just the real simple way to cook a fried egg properly
uh there's a video of itachi doing this from naruto somewhere online as well oh that's that's
true that's there's a thing of that um is that where it started for you what what is that is that
where your love of fried egg started no but i was happy to be you know uh reinforced by itachi's
love of it you just you take your pan yeah you turn on the heat real low yeah you spread your
oil you spread it around yeah you can turn up the heat a little bit if you want and you crack your
egg in the center you can put two or three or whatever and then you have this is the most
important part you put the lid on top you have to put a lid on top so that it cooks the top of the egg
but you don't do it too you don't turn the heat up too long and then you just like really i'm just
trying to tell you to put the lid on the top because that was the most important thing i learned
i can see long hair you reminded me of taking notes of this anime scene you reminded me of a
itachi did it too from a really early pcp episode where we were talking about like life and uh just
you know making the best of yourself something like that and you chimed in with you know that
reminds me there's a really great chapter of one piece about this that really adjusted
my life view of this and i and i just have ever since then i've imagined you as like a man in
the library that the grandchildren come to for wisdom and your library is just a shitload of
jump volumes and it's like oh it's just as this bloomer thing describes nostalgia motivates him
instead of depressing don't forget very racist at the risk of this being uh at the risk of this
potentially being a whole other topic like i i think um there's this common sentiment people
have or they're like you have to read to like you have to read because it'll enrich your understanding
of the world and you'll learn so much from reading but they always say books like this is implication
that only books can do this for you and like books are literally no fucking different from any other
medium like well they do stimulate the brain in a pretty good way i think i'm absolutely gonna
turn this into a into a topic or i do definitely have a thing to say about that books don't automatically
change anything but the fact that there's a different business model means there could have been
a very different production model let me tell you that's true but i just think that like i'm talking
about just on the baseline people talk about it like only books have this power and it's like right
all media has this power because it all comes from the same fucking place it's all just remember
our boy ty Lopez the the the the read a book a day guy who actually just like has people summarized
books for or something yeah yeah like dude no no like the thing about books though is that
it's just the amount of options and the amount of just the odds of stumbling into something
that's like holy shit like level of effort and insight in depth is higher than youtube videos and
the example i'm gonna go to is i agree with that but i think that okay i don't think that there's
anything you can't learn from like just consuming like even fairly basic shit
because you just can extrapolate from it like typically like let's say reading one piece again
like Nate might see it might not be presented with a huge amount of depth in the in one piece
but like it might present you with an idea that you can then think about and extrapolate on and
add that depth to by thinking about it and like i think that that's just like what me like we all
learn like most of the fucking shit we know from like most of what we consume because it's not like
any of it comes from a place of mindlessness like every story is just somebody taking their
understanding of the world and translating that into a story and all of our understanding is
pretty fucking similar because we're all there is an extent to which like people will go out of
their way to do a crazy fucking research project and go out and be a journalist and get original
interviews to attain information and it's like a lot sometimes people turn that into a youtube video
but sometimes they turn that into a book and you gotta get the book if you want the full story
what i want to bring up is Good to Great by Jim Collins which was an audiobook that was so good
i'm like i need to stop listening to audiobooks now before i get into a munchies mom loop of
just listening to books about how to make life better and never actually getting around to it
whatever that i'll devotee you're my oh my god so i almost forgot i'm sorry to move here finish
your point that i've got something to say so Good to Great by Jim Collins was written from the
mid to late 90s with not just Jim Collins but a team of 20 or 22 different research people he had an
entire fucking like like an entire fucking class of people who were doing research for five years
to examine every fucking business in america and crunched thousands and thousands and thousands of
data to attain a very selected highly curated sample set of companies that were mediocre and then
became great later so that they could look at the common elements and just the amount of data
that they amassed an amount of math that they crunched and then the uniqueness of the insights
that they pulled out of that you know you can't if you decided to make that a youtube video well
to live in five let me ask you something book you gotta get the book do you think that i would get
significantly more out of reading this book than i would out of if you just explain to me what the
book said yeah i mean in like 15 i probably not because like because i often people will tell me
things like uh like there's a lot of academic books that like i've seen youtube videos that
explain the point of them and like you always get this impression like most of the book is just
justifying the point but like the point can be made in like a sentence but it's a but it's important
that the book exists but is it important that i read the book if i if i already take it for granted
that the point it's making is correct because i know that it was justified by the text because
people i trust have told me as much will i get anything more out of reading the book and having
it readjustified for me then if i just i think i understand your own thoughts better if you take
the book yeah it helps you internalize the information not yeah that's what i was gonna say
like i think i think you've all spoken at the same time and i didn't know what any of the fact that
you're reading it like firsthand i think it helps you internalize and like retain the information
better what it's also is that you understand like if you if someone tells you the moral of a story
or you know the point of a book and then you you in turn believe that and put that into your life
then you're not gonna know why you believe things if you just take what people say is like oh yeah
the book was about since what i don't know why i believe that gravity is real other than that it's
a thing i can look at and be like that's a thing like i don't look at gravity it could be bullshit
everyone was telling you your whole life i don't need to read a book on what is gravity to know
that gravity is a thing you know why do i need a greater understanding this is your smart so
you're not dumb as shit is why why do i want to be smart what's the benefit being able to better
articulate any ideas i don't i don't even know how to respond to that well you justify it in your
worldview i suppose you do it you you basically justify how 99.9 of everything that everyone
says you need to do in life to be happy you don't you can just skip it and you do and i guess it works
so i guess i guess digi's mentality about books he's talking about right now is answers the question
we were talking about early about media and why people don't expand their taste it's like well
who cares why do i need to be you know nuance in my taste there is there is no need however what
i'm advocating for in that is that people will find something they will like more like that they
i think you like books more i think people are limit well forget about that because i'm this is
all of just me postulating this is for the sake of argument none of this is real i don't actually
feel these things i'm saying i'm making an argument and why are we talking about it yeah
and also why is there not this episode is over forget it fuck you guys okay i don't want to make
you know what in that point 245 into the goddamn episode i've got a surprise announcement at the
end of the episode that i meant to bring up our hero at call me puzzle happily just tweeted
that it is international podcast day right oh i forgot about that yeah i i i post that i post
that in chat i was like oh my god guys it's gonna be national podcast day and then it was like oh
i require that day oh and i was like yeah well i remembered didn't i i i remembered not you you
baby you you twink uh well uh so eat it guys our podcast good are they were are they worthwhile
as an art form do they impact society let's do do this for 45 minutes okay it's like about the
the social benefits of podcasting and if they're morally right i think a lot of people can waste
a ton of time with podcasts as they do everything for example i was listed yeah that is true i was
listening to a sam harris podcast the uh yesterday because the title was something like safe space
culture i listened for five minutes it was clear that they signaled that they agreed with my position
that they're bullshit and then i continued to listen to just feel good about them justifying my
opinion this is exactly what i was just saying about books by the way is that like because every
time for any media every time i like go and read the study that like the the result was from i'm
just like oh this is just literally saying the thing like i already i already know that the thing
why am i reading the thing that's about the thing because you understand why the thing is i don't
i don't need to it has no application to know why it is all right all right fine but here
is my point like if i listen to a podcast and then they clearly signal that they believe something i
don't believe odds are just much higher that i'll stop listening and i think a lot of people are
that way so i just wonder if we really do a lot of convincing people of anything with these uh
we don't you know with these i don't know those types of videos i mean those are very like you
too okay youtube political videos are so fucking bad they make me so like embarrassed
on like a visceral well it's the problem with all of them is just you can tell what side the people
are on and like that's that's why i think it's i think if you want to change anybody's mind
stop being on a side obviously like because like nobody's gonna really believe one is right though
there's a difference between people who are not on a side do it through peril or something like
you're never going to get to the other side from a reporter i think people who vote democrat and vote
republic i'm gonna get real fucking specific here okay i don't think is this gonna be another
topic because i've got to piss real bad all right well okay well if you want to if you want to hear
real quick finish your point yeah all i'm gonna say is that i don't think anyone is like literally
believes everything that the major parties do and they all are just a mishmash of different ideas
and they should just embrace that everyone is different there isn't a clear red or blue
you all right i'm sure you democrat have some republican views i'm sure you republican have
some democrat views so stop fighting each other easier to think that way yeah politics is a sport
for some reason humans human thinking tends to always go towards binary that's why everything
always breaks down to a or b and like business and everything else that's why you have coca
pepsi or intel or amd or democrat republican it's easy to be i'm either a or b we're just
that's why that's why there are no more great people that's why everyone there's a cap because
of the nsa and uh let's go all right well that being said uh the end everyone's bad everyone's
shit uh except i'm a bloomer so everything's great and secure our future for the white race
ladies and gentlemen uh all right thanks for listening patreon.com slash uh the pro crass
five dollars million bonus episodes go listen to them all um one dollar and you're in the bonus
lounge there you go have fun have a great time neku uh we'll see you next week with another one
bonus episodes coming out oh it's already out by the time you hear this and it's dope
and it's about your new favorite movie so you're gonna want to go listen to that shit uh all right
goodbye bye
I've got a deadline, don't wanna do it