Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
Hello and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. Ben Saint is here. Gibbontake is here.
I have blisters on my fingers.
And despite the rumors of his death, Tom Oliver is here.
Oh no, I did die. I'm just here anyways.
People have been saying no Tom, no watch in the comments for years and that will show them. They will have learned their lesson.
I'm glad they can finally watch and understand. Unfortunately, it probably won't be worth the wait.
Our guest this week is my friend, and what's the word, partner in various crimes, Crack AC.
Oh man, it's been a long time coming. I can't believe I finally made it. You may know me as the programmer behind Endless War back in the early days.
I was going to say, or the programmer of Endless War, or I mean more importantly, the creator of the acclaimed, isthereanrv.com.
That's correct. My now world famous enshrined in internet history, isthereanrv.com.
A historic resume.
Yeah, so it's fucking August 8, 2021, I guess, and I am sure feeling it, if you know what I'm saying.
Where does the time go?
Where does the time go? I don't know what's going on. What's this week about?
What's our podcast? Wait a minute, we recorded 280 episodes and we don't even know what this show is about.
This show has a topic? No, it doesn't.
What's our mission statement?
To be as boring as possible and see how much money we can make doing it.
To fill the ears of our listeners while they do monotonous tasks, I guess.
To fill the hours between cradle and grave, baby.
To just wither away, live on stage.
Yeah, I mean, it's a noble goal. Somebody has to do it.
Would you rather be listening to ambient noise right now? That's so 2004.
I would rather be listening to a plot summary of a video game that I played when I was a child.
That's what I wasn't on the PCP.
God, if only. If only you could be right now, just escape all obligation and be baby again.
Just have some YouTuber explain to you the plot of Final Fantasy 7 that you already know backwards and forwards.
This is the seventh time listening to that video.
I don't know if it's one channel or just like a trend, but there's like X explained.
Just annoys me in concept.
I just see them and I'm like, sure, you're going to explain it, but I hate you and I want you to stop.
God, I saw recommended again that thumbnail of Lucas from Mother 3 and it's how Mother 3 breaks you.
And I'm like, oh, I fucking hate that thumbnail. I see it recommend all the time.
Just click on the little dots and just be like, don't recommend video and then you'll never see it again.
I got to tell you, speaking of Super Eye Patch Wolf, I happen to catch his little Dell saga and this shit drives me insane.
I don't know the saga.
The short version is he put out this like hours long video where he's crying and upset about having bought a computer
and like the computer was both exactly what he ordered and a piece of shit.
Well, you bought a Dell computer.
Yeah. Well, right. He buys a Dell computer.
So what was it down to the absolute bare minimum because he wants to be as cheap as possible.
And then he's like sure shocked that he doesn't have a solid state drive and that it doesn't work.
You know, it's not fast enough.
And it's like made a whiny video about it.
He made this whiny video, but it's worse than that.
This is a month's lawn saga where like the people in his discord had been trying to help him and he's just been ignoring their assistance.
And it just drives me crazy.
He knows nothing, but he certainly knows everything and it's his constant downfall.
The only thing he knows is that he doesn't like it.
I tried to watch a Super Eye Patch.
I liked his Scooby video.
I remember liking the Scooby video.
I tried to watch another Super Eye Patch Wolf fairly recently and I was so disgusted by his delivery.
His voice is so cloying.
It's okay. It's fine.
It's trying to get its hook.
No, it's not.
He doesn't have any ground to criticize people's voices.
Neither of ours are smooth and sultry.
He does these little like, well, I, you know, it made me feel...
I don't know.
I don't think that's an accurate representation of Super Eye Patch Wolf.
He does these performative little like, whispery stops and like giggles.
He whispers. He has a whispery voice. That's for sure.
He's being all oo-woo at you and like it's sickening.
He's putting on a fucking show.
He's putting on a show on his YouTube show.
What I'm saying is I really feel the artifice of it and it feels very, very cloying and manipulative.
That's my take.
The only Super Eye Patch Wolf video I've watched recently.
Night Mind has the worst voice on YouTube.
Night Mind's voice is definitely worse than Super Eye Patch Wolf.
Yeah.
I watched Super Eye Patch Wolf video on Space Jam.
He did like his whole like Space Jam 2 leaked script, but it wasn't actually script.
It was just something he made up. It was a shitpost and it was hilarious.
I loved it. Super good.
I mean, I feel like, I feel like I'm in, I don't know.
Whatever.
I make that one video, but I don't know if I can get past it.
But anyway, okay, so he's crying about his fucking computer.
I remember, I mean, years ago I did that GoFundMe to get a computer and you recommended me a bunch of parts.
And somebody recommended me and I feel bad being like, oh, one guy fucked up.
It's my fault. It's my fault for going against specifications.
But someone recommended me a cheaper motherboard and I decided, okay, I'll get the cheaper.
Yeah, why not get the cheaper motherboard?
And I did and it completely ruined the whole thing.
It just didn't work.
It took me six months to get the computer working.
I just had to buy the fucking better.
You just got to buy the fucking.
Yeah.
It's like Nauta says in Fully Coolie when he's on the run with Haruko and they're buying the ramen.
You can't just go with the cheap brand just because it's jumbo size.
You got to stick with the good stuff.
Like I said, he was right.
And you know, I mean, it was literally like you tried to save 50 bucks and it cost you six months of your life.
You know?
Yeah.
Exactly.
100%.
Point of point of order.
Always get a decent motherboard and a good power supply.
You will thank yourself 100% of the time.
This is why.
Absolutely.
This, this is why I'm, I mean, I hate to endorse a company, but I genuinely, I genuinely get
so much out of my fucking Instacart subscription.
It cost me like $100 a year and I never have to go grocery shopping and it's amazing.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, especially for you.
That's like $10 a week.
That's pretty good.
You don't.
That's like tens of hours saved.
Yeah.
It's like a huge hassle if you go to the store.
I could see that being like gigantic and life-saving.
It's paid for itself like so many times over.
It's a miracle.
Yeah.
It's great.
It's really great.
What's that saying?
I've heard some people say like, when you're, when you're, is it like when you're young,
when you trade, you spend time to save money and then when you're older, you spend money
to save time.
That's my saying.
I said that.
Did you say that?
Oh, I thought someone smart.
I thought someone smart said it.
Excuse me.
One of those world famous gibbon quotes.
I swear I said it somewhere.
I mean, it's absolutely true.
It's very true.
Since time is money, if you can ever find a way to spend money that will save you time,
but you save more time, the value of the time that you save is worth more than the money
that you spent to save the time.
That's the fucking, that's how you fucking hack your life.
That's like the fundamental principle of life hacking or something.
That's how you get on top of your shit.
Yeah.
Speaking of eye patch wolf and weird voice voicings, whatever happened to nerd writer?
Is he completely gone or is he just still making videos that nobody ever sees anymore?
I bet.
I mean, without even looking into it at all, my gut feeling is probably that, you know,
he had his heyday.
He, you know, he made, he became as successful as he was ever going to get on YouTube.
And then some fucking Corpo company like hired him in some kind of like, some kind of like,
managerial position or something off of his reputation.
And now he just works for someone like that and makes way more money than he would ever make on YouTube.
And we'll never hear from him again.
Well, I'll tell you then.
He made a video on YouTube.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Because I mean, I had not not heard anyone talk about nerd writer in like a year or more.
You know, he still gets decent views.
Yeah, I thought he was gone.
I guess it's just one of those, those like, like YouTube is so big that there's entire like,
juggernauts of industry that you can completely miss if you're not in the right algorithm circle.
Yeah.
It's pretty interesting how quickly you can forget people exist if you just like click a couple things on YouTube.
Like I constantly, I like got rid of a lot of like political stuff on my YouTube because I was sick of seeing it.
Because I already know the world's bad.
I don't need to hear about it.
And I just forget.
And I'm like, oh yeah, Vosh exists.
I haven't seen Vosh's face in like eight months.
Vosh, man.
I mean, he was all over Twitter yesterday.
I can't escape him.
Yeah, I didn't even know.
I didn't even know.
Everybody existed till literally right now.
It was because there's a picture of him like hugging a fucking Charlie Kirk and Tim Pool that everyone.
Okay, honestly, it was actually kind of funny.
It's actually kind of funny because everyone was analyzing it like they were they were drawing like they were drawing the lines.
The alpha like who's leaning into they were drawing the alpha lines and they were comparing their stances like who's the most alpha in the situation.
And Justin Wang was like, hmm, Tim, Tim's line is the most alpha, but also he lacks cock confidence because he's got his hands crossed over.
So that's kind of a watch.
Not sure what to make it.
This is actually pretty funny.
Yeah, I've been keeping up with Vosh and the the reason he was all over the place on Twitter was because he did that debate with Charlie Kirk on Tim Pool's show.
And it was apparently really well done for like, you know, bridging the gap or like getting Tim Pool fans to be more left leaning or whatever.
So yeah.
Big news, I guess.
I mean, Charlie Kirk is like he was in he's like a he's like a politician or something.
He's like some sort of a guy.
He's a he's a radio personality.
I thought before he was on like a radio talk show host or something.
I don't think he's an official like he's not an elected official or anything.
Well, I don't know.
I thought he was like another media guy.
Yeah, I don't know.
Like I said, I don't look at the turning point USA guy.
Oh, maybe.
Yeah, he's not the guy from two and a half men.
No.
If only that would have been a much more interesting face.
Is that the name of the image where they're all hugging each other?
That's what I'm saying.
Charlie Kirk is so tall.
He's like like Vosh is like a kind of tall guy and Charlie Kirk fucking towers over him.
He's like seven feet tall.
It's insane.
No offense to Tom, but I just I don't trust people that tall.
I mean, I don't trust myself.
Absolutely.
It's really funny because Vosh is like he's kind of big and he makes Tim Poole look tiny
and then and then fucking Charlie Kirk makes Vosh look tiny.
It's it's it's a trip.
It's wild.
It's like Tim Heidecker next to Mike Stoklasa.
And then you realize how big Eric Wareheim must be.
Wait.
Do you remember when Tim Heidecker was on half in the bag?
One of the earlier?
No, no.
What?
He what he was?
Yeah, he was.
He was like he was the guy.
He was like the manager of the game shop, right?
It's like I don't remember that at all.
Well, you can't rewatch it.
I've not seen that.
There's there's an episode where they transition from being at Mr. Plinkett's house all the
time to going back to the VCR repair shop for the first time.
You see that set and they come back and they're like, oh, Tim Heidecker is the boss.
And you're like, and then he leaves.
He jumps through the ceiling.
Does it look like a shootout on George Lucas, Rich Evans as George Lucas comes in.
He's like, I'm going to kill you, Mike and Jay because of the Plinkett reviews.
And then there's the whole thing.
And then they kill George Lucas and Tim Heidecker flies away and then they own the store.
And then from there on, they do reviews in there as well.
Half in the bag of PCP University lecture when the lore is deep.
I mean, it's deep, but it's fun to watch.
You just watch it.
You know what?
I mean, in terms like things with obscure lore, I mean, red letter media, I mean, specifically
half in the bag does have a continuing narrative that nobody follows.
You could probably do a lecture on half in the bag.
I have seen people take like all of the skits from the beginning and ends of half in the
bag and then turning them into half in the bag, the movie, which is like a couple hours
long.
And there's like in parts.
There's quite a lot of stuff still.
Wouldn't you rather spend a couple hours watching some socially awkward people talk about it
in a room with a whiteboard?
That just seems so much more entertaining.
Oh, tempting, tempting.
My Sonichu lecture is it got like a hundred and it got 70 K views on its first week.
It's going to it's going to pass the it's going to pass the Kokoro wish lecture probably
like a week and a half.
Well, considering the circumstances, it would be shocked if it didn't.
I mean, it's it is it is getting it is getting, you know, I'll just show the graph.
I fucking love looking at these graphs.
It is getting the my other lecture.
It's getting Kokoro wish more exposure, which is the most important thing, obviously.
Yeah, of course.
Here's here's the here's the relative views lately on hold on.
Let me put them here in the fucking chat where we all can see.
Wow.
I didn't realize you posted the the lecture on the Ben St. Channel.
Yeah.
Yeah, everyone's pretty stingy about their lectures, except for me.
Well, I only mentioned it because I thought you had way fewer subscribers on the Ben St.
Channel, but it's like nineteen thousand.
I'm looking at it right now.
It's gained almost a thousand since posting the video.
I think I'm going to hit twenty K maybe like next week or something.
Graduates are all going to be disappointed in two months when nothing else has come out.
Yeah.
Well, I don't know.
We'll see.
Did you explain the colors on this chart?
We're looking at.
Yeah.
Sorry.
The blue there is the blue is a Sonichi 102.
The green is Sonichi 101.
Purple is Kokoro wish.
Orange is Tails gets trolled.
And red is a chat with Chris Chan, Sonichi, the stream.
So as you see, you know, historically, Sonichi 101 has been topping everything.
And then, you know, Sonichi 102 has propelled itself and Sonichi 101 up to heights.
And it is it's pulling the other two lectures up with it.
They're getting maybe like five hundred.
Those lower ones are getting maybe five hundred views a day at the moment or something.
So that's going to squeeze out some more attention.
Could you rescale this logarithmically so we can really see those differences?
Look at the trend.
I don't know if there's an option for that in the actually.
Okay.
Lunge.
I can sit.
I can't do logarithmic, but I can make it a bar graph.
That would do it for you.
No.
Sorry.
My options are limited.
Do you do a pie chart?
I can.
You do a Venn diagram.
Hmm.
I can.
Wait.
Just just a giant Venn diagram of viewers who've seen.
Crystery 101 102 right in Kokoro wish.
I have one more.
I have one more interesting.
Debateably interesting graph to show these are these are these are views over time for
Sonichi 102.
As you can see some time on the fourth day, it had started getting a bump and it basically
had like a renewed spike of viewership.
It's not even slowing down.
It's it's debatably only accelerating.
Yeah, it looks good.
I mean, it looks totally linear to me.
It looks pretty good.
That's a good.
You see, after 40, it kind of started to flatten and then it was like, nope, not flattening.
Oh, yeah, baby.
This shit's going to be around forever.
It's changing the YouTube landscape.
I noticed you on Twitter put you made a PCP lectures tier maker tier list thing.
Yeah, I did because I made them.
I made one the day before for down the rabbit hole because nobody there.
There was nobody that had made a down the rabbit hole tier maker before and I was talking
to someone about those and I was like, man, this the Christian, the Christian down the
rabbit hole is pretty bad.
But the Darger, the Henry Darger down the rabbit hole is amazing.
I wonder if I could place the others on a spectrum in between and I could and then I decided
to do it for because people always argue that the most the most contentious ones are like
spirit science.
Some people really like the spirit science one and other people really don't.
Some people really like the Kingdom Hearts lecture and some people think it's overrated.
So I was like, OK, I'm going to make a I'm going to make a fucking way.
I'll post the image of my my tier list.
So wait, is the tier list your personal opinion or based on what you believe to be correct
in a larger sense?
You mean like, no, this is just this is my personal opinion.
These are these are my personal opinion.
It's not.
I think I did one.
But it was sort of.
I don't know.
I didn't find it particularly interesting where I placed the lectures.
I hadn't seen them in a while anyway.
I put I put Tom's lectures in a tier and some of the comments are like still the thing where
they're like, it should be higher.
They're like, Animorphs should be number one of S tier.
It's not enough to merely put it in stands.
I don't know.
Yeah, it does.
It's a strong.
It's a strong contender.
Tom, you have done you have done two lectures.
And as far as I'm concerned, they're both they're both a plus your two for two with the hits.
I can't wait to let everybody down with the third one.
I don't know what it will be, but it'll be something.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't I don't know what I would do if I was going to do another one.
You don't know what it you don't know what it would be.
I thought the usual scheme is you.
You say it was recorded already, you know, and it's coming soon.
And you just do that for a few years.
True, true, true.
Wait, the real story is on a tier.
Is this just because you were there to experience in real life or did it actually get released
somewhere?
No, no, it did not get released.
That's just that's just I put that in.
You can lord it over everyone that like it is that good.
I kind of just put it in there as a as a troll.
Where did this thumbnail come from?
I just made I just mocked it up and made it because I was like, what?
What if I just put in a fake thumbnail for a video that doesn't make sense?
I was expecting for a fucking.
No, I'm not.
I mocked up a fake thumbnail just to put it in there and get it cut off.
That's true.
I did.
It was worth it.
It was pretty good.
It's a shame.
None of you will ever be able to see it.
It it was pretty good and people have asked me.
I saw somebody asked Nate about it and Nate said he didn't think people were missing out
on on it.
And I don't agree.
I think it was good.
I think that anyone who was a PCP fan or or a Trixie fan would like it because it's basically
about our personal history in the bronie fandom.
So I think it was good.
If you would rate it, I might be a little biased.
It might be it might be low A tier high.
No, no, no.
I think maybe if you had rated it less than A tier, it would be an admission that it, you
know, people weren't really missing anything.
And that's unacceptable.
I wouldn't admit that.
Absolutely.
You know what?
You're right.
Absolutely true.
I think I appreciate you putting the risk at higher than two of Nate's lectures and Munchie's
spirit science.
I think I think risk honestly, I think maybe it should have been low A. The thing I mean,
the thing that I don't like about Final Fantasy and One Piece, I don't think those are good
lectures.
I think the Kingdom Hearts lecture is a really good lecture.
I think Final Fantasy and One Piece are not good.
They're too long and they're not like they're too long.
And they're what they're about is not something that that demands a lecture.
I think the the the risk a lecture, it is kind of surface level and it's not it's not very
in depth and it's kind of short, but I like that it's short.
And what it is, what it does cover is lecture worthy.
So I think it's got a special sauce for a good lecture is when it's like really in
depth, but also it's like unraveling some mystique.
You know, like Final Fantasy and One Piece are so mainstream that it's easy to find information
on them.
Like where else are you going to get Kokoro wish broken down in that kind of extreme
detail?
You know?
On the one hand, on the one hand, you could say, well, you know, people say, you know,
One Piece doesn't need a lecture.
Just read One Piece.
I guess you could technically say that about Kokoro wish.
You can just go and read, you know, Unicorn Jelly, if you want.
It was about more than just Unicorn Jelly, though, it was kind of about the author and
like their meta journey on top of everything, which gives an add so much to it.
I think that specifically the lecture format, it works best as a way to explain something
because otherwise you could do a video essay where you just talk about something with editing
and stuff.
The audience being there reacting to the crazy shit is the fun part because like, you know,
the person telling the story gets to tell something wacky happened with Tails gets
trolled or Kokoro wish.
It's like, wow, and people Pog in real time, and it has a certain energy to it.
If you're explaining like the plot of every single Final Fantasy 7, Final Fantasy 7,
every single Final Fantasy 7, just wait like five more years and we'll be at that point.
Oh my God, there's going to be more.
There is.
Oh, no.
We're going to have to have Final Fantasy 7, Vanilla, Final Fantasy 7 remake, Final Fantasy
7, Battle Royale, which is real, unfortunately.
How long is it going to be till the next installment of the remake?
It could be some of the ten years probably.
Something insane like that, right?
But like the Final Fantasy stories, they have like Pog's moments within them, but they're
not as ridiculous as like the story of Chris Chan and Sonichu.
Some of those things.
There's also like, there's a functional purpose too to having the audience because when you're
explaining something so esoteric and dense, when you're the person who knows it, you tend
to kind of like make assumptions just almost by accident because like you're so deep in
it.
Yeah.
So like the audience is there to ask questions that you would get in the comments that can
be answered in the material itself, which is really helpful.
There's yeah, there's there's one there's one point and I included I included tectonic
improv's atop the fourth wall one because I think it's I think it's you know, it's it
says good as a as a PCP lecture and it's got and I like that the subject matter.
I think atop the fourth wall is the perfect kind of thing.
So I included it and but it's got a moment in it that is maybe like the downside of the
lecture form, which like one of his friends that he gets to like sit in the audience,
one of his friends like gets annoyed and like heckles him at one point and they have like
a little like moment where you can tell they're like genuinely mad at each other.
I miss that.
I didn't I didn't watch all the lecture.
I could be that's really I could be reading.
I could be reading too much.
I don't think I'm reading.
There's a there's a moment where they get kind of bit like she's like have to go back
and that's the risk you run.
That's the risk you run.
It's a good lecture.
I like it.
And then fuck.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I felt bad putting it in low tier, but the video quality and the audio quality are really
unfortunate on that one and it I really liked making it.
But look, it's a little the quality makes me a little bit embarrassed about it.
So when did that lecture come out?
Like what is that up to?
That came out it would we did RFC Kcon February of 2020.
And I think it came out like not too long after that.
So that's like, yeah, that's as of like February 2020.
So a year and a half ago.
So it's pretty much caught up on everything significant that ever happened because there's
supposed to be season four, right?
Like what's the deal with season four?
Is that happening?
Is that coming out soon?
It is on.
We're in season four.
And by the way, the name of the generation of people that joined during season four is
foreskin, which is pretty good.
Pretty good.
I learned that the other day.
Yeah, it is going on.
Server is still active.
People are still are still going at it in there.
Yeah.
I know it.
I dip in every so often and I just am overwhelmed by all of the people being active, being people
I don't know who they are.
And I just did that New Grounds video, give it a bump because I saw that on the front
page of New Grounds.
I got front page.
It definitely did.
Some people did.
Definitely gave it a bump.
It was a good video.
Not as an incredible video.
Not as many as it should have because it didn't get as many views as it deserves.
Well, New Grounds, unfortunately, doesn't have a lot of like raw traffic, but what
are you going to do?
I mean, it's on YouTube, too, where it is.
I didn't know.
I just saw it on New Grounds.
Yeah.
Obviously, it's easier.
Oh, yeah.
No, it's on YouTube.
What?
Did you just like?
Shaddox find it randomly?
Well, no, it got front-paged on New Grounds.
Oh, that's right.
Like a couple of weeks ago.
That's how you found it.
Yeah, it was on.
You just saw it.
You just happened to see it on New Grounds.
Well, no, I mean, what they do is they front-page things on.
They do daily front pages and they do like spotlight weeklies.
And so it was front-page the day I was there.
And so I was like, there it is.
Yeah.
I know.
I just think it's funny to me that like you found it organically instead of like seeing
me like retweet it or something like that.
I did not see.
No, I found it organically.
It was super cool.
I was like, wait a minute.
I know those guys.
It was great.
Wow.
Yeah.
Shaddock's YouTube channel has like a hundred K subs.
But I think her there.
I don't know.
I think they're genuinely I genuinely don't know.
I've never, never spoken to them like in voice, but they have them.
I think they did like fan animations.
Right.
I think that was what they.
Yeah.
So, you know, it's the difficult transition of, of moving from, you know, fan content
into like original content.
I mean, I guess RFCK is fan content, but it's not like, you know, it's not about like a
big mainstream property or something, right?
So it's, it's, it has that, it had that, that, that burden upon it.
I hope that it eventually sees a wider audience.
It's so good.
It's such an impressive piece of, of animation.
It's really, really gorgeous.
It's gorgeous.
Yeah.
And we talked about it last week and I forgot to put the link in the description, but I,
I fixed it.
A commenter pointed out that I didn't put the link in and I, now it's there.
I'll put it in again.
Eleazar put the link top, top of the description.
It's important.
What were we talking about?
Tier lists.
Tier lists for the lectures.
Lectures.
Down the rabbit hole.
Yeah.
I just, I just was like, I was just imagining like, man, imagine you're just some guy, just
some PCP head and you see this tier list and you're, and you're going through it and you
get to the real brony story thumbnail and you're like, wait a minute, there's a thumbnail.
It has to be real.
I didn't know this was out.
I have to find it.
Where does this thumbnail come from?
I hope I confused at least one person with it and cause righteous indignation.
Yeah.
And cause righteous indignation when they realize like, wait a minute.
It's not out after all.
I'm fucking mad.
Me too.
Me too, bros.
If we ever do another Radcom, I'm going to make sure to have my phone record at every
lecture just in case one of you guys gets cold feet.
It's like, I don't want to release it.
I'll have the pirated of the cam version.
I'll put it on a torrent site so people can get the illegal cam.
Literally like a theater, like phone recording.
Exactly.
With people's heads in the foreground.
Could you imagine if that actually existed for the brony lecture, it would be hilarious.
Oh, it would be perfect.
If only we lived in such a world.
I asked, yeah, I asked Victor if he had like the footage and he told me no.
I didn't keep a copy.
I just gave it to.
There were huge files.
I'm not surprised.
Yeah.
They have shot in like high definition, like two hour long videos with like audience.
Like a pro camera.
It was like bigger than my head.
Red cams.
8K.
Yeah.
Wrong.
Compressed.
Dude, we had to work.
We had to buy hard drives every single person.
We had to next day order them from Amazon just so we could bring the files home.
They were massive.
Yeah.
Totally unnecessary.
But we did it.
I could just recorded them on a fucking iPhone.
It would have been fine, but.
Probably.
Well, well, I mean, that's what we did with RFCK lecture and it was.
I take it all back.
Well, and we didn't record it.
It was, you can tell the difference.
So it was, it was probably worth it.
Oh, I remember now in the RFCK lecture, was that when you chipped your tooth again?
Yeah.
That's when I had to turn it off.
It was terrifying.
It was too much for me.
The body horror in the middle of the lecture.
I mean, you can't, I mean, you can't see my chip tooth or anything.
It's so on brand for RFCK though.
I do.
It is.
I pick, I pick up a piece of post your board and I bite it with my teeth and I tear it and
then I, there's, then there's like, then there's like five minutes where I'm where
Munchie is talking and I'm kind of like more quiet than usual.
Occasionally just kind of like touching my mouth and being like, what?
What happened?
And then I announced like, hey guys, I just broke my tooth on the, on the, on the, on
the thing.
But don't worry.
Like the lecture will continue.
We don't have to stop.
Let's just keep going.
Jesus.
That's professionalism.
That's what I did.
Absolutely.
I was there to do a job.
God damn it.
All zero dollars.
You know what?
I think maybe it's a little unfair to put it in the bottom tier.
Yeah.
The quality, the audio visual quality is poor, but it is genuinely informative about like
what is the deal with RFCK, which is the most valuable thing.
When I was doing, when I was doing the, the down the rabbit hole, I was, you know, I made
the tier list that and then I made my own tier list.
And like one of my biggest criteria for that is like, how much did I learn from it?
Which is why I put, I had to, I had to put good ones like the final fantasy house and
time cube down in like C tier because like I already knew about them.
I didn't learn that much from them.
So I didn't like them that much.
There's nothing wrong with them, but I had to RFCK lecture.
It's, it's a very niche topic, but if you're interested in it, it is genuinely informative.
So maybe it should be in B tier actually.
Yeah.
See the biggest problem with the RFCK lecture is that it spits in the face of RFCK because
it has audio and visuals.
You should have just talked into its speech to text program and just put it in a paste
band.
That's how you experience the RFCK lecture.
That's, that's probably true.
I mean, that's what you should, that's what should docket it eventually did right with
Love Web.
You, you should have had, you should have had to download it as a like .txt file from
like a, a media fire download or something.
Yeah.
The lecture itself should be like lost.
Like you literally have to like join the discord and find like a hidden channel, complete a
quest to get some role to find a hidden channel to find the download link or something.
Sounds better.
Yeah.
Well, maybe next time, maybe next time for RFCK 102 to explaining seasons three and four.
Why not?
Okay.
Right.
So what happened in season four?
What do we got?
Is there like a big story point?
Is there some great new gameplay?
There was.
No.
I mean, yeah, I know there is.
Nothing happened.
Okay.
I don't, there is, there is a story.
There is lore and there is, there are gameplay ramifications, but I am not like qualified
to explain them.
I don't know all the details of them, but yes, those things are there.
Yeah.
I think I heard there was some kind of election going on to replace the rowdy fucker.
Oh yeah.
The rowdy ringleader.
Yeah.
They're having an election for rowdy ringleader.
Lord goes swooping right at the last second.
Absolutely.
Now is the time.
Lord of Goat, Lord of Goat, you got to finish, you got to finish the comic real fast in time
for the election.
Oh shit.
Got to use all that kick story money to fund the election campaign.
Yes.
Publicly.
Based, based.
Chased.
I have been, I have been proud, proud to report that I have, I have started working on the
game again, Phantom's Revenge and as I said on Twitter, the recent news about Chris will
not impact it whatsoever.
It changes nothing about the plan or how the story was going to end.
So I'm just going to keep, just going to keep plonking away at that.
By the way, have any, I don't know, have any of you seen like the new, new news about that
that's going around on Reddit and stuff?
I saw an image compilation of the girl who had the phone call that was leaked.
And they found out that she's like a psycho.
I don't know how true it is, but it seems to fit.
If it's true, I called it because in the call where Chris admits to what was going on, she's
clearly like enjoying it and like excited about it.
So it's, it's, it's not, it doesn't surprise me.
I said on Twitter, I was like, whoever was doing this, they're guilty of incitement.
Like it's really sounds like they like caused this to happen in some way.
And it seems like that's true.
So I feel pretty good about that.
Yeah, something about like the phone call, I don't know, like egging Chris on to, to
do the mother to use that as blackmail to make bleep that out or we'll get demonetized.
It's like, oh yeah, bleep everything I said.
But yeah, that was what I heard.
So fucked up that you would bother with that.
Sounds like sound.
I mean, that's the story is that she's just some genuine psychopath who like just wanted
to get Chris to kill herself for fun.
That's what I've heard.
I mean, that seems like the end game of pretty much everyone on Kiwi Farms.
It's, I don't know about that.
You know, you know, yeah, I wouldn't be surprised.
I feel like that that's sort of a place where people like that can pass as just like jokesters.
Like not everyone is there doing that, but some people are and they are indistinguishable
from the rest.
Yeah.
So people actually do horrible, fucked up shit.
I do see people on Kiwi Farms saying, sincerely saying like, you know, don't fuck with them,
leave them alone, just let them be low cows and entertain us.
And like some people are like that, but not everyone is like that.
Yeah.
Well, the people saying, you know, just leave her alone.
It's gone too far.
Those people have been duped the entire time.
You know, they're the ones going along saying it's funny, but the people who've been driving
everything aren't going to stop because of them and they don't care about them.
You know, that's the purpose of the website is to drive these people further and further
into whatever mess they're in.
Yeah, I mean, you're using people as your entertainment.
So like you don't want the entertainment to end, so you're going to keep pushing and
coating them on further.
Yeah, it's pretty pretty disgusting.
Wish they'd shut them down, you know, poor Chan, too.
But like, what are you going to do?
Yeah.
All you can do is co-concease.
And I'm gonna, that's exactly what I intend to do.
So I will.
I saw I saw Dick Masterson being
even more of a sicko than usual on Twitter today, saying like the girl is a hero
for exposing Chris, just conveniently ignoring the fact that it kind of seems like
she literally like caused it to happen.
She, yeah, she exposed it after causing it herself.
So, you know, that's, you know, he sounds like one of those dumb guys who's like,
oh, OK, yeah, this is real fun.
And then he'll have some point where we'll say, oh, guys, we should we shouldn't
go any further.
You know, he guys, he's one of these dumbasses, just like
just like the rest. Yeah.
That sounds about right. What a fucking idiot.
Yeah, fucking gross.
Pretty unfortunate that he has such an audience.
Yeah, they're they're they're bad.
Dick, Dick Dupes are fucking low, low intelligence.
I don't know. I don't know.
He's just a particular kind of a particular kind of a sap, I think,
is is vulnerable to that that kind of messaging.
Yeah, it's sad and you hate to see it, but it is what it is, I guess.
That's I don't know. I guess that's whatever.
Let's fucking let's talk about something more, more uplifting.
Oh, fuck, I don't have anything.
Well, no, I don't have anything uplifting.
No, there's nothing I've mostly been sick and trying to get better
and playing video games, and that's not very interesting.
I went to Ohio to try and move.
It didn't work. Moving's really hard.
I heard you were going to move to Ohio.
That's what people were saying on the great. That is the plan.
Still, I mean, I'm going to have to move still.
Yeah, it's just, you know, you know how it is with moving.
All landlords are evil and they need to die in the revolution.
Yeah, yeah, I I guess I had.
It was a huge hassle moving for me, and it's still going to be going to
continue to be a hassle.
I guess it could it could have been it could have been worse.
You know, I did manage to find I'm housed for this month,
and then I got a new place lined up for September.
So dope.
Yeah, you just are you moving to Ohio because it's cheap?
Is it cheap in Ohio?
It's cheaper there.
I can get a studio for like 600, which is pretty good.
Wow. Yeah, that's pretty good.
But even that, it's like, you know, because I was like my plan
initially, which was shortsighted, foolish and ignorant, was like,
oh, I have a bajillion dollars in savings.
I'll just like use my savings to pay the rent.
And they're all just like,
we don't care if you have 10 million dollars in savings.
Make three times the rent at income or no deal.
So can't you?
Well, I mean, you just need a co-signer.
Well, OK, here's the thing.
I have a friend out there in Ohio and they're like, I'll be your cosigner.
And they're like, well, your friends are going to be your cosigner.
They need to make five times the rent.
I'm like, oh, my God.
And they're like, they need to.
And I don't know.
They're like, they need to make five times the rent.
And then they're like, do they are they renting right now?
I'm like, they pay rent.
They're like, OK, subtract all their expenses.
If they make five times the rent after their expenses,
then they can co-sign for you.
I'm like, so they have to make almost five thousand dollars
to rent a six hundred dollars studio.
And they're like, yes.
I mean, I, which isn't I literally I, I opened all my like my emails
to prospective roommates and or landlords with like, yeah, I know
I'm like self-employed and that's like scary and like I don't have any.
And it seems really shady and you probably think I'm just a hobo
and I have no guaranteed income, but whatever.
I'll just have my parents co-sign.
So just don't even worry about that.
That I mean, I mean, because I knew because I know what they're going to say.
It's like what you're a you're a wait, you're a YouTuber.
Right.
Uh, I don't know about this.
Just trying to explain like I just I I've basically lost my EBT this month
because Nate sent out those those 1099 NECs last year.
So then they realized I have income from two different sources
and they were like, what the fuck is this?
You have two jobs.
I'm like, no, it's just really dumb the way the money works.
And they're like, uh, we're pulling your thing.
You need to like break down month by month, all your income, how many
hours you work for each of these places.
I'm just like, I'm going to be gone in a month.
Nevermind.
So it's just a fucking night.
Government logistics suck.
Depending on who you talk to, the rules are different.
I don't think there's any rules in the government.
I think it's just like that you open up like the government rule book
and it's just like whatever, man, and then a thousand pages of nothing.
Now, you know what it is.
It's all just testing how tough you are.
Are you going to fight back?
Are you going to take him to court?
You know, they're seeing if they can push you around.
I mean, I'm still I'm I'm on week 15 of my eight to 12 week
waiting period for for the the pandemic unemployment hearing.
Yeah, sounds about right.
God, I still it's been it's been 15 weeks.
Yeah, are you kidding me?
15 weeks and I called 12 weeks ago and they were like, well,
normally we would escalate your case, but it's really hard to get contact
with that office on a good day and we're having technical problems right now.
So I'll connect.
I'll transfer you and then they call immediately hung up
after I waited on hold for an hour.
And I was like, our phone's not working.
So at this like like the fine print on their thing is just like if you don't
pay, we're just going to like deduct from your taxes.
I'm like, I pay you in taxes.
So good luck with that.
Plus, I'm leaving the state.
Yeah, come find me, I guess.
I guess that's kind of my game plan right now.
It's like, come fight me, bro.
I'll lawyer up.
I I was going to stand.
I made a joke about like, Tom is like moving to Ohio to flee the tax man
in Massachusetts. I guess I was.
I mean, it's not the primary reason, but it's an added bonus at this point.
Sure. OK.
Bay is the only thing it sucks is I lose the five
thousand or so or not five, maybe like two or three thousand dollars that I
should have gotten since then to now in benefit since the cases hasn't been
decided one way or the other.
But yeah, that's that's pretty cringy.
The state doing what it does best, making you wait.
The state doing what it does best, nothing pretty much, pretty much.
This is this is a sort of, I mean, it's related.
And that's that I'm waiting for some fucking Corpo shills to get back to me.
But I had like a week and a half ago, I had two people as a weird
coincidence, two people filled out the the Vapors to Kickstarter backer
like survey, like basically like reported their mailing address to tell me
like where to mail there. Remember, you know, I did that campaign
like more than a year, like almost two years ago.
Yeah, long. And yeah.
And and it's been like a year since anyone filled out a survey and yet
like two people on like the end of July just filled out their survey.
But on Kickstarter, they don't just let you see your backer report.
They give you like a certain period of time to look at it.
And then they hide it from you as like a privacy measure.
But you can request access to it, which I did.
So I sent them an email.
It's like, please, please let me see the backer report because these two
new backers just gave me their info and I need to see that info to get them
their shit. And they're like, I waited for a reply.
And then I finally got one and they're like, OK, I'll upload an image
of your driver's license to prove it to you.
And I'm like, sure. And I did.
And now I'm still waiting for them to get back to me on that.
And I know that I got to copy that info. Yeah.
So I. OK, because this is OK, this ties into the other thing
I want to talk about, which is the Road to Radcon book,
which I am I have gotten the cover art from Michi Fostered.
And I am I have arranged it into printable PDFs.
And I'm going to be sending those to the printer tomorrow on Monday.
And I've ordered envelopes to send them out in.
And because I knew from my Vapors Kickstarter,
because I knew that they do this time limit thing.
And I knew that we were going to have late
backer fulfillment on the Radcon Road to Radcon
book for the the PCP Kickstarter.
I went through and I and I like saved.
I screenshotted everyone's like info, so I could have it later.
Everyone's like mailing address.
So I can. OK, I can see the backers.
So I have the I have their addresses saved for shipping those out.
But I'm still going to have to like make an announcement
because I'm sure in like the year since a bunch of people will have changed
their addresses, so I'm going to have to make an announcement being like,
hey, if you change if you live at the same place
and you fill out your survey, it's OK.
I'll send the book to where you were.
If you change your address, don't update your survey
because I can't see the survey anymore.
Just send a message saying this is my new address.
It's changed. And then I will send it to a new place.
So I don't know. I don't know why Kickstarter makes it that hard.
It seems dumb.
Probably like one probably like one guy at some point ran a scam
to like harvest people's addresses using like Kickstarter,
backer surveys or something.
And then he ruined it and he ruined it for everyone else.
And then they, you know, in the EU, they have I think it's GDPR.
They have really strict data protection, DRPK.
No, no, no, no.
They have they have really strict data protection rules.
And I wonder if it's related to their compliance there.
Like if they can't work in the EU, if they don't
delete this data after a certain amount of time, I wouldn't surprise me.
It's not it's it's not deleted.
It's just hidden and they are going to ring me out trying to get me
to prove my identity before they'll show it to me, I guess.
Yeah.
Man, but I put I put like illustrations.
There's like illustrations in the Road to Radcon book
because me, she did she did sketches.
She did a cover sketch that had a bunch of the characters on it.
And then she did like a final version.
So the final version is the actual cover, but then I took the sketches
and I kind of like picked them apart into the individual like characters.
And so the the you know, the blank pages between chapters in the book,
they have the character sketches kind of like, you know, one here, one there.
When there's like there's like five of them or something.
Just kind of just kind of interspersed in there because I had to pad it out
to make the the number of pages a multiple of four,
because that's how like bookbinding works.
I'm very proud of it, actually.
I think it's going to be a really attractive little little pamphlet.
A little bespoke item that only
Radcon four backers will have unless we sell them to other people.
Maybe which maybe I will because why not?
I'll probably have like seventy five extra copies at the end.
If anyone wants one, I'll fucking sell you that shit, I guess.
I don't know, it's going to be it's going to be cool.
I'm excited.
And then all we have to do is get the video,
is get the music video out and the OVA.
And then we can have Radcon money.
Yes. And then we. Oh, my God.
No, you still have a K-Day coming in from that, don't we?
And the dojin. Yeah, we still have like a all the left.
Oh, and the dojin. I've got people working on the dojin.
I've got people working on the dojin.
The the yeah, PCP payday, Radcon money is is in escrow.
It will all be liquidated and it will rain down upon.
Like like breaking a pinata.
This is what it feels like I'm doing all this work.
It feels like I'm hammering away trying to break this pinata of the PCP
Radcon money, just break it up.
So it all just comes pouring down on top of you're welcome all the candy.
Yes, yes, all the all the PC pennies that come exploding out.
All markets down.
So not worth as much as they used to be, but, you know, you do what you can.
It was a bubble. It popped.
I wish I wish it popped the pinata along with it.
I'm still. So that's what I've been doing.
That that was wait, wait, one last that's why I haven't.
I've just kind of gotten around to doing game stuff again.
I was going to spend this whole month doing game stuff,
but I had to spend like the first, you know, a couple of days
just finishing up the the Road to Radcon book stuff.
But it's satisfying work and I'm excited about it.
I don't mind. I don't mind it at all. Ha, ha.
OK, anyway, go on.
And I was going to say, I'm I'm still waiting for the plush
to be sent to me or to get here.
I'm so mad. Are they are they made?
I didn't get to order one. They're not making it. So fucking mad.
Oh, well, Tom, Tom, I know.
That's so un-pog of you. It's super.
I haven't ordered them yet.
So I there's there might be so much as there might be room for someone to slip
you a little, a little, a little cash on the side, a little.
Yeah, yeah. Imagine not pluging.
Imagine not being a pluging, dude.
I had it. I had the tab open, but I got buried in fucking
calling apartments and trying because I figured out while I was trying to get
apartments that my phone just doesn't take calls anymore.
Like I was holding my phone watching.
I was I was holding my phone watching a YouTube video.
It's like a Pixel 3a.
So like a little Android notification popped up and says missed call.
I'm like, didn't ring, didn't vibrate.
It just like, eh, you don't need to know you're getting phone calls, right?
So I missed like a bunch of calls from people
because it just doesn't let me know I get calls anymore.
I'm just like, sick. Awesome.
Now are those all calls from Ohio area or is that every call?
It really depends because like I know some people in Virginia
and like they can they've called me.
I've got notifications for that.
But like sometimes Massachusetts, it's just like random.
It works like it's like a coin toss.
Well, I get your phone call.
It really fucking depends.
Yeah, I wonder if it's like some too smart for its own good spam detection.
You know, that sounds like an algorithm
Google would implement without my knowledge to fuck me.
You could probably look and see right now.
There probably is some spam detection on my phone is so bad.
And it and I don't know what.
OK, when I'm when I'm out and I'm not on my computer,
I basically can't type anything
because something happened to like the autocorrect settings of my phone.
And I can't I've looked into how to fix it.
I don't know how to I've gone to all the options
and I've turned like autocorrect off and it doesn't do anything.
It doesn't change this at all.
But like when I'm trying to type in like discord or on Twitter or something
on my phone, the autocorrect is so it's so aggressive that I can't.
I literally can't type with it.
It like I will I will tip.
It does the thing where, you know, one button is assigned to like
you three different letters and you have to hit the button three times
to get to the third letter, right?
It does that it does that.
Wait, you're talking about.
Are you typing with a T nine keyboard in twenty twenty one?
No, it's a digital.
No, listen, you don't understand.
This is not a choice that I made.
These it just did this on its own.
And I cannot just download a different keyboard.
Just go to the disco.
G board from the Play Store.
Just I guess I guess I guess you're using.
I'm just using the fucking Google keyboard.
The get a different one.
Get like Swifty or something.
Oh, my God.
It's it's it's worse than that, though, because it's it's that
like you have to hit the button three times.
But it's also auto correcting to not even words, but like groups of letters.
I will I will hit, you know, the button is assigned to like,
you know, RQ or a fucking QQRST or whatever.
So I'm trying to type an R.
So I'll hit the button and it'll go to Q and then I'll type it again,
trying to make an R.
And it will think like, oh, you're going for like a double T.
And then it will just change to like two two capital T's in a row.
And then I'll be like, no, it looks like this sounds arcane as fuck.
It looks no, it looks normal.
It looks normal, but each key represents three letters.
Don't you you've never you know how like on a on a traditional like dial
phones, you know, so if you wanted to type in a letter,
you would you would use the number corresponding to nine nine keyboard.
Yeah.
So yeah, it's like numbers with the letters behind them.
It's it shows me the numbers.
And then on top of the number, it has the three, you know,
like one is why are you using a keyboard on a smartphone?
It's it's just what it's I was using the regular Google keyboard.
And now it looks like OK.
Yeah, I'm sure there's there's a button
somewhere on the keyboard to like change the layouts.
Let you just need to you button.
OK, you say that I have I have given the phone to other people
being like, what is it doing?
How do I make it not do this?
And no one I've given it to has been able to find.
Yeah, it feels like there should just be a button that fixes it on my old phone.
I remember I think I had G board and I'm pretty sure I could change it
to that mode if I wanted to like I've seen this.
I'm sorry that this could be fixed.
I'm I'm I'm sure it can be OK.
But I can't figure it out and I'm not the only one.
I've handed it off to people and they can't figure it out either.
But it's it's so so the way the way that I've had to type on the I mean,
the reason I haven't fixed it is because I almost never do it.
I almost never type stuff on my phone.
I use my computer.
But when I'm out, I have no choice but to use my phone.
So the way that I have to do it is I have to I have to
hit one of the buttons, wait for it to show all of the letters that it could
represent and then select that in.
I can't like type it with I have to then select that letter
from a side menu and then before typing any I have to hit space
so that it like forgets that it's in the middle of typing a string of letters
because if it if it knows that it's typing a string,
it will try to auto correct the string and just completely ruin what I'm doing.
It'll change change the letter that I'm currently typing to what it thinks
I'm trying to type.
I can't I'm looking through my settings now.
I can't find T nine.
But apparently you can set your keyboard to Morse code if you really wanted to.
I have no idea why.
Good. It would be an it would be an improvement.
It would be an improvement.
Go to settings then go to languages hit English Quarty
and you can change the layout to handwriting Quartz, Zerdy, Dvorak
or Morse code.
Maybe Ben, you should just cool.
You should just take this extra phone.
I've got I've got this HTC phone that's really good.
You can just have it.
You just got to come get it. Come get it.
OK. All right.
It's a trap.
I am you you are in.
Damn, I feel like I had something else I was going to say after the phone thing.
I had like two topics in mind and one was the phone.
There was another one we were talking about before the phone.
Was it was it bureaucracy, government bureaucracy?
I don't know. Whatever.
Kick Kickstarter stuff.
Kick Kickstarter. Red man.
Tearless. Red man.
Tearless. I've I've derailed.
I've derailed. I've lost.
I've completely lost track of what's what's going on.
Well, I'll show I'll show and say I have commissions open right now.
So I saw they seem.
OK, yeah, I saw those models you were offering.
Does that include like textures?
Yeah.
It's a complete model.
That seems like a really good value.
I think it is.
They're pretty low.
I mean, I posted them in my Patreon discord and that someone's like
message like an hour later.
Oh, my favorite 3D artist open commission.
They started $1500.
I'm like, I'm a bargain compared to that.
You can get to you.
So OK.
So does it include the modeling and the texturing
and like an idling animation because they were moving?
You the idle animation would be extra.
I guess I don't manage to be.
It's it includes a fully textured and rigged model
with like a couple stills and a turnaround.
So you'd get that and then you can pay extra
if you want a little animation under six seconds
and a bunch of things like the whole I'll put it in the chat.
There's there's here's here's the post with all the shit there.
It's got all the info there.
Cool.
By the way, I just want to say that Azumi that you showed.
Incredible.
I love her.
It's so good.
I'm so mad that I was like really hoping to like get more progress
on the game done because I was working on a little thing
and Unreal Engine moving around and have like a little jump
animations and stuff.
I'm like, I'll be so cool if I can fucking show this.
They have a big reveal, but I needed money
because I found out coming home from Ohio that the move date was
moved up from October to the end of this month.
So now I'm just like super panicked and need money.
So it's like, well, I'm just going to be a whore
and open up commissions forever now, I guess.
So the the I mean, the Azumi game is still a 2D game.
Right. I'm a worker.
I was working on a 3D game and it looked really cool.
Oh, I didn't.
I didn't even know because it was a secret.
I didn't even realize working on it in secret.
But now the jigs up because I had to show off all the models
that I was working on for it because I need money.
And that was the only example I had of a complex model.
I was thinking I hadn't heard anything
about Azumi game in a little while.
And I guess that explains it's a lot of ruin.
It's all on the back burner now because I need a house slash apartment.
In my opinion, 3D games are better than 2D games
because there's more D. There is.
There's additional D and I want the D.
So I want more everybody does.
That's what the people the people crave.
Yeah. Exactly.
I really I really I really like these.
I'm looking at like that like they're the older models.
That one like horned zombie with the big toothy mouth.
I saw that before. This looked really good.
This this like industrial elevator looks awesome.
It looks like something out of solid metal gear or something.
Yeah, I feel like metal.
I figure like I really got the PS1 look down.
I feel like it's definitely there, which was the goal.
Yeah, yeah, definitely for sure.
So what did you do for me?
Oh, the other animations for Azumi you showed
where they're running and the role, the role in particular looked so smooth.
I really could imagine doing the jump and then rolling after a jump.
And it just imagining you want to know why it looks good
because I modeled it after Dark Souls.
Oh, I went frame by frame.
Dark Souls is like, how did they do it?
And I was like trying to get her to do it.
But like it was really hard because I did it just like Dark Souls.
And then I was like, I'll just use a blend shape to blend back into the idol.
And it like didn't work.
So I had to go back and like redo the end half of the frames
to have her come back to that like actual kind of like
ninja pose idol animation she stays in.
There's a lot learned a lot is really interesting.
3D animation is so fucking confusing.
Dude, it's all those different little little rotatory.
I opened up the graph editor for the first time and I cried.
It was terrifying.
Every single part of the skeleton has like
nine different graphs for each like rotation and location axis.
And then you just open up the graph and there's like 500 lines.
And it's like, you need to manually adjust these.
I'm just like, it's scary.
Oh, yeah, the curve. Yeah.
The curve fuckers. I could never.
We got to flatten the curve. Yeah.
Yeah. If you flatten the curve, you can right click.
You can be like a straight line, please.
Yeah, yeah. But then it's all jerky.
Yeah. If you're making guilty gear, that's what you want.
That's how you make it look like an enemy.
Yeah, guilty gear. Never heard of it.
Hey, I watched those.
I watched those woolly versus lower videos.
Yeah. And at first I thought they were kind of good.
But actually, I don't think they're that good.
Like they're just OK.
I watched the first one. I think your lecture is better.
I haven't watched the rest of them.
Well, yeah.
But by the I let the whole series play out in the background
and by the end of it, I was like,
he's just recounting the plot of the game.
He's just he's just giving a point by point.
This happened and this happened and this happened and this happened.
It's the lecture, your lecture is a better like top down overview
of the lore of the world of guilty gear.
His where's his are just a recounting of these are the stories
in the games, which is fine.
It's a different goal, I guess.
It's it's yeah, I think there's that speaking of the lectures
having like unique benefits, it's sort of like the difference between
reading a textbook and then asking the teacher what the hell
the textbook means and then getting an answer tailored to the question
because the lecture has more of that.
Obviously, not the audience at home can't like ask questions
and get an answer in real time when the audience aspect of it.
It helps with some of the more confusing things that
may just be hard to read or just when you you say them flatly
in like a plot synopsis, you're like, huh?
I don't get how that follows.
I don't get how it tracks and you can ask the person in the lecture how.
When the audience is unfamiliar with the subject matter
and they react in real time to like the surprising elements of it,
that's really good.
That adds a lot.
And then when they're confused or when they notice like a contradiction
or a or a weird element and they ask about it
just because it's like what they were thinking, you know, for sure,
some portion of the audience of the lecture at home is probably also wondering
about that thing, right?
If you thought of it and you were like, hey, what's what's the deal with that?
And then you ask it and then you get to the the lecturer
who doesn't have a written response to it, but they get to sort of opine
and give their thoughts about like, well, here's what I think is the deal with that.
Or like, oh, yeah, actually, I I wouldn't have mentioned it.
But actually, that is interesting.
So I'll go on a little tangent about it.
Yeah, it's good.
It's a good vehicle.
It's sort of it's it's more.
I think it's more.
I think it's a more engaging than like a video essay format in a lot of cases.
Yeah.
Adds a lot.
The freeform nature of it's pretty close.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah.
Oh, Pog, I really should do more.
That would be I mean, that would be the thing to do, right, based on like
with the kind of views that my videos get.
It's very, very clear that what I should be doing with my channel
is making more lectures about stuff.
That's what the people respond to, but I have no idea what I would do one on.
And also organizing.
Organizing is really hard.
It's a lot of prep.
It's very hard.
Yeah.
And that's why only like three people outside of the PCP have done.
I think it's important to realize because everyone, a lot of people are just like,
well, you know, it's just a video essay.
Why not just do it as a video essay?
And like, why does it take so much work?
It's like because the video essay, you have a script that you've written all out.
You can retake things.
If we're doing these live off the cuff, pretty much, we just have like rough notes
and you just have to speak it all.
You have to be familiar enough with it to talk about it conversationally,
but keep the structure of a video essay.
It's tricky.
Yeah.
Well, something that doesn't Victor have the teleprompter.
He's holding up.
He's holding up flashcards.
We're not.
No, nobody knows about that.
Cut that part.
He's the cue cards.
He hands out to the audience members when to laugh.
Yeah.
There's there's an applause sign just right out of frame.
Yep.
There's a there's a riff.
There's a sign that says riff to alert the audience to start riffing.
And in that one, like 360.
The one that was the same.
What was it?
The your first one, Ben, we had the 360 camera.
That version lecture in 360.
Such a stupid idea.
But like, whatever.
Sure.
Why not like that one?
That one has like the cue cards as well.
But they're always not where you're looking.
It just so happens that it's.
Yeah.
No, you know, it's just like the moon landing.
You know, Apollo 11, they faked it, not real.
And that's that's what Ben was doing in that one.
That was the fake one.
It was all preplanned and everything.
But Apollo 13, where they had all the problems, that was the real one.
That's why it went so bad.
They had to do it for real.
It wasn't in Hollywood.
And that's why they couldn't do the 360 anymore.
You guys couldn't do the 360.
You had to do it for real.
We blew our budget on the first one.
We had to make the lectures real.
What one thing that I don't one thing
that I don't think I could do a lecture on.
But I think I sometimes I think about doing basically a video essay about
is that thing that that old forum
from the people that believe that Digimon were real, the real Digimon.
Oh, yeah, you were talking about that way back.
Or the Digi Clips and yeah, I considered even back like when I was
I think when I was about to do the Sonichu 101 lecture,
I was thinking maybe I could also do one on the Adragon too.
I was really hype about it. Yeah.
Well, I tried looking up information on it.
And like a lot of the info that I used to have has been like scrubbed.
There is OK.
There was like when I learned about the when I learned about the Digi Clips,
you could the forums still existed.
And I went to the forums and I read through the threads and they were pretty funny.
Now, like the only evidence that exists of it is the something awful thread
or the something awful post from years and years ago.
So I think what I would have to do if I did that video is I would I could.
Yeah, I could summarize like what's on the something awful thread.
What was the deal with it?
What happened?
And then I think a big chunk of that video would just be being me being like,
hey, guys, I can't prove any of this,
but let me just tell you some really funny shit that I remember seeing
from the the real Digimon Believers Forum,
like in the aftermath of the something awful rate.
I don't know. I don't know if that's really going to be good.
That doesn't sound that great.
You know, damn, I thought it might be funny.
But OK, I mean, never mind.
Bummer.
I don't know. It's it's that one's a that one's a read.
That's one of the funniest stories of Internet buffoonery that I have seen.
And nobody talks about it probably because it's all like gone.
The information is not like on archive.org or anything.
It's just all been scrubbed for real.
I have I have tried to find like I've tried to use like the wayback machine
to go back and like look at the old forum post and I wasn't able to do it.
I am.
Maybe one of these.
What a nightmare.
They'll try archive.
So what you're saying is that not only are the PCP lectures great pieces of art,
they're also like cultural archiving projects.
That is precisely what I'm saying.
Wait, is archive.org and wayback machine the same thing?
Yeah, I think the wayback machine is powered by archive.org.
Yeah, yeah, it is. OK.
Oh, well. Oh, well.
Um, I just think the DigiClips is really funny.
OK, what else?
How's everyone doing? How's everyone's man?
You know what I wanted to talk about?
I wanted to talk about what's the process of buying a house
because it's it's really fucking mysterious.
I just recently went through and I bought bought my first house.
Pretty exciting. Jesus.
Yeah, I've seen your your update.
Your update posts about the renovation.
Yeah. And it's like it's it's so much more difficult
than you would even imagine, right?
Like in order in order to buy a house, you know, you start,
you go to like Zillow dot com and you're like, oh,
look at all these houses for sale. I can just just go on.
You just go on eBay.
I could just pick any one I want.
And I'd like, hello, sir, I'd like to buy your house.
What?
Me, it's yeah, millennial, millennial, stupidly.
Avocado toast, please.
Me, nodding wisely, one house.
Yeah, it's just that.
But but it's so much worse.
So you have to first of all, you have to find yourself
a real estate agent, right?
So you find your agent, you have to need an agent.
If you don't have a they call it your buyer's agent.
If you don't have an agent, you're fucked.
You're not even going to get to see the houses.
So that's like the first step.
You find an agent and then you find a house you want to look at
and you tell the agent, hey, can you talk to their agent
and get me into the showing?
Right. And you have every house is selling within like a few days.
So you have to find a house immediately email your agent,
get the agent to set up a showing like the next day.
And then you can put an offer on the house like the day after that.
And the offer process, you would think like, OK, just tell him,
yeah, I'll give you your asking two hundred ninety thousand.
I'll give you two hundred ninety, right?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You have to find a loan officer, somebody who works for like a mortgage company.
And then tell them what the house that you want to buy
and what you think you want to offer.
And then they have to pre approve you for a mortgage
for like a little bit more than that, but not too much more.
Otherwise, it looks suspicious to the seller's agent.
So you get this pre approval letter and they won't produce that
unless you give them like bank statements
and like pay stubs for a couple of months of recent history.
So there's this whole process, right?
And if you manage to navigate this, you got your pre approval,
you put your offer in, you'll still fail.
You'll still fail because if you offered two hundred ninety,
you're asking two hundred ninety.
You're not even you're not even on the table.
You're not even playing the game.
Oh, oh, is it like a game where like everybody knows that like, yeah,
you say two ninety, but it's like how much more exactly.
It's this whole fucking game.
So you go to Zillow or whatever, you see the price the house is listed
or realtor.com or whatever.
All that's another thing.
All the sites are all pulling from the same one database.
There's only one database of listed houses and every every like,
oh, we'll find you a house site is just pulling off of the same database.
And then they reformat it with their own CSS in some way.
So that's a whole scam.
Wow. Capitalism sure does breed innovation, right?
But yeah, every day I find a new reason to fucking buy a guillotine.
It's incredible. Yeah, it's crazy.
They list their house for for some number.
They have some number that it's supposedly worth.
And nothing is worth what they're listing it for.
But that's what they say, you know, because the housing market right now
is just like going up and up and up to infinity.
So you got to you got to come up with your your pre-approved mortgage,
whatever document that says you're you're worth like like 10 percent more
than you need, and then you got to offer like five percent more than they're asking.
And that might get you considered.
But then there's like all these.
So there's different types of mortgages and like the the buyer's agent
will convince them that different mortgages are better or worse.
And so they'll disqualify certain buyers.
Excuse me, the seller's agent will convince the seller
that different mortgage types are like better or worse.
Like they don't they won't take the the VA loans from veterans
because that has contingencies and that's you don't want that.
You don't want contingencies. That's bad.
So they only want convention. No, obviously.
They only want obviously, you don't want.
What kind of a fool would be OK with contingencies?
They want the buyer to have a conventional mortgage with no contingencies
or ideally cash.
And you're like, no, who has who has hundreds of thousands of dollars in cash?
Right. If you could just if you could just buy it with cash.
What's the point of all this fucking rigmarole?
But but you still have to do it. You still have to do it.
You know, such an alien.
I like how you've just confirmed that I will never own a house.
Like, like, but no, no, it gets worse.
Tom, it gets worse. I mean, you can believe it.
It's I'm sure it can.
We live in America and everything can get worse.
So you kidding me?
So I for my personal house, they did list it.
I think they listed for 280 and I offer 290 and I wasn't even the highest offer.
But again, I had the conventional mortgage.
And so that got me it.
They said, OK, we'll take your offer.
But then I had my contingencies.
So I said, I have to do a home inspection before I'll buy the house, right?
If the home inspection says the house is no good, then I'll walk away, right?
Or we can negotiate on the price.
And I was lucky that they accepted that because now a lot of the time,
you can't even do that.
You have to just like buy it as is pretty much sight unseen.
You walk through the house one time for five minutes, right?
Sure. And then you realize there's like ants in the walls and demons under the floor.
Yeah. So. Oh, so then you got speaking of speaking of ants in the walls
after the store, I got to tell you about the ants.
OK. Oh, OK.
Well, this is a this is a note about apartment hunting, right?
This is about moving.
This is about homes, I guess.
Just a funny story.
I moved in to this temporary house that I'm staying in for a month
before I start my other lease at another place in September.
When I moved in, my roommate here, I barely see him like at all.
He just stays in his room, smokes weed, fine by me.
Yeah. I moved in.
There was a pizza in a box on the floor.
Yeah. In the main living room.
No pizza in the box.
I'm like, OK, guy was eating a pizza.
That's cool. I like pizza.
It makes sense. It is.
It is. It's the eighth.
It's the eighth of the month.
The pizza is still there.
There's ants crawling into the box.
And I'm I'm at the point where I'm like, I think I might need to do something about.
I know it's not my pizza to move.
I may be my apartment to deal with this pizza situation.
You're looking at it too short term, right?
Because eventually the ants will have consumed the pizza.
No, the problem solves it.
That's probably what he was thinking.
He was like, I could pick this up or the ants will take care of it for me.
Why why spend the effort doing what the what nature will do.
Exactly. He's got an army of mates working for essentially.
Yeah, maybe he's got to figure it out.
Man, man, so so back at the ranch here.
Yeah. Yeah.
So I have to have the home inspection done.
I hire a home inspector costs a thousand bucks, which, you know,
you think, oh, a thousand dollars, that's a lot of money.
But no, you'll be believing a thousand bucks here and there.
The whole process, that's just constant.
Yeah. Yeah. Everybody needs their fucking every fucking bloodsucker
involved in this process needs their needs.
Oh, yeah.
It's because the entire industry needs to die.
But yeah, the the big guy comes at the end of hidden surprise fees.
But so you get the home inspection and then you also need to get an appraisal done.
So you think you know what the house is worth.
You made an offer that you believe is more than what the house is worth,
but otherwise you won't get it.
Now you need to convince somebody who works for the bank
that the house is worth at least the offer that you made on the house
that you know is more than the house is worth.
Say that again.
So they you have to hire an appraiser who comes in and they value the house
and they have to come up with a valuation that's more than your offer.
Otherwise, you can't get a mortgage.
They have to value the house that you are buying that is more than your offer.
Otherwise, you can't.
Why do they want the value to be bigger than what you want to have a mortgage
on a house that they think is worth less than what you want to pay for?
So you have to convince the bank to give you money.
And then you have to convince the bank to let you spend the money.
So basically, you pay you pay this appraiser.
You pay this appraiser to to tell the bank.
No, it's a good deal. No, it's a good deal.
You have to pay the bank to tell them that they're fucking you.
You already know what the house was worth.
You made an offer that's more than that because the bank makes you pay
to tell them that you are fucking yourself over for their benefit.
And that you're happy about it and they can convince them that.
No, no, no, it's time to burn it all down.
Burn it all down, pay more and less, but not actually.
Yeah. OK, crack.
Why did you do this?
Well, I'll tell you why, because it's way cheaper than renting.
And I can I can do it in the long run.
But at what cost immediately immediately?
You just it just costs you your dignity.
It's it's not it doesn't cost.
It's not immediately cheaper because you don't have to spend
two hundred and ninety thousand dollars to immediately to rent.
No, no, it's immediately cheaper
because you ever do you ever think about how you can like 3D print
an entire house for nine grand and for some reason we're not doing it.
We know why we're not doing it, but isn't it strange?
Yeah. So so you go through the sole process, right?
You get the appraisal, the appraisal.
If you're lucky, it comes in at the number you need.
You've got the magical valuation, your offer was accepted,
you're approved.
Now, maybe if you're lucky, the mortgage company,
the loan guys will actually come through with the money
before the deadline that the seller is set.
Now, there's like an extra three weeks where like they're just coming up
with the money and going through all of your your finances and history.
Just secretly, there's this underwriting process, they call it,
where they're just they're digging into your history in a deep background check
and like maybe anything they can do to be good.
Yes, or anyway, is there anything in here?
Or anywhere we can just run with all the money
they've already spent on this process and make them restart the whole thing.
That is correct.
So if you get through all of that, I see.
If you get through all of that, it sounds a lot cheaper to buy a gun
and start going to Wall Street.
Yeah, the same.
Don't say that you can't you can't bleep it.
If you get through all of that, then the big kicker comes.
You have to hire a lawyer who will do what's called the closing
and you go to the lawyer's office and sign all the paperwork and everything.
And then you need to both pay the lawyer
and the company giving you the mortgage, a shitload of money.
So like in my house, for example,
I was going to pay five percent of the price as my down payment.
I needed an additional five percent of the overall cost of the house
just to pay the the lawyer in the bank, the closing costs.
All the all the fees.
Yeah, just lost money to fees.
Yeah, an additional five percent five five five percent of the of the cost
of the total value of the house.
So it's like, you know, if you talk to a boomer about this and they'll say,
oh, yeah, to buy a house, you got to have 20 percent down payment.
You want to have 20 percent of the you will never you will never be able to do it.
Right. If your house was three hundred thousand dollars,
you would need $60,000 and then probably
twenty thousand dollars on top of that to pay for closing costs.
It's impossible. You cannot do it. Right.
So I was able to do it was this is 10 percent.
This is because, yeah.
Wait, I thought you said, wait, how do you do it with 10 percent?
I thought you said 20 percent was was not enough.
Yeah, no, no, no.
So they tell you you need 20 percent because if you pay 20 percent down,
then you can avoid private mortgage insurance, which is an additional monthly cost.
But it's impossible. You cannot do it
because nobody nobody could save 20 percent of the value of a house today.
Man, all of this fucking process, it's a good thing.
This process isn't in the way of something essential like housing.
You know, that would seem kind of cruel.
Yeah. Oh, meanwhile, right?
Like you're renting a place and you you don't do I pay my rent this month
because I'm going to stay here another month.
I don't know when will we close?
I have no idea. Right.
So you better plan to rent a house and also buy a house
at the same time for a couple of months and have them overlap.
Otherwise, you're back.
Yeah, I see. I see.
I see. Pretty exciting.
Pretty good. Yeah.
The surprise at the end where it's just like stuff.
Oh, yeah. You remember how you had your down payment?
Well, if you just have all of that money that you saved up,
if you could just have already saved twice as much of that
to pay the other guy, that'd be great.
So what what a closing cost to other than nothing?
Closing costs. It's just a scam.
It pays the lawyer that you sign the documents for that.
And then you pay the bank that's giving you the money.
You pay them.
Haven't you already paid them for giving you money?
You already paid them twice, though.
No, you pay them because then they disperse part of those costs
to pay the the two real estate agents who are involved.
So because they have to get paid, that's how they get paid.
And I remember when you could just go to a store and buy something.
Yeah, that was cute.
I that it feels like it would be cheaper
to buy the necessary materials to build a house in the woods.
Yes, it feels like it would be cheaper.
But you don't own the land, so you can't build out there.
So you'll get arrested.
You need you need to you need to buy the land.
And I mean, you you can't really build a house yourself.
So you need to you need to like hire contractors for that.
That's I'm sure that's it's I've played mine.
I'll tell you hiring contractors is a whole separate pain in the ass.
Yeah, I can only imagine.
So I move into this house and the roof starts leaking.
And I'm like, all right, cool, cool.
And I paid three hundred thousand dollars.
Yeah, no big deal.
I'll just hire a roofer to come out and and check it out.
Fix it, right? No big deal.
Hmm. Yeah.
Well, I'll tell you, I've had obvious.
I've called like 10 different roofers.
I got one to come out and they had to come back five times to keep fixing it
because they fucked it up every time.
And that's just how it goes.
OK, you just you just smile and say, oh, good to see you again.
How's it going, Bill at the roof and company?
We're on a first name basis.
And that's just how he likes it.
This is what he wants.
Now, did you have to play every time?
Or did he actually like have no, no, I only had to pay him the first time
when they supposedly fixed it and then they came back four or five times for free.
But, you know, the only cost is water has been pouring down
on my sofa and my computer five times during the rain.
Not a big deal.
No, of course, I take it.
You know, it's funny, I was it's funny.
I just was I was just telling I was having a conversation
with Kazi the other day about about spending about, like,
you know, using using money to, like, make create more money
and how like home ownership is like the is like the thing.
It's like the thing that you do to, like, to, like, build wealth in America.
That is a thousand percent true.
And I'll tell you.
So in order to buy the house, what I did was cash out my 401k for my old job,
which I could do with no fee because of the pandemic,
because of the pandemic, all 401k cash out if you if you had a quote unquote
pandemic related impact to your finances, which everyone did.
So you could cash it out with no fee.
And I took that money and then combine that with some some money
that I got when the company I worked for got bought out, which was like,
I didn't have much savings, but the two of those together was just enough
to have like 10 percent of this house.
So it was just barely enough money, right?
And if you look at the value of the house today,
just like a few months later, I bought this in December and November.
I already, on paper, have way more money than I had before I bought the house.
Like, I'm I'm just make including including like the value of the house.
If you look at the net, if you look at the value of the house today
versus like what I spent on it, I already have made back all that money.
Like it's no big deal.
Yeah. Yeah.
And, you know, and it's good for the foreseeable future.
Like and so my monthly costs are lower.
I already have that that extra value.
Like I there's no downsides as far as I'm concerned,
except for everything you just said for the night, the nightmare process.
The nightmare process of the except for one needing
front fee that you need. Yeah. Yeah.
So honestly, what I would recommend if you have if you have a regular income,
like if you have a steady income and you can somehow like liquidate a bunch
of shit to get just enough money to get your foot in the door and buy a house,
do it. It is absolutely worth it because you then immediately start saving money.
Yeah. Because once you have the mortgage,
once you have the house and you have the mortgage,
your rent payments are basically going to yourself. That's correct.
Yeah. So it's just, you know, I pay like
like $300, let's say, of my mortgage payment is just lost to interest or whatever.
But the other like $1,200 goes basically into a bank account.
Right. Yeah. Which is which is sick.
You have you have assumed debt and now your rent goes to like pay down.
Yeah, exactly.
More or less. Yeah.
And and it's not just lost, right?
Because all that debt is just equity.
It's just I own a greater percentage of it's the value of the house. Exactly.
Yeah. Yeah. Sure.
That's um, but I'm too hard, though.
So hard for capitalism.
It's so annoying. It's too much.
Yeah. It's, you know, it seemed basically impossible.
It sounds all the way up until I did it.
Yeah. Yeah.
I just can't imagine having a large lump sum of money.
I don't even know what that looks like. I have no idea.
I just, I don't know.
I still get excited when I find a quarter.
I'm just like, oh, my God.
It's the most the most affordable houses are like out, you know,
they're out of way from like, you know, civilization.
And I like I like urban.
I like urban living.
And I could never afford a building in like the city.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, yeah, that's housing costs.
Real estate costs is location, location, location.
Yeah, for sure. And I was able to save some money.
I bought a small house and I bought it.
You know, next to Worcester, instead of Boston, where where it's a little cheaper.
Yeah. I just want a house the size of a studio that costs like nothing
in the middle of nowhere, as long as I get decent internet.
That's all I care about.
But the inside of my house is like a thousand square feet or so.
Maybe a little bit more if you count some of the loft area.
So it's not like a big house, but I've also got gigabit fiber.
So like I got the killer internet and it's it's sick.
Honestly, I love it.
Think how much slime you can mine with a connection like that.
Why do you think you got the profits are the profits are skyrocketing?
Like I said, I'm already making money.
It's all it's all in slime, but I'm making money.
I don't have money for the down payment.
But if you look at my.
Also, I'll sell you I'll sell you my discord account
that's tied to my endless war profile that has like so
is like quadrillions of slime coin slime, corn, gold, farming.
You could probably get pretty far doping someone
into thinking that it's an actual cryptocurrency.
Yeah, I mean, the only thing that gives crypto value is faith.
So like there's no reason you couldn't just make it.
The block chain, Tom, nobody knows what the block chain is.
You just say that you're on the block.
It's all the it's all the Persian general problem or whatever.
Tom literally don't know what you're talking about.
I it's that some fucking thought experiment that Bitcoiners are like,
oh, it's it's an age old question.
And Bitcoin's the all the greatest solution mankind has ever
has ever come up when I when I think of block chain.
Well, I can think of is cube anal beads.
Gross. Oh, I'm just saying I get it.
But I don't like it.
That's fucked up.
Man, speaking of speaking of horrible things, speaking of
disappointments, speaking of speaking of speaking of both.
Speaking of speaking of things that go up your ass.
Bitcoin is on the rise again.
People are saying it's rallying again.
I know.
GPU. Holy shit.
I haven't been able to render in cycles for three fucking years.
It fell under 30 K for a while.
And now it is it's almost back up to 45.
People are saying, oh, people 100 K.
Crack, were you able to get a GPU?
Do you even need the GPU?
No, I've been running.
I've got a GTX 970 or something.
I've been running that shit since it came out.
And it's great.
I I got it right before GPU prices started going totally insane.
So it's like I'm so, dude, I have.
OK, I almost bought a 20 60.
But I was like, eh, the three thousand series will come out.
And that fucked me.
But then I found one.
I got a 30 60 TI.
I paid way too much, but I got it.
And then it was defective.
And I was like, oh, fuck.
New egg was like, we can't.
We don't accept returns on this item.
We can only replace it.
I'm like, oh, so you'll send me another one.
And then I waited two weeks and they're like, we have no stock.
Here's your money back.
I'm like, back.
Got him.
And it's been it's been a nightmare ever since.
That's terrible.
And yeah, I've been trying to get like a 30 70.
And it's just you can't do it.
I mean, I'm just at this point.
I'm just like, I'm just going to get a four thousand series.
They're going to come out next year like clockwork anyway.
So like, yeah, and hopefully they make more of them right there.
The rumors right now is that like, oh, they're going to be like
twice as power consumption, but like twice as powerful as the 30 series.
I'm like, so they're just going to like charge scalper prices at MSRP now
because they realize they can get away with it.
Yeah, exactly.
They're just going to come out.
It's going to be a thousand bucks.
Yeah, it's going to be 70 or whatever.
Fucking Jensen's going to come out with his fucking leather jacket
and pull one out of his stove and be like, hey, guys, it's fucking.
It's only eight ninety nine for the forty sixty.
And what a bargain.
Like, I hate my life.
Money, so it's the worst.
I'm just the fuck.
I just remember, did we did me and crack and Tom, did the three of us
ever hang out at the same time at like Trixie's house in Boston?
I think just one time we did.
We went into Boston and like with Munchie
and we hung out and we went around the city and we went to that fucking
park and it was cold, but we were hanging out there anyway.
We were just dicking around.
Oh, when we played Pokemon Go in the in the Commons.
Oh, I was thinking of the was that the same time?
Like, I know that crack, you came and hung out that one time.
I think it was on like Christmas or it was like around Christmas at Trixie's place.
And that was the time I got really drunk.
Mr. New Year's, I went to and I don't know if you were living there.
That doesn't narrow it down.
Yeah, that was there.
But Tom was like in a tonic state.
Yeah, I wasn't there for real tired or no, you were.
I mean, you were physically there, but like you were not.
You were not engaged in whatever was going on.
Oh, when we went to like the Chinese place and stuff.
No, no, no, this was at the house.
No, no, when we're hanging out in the house, I'm thinking,
I'm thinking maybe these were two different.
I think they were the time we went to the Commons and then maybe because I was
definitely alive and doing things and the trip I'm talking about or excursion,
whatever you want to call it.
I forgot about the crack was there for the Boston Commons,
Pokemon Go trip.
No, I don't think so.
You were there for no, you were definitely there because that was the first
time I saw you in real life was this this outing that I'm talking about.
Wait, wait, you're thinking are you thinking there was the separate time
when we all met up for Christmas?
I think the year before, like when I was still living in Georgia
and I came up to visit and
Nathan or no, that was the same time.
No, that was that was the same time.
I don't know if you were cracked.
You were definitely there because we ate the spicy.
The do you eat the spicy sauce there for the major cross.
I was there.
I don't know if Tom was.
I don't know that.
God, wait, give you were not.
You were not there.
Give you were not.
No, you're just you were not there.
Oh, my God.
Well, I guess that makes sense.
And where are you going?
Where are you going with this?
I don't know.
I'm just trying to piece together.
I'm just trying to figure out my life when we hung out and why.
I don't know what I think.
Why would we do such a thing?
Why would friends hang out?
OK, and like have a good time?
What a strange concept.
Man, there was it doesn't make any money.
It doesn't pay the mortgage.
It's true.
It's becoming increasingly risky to have fun in today's economy.
Doesn't grow my portfolio.
Speaking of the one time we did the sauce thing
where where you guys famously ran out of the place to eat snow.
Oh, I know that.
I don't know if I did.
I think after that, I don't know if like I dropped off
you and and Nate and Michelle and everybody down like a parking garage.
And we took a picture together.
I wish I could find that picture.
Hmm, that sounds familiar.
Yeah, I remember you just you ate.
We all I didn't run out to eat the snow.
Everybody else ran out to eat the snow.
I just bought a bunch of bottled water
from the counter and started drinking bottled water.
You didn't like move.
You didn't move.
You just sat there with your face like puffy and red
and like tears streaming down your face, just emote, just staring,
just like, yep, hurts real bad.
Yeah, it was terrible.
But just but just placid, but just placid about it.
I mean, I ain't trying to make a scene.
Everybody else had no problem making a scene.
No, you know why?
Because May had just eaten a ton of the sauce.
And I was like, you know what, I I'm just going to eat a bunch of the sauce.
And oh, yeah, didn't she like not just is what it is.
Didn't she like not even care?
Not. I remember she didn't even notice.
She had like no real.
She was like inhuman.
Basically, I'm feeling look like a robot.
Yeah, scary in hindsight.
Creepy, creepy.
Yes.
Whatever, I just like to reminisce about the good old days.
All right, listen, we live in a post COVID world now
and nothing good is ever going to happen again.
All we have, all we have is our memories, guys.
All right, get on board.
OK.
Yes, true.
I have.
Oh, I have I have a note here about
Nate Nate's new Nate's podcast, The Gamer Zone.
I don't know if anyone. Gamer Zone.
I didn't I didn't listen to it.
I just I didn't I don't know.
I saw that that's a thing that exists.
And I'm not I'm not clear on if it's a I'm not sure if it's a one time.
I think it's conditional on its success.
If the, you know, people watch the first one, they'll do another one.
I mean, how I mean.
I mean, it's going to get it's going to get whatever I imagine doing a podcast.
How embarrassing. I know.
Very, very embarrassing.
I was looking if I could find everything is conditional on everyone at the table.
But I don't have it.
I don't think of the thing that you were talking about with the snow.
But instead, I found this, which is like, I think.
Redcon one or two.
No, that that was.
That was I'm retrieval.
Con was a Brony Con.
What was that was in Boston?
Because we were in South Station.
We took that photo.
That was for the meetup.
Remember trying to do a impromptu meetup at South Station?
The the the the the that was like Redcon, like three.
Yeah, it was like on three point five people call it.
That was when we all went to Trixie's place.
That was when we had that stupid meeting.
Where nothing was accomplished except that, like, very unproductive.
Nate decided Nate.
No, that was when Nate made the decided, like, yes,
I will be moving to Virginia Beach to do canton.
That was that was like the only that was like the only thing that got it.
It is that proceed in the orchid events.
They all they all talked about it
like it was we were making plans for all of us.
But nobody had it was just those two.
And that was the only thing.
And they could have just fucking talked about it under any circumstances.
Yeah, it was it was because Trixie would never come to meetings
and or something.
And so, yeah, they decided to all meet up.
Or at least it was it was Nate and Trixie
in Boston, because Trixie was in Boston at the time.
Then you were around.
So you're like, yeah, I'll be there.
And then Tom probably.
And then I heard about it.
And I was like, oh, everyone's going to be there.
Yeah, I want to go and then I flew over.
It's like it's like it was no it was no travel for like me and Tom.
Nate, I don't I don't know.
I think Munchie was just visiting.
Munchie was already there or something.
He was. Oh, for school.
No, he was there for school, I think, or something.
And then, yeah, the weird part is Nate deciding
that he had to come to Boston to like have a pow wow about whatever it was.
Was that the same weekend that we all had the discussion
with Munchie about college?
Because wasn't he there to visit Kaze before going to school?
I don't remember.
That did happen. Maybe.
Yeah, it might have been before.
It might have been before he might.
He might have been looking at colleges or something like that.
And just, yeah.
Yeah, but then I mean, yeah, since everyone was going to be there,
I mean, you can say it was a waste of time to just be like, well, that event
was where I believe where Noogle was born.
And that was worth all of all of the trouble.
Noogle was pretty great.
Noogle, I mean, it's I mean, it's not.
I mean, it was fun. Don't get me wrong.
I just think it's weird was that they had that Nate had to travel
across the country to have a to have a desk or a person.
Yeah, basically, but whatever.
I mean, we had played.
We did have Jack three.
And then you and Munchie did like an RFC K thing.
No, that was when that was when we did the
infamous for all.
Wait, what's the the campaign in Brawl called?
Subspace emissary.
Wait, no, that was. Yes, we did.
I think so. Yeah, we did that.
Like the eight hour subspace emissary
play through that got destroyed by the fat 32.
It's because it was my hard drive.
Yeah, what a nightmare.
Fuck, fuck that game.
I thought because the I have a clip from a stream that you did.
RFC K wise.
Hmm.
So you know, I'm just like, if that was did you also do the subspace emissary?
We might have streamed.
We know it wasn't a red come through.
We might have streamed some Brawl at some point,
but we did off stream a recorded
subspace emissary run and it was lost on the hard drive
because of the fat 32 format.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, OK, OK, whatever.
OK, well, now I know.
Speaking of speaking of the sauce,
I found the picture of not the one that I wanted to find,
but this picture of me after I suffered the sauce.
You, this looks like you had recovered.
This seems like this looks like your expression the entire time getting a house.
That just seems like.
Yeah, that's that's about what the process was like.
Yeah, yeah, this is this is after you'd had a little time.
You'd had a little time to like kind of recover from it.
You were more intensely.
It's hard to imagine.
Like before.
Yeah.
That was some fucking sauce, though.
That shit sucked.
Good, good times, good times.
OK, well, I guess nothing to say about the gamer's own, I guess.
I guess I just thought it bore mention.
Yeah, it's about Dan.
I'm I'm all out of I'm all out of fucking topics of interest.
I've got I've got a couple more.
I've got a couple more.
I mean, first, I got to plug the quake map.
I made a quake map just recently, just for fun.
It's the 25th anniversary of quake.
Then played it.
Yeah, I think you probably had a bad time.
I played it.
No, once I figured out what I was doing, I played it and I had a good time.
But then this I didn't find the secrets because they involve kind of high level
quake strats that I was felt sort of exhausted when I learned what was.
What do you use to map quake maps?
Or like, these are like a modern editor that people are using?
Yeah, I assume so.
There's a combination.
So in order to make the actual geometry to do the modeling,
you can use this tool called trench broom, which is really good.
It's really modern. You pretty much just paint in 3D.
It's wonderful.
Absolutely wonderful.
But every other part of the process is ridiculously antiquated.
So like really to manage textures.
I use this tool Wally, which has been unchanged since about 1998.
But it runs it fucking runs in wine.
No problem.
So no big deal.
Jesus, that's incredible.
And there's there's some other little tricks.
So there there's this guy, Eric W, who does
the the current iteration of tools that everyone uses to compile their maps
and the lighting and stuff.
And those are good.
So you just download them and their command line tools.
But people make like like GUIs that you can use to pretty much just like
check some boxes and have it make the map.
So that's no problem.
Yeah. And honestly, I would recommend it.
I would say go download trench broom.
There's this guy dump truck DS on YouTube who does tutorials.
He has a ridiculously in depth tutorial series that literally
anybody can follow and it'll get you started and you should do it.
Tom, you should actually do it.
Go make a quick quick map and have fun.
But everybody listening, stop listening.
Go to my website, download this this map and play it and then come back.
So that's wait, link link it right here.
Link it in the in the chat so LES are confined.
Yeah, it's just if they just go to kissy.net, it's on the first story.
But I'll link the the actual link in case, you know, in case it's two years.
No one's going to type a link in a browser.
You have to give it too many numbers.
Play the check. Check out.
Check out the slime factory.
Take a tour. Take a tour of the slime factory.
See where the see where the slimes like fuck.
Yeah.
Hmm. Yeah.
And even if you even if you don't have quick install on your computer,
there's a link to get you started.
You don't have to like figure anything out.
You print, download a thing, click a button and you play.
So I'm glad you have texture filtering off, as God intended.
Yeah. Oh, absolutely.
And I would recommend I would recommend if you know how to do it to do it
because, God, the blurry textures.
Why? Why do people play every time I watch someone playing?
Wait, what is it? What is it?
Try it? Does it like smooth out every texture and quake?
The pixels are like gigantic.
They're all 64 by 64 for a face.
Yeah, it rules.
So you want to you want to turn the the texture filtering will be on
by default with any OpenGL engine and turn it off.
Turn off the texture filtering. Oh, turn it off.
God, I. God, I hope I wasn't playing with it and not even probably work.
I don't think I did.
It was probably on. Yeah.
I like those. Every time someone plays Doom with those on,
I just like want to shoot cringe.
It's extremely cringy. It's super cringy.
Yeah, it feels kind of missing the point like this.
There's new Doom.
If you want smoother Doom, it's it's not going to play the old one.
It's going to be I want to doom.
I want to doom where the like the like 20 polygon enemies are rendered in,
you know, for 4K resolution.
They have to run at like at 124 frames per second.
Why? Yeah.
And you know, it's the mind of the there's a huge community of people
who who make like high res models and textures for Quake One.
And like, you know, more power to make whatever you want.
That's cool.
I would never ever in my life play with that.
I wanted to look like shit because that's what it looks like.
That's great. That's great. Yeah.
Is there a way it looks great?
It looks great to have like a super high
poly game with shitty textures.
Yeah, absolutely. And cool. Yeah.
I feel like that would look awkward, like a really smooth,
like a really smoothly rendered model with big, crunchy pixel textures on it.
Would like like a like a very crushed Photoshop face of an actor on the face.
If you look very bizarre, because you probably like
wouldn't be able to line up like your four textures or four pixels of an eyeball
onto the geometry of your photorealistic eye properly.
Yeah, it's doable.
I want to see it.
Go download, make human, get like a low poly Quake One model,
just slap it on there and see what happened.
Yeah, you know, I did see in in in Crash Four,
there's like a bunch of skins that you can have.
And one of them is like Crash from PlayStation One.
You can play the Crash Four game with a Crash One guy.
But it kind of it looks horrendous
because it's not the actual same model.
They make it look like it, but it maps on to like the new
like rig, the skeleton of the new characters or the animations for it.
But I think the worst thing about it is that the lighting
that, you know, cuss shadows that that that on that sort of low poly
like single color for like Crash Bandicoot
completely changes the way he looks.
You have to use and you can't change the the shadows.
No, that's so bad.
Yeah. So it looks like it's so as I was as I was importing my models
into Unreal Engine, like it defaults to like a PBR texture.
The show has like realistic lighting and stuff.
And it completely ruins the effect.
You have to make it unlit.
Pete, PBR photo based rendering.
It's like it like simulates how light interacts with materials
like in a game engine.
So all the stuff will like have like realistic reflections
and realistic shadows and all that garbage.
And I'm just like, no, turn it all off.
Well, who needs it?
Honestly, who does?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I agree.
Like you really don't need that much to make the game good.
It's honestly better if the graphics are worse, but they just, you know,
you can feel something when you look at it.
Yeah, like making it look more real isn't better.
I just played.
That's like better. I just was playing.
That's like how I feel that way about art in general.
Like if you can get across the same amount with less detail,
it's just better like most of the time, minimum conveyance is is ideal.
Yeah, I was just playing the version three, the beta version three
of Project Rutality, which is like a crazy high gore over the top mod
for the original doom.
It's so much more fun than the new doom games.
It's so good, though, the just like crazy amount of just like
catharsis they have to all the weapon effects and stuff,
because it's just like these little pixels just getting blown apart
and spattering pixely blood everywhere and like all the sound effects are
because like the visuals look like shit.
So they have to make the sound sound really good to sell
like how fucking powerful these weapons are.
And it's like the best.
It's so fucking I mean, it's really I hadn't heard of Project Rutality.
You know, there used to be Brutal Doom.
Yeah, I don't know.
This is a fork of that from by another guy.
OK, yeah, and more guns and more effects and crazy shit.
If it's not related to Brutal Doom, that's like really unfortunate naming.
Yeah, right.
No, he like forked it and like took it and like I guess I don't know why he
forked it because I haven't looked into the history of it.
I just know that it's a fork of that, but it's kind of the same idea.
But like even more ridiculous and like you can get like weapon upgrades
and like there's like three different kinds of BFG is just like an inventory
for days. It's like really fucking cool.
It sounds cool. Brutal Doom was sick as fuck.
Oh, it's so good.
It's like still my favorite shooter is like those kind of things.
It's like what's the difference between doom and you can explain it if you want.
Oh, so doom, the base doom game is extremely primitive, right?
Like you're you're essentially moving on a 2D plane, right?
And you can look only straightforward and you have some simple weapons
with Brutal Doom. What they did is allow you to first of all,
you could look all over the place.
The weapons are more complicated.
So you can you can do things like look down the sights of your shotgun, right?
And they have different weapons and just just generally improved
gameplay all over plus a whole new series of maps.
Yeah. Hmm. But isn't isn't the original?
I mean, the original doom is built around its simplistic gameplay, though, right?
Yeah. So you can revisit that the original maps with the improved gameplay
and also there's new maps. Yeah, because I mean, you can it works
with any map file from doom, but like obviously with like the increased
like weapon damage and stuff, you can get map packs that are made,
especially with this kind of refined gameplay in mind.
But like, I mean, you know what doom looks like.
Like this is the video I saw.
There was like, I got to play this. It's fucking nuts.
Hmm. I see. I see.
Speaking of games, I just I saw.
At you know, we've we've been to a Brony Con or two and at
and at previous Brony Cons, this I've I've I've met this guy,
this guy Tony Yotes and and he has been making this game.
He's been making a pony game for, I don't know, but several years now,
like since the T-Bap days, I think, and battle.
Yes, battle gem ponies.
And he just launched the Kickstarter for it.
And it's it's like, I honestly, after like, I've just kind of had this guy
as like a follow on Twitter for years and years every now and then.
I see a battle gem pony.
I'm like, huh, looking good, looking good.
And it's it's actually real.
They actually did the the Kickstarter.
I can't believe it.
But I thought it was cool that it's actually happening.
It seems like it's it's actually doing like pretty well.
I think it's up to like eight. Oh, man.
Something you can you can download a demo right now and play it.
I have I have not.
Yeah, I was just looking at Kickstarter, you know,
because the concern always the Kickstarter comes out.
And it's like, does he even have anything?
Is there even actually a game?
Is this just an idea after all this time?
I hope so. But yeah, no, it's real.
So he's got a demo.
Yeah, I I asked I asked him how how much it would take
to get to get Phantom Horn in the game.
And I think it's it's it's a little it's a lot.
You'd have to make like a whole sprites.
I don't think it's feasible.
It's just made me sad.
But. Oh, well, that's OK.
That's OK. I'll still I'll still buy it.
But still fucking got me by the balls.
I got to do it.
Oh, well.
Yeah, I don't know, fucking Battle Jam ponies.
That's I just I invested in it just because
I have known about it for so long.
And every every every once in a while,
I see it on the timeline and be like, hmm,
will this ever be a real game?
So I would think it was neat if it was.
And here it is. Cool, cool shit.
I don't know.
Games are coming back.
I guess there must be a there must be a
brony contingency that's still there.
Just like alive.
You made a fucking a pony,
a pony themed Pokemon like indie game.
Take my money.
There must still be a contingent because, you know, it's going.
Movies coming out like this month or next month.
Are we going to?
We got to do an episode.
We got to do. We got to do it.
I'm ready.
I'm I'll go see it in theaters.
I don't give a fuck about the Delta variant.
I, you know, I assumed it was, but maybe it's not.
I mean, the the the last pony movie came out in theaters.
Yeah, I feel like it probably will.
It says Netflix.
I don't know if it's coming out in theaters.
No, no.
That's just we'll all have to gather at Crack's house and watch it.
Yeah, come on down.
Yeah, you know what?
OK, I'll fly over.
Why not? I'm in.
Hell, I'm in.
Hey, so speaking of kick starters,
Tom, you were saying you got the the framework computer
and my immediate concern, right?
So I've seen so many kick starters for like, this is the new modular phone,
which is going to revolutionize phones.
And like, you'll be able to just upgrade it piece by piece.
And literally, none of them have ever materialized into a device.
Mm hmm.
This laptop looks better.
But like, what's sold what's sold to you?
Well,
it's not a kick starter, which is important.
First of all, they have pre-orders open.
The device exists like reviewers, like everyone in the tech
like reviewer sphere has already used the device, had hands on and like,
it works, it functions, it's been reviewed.
They've already shipped out two, I think, waves of them
and they're on like wave three of orders.
OK, so it's real, which is the first like big sticking point,
like it's out and exists.
I think the second thing that sold me is that all the components
in it are off the shelf.
There's no proprietary hardware except for the main motherboard,
because like you have to solder the CPU onto something.
But even that, they have all the schematics for the board available.
And unlike every other laptop,
you can actually take the main board out and use it outside of the laptop.
So if you, you know, you're done with the laptop,
you can like set it up as like a NAS or whatever,
because it'll run unconnected to the rest of the components.
And that also means like if the company tanks,
you can still replace things because all these components are off the shelf.
So like you can buy a battery from a third party, you can buy a new display
from a third party.
But that's like the great thing about it is literally the entire computer
is modular, which is like I've been bitching about it forever
that like it sucks at like these like really portable like ultrabooks and stuff.
They're all designed to be throwaway products, you know,
like everything soldered to the board and the excuse was like,
oh, you can't get a computer this thin and light unless you solder everything together.
And like we've all kind of like accepted that as being true.
So this this company framework is made up of like X people from like Facebook
and Apple, I think.
And they were just like, why don't we make a laptop that's like actually
decently designed, but all the ports can be swapped out
because it's just it's just four USB-C ports coming off the main board.
And you get, yeah, so you essentially got like tiny dongles.
Yeah. And then you just have dongles that just slot into the chassis itself.
Same, same.
Rigid, rigid, compact dongles.
Yeah, exactly.
You know, as we're all familiar with.
Stop your turning wheel.
And so even even the like the the schematics and stuff for those are available.
So other people can make their own kind of adapters for for the computer itself.
And I don't.
I mean, my laptop that I have right now is like more powerful than this thing.
So I technically don't need it, but I'm kind of just like putting my money
where my mouth is and being like, you know what, I've wanted something
like this to exist forever.
And if I can just do my little bit to like give them the momentum
they need in the beginning, maybe like next year or the year after they'll
release like a 15 inch laptop that has like a full fat, like, you know,
45 watt CPU and a dedicated graphics card, which is something I would actually buy.
And then that's fully modular.
So like if later down the road, it's like, you know, 1080p is nice,
but I could really use a QHD screen or a higher refresh rate.
Instead of having to buy a whole new computer, like with this one,
you can just take the magnetic lid off and just drop in a new panel
and seal it back up and like actually upgrade your notebook.
Like I would have my desktop, which has like half of the components
have been sitting in it for five years versus, you know, the motherboard
and CPU are new because I upgraded that recently and just like being able to do
that because like it sucks having to like throw out a perfectly good display,
perfectly good motherboard, perfectly good RAM because like one thing broke, you know.
So I just said, fuck it, it's a hundred bucks down.
I can still cancel it for a reason.
I decide I don't want to, but it's shipping in October.
And it's like, I don't know.
I just really believe in the idea and like it's not vaporware because like,
you know, Linus Tech Tips and a bunch of like reputable people
have had it in house and swear that it's actually good.
So fuck it. I'm going to give it a shot.
Yeah. Yeah. And I just, you know, I just hope that all the all the hardware
that's included and available is like supported in the Linux kernel.
But I don't know.
That would be my next concern.
I know you buy a laptop and it's like 50 50 chance,
whether the the wireless or the Bluetooth is going to be in the kernel.
From what I understand.
And again, I'm not a big Linux guy, despite me wanting to the Linux.
Like some people have tested with Linux and it does work.
And even the the fingerprint scanner on it works with Linux as well.
They made sure that that was supported.
Yeah, I've never seen one work.
I've never seen one works.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, it's pretty nuts.
So and then because like there are the compatibility,
like they're saying, like right now, you just have, you know,
the the 11th gen ultrabook main board.
But they're also going to make options going forward
that you can put both arm and risk V.
So season there as well.
So like, yeah, the the future sounds really interesting.
So if you could just like, oh, yeah,
I just want to drop an armboard in here for a little bit.
Like that'd be pretty fucking cool.
Yeah, that sounds sick.
You know, and and honestly, like I probably should support that.
But the truth is that I just have a Dell XPS 13 and it's six.
It's like good enough.
Yeah, you know, it's down down the road years from now.
It's like I would love there to be this option available.
That's that's exactly what I was thinking.
It's like I could still use my laptop for like three or four years.
But like my thought process was like, I want this to exist in three
to four years when I do need a new 15 year notebook.
So I'm going to like put my money where my mouth is because I have like
you want to dive into my fucking comment history on YouTube.
You can find me bitching about sealed ram and shit on laptop reviews
for like 10 years now.
So I'm like, well, I'd be a pretty big fucking hypocrite
if I didn't like throw down for this.
So, you know, and it's crazy that it's been so long
and this doesn't really exist yet because years ago when I was in college,
I had a 15 inch, I think alienware laptop.
And that was so close to like a full modular laptop.
And they just completely abandoned that that whole design practice.
Like with that laptop, you could take off one panel and expose
almost the entire main board.
Yeah, and it had a discrete video card that was slotted and.
Oh, my God, that's insane.
Right. It just doesn't exist anymore.
It just doesn't exist. What happened?
We were right there, you know, because money like it's so much more.
I think Apple leads the charge on a lot of this shit.
And they are money grubbing bastards.
Yeah, right.
Everyone wants the ultra slim aluminum case.
But like, here's the thing, the fucking the framework laptop
is thinner and lighter than like a MacBook Pro.
Yeah, but it's completely modular.
And it's just like, OK, so what's your excuse for sealing everything in?
It's like, oh, because Apple wants to charge like a thousand dollars for a pair.
So they'll just make you buy a new one.
Yeah, there's just no like this is a tiny 13 inch device
that has two sodium slots and everybody like everybody
who makes a 13 inch notebook, it's like it has to be soldered
or we can't get it to be slim.
It's like can't do it.
It's like these guys designed this look.
They designed this entire computer in less than a year.
So like, if you're Apple, you spend billions of dollars in R&D every year.
Like you clearly just choose not to.
So yeah, yeah, it's pretty fucking sick.
So I'm definitely I'm super interested in what the community is going to do with it.
Because like as much as like framework offers, I'm sure they're going to be like,
oh, dude, this fucking panel from China that you can order from AliExpress totally slots in here.
And like, there's going to be crazy shit like that's going to start popping up.
And that's that's really going to start taking on a life itself.
Yeah, well, because the reality of it, right, is that a lot of hardware
that's in laptops is standardized and it's just not a standard device
that's available to you as the consumer.
But like the the form factors are standardized.
The parts are interchangeable and it's just a matter of just you can't get to them.
But like with this one, like the bezel is magnetic and comes right off.
And then it's four screws and the display pops out.
It's like, oh, yeah, I can replace slash upgrade my display.
And like the motherboard, because like they don't have any touch options on the display,
but the motherboard supports touch.
So if you can find one that is compatible, that has a touchscreen,
you just drop it in and now you have a touchscreen.
And like it's it's super cool because like you can up because like they also have it.
So like you up you open up the the computer and all the components have QR codes.
So you can just scan the QR code.
It brings up all the documentation on how to replace it, how to upgrade it, what works,
what doesn't work with it.
So it's like and then I think like this is like such a little fucking nerd thing.
But like when they mentioned this in the minus tech video is like, oh,
that's so fucking cool.
So all the screws are color coded so you know which goes where.
And then there's a little tiny little extra bit of space at the top of the case.
And so instead of just leaving it empty, they put three replacement screws of each kind.
So you miss one.
There's some sitting right there to replace them with.
I'm just like, they thought of everything.
It's fucking brilliant.
So, yeah, I don't know.
It just seems like exactly the kind of like company philosophy that I've wanted
for a long time is like, well, I got to do it.
So I did it and it looks pretty dope.
Well, cool.
You should probably move on.
Dope as hell.
I agree with all of that.
Couldn't have said it better myself.
I sometimes use the computer.
There was like three people in the audience who appreciated that conversation.
Yeah.
And, you know, we do it for them.
I came on here for them.
There's three or four holdouts in the audience.
Like, when are they going to talk about the beveling for those three or four people?
Here's here's a link to the Linus Tech video that really broke it all down.
It's fucking really sick.
We are we are more than two hours in.
So I think maybe it's time to go to voicemails.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
Unfortunately, yes, we still get voicemails.
Do I even have the login info on my fucking browser?
It's been so long.
Oh, no, don't even worry about it.
I'll just put them.
I'll just put them right in the.
I'll put them right in the links.
Cracks here.
That's right.
So here in the end, I so I got to apologize.
I left 30 voicemails under various names.
Geez, just just in advance.
I'm sorry for all the voicemails you're about to hear.
It was all me.
I was I was I was looking at the voicemails yesterday
and I saw that there were less than usual.
And I was like, yes.
But then I check again today and the number has doubled up to like the normal amount.
So now we know where they came from.
It was all crack.
Yeah.
So we can skip them.
Like, yeah, I hope so.
You could just skip mine.
I left them all yesterday.
You could just skip.
They're all about the framework laptop.
So we just answer them all.
That's the first voicemail is actually like crack, like says the voicemails
at the same time as they they're played.
So we get like a like an echo.
Recite them, recite them in real time.
The first voicemail is actually an image.
So that's there it is.
Look at that.
I appreciate it.
Yeah, they've got me surrounded.
Is that you?
Yeah, I'm sure that's me.
Yeah, that's definitely me.
I think.
Yeah.
I.
All right.
It looks more like Munchy, but I don't know.
Yeah, I thought it was much initially too, but like much he doesn't hate Homestuck.
Well, I love Homestuck, so that doesn't work for either of us.
Well, no, OK, I was confused about this meme.
I guess the point of the meme is that the person behind the table is saying something crazy.
So if I'm saying I hate Homestuck,
that means I've gone crazy because I actually love Homestuck.
I don't get it.
I think it's a bad meme.
This is a weird meme.
Is it supposed to be any of us?
Maybe it's just some random guy.
God, I hope not.
You know, it's like it's like an ink plot test, right?
It says more about you, your perception of this.
Right.
That's where you think it is.
Yeah, true.
OK, the the wait.
Oh, no, I've got to hear it.
The next voicemail is called proper JoJo reading order.
Oh, it's sorry for my connection is slow.
I will have to upload these early three to one.
Oh, there it is. OK.
Proper JoJo reading order in three, two, one, go.
OK, so JoJo part one and two.
I can't start at that because I know what's going to happen.
I know there's an evil vampire.
I know there's a bunch of scary.
Skip this one, actually, because I don't have any opinions about JoJo.
JoJo part three is where they use.
Yeah, not about it either. OK.
All right. Thanks for the voicemail.
Sorry, I can't help you.
I can't can't help you with that one, buddy.
We're moving on. Good.
Oh, sorry. It's got to load.
Next one is called confusion.
Ah, discussed contempt.
Three, two, one, go.
All right. So recap.
Trixie works with Vizier.
Vizier is the producer for Dick's show.
And Dick is buddies or whatever with Ralph.
Ralph ruins Trixie's life by way of May.
So why does Trixie put up with being only two degrees of separation?
Because she's a simp.
She's a simp.
Does that make sense to anybody else?
Because why would she put up with this shit?
Dick is famous and has big money connections.
You put up with that shit, just like lose your wife to somebody
and then like be totally fine with being, you know, that that close
to a direct business relationship with them is sickening.
Yeah, you know, this voicemail are really, really hit on something.
I think we've all been missing.
I don't think Trixie has been acting in her best interest lately.
You don't say.
I just can't believe.
That's true. It's true.
Ethan Ralph is a terrible, heinous man who, in addition to all
his many other personal failings, personally,
yeah, cucked Trixie, the fiance cheated on Trixie
with this man, but she's fine with being friends with Dick Masterson,
who is buddies with Ralph because, well, I don't know why.
Just whatever the reason.
Yeah, it's true.
What a strange narrative being spawned over there.
I think it's dead now.
Next voicemail should have uploaded this sooner.
Next one is called, OK, Henlo Corgo, eight,
Ben's next PCPU lecture three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben, if you guys ever do a rad con again,
I have a great idea for your next lecture.
Are you ready for it?
OK, here it goes.
The hottest goss in the universe, volume two, PCP edition.
Huh? Huh?
You were just think about it.
Just think about it.
You're not the first person to suggest a PCP
lore or history lecture.
It's it's it's it's an idea.
It's an idea.
I feel like the problem with it on a conceptual level
is that the only people who would find it interesting
are people who are already clued into it.
Like, who's going to want to learn about this PCP show?
I mean, I didn't see I didn't see that as a problem
with the RFCK lecture, and I don't necessarily see that as a problem.
Yeah, but RFCK lectures is promoting like a fun discord MMO.
PCP lecture would be promoting instead of the history,
the nightmare that is the PCP.
Yeah. Yeah. Why would you ever want to promote?
Yeah.
The lower this is, the more successful it is, the potential of being.
I don't think it's a terrible idea.
I've part of it's disingenuous.
Part of me feels it's a little disingenuous to do something on yourself.
Like, if someone else feels you, actually, that'd be one thing.
But then they get it wrong.
I feel like I kind of see what you mean.
But but nobody else is going to do it.
Right. Nobody else is going to make a video.
No one in the right mind would do that.
Yeah, we have to be the change we want to see in the world, maybe.
OK, the next one is called it's called Be Better.
Three, two, one, go.
The truth is, Trixie hasn't said shit about Ben in months and months.
All that's left is Ben obsessively sticking to the same talking point
and cracking jokes to the applaud of a handful of people on Twitter.
Call anyone who thinks you're being a massive loser.
That should make the emptiness go away.
I mean, I don't care, dude, if you don't think it's funny,
if you don't think Trixie is funny, then, you know, that's that's OK.
You're you, I guess you just don't get.
I guess you just don't see the humor in the situation, which is fine.
Not everyone is cut out for the high level stuff.
OK, not everyone understands dramatic irony.
That's all right.
Next voicemail is called a theory on was on Shreddit.
Lull Keck Omega Lull Keck G three, two, one, go.
Hey, guys, guess what?
Did you know that that incel dude, a theory on was actually on that show
that you interviewed last episode?
Yeah, it's true.
I hope you guys don't believe in guilt by association.
You know, it's like to have shitty people on your show.
What? Also, but Christian and but Ben
states for making his garbage ass OC candidate.
You're really everything you fucking shit.
What the fuck is that guy OK?
He's not OK.
He seems to be mad.
Wow. OK, buddy.
Maybe the thing was a joke at the end.
Maybe. I didn't hear.
You know, let's just try to tell me this when he when he when he came close
to the mic and said I didn't know what he meant there.
Let's let's just assume it was it was a it was a goof.
It was a weirdly delivered comedy sting.
Yeah, I don't know who Ethereum is other than people were saying he's like
a racist incel who was I saw a clip shredded of some of his discord messages.
Very, very bad.
Yeah, he seems pretty bad.
I'd never heard of him before.
I don't know what else to say about it.
Next voicemail is fuck.
I forgot to fucking post it.
Next voice is called now you did.
It's what did I.
Oh, yeah, no, I did. Yeah.
OK, yeah, the one that's three.
You missed one. You're right.
You're right. OK.
The one that's five seconds is called Nate's new podcast in five seconds.
Three, two, one, go.
Am I so out of touch?
No, it's the children who are wrong is give you you listen to it.
Is that is that an accurate summary?
They talk about YouTube and in video games,
and I vaguely recall it being very
like old hat conversation topics that have been talked about on the PCP and before.
Nate really is really listening.
Nate really is very indignant sometimes that like video game is not like old video game.
So unfortunate.
Hopefully, hopefully he changes his mind, opens his eyes
and and comes and just quick comes to the modern day and plays and plays
and plays the quake mod of the slime factory quick.
Yeah, I think I think he could learn a lot
if he just goes down to crack slime factory and quake,
you can download on my website, courtesy dot net.
Everything you need to know about game design.
There's a new 10 seconds new game is old game.
It's amazing. Yeah.
And in fact, also, just a plug, if you download it from my website,
you can also get the the map file and the WAD,
which you can then open up in the editor in trench room.
And you can see how I made it and you can make your own level based on the same assets.
You can you can modify the level as as it exists.
You can tweak it. Oh, very nice.
Very cool.
OK, next voicemail is called Easy Breezy, Beautiful Tarbuck Transom.
Three, two, one, go.
You ever get into a pool that's too cold
so you hold perfectly still and you can tolerate it for a while
because you develop this aura around you of comfort.
But as soon as you move, it's too cold again.
Think about that.
But with air fucking, a fan isn't a total replacement for air conditioning.
But you can forgo having it run every five minutes
if you supplement it with a fan and you'll get the same effect for less money.
My fuckers never heard of windshield. God damn.
What? I feel like this is in response to nothing, but I agree.
My my air conditioner has a fan in it.
It runs on an automatic temperature sensor
that when it gets below a certain temperature, it turns on the air conditioner.
And when it gets above that, we're going to get below that.
It's just the same sensation of air moving,
air pressure changing across your skin is enough to make you feel cool.
I know. And I know that. Everyone knows that.
So I don't know. Is that controversial?
I don't know. I don't get it.
Big, big fan fan, big fan stand, tarbuck trance.
Next, the next voicemail is this one came through
some fucking vocaru secondary website.
This was uploaded via fast upload.
It is called snippet of Trixie singing at a music
show. It's taking a second.
It's taking a second to wait. No, I already uploaded.
There it is. OK, three, two, one, go.
It's that Trixie. Yes, I get it.
Yes, I can't even remember that she did a song, but I guess she did.
I mean, I I'm sure this is after I stopped watching.
Yeah, it's later on.
I would believe.
Well, she was like a sort of main character.
Equestria Girls 2 Rainbow Rocks.
Right. Oh, so this is the good one.
It's the good one.
Yeah, next voice.
There's like three more I found out recently.
I know there was a I knew there was at least one more.
And I assumed there were at least two.
But I think there's the one where they do like the fucking school
like athletics school Olympics.
And then it also ends in like demonic something or other.
They just don't have any good ideas for those things.
They did not.
And I mean, that's the first question girls.
It was never it was never a good idea to begin with.
So, yeah, like you can have a.
I stand by this the second one is kind of good.
The second one's kind of good.
The first one. That was as good as it was ever going to get.
They should have stopped there.
But they it's the best thing they could have done with what they had for sure.
I still find it to be boring.
Compared to real movies.
Well, of course, definitely.
We're sitting on a curve.
This isn't cinema.
This is this is where is my something else?
This is a toy commercial that's two hours long.
Next voicemail is called Big Chicken's Egg of Quote Penance.
Three, two, one, go.
When I made that last voicemail, it was before it was before
Kristi got arrested.
I was asking, I was asking to have her on the podcast,
but it was before she got arrested and then and then she got arrested.
And you said, oh, you said you can't get her out because she's arrested.
I'm sorry.
It's OK, Big Chicken.
Pog, Pog, Pog, Soy.
So I forgive you, Big Chicken.
Nobody could have seen it coming.
It sounds like what a chicken would sound like if it was a human.
Soy, Pog, Pog, Soy.
When you Pog too hard, that's when you Soy, that's that's the line.
Next one is called Dammit Gibb.
Three, two, one, go.
You have to stop fucking dying.
I'm trying to fucking die with it.
I mean, I had you considered just stop, stop.
Just just quit.
Just control Z dying.
Hmm.
But I like dying, though.
It's fun. I knew it.
I knew it. I knew it.
Are you saying that you were the reason you're dying?
Yeah, must be something.
Because if it was someone else, I would have an enemy to fight.
Next voicemail is is called
Ben St. More like been gamed by Nate's new podcast, Lamal.
Three, two, one, go.
Trixie's biggest problem that will come back again and again
to fuck up everything she does is and always will be that she is incredibly
intellectually lazy, complete and utter refusal to read up on a research.
Anything bursting onto a scene where summarizing a plot while throwing
in occasional nitpicks and shitty sketches was considered good criticism.
She had obvious appeal as someone who tried to talk about cultural context,
art history, motives, themes and the likes.
But like with everything she touched, be it neurotyping, music or politics,
she refused to read up on the most basic concepts and look further than what
immediately occurred to her, opting to try to reinvent the wheel, trying desperately
and failing to formulate theories that have been well established decades ago.
Bogey Pop Lamal threw her way or lens of wheat and internet addiction induced
brain rot, no wonder other essayists who came long after her run circles
around her in terms of writing, ability and analysis.
Hope those twist teller rap shows pay good.
Now gossip more about may please also wears, Tom, I miss my boy.
My boy, I agree.
Yo, I agree with everything that you just said.
Yes, that was a pretty, pretty good summation, pretty good take.
Yeah, was this a synced summary of the court issue that has always been so.
Yeah. OK, next one.
This one is a Nate head with rage.
It's a minute 30, three, two, just like a Nate had to fucking take a minute
30 to say what I'm sure they could say in 20 seconds.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, self-proclaimed Nate here.
No, because Nate is a genius and it's a shed.
Nate's a fucking gay boy.
Everyone knows is he's fucking true.
He cries in the enemy.
He cries in musicals and shit.
He's at least tries to be a human being.
He at least has a fucking soul.
And he's the only guy in his own relationship.
And you guys are fucking garbage friends who allow these fucking
whims and cowards on the voicemail to shit on his content
and she was even there to defend himself.
And you don't fucking live to now to defend your fucking friend
and your fucking brother and give the listen to the beginning
of the Virginia report test and see how he talks about you
and how he loves you and shit.
When he is not there, you fucking shit on his corner.
Say, I don't get it.
Of course, you don't fucking get it.
You're fucking stupid.
The fucking fun was of a human being.
The educational system they came was fucking sucked
because you're so fucking stupid when I talk about lifting weights
instead of just lift the fucking weight and not even move your arms and shit.
And when you told this to Nate, she just left.
Oh, yeah, it was.
He didn't even make fun of you.
But when he is not there, you guys shit on him.
And your comics fucking suck.
No one's going to fucking read that she is.
You allow Munchie to say the end one of the podcast when he was a minor
and you got a fucking moron.
Wow, damn.
Hold on.
Got us there.
Shit. Hope you go to hell before you die.
It's so. You go to hell before you die.
And I thought.
He at least ended it with a funny Mario reference.
He did end it with a funny, you go to hell before you die.
Wait, did he say he hopes we go to hell before we die?
I like the implication that like it would have been OK for Munchie
to say the N word in the podcast if if he were an adult.
Yeah, I hope you go to hell before you die. Wow.
OK, I mean, we're in America.
OK, what did he say?
Like the Virginia pod or the virginity podcast, Nate says.
OK, that was like three years ago.
That was like three years ago.
And like this guy is like you you you you you you let the voicemails
shit on Nate when he's not here to.
He's not here to defend himself because he isn't here.
He could fucking be here if he wanted to and he chooses not to be.
So like, why is that our fault?
Guy, my guy, you're you're you're you're misplacing the blame here.
I mean, we've said multiple times, we don't screen the voicemail.
So it's not like we're allowing anything.
It's just whatever shows up.
I'm not going to.
Has has anyone here actually like seriously been like fuck Nate?
I don't think so.
I mean, I mean, a few occasionally in voicemail.
Well, yeah.
No, no, no, I mean, if any of us been like, yeah, fuck Nate,
I don't think anyone's been like that in his time.
I think I'm pretty.
I think I'm I think I'm pretty generous, honestly.
Like, I yeah, I don't.
Like I didn't say I didn't watch his Michael because because like.
So I don't know.
I want him to make good videos and it's sort of a shame when that one was
so confusing and bad and lots of other people felt it was.
That's just talking about it.
The Michael video.
The the it's a new one.
See that time?
No, I don't know what you're talking about.
It's it's it's a new it's a new it's hard.
It's really hard to explain.
Actually, the the the basic thing is that it's a very long
beyond during video of multiple different topics about the video game
industry, which are at their core kind of basic, but they are elevated
into seeming as if it's a big smart thing.
And it just it was very confusing.
OK, I reject the idea that I was too dumb to figure it out.
Yeah, the this kind of I'm kind of annoyed.
I'm kind of annoyed at this guy is like, guys, Nate said he liked you
one time three years ago, and now you allow criticism of him on your show.
That's so unfair.
Yeah, I don't hate Nate or anything.
I don't know if you listen to the old episodes.
We like joke and dunked on each other all the time.
I mean, my God, Nate, Nate has basically
has basically bailed on two podcasts with you, give Nate doesn't come
on the PCP anymore, and he's basically stopped doing the the the the body cast.
So like if he whatever, if he wants to defend himself, he can come on the show
if he feels the need. Right.
I didn't even realize the I don't I don't did it end.
I didn't like officially end, but they haven't done it.
I never officially.
Months. It just I didn't know it was still
it wasn't going on anymore, because like obviously I don't watch it
because I haven't watched one piece on a spoiler for myself.
But it has it has been a while.
Well, he's been a while.
Sometimes like taken like, oh, sure, we haven't done an episode in a while.
We'll do like three chapters this time.
And it's just been one of those but extended over a longer period of time.
And to the point where people are like, oh, it's over.
I'm like, well, I never was intended to be over.
But I did ask him at one point and he said he was busy with with editing.
So I don't know. I guess I could ask him again.
Hmm.
Um, yeah, I don't know.
I really don't get where this voicemailer is coming from, but I don't know.
He could have just it really is like a longer form version of a thing
that you could have just said, fuck you.
And then that that would have been I do.
I do feel like it could have been half the length, right?
I think I'm I'm right on that.
Next next voicemail is called where was I?
Wait, OK, I'm sorry.
I uploaded the wrong one upload.
Well, OK, the one that's there right now, one thirteen is called Hugh Janus.
Three, two, one, go.
There is a non-zero percent chance
they may as getting gunned at this very moment, feeling Ethan's sweaty.
Harry Belly resting on her spine, grinding her vertebra together.
As he forces his unimpressive pecker down to try to get her trusty
as I like to call it.
Maybe he even has to stand on a foot still to reach her.
Anyways, did you ever notice that in all green screen scenes
in the nostalgia critics, the wall, no one is wearing shoes.
They're all in socks, sometimes even with colorful, funny designs on them.
That's.
No, why did you cut off?
I wanted to hear more.
Well, I guess that's because I don't want to get mud on the green screen.
Why would they have mud on their shoes?
Well, they probably just fill me in doors and they don't wear their shoes
in doors, something that simple.
And they just they didn't consider it.
They're just like, we're all just wearing socks.
That is really funny that they're all wearing socks all the time
because Doug was like, don't take your shoes off
before you step on the green screen floor. Absolutely.
Well, it's too big to fit in the washing machine.
You can't wash it. You guys got we got to be careful.
Fair enough.
But like then just crop the scene so you don't see the feet.
Right. Oh, my God.
Well, that was that was a treat.
Next voicemail is called Robo Sam Tokyo Robot Chef 321 Go.
I am Robo Sam.
Jack Knapp, the big man is your foreskin.
Where's your foreskin, Ben?
We still get voicemails.
You cut off your foreskin.
No, I mean, you know, man,
your foreskin is the secret ingredient to my soul.
I am creating that safe foreskin film.
The other ingredient is the sweat of your feet.
Is this the villain of Phantom's Revenge?
See, if we were going to do a PCP lecture,
it's this kind of stuff that'd be really interesting to try to integrate.
It's like, yeah, then we got to the weird voicemail arc and.
It never stopped.
I understand I understand where this guy is coming from.
He wants to make soup and I want to keep my anus, my taint sweat.
So, you know, clearly there's a there's a conflict of interest there.
He's a natural foil for me.
But it's just it's just going to have to be what it is, you know, conflicts.
The conflicts just keep on keep on mounting.
Next one is called
born born to mop three to one go.
This is Ben's weekly reminder to not watch.
It was about watching one piece.
It was about reading it.
Does anybody ask about watching one piece?
I would never watch one piece.
People do tell me to read one piece.
You must have meant not read one piece.
Well, wait, no, he's right.
I should not watch one piece.
So he's right, actually.
I should read it. Yeah. OK.
Well, that's fine, then that makes total sense.
Next voicemail is called.
Oh, I already put it there.
Re bad comments award show number one, three, two, one go.
Forgive me for not knowing the lore
because there was supposed to be a fucking lecture
about this shit that's just never coming out now.
But the PCP is originally the horseshoe crew, right?
And that's a Jesse thing.
Sort of the horseshoe drowning in horseshoe's channel.
So therefore, if the PCP had originally been
on a specific person's channel,
wouldn't it have been on the drowning in horseshoe?
It was not a group formed as Jesse is the Jesse being the leader.
It was just a cool name and we were all friends.
But the but the first horse cast was on Jesse's first horse cast was
yeah, Jesse and and Trixie.
And then I was there and then T-Bab was there.
Yeah, I don't I don't think there was ever any real chance
it was going to be housed on on that channel, though.
Next one is called making comics is hard three, two, one go.
Have you ever considered so that, you know,
making a comic doesn't take literally forever?
Tommy J is sending too many voicemails.
It has to be said.
There's three artists there.
You have Ben, the artist, give the artist and Tom, the artist.
So is it so insane to have one of you
write a comic and the other one draw it or one of you writes a comic
and two people split up drawing it?
I mean, I don't even care if the fucking art styles clash.
That would be what are you talking about?
Which panel was the give panel?
All right, I know was this all right.
That's which panel and panel.
You know, I don't it doesn't sound like a very bad idea to me to be completely.
Yeah, it'd be cool and it'd be funny.
I don't know, man.
I just I don't know.
The answer is because we don't want to. OK, we just don't want to.
I don't know. I got I got people.
I'm paying people with Radcon funds to do the dojin.
It's fine. Next voicemail is called I'm working on.
I got my own shit.
I want to get a fanish fan of revenge.
I want to spend I'm going to spend this fucking month drawing the PCP dojin.
I guess I guess drawing comics is really easy and I was wrong.
So, sir, for us and send the completed
you have one week next voicemail link us the completed comic.
You know, it's just like to bias in Animorphs.
By the way, check out my appearance on the Animorph in Time podcast, by the way.
But it's just like Animorph says, you know, just because you're a bird
and you're made to fly and flap your wings doesn't mean it's easy.
Doesn't mean it's not hard and exhausting to flap your wings and fly
unless you find a juicy thermal to ride around the sky. Right.
Comics is like 99 percent flapping your wings trying to keep yourself in the air.
And it's only really once you like finish the last panel
that you finally hit that thermal updraft until then.
It's just I think so.
It's it's all grinding until you get a publisher to
until you get Diamond Publishing to distribute you nationwide.
It's all flapping until then. It really is.
Next voicemail is called Starbucks Ransom three two one go.
Tarbuck, that doesn't sound very trans or handsome.
Get a life. Yeah.
Oh, transom. Sure.
I get it. Why? Why not?
Next voicemail is called
Bad Comet Awards Show two seventy two Shreddit three two one go.
You know something, Salaro.
See, I guess you could see I'm getting red right now, man,
because your live tweet asked comments about how bends of live
are annoying me to the point of facial discoloration, dude.
Next time you should explain what exactly your problem is, brother,
because your groveling attitude will be no favors.
So what you're going to do when procrastinemia runs wild over you?
That's a great comment. What are you talking about?
Tommy J. What are you on? That's that comment ruled.
First of all, these are all these are all time.
Tommy J. You send too many voicemails, dude.
I like I fucking we fucking been over this.
OK, fucking get a grip.
What if Tommy J. is just crack with putting on a voice?
Yeah, this is just yeah, that's all there you go.
OK, I love that this one threatens the other commenter
with defeat in the Royal Rumble.
Like that's the consequence for making a bad comment as it should be.
Second of all, OK, I don't want to single out Salaro, but two two weeks ago.
So Salaro does have this habit. Salaro will.
First of all, I love Salaro.
Salaro is very supportive on the Shekels for Heckels streams.
So I'm not trying to call them out, but they do make comments
where they will just be like, Ben, what you said about this was a lib take.
You had a lib take about this thing, and then sometimes they just won't elaborate.
And they did this two weeks ago.
This was when we were talking about gender stuff and how I said that like
I said that like, you know, maybe it maybe I should be a they
because like I don't because gender stuff, right?
I said that thing about like, maybe I should be a they maybe that would be the right thing to do.
And Salaro commented like, Ben, your take about gender was really live
and you should and you should, you know, rethink it.
And they didn't explain it at all.
And honestly, that one really kind of annoyed me
because I genuinely don't think I said anything that I should be embarrassed about.
And, yeah, fucking if you got a problem with what I said, tell me what it was.
I guess I was holding this in.
I was holding I've been holding this in for two weeks, that that one comment
just rubbed me the wrong way and it got under my skin.
Fuck, Tom and Jay, don't make so many voicemails.
Somebody else talk, I can't remember what was said.
So it doesn't matter.
I said, I said, I don't I said, I think gender is fake.
I said, I think gender is fake.
So maybe maybe they is the way to go, but also I don't want to do that because it's hard.
Yeah. Oh, I think I think it's the maybe the declaring gender to be fake
when clearly people do care about gendered expression.
So rather about all kinds of fake shit.
So it's like it's it's more correct to say I don't care about what my gender
expression is.
I don't see things as male or female.
I just do what I want and then that would be a non binary action.
Yeah, I mean, binary mode.
The trouble you get into is the same thing as saying, well, you know,
I hate all the racism.
And in fact, race isn't even real.
I don't believe in it.
You know, you go down that path and it's just that's true, though.
I don't. It is fake.
Race is also fake and socially constructed experience that people feel
because of the social construct is real.
And so I didn't say that it's not real.
No, I know. But that's that's probably where they're coming from.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Well, yeah, OK, whatever.
Just don't bully me. Come on, I'll kill you.
Just don't bully me and we won't have any more of these little problems.
Uh, next one is called
I don't feel like hooking up the good mic for this one.
Three, two, one, go.
They should make a magazine.
That's just pictures of poor people looking real sad.
And they can call it vanity unfair.
Yeah, yeah, the idea of a magazine
with just poor people in it was what made me laugh.
I don't know if that's appropriate.
That's the good shit.
That's what I'm here for.
Did I? Next one is called
Bad Comments Award Show two waifus three, two, one, go.
I use the term best girl by sky or sometimes best person
because I don't like the connotations of non-concentral ownership
that come along with the term waifu.
Osteria Leaf Green, you thought you had a fantastic moral wink
in the making with this comment, didn't you?
That you could look down on everyone from the top of the pile.
The one person educated enough to know that waifu was a misogynistic term.
But there's one problem, one little thing to slip you up.
You're wrong.
You got your little factoid backwards.
Kanai is the term with the connotations of ownership
and waifu was the modernized loan word that replaced it.
But you feel real smart now, huh?
I mean, I mean, waifu is still the same thing kind of.
I think it's kind of the same thing.
If you think that waifu is a term that connotes sexist ownership,
then I guess people talk about it in an ownership way.
It's like, oh, they're mine.
You can't have them, you know, like.
Well, I mean, when it's a fictional character that like, then like.
I know, it's it's it's innocent enough.
But like, if you're going to criticize it for being misogynistic,
I don't think that's like in real in real life.
Ideally, a person who is a wife is married is, you know,
doing that of their own volition, right?
So it's not, you know, we don't.
But if it's a fictional character, you have to declare it for them
because they don't have agency. They're they're fake.
They don't have they can't make the decision.
So I don't know, whatever.
I don't fucking care.
Next voicemail is called.
Wait, sorry, I lost track.
I lost track of the voicemails.
Good, I have to go from the top.
Listen to all of them.
Yes, it's bad.
Bad comic award show three, Steven Universe.
Three, two, one, go.
Yeah. Wait, OK.
I really didn't like you guys simplifying the characters.
Now I'm literally just rocks and over sexualizing them.
Rebecca's sugar put time and effort into each and every one of them.
And you just say, well, I love to go down with this fucking disgusting.
You know, you know, Miss Anna, it's just so precious the way you come down here
and get so upset, so upset about the mistreatment of fictional characters.
I just bring scary Internet guys.
Any more bad comic award show?
Yeah, I think so.
I think the bits.
I think the bit.
I mean, the bit relies on, I mean, first of all, the voice terrible.
The fact that they didn't stop the voice when they stopped reading the comment as well.
Their voice is just the voice they're making.
I just I just I just don't want these.
These are not like entertainingly bad comments.
These are just like asinine, irritating, pointless comments.
And I just don't want to hear this is just insulting and annoying to the listeners.
Yeah, I'm done with it.
Find nuggets of like really bad comments and have like a funny take.
Yeah, you have.
Yeah, it's like not every episode is going to have a fucking
jewel of a goofy bad comment.
It's just it's just not going to be universal.
The next voicemail, mercifully, is a Imgirlink.
To Yager's Anonymous here.
Why is Sarah's Hand there?
I don't know.
I don't think she is one.
And I don't know who that goth girl is on the right.
I would imagine that is a Toho, something or other.
But I don't know some sort of anime thing.
I like I like it.
But I got to be I'm not.
I don't think I'm getting.
I don't think I'm getting the intent behind this one.
I feel like I'm missing something.
But nevertheless, love your love your work.
Voice mail, voicemail, Imgir, art man.
Yes, next.
Can all the voicemails just be images?
They're so much quicker.
This is the last episode.
There was the the real this person did the really good,
you know, virgin voicemail versus Chad, you know, voicemail image poster.
And it's it's absolutely true.
It really is.
It's just next voicemail is called.
Sorry, I got it here.
Next voicemail is called Sorry, It's Bad.
Oh, great.
Wait, no.
Wait, no, sorry.
Yeah, no, sorry.
The next one is called Applejack.
This is called.
Sorry, It's Bad will come later.
Applejack three, two, one, go.
Howdy, bad horn.
It's me, Applejack.
Now that the dimension was just happened,
every pony lives in the same dimension.
Ain't that something I think me.
It really you twirl out in textured collab.
We should open a cider stand.
Oh, handle the apples.
You can do the art and graphics.
If this sounds like a darn tooting good idea to you, send me a message.
I love you, Applejack with a Twitter.
Get on it.
I Applejack is a Applejack is a is a dependable pony
who would not bail on a business that we started together.
So I think it's a sound requiring it's a serious offer.
It absolutely Applejack won't waste my time.
I'm down.
Let's fucking let's strike a deal.
Let's take out a mortgage together.
Oh, God, Slime and Punishment will never end.
It'll just be a whole new pony arc.
Phantom Phantom Horn gets married to Applejack.
Slime, Punishment, Applewog.
He he he brings he brings Applejack to New
Los Angeles City and she becomes like the she like rises to the ranks
and becomes like a mining tank, a tycoon, right?
I think she would start a.
I think she would start.
I think she would start a co-op.
She would start a mining co-op to resist the dominant dominating
capitalist power of like a do the farming.
What do you call it, the reaping and sowing stuff?
I know, I think that's I think that she if she were thrust into a new situation
and she had to make the bet, I think she would take up whatever industry was like.
No, maybe she would grow the apples.
I was thinking maybe she would just do what's more practical.
Yeah, no, she's naturally.
No, she's she could find a way to fashion apples out of Slime and sell those.
I'd be like acid candy apples dipped in Slime.
Dire dire apples.
We are they already grow dire apples in New Los Angeles.
Oh, well, perfect.
Major major cash crop.
Next voicemail is called a belated apology.
Three, two, one, go.
I realized that if you played that 20 second clip of Trixie singing,
you might get a copyright strike.
Well, I'm sorry.
Too late.
I just wanted to be funny.
Oh, would we get a copy right strike?
You know, Pony, probably.
It's definitely possible.
Possible.
Ellie is our, I don't know, fucking scramble the audio or whatever.
Or just pitch shift it, delete it and then add it back in, reverse it, reverse.
Cut it down to be like two seconds long.
At a noise gate that's extremely high.
Yeah, next voicemail.
And we're getting down to the end, by the way.
Oh, I think we've got I think we've got three left.
The next one is called Twilight.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Phantom Heart, it's me, Twilight Sparkle.
I've been a big fan of T that for years,
but I've never gotten the chance before to tell you base.
You're like my third favorite MLP creator, just behind KP and Dr.
Wolf, why'd you quit the fandom?
Don't you like our show?
Why you hate me?
I used to love you and now you hate me.
I'm never watching Tbap again.
No, please don't change that channel, Twilight.
Speaking of Dr.
Wolf, I just I don't know if anyone's keeping their finger on the pulse
because I certainly aren't.
But for some reason in my recommended news,
there was like an hour and forty five minute Dr.
Wolf video, like like with like an actual thumbnail,
like commissioned art or something.
And I had no idea what I was looking at.
And I was too afraid to look.
Oh, OK, Howard.
There is a nearly two hour Dr.
Wolf epic floating around on YouTube.
What is it? Is it I have to review something?
I don't know.
Hold on. I was too afraid to look.
I was on my phone on the web.
Zero, zero could be the latest Magnum Opus.
See if I can find it again.
This is I'm looking at his channel.
He's got a.
All of his latest videos are like two minutes long.
Are they shorts?
There's there's some karaoke recommended.
So it could have been old as fuck.
I don't even know now.
You're taking the wind out of my sails.
But I don't see anything like that in the last several months.
On his channel.
What what what could be old?
That would be that long.
Can we search?
I mean, you should have clicked it.
It's gone. I should have.
Now I'm upset.
There was a fucking.
You know, it's a fucking part of the dimensional merge.
Whatever it is from an alternate universe.
Was it was it the keepers of Discord full movie?
I don't know. I'll look for it.
If I can find it, I'll link it.
But it was the epilogue part one.
To this one, there needs to be there needs to be
an option to filter uploads by length.
I think we've reached that point of YouTube
where that'd be a valuable metric.
I agree.
I have never seen this before,
but I guess there's a full movie on his channel
and it's five years old.
And I guess he's been doing this for a while then.
Never mind.
I guess it's not news.
This TF2 analysis red versus blue, the movie.
Oh, that was not a movie.
Of course, Dr. Wolf has been doing this.
He's been doing this since the.
He's still doing gangbusters with numbers.
MLP generation five from three months ago, two hundred and fifty two K views.
The world still. Wow.
So yeah, he just he just uploads like reaction stuff to like a new G5 news.
And yeah, he's just I guess it just shows that there's there's still interest there,
which means we do we do an episode on the movie.
We'll get all those sick brownie views.
They're still out there.
I will never get over the fucking the last thing
that the staying power of the TF2 aspect
of the fucking analysis community.
You know, so I was re I was rewatching Sonichi one or two
and I wish I had I say it, but I wish I had emphasized it more.
Just how funny it is that Chris was at the panel for the TF2 thing,
which has Phantom Horn in it.
And then Phantom Horn is also the protagonist of Slime and Punishment,
which is the canon end of Sonichu now because Sonichu's over.
But Slime and Punishment's canon.
So Slime and Punishment is the canon ending.
I just so what a what a bizarre coincidence, I don't know.
It all, like I said, in the lecture, the threads of fate,
what a tangled web they weave.
I think the most interesting thing to take away from this is that,
for some reason, YouTube decided that a X year old video, apparently,
from a channel I've watched, maybe one video on my entire life
was somehow relevant to me two days ago.
I can't believe I mean, you weren't you weren't watching.
No, of course you weren't.
You weren't watching Dr. Wolf back in the day.
No.
I had my finger on the pulse of that shit.
I was when when the when the moment with Dr.
Wolf series started, I was like, I got to get it on.
And I did.
And it worked.
Well, I guess it shows what you know.
I've made a lot of mistakes in my life.
On the ground floor.
I did the first animation for the moment with Dr.
Wolf with with voice of reason, right?
The voice of the thing about that.
What what moment with Dr.
Wolf became is kind of awful.
But like what it started as like that video, I kind of like it
because it's sort of like self.
It's sort of like knowingly silly and like funny on purpose.
It's it's like a it's like written for comedy.
Yeah, it's like voice of reason, wrote it to be like
what if therapy, but I'm insane and you're the therapist.
Yeah, Wolf.
And Dr. Wolf was like, I am a therapist.
And then he ran with that.
And it's a perfectly good and and funny
like idea for like a skit about these characters.
But, you know, then it eventually becomes this accountant
fucking like genuinely like giving life advice to like
bronies who are like, Doctor,
I'm afraid of becoming irrelevant as I age.
And it's like, oh, God, fine.
Yeah, those are my thoughts on that.
You got one one.
I'm sorry, audience, that I dragged out the final voicemail
longer than it needed to be.
No, there's there's there's there's two more.
Actually, never mind.
I take you back. I owe you nothing.
Wait, OK.
This this is the one the one that's uploading now.
The one that ends in two, six is called.
This is sorry. It's bad.
OK, here we go. Three, three, two, one, go.
And then how is your conversation about?
Isabella Laureata, I think it is.
Who? How it's pronounced?
How was your conversation about that earlier?
And what? Yeah, just one thing.
Chris is going to get upstained.
Ha ha. Why? Thanks.
Who is Isabella Laureata?
Is that a G5 pony?
Oh, oh, wait.
I think that might be the girl who allegedly
like was was like convincing Chris to do the stuff.
I think that might be Chris is going to get.
First of all, it's it's Epstein.
And I don't know, probably not.
But like, I don't know, whatever. OK.
OK, the last one is called Help.
I was raised by Brownies. Three, two, one, go.
I was watching Lyra's song as a little nostalgia trip.
And like, I realized something.
I was watching T-Bap when I was like 11.
Is that horrifying? Is that like horrifying?
Yes. Like, is it we're going to know
that someone has grown up with your content?
Because I think it's horrifying. I'm scared.
Yeah, me too. I'm terrified. I'm scared.
I feel like we have a lot of taxi who piece of shit.
I hate you. Yeah, OK.
Well, yeah, a taxi is pretty sick.
People have been telling me in the in the voicemails to watch
a taxi for months now, and I just don't want to.
It just doesn't look interesting.
It's good. I don't know if it's like be your thing, but it is good.
It doesn't look like my thing.
I don't know why people think I like it.
I definitely didn't pick up any
like this is a Ben St.
thing vibe from it, but it's just a decent show
that I haven't finished going to fill in behind, but it's cool. Sure.
Yeah, it's horrifying.
I guess it's not that surprising
that some 11 year old who have been watching it's not pony content,
but it's still weird.
It is pretty weird because I remember I I've been so what they must be
like 17 now. Yeah, I don't like that.
I don't know how young, OK, the youngest one.
Well, I know one person who is, I mean, there must have been at least
a few really little kids, one person who watched me
or I'm now friends with has only just turned 18.
So that's that's that was wacky when I learned how old young they were.
I was like, what?
And it was like I was uploading.
I was uploading on YouTube thinking,
yeah, people are my age, right? Of course.
People are just my age.
There are no children here.
But of course, it's a pony show.
It's because it's because age sneaks up on you.
Like, because like back when we started using the internet, we were young.
And so like no one else younger than us could use it.
But that's not the truth. I said the word.
I said there's so many the fuck words and children were saying.
Sad. That's pretty funny, though.
Um, I mean, geez.
Well, we just we have to go back.
We just have to go back.
You, a viewer, voicemail, go back to being 11 and I'll go back to being
twenty seven or something.
And we can try again. All right.
This this this this run didn't work out so well, but we can try again, I think.
Shit, that's it. That's the last voicemail.
What a what a note to end on.
We're all old.
Well, we're terrible role models because we never were trying to be in the first place.
We let we let Munchie say the N word on on this podcast, even though he was a minor.
Yeah. And that's so I mean, I mean, it's I mean, it's funny to let
I mean, it's funny to that he said that in that way.
But he's also kind of right.
Like that was a thousand percent, actually.
Yeah. Oh, well, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Lesson learned.
Lesson zero.
That's it, everybody.
Thanks for watching.
Is that it? Are we are we at an end?
I would. Yeah, I'm I'm looking at Dr. Wolff.
Oh, well, that's how you know it's over then.
That's how you know there's no more.
OK, well, God, send a speak of voicemail to speakpipe.com slash
PZV voicemail. We really want to tell them to do that.
Should we really continue to incentivize that at the end of every episode?
But not that many. Don't send a lot.
One voicemail, an episode.
Probably one craft.
Probably one good voicemail instead of trying to make 10 terrible ones.
Yeah, absolutely.
Next, the patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
We have.
Elisar has finished editing.
You're not going to believe this.
Three bonus episodes are ready to release.
We have three of them in the can that will be out soon.
I know, I can't believe it.
That's so much content for only five dollars.
Only five dollars in the.
We don't have as much procrastinators.
No, hardly anything.
And I guess that's it.
Go watch Shaddox RFCK cartoon.
Love web.
Uh, are we done?
Yeah, good.
OK, bye.
Easy.net.
Do it.
Yes.
Play the Quake.
I mean, Quake.
Go play Quake.
Slime.
Quake. Bye.
Goodbye.
OK, that was great.
Great ending.