I'm supposed to be working right now, I'm supposed to be working right now, but I'm not working, I'm doing nothing, I didn't got the surgery, I tell my son, I have an asshole, I am so stupid, I gotta get one.
Doomer, we have you on YouTube for my music.
Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast, the only podcast on the internet.
This week it's me, it's Ben Saint, it's Gibbontake, it's Tom Oliver, and there's, I was
gonna say Digi, but I guess it's not, what's up?
There's no such thing as a Digi anymore, this Digi character has been put to rest.
I'm just gonna, this podcast I will be known as Trixie, 21st century Trixie old girl.
That was one of my favorite ponies, one of my favorite ponies too!
I guess it kind of sounds like Digi, it's got the same vowel arrangement, it's okay.
That was also part of why I figured that would work for this show, I was like, I'm not gonna
convince you all to stop using the double I sound when referring to me, but Digi, Trixie,
it's not that hard.
Plus it's a character you all know already, so you can just visualize Trixie in your mind.
It's easier to remember than Gray, I think, were you going by Gray for a little bit?
I was Gray for a bit, but that was always kind of meant to be a placeholder name, it
was like until I figure out what name I want, and then for a multitude of reasons I landed
on Beatrice, one of them being that one of its shortened versions is Trixie, so, yeah.
Yeah, this is not an internet handle, this is a real name changer.
Yes.
Yeah, okay.
Trixie is one of my now IRL nicknames also, which is nice, because a lot of this was spurred
because the other day I was doing Canton, and Victor kept calling me Digi, and I was
like, you're not allowed to call me Digi, and he was like, wait a minute, yeah.
Why does, oh, right.
Victor's never called me Digi, not even on the internet.
I was gonna say, wait a minute, Victor always called you Conrad at Radcon.
Right, exactly.
Okay, I get it.
So in my mind, I was like, well, you have to call me by my real name, that's how this
works.
So he wasn't calling you Gray, so he just didn't know what to call you, I guess.
I mean, I haven't used the name Gray for a while.
In my personal life, most of the people around I told them Beatrice is my name now, call
me B, Trixie, these are the ones that make sense, you know.
My friends have been calling me B, or Goldie, short for Golden Witch, because I'm also still
using the Golden Witch name.
That's how you change your Twitter handle.
But just Victor calling me Digi, I was like, well, you have to use my real name, goddammit.
He was like, well, Digi's been around longer, and I was like, well, that's a problem.
If you're still thinking about, if you still think of that name because it's been around
longer and not just because it's a brand, then I have to get rid of it, because I'm
not Digi.
Digi is a brand name, you know.
I've killed the brand.
This is so fucked.
I think at some point, Munchie thought it expected me to start calling him Anthony, and I can't
do it.
I don't like real names.
I like brands.
Well, you can pretend that Trixie is a brand name, it's just a My Little Pony character.
We're on a My Little Pony podcast.
I think we're moving towards a glorious future where brand names and real names collide and
you can change your real name as easy as you can change your brand name.
I always like calling people by their internet handle names, because that's the name someone
chose for themselves.
I mean, if you want to go-
I always thought that was cool.
If you want to go with Goldie, that's the most internet version of a name that I've-
I'm fine with Trixie.
I'm just saying that I cannot separate branding from reality.
They are one and the same to me.
I like that you can collect a bunch of names.
I have so many names.
I also associate my characters as names I could have by one or two.
It's like a demon.
You have all kinds of different names, but you have your true name that can banish you,
but you don't tell anyone that one, because then they can bind you to their will.
Or any fantasy character, like Khaleesi, when she gets up to 12 names by the end of Game
of Thrones.
Oh yeah.
The Golden Witch.
I just want to have that joke.
I want that list of titles.
I want people to-
The first of the-
Yeah.
I want people to be giving it to me, though.
I don't want to just be making up my own.
Stormborn, first of the Great Breaker of Tams, 100,000 Subscribers, um...
Wait, you'll weight plus 100K on you.
Every-
It's like every time-
And she gets a new name every time she goes from like, from like, from, from, from Mere
to-
The name will be official when you hit a million, and it's on the plaque.
That's how you know you're actually-
That's when you know you're really famous.
You get a new one for every platform.
The way I'm planning on selling this name change, uh, is by privatizing all of the content
on the Digi and Digi collective channels.
Bam!
Daaamn!
I'm gonna release-
Privateize.
Yeah, I'm gonna make a video called, you have three weeks, I have a video called, you have
three weeks to archive all of my content, and then it's just gonna be gone.
Whoa!
That's a pretty big one.
Yeah.
Well, that's some crazy shit.
Good, good thing, good thing, uh, good thing there's a list of all that that you may-
Well, I already know that some people who have like, I already know for a fact that it's
all archived up to at least last year, from last time my channel got taken down, so.
There will be people who have saved it all, probably will re-upload it.
I just don't want to be the one hosting it, basically.
But I'm gonna go back and like, recreate a bunch of the good stuff, you know.
Wait.
The HD remaster, the HD remasters coming.
I don't understand what you mean by that.
Project Wholesomeness, right?
No, do that again.
More like, more like if there's videos for that word.
Oh, like, like, Modal Soul Productions, like, uh, Action Adventure RPG, you're gonna like,
remaster-
You have to remaster Madame.
It's the best video you ever made.
How come you don't make Action Adventure RPG anymore?
This is what I followed for, and it's been like 12 years!
Unsubscribe it!
Unironically, I feel that way about myself.
There's a person inside me who feels exactly that way.
How dare you fucking abandon Adventure Action RPG?
All I ever wanted to do in life is play Action RPG's, so, like, shifting gears away from
It was definitely a huge mistake.
I did not want to spend all of my life, you know, analyzing anime.
So.
Agreed.
Sad.
Lol.
I said digi.
You know what I mean.
Yeah.
I didn't even know this.
I did.
Me either.
It's a weird process for all of us.
Yeah.
To get used to.
It's a gay world.
Yeah.
That is true.
Tom, you were like musing on Twitter about changing your name from Tom Oliver.
That's right.
I was thinking about that for a good while now.
That's so fucked up.
Yeah, I know.
I don't know if I'm going to do it.
It's so fucked up.
I don't know what I would even change it.
Do it.
Let's all do it at once.
You're all doing this to me.
I'll just abuse that you're all doing this to me.
Well, okay.
Ben, you're just jealous because you picked the perfect name from the start and have nowhere
to go.
Yeah, that's true.
You will never top Ben St. It's fucking incredible.
I am jealous of my own perfection.
It's true.
Thank you.
Oh, this is so nice.
Oh, well shit.
You flattered my name so now I can't complain anymore.
It rolls off the tongue really well.
It's good.
I know.
I don't know.
Maybe Tom should use the name Ben St. I think that would be a pretty good one.
I'm a little jealous of like, I was watching a, oh fuck, I was watching a video by The
Right Opinion.
It was about the Nikocado Avocado guy who I'd never heard of, but I was watching this
video just to have something to listen to, explaining like his drama or whatever.
And like the story of his drama within the mukbang community is like, it's like, he keeps
referring.
It's like every time he makes a video explaining like, explaining the latest tea or whatever,
his story is like, oh, you know, I have to publicly call out what, you know, and like
everyone has the stupidest names like everyone's called, I don't know, like, like, like, I
don't know, a fit, fit raccoon, fit raccoon buster, you know, 12, 18 or whatever.
I'm writing that one down.
That's a new candidate.
I'm referring to each other with deadly seriousness, like real people, but with these like, these
outlandish screen names.
And I'm like, my screen name is just a, is a regular human name.
I'm like, mmm, some, it's a little unfortunate that I'm not like, I don't know.
I have a good excuse for you, Ben, because.
Yeah.
Patreon.com slash Ben St. was a classic meme that's, that's for the ages.
It's rolls off the tongue, but subscribe star.com slash Ben St. doesn't roll off the
tongue the same way.
So if you ever need to open a subscribe star.
You can come up with a new name just for the purpose of a better and a second meme.
I don't know what I'd need to open a subscribe star for.
I mean, it's just Patreon again, right?
Pretty much.
But like, yeah.
I have some people who are like, I refuse to use Patreon.
Right.
Make a subscribe star.
And I'm like, okay, but I hate subscribe star.
It's really bad when you use it as a secondary thing and you're small because it's like,
hey, because I only have like three people who are just like, I refuse to use Patreon.
So I'm like, okay, I made a subscribe star.
And the subscribers are like, hey, we won't let you take any of the money until you have
at least five people.
And so I just had like, I'd like, yeah, I had like $400 just sitting there for like,
wait, that is a number of people.
That's really weird.
You need at least five subs before they'll take your month.
They'll let you take the money out.
What the hell?
Take the money from those less than five people.
It's really dumb.
So yeah, for like a year, I just couldn't take the money out until one of the people on
there was like, I'm just going to make two more accounts, give you a dollar, let you
withdraw it and then I'll move back over to Patreon.
I'm just like, okay.
At some point I would have just been like, like, just go to your Discord and just be
like, hey, somebody please make a subscribe.
I didn't realize for a while because like, not only does it do that, it won't automatically
charge the people on there.
If you have under five, so every month I'd be like, hey, people on subscribe star.
Just a reminder, it's that time of the month because it won't auto do it.
It says it's to prevent fraud.
I'm like, what are you fucking talking about?
It's so weird.
Yeah.
So unless you end mass, tell people to go there.
Just just laundering my money through subscribe star.
Right.
Subscribe star sucks if you're tiny.
That's unfortunate.
But onlyfans.com slash Ben St still sounds good.
Ooh, that's the power of right there.
That's the end goal.
That's the inevitable end goal and we all know it.
Wait, have I talked about only fans on here at all and how it's like the best?
I don't think so.
No.
Because what's great about only fans is you can just upload video to only fans of any
size and they don't have content ID.
So the negative side is they take 20% instead of 10%.
But other than that, they host your content and the way that the feed is on only fans
is just a Tumblr feed.
It looks exactly like Tumblr and it's like you can post images or videos or text.
You have those six options like Tumblr had.
It's just fascinating that it's a good social media site in a way that Patreon completely
failed at trying to be and also a great payment processing site because there's no content
ID, no content restrictions at all.
It's mostly for pornography and you can upload video to it.
There must be because they take such a large cut because I didn't like using only fans
for that one time.
I was making like punk eludes and that was funny.
But they take quite a lot and for doing drawings, I'd rather not spend so much time for such
a cut of my pay.
I probably wouldn't think it was worth it if not for the video uploading ability.
It sounds like if you can upload the stuff elsewhere, then it's probably better to do
that.
But for whatever reason, you can't just host it on YouTube or whatever and subscribe.
Sorry, it's a good alternative.
Only fans is still a better deal than a YouTube subscription.
It's also just a great way to release bonus content because on Patreon, you still have
to upload your bonus videos to some other site and then have an unlisted YouTube video
or something.
That's true.
That's annoying.
On only fans, you literally just upload bonus content.
Only the only fan subscribers can ever see it.
I think the goal for 2021 should be to reclaim only fans, take it away from the ethos and
make it for everyone.
Yeah, I completely agree and that's what they want.
There's nothing on the only fans website that in any way implicates its meant for ethos
or sex work.
It's just a payment site just like Patreon.
It just happened to originally be run with ethos.
The savior we wanted this whole time has been right there.
I will say it does have the one thing that it has that kind of facilitates parasociality
because it has like a built-in odd DM system, but people can also just give you straight
tips and donations like one-time tips and they will.
People who have already subscribed to you will just tip you money on individual posts.
It's pretty cool.
It's a great infrastructure.
I'm just saying.
That's pretty fascinating.
I had no idea.
I had no idea it was that well-built.
I don't know what I would put on it because I don't make any new.
Also Tom from MySpace told me to use it three years ago and I didn't understand what he
was trying to tell me to do.
Damn.
Like personally?
Yes.
Tom Anderson.
Remember when I talked about being DM'd by Tom from MySpace?
He was telling me that OnlyFans was like the most interesting alternative to Patreon,
but he was like, oh, it's mostly for nudes or eat.
I thought he was telling me that he was using it mostly for nudes, so I was very confused
why he was telling me this.
Why was Tom from Facebook DMing you?
Because of my videos about Patreon being not great.
I had made some videos about how I thought like he was like, oh, if you looked into the
alternatives, though, and I don't know if he has some kind of stake in OnlyFans or if
he was just investigating it at the time, but that was his suggestion to me.
That's what he's been working on this whole time since to follow MySpace.
He's like, I can just capture that ethod audience.
That and his big-ass Instagram.
Right.
But yeah.
How old is he now?
He must be old now.
He's in his 40s, I think.
Too old.
Yeah.
Come back to me again when he's 60, and he's a cool old guy right now.
He's just in that middle space where like, I don't care.
Yeah.
I agree.
Okay.
Well, that's good.
I was having a productive week, but then I started a world-ending Noida run, the ultimate
Noida run.
I am a god gamer of Noida.
Noida stands for...
It's finished for which.
You play as a hooded weirdo, and you do alchemy, and you create wands, and I have the best
wand now.
I do...
Okay.
When you're just playing the game, when you're an idiot, when you're one of your
rube, like I used to be, the game is like a progression from level to level, trying
to beat the final boss.
When you ascend to the next level, when you become a god gamer, Noida becomes a resource
management exploration game wherein you are collecting a lot of spells and creating a
layer somewhere.
I open steam, and it just shoves Noida directly in my face.
So there you go.
Holy fucking...
Didn't even have a new game?
There was just a strange coincidence.
It's just on sale, I think, right now.
Yeah.
It's 25% off.
Well, people should buy it.
I have not gone to the moon yet, but I went to hell yesterday.
I finally got to hell.
That was pretty difficult, but I managed it.
Had to use lava to blood to turn this lava sea underneath the final boss into blood and
dig down for a while to get to the boss.
Kind of like Terraria with better graphics, a really cool part of cool effects.
I went to a parallel world that was really hard.
I had to use sand, I had to use ground to sand to change the rock walls on the side
of the world to sand, and then I had to dig through them and create pockets of ambrosia
and use a teleport bolt to teleport from puddle to puddle of ambrosia so that the cursed rock
in between worlds wouldn't kill me, but I did it.
I've killed some more bosses, killed a bunch of bosses I've never even seen before.
I don't know.
I just want to gush about Noida, but I know most people haven't played it.
I really like the aesthetic of its title, its text.
Yeah, pixel art with the dithering.
It's good.
I have talked about Noida before, so I won't go on at length, but I will say that the dithering
is that way because the game is based on falling sand game-style particle physics.
I remember seeing previews for this game, now that I'm looking at it, and the aesthetics
of it and the monster design and the names of everything are based on Finnish mythology,
and it has an alchemy theme to it, which is pretty...
Okay, this is funny, this is fun.
Because I needed ambrosia to cross between worlds, because the parallel worlds are separated
by a huge rock wall, the center of which is cursed rock, and to get through it I was using
a spell called ground to sand, and firing a projectile and the projectile's path would
turn the ground to sand, then I had to dig through the sand, but the cursed rock would
hurt me, so I had to make dig holes and put ambrosia in it, so I had to get lots of ambrosia
in order to put pure ambrosia in these holes, so I went to the fungal caverns and I had to
dig a hole and I had to find... I didn't have any ambrosia, so I had to go and find puddles
of spilled ambrosia from potions that I had broken throughout the rest of the game, go
down there with my own bottle, scoop up as much as I could, go back to this hole that
I dug, throw in as much ambrosia as I could but along with all this other crap, and I
had to find materials that were denser than ambrosia, or lighter than ambrosia, to throw
in with it so that the ambrosia would sink to the bottom and the lighter fluids would
float to the top and then the lighter fluids would leak off the top, so I would be left
with pure ambrosia that I could then scoop up into a bottle and take to the wall between
worlds and put in these holes for me to traverse between them, and it was so cool and satisfying.
I was like, I figured out how to do that all by myself.
I feel like a real alchemist, doing chemistry.
Wow.
Brilliant.
Okay.
I can't visualize it, so I'm not impressed.
No.
In fact, you suck.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I apologize for doing all that.
Well, everyone just needs to play Noida so they can understand what I'm so excited
about here.
If you play Noida for like 100 hours like I have and then you're like, okay, I will
undertake the task of traversing to a parallel world, then you will come back and listen
to this podcast and you will appreciate, wow, the process Ben is describing sure is tedious,
but I can see how it would work and I wonder if I could do it myself and then you'll try
it and you'll die.
You'll die like I almost did because you'll fuck up going from puddle of ambrosia to puddle
of ambrosia and the curse will activate and you'll start to bleed slime because you took
the slime to blood perk and then all your slime will explode out of you and it'll get
all in your ambrosia puddles and then you can't touch the, and then you've got to use
your teleport bolt.
Oh God.
We've got to get back to the world before I die.
The game does sound pretty cool and is on sale for $15, but for only $9 I could get
the Bayonetta and Vanquish combo.
I don't even know what that, I don't even know what Vanquish is.
Vanquish is pretty fun.
Yeah, Bayonetta and Vanquish are both on the computer now after years of people wanting
it.
Wow, the personal computer.
Everything's coming out to fucking PC.
They just announced all of fucking Kingdom Hearts, which I don't care.
All I want is for any commenters, if you've played Noida and you appreciate, if you appreciate
all the, how tedious and difficult what I just described is, give me a, I don't know,
just say, then just say, just give me a gold star and chat in the comments please.
Thank you and goodbye.
Shout out to Daniel Desalt or at Lasership84 on Twitter who did the cover art of the Vanquish
and Bayonetta PC release for the US and it also is designing me a VTuber.
Oh my God.
Wait, so you're getting rid of old content and you're going to be a VTuber now?
I'm not going to exclusively be a VTuber.
Well, okay.
I will have a VTuber.
So you're going to, what are you going to do?
You're going to play your games?
I, you know, I just kind of figured having a VTuber would just be good for every conceivable
reason.
It is pretty cool.
I think VTuber, VTuber Trixie is going to be a great time to revive.
And powerful time.
A great and powerful time to revive Gamecube forever because I still get comments on IMGames.
Gamecube forever going to keep going.
I'm like, I don't know.
It's not my project.
Don't ask me.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Gamecube forever.
If there's any video gaming project I would continue.
That would be the problem.
That and Tales of Tales of, I still, I get asked about it all the time.
Tales of Tales of is one where like I kind of don't see myself finishing it unless more
of the fucking older games get translated because not all the ones that I wanted to review
have been, and like there's no effort that I could find at the time at least to finish
them up.
I was thinking of doing like series in that vein on Game Series.
I'd actually want to play, but I'm lazy and I haven't done it yet.
It was either going to be Discussing Disgaea or The Legacy of Legacy of Cain.
Those are two games, series I'd like to go through.
Well, I mean, you'd have to play like 300 hours of Disgaea.
I know.
That's what scares me because like I don't even know if I like the games.
I just look at the art and I'm like, the art looks pretty cool.
And that's all I know about them.
So do you like tactics games?
They're pretty fun.
I'm sure I'll have fun.
I just don't know.
Final Fantasy Tactics Advance.
Yeah, it was a great game.
Okay.
It's like, I would say like it's along the lines of that kind of going into battles.
Yeah.
I just don't know if I have, you know, like 5000 hours to actually do all that.
The biggest problem with the Disgaea games and a lot of the Niponichi games is that the,
there's like, you want there to be way more cut scene and story and there's not very much.
I don't know.
Maybe you'll feel different, Tom.
Are the guys who made Disgaea, right?
Correct.
Yes.
I really, really liked.
Oh, okay.
I must have missed the name, but I really, really liked Disgaea.
And then I think before Disgaea 2 was out, they had Lapusel Tactics was out and I thought
Lapusel Tactics was lame as hell.
That game is too fucking slow.
So that was, that was actually their first game for the PS2.
Yeah.
But I think it was released second in America or something like that.
It was.
I think it was off the success of Disgaea that they started releasing their other games.
I have all the old Niponichi games and fucking Lapusel is like the amount of time it takes
for every turn to happen is just like preposterous.
The game takes fucking forever and it's, it's unplayably slow in my opinion.
I don't care if the mechanics get interesting or whatever.
It just takes too much patience.
They fixed all that.
Have people seen, have I talked about the pictures of me cosplaying as Master Lammington from
Disgaea at Anime Boston in like 2006?
I've never seen this.
No, it sounds super mythical.
I'm not, I'm not going to find them, but anyone who has stalked my old Facebook is from,
or MySpace or whatever, we couldn't find, like they're on the internet.
I look like a fucking dweeb, but yeah, I have these huge wings that my mom helped me make.
Incredible.
And I, I, you know, Eleazar, I don't know, I'll try and, I'll try and find the picture
somewhere.
And if I find it, throw it up here, I guess, okay, okay, even though it's, it's embarrassing
and I got my stupid, my stupid long high school hair and I look all stupid and shit, but
that's okay.
That's right.
That's a photo next to it of, of Nate with the, of the Empire Hunter D hat, and it all
balance out.
He was, he was, he was dressed as a Vincent Valentine from Final Fantasy 7 at that Anime
Boston that year, so, well, I mean, his, I think his costume was a little less embarrassing
than mine just because it's a character people actually know.
I don't know.
But he had the claw and everything.
Okay.
I just wanted to bring, bring attention to that to embarrass myself.
Excellent.
I really wanted to love all those Nipponichi games because of A, I wanted to, I, when I
was younger, I really wanted to be good at tactics games because it would mean I was
smart and I was not smart, so I was bad at them.
So I owned a lot of Tagnus games and never got very far in any of them.
But like, other than that, like the characters looked really cool and like were aesthetically
interesting, but most of the cutscenes are just like goofy nonsense that kind of flits
by and it takes a long time for any kind of narrative to get involved.
And even then, like the, the, the characters don't take the situation there and seriously
at all.
Like it's constantly breaking the fourth wall.
It's, you know, it's, it's very slapstick in that way.
So like, it was hard for me to get invested enough to want to play the hundreds of hours
of the game because at the time I was playing RPGs because of the story.
Like I wanted to have cool, I wanted to see cool anime characters do fun things and have
a plot and this guy is like, it was for the tactics game.
It's like, this is not a story-based game.
They have such a cool aesthetic, they look and they feel so cool even though the story
is like very, very superficial and like very, doesn't really take itself seriously at all.
I wanted to, I, I, you know, they make those, uh, the printing games that are like a spin-off,
uh, which I always wanted to try, but like I didn't have the platform they were on and
like I heard reviews that were like, it's okay.
The reviews seem pretty mixed on those, but I never, I never tried them myself.
I had a friend who was into them, so they're fine.
If you like the Disgaea series, but like all of the Nippon Ichigames, just like the dialogue
can be so obnoxious.
It's always like, all the characters are loud.
They're all shouting at each other and salting each other and just kind of, uh, being terrible
trash humans.
Do you remember that video Jesse did about the witch in the Hundred Knight?
Yeah.
Um, yeah.
That, I mean, that summarizes all my thoughts on those games, really.
That was his first noddle review, wasn't it?
I think so.
I believe it was.
What a classic.
Mm.
Tragic.
Um, okay, well, uh, anecdotes, anecdotes.
What happened?
What's everyone up to?
No, no, no, no, I've just, I, I told you, I, I, I went, I told you, I went to hell and
I went to a parallel universe, uh, and I made Ambrosia.
I'm in hell right now.
I have to, I Comcast is my worst enemy right now.
I hate them.
They suck.
They're terrible.
Um, so I think the last time I was on the PCP, I was talking about how Plex is sick
and I'm just like building my Plex empire because it's, wait, I don't remember what
Plex is.
Wait, Tom, you have, you have Plex.
I do.
What is Plex?
Is that a?
Plex?
I don't think you have talked about it.
I don't.
Talk, talk, talk to us about it under the table and not in public, if you will.
What?
Why?
Is it like crack cocaine you have?
Yeah.
I'm, I'm doing hardcore drugs.
No, Plex is just like, Plex is an app you get on your computer and it takes all of your
torrents and shit and definitely legal downloads you have and it basically gives them like
a front end that looks kind of like Netflix, like populates it with like thumbnails and
metadata and all that shit.
Okay.
And then you can like share your library with people if you want and people can like
access your, you're basically all your like media downloads.
Okay, okay.
So wait, it's like, it's sort of like a, like a shell in which to like, like display or
like interface with torrents and stuff.
Yeah.
It's the convenience of torrents with the presentation of Netflix.
It's the, it's the, it's the, it's the windows to the torrents DOS.
Sure.
The most ideal time, the most ideal scenario I've been dreaming of building in my house
for years is to have a server computer that just is full of fucking all the video files
of all the stuff you want to watch and then you just have a Plex set up and from whatever
computer you access, it's literally like just going to Netflix and watching stuff off your
server.
Yeah.
That's kind of where we're at right now.
Cause I got like the smart TV and like the phone and like all that little plug in.
So like all the screens in my house that I access have access to my Plex server now.
That was like the, that was one of the hopes of what we were trying to do at the back in
Boston.
If only, if only Plex was as good back then as it is now, but it was like, it works great
and I love it.
And it's, it's awesome.
And so it was so awesome.
I told my, my real life friend, Devin, cause he has, he's like, I've been a media hoarder
for years and I was like, Hey, you should add your shit to my Plex so it can be super
powered.
Um, so he's like, all right.
So I bring my hard drive over to his place.
We're transferring everything over and he gets high and he didn't realize that he's
sitting on the cable for the hard drive and he knocks it over and it falls over.
And in the middle of like a, a like 12 hour transfer all day, we've just been hanging
out and like at like 10% left, the hard drive tips over and dies.
So all of my shit gone.
All of the shit he'd been transferring all day gone.
So everything gets destroyed.
I'm like, oh, oh, I feel my soul.
It hurts.
All those rare fucking 1080p Godzilla and Ultraman things that I'll take forever to find.
So my, my, my heart tribbles up into nothing and I'm a shell of a man.
And so in January, like this is like the beginning of the year.
So I'm like, I need to start rebuilding my empire from nothing again.
This is like the third time my hard drives have died.
So I start doing this.
I'm like, oh God, that was like terabytes of shit.
I'm like, okay, here we go.
So I start doing this.
I'm like, this is already a bad thing.
But I find out that in January, Comcast was like, hey, you now have a terabyte data cap.
Everybody has a terabyte data cap on their home internet.
There's no unlimited internet unless you pay $30 more a month now, one terabyte data cap.
So like January 7th data cap hit because I'm just downloading all of this shit.
I'm like, oh fuck.
And they're like, don't worry.
The first time you do it, we won't charge you.
But after this, it's another up to $50 a month for using more than a terabyte of data.
How are data caps real?
How is this a thing they're allowing?
Don't you love how Comcast is like, it's the middle of a pandemic.
Everybody's working from home.
Internet is essential.
This is the time for data caps.
So they've been testing it out, I guess in like 20 states the last couple years, but
like this month, or last month, January is when they're like nationwide, every customer
now has a one terabyte data cap and they're claiming this is to make things cheaper.
I'm like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, because if it's $50 more for unlimited data and I had
unlimited data last year, it's not cheaper.
Don't lie to me, you motherfucker.
So it is now, so this month, I'm like, all right, I got to cut back on my downloads.
I got to space this out a little bit.
It's only half way through the month.
We're already at 75% and that's with me not trying.
So I'm like, this is going to be a problem.
This is preposterous.
It's cheaper for them because like everybody is downloading stuff.
And yeah, and it's it's so bullshit because it's like you go look for there like unlimited
data plans, like you can only do it if like, if you can only do if you rent their like
expensive router as well.
So that's extra money.
It's like more money to get unlimited data by itself than it's getting limited data with
their fucking router because then they can use that to like also project out a network.
So their phone customers get access to Wi-Fi everywhere.
And I'm just like, this is the worst company of all time.
What I understand the American Internet systems is like, there's like five or something
small amount of companies that have like, like monopolies in certain areas.
They do.
Yeah, and they've they've they've like, gather together to decide who gets what it's not
even so much.
OK, it's not that they have monopolies as that there are only a few that are even
remotely decent.
It's like a cartel.
It's like they've carved up the country.
It's like, this is our fiefdom that we're going to be here and you're in it.
Like, because like my friend who lives in Ohio was like, why don't you just get like
spectrum spectrums and great for us.
I'm like, you think spectrums available here?
We only have two options.
Everyone only has two options.
Also, literally, everyone in New York's biggest complaint is spectrum.
Like it's fucking terrible.
It's just as bad as Comcast.
They're all bad.
Oh, yeah.
All equally bad.
And they don't compete with anybody.
There's no need to be good.
Right.
Like where I'm at, it's like I have cocks because that's the one that has good
internet. There are eight other options.
They're all like, you know, like 90s dial up level.
Right. The satellite internet.
That's bullshit.
That's what I'm trying to fix right now, but like they're still really bad.
Yeah, it's a nightmare.
And I'm just like, well, I mean, I guess I can't complain too hard
because I am doing definitely legal things, but still.
No, you can complain.
You can definitely complain.
It doesn't matter because like I'm just thinking like even if it doesn't
matter why you need a terabyte of data, here's the thing.
I had to reformat my computer, right?
So like I'm thinking like, what if I want to like download on my steam
case? I haven't reinstalled steam yet.
I'm like, I can't do that this month.
Like I just can't play my steam games this month because I'll blow the data cap
just trying to download like like do maternals like a hundred gigs.
It's like that's that's a tenth of my monthly internet usage right there.
It's like, are you fucking kidding me?
Shit, like, like if you like download an image, like enough images,
you'll run out of space.
Yeah, I mean, like streaming YouTube video and like 1440p, that's
like a couple gigs.
If you like watch like because I've been watching Critical Role.
That's like four hours an episode at 1080p and there's like 200 episodes.
I could probably blow through the data cap just watching Critical Role every day
like I've been doing.
So you can stream the yeah, everything counts as data.
So downloading is like anything that is just data usage, data usage.
Just using the internet.
So like, you know, my whole family watches a fuck ton of Netflix.
We don't have cable anymore.
So that's all data being used at 1080p constantly all day.
I'm thinking about how like for all of our jobs, we have to like send files
to people at, you know, filmed at professional quality.
Hopefully, you know, like big ass fucking 60 frame goddamn, you know,
your output, you're like four gig YouTube file.
You got to upload that's yeah, it's a nightmare.
It's the worst.
And of course, you know, my dad's been working from home for like the last
year and like he's like going like big dialing into like the fucking secure
like military encrypted internet thing.
So that's like data and shit constantly.
So it's just like we're fucked.
We're fucked.
It's too, there's too many people in this residence for a terrible amount.
They found a way to squeeze more money out of you and you can't do anything about it.
My little sister's been vinging all of Dragon Ball Z because she's never watched it.
You know how big Dragon Ball Z is.
She's watching it in 1080p.
There's no way this terabyte cap is going to work.
It's fucked up.
Yeah, it's really bad.
So and of course, since nobody here understands internet, except for me,
everyone's like when they get a message about the internet,
that it gets your fault, you're doing it, right?
And I'm like, it's not just me.
So yeah, it's the worst.
I do believe Comcast is like a regular winner of the worst, worst company
in America. Yeah, they are the legendary worst company in America
multiple years running.
And now I know why.
I mean, I bet there's stiff competition for that, too.
Well, the EA is usually the runner up.
There's three.
There's three internet providers in this area.
There's there's Comcast and then because we're in Massachusetts,
we also have Verizon Fios, which doesn't have data caps yet,
but I'm sure they will soon because like, why would they not?
And then there's Hughes net, which is satellite internet,
which is like one tenth of the speed has a monthly data cap of 50 gigs
and is twice the price.
So really competitive over there.
Bayes, we got to go back to the old pigeon sending messages.
Yeah. Isn't this like, isn't this what like the like
Copa and Pippa were about that like this stuff is like they're not allowed to do this?
That this is like a net neutrality thing.
Well, there's no net neutrality anymore.
That's been gone for a couple of years, but oh, really?
So like all of the yelling about soap and people,
it didn't actually change anything, unfortunately.
I mean, the first thing I did like back in 2016 was completely destroyed
net neutrality America, but net neutrality.
What I this is, this is what I think is probably going to happen.
This is why I was tweeting about it a couple of weeks ago.
My thought is that what they're going to do is like,
this is step one, because Comcast is like, all right,
we're going to have data caps everywhere.
Step two is going to be, hey, man,
data is getting pretty tight during COVID.
Huh? Well, we're going to be really beneficial to you
because we own NBC because we're Comcast, the new Peacock streaming service
because there's no net neutrality anymore.
That's not going to count towards your data cap.
So all you normies who are streaming Netflix and blowing through your data cap,
you should use ours to subscribe to our streaming service instead.
And you can use it free of charge because we won't count that torture monthly data.
So we can get your subscription money from Peacock as well.
Wink, wink, nudge, nudge.
So I expect that to happen in the next couple of months.
All right. If that's the case, what do they have on there?
What's the likelihood that that actually works for them?
You know, it probably will not work at all.
But like these companies do things that are completely stupid all of the time.
So of course, it's easy enough for them to just go
whoops and then correct course and, you know, just eat the money, fire a guy.
I mean, what are they going to do?
They're probably going to make money regardless.
Like they're going to be people who are going to need unlimited internet.
Well, you have no fucking choice.
Right. You're you're going like they're going to make less money,
which to them is akin to like losing a limb.
But, you know, it's not the same as actually losing a limb
because they can grow their limbs back. Yeah.
I think if that's a system like, well, yeah,
that's that it requires like a market that is competitive with itself.
Because like I was imagining if there's more than one choice,
then the other choices could say we won't have a data cap.
Now you can watch Netflix and because Netflix is so big,
that'll be a huge draw.
They'll get way more of the customers in the area.
But the way that it's that's carved up, it's like not possible
to have a good choice.
So people are fucked no matter what.
It's not it's not like because like the most efficient analog,
I think, in terms of like the U.S. is like cell phone providers,
like the big four cell phone providers, there's only three now,
actually, because fucking team mobile bought Sprint.
But like there's three of them, which is not great,
but they all operate everywhere.
So like they're kind of like forced to not be completely scumbags
that they all have to have feature parity with each other,
otherwise they'll get BTF owed.
But that's not how it works for home internet.
So it was only a matter of time before it all devolves into the garbage
I'm dealing with right now, and it sucks and it's gay and I hate it and die.
That's my story.
That's that's my tale of woe.
That's give and take.
I found the Adventures of Ultraman on VHS rip again from 1981, though.
Woo, that was a hard time to find again.
I love media.
That's that's the funniest fucking thing,
because like it's like this like dub of like this like old 1980s animated
Ultraman cartoon that came out and they for some reason like America
back in like the mid eighties, they took it, they made it a movie,
redubbed everything, but the main villain is called Barak, the Star Lord.
And I still find that funny.
Wait, that's great.
It's a 10 out of 10.
It's worth watching just for that.
I'm looking up.
It's also it's also the first project by the student that eventually
would be Sunrise, who went on the anime Gundam.
Oh, how do you spell Barak?
That's B A R A C K in that, I believe, but it's dubbed.
So I've never seen it spelt out.
So I've always just assumed that's how it was spelled as an Obama.
Yeah, I cannot find it on Google.
This is like you can see the whole movie on YouTube.
That's where I found it.
Couldn't find a torn again, but someone just uploaded it to YouTube
like three months ago, knowing that I would need it.
What a beautiful soul.
Yeah, I searched Barak, the Star Lord, Ultraman, and I find your tweet.
I find a tweet.
A tweet. Well, I find a tweet from you from May 26, 2019.
Yeah, because that was the first time I was looking because I was looking for it
initially. That was like the first time I found it, because I used to rent
this on VHS back in Blockbuster all the time.
And I wanted to watch it in 2019.
I finally found it after like doing this huge, big tweet thread of like
desperately looking everywhere for this fucking movie.
I could only find it in German for a while.
And it was really pissing me off.
Based. I got to do a PCP lecture on the Adventures of Ultraman,
because clearly I'm the only person in the world who knows about it.
I mean, yeah, perfect, perfect.
Radcon, Radcon 5 win.
We're doing it.
We're coming up on a year of Radcon 4, the year anniversary.
We're coming up on a year.
It's getting that time again, boys.
It's March, end of March or something.
March 16th, I think, was the end of Radcon 4.
It really feels like that.
That's like the last thing of note I've done.
So like everything between.
So sorry.
It's been like a year of just nothing and it's.
I've definitely, we definitely, well, I don't know about,
I don't know about all you, I don't know about you people,
but I definitely died at Radcon 4.
And the rest of everything has just been me in the after life.
Being tormented and purgatory.
Absolutely.
Abney, we both died in a little way.
I know, I mean, we literally like the plane crash
and I one day I will remember, but, you know, as the moment.
At the moment, you're like the ironic punishment to take effect.
All that's happening in your head is just like a simulation
of what could happen in the future.
And then you'll realize that you died back then
and none of this actually happened. Exactly.
I'm pretty sure that the Brony lecture
is the last thing that I actually did.
Like that was, I think that was the last thing Digi ever did.
And then did you actually died there?
And what you've seen has been like a like an aftershock,
like like ghosts, like a force ghost of Digi since then.
Yeah, and it's finally dissolved into nothingness.
That makes a lot of sense to me.
I've got to say of Boyd Chasers and Boyd Gazers
has been a little hard to understand.
And I haven't I haven't really made an attempt to try and understand.
Hard to understand exactly.
I think it was just the the documentary thing was very long.
And it was just a road trip blog.
It was a road trip blog.
And I was like, OK, I didn't watch all of it.
I watched a bit of it.
And then the podcast, there was something about a banana.
I was like, OK, this is clearly like very silly on the surface.
I don't know whether I'm interested.
And I just sort of stopped paying attention to what was.
Well, you know, a good way to find out is to fucking watch it, given.
That's right.
I mean, it's just I mean, it's just it's just it's just vlogs
and it's vlogs and podcasts and stuff.
You know, yeah, well, I mean, it's pretty self-explanatory.
The Void Games is a variety show is how I would describe it more so.
It's because the concede is that it could be thought of as a podcast
because it's got like call ins and it's, you know, of discussions and stuff.
But like it's meant to be watched.
It's highly edited and it's got lots of different segments,
so it's like a cooking segment in each episode.
There's all kinds of shit going on.
So, yeah, it's a variety hour meant to feel like one of those
like Japanese morning shows or something.
OK, I'm not familiar with Japanese morning shows, but I believe you.
I just felt like I should mention that even though like I could easily
have given it a chance and I didn't.
And that's I could.
Because I see I see that opinion a lot and I'm like, yeah, you know,
I feel I feel the the I don't get it sort of feeling.
And the obvious solution is to watch the thing that is there.
I I I don't understand.
I don't really understand not getting it.
I understand. I understand.
It's easy to not get something that you haven't watched or if it's not
or if it's not we subscribe for I understand that.
But I don't understand not getting it like it is what it is.
I just wasn't sure what the direction of the channel was.
But I don't know who cares.
Why would that matter?
And how would you figure it out other than by watching the content?
Like I'm playing devil's advocate. OK.
I'm just. Are you sometimes clear that clear pitch.
You know, like this is this is what you get.
I have I have seen I have seen people say.
Yeah, but like I guess I guess what it is.
It's what it is.
Well, the funny thing about that is what was ever what was ever the
direction of the channel?
Well, no, no, it wasn't like the direction of the channel was
like difficult to understand.
I think it's just like I'm so used to Digi being so open and so long
form about discussing the nature of the channel.
And I was really into befriending the Internet and then that stopped.
And I was like, oh, what's all this weird new stuff?
They're doing weed in the car.
That's interesting, I guess.
A watch. It's too visual.
I wanted a podcast.
If you if you really want if you really want what I think you want,
the problem is you can't have over and listen.
No, go to go to Voidchaser's episode one, skip to the last 17 minutes,
which is just me pacing around vlogging, explaining the point of the
previous two and a half hours, then watch the two and a half hours
that lead up to it.
Then it'll make sense.
Thank you.
As for as for Voidgazer, skip to the part in episode two,
where I'm sitting on a bench and I spend about 10 minutes explaining
that show in that episode.
So it'll all make sense after that.
All right.
I think.
Pro strats would be a block.
Well, the thing is that dark souls of well, what drives me insane is that
throughout throughout my whole career, every time I make a shift,
it's always met with people saying, like, I don't get it.
Like, what's going on?
And I usually have made an update video that has like 100 views
because no one watches.
I always watch those.
They're fucking boring.
Like I do too.
So like I was always confused why people wouldn't.
But like, like I would release my next video, which is in the new style
and like every comment is, what's this about?
And it's like, well, I just explained it last time.
So at some point, I just gave up on ever doing that again.
I definitely know the feeling.
Of like giving up, explaining.
Well, and the worst is like, well, what am I going to put it like at the start
of the video that is supposed to just stand on its own?
Because then when you come back to this video in a year, it's like, well,
now there's this fucking intro that is completely irrelevant.
You know, like it only was relevant to the moment that the video came out.
Like people, it's the weird thing about YouTube is that people have a tendency
to think about it like video hits my sub feed.
I watch it. It's about today.
But like actually these videos stick around forever and I get most of my views
through people watching my old shit.
Like so, you know, I consider them all legacy content in that way.
And like to to have that, you know, that legacy start with something
that was totally incidental to that moment.
I don't know. It's not the worst, but it's annoying, you know.
Yeah.
I will go. Especially if it's long wind.
I will go check those.
So it was like the last 17 minutes of the podcast, do you think?
The void chasers, the the blog documentary, the last 17 minutes is me
pacing around like decompressing everything that happened throughout the video.
Yeah. OK.
I think earlier, you you were also asking me what I've been doing the past week.
Yeah, I have a well, I've been there's the secret project
that I've been working on on the weekend.
So you can learn about on the money to spend this podcast.
I have also been working on my secret project.
Secret project, secret project.
I also do that. The thing.
It's secret, not a different thing.
Shut up. I'm saying things.
It's secret for managing hypereasons,
not because I have been coy or anything.
But I want it to be.
More robustly completed to a point where it's like
now it's a good time to mention it.
So stay tuned.
So that's most of my bulk of my weekday stuff.
But on the weekend
or rather just every night, I've been getting into Buffy, the vampire slayer
and it's an incredibly good show.
Like I in my head in the back of my head,
aside from the times when Jesse said it was a really good show,
before that, I just assumed it was like, oh, it's a Saturday morning cartoon
Esk TV, like Disney Channel, Sabrina, the Teenage Witch kind of sort of thing.
Not that it was like it's like a series.
It's kind of like a drama, right?
It's it's a drama. It's a teen drama.
It's like it's more to closer to an HBO thing
than it is to a Disney Channel thing for sure.
And there's a lot of really good writing, good comedy, great acting,
very, very cheesy choreography.
But I kind of love it and and makeup and effects and stuff.
It's really quite fucking good.
And I'm really into it. We're on season two right now.
I'm pretty sure that's like so cool.
Jenny Nicholson said that Vampire Diaries is better than Buffy.
So they just write in their diary, like I'm still alive, I guess.
But it's I mean, the dark because I can't go out in the summertime.
That sucks.
It's been a thousand and one days since I've seen Sunlight.
That's all the vampire diaries they would write.
That's the only thing they would write in those diaries of theirs.
I've never seen Buffy.
A bunch of fucking nerds.
A bunch of a bunch of stupid band chicks.
They had a crush on an high school like that.
Fuck that show.
Buffy's cool.
Xander and Willow are like the comic relief sidekick
normal school, high school friends characters.
And Xander is really funny.
He's like the soccer from Avatar Last Airbender of the group.
And Willow is
is really funny as well.
I can't think of it like a comparison, like a
like another character from another thing that's popular.
She's the Dark Souls of the group.
She's the Dark Souls of the group because she has the best comedy
liners, the best like dry humor.
No, I guess no dry humor.
I don't know how what I'm fucking saying.
I'm not like a reviewer or anything.
I'm just like a Buffy is cool.
That's all you need to know.
Well, that makes no one.
No thoughts had empty.
I mean, it's it's cool to watch just because
it's nineties and so many things from that era
are so much more antiquated than they were 10 years ago.
Is there witchcraft in Buffy the Vampire Slayer?
Oh, there's tons of things.
It's it's mostly for the most part.
Yeah, a monster of the week, and it's not always a vampire.
So they could like say any weird occulty sort of thing.
Like does Buffy herself have like powers or any kind of occult shit going on?
Or is she just like a regular person who fights?
She's the Slayer, which means that every generation,
there's a Slayer who is a female and she kills vampires.
And then there's like the Watcher or the something.
And he's like the informant for the Slayer.
And he's like the librarian of the school she's going to.
And she just punches and kicks and has a stake.
She's basically just martial arts.
But she's friends with like witches and demons and stuff, right?
She's there's one friendly vampire called Angel
who falls in love with her because he's fucking stupid.
He does like a there's this there's also a show called Angel, right?
Does he have a spin off show? I guess he does.
Yeah, I haven't seen much other than the first few things of Buffy.
I did I did remember seeing a YouTube video about how the
the HD remaster of Buffy that's put on Netflix is like it's cropped.
It's like zoomed in and cropped to the detriment of the show.
And there's a lot of effects like the remaster shows more than it's supposed to show.
And you can like see the set.
No, no, no, it's like that.
I don't know about maybe that happens.
But from what I can tell, it seems to have been zoomed in from four three
to the 1080p aspect ratio.
So the top and the bottom are cut off a little bit,
which doesn't matter most of the time, but sometimes it's pretty weird where
like a character is blocked to be like just their head is visible at the bottom
of the screen and the person that they're talking to is like standing up next to them.
And their head is at the top of the screen and slightly cut off
and it just looks awkward, but only sometimes.
I hate that shit.
They did the same thing with the Simpsons, too.
They like re-released it with like just bad, bad cropping that like ruins jokes sometimes.
They're like the wrong aspect ratio.
It's so annoying because of normies we'll never know.
Unless you're like a nerd that watches YouTube videos that complain about media,
you'd never know that like, oh, yeah, this is like if you're watching
Simpsons for the first time and you're just some guy who's like,
you know, you're a kid, you're like 18 or whatever.
And you're like, hmm, Simpsons is like a classic show that I've never seen.
I guess I'll just let's binge it all and then you watch like this fucked up version
that's like some some of it is ruined.
It's sad. It's a sad thought.
I don't like it.
I want I want to get to the part in Buffy where the guy says,
I'm drowning in footwear.
I've always wondered, I think that's literally the last episode.
Yeah, well, I've I've also heard there's a great show.
So I don't feel like rushing to get to there.
Yeah. I'm enjoying the ride.
It's very good, like very good.
Like like so good that I would even recommend it.
Whoa. No, that's crazy.
Even in the HD, like cropped version, it's it's mostly perfect.
I'm going to watch it.
I'm going to want I want to have things to talk about my friends
of the procrastinator's body.
My pain is immeasurable.
I literally when Gabe was starting to talk about this, I'm like, oh, sick.
I'm going to go down.
I can't.
And now I now I hate Comcast.
You know, I was ready to go out to my flex.
Immeasurable, legally ruined, and dude, let me check.
Is there a fucking DVD box set up?
I'm sure there is.
But but I'm not going to be some fucking disgusting physical media.
No, it's great.
The leader is so cool.
Because I'm going to buy me.
I'm going to buy the official 1080p blu-ray releases of
Ultraman, Ultra Seven, Ultraman Taro in steel boxes.
That shit's pretty fucking cool and my speed.
But like, Buffy, boy, these episodes are 45 minutes long.
They're quite long and it's it's quite a big thing.
Oh, look, look, look, Buffy season, Buffy complete season one to seven
20th anniversary edition DVD 2017 for like 43 pounds.
That's not that much.
It's I mean, it's not terrible.
Seven seasons.
Oh, I could just wait till next month and then download it.
Dude, VHS.
I watch first if you like buying are all on a daily motion.
I mean, but it's still I'm still down.
I'm still using data.
Oh, shit.
It doesn't matter.
I forgot you can't stream either.
That's fucked, dude.
Yeah, it's bullshit.
They should at least get kind of data cap you have on your phone.
Nothing.
It's literally more efficient to watch things on my phone now
than it is to use my devices.
Tether your phone.
You only have two gigs of tethering per month.
I can only watch it on the phone now.
It's a crime against humanity.
Well, you know, it's from the 90s.
It'll look fine.
I guess I got to get I got to get like one of those like fucking
Game Boy things where you snap it on there.
What about you use the other phone to HDMI like converters?
Can you I mean, I could like cast things, I guess,
with like a Chromecast or something.
But like now I'm living like a fucking caveman.
This is unacceptable cast through Plex, I'm sure.
Maybe God, I hate it.
I hate it.
This is where you're in.
This is just where you're at.
There's no other option.
Yeah, you've got to.
You've got to get into like the black market,
like physical media circuit that used to exist.
Yeah, yeah, it's going to come back.
You've got to go to start.
I'm going to have to convert all this amazing place.
You can go actually called the Philippines,
where you can legally purchase physical versions of literally
everything that exists for very, very cheap.
And your American dollar is worth way the fuck more there.
Can you even go to a different country now?
Is that possible?
I think it might be.
I don't know.
I don't know about the Philippines.
I don't I don't think America is like I don't think America
has like travel restrictions.
I guess not.
I think I know like maybe it could be there.
People are restricted travel from America.
No, no, no, here's what they do.
You're allowed to get on the plane.
You're allowed to buy the ticket.
But then as soon as you're in the plane, it flies off.
They shoot it down.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, because that way they still make their money.
That makes sense.
They can't but they can't cancel the plane
because that would just cost them too much in red tape.
It's cheaper to just keep it going.
Well, unironically, though, if you really did,
like this is not even a bad way to amass a collection
like I'm describing, because while it might be like
probably a thousand dollars for the plane ticket to the Philippines,
you could stay there for a month on less than a thousand dollars
and buy a media collection like with like like for the thousand
dollars that you would spend there.
What I'm trying to say is I once went to the Philippines with two grand
and I bought a lot of figures.
Most of my collection I got there.
So God, yeah, it was very cheap to live.
And it was very cheap to come back with a whole lot of shit.
So, you know, unironically, if you're an adventurous person,
just fly out to a third world country,
buy a whole bunch of contraband and mail it to yourself.
Incredible.
Well, if I get that desperate, maybe I will.
Don't spend the extra fifty dollars a month on unlimited Internet.
Spend two thousand dollars going to the Philippines.
I got the you might go to spend money to make money.
The conversion rate from USD to the Filipino, whatever is good.
The Filipino.
But if you convert those US dollars to Bitcoin, then you'll have you.
That's even better.
That's true.
I've made like a grand in Bitcoin in the last month.
Damn.
Just from everybody else in the world.
I fucking hate you so much.
I'm so I'm so I'm on the I look.
I need that.
I wouldn't be able to pay rent probably with that.
I I looked at it like an hour ago and I saw that it had kept going.
I want I want you to know, Digi, that I am actively rooting
against you because every time I see Bitcoin go up, I get angry.
I get mad because I sold it.
I sold it at a slight loss.
I was just wait for that anymore.
Just wait for the next step.
It's fine.
Oh, you're a fucking dip.
You'll buy the dip.
Oh, buy the dip.
No, I don't count twenty seven.
I'm fucking done.
Jimmy, Jimmy fucked me.
I don't have fucked me.
Everything I don't have this Bitcoin to like pull it out at any point.
Like I have I might spend some of it, but like it's there to be there.
Like Bitcoin is going to only ever go up.
Bitcoin like in the long term.
So and Ethereum.
So I'm not trying to spend that shit.
I'm glad Ethereum's going up because I got like forty dollars
of free Ethereum from M.Strange in like twenty eighteen.
And now it's worth almost three hundred bucks.
I'm like, yeah, yeah, yeah, I had my doge coins going down,
but I'm still up almost three hundred percent
and my initial investment of doge coin.
So what's what's what's that's that's six cents.
I bought it.
I was shocked to see that it has continued to rise
since the after the peak.
OK, it's down a little bit.
Oh, it's it was high.
It's high. It was like eight, eight and a half cents.
So it's still down.
It reached it reached it again.
Like it, you know, I mean, most things they spike really
like GME spiked really high and then it settled down again.
Dogecoin spiked really high
and it's lean like it was still down, but then it went like back.
It went back to where it was spiking to.
I was shocked and appalled.
OK, OK, it looks like it's kind of consolidating right now.
I'm hoping Bitcoin crashes so I can actually get put some money into it.
No, just put money into it now.
Don't that's not how this works.
Just money. I mean, I have one pound in right now.
Well, put more one pound twenty.
One could put one could crash.
Put in crash that.
Yeah, but that wouldn't that wouldn't hurt you
unless you spent it when it crashed.
Like you just hold it until it's uncrashed.
Like it will uncrash.
It's I think Bitcoin and Ethereum are stable enough at this point
as like the go-tos that like the entire fucking crypto economy is built on.
That like if it crashes, if it crashes, though,
then it would be better to buy when it crashes like let me put it before.
This is how my it makes intuitive.
I guess it makes intuitive sense that since it's like been high,
like it's got high and then it stayed pretty high for a while.
And well, it's gone up like considerably continually over.
Like if you look at the trend over time, it's just going up.
I mean, it's pretty fucked when you think about it,
that Elon Musk like made one purchase and it like doubled the value of Bitcoin.
It's pretty weird.
And he can do that any time is the other thing like that can keep happening.
It's all about how people are playing the the long game with the market
because like it doesn't necessarily benefit people holding Bitcoin for it to.
I've decided after doing this whole stock thing and like doing the game
stop shit and like having doge and Ethereum that crypto and stock market
is gay, it's good, but it's also incredibly gay.
And I hate it. It's I hate it.
I mean, I'm I have I have I have hated every second of being involved with this
stuff. It has been a miserable, so I'm crushing 200.
I love this. I'm fucking mad into it.
I love $200. It's always good.
It's always good when the market is bullish.
It's always good when the market is bull.
No, I'm like, OK, and I'm up $200 on Dogecoin.
And I am like insulted by the fact that like I just have $200
that I did nothing for and I hate it and it's it makes me like mad.
But you didn't do nothing.
You made a sensible investment and we're smarter than everybody else who didn't.
I am with Tom. I'm with Tom.
No, the fact that the fact that it paid off
does not mean it was a sensible investment.
Not even that. It's just like I get make call me an old fashioned pro.
But I feel like gains not made by direct labor is wrong and unethical.
I feel the apps. I know I know what you mean.
But also, like, OK, we can you can you can you can say that
unlike in like a theoretical sense, like what you say what you say.
What I'm saying, Tom, is that capitalism works on paper,
but in practice, it just doesn't it just doesn't pan out.
It never works. And and you're you're I don't know.
I don't know. I don't think there's anything more capitalistic than the stock market.
There are plenty of other.
There are plenty of other cases why, like, you know, the wage wage laborers, like.
Uh, you're you're in a you're in a it's an idealistic way of looking at things.
And like, I'm already I've already been convinced that it is not true
that, like, an honest day's work for an honest day's pay makes the world go around or whatever.
So, like, agreed. But like, also, I'm past it.
I'm past your point.
You said you hate it, but you're also disagreeing with me.
So I don't know what your stance is at this point.
Well, it's just that.
Are you just mad that you lost money?
Is that because I know you're not actually saying that it's
I know you're not actually saying that it's unethical.
I'm just saying I understand that feeling, but I don't have it
because I've been disillusioned of the idea that, like, working for your money
is like the is the right thing.
Well, money is wrong. Money is the problem.
That's my whole thing.
It's like the next step is like, oh, this is bullshit, anyways.
Right. Like, every time it exists, I don't I don't think there should be
a system that allows someone to do nothing and make more money than 99
percent of the population, like, working all day.
Sure. And the fact that I'm benefiting from that system
and how helping it perpetuate, even in a tiny way, does make me want to wretch
and I hate it.
But other people have been doing that all along.
Correct. And we should murder those people.
It's not like it's a news.
Wait, Elisar, shut that out.
All I know is that making investment gives you investment
capital to make more investment in the future so that you can actually put
money into the things you want to do.
And it's really, really great.
And that's why I'm doing it.
Unless it, unless it crashes, though, unless it crashes, because it can happen
any time, just leave your money in there until it's good again.
OK, I mean, pull it out when it crashes.
Don't do that. That's bad instincts.
That's weird. That's stuff people do to kill themselves.
Like it's like it's a weird suicide thing.
Like, so, OK, let me just I want to run through my last
the simple story of my three years with crypto so far, because I started
with just $50 in Ethereum and it immediately went down in value.
And it continued to stay down in value for two years.
It was two years before the Ethereum was worth $50 again.
And as soon as it went over $50, I was like, oh, OK, like this thing
is this thing's still alive and it's on the upswing again, as it had been.
Like I had bought in at a time when it was at its healthiest.
Like it had just reached a new height.
So I bought some.
It dips for two years, reaches a new height again.
So then at that point, I put more money into Ethereum and Bitcoin.
I think I had $100 in each as of last year.
And then I put like $600 into Chainlink.
And this was at a time where last August, like Chainlink was surging.
I got in at I got in just before the peak.
So I did make money when it peaked.
But then it immediately went like to half of its worth and stayed there
for a long time.
And so I was like, well, either I just lost this bubble
because it was completely possible that link was only ever going to have
one bubble burst at this moment and it would never be worth this amount again.
But there is logic when it comes to bitcoins,
it's not just gambling because there is actual reasons that each of these coins exist.
So like in terms of what Bitcoin and Ethereum are so valuable
because the entire structure of the economy is built on them.
So Chainlink is similar in that it helps to facilitate
Ethereum's ability to work faster.
So the more like Chainlink there is, the better the whole system runs, essentially.
So that like in that's because of that, I was like, OK, I'm going to hold on to this.
But like I was down to like half of the value of it
up until this whole fucking game stonks thing happened.
And just because of this, my Chainlink increased in the what had been originally
600 had been at 300 most of the time is now worth 900.
I transferred all that into Bitcoin immediately
because I don't trust Chainlink enough to, you know, to stay at this height forever.
But I do trust Bitcoin to keep going up and I wanted my money there.
So I still have a little bit in Chainlink in case it one day moons, as they say,
where it just has a sudden spike in my $70 is worth something dramatically different.
But like actually the fucking Ethereum and Bitcoin that I had that I had
$100 in each are now worth $500 each from this spike.
Those I don't think are just going to drop.
And even if they did, they would drop to a level
that was still higher than what I bought in at.
And then if I didn't sell, then it could still go higher up than what I even have.
That's the current height.
So I have I have fucked up at every stage.
Like I bought when I bought of crypto.
I have a Bitcoin when it was like close to peaking.
It went up for a while, but then it went down again.
So that's when I sold.
If I it's true, if I had just held it, just don't never sell when you're down.
Just never if I had just I didn't sell when I was down.
I sold basically when it was back to where I bought it.
So like I lost like a slight amount.
If I had just held it, I would be up like a ways.
So I'm very angry, very upset, a fuck Elon Musk.
It was the same with GameStop.
Also, I bought it at like the literal peak.
I bought it at the literal peak because I was like, OK, the hype train is real.
I was going on Wall Street bets.
I was seeing like everyone saying it's going to the moon.
Oh, my God, fear of missing out FOMO.
I got to get in on the rocket before it goes.
OK, it didn't work.
I whatever.
Yeah, that's fine.
It was for the means for the meme.
So it's all good.
A general good bet with all of this is if you are not plugged into any kind
of financial sphere enough that you heard about it before other people did,
don't get in on it because you're in the shock.
The fact that I was the fact.
Yeah, you're right.
The fact that I was just hearing about it then when I was not involved
with the community meant that like it had already gone off.
If your advice is coming from Twitter, you're too late.
So yeah.
So I'm very smart, though.
I mean, I still have my one share of GameStop.
It's worth like a fraction.
I actually just bought more.
I actually just bought more because I set a I set an order to auto go off
when it when it hit like 50 bucks and it just hit 50 bucks.
I don't think it's going to go up anytime soon.
I mean, as long as it doesn't go any lower than 50, I won't lose any more.
To me, the unsung power of all of this, though, is that like so many people
who never would have ever got involved in stocks or fucking crypto just did.
And like even having a negative experience, at least you like get your foot
in the door and know what it is so you can say, OK, well, I know what the apps
do. I know the only good thing that's happened with my stock portfolio so far
is that Sundial Growers did pretty good.
I got it at 80 cents.
It went up to like four.
I sold a little bit then.
So I'm up on Sundial.
I made some money there.
Oh, I have I have only lost money.
I've only lost money on these.
I just want to I just want to get to 10 cents.
God, well, you didn't lose much money.
So I thought I was so clever.
Well, I lost a little more.
The stuff I've seen people lose in this is like the the amount of down
people will sell at is absolutely preposterous.
Like I saw people like as soon as link went from 17 dollars to 12 dollars
immediately sold their link, even though they had thousands of dollars in it,
because they're like, oh, I don't want it to go down any further.
And it's like, well, you should have considered the money forfeit
when you put it in, right?
Like that is the way I did with GameStop.
And that's why I'm not that I put $500 in total.
And I was like, well, I can't get a PS5.
So I guess this is where that money is going, right?
That's that's really the best way to look at it.
Only put in money you won't miss, you know.
Yeah, that's that's what I did wrong.
That's what I did wrong with Bitcoin.
I put too much in.
And if Bitcoin had fallen to zero, I would have been devastated by the loss.
That's why I got paper hands and I was like, I can't do it.
I can't stay in. This is too dangerous.
I took it out. Now it's up 50 percent.
I would be way, way up. I'm I'm I'll never get over it.
Also, nobody listening to this listen to anything I'm saying.
I'm not a financial advisor.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I have no money to my name.
Except this crypto that I happen to have got lucky with.
I hear someone making stock advice and then saying, I'm not a financial advisor.
All I think of is like YouTube videos where it's like, this is not my copyright.
I don't claim copyright for this. I'm like, yeah, OK, fuck you.
When I hear someone say that, I think, hmm, this guy knows to cover his bases.
This guy is smart.
The thing with with all, you know, the ethical
nurse, like I think it's sort of immaterial.
Like it's it's easy to to to think of it as like, oh,
you're not doing any work and you're making capital and people work
and they they don't even get as much as it's more of a damnation of working
than it is the stock. It's it's it's I don't think that there's a problem.
I make my living from YouTube ad revenue.
So I already like don't like like working for honest work
for for money is already like out the window for me.
It's like that ship and sail.
I mean, I think it's fair to consider artistic creation
and entertainment to be to be honest work.
It's the hardest work of all. Yeah, sure.
But but like I think I think that all it does really is just it just
creates a lot of easy jealousy.
Like you see people who have in your eyes done nothing necessarily
and then they get become billionaires.
And you're like, well, not necessarily billionaires,
but like they get thousands of thousands of something or other
because they were in early on something and you're like, fuck,
he ego raptured it.
He fucking ego raptured that cryptocurrency. Yeah.
And and it's easy to get jealous and to, you know,
to get really emotionally invested in it.
And I just I don't like which is which is the correct response.
And I'm going to pitch you and you should use it.
I don't like you.
And I'm not fucking super upset about it.
Teens to people's door.
The whole thing with the stock market is that like it's not for
Pearls anyways, right?
Because like even if like GameStop doubled, well, here's my point.
Even if GameStop had doubled in value when me and Ben bought in at like
three hundred and was sitting at six hundred right now, like, oh,
we'd have three hundred more dollars.
Hurray. Like we don't have enough money to make any substantial
money on the stock market.
You know, I guess if you're considering like, I mean, we're like
particularly broke, like compared to I think the stock market is great
for like middle class people over half of America can't afford like
a four hundred dollar surprise bill.
Like I I'm doing I'm have more savings than the majority of Americans,
which blows my mind.
That's this terrifying to me.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think the I think the metagame of like the the capitalist money system
we're trapped in currently is that like basically in lieu of their
being socialism, people want to create a like definitive self like a
self safety net.
And so like most people who get involved in investment, like if you see
the people who talk about it online, almost all of them are just like,
I just feel like I need to have at least a million dollars or else
I won't be able to survive this world.
Like it's just that mentality of like the safety of money that these people
have, which is not even real.
Money doesn't really make you safe.
The best way to be safe is have connections and people who will don't
want to kill you, which if you have more money, more people want to kill you.
So it's not necessarily the best way to go.
I mean, I mean, money.
Well, I know what you mean.
Money does make you safe from some things.
It does.
I think it makes you safe from poverty.
And that's a difficult.
Yes, yeah, poverty is pretty dangerous.
Or so anything above the level of like, like if you have more than like,
I don't know, if you're making more than, say, like five hundred thousand
dollars a year, then like you're a target at that point, you know, maybe.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I'm not making anywhere close to that.
So I don't even want I have nowhere to go, but I just want like 40 K a year.
That's all I want.
I'd be totally happy.
I would like, I would like to make, I would like to make.
Well, I wouldn't like to personally make five hundred thousand dollars a year.
I would like as Yig Studio, a group of content creators, you know, like with
money being put in and out of, you know what I mean?
Like I'd like the profit of my endeavor to be that
not not that it's just me being rich or whatever.
Yeah, yeah, like, I don't I'm at the point where
because I was living I was living so meagerly for a long time and I still am.
But I'm I'm making a little more money now.
And like I'm still at like a I'm still at like like a submittal class income.
But like my expenses are so low that I like I've been saving money for a while now.
And I don't know what to do with it all.
And I'm starting to think like, yeah, this is like it's time to reinvest
this in like projects or something, whatever that means.
Like, I don't know, pay people to make stuff that I can incorporate
into something, I don't know, maybe it was like
pay comic artists to do more vapor or something for more of that.
Like because that money is not for anything else
because I have nothing really that I need to spend it on for myself personally.
So it like it needs to do something.
But I don't know what.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, it's just sitting in your back again.
And it's just like this is like wasted potential.
And so I guess I see that I see that more as like it's not like it's money
that I have made, but I feel like it should be, you know, like budget money
for like a a an enterprise or a I mean, not like a studio because I'm just one guy.
But you know what I mean?
You want your money to work?
Reinvest essentially, as long as you're sitting on it, fuel fuel the power
of some kind of creative machine.
Indeed, based, based.
All right, someone else talk.
I'm done.
Well, I don't like money, but I sure need to get some.
Preach my dude.
Patreon.com slash give and take.
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
Go to the Money Spenders podcast.
We can learn all about stuff that I say.
We all have bonus podcast, right?
Like all of us are doing one.
Yeah, I think so.
I should start.
I should do a Noida cast.
I should I should do a podcast.
You should do a Noida stream.
I should.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I think it OK.
I think it would be boring because post your Noida streams on only fans
and people tip you.
That's what we've learned today.
I feel like OK.
I feel like if I was streaming a normal Noida run, I would be distracted
by the chat and I would just die a lot and it would be boring and annoying.
But now that I'm on a good run with someone with you to read.
Yeah, I was going to say that was the thing we learned from I am Games.
It's so much easier to do stream when one person is gaming and one person is talking.
Then that makes sense.
Every time I solo stream, it's a nightmare.
But now, but now on my current run, I think it would be boring
because like so much of what I'm doing now is just like collecting
wands and spells and like storing them somewhere and just kind of going through
my collection like, OK, put this here.
So I have this and just like arranging things and then like just doing trial
and error where I like I'll stand there and like, OK, what if I put this in a
wand and fire it and then what if I put this in a wand and fire it?
OK, the the fire rate changes.
How long can a run potentially go for?
Like you're you're saying this run like you're in one continual run.
OK, well, a normal run where I just go to the boss, like usually I would die
within like half an hour or an hour.
Maybe like a good run might take a few hours if I like made it all the way
to the boss and won this run.
Where I'm like trying to like I've become like insanely powerful
and I have like the world is my oyster and I can do anything.
I mean, I've been the last for like several days because just doing a lot
of like man wand management and a lot of like, OK, like like like getting
through the the parallel world rock wall, I had to do a lot of like preparation
for that. I had to like I had to find the ambrosia.
I had to like separate it out.
I had to put it in potions.
I had to go like prepare my one specifically for the task and go do it.
So like a lot of it is like stuff that is not even that interesting to see.
A lot of it is me just like managing inventory slots.
And then, you know, it would have been cool.
I guess it would have been cool to stream that because it's like, OK,
I would be like preparing and preparing and preparing and talking about like,
how am I preparing to do this and then to go do it.
But it's too late.
I guess I could do that to like go to the moon or something.
But I feel like boring through the the parallel
world's wall was the big was the big challenge.
And I've already done it.
So oh, God, it's just like Bitcoin.
It's just like Bitcoin.
I didn't I didn't I didn't get in the ground floor.
I didn't start early enough.
It's too late now.
It's never too late by Bitcoin.
Yeah, I feel this way.
I feel like it's too late for a lot of things.
And like it's I just I guess I want to be part of a year ago on to everybody.
The idea that like rather than looking at it is like I put X amount of money
into Bitcoin with the intention of removing all of that money when it goes up.
Think of it like just I can spend whatever I have earned.
So like if you put in 500 and then it goes up to 700, spend the 200
and then don't spend any of the 500 you initially put in like.
Oh, back on back on the crypto thing.
There is one. OK, I watch this.
I watch this channel called Clear Value Tax, where where a very dignified
Asian man who is an accountant explains to me how taxes work.
And he made some videos recently recommending this app called KuCoin,
which lets you do things like you can invest in crypto
but then you can like assign your crypto to be like automatically
lent out to people and repaid to you with interest.
And and also you can create like a robot that will like automatically trade
cryptos like as the price fluctuates to like generate profit for you.
So I have been like trying to fuck with that a little bit as like an old
because I didn't I didn't like the experience of investing in stuff.
And it has failed at me every time.
But like people say I've heard people say that like, OK, investing
and holding is one thing and trading is another.
And it's like a different way to make money with cryptocurrency.
So I put like I put like a hundred dollars into my KuCoin account
just to like see just to see what it does.
Actually, it's been in there for like almost a week now.
Another thing that's very helpful to my
crypto trading has been that I have a lot of basic attention tokens.
And I don't know if you guys know about that.
But I don't know what the fuck that is.
So do you use Brave browser at all by chance?
OK, well, Brave browser is like a slight chrome,
but it has a built in ad blockers and and tracker blockers.
And also it has a crypto wallet that you can activate
where you collect passively a type of crypto token
called basic attention tokens, where if you allow it to like show you ads
or even just going through web pages, like you slowly collect
basic attention tokens and then you can spend them on
like creators and stuff who have who are like are signed up for the program.
So for instance, if you had
like the bat thing set up on your brave, then you go to my YouTube channel,
there will be a button you can click that allows you to just give me bat.
I've made a couple hundred dollars worth of bat this way
that I reinvested into other cryptos.
So that was a big starting point.
Literally money that I just got from people
decided to make their donation via crypto instead of regular money.
I use brave, but I have never understood that stuff.
Let me do brave is getting so sick into it bats always been dope.
Did did you or Trixie?
Did you hear that brave and their last update?
They just integrated IPFS.
I don't know what that is.
That is the Web three thing.
Remember that shit we were talking about back in 2018?
They built IPFS into brave.
So now you can go to IPFS websites directly through.
Oh, oh, sick.
Well, that makes that way easier because then we just promote the brave browser
more and can also make those websites.
So OK, like Web three.
I'm still following like bat or not bat IPFS and like all that stuff.
All those kind of things.
So I keep my finger on that.
It's getting better at some point.
You and I were way too far ahead of the curve.
We just dive into early.
But like, you know, literally five years ahead of maybe like in two years
would be like, yeah, yeah, we're finally there where we need to be to make that shift.
Because like everyone, it's funny.
You watch like the people like the doing the IPFS presentation.
They're all talking about what we were talking about in 2018
about how everything's too centralized.
It's all bullshit.
I don't know if you've seen the huge push of after Donald Trump got kicked off
Twitter, there was a gigantic wave of all kinds of people, just not even like
right wingers, just funny accounts.
Anybody funny on Twitter got like taken down.
Huge mass migration to Mastodon, which is itself a decentralized thing.
No, it's not even decentralized.
Instead, it's server based.
Like you had federated the federated thing.
Yes, you federate different servers, similarly to Peartube.
We'll get into all this explanations later, I guess, but some other time.
But yeah, like Dick Masterson immediately set up a Mastodon when all this happened
that started popping off.
And so that's all a fascinating world.
And if if that keeps taking off, I think it'll lead more and more people to
you got to you got to find the federated net.
That's what we've been calling it.
It's the federated internet.
You got to find the right federation because like Mastodon is like when I was
on one of the networks for that, that was when I got banned for saying I was
crippled because my life was hurt.
So that was the thing.
Like, yeah, what even did you do?
You I said I said my because my that was somebody had my leg injury,
which is still, I guess, technically there.
But like, when it was really bad and it's like, yeah, I'm like crippled.
I can't walk.
It's like, you can't say crippled.
That's a slur.
You're bad.
OK. Wow.
I look like even in the context of I am, yeah, they're like, it doesn't matter.
You can't say that language.
Well, to be fair, that was a warning.
And then they listened to the procrastinators podcast, listen, and then I got
banned. It's funny you mentioned that because Dick had initially made a
federation called his is called paypig.net.
But then because of the fact that everyone just jumped on there and started
saying the N word over and over again, he made a second one called verify.af for
just people who he could trust to not say the N word all day on his Mastodon server.
Incredible.
Hmm. I have OK.
I have had I bought a hundred dollars worth of US US DT on Kucoin.
It has been auto lending itself for about six days.
It has made 50 cents worth of interest, which does not sound that impressive,
but but that's in less than a week.
And if I iterate that 52 times for a year, that's a profit of about 30 percent,
which is a lot.
But the problem, though, is that like I would have to spend like eight percent
just to like put my money in there, which seems like a lot because they take fees out.
So this is a nightmare.
I hate I hate it. I hate numbers.
I hate now. I'm just dumb.
I just want to make cool art get rich.
That's that's that's about as complex as my mind.
That's the thing that's behind me as well.
Like I don't want to be a money person in order to do all this.
But it's so it's so I mean, because in order to get good at it,
you have to just like, well, I'm not an artist anymore.
I'm a financial. Here's that's not money.
I don't think that's true.
I don't think it's as hard as it seems.
Here's what fucks me up.
Here's I don't think I'm a person.
I'm an all or nothing person.
I want to do what is optimal all of the time.
So if keeping my money doing art, then holy shit, it all.
If keeping my money as US DT in a Kucoin account,
you know, just for example, if that makes, you know, 30 percent a year,
then that's objectively better than keeping it in a bank
that makes like less than one percent a year.
So it seems like, OK, obviously I should do that.
But like if I put all of my money into US DT on Kucoin, it's like,
what if that app just fails?
Like what if US DT becomes like what if it was a problem with the tether
and the currency crashes?
Like that's that's too risky.
So it's like, I can't do it.
I can't make the optimal play here.
Because we're too scary.
We don't have enough money to invest.
To make a substantial return.
Give us investment capitals.
Well, even if I had a billion dollars podcast, I know you're even if.
Even if I had a billion dollars, if it was like, OK, well,
Kucoin can make me 30 percent versus a bank can make me one.
I would I would want to put all of it in there.
But like still, that would be risking it all.
And and that's stupid.
I mean, having it in the dollars, risking it all, because that can crash.
We all collectively need to start.
I guess that's the that's the number one thing.
I also like whenever people talk about their fear of like these other coins,
I'm like, yeah, but the real money is super unstable.
All right, this is what we do.
Are you ready? Here's my goal right now.
That's kind of true.
But like, you know, at least with the I mean, true, the dollar value
fluctuates and it can change and it can crash.
But like it has, you know, the only thing that keeps the dollar from crashing
is that the US government just prints more of it.
Like we're in danger.
Just print more of it.
Like, yes.
I mean, I know.
I know, I know, but look, but like it makes sense to have a little more faith
that like the dollar isn't going anywhere.
This is what we have to do.
We need to we need we need all the reward and none of the risk.
So this is how how it's going to go.
All right, we start a second podcast collectively, like the pro investment
podcast, and the way it works is that if you go to the Patreon for that podcast,
we take that money and we invest all of it.
And then every week we talk about how the investments are going.
So we just take our patrons money.
They pay us for the podcast.
We pick all the patron money, put it into investments.
And then we just talk about the middle man that is just taking their
investment, like if it goes to the no, no, no, no, they're they're paying us
to be the guinea pigs to figure out the strategy so they can take the rest
of their money and invest it the way we are.
Yes, that's smart, that's smart.
Wait, audience.
So it's like crowdsourced testing on stocks.
They wouldn't know what's going to happen to their money in our hands
until it happens.
Right.
And so they would need to put the same amount of money that they're giving
us to to the thing themselves.
Well, no, here's the thing.
Here's the thing.
If they just give it to us to invest, then they don't have to worry
about whether it goes up or down, right?
They know it's gone.
It's a learning experience.
They're insulated from that emotional pain.
Basically, like if you were going to invest by yourself, you'd be like,
well, I need to put like X amount of money into something that I can
afford to lose to see if anything happens.
But instead of doing that, instead of doing that learning experience by
yourself, you pay a fraction of that to four idiots on the internet and
we'll do it for you instead.
But then collectively, we'll have more money so we can make more legitimate
investments and have see how it plays out at scale better than any single one
of us could do individually.
And then collectively, we can gain a better understanding of the market and
drive all of our audience to a brighter tomorrow.
The procrastinators hedge fund.
Are we building?
You caught me, you caught me.
I mean, it makes sense.
It makes sense because like if people are pledging to something like that, then
like they have a little bit of stake in like knowing like, how are these investments
going to do on a rock and then they tune in and hear us say like, OK, well, the
part we put in Bitcoin, you know, it went up.
The stuff we put in Ethereum is state stable.
The stuff we put in GameStop went down.
So we're going to move it here.
We're going to move this.
We're going to change the percentages here and here.
I'm just thinking about how if like if my $100 in Bitcoin is now worth $500,
then if I had put the 30 grand of Radcon in there, that would now be worth.
Oh, I think about 150 grand.
I think about even my Dogecoin.
I could put all my money into Dogecoin.
I would have imagined.
Imagine how much we can make to do more radcons with if you just.
So I think the best plan of action would be to to get this investment capital.
Put it into something that grows because that's, you know, we can do that.
You can just play on that, make that happen.
Get all that extra money by a weed store and have that as the ground base.
The operation that people that anybody who just needs a job that we know can work at.
And then we get a literal growth market where we grow the weed.
Yes. And then we also get free weed.
It'll be perfect.
Dude, what if we just had our own country, the pro country?
That's what I'm trying to.
That's where I'm heading with podcast.
That's why PCP HQ is too small thinking.
We need to go big.
Yeah, I want to have all of the things that you can possibly have under the brand PCP.
There you go.
We'll have our own PCP broad brand.
Interbrinton hit.
God, no, no data caps.
We can bully concuss.
We'll invest so well that we'll become more powerful and concuss.
We'll have nukes and then we'll declare war on concuss headquarters.
How far away do you think we are until like warfare is waged between corporations and not countries?
It already is.
But like open.
They'll never be open war again.
Kind of already is.
There's open war right now.
No.
Where?
In like Afghanistan.
With who?
Between who?
With we're still in Afghanistan.
Are we fighting though?
Are we like shooting stuff?
Yes.
I don't know what we're doing, but we're occupying it.
I'm sure Joe's getting those drones ready to go right now.
He's like picking up where his bro left.
Fortnite is not a real, Fortnite is real.
You zap into Fortnite and you're actually controlling a robot that's in Afghanistan
and it's copying your movements exactly.
And everything you do in Fortnite is in real life.
Victory Royale just bodies strewn everywhere in the Middle East.
I just think that the reality is we are already living in Metal Gear Rising Revengeance.
It's like already real.
Like it's not the future.
It's just now.
We're like Metal Gear Solid 2 at this point.
You know, like the Patriots.
Where's mine?
I think we're past that.
I feel like Metal Gear Solid 2 is in the 2000s.
Like we're already in the next stage.
Just most people haven't proceeded.
Well, I think we're probably closer to Metal Gear Solid 4 than Rising.
We don't have cyborg bodies yet, unfortunately.
Does that mean Death Stranding is in our future?
Yeah.
Death Stranding is Metal Gear Solid 6.
They never told you that.
Those don't actually take place in the same universe.
I highly doubt it.
It's not the universe thing.
It's the Kojima effect.
If he's so good at predicting what's going to happen.
They all do take place in the same world.
The real world that we are in.
They all actually happened.
It's all documentary from the future.
Even the ones that contradict each other.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
I mean, the world contradicts itself all the time.
We've learned a lot today.
I learned how to make the big bucks.
Wow.
Do we want to go to voicemails?
I guess.
Had to happen eventually.
Okay.
I've been gone for a while.
Have the voicemails gotten any better?
Has there been a golden age of voicemails in 2021?
The great thing about the voicemails now
is that they're all addressed to Ben.
Because he's the only person anyone could expect to be there.
That's somewhat true.
Ben is usually funnier to talk about.
The, okay, last week there was a bit of a kerfuffle
because a certain individual named Tommy Jay
was sending too many voicemails.
And then they sent one that really pushed me over the edge
and I got really upset.
And I want to acknowledge that Tommy Jay probably
had not heard all of the,
because of the delay between recording and uploading.
He had not heard the second episode in which I said like,
okay, funny joke, but enough's enough.
No, it's not funny anymore.
So, you know, it wasn't entirely their fault
that I got so upset.
However, I will be honoring my promise
to never play a Tommy Jay email again.
That much has not changed.
But I want to say, look at how funny,
funny misunderstanding.
But fuck you anyway.
Are you guys on speak pipe?
No.
I'll be there in one.
Can you, can you, can you pull up speak?
I guess I could just upload them to Discord
if you want me to.
Sure, yeah.
I don't know how to.
Where's the link?
I will, I will just put, I'll just put the fucking things.
Where did I, where did I save them to?
Here we go.
All right.
The first one is called, where did I put it?
First one is called, it is number two, seven, 18, two.
Here we go.
First one is called, no Nate, dot, dot, dot, dot.
All right.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Another episode without Nate, huh?
You know what that means?
No Nate, no not.
True.
Oh, I should say, but so last episode we talked about wanting to
do some funny rebranding for the new era and I was going to make a new banner
and I will have made a new banner for the channel by the time this episode goes up.
But it will already be out of date because I was going to make a joke banner about,
it was going to be me and Gib pointing backwards at the gravestone with the PCP logo on it and
laughing about it.
But it's already an obsolete joke because now there's four people on this episode.
So I'm still going to do that.
I'm still going to do that even though it's already pointless.
Sick.
Glad I ruined that for you.
But we said we will, if anyone wants to submit anything or send us anything,
use this, we still might do that.
Help us brand our channel.
Okay, the next one is called a do apology.
And there it is.
Three, two, one, go.
I'm sorry about the last voicemail.
I was only being a Nate had ironically.
Yeah, yeah.
Everyone's a Nate had ironically at first.
But then always.
And the disease sets him.
That's how it starts.
Okay, the next one is just called a Janess J N E S.
So three, two, one, go.
When best guy ever hears a voicemail from Tommy J.
Yes, I understand this one.
Oh, there's nothing to it.
Okay.
Well, why would Nate respond that way?
Wait, what was that music from?
I know it.
Kill Bill.
Okay.
So it's the idea that if Nate heard a voicemail from Tommy J that he would hunt
him down and kill him.
Is that the implication?
He would have a thirst for revenge, boiling his blood, reddening his vision.
I will do that.
I will do that personally.
Next one is called.
Easy to confuse the two.
That would be so, that would make me really mad if.
Next one is called Cody three, two, one, go.
Ben, it's not racist.
It's really good.
It's not racist.
What does that mean?
He's implying that you're pretending that you said something that you were like,
it's not resused about that was a thing.
There was a thing a couple episodes ago.
I think the NE words, the ha ha word.
You know, the mean Ben.
I'm right about that.
Yeah.
I don't really care, but.
Man, it's so nice being away for so long.
I'll die on this hill and every attempt to argue against me is in complete bad faith.
I haven't heard a good one yet, including yours.
Fuck you.
That wasn't even an argument.
That was just a guy making noises.
Oh, you're like.
Fuck you.
You're arguing in bad faith.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Next one is called the human guitar, the human guitar, the human guitar, the human guitar.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, this is epic.
This is funny.
Is this guy a part of the league of Nate fuckers?
He is.
I knew it.
All right.
Oh, God, it just keeps going.
Okay, funny noise make me go live.
I'm so bad.
Tom and Trixie.
Tom and Trixie, you are out of the loop.
But last episode, last episode, we were introduced to the league of Nate fuckers.
All of the worst, all of the worst and most heinous PCP villains, them snakes and
a cluster punk kitchen at Al were joined with some freaks like the man with a thousand lones.
Everybody's ever used a crazy poise modulator in the league of Nate fuckers and even some new ones.
They're all going to fuck Nate.
If I was this Nate, I would be building a moat around my house.
If I was Nate, I would invest in Bitcoin now because Fiat currency isn't going to protect him
from the league of Nate fuckers.
Okay, the next one is also called human guitar, human guitar, human guitar, human guitar,
three, three, two, one, go.
It's for guillotine.
I'm sorry.
I deserve you deserve better.
You deserve better than the PCP.
Why?
I can hear myself being speech jammed.
I am being speech jammed at this moment.
It is painful.
Okay.
I like the human guitar.
I'm going to dig a trench under my house and live in it.
It's like, you know, a new Minecraft mode with a scary aura to it.
It makes this sound.
The next voicemail is called veggie pilled.
Three, two, one, go.
Are they supposed to be God's chosen people?
That's what the Bible says.
Oh, I bet they always followed God's directions.
You'd think so.
Is that from VeggieTales?
Yeah, it sounds like it, but I don't know what the point was.
Did you?
It's a funny clip, I guess.
Did I just hallucinate that time that the VeggieTales guys said that the vegetables
in VeggieTales don't have souls?
No, we learned that during a heckles for shekels.
Somebody was in the call with us talking about it.
Right, right.
They don't have souls.
Why do they care about God?
It's literally like they feel they want to save those who can be saved,
even though they can't, because they're not God's chosen and they don't have souls.
What kind of a God would make his most ardent followers unable to be saved?
So they put on this 3D vegetable puppet show as themselves acting out roles.
It's like, boy, I wish I had a soul so I could watch this as a kid and become a Christian.
Is that a metaphor for the people who did VeggieTales?
They've just done so much evil in the past that they feel they will be saved.
So they're just literally vegetables.
They're in a vegetative state and somehow can make a show as well.
There's too much for me to handle right now.
The next voicemail is called The Truth About Mage.
Three, two, one, go.
Mage is just purple nepeta.
Discuss.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know who that is.
Yeah, nepeta is a homestuck troll.
Nepeta is green mage.
Just think of green mage and you'll understand nepeta.
Just green mage.
Sure, I guess that makes sense.
Next one is called Sonicoo 102 When Ben, When Is It Happen?
It is three, two, one, go.
Sonicoo 102 When Ben, When Is It Happen?
Yeah, I've already said I gotta do another thing before I release it,
but I will say.
How many layers deep are you in distractions?
Sounds like a lot.
You put 100 hours into a video game before finishing Sonicoo, so.
Okay, to be fair, most of that was spread out
for a while.
Not anymore, though.
That doesn't make it any better.
That's been about the last...
Noida has been most of the last two days of my life.
Think of what you could have done with those 100 hours.
I will exhaust it.
Oh, fuck you.
What could you have done with the time that you spent,
I don't know, what's something you like that's stupid?
I mean, to be fair, I fucking berate myself every evening before I go to bed
thinking about how instead of watching Ultraman,
I could have made the next Ultraman.
I think about that all the time.
Exactly.
So, I'm only holding you up to my standards.
I also fail to be.
You gotta get into a weekend situation where you're allowing weekends to be video games
to constantly non-stop, and then you do things on the week.
I can't let the man define my life like that.
When I try and schedule things out and keep the weekend free,
it's like, no, too many things will happen.
I can't let the man define my life like that.
When I try and schedule things out and keep the weekend free,
it's like, no, too many things will slip if I don't do things on the weekend,
and then I collapse under my own schedule.
The weekend is just two days.
You could flip them.
I'm just saying, seriously delineate the time between,
I can fuck around to I am supposed to be doing stuff,
and stuff will get done more often.
Yeah, I know you're right.
I know that you're right.
But I hate it.
Yeah, unfortunately, I'm in the same boat.
I'm just too shitty of a person.
With regards to, before anybody asks on the next voicemail, the Brony lecture,
I'm either going to have to record a whole fucking bunch of extra shell stuff to put around it,
or just redo it.
So that's why I haven't finished it.
What purpose?
Addendums to it?
Addendums?
Not so much because I was wrong, but that I just don't like the tone of the lecture at all.
It was, the sentimentality of it is very over it.
Very like, I was trying to get the last anger I had out about the whole thing or something like that.
Why don't you just, I mean, why don't you just maybe put an addendum at the beginning?
That's what I mean.
There would be a reframing, and I'd have to add in a bunch of shit, too.
So I just missed a lot of stuff that I would have wanted, but I don't think it's that good.
You'd have to, though.
Yes, because it's not, first of all, I just don't even like it.
I would rather redo it, but if it could be salvaged, I'd just build a framework around it.
Why not just, I mean, yeah, put an addendum if you're like,
I don't agree with everything I said in this one.
I don't like the tone of it.
I don't know, just release it.
It's like a historical artifact.
I mean, you don't have to stand by everything that you said.
I mean, granted, remember, I am about to just literally take everything I've made off the Internet.
So like, to me, not much sense in putting that thing up when everything else is gone, you know?
I want it, though.
I mean, with that, I can send it to you.
The state it's in.
It has about 15 minutes of highly edited part at the beginning and then the rest, so.
I mean, okay, what's...
It just kind of sounds like you've fallen down a hole with it where,
if things continue as they go, they will simply never come to light.
I think it's, yeah, it's sort of like the way I had initially made it.
I mean, even just when I got home with it, I was editing the fuck out of it
to make it like very different feeling from how it like,
and to add lots of visual reference into the stuff I'm talking about.
But like, it's kind of disorganized and like, I don't know,
I guess I just wouldn't explain it the same way.
Like, just in general, the approach I took, I think that it didn't come out how I thought it would,
like when I created the board, you know what I mean?
Here's...
Sure, yes.
I understand, but here's what I think.
I think that, yeah, maybe, I mean, you wouldn't explain it the same way now,
but at the time, that was how you would explain it.
That's how you did explain it.
And I don't, and like, I don't know, if you wanted to re-explain it, you could just make a,
I mean, you could, you could, you could redo it if you wanted to,
and that wouldn't preclude like putting out the original.
Even if it's like, disclaimed with like a, you know,
this isn't how I feel about certain things anymore.
Right.
I just kind of like being able to see it again.
I'm trying to encourage you, I'm trying to encourage you to release it in some form.
And I mean, you don't have to, but...
You did that great big weed thing right at the beginning, it was incredible.
I mean, you might, you might not like it for whatever reason, and that's fine,
but like, I remember enjoying it at the time.
I feel like, I feel like people would enjoy it for what it is,
even if you've changed your mind on it at the time.
That's what I think.
I'm sure, I, I do agree.
I think people would enjoy it for what it is.
I don't enjoy it for what it is though.
Like, I, I look at it as like, I can, I can watch,
I guess I feel that way about a lot of my videos, like, yeah, they're good,
but they're just like boring or wrong, or like, I don't care.
So that's why, like, you know...
But so what though?
But so what?
You don't have to stand by any of it.
That's true.
I mean, that's why everybody, I mean, other people can re-upload all my shit.
Dude, what if we just put it on the PCP channel?
Well, all my videos, yeah.
No, not all, well, it's a lot of videos, but like, the lecture,
because it's supposed to be you.
I kind of expect that's where it would have been.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Okay.
Probably.
I don't know.
I, I, I might still finish it, but I would much rather just redo it and do it better.
Um, get it as a trial run.
That's such a, that's such a trap though.
That's such a trap.
That's like, it is what it is and you can't be redone.
It happened, it happened in a very specific context that can never be replicated.
Sure.
I mean, it wouldn't be the same thing.
I would just do a different Brony lecture.
Like, that one's just, you just never get to see it.
Lost media, you know.
But it's got all of us there.
It's got Jesse and Munchy.
Uh, I don't think those two are going to come.
Come to like my, well, actually maybe they might come to a rack on five.
I don't know.
Munchy more likely than Jesse, but that was like a big Brony moment.
That was a brohoof moment.
I liked it.
Yeah.
Well, I'm sure I can salvage parts of it.
Like to throw in, to sprinkle throughout or something.
What?
I'm so like sprinkled throughout a longer, like second lecture.
You know what I mean?
Like, like if I did another one, I could incorporate parts of the original into it.
I, I don't see, do you even want to do a second one?
Uh, I'd be interested.
I mean, like I could, I think I would do a better job.
Uh, I think I, I feel like a second one is like, I mean, if you could, if you wanted to,
but like wouldn't it make more sense as like a, a second like rebuttal to the first one?
Like wouldn't having the first one exist, make a second one make sense?
And with it, like without that, like without the first one, the second one is like, what's it,
what is it even about?
I don't know.
The same thing except better done.
I don't hear.
All right.
I'm just, I'm, I don't think it would be better done.
You might like it more, but I don't think a redo would be better.
It would just be a different thing.
Okay.
That's fair enough.
Yeah.
Uh, all right.
Next voicemail, uh, is called, uh, where did I put it?
It is called deja vu, but it's relevant this time and I already put it in the chat.
Three, two, one, go.
Gip, you were talking in previous episodes about how Picross is really cool, except it
sucks sometimes at the very end when the board just happens to not be solvable and you're forced
to take a guess.
Um, I've had that same experience with Minesweeper and honestly, like, I know I've called in,
like, a meme-y way about this before, but from the way that you talk about Picross,
I feel like you would also really enjoy Minesweeper and Minesweeper.online has a no guessing mode
where the board is guaranteed to be solvable every time.
So, uh, yeah, I recommend that you go try checking that out because I think you would
really enjoy it.
That's Minesweeper.online.
It also has like quests and stuff where it has like different goals with like, oh,
try to solve it efficiently with like as few clicks as possible or try to solve it quickly,
like, in the quickest time possible, stuff like that, if you want to like spice it up.
So, uh, yeah, I think go try and do, uh, yeah.
I have played Minesweeper before.
The only thing I don't like about it, as opposed to Picross, is the default game mode
involves a timer to determine your score and I hate being pressured for time.
I would rather like sit at a puzzle for like three hours trying to figure it out than like
fail at rushing it and like, like, I would, I would sit at a, like a Picross, like a 25 by 25.
I've gotten bigger with the, with the Picross puzzles because I managed to do them correctly
and I was so fucking psyched when I did and I just keep the, on the Picross dot something
site, you can just go to like 30 by 30 and I'm working my way up to that and it's so
satisfying when I figure out one of those huge things with no mistakes.
Um, Minesweeper, I guess I could try it as long as it, like the timer just annoys me
because it's like, I don't want to be, I don't want to feel like I'm rushing.
I want to take as long as is necessary.
Isn't this the same guy, didn't this guy recommend us some other like,
play some game on a, on a website?
I think specifically he was recommending like,
a site that lets you play Minesweeper in certain modes that like,
would help with the issues you had with it.
That's what it seemed like he was explaining.
Was there, was this, was this guy like doing more like Minesweeper Apollogia before I,
this feels like it's revisiting a previous voicemail.
That's what I mean.
I think he was saying, oh this website allows you to play in modes that would get rid of
the things that you had as a problem with Minesweeper.
I died in two.
I do, I died in two.
Fuck this, sucks.
Well what?
I'm on my second round right now.
God damn it.
Well, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not indulging in this.
I'm not gonna humor this.
Next voicemail is called more like Mr. Poop.
Wait, didn't you, didn't you post two?
Huh?
There's one that's 48 seconds that we didn't play.
Oh god, you're right.
Yeah, okay, play the last one, not this one I just posted.
Yeah, yeah, the 48 seconds one.
It's called more like Mr. Poop.
Three, two, one, go.
Also, the problem with the ending of Mr. Boop is just that the themes aren't interesting.
Like, oh it was building up to how escapist fantasies are bad the whole time.
What, you don't need to explain to me that thinking you're married to Betty Boop is unhealthy.
That was the joke from the very beginning.
The appeal of early Mr. Boop was the absurdity of its presentation,
the absurdity of the universe, the way that lore is getting dynamically generated
as Alec improvises new ways to insert different characters.
Like, that's what was so interesting about it.
And once it becomes this meta thing that's all in the guy's head,
it just totally deflates all of that intrigue.
Doing something like that feels like the obvious route to ending a story
that involves a bunch of different characters from different franchises like this.
And it ends up not saying anything.
The only appeal is that it is meta.
And so it just ends up being unsatisfying for those reasons.
I completely agree.
Yeah, I couldn't articulate it, but yeah, it's a very good way, putting it.
Yeah, it's, I mean, on the one hand, I think, yeah, the real intrigue was like the,
all the weird, like, the weird jokes and like the non sequiturs and like the twists and turns
and like the new characters that would be introduced.
Like that was what made it funny and that was what made it interesting.
So really, like there is no like ending you could do with that.
That would like not fail to have that element to it, I guess.
But yeah, like the last, the last arc, the fourth arc,
the fourth chapter doesn't really have that because it's, it's, you know, it's,
it's building to the climax, which is really not what made the comic funny.
So yeah, I totally agree.
Let's go, good, good voicemail.
Next one is called Kringus Bingus Six.
Yes, three, two, one, go.
Hey, everybody, it's Kringus Bingus.
Yay, it's Kringus Bingus.
Normally I record these in my car when I'm driving around,
but this week I can't do that and that ties into my Kring for this week
because my car isn't working.
It's too cold or something and the battery isn't charged, I guess.
I don't know, but I Kringed about that real hard when I had to go somewhere
and then my car wouldn't work.
Yeah, yeah, agreed.
And what I binged at, what I binged, not what I binged at, silly,
you, I Kring at things and I binged things.
The thing I binged, I've been watching so much adventure time.
I've been watching like, I watch like four and a half
seasons of adventure time in like a week.
It's pretty crazy.
Less than, yeah, like a week.
It's almost as much time as I've spent playing Moida.
It's been pretty good.
It's a really good show.
I really like it.
Yeah.
Also, I just, if I can be serious for a moment,
Kringus Bingus has kind of been in a rough patch in their life.
Not Kringus, no.
And I would just like to say thank you for having me on the show
and, you know, having such a positive reaction to me.
Kringus Bingus.
And it's really brought a lot of light in my life.
We love you, Kringus.
It helps me that I can help you.
So yeah, Kringus Bingus out.
Goodbye, guys.
Goodbye.
Kringus Bingus loves you.
Kringus.
Yeah, we love you, Kringus Bingus.
We love you too, Kringus Bingus.
This is my first Kringus Bingus exposure, but I am so far impressed.
Kringus Bingus is an institution.
Yeah, I very much prefer Kring to a Kring.
Honestly, Kring is Kring.
Oh, God.
Fuck yeah.
Another masterpiece voicemail, another joyful visit from Kringus Bingus.
We've been blessed.
Next one is called, I don't know how to pronounce it,
Bwertkwap, B-W-R-T-C-U-O-O-P, number one.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Eleazar, you're my boy.
I need you to do me a small favor.
What I need is a jingle, because it's Ben's weekly reminder to catch up on one piece.
God damn it.
Ladies and gentlemen, Ben, please catch up on one piece.
Thank you.
Bye.
Okay, I should really do that.
Gabe, how's one piece going?
Uh, how far back are you?
What's going on?
I am at, I'm like kind of near the beginning of Wano.
I think like I just saw spoilers, by the way.
I just saw Kido's Dragon Form.
Oh, you're really early.
Yeah, there's a lot of this happening.
At the moment, there's, it's big fight moment right now.
There's a lot of big fights going on.
A lot of big people involved.
It's very epic.
There's a lot of big people in one piece.
They are.
They're huge.
It's pretty big.
It's big in its scale size and girth.
It's, it's, it's an acronym.
B-W-R-T-C-U-O-O-P, Ben's weekly reminder to catch up on one piece.
Got it, got it.
Well, if I catch up on one piece, then this segment will end.
So no need for a jingle.
Next voicemail is called Nine Year Old Anime Huge Titties Episode Two.
Nice.
I don't remember an episode one.
I remember.
It was, it was the, the, it was that, that one anime.
That one infamous one.
I remember.
Three, two, one, go.
I went ahead and researched the show with the big tid nine year old girl.
It's called Hinako Note and the girl's name is Ruriko.
And I was not hallucinating when she gets introduced in like episode four
and she gets knocked over and sprawls out on the floor.
We know it's not a hallucination.
The animators like took loving detail and accentuating the form of her
like well-developed nine year old body.
Yes, I know.
So I think these guys are like the, what is it called, pedophile virtuosos or whatever.
So these guys are the heroes.
This is a stupid voicemail because we literally said all the same stuff.
Not enough porn of her on the internet.
Dumb, useless.
I think he's saying that he remembers it and he found an image,
but now he's got him rewashed it and he's just saying it again.
Great.
Okay.
Next voicemail is called No Nut Nate based three, there it is.
Three, two, one, go.
You ever go back and listen to old PCP episodes
and hear Nate go on weird Ayn Rand rants and like just say a whole bunch of like cringy,
libertarian bullshit while simultaneously dreaming of living in you know post-scarcity
space communism like Star Trek.
Oh man, what a fucking dork.
Remember when you went to Jordan Peterson and shit and like still thinks that like Sam Harris
is the smartest guy ever.
Oh man.
Okay, no, this pisses me off.
Fuck you, dude.
You know why?
Because like we don't have any context into what you were doing fucking five years ago,
probably being like 15 and I don't know something dumb.
Imagine listening to a PCP episode more than once cringe.
I just think it's real fuck to come at how somebody was five years ago and be like,
Oh, remember when you fucking sucked and you're not you knowing he's not going to be on the
episode to defend himself.
I mean, he could be on any time he wanted.
Right.
But this guy knows he's not on the episode to defend himself.
No, I agree.
I'm totally with this guy in hindsight.
Weird utilitarianism is really just like a Randian objectivism.
That's what it always was.
It wasn't there's no hindsight needed.
He said so at the time.
Did he actually I don't remember.
I don't remember that.
He was like, yeah, I'm a Randian objectivist.
That was his stance at the time.
Lol, cringe.
I didn't even know what that was at the time.
So I didn't I feel like a lot of people saw like liked Jordan Peterson for a while there.
Like I didn't know about him until the backlash against him started.
So like I heard about him.
It's like clean your room.
It's like, yeah, yeah.
Like that that is good advice still.
Sure, sure.
But all the other stuff is pretty cringy.
I knew a guy in Georgia who told me that like he wanted to get his life back on track.
And he was he was like going to apply for a job.
And he was like he read this book by Jordan Peterson that had like, you know, really like
opened his eyes or whatever.
And at the time I didn't know anything about JP.
So I was like, okay, that's cool.
That's cool.
I would have had more to say about it if I knew more, but I didn't.
So probably good.
Probably good that this guy didn't like tell me that and it didn't go.
Don't you know that Jordan Peterson hates trans people?
And the like it probably wouldn't have been a productive conversation to have.
Right.
So I was spared.
I think the most like comforting thing that I've since learned since like initially
being exposed to Jordan Peterson is that at the time I remember a lot of people were watching
his content and I thought like on the surface level his stuff was like interesting and out.
But like my thing was like a lot of it just sounded like like like babble,
like just like big words strewn together and attempt to sound smart.
Yeah.
And then you read his book and you see the diagrams and you're like, oh yeah, this guy's nuts.
Well then like because I'm like perpetually self deprecating.
I was like, because like everyone in the comments like this guy's so profound.
I'm like, am I just like too retarded to understand what's going on here?
Just sounds stupid.
And then later on a bunch of people are like, actually everything he says is just kind of
sounds stupid.
And I'm like, oh, okay.
I feel a little better about myself that like I wasn't the only one who listened to this
and thought like it was just like techno babble.
I never looked into any of his videos.
I read 12 Boos for Life.
It wasn't a bad book.
It was just like so overly verbose.
And I was like, why is it so overly verbose?
I must be dumb.
And then I realized, no, it's just overly verbose.
I'm like, okay.
Yeah.
I think the first time I saw Jordan Peterson was on the H3 podcast and he took a big weed.
No, he took a huge vape.
Like Ethan had this like vape the size of a fridge and he took a big vape.
He was like, yeah, that's pretty good.
And I was like, who is this old man who's like a professor on H3?
That's kind of weird.
Was it weed vape?
No, it was just vape because he was do you vape nature or that stuff?
Well, Ben, every time you vape, you're just invoking Jordan Peterson.
I don't vape anymore.
They don't sell the, they don't sell pods anymore.
I cannot find them on the internet.
They're just like, how is it still a thing that's happening in Massachusetts?
I don't think it's not just Massachusetts.
I can't find them anywhere online.
Really?
I don't know if I'm, I've like, I've looked around and I cannot find a online retailer
that still like has stock that is not sold out.
It's easy to get weed vapes and it has to get nicotine vapes now.
That seems not correct.
I don't know.
It's like, it's like they just have to be manufactured.
It actually seems correct just in a way that you can't believe our world would actually be.
Oh yeah.
That's what I mean.
In terms of like how the world works, not how the world ought to be.
I don't know if they're still like banned to be sold in Massachusetts.
I would imagine yes, probably.
The flavored ones anyway, but I don't know.
But cigarettes?
But nobody has them.
Still in any corner store.
But I like, whether they're real loud or not, nobody has them regardless.
So it's, it's a mood point.
Oh my God.
I'm genuinely baffled that like I can't find them online.
That's so strange to me.
I guess, I guess what we've learned is you just need to spend $2,000,
go to the Philippines, you can get like really.
You can buy individual cigarettes for like five pesetas there.
So, you know, which is like so little of a fraction of a cent that I couldn't compare it
to an American piece of currency.
Cool.
How many Bitcoin for a whole pack?
Okay.
Next one is Meow Mix 64.
Three, two, one, go.
You know, I'm just finished watching some creepy web series like Illusion Lock and Diminish.
Is there a creepy or haunted web series that you've enjoyed as well?
Thank you.
Wait, what was the series?
Diminished and what was the first one?
I'm not familiar with that.
I can't tell what the first one is.
It's not really creepy.
I've always championed Tales from the gas station.
It's like a, not ironic creepypasta, but like kind of like a meta creepypasta sort of thing.
And it's really good.
Highly, highly, highly, highly, highly recommend it.
Really, really good.
Wait, what was the genre of stuff?
Like just creepy anything?
Creepy or haunted.
He said haunted, but I'm assuming it could be anything.
Dude, I remember.
I honestly don't really know what that means if that's like a specific genre.
This is like my first poop the pants moment online.
My first poop.
Everyone remembers their first poop the pants.
It was this Newgrounds game series called Ghost Motel.
And this episode one, which is, it ends like a, it's a point and click series.
And you're just pointing and clicking and going around.
And it's very, it's Newgrounds.
So it's flash and it's like low fidelity, but it's sort of, it's really,
I don't know how to describe it.
It's gory and bloody, like as you would expect Newgrounds things to be.
But it's also quite creepy and unnerving.
There's a bit of like possession of a girl and you get, you just can't do anything.
You, you just have to watch this girl get possessed.
And as part of a scene and you feel like you have control, but you can't.
And then, and then he's like, man, I couldn't do anything.
It's like a scene happens after that.
It's like, oh my God, I really fucked up.
I don't really like creepy stuff and I don't like spooky stuff, scary stuff.
I tend to not be there, which is why I give Tales from the Gas Station just a glowing recommendation.
Okay. Oh God, what was it?
This is so embarrassing.
I, I, I, I heated, I literally, I've never done this before.
I heated a trigger warning.
Can you believe it?
Oh my God.
Was it, was it about brains?
No, it was just about jump scares.
There was, I think it was, I think it was a night, a night, night, not night mind.
Um, um, masterclass, nightmare masterclass.
I think it was a video or it was some channel that I followed.
They put out a video that was about something and they said like trigger warning.
You know, I don't do any jump scares in the video, but I will be showing the media in question
and it will contain some jump scares.
And I was like, well, I know that's going to fuck me up.
I hate that shit.
So I'm not going to watch the video.
Thanks for the trigger warning, buddy.
Yeah.
And I didn't watch it.
I guess I should give a trigger warning for the, the Ghost Martel,
because the first episode obviously feels like they didn't intend it to continue.
So it just ends in a jump scare.
Um, yeah.
But every other thing after that is much more like serious and cool.
I, yeah, I would, I, I think I would, I think I could probably live the rest of my life
without being jump scared.
And if I could, I would say yes.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Uh, I don't like to be scared because it's scary.
You mean you don't like to be startled?
Yes.
True.
Well, I don't like to be scared.
I don't like to be essentially frightened either to be, to be honest,
but I feel less like strongly about that.
Like if a trumpet goes in the night and I'm not expecting a trumpet,
then I'm going to, I'm going to run.
I'm going to pee in my pants.
If, um, I've said, I didn't like, I didn't really like, like Midsommar and it was,
that didn't have any jump scares in it, but it was like, it was scary, right?
It was like unsettling.
It was creepy.
I don't like it.
I don't like that I watched it because sometimes I think about it and it makes me sad, right?
And like, did that improve my life at all?
No.
So I don't like that either.
I, I agree with you.
I tend, that's why I haven't watched that movie and like a lot of ones like it.
It's just like when people tell me, oh, this movie is like a nightmare.
It makes you fucking feel haunted for the rest of your life.
I'm like, thanks, I've never watched that.
Yeah.
I mean, yeah, yeah, I don't know.
You can get desensitized to those things, but I don't want to do enough of it to do,
to get to that point.
Right.
It's, it's, it's not my cup of tea.
Next voicemail is called, it's Margar, three, two, one, go.
Margar here, Tommy J.
If you want to be a legitimate voicemail member like me and so many other esteemed members,
just be concise.
If you have a question, ask it.
If you have a bit, do it.
I am a successful voice caller many weeks in a row.
Don't send more than like two voicemails a week, or you're just going to be considered epic cringe,
bro.
True, true.
Margar, the esteemed.
Margar.
If anyone, this guy could write like a self-help book about like how to succeed at voicemailing.
12 rules for voicemails.
Yes.
Exactly.
Margar knows he's the expert.
I skipped, I skipped a voicemail.
Sorry, Eleazar, you might have to flip those.
Okay, the next one is actually the previous one, but there it is.
This one is called facial hair voicemail.
Three, two, one, go.
Facial hair is cool.
Did you bro?
Had a really cool beard and I'm going to miss it a lot.
Tom Oliver had a cool goatee at one point.
I have that same goatee like right now where it's not on the sides.
I'm going to just have a mustache and a chin bit.
Ben Sainte, I think you had a beard at one point.
It's true.
You can find evidence.
It was glorious.
It trans people.
Tell me about what you plan to do with your facial hair.
You going to laser it off?
Talk about facial hair.
I want to say I have, I've been feeling pretty good lately because I have actually managed to kind
of grow the beard back.
Infamously, sometimes I have to shave the beard because I pick at my beard and I like,
I'll pick too much of it out and it looks fucked up and I have to trim it.
I have managed to stave that off long enough that I actually kind of have a beard again.
It's not long.
You look good with the beard.
I'm just going to say.
I do look good with it.
I think I look way, way better with the beard.
It makes me really angry that I have this tick that like ruins my beard.
Yeah.
Which is like.
It's so crazy to imagine that you could pick your beard so hard to pull the hairs out.
All three of you have God tier facial hair and it makes me so mad because that's what I want.
Not anymore.
And I can't grow it.
I know.
I'm just me.
I'm shocked that anybody thinks that Digi Bro had great facial hair because in my opinion,
Digi Bro had a fucking air of cubes.
I am like coping so hard with the fact that I can't grow a normal beard that if I ever
did grow a facial hair, I would go full Gandalf to compensate at this point.
Well, Digi never like had.
Okay.
The Digi beard was very like scraggly.
I think it could have been like trimmed.
I think it could have been trimmed into a very like it could have been very,
very much, um, yes, yes meme guy.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
You know, the blonde guy that says yes and he has a nice beard.
Oh, okay.
I know what you're talking about.
You could have done something like that with it.
That's kind of what I'm trying to do.
I'm gonna, I'm really trying.
What the tight curls.
I'm really trying to keep this streak going of not ruining my beard this time because every
time I shave it, I'm like, oh, I look so much worse and it makes me sad.
And it's actually taken me a long time.
It's been like, it's been several weeks.
It feels like it's been forever since I had a beard, even though I shaved it, like not
that long ago.
Um, I, I can't, I can't lose it again.
I can't lose it again.
It honestly, it boosts my self-esteem tremendously to have it.
And the inverse is also true.
So I have to protect it from myself.
If, if, if anybody like instead of like lasering your beard off, can you just like take your
stat points and beard and give them to me?
I will gladly accept that.
If I could, I definitely would.
Got it.
I got like some, at one point I got some like, uh, what's it called?
Like the fucking, um, like beard oil you can get to try and like grow your beard out more
and it didn't work.
And I was, it was devastating.
I, I give such an oil.
Yeah.
Like the oil, isn't the oil just for like styling it?
No, there's like some sort of like, forget what it's called.
It was some sort of like, what's the stuff that like makes you grow your fingernails?
Not melanin.
What?
I have no idea.
Biotin.
They say that like, if you, if you, if biotin, it like makes you, it like increases like hair
growth and nail growth.
That is the case.
Yeah.
I've been taking it as well.
But that's what they say anyway.
I think I took it for a while and I didn't see much difference, but it wasn't taken for that long.
Well, maybe I just need to inject biotin directly into my face.
Um, uh, I, I still have the good to know.
My facial hair hasn't changed in like a decade and I plan, no plans on changing it anytime.
Laser hair removal is very expensive.
But a Twitter user called 120 pounds of lean cave beef, uh, said that after doing it for
two years, they don't have any beard shadow whatsoever anymore.
So as far as I'm concerned, it's the only option.
Now we know the bit.
Soon as I can afford it.
I, I don't know.
I have no money.
So any amount is too much struggle.
I've also heard that it's like a session.
Like you go there every week for a number of months and it's like each session is like upwards
of a few hundred pounds.
It's definitely that's not cake.
It's not something that it was all told like two grand across two years to just on just the
facial hair.
Okay.
So I, I have, um, Jesus been using this, this handheld like consumer product
IPL laser hair remover, which, um, I don't know if I've talked about, um,
well, first off, I don't think it's supposed to be used for facial hair, but it,
because it says like, don't you, it doesn't really work on male facial hair because the
roots are very deep and it can't reach that far.
Okay.
But basically it's a, instead of a laser, it's a light bulb that pulses.
It's IPL stands for intense pulse light.
So it just zaps you with an extremely like quick and powerful light bulb zap and it hurts.
It's like slapping you with a, with a rubber band, but I've been using it on my arms and
legs and my arms and leg hair is basically completely gone, which is epic.
Okay.
Well, so it definitely works for most of the body.
Men and women can use it.
It's just that the male facial hair.
Actually, just link me the thing you got.
Well, it's kind of expensive as well.
The only reason I have it is because, um, a friend noticed that Black Friday last year
or the year before, oh no, it must have been last year, Black Friday, it was off by 70%
so I could afford it pretty easily.
I know the brand.
It's IPL Brown, like B-R-A-U-N.
That's the thing.
Yeah.
Like the brown tubes.
Yeah, yeah.
The ones you put on your car.
Yes.
I don't know what you're saying.
Oh, fucking 600 pounds.
Yeah, wait, that's a bit much.
I mean, cheaper than laser surgery.
No, I think it's definitely cheaper than laser surgery, but it's different from laser
surgery.
I don't think it could possibly permanently remove beard shadow, but it could definitely
get rid of body hair, which is what I'm using it for.
God fucking dammit, I've been losing it.
Mindsweeper non-stop since it's fucking since that call and every time I get farther and
more pissed.
This game does suck because you have to guess.
There is no mind sweeper game that doesn't involve guessing no matter how fucking far
you get in.
I would complain about the fact that it is inherent randomness, but I play like Pokemon.
I played Pokemon showdown a lot, so, you know.
Where's the thing?
They said that you can do a version that has no guesses guaranteed and I don't know where it is.
Okay, that's what they were saying then.
Did you?
Wait, how is that possible?
The fundamental mechanic of Mindsweeper is that it gives you limited information and
you have to make educated guesses.
No, it's that you use the numbers to determine
like, I don't think anything is a pure guess.
You always have enough information to figure it out if it is set out in such a way.
There's a subset of possible Mindsweeper maps that maybe start with one square already selected.
It's right there, no guessing mode on the left above ranking.
That's fascinating.
I wonder what the algorithm is, or what the rules defining a no guessing
Mindsweeper map is.
I don't know, but if I just match that out, I'm switching over.
I did a Mindsweeper earlier, and I just did it methodically, and I got all of the numbers
without having to guess once.
And it was only a medium, so it wasn't that big.
Oh, I don't even consider that Mindsweeper.
But like, you hit a thing and it's like, okay, there's a two there, and then it's like, well,
wait, how is there no guessing?
Because you know that there are a certain number of Minds,
but you don't know which squares they're in.
Don't you have to guess?
I don't think so.
Like, you use all of the other numbers.
You go for all the ones that are absolutely guaranteed, and I don't know.
I'm not a Mindsweeper person.
Is it Mindsweeper.online?
It's not that no matter what you have to guess in a match, it's just that the odds of you having
to guess at some point are so astronomically high that it's almost guaranteed to happen in most matches.
I mean, okay, I hit a button and it said one.
So I was like, okay, there's one in the surrounding eight.
So I have a one in eight chance of hitting a mine.
So I click another one and it says two.
So I'm like, okay, now there's, I know that there's one in the seven remaining surrounding
the first square, and there's two in the seven surrounding the two, and one of those two might
be in the, like this is still, it's, it's still guesswork.
It's like, it's like I can make a pretty good guess.
I, oh, I'm playing right now.
Okay, all right.
That's all I got to say about that.
Fuck Mindsweeper.
Anyway, yeah, laser hair removal is expensive, but the body hair removal is affordable kind of.
And that's what I'm doing.
I am experimenting.
I am experimenting zapping my face just to see if it does anything.
If it like reduces the speed or the thickness of it, that'll be handy.
So I'm going to do that anyway.
And apparently zapping with the IPL is just good for the skin.
Uh, you know, if you don't do it, if you do it once a week, then it's fine.
But if you overdo it, it's a bit much.
Well, I'm going to check it out.
The next voicemail is called Poopy Pie.
Three, two, one, go.
Do you guys remember when the universe weirdly aligned so that some random Swedish guy
screaming at Five Nights at Freddy became the biggest YouTuber on the platform?
And then he was universally hated by every like cool YouTuber.
Everyone knew that his content was bad and he wasn't anything special or good or cool.
I remember that.
Then do you remember when a couple of newspapers correctly pointed out like, hey,
this guy says some pretty wacky stuff and kind of kind of racist stuff.
And then all of a sudden all those YouTubers who hated him before were like, now hold on.
We think this guy's cool.
You're ignoring the fact that he did change his entire content.
That was pretty weird.
He became a completely different YouTuber in fairness.
I still don't watch PewDiePie.
I still think his videos are fucking boring and obnoxious.
What do you mean he changed his, did he?
Yeah, like after all that happened, he totally changed like the way he presents his persona,
the style of the videos and stuff.
Well, when you say all that, like how, which controversial you're talking about
and how early there's so many I don't actually know.
I hear about PewDiePie from my brother.
I don't know.
Okay, but that's not the reason why people turned around from like hating on him to
defending him.
It was because he came under fire from traditional media.
I mean, maybe YouTubers were defending him for that reason.
But like, for instance, Victor was never paying attention to PewDiePie until that happened,
but he started paying attention to him because out of the saga of him chronicling it happening,
he then developed like a vlogging style more based around like the content he was doing
to cover that.
And so like, it just was appealing to an older audience and was a more serious subject matter.
So like, a lot of people newly got into PewDiePie who never would have watched him before, you know?
I guess so.
Yeah, I mean, it got him a lot of exposure and it didn't actually do anything bad for him,
obviously, as these things, as these things always go.
Not in the long term, yeah.
Uh, next voicemail is called, uh, Erare, Prepare for Bear.
New mic call out if audio bad.
Okay, here we go.
Three, two, one, go.
That's the best voicemail I ever heard.
I'm glad we had a winner today.
How do I prepare for the bear?
No, you can't prepare for the bear.
No.
You can't prepare, you can't prepare for the bear.
If he wants you, he's gonna get you.
That's all, that's all there is to it.
Best bet is to leave out something he might want to eat more than you.
If you, if you can like, have a friend who lives even closer to you.
Do they sell bear traps on Amazon and how quickly can they deliver?
That's the question.
Get, get, get your friend, get your, get a friend to move to your city and be like,
hey, I found a great house you can move into and have it be like directly between you and the zoo
so the bear will get him first.
That's the only, what if he's going for you specifically though?
And, and when he moves in say, hey, listen, uh, I'm glad you're, glad you're here.
Uh, but, uh, just, uh, not for any, not for any reason, but if you were to,
if you're getting mauled by a bear, uh, call me and let me know about it.
Okay, uh, just give him that heads up, make it, make that part of the agreement.
Um, okay.
Good voicemail.
Next one is called, uh, Ben's Valentine Wish three.
There it is.
Three, two, one, go.
I, Ben, Saint, uh, am gay.
I am saying it now.
Now this is false.
Any, any claims.
Like we've been over this.
Any future claims to the contrary are, are just, are mere posturing.
This is a deep fake.
I'm just pretending, you know, I'm just keeping up appearances.
This is gaslighting.
It's a lie.
This is the truth.
I am gay.
This is not, can't.
Uh, don't let me fool you when I claim to be straight.
This is photoshopped.
Wait, this is you.
I should edit this out.
You sound so different.
I don't want anyone to know that I am gay, but I am gay.
Yeah, it's a different person.
Yay.
In fact, in fact, every Ben Saint from before like 2018 or whatever, or 2000.
You were killed and replaced for the crime.
Is a different person.
I was, I was, I was a Paul McCartneyed.
I was, I was killed and replaced with a, with a body double.
So that doesn't, that doesn't count.
The voice difference was so like uncannyly different that I thought just a person had,
was quoting you, like just saying the thing you said once.
I did very briefly think, wow, this is a really good Ben impression.
And then I was like, oh, I thought it was a terrible, I had no, I didn't even consider
there was, could it be an impression?
Like reverse Paul McCartneyed.
The body double was the original one and the original one is the double.
There used to be a Ben body double, but then I, then he killed, he was killed by the CIA
and the CIA called me up and said, Hey, sorry, we killed your double.
You're going to have to resume your regular duties now.
And I said, fuck.
And then here I am.
And that guy said, said he was gay on the internet and it's haunted me ever since.
Checks out.
I'll never escape from the shadow.
Okay.
So I hope that settles that for once and for all.
Next one is called Shin Megarfield Ten Spain.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh God.
It'll contain no great power, ancient knowledge, contain no great secret on it above all,
but one day I've been no center, sir.
Take control parentheses.
And now we're summarized summer.
Heart broken.
Divisional between the summer I summer and the great power.
Divisional between the rabble and the oneru.
Once a broom like a Sakura blossom.
Now a empathy like a bottle of sake.
And summer I not to talk about scroll.
No, no, no, no talk.
How I sucky scroll.
Neto son boy.
Samurai summer defect.
You never stop.
Of a net.
But until you next time.
I can't believe Samurai summer is in the League of Nate.
Samurai summer.
I can't believe you would.
You would become my enemy like this.
So this is terrible, terrible news.
The League grows in power with every passing moment.
Wait, are the Nate fuckers pro-nate or anti-nate?
It's hard to tell.
They just want to fuck Nate.
They just want to fuck, like they all want to fucking for different reasons.
Like some of them are noble reasons and some of them are evil.
They're all they're only united.
The group hasn't decided if the fucking is metaphorically or literally yet.
Some of it is clearly literal.
Oh no, it's very literal.
It's explicitly literal.
But make no mistake about their intentions.
I want to say there's a video.
Cassidy uploaded a video condensing all the Samurai saga voicemails into a single video.
I retweeted it the other day.
Link in the description.
Why is that not on the fucking highlights channel?
We have clearly dropped the ball.
You know?
Maybe we did.
Maybe we fucking did.
Next voicemail is called Melonbread Rebuttal.
And there it is.
There we go.
Three, two, one, go.
Look, look.
Pancakes with craters.
You fucking do one of those.
This is Marin Pan.
I don't know what the fuck you were talking about last week about inadequate posturing.
But what I do know is, is that you made me feel called out and humiliated.
And like a fool.
So if you want to elaborate, let's communicate exclusively through PCP voicemails.
Oh, and by the way, listen.
By the way, I don't want to hunt Benzart work.
All right.
The only thing I want to hunt is Nate's utilitarian little boy pussy.
Motherfuckers know I want to utilize that Nate pussy.
He didn't say league though.
I think he's associating himself.
Maybe he's maybe maybe applied and they haven't got back to him yet.
Yeah, this is his application.
Do you remember what Pancake said about Mellon last time?
Marin.
Marin Pan.
Well, this is, okay, but he wrote it as Mellon in the title of the voicemail, whatever.
Do you remember what they said?
Because I don't even remember what this is in regards to.
No, I can't.
But I guess they do so they can have their convo.
They definitely should do a back and forth entirely in PCP voicemails.
We'll stay an impartial observer.
I'll stay not knowing what they're talking about for as long as they want to continue.
Next voicemail.
We've got three more, by the way.
Next voicemail is called Tshepi.
T-S-H-I-P-I.
E-P-I.
Three, two, one, go.
I remember Benzart.
What?
This audio.
Can you hear anything?
No.
I hear thumping noises.
I don't know if this is intentional or not, but I'm assuming it's not a touch.
Is he sitting on it?
YouTube series.
I came to like YouTube poops one last time.
My version was called Martin the Lawrence.
So I was going to take clips of Sonic the Hedgehog specifically to set an M cartoon
and then just interject clips of Martin Lawrence.
I don't know how I was going to do that.
Martin Lawrence?
That's that.
I just wanted to also say, I'm going to have to go on your top.
That's even a movie.
I couldn't.
Okay, I heard YouTube poop, so I assume...
Something about making a YouTube poop out of Sonic the Hedgehog and clips of Martin Lawrence.
That's all I got on that.
I'm afraid for YouTube projects if recording with a microphone was this difficult.
You shouldn't have told us.
You should have just done it.
Now that you've said it, you won't do it.
Now that you've said it, it's over.
I mean, I was talking about an idea that I had for YouTube poop,
and I think he's just saying, oh, I also had one.
Here's what it is.
But obviously, we don't know how funny it would have been.
Now we'll never know.
Next voicemail is called Boopity Shoopity Fuck That Guy.
Three, two, one, go.
If someone sends in eight voicemails, Ben, you just have the right to not play them.
Just don't play them.
That's what I said I was gonna do for the record.
There have not been any Tommy J voicemails this week.
I have not had to censor any out in case any...
If there were any, I would have censored them out, but there weren't.
So in case you're wondering.
Um, last voicemail is called Addendum, three, two, one, go.
I have an addendum for my last statement.
Well, okay.
I'm sure we'll be glad to listen to it later.
Oh, wait, wait, one more.
We just got one three minutes ago.
Three, exactly three, three minutes ago.
Someone left a voicemail, so...
Is it the addendum?
Here it is.
No, I think it's a different person.
This one is called I'm Not Working.
Three, two, one, go.
I have an addendum.
I am so scared.
I gotta get one, go on and get one.
Doomer, we have you on YouTube for my music.
Hey, that was nice.
Yeah, that was good.
That was a good closing of the original PCP arc.
I imagined like the new banner like slowly fading in from like a big to like
zooming out to a full size as that's playing, you know,
it's the end of an era, walking away.
The only difference to the theme is that now it's nightcore.
Eleazar, make that the intro.
Make that the intro to this episode, and then we can end the episode
with the story of how it became the theme song for this episode.
Making it come full circle or something.
Yeah, I'll make a new banner and maybe then I'll just
make it replace it with something else in a week or whatever.
It's time to fuck around.
It's time to fuck around with the branding of this goddamn YouTube channel.
It's a bold new era.
It's a new year.
It's a new era of the PCP.
Okay, that's it.
Okay, that's all.
So really thought I could beat a Minesweeper match before this episode is over,
but alas, nothing but fucking failure.
The struggle.
You lost at the moment you decided to play Minesweeper.
I know, I always do.
Much like the stock market, you lost as soon as you decided to play.
Pick Rust is better than Minesweeper, and I guess Sudoku is better than Pick Rust,
but Sudoku's, I've mastered it.
I mean, some Sudoku's are really hard, though.
I know, and I'm good at them.
The confidence with which you say that makes me believe you,
because I would never dare to say that I was good at Sudoku's.
I mean, I've done a few, but not like the really bad ones, though.
Have you never found a Sudoku that you couldn't coup?
No, eventually I complete them.
I have an app that has easy, medium, hard, and I've run out of hard ones.
I need to download DLC for more.
DLC.
Yeah.
I mean, literally downloadable content, so.
I guess that's it.
I guess we're done with the episode.
We're almost at the three hour limit that Eliasar gave us, so that's good, lol.
A patreon.com slash the procrastinators bonus episodes.
Yes, yes, the behind the scenes.
Yeah, the behind the scenes clips episode is out.
Is it good?
I don't know.
The speakpipe.com slash pzp voicemail.
If you want to send us a voicemail, thank you.
And I mean, in patreon.com slash bensaint, obviously for me, just to give me money.
Me personally.
If you would rather give your money to me and get access to over 100 bonus podcasts,
which are all really good and they're gonna come out weekly instead of monthly, like these slackers.
patreon.com slash polystage2.
Baby.
Come on, man.
Come on.
Don't listen to that.
Bensaint Malarkey come over to me.
It's true.
The Bernie of Podcasts.
If you like Malarkey, if you like Malarkey, you should follow me.
You should support me over that comment.
Okay, goodbye.
Okay, that's the end.
Don't follow me anywhere because it's all going to go away.
Okay, day is dead.
There's a business strategy right there.
Yeah, I love it.
End of the episode.
Good night.
God bless.
Godspeed.
Goodbye.
Good night.
See ya.
Bye.