Hey everybody, welcome to Episode 2 of the Bustercast, the only podcast where we've ever
me and Ben have done something by ourselves.
Is that true?
I think it is.
Is the Bustercast the only other one?
That could be true.
Yeah.
I think we've done other things, not PCP related, but when it's just us two, I think Bustercast
was the only thing.
I think you're right, actually.
We did have the little D&D back and forth at one time, but they were two separate videos
so it doesn't count.
Nothing counts.
So what is it?
It's July 5th, and what is it going to be like a month now, since YouTube deleted our
videos for no reason, and has just told us, like, no, we'll fix it.
No, we'll fix it.
No, our internal team is going to take care of it.
No, don't worry about it.
Much like the government responding to COVID, saying everything is fine, and then doing
nothing and letting it get worse.
YouTube is modeling that style for success quite well, unfortunately, and here we are.
If they were going to fix it, they could just do it.
And if they don't care and aren't going to do it, they could just not answer our emails.
Right.
I don't understand this weird middle ground, and I don't know why it should take this long.
This is how they keep the peons in their place.
They pretend to care.
There's just some algorithm that just is appeasement.exe and just sends out those emails.
Just why even pretend?
Why even pretend?
It's just making me matter.
But we're not, we're not rebelling.
We're not going to YouTube HQ and shooting it up like someone else did, because we have
this tiny thread of hope, keeping us from going on a riot.
I mean, there will come a time when words will no longer be sufficient.
That's true.
An action will have to prevail.
I guess we're not there yet.
Like they're just delaying the inevitable.
They, they, it's so bizarre.
The way this whole thing has transpired is so bizarre.
Like there was no need, there was no need for any of this to happen.
They just like someone like read an email wrong or something that was like, oh, this
channel was hacked, better delete all their content.
It's like, no, this was solved already.
You solved it.
And then you came back and unsolved it.
It's very incredible how like, oh, we're going to delete this entire channel.
Then we're going to bring it back.
Then we're going to delete a quarter of an entire year's worth of uploads because like
that seems like it would be more effort.
Like it seems like something you'd have to go out of your way to do as opposed to be
like a, a consequence of some automated system.
It seems something so fucked that automation couldn't be responsible for it.
And yet here we are.
I just don't know.
I do.
You think it is automate?
You don't think like a human being sat down and was like, let me decide which of these
things need to be deleted.
Yeah.
I think if it was by a human, there would be like patches in between those two dates
where things stayed, right?
Cause like it's just like everything from 195 forward was deleted.
Except for that one stream inexplicably, that one, the radcon opening ceremony stream
escaped it.
No reason why.
So I think one exception.
I think unfortunately it's, it's after four weeks of time, I think it might be time to
finally bring up the question.
What do we do?
Yeah.
If they don't come back, not going to be solved.
It seems as if, but they, but they keep telling, okay, like I understand, but they keep telling
us through email, they keep saying, no, no, we're going to fix it.
No, no, we're going to fix it.
Well, I mean, corporate CEOs keep telling me that if I work hard, I'll be rewarded.
And yet I'm still poor and not rich yet.
I, yeah, but I understand the motivation for keeping you poor, Tom, that makes perfect
sense to me.
And if I were in their position, I would do the same.
But this, their motive, I don't understand their motivation for just telling us they're
going to solve the problem if they don't intend to, I guess it's just part of their
long game to keep me poor.
I guess it's all my fault.
I think if they really just weren't going to do anything, they would just say we can't
do anything.
I don't understand why they wouldn't just do that.
Do we just need to yell more?
Like if we just not yelled enough, I do think that it's like, I was going to yell on Twitter
some more, but then I saw that like Nate had been like emailing them like fairly, you know,
somewhat regularly, and he had gotten a bunch of responses from them.
And so I was like, okay, I guess they are still talking.
I guess they're still communicating with us.
We don't really need to raise a stink on social media, but like a month is a long time.
And I just don't believe that it takes this long.
Yeah.
I'm so confused.
I'm so confused why they're going to, why would they make any promises?
And then just ignore, why not just ignore us completely if that's what they want?
Like, I don't know, man.
It's a mystery, my dude.
Hmm.
I mean, if the day comes when we are like, okay, the videos are never coming back.
I think, I don't know, maybe all, but at the very least, most of the content, people have
it like saved.
Like, like I've heard, I have had people on Twitter and there have been people in the
YouTube comments saying, hey, I have some of the Radcon stuff saved, or I have some
of the streams saved or whatever.
So worst case scenario would be, yeah, we lose the initial videos, we lose the initial
views and comments and stuff and all that, but we can re-upload it.
I really don't want to do that.
No, I do not either.
Yeah.
I mean, you in particular, right, the Animorphs lecture, if it, like, it would get like 200,000
views more.
I don't think it hit 200 yet, but it was getting there.
It was like 180 something, I think.
Yeah.
It was going on 200,000 views and without that, you know, it's a big loss.
Which is why I'm willing to just kind of hold off and be like, let's see, let's wait and
see what happens.
Let's wait and see what happens.
It took them forever for us to, for them to fix the hack the first time.
And by the time they finally did it, I was convinced they weren't going to.
So I guess maybe I'm a little more hopeful this time because I was proved too pessimistic
in the past.
But that is, you know, we have that option.
And I think that probably, so if you're listening to this and you've got some shit saved, you
know, hang on to it, there is a real possibility we'll have to put out a fucking call to be
like, hey, everyone, if we have anyone who's got our old shit saved, we'd really appreciate
it.
That's all we can do.
We, I mean, I have some stuff saved, but not most of it.
Yeah.
You know?
Like I have some of my own stuff.
Coconut milk.
Excellent.
Yeah.
Um, boy, it's frustrating though, boy, it makes me fucking mad.
It's pretty, pretty bullshit.
Pretty lame.
Pretty lame and gay.
Not cool.
So that's the situation with that.
How's, how's your week been?
Were you, were you on last week?
It was you, me, hippo, right?
Yep.
Yeah.
So how's your, how's your week been in the time since then?
It's been, it's been chill.
Just kind of working, grinding, doing a bunch of projects that I'm playing close to the
chest right now, trying to learn things and get smarter and cooler and better.
Are they a zoomie related?
Are they not a zoomie related?
A little bit of both, a little bit of both, assuming and not assuming related.
Okay.
Um, yeah, it's pretty cool.
Pretty neat.
Hopefully someday they'll see the light of day.
That's kind of the idea.
Did you finally said she's going to mail me all the posters so we can get those out to
the rad con backers.
I can't wait to do more grindy work.
Right.
She said she, she said she mailed them, right?
Yeah.
They'll probably be here in a few days.
Cool.
Boy.
Um, that's pretty sick.
Yeah.
It's nice to see that the patron shit or not the patron shit, the Kickstarter rewards are
going out.
Very exciting.
Um, from, uh, on my, on my side of the aisle, uh, my, my Kickstarter is, is also, I'm getting
ready to send that because I have all the vaporettes, Tom.
I have all the vaporettes.
My God.
I have all six of them.
Yes.
So last night Jade sent me hers and she was the last one.
Now I got it.
Uh, I have to like just put the pages together and like decide if I want to put in some like
bumper pages to like keep things like even like keep the left pages versus right page
alignments or whatever.
What's like, what's like the page count?
What's like the, the final page count is it depends on whether I want to put any of those
in, but it's going to like, like 55 to 60 or so, which is, um, it's funny because like
Vapors two is only 15 pages long.
So it's like mostly guest content, uh, which is kind of how I hoped it would be.
Uh, I'm very happy.
A lot of the, a lot of the vaporettes are long.
A lot of them are like six, seven, eight pages.
Um, pretty cool.
That's how you do it in value.
Yeah.
It's going to be like 55 pages.
I sent, I've sent all the guest artists their, their money.
They're fat stacks of that Vapors cash.
Uh, fuck yeah, um, it's a, it's a, I don't know, like if I can finish, if I can finish
doing the layout stuff today, I will send out for a test copy to be printed, get that
in the mail, look it over, be like, yeah, it looks good.
Then I will send out for them to make like 500 of them and then I want to be fucking
in time to do all that shit.
Time to fucking address envelopes and start like doing doodles and people's copies and
stuff.
I can't believe it.
You gotta, you gotta do everything through stamps.com so much easier.
Stamps.com.
You've told me about this.
Yeah.
That's what I use for all the rad con stuff instead of like handwriting all the labels.
I just, cause you can imp, you can export a CSV file of all the patron information and
the stamps.com file, then import it and then you just kind of go through and you, for each
one you say this is the package weight and then it'll just print out labels for you.
If you print them out on the label paper, you just slap them on there and have a good
time.
I, I understand why that would be an efficient way of doing things, but I just kind of like
labeling things by hand.
Just like that personal touch.
I like to give it the little personal touch.
Yeah.
I don't know.
You like, like, did you see the envelopes I sent for the first one?
They were like black with like silver sharpie, right?
They were, they were written in white out on a black envelope.
They're using like a white out pen and they, and they looked sick and I'm going to do that
again.
So, you know, no shortcuts for me, Dab, I'm going to do, I'm going to try and do a similar
thing with the, the RFCK Kickstarter.
I'm going to try and, I have green envelopes.
I'm going to try and make them fancy.
You're juggling multiple Kickstarter's.
Well that one I won't have to ship out for a little bit.
They are still in the process of like actually making the like tests, like the sample items.
So I'll have to get those made, approve them, and then say like, yes, make hundreds, please.
So yeah, like they will probably be shipping out at around the same time, more or less.
But I don't mind.
So like addressing envelopes is like thoughtless busy work that's kind of relaxing to do.
I'm not even like, I'm not dreading it at all.
I'm kind of looking forward to it.
Yeah.
Like, I like that shit.
It's easy.
The label stuff is pretty, pretty Zen.
You just kind of like put on like some music or a podcast, just get it done.
Exactly.
The only thing that sucked is that for the rewards for GradCon, you had to like match
up shirt sizes.
So it wasn't just like put label on, toss out of the way, you had to like go and sift
through them all.
Just a little bit annoying, but yeah, it's fine, whatever.
This time, because like the first time I sent out the Vapors Kickstarter books, not like
a lot, but like a significant number, like maybe like a dozen different envelopes ripped,
like the envelopes just ripped.
Maybe it was because they had a pin in them or something.
And like a lot of just people's like stuff got damaged and transit.
This time, I bought bubble wrap.
So I'm going to put, I'm going to tuck bubble wrap in there.
I'm going to wrap the little pin in it just so it doesn't like prick its way through the
paper.
It's going to be, it's going to be fucking great.
I have big rolls of it over here next to my bed.
It's probably not enough.
I'll have to get more, but that's fine.
No, it's going to be plush.
It's going to send it in plush.
It's going to travel in comfort and style.
Yes, yes.
Hey, I've been working on, I think I mentioned this last week, but I have I've kept working
on, um, slime and punishment finale.
That's going pretty good.
It's probably about half done.
I think last time I said it was not quite half done.
I've probably passed the halfway mark.
It's going to be exciting.
What's, what's the ETA on that?
Do you think?
Uh, definitely before the end of the month.
Um, yeah.
Um, I should probably do a bunch of work on it tonight.
Maybe after I do the vapors layout stuff, it will.
When I get like, when I get into the zone with it, it actually goes pretty fast.
Um, when, but it's getting into the zone is hard and takes like time.
I have to like block out time to like sit down and be like, okay, I'm going to make
this shot.
I'm going to, I'm going to make this scene or whatever.
Uh, there was a particular, there was one shot that required making it goes really
fast when there's not, when it's about like video editing, but when I have to like draw
something to put into the scenes, that's what takes a lot of time.
I had one shot that took me forever to draw because it was all these figures that
had to do two different frames and they all sort of move together.
And that took me like four days to just draw this, draw all, draw these figures
all out in both different poses.
Well, mostly it was actually putting them into the scene and having the move easy
took like less than an hour, but the actual drawing was like, oh, I got to fill
the scene with bullshit.
The labor scenes are always a pain in the ass.
They, they are, they are.
I hate them.
Man, why can't I just, they look cool.
Yeah, but like, man, why can't I just have a bunch of like close up on a face
and shot reverse shot?
That shit's like, that's, it's easy.
George Lucas did it and made millions of dollars.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
He had the right idea.
He invented, he literally invented it.
Okay.
Oh, he pioneered shot reverse shot in Star Wars episode one.
He copyrighted it.
So now I can't use it.
I have to pay him royalties.
That's why that's why I have to do work.
That's why he's not making them anymore.
Disney bought them and they bought shot reverse shot.
So he's just like, I don't even know how to make movies anymore.
Like I, I copyrighted movies.
I copyrighted editing.
I can't do it anymore.
Shit.
I wouldn't put it past Disney.
They're working on it.
They got their lawyers chipping away.
And like, can we just like own the movie format?
We should probably abolish copyright.
I just think, I just think laws should only apply to people that have more
and they should never be used against like people should be allowed.
Like I was about to say abolish copyright.
But I was like, no, no, no, no, no, don't abolish copyright,
but just only make it apply to Disney.
Like Disney can't steal from anyone, but anyone can steal from Disney.
I think that's fair.
There's I think that's completely fair.
Laws are more strict, the more successful you are.
Yeah, yeah, one hundred percent.
That should be how it works.
If you're already making like billions of dollars from your intellectual
properties, there should be a there should be a gradient.
It's sort of progressive intellectual property ownership where,
where and it's like, OK, you've made a certain amount on your property.
Like you can't own it anymore.
It's fucked up.
Like, isn't California kind of like doing that with like stealing and shit?
Isn't like if you like steal something under nine hundred dollars in value,
it's just a misdemeanor and they they can't do anything about it.
Isn't stealing.
I mean, that sounds like it would be a misdemeanor anyway.
God, what was it?
There was like they changed something in California with stealing.
And it's just like if it's under nine hundred dollars,
like they can't prosecute you or anything or you can't be arrested.
That sounds like something.
I mean, that totally sounds believable.
I feel like there's already places that have laws like that.
Well, like what you're talking about, like shoplifters, right?
I guess I just know that there was like a big stink about it a few months back
as people are just like going into stores and just like walking out with shit.
And there was nothing anybody in the store could do about it because it was like.
Yeah, the thing about that is that it's a totally victimless crime
and everyone should do it, whether it's legal or not.
I feel like that law should apply to big box retailers,
but like you shouldn't go to a mom and pop shop and like steal all their shit.
But you can go to Walmart and like it's all free and less than a thousand dollars
or more, basically. Yeah.
And even then, if you're like, if you if if you'll like promise you'll be good,
they should just let you off with a warning.
You see, everybody should get one. Everybody should get one.
Yeah, everybody gets one freebie where they can go in and steal
like a like a hundred inch flat screen TV or whatever.
Sick is that in California, the PlayStation five will be free, fucking base.
Wait, what?
Think about it. If it's under nine hundred dollars,
the PlayStation five will be under nine hundred dollars.
You can just walk in there and fucking take one.
I see. OK.
Wait, hold on.
It's not. Is it law or is it just like company?
Because I know that a lot of stores have have like don't know chase company policies
where like technically you're supposed to like stop a shoplifter.
But company policy is like you don't actually like follow them.
Like if someone just picks up some stuff and walks out with it,
you don't do anything. You say, hey, sir, stop.
And that's it.
Like that's the only thing you're expected to do
because it's like a it's like a bad idea to do anything.
You're not a law enforcement officer.
You don't have the legal authority to like tackle someone.
And even if you did, you wouldn't want your employees doing that
because you don't want your employees getting fucking injured on the job.
Like that's just going to that's like leads to more problems for the employer.
I'm looking. I'm looking at it.
I don't know. Maybe this is a different thing because this is from 2014
that must be older.
It says California Proposition 47 is what they were talking about.
Some of these articles, but maybe that's not.
I don't know.
I'm not in California.
We're in the other liberal bastion, you know, on the other side of the country.
Yeah, hell, yeah, dude.
We haven't done it yet.
Shoplifting is good.
Well, we know you have a personal vested interest in history with the subject.
We looting is good.
Antifa is the good guys.
I mean, whatever.
You guys all know what I think at this point.
What I don't even need to show.
I don't even need to show up or say anything.
It can all just be my opinions can all just be taken for granted.
Eleazar can just insert like quotes from past episodes.
Eleazar, just just just just paste in a bunch of times when I said that,
like, we should eat the rich and then it's fine.
That's you get the idea.
No problem.
We just added, like, another 45 minutes of the podcast, just with that one edit.
Yeah, yeah, it's like every time to go to voicemails.
Finally, I feel like what's the thing?
Was there anything like that in the news this week?
I mean, like, bullshit happened.
Oh, I went to a fucking I went to like a protest yesterday.
I broke I broke it.
Yes, I broke out of quarantine and I went and I did a march through Boston.
I quit being a pussy.
It was pretty funny.
I actually got there really early because I had been out with
Munchie and Kazi the night before and I had, like, stayed over it.
Like, like, slept on, like, their, like, dad's couch or something.
Oh, God.
As in Kazi's dad, not Kazi and Munchie's dad.
They don't they don't share a dad, as a matter of fact.
Not yet.
Lamal.
But I have, like, stayed over there and I so I had to go through the city
and it was the fourth and I knew that there was there was an event going on.
I was like, well, since I have to fucking risk infection to travel anyway,
I might as well stop in the middle and like do this thing.
So I got there really early and I had to just walk around
and wait for like several hours.
And I ended up getting I bought I bought a big bottle of hand sanitizer
to keep hands, you know, disinfecting myself with.
But I forgot to get sunscreen.
So I was out all day in the sun and I forgot to sunscreen and I.
And I'm all red and it hurts really bad today.
But that's but that's fine.
It was worth it.
And the march was very it was pretty fun.
It wasn't it was like three or four hours, which is like, OK, whatever.
It was kind of long, but not like unbearably long.
And it was a little bit.
It was a little annoying because they slipped in a bunch of
they slipped in a little bit of some like hippie dippy spiritual nonsense.
You know what I mean?
Oh, no.
There was.
I mean, they did some like did some like African chanting,
which like that's fine. That's cool. I get that.
But the the ladies that led it, they called them.
They called them the healers, which is like, OK, that's fine.
And like and for the most part, you know, they they invoked
some kind of like spiritual sounding stuff, which is like, yeah, fine, fine, fine.
But there was a part when we stopped at the Harriet Tubman Memorial.
This was like near like a house that I guess she lived in.
I don't know the fucking history of my own city now.
But this was a Harriet Tubman Memorial.
And we stopped and they sort of had like a moment of silence
and like some deep breathing exercises and like a like we want to honor.
They were they're going to honor the spirit of Harriet Tubman,
which like got it makes perfect sense.
But then they added these a little bit more.
They were like, we want to honor the spirit of water
because water is such a powerful elephant in the elephant,
such a powerful element in our tradition.
As you like, you know, these water spirits, these merfolk,
you know, followed our people across the sea.
If they slave ships.
Whoa, whoa.
Like whoa.
Do you want to honor their merfolk?
Clearly they didn't do much to help.
Yeah, yeah, they just were they just watched.
They were fucking centrists.
They were like, hmm, slave slave owners.
I can't tell the difference between these people.
Maybe they're both a little wrong.
So I don't know.
So there was there were a couple of little bits like that.
But, you know, whatever is fine.
It was very cool.
We went in front of we went in front of the police department.
I think it was the police department headquarters.
It was near Ruggles and it's this big.
It kind of it's like a big blue, like sort of semi-futuristic box.
It kind of reminds me of the IDPD headquarters from Nuclear Throne.
It looks a little bit like a prison and a little bit like a car dealership.
That sums up the police pretty well.
Yeah, I thought so.
We went right in front of it and we chanted, we chanted, you know,
no justice, no peace, abolish the police.
It was pretty cool.
They didn't do anything.
It was perfectly peaceful protest, which means that it accomplished nothing.
Nobody cared.
But whatever, we made our statement.
Unfortunately, nobody broke any windows.
Cy, nothing was set on fire.
Maybe next time.
Well, next time we get to get some of the Murfolk involved.
That'll that'll rile things up.
We got it.
We didn't invoke them hard enough.
I guess not.
The Murspirits or whatever the fuck they called them.
I don't know.
I get it's hard.
It's harmless enough, but it's a little it's a little
feels like a little bit of a waste of time, like I don't give a shit.
I don't give a shit about spirituals and I'm not here to fucking
I'm not here to fucking worship the elements.
I'm here to fucking defund the police and get the issues and get killer cops
put in jail. That's all I want.
And you're fucking it up.
But it's fine.
Cop killers, not killer cops.
Exactly. Exactly.
Thank you. That's that's going to be your fucking sign you bring out next time.
I somebody gave someone was handing out signs and I kind of wanted.
I don't know.
So I was holding up a sign, but it wasn't one that I made.
And then I ended up just picking a kind of generic, just like BLM one.
I was like, OK, this is fine.
I kind of wish that I had made my own and I could have made it a little more
pointed, you know, about specifically about like defunding the police or something.
But I don't want to get confused with the Murfolk.
No, I'm not with them.
There's like there's there's the defund the police people and there's the
Murspirits followed us from African people and we have nothing to do with each other.
That's that's interesting.
I don't know.
These these healers are a little whatever, they were fine.
You know, you know, they they went to all the trouble to organize this.
I'm sure it was a lot of work.
Do I if I if I had been making the speeches,
would I have said the exact all the same things?
Maybe not. But that's OK.
The doer is it is the doer of deeds, you know, who matters, not not the man
who stands aside and says how they do or could have done them better,
whatever that Teddy Roosevelt quote is.
Are we allowed to quote him?
Isn't he a bad person?
Isn't everybody a bad person who wasn't born like 10 years ago?
Um, Teddy Roosevelt is like you can he's, you know, everybody's problematic.
Everybody's got their issues.
I think Teddy is like pretty good for the time.
Like, is he a little racist?
Like, yeah, sure.
But he wasn't like a slave owner or anything, you know?
He wasn't like, like, I mean, there's like that Edward Colton guy
who they pulled down the statue of in London that one time.
And like, he like literally owned like a slave trading empire.
And then there's like Ulysses S. Grant, who owned one slave,
but only because like his wife already owned the slave and he just married her
while she owned it. So it's like he technically did.
But like, you know, there are there are degrees.
There are degrees. That's a little that's a little that's a little.
Am I am I being a little problematic here?
Just a tiny bit. You might want to.
Oh, oh, he only owned that out.
Oh, oh, he only owned one slave.
Like, oh, die, Ben St.
canceled like, no, but come on, but come on. All right.
Like, yeah, Teddy Roosevelt was a little bit racist,
but he was like that like paternalistic kind of racism that's like, ah, you know,
he was he was wasn't perfect.
But, you know, most most people were worse, you know?
He was pretty he was pretty progressive in his own way for his own time.
So I think that you can only be as progressive as the culture you were born into,
you know, 20 years from now, the fucking post zoomers will be talking
about all the problematic shit we did without realizing it.
I think you're right. I think that's true and untrue.
Like, I think I think that anyone probably,
if they really cared to like take a long, hard look,
probably should have known that slavery was always wrong.
But on the same time, you know,
if everyone's doing it, it does make it harder.
It does make it harder to be like to take a stand and be like, you know what?
I won't own people. I'm going to buck this trend.
Yeah. So I guess so I guess I see it both ways.
I guess if it's like that deeply ingrained, you know, it's kind of like us here,
like money pretty bad, probably should get rid of it. Federal Reserve die.
But it's like, what are you going to do?
Just stop using money like you can't really.
So I guess I'll just keep taking my hand out from the government.
Like, like, um, yeah, I don't know.
But slavery is bad, though.
Slavery was definitely in case in case I'm making this podcast going on the record.
To say it's official position, bad.
The official position of the PCP is that the slavery cringe, pretty cringe.
Not at all.
Based where we map slavery on our three dimensional chart.
Yeah, it'd be cringe, smoothbrained.
Oh, that one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cringe, smoothbrained and what's was the other axis?
Virgin, very virgin, definitely virgin.
Super virgin.
Mm hmm. The worst corner.
Yeah. But.
So that's me. I'm no longer a pussy.
I did the thing.
I did an activism and I feel good about it.
You risked the Rona, which you you were worried you had for a while.
But clearly that that doesn't seem to be in the case.
Did I talk about the Rona on last episode?
Did I talk about that ice cream?
I don't think so.
Well, in brief, I bought a tub of ice cream and I ate it.
And then I was real, realized, like, wait a minute, the seal was broken.
Oh, my God.
Somebody opened my ice cream and licked it to give it the Rona and put it back.
And I have been I am the victim of terrorism.
However, I don't think that's true.
I think it was just a factory defect.
I went back to that same store and I looked at the same flavor of ice cream
and they all have a broken seal.
And in fact, and in fact, the next one I bought not only had a broken seal,
it was like half empty.
So now not only was I exposed to the Rona, I was also ripped off.
So I need to go back and be like, excuse me, I want to talk to your manager.
This tub of keto ice cream was only like half full.
And I would like a replacement, please.
Thank you very much, essential worker risking your life to serve me.
But please, but please fix this immediately.
I mean, if you're if you have the Rona and you want to spread it to the most people,
you're not going to go for the keto ice cream.
That's definitely, you know, you're not maxing your potential damage.
You're right.
I would want to I would want to lick something that was like guaranteed to sell
that day, like because because if you let it sit, it's, you know,
the Rona only only lives for so long.
Although I do think it lives longer in the cold.
I would assume so.
So well, I would have assumed that like sub freezing temperatures would kill it.
But I don't think that's the case because it's not like it's not like a living
organism, it's like a virus, which is basically just like a glorified molecule.
So I do think it can survive sub freezing temperatures.
But I think it just kind of naturally decays and like heat speeds that process along.
So like living in the freezer is probably where it would be the worst
and where it would last the longest.
So, you know, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous stuff.
Although I don't think there's any cases of it having been spread in that way.
I don't think I was looking it up because I was afraid.
And I think there's like no confirmed cases of it being spread through food at all.
And like also cases in Massachusetts are like way down now.
Like we are one of I think we're one of only two states that is like
still decreasing, has not fucking fucked themselves with like a poorly planned
reopening. The Commonwealth works, I guess.
Commonwealth fucking works.
Wait, let me let me check right now.
Massachusetts coronavirus cases.
Are we still are we still in the decline?
Are we still in the decline?
It's like, oh, we were doing great until some crazy people started protesting
about merfolk yesterday.
Now it's a huge spike again.
Wait, I don't see the fucking I don't see the fucking graph.
No, Massachusetts.
If there's no graph, it didn't happen.
Did I misspell Massachusetts?
Mast Massachusetts coronavirus cases.
I just want I just OK.
Here we go. Confirmed cases.
110,000 Lamal.
Um, deaths, 8000 Lamal base.
OK, OK, Massachusetts new cases in the last 60 days.
Oh, my God, show me the graph.
Show me the fucking graph.
My viewers are not allowed.
Oh, here we are. Here we are.
OK, we've actually ticked up a little bit.
But at the lowest, we were getting like 100 cases a day.
Now we're kind of up to like two to three hundred socialists and confirmed
not working, but I mean, at the worst, we were getting like thousands of days.
So, you know, it could be could be worse.
I guess it's all right.
It's OK. It's going to be fine.
It's going to be fine.
We're going to make it.
Maybe someday.
Dude, I was reading, I saw something on Twitter about apparently in Florida,
there's like new cases of this like amoeba
that like goes in through your nasal cavity and like starts breaking down your
brain and there's been like 163 cases ever since it was discovered.
And only four of them weren't fatal.
And it's like happening.
And if you go in the water, this amoeba can go up your nose
and start breaking down your brain to ease your brain.
Oh, oh, no.
Yeah. I was just like, well, it's a good thing I never go to the beach.
And now I definitely never will ever in my life.
Oh, no, that sucks so bad.
Dude, it was like the worst.
It's like, oh, man, like, please, no, let's not do that ever.
I'll see if I can find the link and put it in the show notes.
But it was it was pretty fucking bad.
That's pretty cringe, dude.
Yikes. OK.
I mean, a little bit more Chad than slavery,
but it definitely is pretty close to the bottom of our.
It's it's it's yeah, it's a little more Chad and a little less Virgin,
but it's still pretty cringe. Yeah, that's definitely not good.
Definitely not good.
I'm that I've watched like some shitty YouTube video one time.
It's like, oh, top 10, like stupid deaths.
And one of them was like a guy bet his friend to eat a slug.
And the guy ate the slug.
But the slug had like, oops, the slug had a brain parasite in it.
And he got a brain parasite and it ate his brain.
What a fool. What a nerd.
Like, he really fucking lost the the Darwin award.
Won the Darwin awards that and I'm like, oh, my God, a brain parasite.
I'm going to cry.
I'm going to cry just thinking about it.
I'm so upsetting.
I found the thing I never ate a slug.
Yeah, probably not a good idea.
At the very least, if you have to eat a slug, at the very least cook it.
Cook your food, God damn it.
Yeah. Also, don't and don't make slugs your food.
I would recommend I was looking through.
I was I was trolling through Twitter a little bit last night trying to see
if like there were any pictures of the march yesterday that I was in.
I didn't find any, but I might go through again today
and see if anyone posted any like late pictures that have me in them.
I did take a few of my own, but like it's a little cringe.
You're like, haha, I took a selfie. Like, haha.
No, no, I need to let I need to let someone else do it for.
Yeah, if you do it, you're just like, you know, trying to get attention.
But if someone else did it, it's just evidence that you were powerful.
That's right.
But I stood up for justice. Exactly.
Oh, man.
J.K. Rowling's back.
Oh, back with she's back with more turf shit.
Really? Yeah.
Just doubling down, just doubling down her old shit.
That's really the only move you have to make once you're in her position, I suppose.
It's it's that or apologize and, you know,
I think it's just like at this point,
there's just so much bad blood that apologizing would lead to nothing.
Like no one no one would care.
They would still be mad.
So she's probably just like, you know, well, I don't really feel sorry.
So I'm just going to double down.
You know what? No, I don't agree.
I think if at this point J.K. Rowling like really like
looked into matters, decided she was wrong.
Like like like understood, like understood the point,
like understood why being a turf is bad and then came out and was like,
hey, guys, I was really messed up.
The stuff I said was wrong.
I got bad information and I had some like, you know, bad ideas
that I needed to like get over and understand why they were wrong.
But now I've done it and I've completely changed my tune
and I renounce everything.
I think she'd be a fucking hero.
I think everyone would be people would be like dancing in the streets with
that people like, oh, we.
Yeah, I do.
Like people would people wouldn't have to like people were so upset about
they're like, oh, we millennials sure do love Harry Potter.
And oh, but now our now our fave is problematic.
Like, oh, I guess that I guess people our age would definitely
cut her some slack just because of Harry Potter.
The millennia.
Oh, the Zoomers probably would.
The Zoomers would not.
They don't give a shit.
They would. That's true.
That's true.
OK, like obviously some people would never forgive it,
but I think a lot of people would and I think a lot of people want to forgive Joe
and would take any opportunity they could.
But, you know, she's just she's not interested in that.
Kanye West is running for president.
Incredible.
You see that?
Yeah.
That sucks.
Well, it's pretty amazing.
I don't know. I don't know.
Twenty twenty year that just keeps giving, you know,
there's always something new to look forward to.
I don't know if I think that like more if that's is that going to split
the Biden vote or the Trump vote more?
I don't really know.
I think it'll probably it'll probably affect them both relatively equally,
I would assume, right, because nobody really knows where Kanye stands at this
point, because he was like on Trump's dick for a while.
And then it was like, ha, ha, I deceived all of you.
So it's like, that's so fucking stupid.
Do you know what's true?
What's false?
Nobody knows.
I was only pretending to like, is he really like, you know,
like a Bible thumper kind of guy?
Is he really into God or is that a lie, too?
We just don't know.
Well, the conservative Christians want to go with the guy
who's talking about God, but it also, you know, not white.
Like we just, it's there's so many questions.
I don't know.
I I I think it'll probably cut pretty hard both ways, but also probably
not very much at all.
And it won't matter.
It's fine.
I'm just saying, I don't give a shit.
Kanye versus Trump would be.
Did you?
I mean, would would you not like, I feel like, OK, if Biden, if something
happens and Biden can't like be on the ticket or whatever, or just like
becomes irrelevant and it just ends up being endgame Kanye West versus
Donald Trump 2020, like 50 years from now in the history.exe tablet
because books will be destroyed with this point.
It'll just be like the end of politics in America.
This is when it'll happen.
Like this is when like politics literally just died and reality TV is politics
because it's just like the system has completely broken down at that point.
Yeah.
Yeah, being a little bit.
I mean, it would just kind of be a continuation.
It wouldn't even be that shocking anymore.
No, that's the whole thing.
That's kind of like reinforces the point.
It's like, if Kanye West versus Donald Trump, like would you be surprised?
You'd be like, mm-hmm.
Did did you see did you see Kanye?
I think it was this week tweet out like this like emotional tweet.
It's like, I'm so proud of, you know, my beautiful, gorgeous wife.
Cart Kim or what it right?
I'm so proud.
I'm so proud of my wife, Kim.
She's officially a billionaire.
I love her.
And, you know, I knew she could do it, right?
And like, and there was like a little like artsy little photo.
He made a little collage for whatever.
And it's like, dude, you fucking monster.
I hate you.
I hate your wife.
Read the fucking room.
You miserable piece of shit.
You are a fucking moron and I cannot fucking stand you in the slightest.
You are a blight.
Oh, it made me so it made me so fucking mad.
Like it would make me mad.
Like if that were true, it would make me mad.
And I'm sure it is true.
That fact alone makes me true.
But the fact that he like thinks that he should tweet it and be like, yes,
this is a cause for celebration.
It's like, just kill yourself.
Like just die.
That's just like the bourgeois version of getting a million subscribers.
You know, they're just that's the kind of excitement of the lists.
I feel like even under normal circumstances, it's gauche to be like,
guys, my wife's officially a billionaire.
Like fuck off.
Like I've seen I've seen YouTube channels be like, hey, guys, listen,
like I've seen them embarrassed to make the announcement that they have like
paid off their student loans, right?
But like they're not poor anymore, right?
Like that's embarrassing for some people to ask.
Like like that's the kind of situation we're in.
And then you take your con and you're like, dude, I gotta let everyone know
I'm already a billionaire, but now I don't know.
My wife is one, too.
This is they're all going to be so fucking happy for me.
It's so gross.
If your wife is so fucking gross, if you're a billionaire and you're married
to your wife, isn't she automatically a billionaire by like default?
Um, I think, um, I mean, I think some people don't have joint accounts, right?
Connie is like, I got to keep my shit safe.
I don't even trust her.
I mean, maybe I guess, I guess like generally it's considered that
when you, if you get divorced, like you split your ass, you split assets 50 50.
But if like maybe they have a prenup where that's not the case or maybe they
just have like split accounts.
So like, even though that is the case, like, I guess it's probably just
to her business, they're not, they're not evaluated at a billion dollars,
like they're not, they're not technically her assets yet or something or whatever.
These are questions that I've never had to contemplate and never will.
It's, it doesn't matter.
Like, uh, I saw, I saw a tweet from this guy.
Um, I think his name is Benjamin Dixon, sort of like a political guy.
He shows up on CBS sometimes.
He shows up on the news every once in a while.
He's a fucking good socialist boy and he made like a tweet.
It was like crying emoji.
And it was like that face when you got it, that face when you got it.
Oh, what was it?
Like you, you got to like, I'm going to misquote it.
But it was like when you, you got to criticize hip hop because hip hop is
like all about that grind and hip hop idolizes capitalism and just says,
if you're poor, you're just not working hard enough.
And I was like, yeah, that sounds about right.
That sounds about right.
And Kanye is also like that.
Kanye is all about the brag rap.
I mean, not exclusively.
He does sad raps too.
I mean, he's kind of his own beast, I guess, but he does, but he brags about
his money like a lot of people do.
And I hate that shit.
I hate it so much.
Uh, uh, uh, I hate, I hate that, uh, I hate that there's a certain segment
of the population that doesn't think you should be embarrassed to be a billionaire.
Those people are cringe.
They are the problem.
They are, uh, uh, uh, I hate them.
I hate them.
I just hate them.
It sucks.
It just seems like even if you are proud to be a billionaire, not something
you should probably be saying right now, considering the social political climate.
You might want to keep that in the back pocket for now.
What is it?
Like, like, um, you know, like form, like, is it four million people are
unemployed right now?
And like something it's saying like that, but, and that the, like, there's
another statistic, like it's like, like the top, like the top 1% has like
increased its wealth by like, uh, you know, 25%.
Like, like, like some, like some vast amount of money has moved itself from
ownership of like the proletariat to like the hyper elite bourgeoisie.
Like this is, this is just a fact.
The nor the normal flow of capital has only increased the normal flow of
capitalism, which like, you know, they did the cares act, which like did all the
like extra, um, um, uh, unemployment benefits for people losing their jobs,
which was good, but like a much bigger part of the cares act was just bailouts
for corporations and, and stuff reverse the bunch of tax laws.
So like all the, the tax money they would normally lose, they'd get back.
Yeah.
So, you know, that, that happens.
It's just the system doing what it does best.
And it's like, Oh, but like all this money is going to the poor.
It's like, yeah, but the federal reserve just creating this money.
So it's not like it's anything's being redistributed.
They're just making new money, giving it to you, but they're also making
your money less valuable because of the natural result of inflation of adding
trillions of dollars to the economy.
And so longterm, you're, it's just the billionaires making out like bandits
again, and it's like your pittance is worth less with every dollar they
print every month to keep you substantiate you.
They threw us a bone, but they threw the people that own your asses away
bigger bone.
So like you appreciate the bone, but like understand that they are fucking us.
A lot.
It's like they serve, they serve the bourgeois, they're, they're a silver
platter dinner and then threw us the scrap once it was done.
Yeah, that's exactly, that's exactly it.
That's exactly what they did.
Most of it went to them.
They try to obfuscate it so you don't realize that you're just getting
table scraps.
It's like, Oh, Donald Trump cares about me.
He personally signed my check.
He's $1,200.
Dude, what a piece of shit.
He personally signed the check.
I can't, that's fucking funny.
That's just fucking funny.
Donald Trump, funny guy.
Kind of like him, honestly.
Four more years, MAGA.
Clip that, clip that, put it everywhere.
Hashtag canceled and saying it's happening.
Hey, I actually have to pee all of a sudden.
I've been drinking coconut milk and coffee.
Do you want to spit, do you want to ad lib for a minute?
Sure, I'll try.
Freestyle, lay down a beat.
All right, I'm not doing that.
Not, not in these sensitive times with race relations, am I going to try
and appropriate black culture?
No, this is going to be a perfect time for an ad segment.
Hey, guys, you're listening to this on Spotify or some podcast platform.
And you're like, man, the procrastinators are not uploading on YouTube anymore.
And since the procrastinators aren't uploaded on YouTube, I literally
have no reason to go on YouTube.
Well, worry not, because I have continued the hyperbolic wine chamber,
my own personal podcast that I used to do on the procrastinators channel,
on its own channel, and it uploads three times a week.
So if you are just like, man, I really wish I could get the best PCP member
me to be more active and do more things and be on YouTube.
So I don't have to tab over to Spotify or wherever, because it's just so much
fucking work and I'm a lazy zoomer and I've just been conditioned by easy
fucking internet culture.
We'll just go on over to search hyperbolic wine chamber on YouTube
and you'll get podcasts three times a week.
And do it.
Do it. It'll be fun.
It'll be a good time.
And if you're a patron, you get early access a week early and you can get
the 50 episodes of the bonus podcast where you get to decide what the topics
are every week.
Do it.
Wait, Tom, did I just leave to go pee and I come back and you've
taken the opportunity to plug yourself?
Yeah, it was an ad segment.
Why don't you go plug your yourself?
When you shove it up your asshole is what I'm saying.
Sure.
That's OK.
That's fair.
OK, cool.
All right.
That's fair.
Considering pretty bad.
Hey, funny story.
I was we were taught.
OK, about the unemployment thing and the cares act, right?
It was called the cares act cute acronym.
They're doing they're doing like another one that I guess they're still
debating the like the minutiae of and this one is called the heroes act.
Very cute acronym cringe.
I saw I saw another one.
This was a story about like, oh, I might be misremembering the details.
I think it was that like a law was passed.
Criminalizing hair discrimination in the sense of like.
You can't discriminate in some place in their hairstyle.
The idea being that like black people wear their hair differently and you
can't like you can't discriminate for jobs based on that, right?
OK, which is fine.
But this this act, it was called the crown act, as in like the crown of the head.
And I'm like, how are all these fucking pieces of legislation have these cute
ass acronyms like they fucking get away with it?
I think they're just like like 90 percent of the time and effort is put
into thinking up a cute little acronym for it, because they know that's how
like people will read it in headlines and it's like the name's really important.
That's how we get public support.
I do think that maybe there is a there is a certain amount of effort
that you have to spend.
It's like, yeah, you can write up a really good piece of legislation,
you know, and like maybe make it, you know, work on like, oh, is it bipartisan enough?
Like, will it pass the Senate and Congress or whatever?
Like, OK, it was a good, good, good.
But also, does it have a really catchy nickname so that people will know what it is
and remember it and it'll like get people talking about it, right?
It'll make it sound better, you know, like, yeah, if it was just like
government stimulus four, seven, six, three, that's like cold and uncaring.
But if it's the CARES Act, I cared about the HEROES Act.
I'm a hero.
I'm working hard out in covid and I'm not getting paid any extra money.
Nobody cares, but but I'm a hero.
And that's what this bill says.
So I'm OK with it.
I will vote yes for the HEROES Act.
I will vote yes for Donald Trump in 2020, CAG.
I just love it.
You know, I just love just MAGA and CAG.
They're just fun to say, you know, they got that marketing down.
Yeah. Yeah. CARES Act, HEROES Act, Crown Act.
Yes, please. How could you vote no on any of these things?
Names are important. Names are important.
At the very least, I wouldn't have even remembered that that hair thing,
except that it was called the Crown Act.
And I just thought that was so that was so funny.
Tisk, tisk. Mm hmm.
Mm hmm.
Um, what else?
What else is going on? What else is going on in the world today?
Oh, God, the world is just a fucked up, weird place right now.
Sure, sure. It's good, good, good times.
I don't know about that.
I don't know if I can agree with you on that much.
You know, being a little facetious, a little facetious there, but it's OK.
I'm still trying to do 3D printing.
3D printed a couple more things. It's pretty cool.
I can't wait to make a model that I'll actually be able to 3D print.
I have this great idea for this cool, like diorama print
I want to make with all my characters based off a splash page of a comic
that I'm thinking of also doing. Oh, it'll be cool.
What do you mean a diorama print? What does that mean?
Well, basically, the idea is like there's like I'm working on an Izumi project
and like the last page is like this big single illustration
of like these two characters facing each other down.
And I'm thinking like if I take that and like print it,
you could have like a full like a little diorama of this,
because it's just going to be a 3D environment and two 3D characters.
So you just put that in a little slicer, then I can print that page out in 3D
and then have a full like 3D physical version of the last page of a comic book.
And I just think that's pretty cool.
And I want to try and do that. Hold on.
What do you mean by 3D exactly?
So like I'm going to I do like 3D models, right?
Yeah, that's like my art now. I do like 3D.
Yeah. So if I'm doing a, do you mean it's like Magic Eye?
No, no, I mean, like literally 3D print it.
So it's like a three dimensional sculpture.
Oh, God. Wait, how big would it be?
The printer doesn't print super big.
I think it can print up to like an eight by eight cube.
OK, it would be really funny if you were like,
it's going to be a Magic Eye, you can hang it up.
Well, now you've given me the idea.
I wasn't sure if you meant that it was like that 90s kid money.
I wasn't sure if you meant that it was like stereoscopic 3D, like red and blue,
you know, or if it was like, you know, 3D, as in like it's 3D sculptures, right?
As in it's like rendered, like rendered.
3D is used in so many variations now, you can never be sure.
Right. Right. People do that on Twitter.
Like there are guys like you can you can do stereoscopic 3D renders.
So like it'll render the thing twice.
And then if you like squint your eyes, it'll make it look like popping out at you
because of the way like your eyes work and how like there's a slight bit of separation.
And so there are people who are like, we'll just upload to Twitter,
like 3D models, like a turnaround.
But like two of them slightly off center from each other.
So if you so you like cross your eyes and yeah, it merges into one thing
and it pops out of the screen at you.
And I'm like, whoa, space age tech right there.
The future is now permanently fucking up my eyesight
just to have this pseudo 3D effect on Twitter.com.
Hell yeah.
Ah, man.
It's cool. Too bad.
Too bad the world is broken.
Arts. Art sucks, dude. Art sucks.
What a waste of time. No, no.
What a fucking boring. I mean, it is a waste of time
and it is boring and it is gay, but it's still pretty. Thank you.
Thank you. You're right.
No, I agree with everything, but not that.
That's not cool. Nothing is cool.
Everything's fringe.
It's boring and it's gay and being cool is impossible.
So therefore, boring and gay is all that's left.
See, if you put if you put art on our cube grid, you know, our chart,
it is it is all the way in the cringe.
It's cringe, virgin and smooth brain.
It's smooth. I don't know if it's smooth brain.
It's not smooth brain. You have to get smooth brain.
No, I think caring about art is smooth brain,
but being able to do art itself,
you got to be kind of not smooth brain to do it.
It takes like effort, you know?
But like it's in that corner so much in like the cringe corner
that it like punctures through until like, you know,
a parallel universe Mario 64 style and now it starts becoming based.
No, that's just that's that's the
that's like the death rattle of someone who's so cringe
that they can't that they know they're never coming back.
Oh, no, I'm actually so cringy that I circle around and being basic again.
No, no, you're just an idiot.
You're just a fucking nerd and you can't escape from that.
You're in the fucking cringe basement and I've locked the door
and you'll never come out to the people.
It's leave a comment below.
Oh, wait, you can't.
We're not uploading this to YouTube.
And absolutely pathetic.
I bet they look to you.
I bet they. Oh, can I can I can I scroll down the.
Oh, oh, no, because I'm listening to this on.
Wait, is it on Spotify?
Because I'm listening to this on the procrastinators podcast dot com.
And such a thing is impossible.
Yes. Alas, someday the site will be worth going to.
Maybe. I mean, it's worth going to.
It's worth going to right now because it's where the podcast.
It's worth going to if you just want to see a list of the fucking things
and also see, oh, I see that.
Wait. Oh, I see that this is like this is something
that I would not have noticed in the description before.
But there's a link here to a video by Oblivion Fall
saying like how to like have good audio quality for.
I forgot that was there.
Yeah, I forgot that was the thing.
But I see it pop up on the website because like of the way it like handles links or whatever.
We also have this really aesthetic plant.
With a nice bouquet background.
Where you go to the website, it's right there.
Did I like the header image for some reason.
Did I did I tell you about the aloe?
Did I mention the aloe about about how I got sunburn yesterday and my
and I needed like aloe to rub on it and my roommate has an aloe plant.
And he just like cut one of the leaves off and gave it to me.
And I just had to like squeeze the leaf and like squeeze all the goo out of it
and just like rub it on my body.
Just raw.
And, you know, I was disappointed.
Is a little slime adjacent, do you think?
Aloe is aloe is just full of slime.
It's just full of slime.
It's kind of true.
But here's the thing.
Have you ever had like an aloe drink?
A few times.
Not exactly my favorite thing, but I like this.
I like them a lot.
So I was like, well, I'm going to taste with this raw aloe taste like.
And I was like, maybe it'll be a little sweet, but probably not.
It'll probably just kind of taste like grass, because I know that like,
you know, they add sugar and stuff to an aloe drink.
I didn't think it would taste like the drink.
Turns out it tastes so bad.
It actually it actually tastes like you're like biting
into like an aspirin pill or something.
It's that bad and bitter legendary person known for
not endorsing eating slugs, but consumes aloe of his own volition.
It's a plant. Yeah, it's a fucking plant.
Yeah, it's like, oh, boy, what wacky.
Like, oh, what did you what did you find?
Like a we just plucked a fruit off a tree and ate it.
Like, boy, what a what a crazy thing to do.
It could. It could have a fucking brain.
You know, Miba in a dude you never know.
You're you're right. You're technically right.
Look, I just wanted to taste it.
And you know what? I did. And I'm not sorry.
But aloe is very much slime adjacent.
It is an extremely slimy plant.
And you know what? I think it might have worked.
I think rubbing its blood all over me actually helps
because I don't feel too sunburny.
It's pretty killer. It's pretty killer.
Yeah, cutting something open and rubbing its medicinal blood all over you.
It was just like, you know, it had it was slime time,
like just like in slime and punishment, you know, the cop killer
has got to have his slime time and I had it and it was based.
Do you want to go to voice? Do you want to go voicemails?
Yeah, we've we've done an hour.
We've done our due diligence.
I think so. I think so.
Speakpipe.com, my friends, if you want to stick it to the man
and leave a voicemail, even though we should be paying for it, but aren't.
Speakpipe.com slash PCP voicemail.
And hey, maybe go to the procrastinatorspodcast.com
and check out that informational video by Oblivionfall
about how to get good audio quality if you want to impress us.
All right. So first one we got this week is from Send Ducking Help Motherfuckers.
That's a big ask.
Yeah, I wouldn't count on it, frankly.
But let's see what he has to say. All right.
Three, two, one, go.
I did a blunt, two dabs, a round of pipes,
Jameson, whiskey, bourbon, beer.
I did everything under the fucking sun except the toad.
And now I'm out of work, motherfuckers.
Send fucking help.
Send fucking help, motherfucker.
Oh, OK.
So that's just starting out strong today.
Was that riddle my ass?
That sounds like riddle my ass.
I think that was just riddle my ass, Batman being drunk at work
and calling it just miss messaging the voicemail.
You know, sorry, I think it's too late.
This was sent six days ago.
Sticking to the band, though, I appreciate.
I respect the the effort, you know, absolutely.
We need to unionize and get ever when everyone
the the constitutional right to be drunk at work, I think, you know,
that's construction workers, you know, truckers, Uber drivers.
I mean, what's the worst that could happen?
What's the worst that could happen?
Why it it's a human right.
I just think it's a human right. That's all.
All right. Another one for riddle my ass, Batman, halfway sober this time.
This one's 50 seconds long, so I might get bored.
But let's let's find out three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP, two things.
One, if you played the help me, motherfucker, I need help kind of video.
That was not a joke.
I really was fucking obliterated.
We could tell.
We know. And second.
I'm still lying over.
And second, I'm thinking about doing a comic
like in a comic.
So for the drawboys out there, I have a question.
Yeah, like, would a.
Comic about the riddle my ass Batman series be a good idea?
And so where do I post it?
How do I go about that?
This question is too long.
Sorry. Awesome. It's fine.
It's thank you. All right.
Well, we just had a long discussion about how art is gay and the worst thing ever.
So my answer is definitely yes, do it.
If you, I mean, if you want to do it, then that means you should do it.
So like, that's it.
Like, that's the beginning and the end of answering the question for me.
Do it if you want.
Wanting to do it is all the reason you need room where to post it.
I mean, what do you think?
Where do I mean?
You know, there's a you can post it on like to pass web web web web
tune, tapas, posts, I would definitely put it on Twitter and at
yeah, people. Yeah.
So that's a good way of discovery.
And then you can have the full thing on something like to pass or web
tune or shit. Yeah. Yeah.
Post it and all posted like on every platform you can
and on everywhere you post it link to all the other ones, right?
Yep. Like that's that's how you.
You got it. You got to break.
You got to break your way in somehow and you might as well
just do the biggest all out like social media blitz you can.
There's no reason not to.
Yeah, post it everywhere.
That's the answer.
OK, next one is from a new bit.
Three, two, one, go.
What's up, game?
It's just got back from the gym.
Ready for another Daily Q&A first question this week.
Fuck yeah.
If podcasts only come out every week, how will you do a Daily Q&A?
What's something about like dog?
God, this lost all its momentum.
Wow. You can tell these new with this.
That's OK. It wasn't very funny.
Come back next day for another Daily Q&A.
God, fuck. Oh, God, you had me.
You had me so high.
Damn, that was it.
It was like that was a huge drop off.
It was like a vertical drop.
This video this this voicemail was designed to be like, dude,
we're in for a treat now.
I like, oh, where's it coming?
What's going to be the punchline? Oh, nothing.
Oh, I lost the thread. Oh, what am I?
Sorry, I made this voicemail, guys. Goodbye.
Close, though, close.
He had he had it.
All he had to do was ride that wave to the end.
He couldn't he couldn't stick the landing as the person who invented the Q&A.
My potential.
But you got to you got to spend more time in the gym,
both working out and working on your bit.
Tom invented the Q&A like George Lucas invented shot reverse shot.
Exactly. Every time you use it.
You have to pay for our time.
Speaking of the gym.
Well, today, you know, I got walking around Boston yesterday, marching.
I got more exercise than I got than I've gotten in months.
Maybe I wonder if now is the time to capitalize on my like
on my on my on my on my and crew of energy.
Yeah, because like you say you can't wait to go back to the gym.
I have no excuse because my gym is in my basement.
Will today be the day?
Probably not today.
Maybe tomorrow will tomorrow be the day.
It's not a good sign.
No next week.
Everybody. I know my feet hurt.
No, my feet hurt.
Oh, when I'm sunburned.
It hurts.
It's hot.
Oh, God, you're dropping rungs back into the cringe.
No, that's not true.
No, if I go down deep enough, I can circle back around and be based again.
No, I just get impossible, physically impossible,
conserving the law.
This universe operates according to a certain law,
and that law is known as the conservation of cringe or of base.
And and and and one one thing can only become cringe as something else become base.
You can't just you can't create baseness out of nothing.
Therefore, therefore, there's no such thing like like there must be a gradient.
You must follow an gradient.
OK, there's no fraction of reserve cringing in our system.
I don't think so.
How unfortunate.
I think if there was, we would have seen it by now, and they just we just don't
have the evidence. It's fair enough.
So next one is from Toa.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, can I see your feet?
Can I see your feet?
You know, I was really hoping this is going to be a bionicle thing.
Totally let down completely couldn't be a bigger disappointment.
Toa, buddy.
Yeah, DM me restraining order is in the mail.
Also that OK, next one is from a message to Ben.
So this is going to be this is going to be a difficult boy.
This is going to be emotionally challenging.
So shame Ben's on on the podcast three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben, three things.
Please stop using Twitter like Twitter is cringe, bro.
It only makes people sad or angry.
Second, it's not wrong.
You keep asking, what's the point?
There is no point.
There's no point to anything.
And that's a hundred percent base.
I know, man.
I stop saying so much.
You say like 20 times an episode, like every five minutes you make.
Oh, yeah.
And that's true.
Thank you. Love you.
But damn, right on all points, he absolutely demolished you.
In fact, I think he is right on all points.
Well, what was the first one?
Oh, stop using Twitter.
I know. Absolutely true.
I actually have kind of stopped using Twitter.
I haven't I've barely posted the last three days.
I've like made a couple of retweets, and that's about it.
I know. Yeah, whatever.
OK, yeah, he get he wins. He wins.
I lose. He wins.
OK, message to Ben, more like a message to base.
All right. Message received.
Message received episode of Steven Universe.
Next one is from Darren the Rad.
Three, two, one, go.
So I'm going to say something super controversial,
but video games are the worst hobby, fucking build shit.
Um, agreed, hard to agree.
I don't know.
They're the worst hobby, but they're definitely not productive.
I'll give you that for sure.
What does he mean by build shit?
Because like you could you could be technically building shit
if you're like building like model trains or something.
And like that's equally unproductive.
Like that also doesn't accomplish anything.
I guess I guess you could say you're you're kind of like
learning how to like, you know, construct things.
And I wouldn't say it's like super valuable.
I would say in terms of if like video games have zero percent value,
that's like one percent value.
If you wanted to, you could go and be like,
oh, video games improve your and hand-eye coordination.
That seems like a myth to me.
Well, that's how I feel about the, oh,
well, like you're learning to do construction
or you're learning how to push it together.
I think if you say build things, you mean like create something.
That makes more sense to me.
Like build like a business or a side hustle
or something like that, do something productive.
Even then, I wouldn't go so far as to say the video games are the worst.
I think there are plenty of equally pointless hobbies.
Oh, for sure. For sure.
But in essence, I agree.
The video games are the worst thing in the world.
And nobody and you shouldn't touch some of the ten foot pole.
They ruin my life.
Yeah.
Except a Pokemon showdown.
Fight me on Pokemon showdown.
There's exceptions to every rule. Of course, of course.
Next one is from lack of Ben solo cast makes Araylo sad.
Oh, I see what they're doing here.
I see. I get it. I get it.
Three, two, one, go.
Where is the Ben solo cast?
Ben St promised it.
He even said at one point it was a semi Ben solo cast.
But here we are without any conversation about the best Star Wars character.
Ben solo, please help us, Ben St.
You're our only hope.
Disney has left Ben solo out in the cold, only selling bad guy,
Kylo Ren merch, and yet we only have fans stuff to turn to.
And the promised Ben solo cast
still isn't even here.
Little like a little like Giggle at the end.
Yeah, I get it.
Funny, funny joke, funny pun.
The Ben solo cast was about it was going to happen today,
but then Tom joined at the last minute and ruined everything.
So I'm sorry.
Ralo is crying right now because of you, Tom.
You know, I'm proud.
It feels great. Fuck the Ralo's.
OK, there you go. I said it.
Cool. Well, there you have it, folks.
All right. Next one is PCP
diss track from Do Not Play
if there are less than three people on call at fuck you dot com.
Anyway, I'm going to play it three to one go.
I don't think you guys are ready for this.
OK, there's a link. There is a link.
I don't think. OK, I opened the link earlier
and it is it is like a four minute long song.
It is a it is an anti PCP diss track.
It is a it is, you know, it's laying the smack down on our asses.
I didn't listen to the whole thing
because this was like a minute before the podcast started.
But I will put the fucking link in the description
if you want to go and check it out.
This is this is from the this is from the the procrastinators anonymous.
The pro and on cast.
So it's on their channel.
They guess they wrote it.
They are criminals.
But I'm looking at it now.
My my face is not in the thumbnail,
so I would just have to assume that I am not being dissed.
The thumbnail is give give Nate, Jesse,
Munchie, me and Digi, and you're not in it.
So get fucked.
It just means I'm not.
They don't hate me.
Maybe that's that's how I'm going to that's stupid.
That's so fucking stupid.
From what from a little I've heard of the pro and on cast.
They stand me pretty hard over there.
Really? Yeah. Amazing.
Feels good. Why? Why?
I can't know why I don't get it.
Look a gift horse in the mouth.
What reason could they possibly have?
OK, whatever. As good as mine.
Stupid.
The next one is from Cool Skellon.
OK, this is this is a minute 30.
We're in for a long call on this one.
All right.
Well, we'll see. We'll see if it's worth the time.
All right. Three, two, one, go.
Hey, the progress, natives.
I just did a bit of a science experiment last night,
and I wanted y'all to know about it.
So I was just listening to a PCP episode 123.
I'm a bit behind, I know, but I'm getting there.
And I heard about, you know, when you're talking about,
oh, your phone just listens to you, right?
And it picks up advertising data that way, as opposed to I know this.
I know what he's going to say.
Gay and shitty and bad.
We use them and they're good.
But I last night for like 30 minutes, I was high as fuck, right?
And I was just I was monologuing at my phone about how much I want to see.
Cool skeletons, cool skeletons, skeletons with sunglasses,
skeletons on the beach with a margarita or perhaps one of those fucking
seagrams fruit, like beverages with alcohol, like a tiny, tiny,
like five percent alcohol, not even that kind of thing.
And we'll like a skeleton in a Hawaiian shirt, a skeleton in Ray Bands,
a cool fucking skeleton.
And I got it.
I got the skeleton.
I opened up Facebook the next day and it's a bunch of those personalized shirts.
But is it up like a like a.
Was that it?
Oh, I guess he got cut off.
Damn.
Sounds like the experiment was a success.
This happened to me recently as well.
I was congratulations on your cool skeleton.
Yeah, yeah, go on.
I was talking about how I was just talking to my sister about how I was like
having like a shitty time sleeping because she was kind of come over.
I had something I had to give her and my phone just immediately popped up
like 10 minutes later.
It's like five apps to help you sleep.
I'm like, oh, please never do that again.
Five, five, what?
Five apps to help you sleep better like a personalized.
So I immediately went in and turned off microphone access to all the apps.
I'm sure it doesn't actually work.
It makes me feel a little better.
Um, somebody.
Wait, it was someone on Twitter, someone on Twitter messaged me.
Oh, this guy, nobunty on Twitter said that listening to the PCP and hearing
me talk about gummies infected his Amazon recommendations.
And now he gets and now he gets his Amazon recommendations are full
of like Xanthan gum and stuff.
This is some fucked up shit.
Yeah, world gone mad.
Wait, wait, hold on.
Hold the phone.
Pause. Pause the podcast.
Wait, really? News.
OK. Oh my God.
Uh, before this podcast started, I put it up something on Twitter saying
I had a new T-shirt available, the Pixel Sunset T-shirt, because everyone
thought the background from Ninja Suffering was really cool.
So I made it an all over print T-shirt.
Two copies have already been sold.
Two shirts confirmed sold in the time this podcast has been recorded.
Oh, amazing.
Incredible. They're on Teespring.
These are Teespring all over prints. Teespring.com.
I am merch. There it is.
And it looks great.
It's aesthetic.
It took a long time to make the design because the way the template is
designed is really weird, but it's there.
It's cool. It's dope.
Success, dude.
Fucking sick.
Capitalism, I'm part of the problem.
Have you have you purchased a T from Teespring before?
I got a free sample from Teespring of one of my own items.
What did you think of it?
It was OK.
It wasn't like the best thing in the world, but I don't know.
I feel like everybody tells me that they think that Teespring's T-shirts are bad.
I have gotten like four T-shirts from them and I like them all.
I think they're actually pretty good.
I do. I do get I get like the the V-neck.
I get like the clap.
I get like the premium V-necks.
So maybe I'm getting like, you know, the choice, the choice cuts or whatever.
Well, they say they're bad.
Do they mean the quality of the print or the quality of the shirt?
I mean, I think.
Generally, I've heard people complain about the quality of the shirt.
More than the more than the print.
But I might have heard both.
I don't know.
Because I thought the print quality of what I got was not great.
It was good, but not great.
But I got I got a I got a hoodie and the hoodie was pretty comfortable.
I have not really had any big.
I think I think there was one shirt that I ordered for them with a print quality
was not great and the colors didn't come out quite as like vibrant as I hoped for.
But mostly it's been fine.
So I don't know.
I I still use for not using CMYK funds.
Maybe. Yeah, maybe.
I never do CMYK, even though I should.
Does that help?
I mean, CMYK is formatted specifically to be printed out in physical items
as opposed to being on screen.
That's why it exists, huh?
Interesting, neat, curious, very curious.
I went to college for graphic design.
That's how I know that.
Forty thousand dollars well spent for knowing about CMYK
and choosing not to use it anyway.
Yeah, cool.
Interesting, interesting.
OK, good to know.
I'm going to make a mental note of that.
So wait, we got we got one more.
This is another one from Margar, who called last week.
And I forget what they said.
But here, let's let's fucking do it.
They closed out the show last week, too.
They did. They did.
Weird.
I this was I think maybe this is their this is their M.O.
Maybe they just listened to the episode like a long time into the week
or they must just listen to the episodes at the right time on like a Saturday night.
That just must be their schedule and it lines up.
It's true. But OK, so here we go.
Three, two, one.
Either PCP.
I have a question about the state of the lectures that are yet to come out.
Because I know there are a few lectures that haven't been released yet.
And with the state of your YouTube channel and other circumstances,
do you plan to still release those on your YouTube channel?
If not, what's the plan for going into the future with the lectures?
I would assume they would all be continuing to be going off
by everyone's individual channels.
The only one who didn't do that was me, because a hippo.
Oh, yeah, hippo did, too, with the risk of lecture.
Fuck yeah, because like collectively those brought in like over two thousand
new subscribers to the PCP.
Um, I would assume that.
We were like, I think Digi was going to upload hers on the PCP channel.
I think that was the plan.
And so I would assume that, like.
I mean, best best case scenario, our videos get restored.
We post all the content that we have not been posting there, you know,
retroactively, and then we continue posting there.
And, you know, that lecture, for instance, goes up there.
I think Munchie was going to post his on the channel, too.
I'm not sure about that.
I'm not. I'm not a team player.
I'm I'm an asshole.
I'm I'm bow guarding mine.
I'm keeping it on my channel.
And the the OK, so that's the best case scenario.
Worst case scenario, I guess, would be that the videos never get restored.
But I think even in that case, we're still planning on, like, at some point,
just calling it a loss, calling in as many of the lost videos as we can from,
you know, people that might have them saved, reposting them and then,
you know, continuing to post anyway.
So I think in either case, yeah, the videos that we're going to go up
on the PCP channel will still be going up there.
So, yeah, that's the plan.
And it's mostly just a question of, like, when will we know?
What the plan is for the channel?
And the answer is whenever YouTube decides to do the thing,
it's been saying for a month that it's going to do and that they could do
in minutes, but there's the guy that it doesn't matter.
Dude, it makes me OK.
Let's let's close out this fucking episode of the roundabout YouTube.
It makes me so fucking mad that on Twitter,
they, like, answered me saying the channel has been terminated or,
like, no, they answered me saying, hey, the channel came back,
but the videos are still gone.
All our Radcon stuff is gone.
And they were like, give it give it 48 hours.
We already see the Radcon content back because of that one stream.
They saw that the one stream was was there and that it had the same word
in the name just assumed that that was what I was talking about.
And we're like, oh, no, no, no, OK, he's already wrong.
No, this idiot just doesn't know what's going on with his own channel.
Like, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, the problem is fixed.
He just has to figure out that we already fix the problem.
This fucking idiot, like, no, no, they didn't fucking fix the problem.
And they don't care.
And and I. Oh, my fuck.
Like the fact that the fact that I know exactly and they had a little
fucking smiley face, I'm like, haha, silly, that's not real.
You just imagine that there's a problem.
We fixed everything. We haven't handled.
You fucking didn't.
You fucking ruined it for no reason.
There was no reason at all.
The case was solved.
You you fucked up the first time, right?
Well, we fucked up and then you kind of fucked up.
You took a while to fix it, but you fixed it.
OK, and then you came and you were like, hmm, uh, hmm.
Why don't I just ruin it again for no reason?
And that's what they fucking did.
And now they're like, all being all tweet about like, uh, no, no, no,
no, we understand the urgency of fixing this problem.
We understand that you want your content back.
Don't worry, our internal team is handling it.
Oh, so we already see the video back.
Like, no, it's going to be finally.
Haha. Oh, I hate it, Tom.
I hate them so fucking much.
Yeah, YouTube is a goddamn nightmare.
I mean, it's like I've said it before, but as soon as as soon
as the videos come back, if they do, I'm immediately setting up a library
account, everything will be mirrored on there.
And this won't happen again.
And God in heaven, please stop YouTube is shit.
They can't keep getting away with this.
Like, people's entire livelihoods are on this website and there's
just no communication at all.
It's like, seems impossible, yet here we are.
Yeah, I.
Part of me wishes they would part of me wishes they would just say, like,
now we're just not going to restore it.
Like, stop emailing us just just so we would know.
Like, just so we could be over and we could, like, move forward.
You know, I do think.
The fact that they're they're continuing to correspond
does make me think that they at least intend to fix it.
I think it's giving them a lot of credit.
Well, but when I say that intend, I mean that whoever is sending these emails
probably has faith or at least is paid to present as though they have faith
that the system will work itself out.
You know, it's just appeasement.exe sending emails.
I do think they are written by a person.
I don't I don't I don't think they are fully algorithmic.
There are algorithms are pretty advanced.
They can make reservations over the phone with a real voice
that sounds like a human being doesn't seem out of the out of the realm
of possibility to be able to write emails algorithmically.
I guess, especially when they said there's like basically nobody working
at YouTube right now because of covid.
God, what a fucking dystopian nightmare that would be
if like it has just been a robot auto responding the whole time.
Do you think that's likely?
It's possible. I mean, this is if any company was going to do it,
would be Google, right? They're the ones.
Yeah, algorithmic ties, everything.
Yeah, and now would be the time when like people aren't work.
They don't have as many employees.
Like now would be the time for them to roll out those algorithms
to cover up the work shortages happening, right?
Because like you would think they probably have a thing set up where like
an algorithm is responding to all these emails and mask and then flagging.
And then they have staff that goes through those flags and makes changes.
But if nobody working there, it would explain why nothing is happening.
Yeah, it's just sending flags and there's nobody in the office
to actually examine the problem.
Meanwhile, the robots just like, we're working on it.
We're working on it. We're working on it.
And no one's actually there to do the work.
The. OK, the the weird part or a weird part about that is like,
I don't want to read the whole thing, but like there was a point in the emails
where it claimed to change identity.
This is OK. There was one.
OK, all the correspondence has been with someone calling themselves Martin,
except for one email two days ago, which claimed to be from April,
filling in for my colleague.
This is April filling in for my colleague.
The colleague is presumably Martin.
And they both they both have like a little Google YouTube team logo
at the end of the email, but Martin has a little extra blurb
with like links to like protect your YouTube channel with two step verification or whatever.
It's all very weird, you know, and like that seems like a person thing
that could be true.
But then like you watch their presentation of that like voice thing
I'm talking about, and they purposely add in like they go out of their way.
But yeah, we want to make it sound more human.
So we have it say, um, and stutter sometimes to sound like a human speaking
so you don't get clued in that it's a robot.
So it's like they're thinking about these things.
There's there's there's no way to know.
Like, yeah, I I think it's a person.
But I can't.
I don't know.
I can't pretend like I'm super confident that it is.
We're getting fucking Turing tests.
Yeah, seriously.
That's what they've used this entire code as a baby test their AI message to Ben.
I'm sorry, I keep sighing.
I just caught myself doing it.
I apologize.
It seems it seems worth it in this particular context.
This is a sigh worthy conversation.
What can I say?
I'm just I'm listless.
This is this is this is removing all my lists.
No complaints about me burping, which I also do all the time.
Well, that's funny.
Yeah, sometimes.
And they're and it's based and it's and it's it's Chad.
Mm hmm.
Oh, OK.
Well, I don't know, man.
And we've come to the end of the voicemails.
Indeed.
You got anything else you wanted to any of the grievances you wanted to air
a live on YouTube and by live, I mean, prerecorded,
prerecorded, not on YouTube.
Right.
Correct.
So that's it.
That's exactly what I meant.
I think I think I'm good.
Everything is fucking weird and just taking a day by day as are we all.
Just do the best you can out there, everybody.
Yeah, yeah.
And try not to sigh too much, you know, it's annoying.
Give yourself a sigh every now and then.
Don't bother it all up.
It's unhealthy.
Sure, sure.
There's a health.
There's a healthy medium to be struck here.
And, you know, thanks for thanks for tuning in.
If you want to hear a whole bunch more bullshit.
What's our fucking Patreon?
Patreon.com slash the procrastinate.
Procrastinators.
That's right.
Yeah, fucking fucking join that shit.
Get a whole bunch of get a whole bunch of fucking doodah,
a whole bunch of fucking content for free, baby.
What would you do?
Do we do a bonus episode last month?
The last one, I believe, is guns versus swords, which was deleted.
Oh, right.
OK, cool.
But it's still up on.
Wait, is that up on like iTunes?
Do the bonus episodes go up on iTunes?
I don't know.
They don't. So they're just gone.
So when well, when?
Well, when the algorithm fucking
deans to deal with our problem,
then there will be a new bonus episode every month.
That's when we fucking do it, lads.
All right.
Become a patron and we love you and thanks for listening.
And we'll see you next week, everybody.
Peace. Peace out.
Good night. God bless.
Sweet dreams. Stay.
Whoa.
Stay and stay on Zoom, stay on Zoom.
Bye.