Welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast, and let me just tell you today, if you thought
your grandfather dying was bad, if you thought your dog shooting himself was bad, you are
not prepared for this travesty of pure unbridled misery we have for you today on this Pro Crastinators
Podcast. We have a devilish person just sitting within our ranks right here. We'll get into
a moment here, but before we break out your bones, before we break out your back, and before
we break out your literal tomb that we have here for you today, let's go over the normal
people who you already know and you're so sick of hearing that you might as well unsubscribe
right fucking now. We have Nate, we have Nate, who cares? Toblerone! Yeah, you see that? Stuff
like that, stuff like that happens on the podcast. Your spine is the Toblerone. Okay, go on. We
have Ben. Minecraft. This is what you're getting into. This is today's episode, a hit bone. Yes,
it's me. We have Tom. Insert meme here. We have Mage. MC Mage, new channel. MC Mage. We have
fucking legendary YouTube and my personal hero. How the fuck did we get this guy? Fit MC! How do
you do, fellow kids? Yeah! Yeah! Fuck yeah! All of the fellow kids have MC in their username.
Oh, okay, okay, okay. Let's get into backstory for this guy because this guy is fucking important.
He's crucial to understanding this entire topic. MC is a fucking dope ass YouTube like
Minecrafter who I found myself and I was a fan of for like a year and a half and it was great and
it was fantastic and I can't like just by one day by chance he commented on a piece of the episode
and I blew my fucking mind and I had to like refresh the page like two times make sure I wasn't
fucking dreaming. Here he is. Would you like to describe what you do, Fit? I'm a mind man,
you see. I'm a block boy, as they say. For the past year and a half, I've been convincing people
that I'm actually a YouTuber but I'm not. I'm just a guy that holocausts children on a Minecraft
server. That's all I have. Hey, Fit, can I just, I'm just gonna address the elephant in the room,
just rip this band-aid right off. What are your feelings about mining at night? Oh, thank you.
There's gonna be some divisions right off the bat. Yeah. Your words will scorch the earth.
I mean, I love Minecraft but the community is just something you tolerate, you know.
Oh, that's true. That's true. You know, when you live by anarchy, you can't combat at all. You
can't possibly hope to combat at all. Now, as I'm sure you realized, I'm sure you realized your
viewer, today's episode is indeed Minecraft. And of course, what is Minecraft? No one knows. We have
to consult the only good book that there feasibly is UrbanDiction.com. And let me tell you, I read
a few of these before the show to get myself immersed. Let me tell you that this is like
rivaling on NICE. These are the worst definitions we have to work with. So I'm just gonna read a
couple here. Minecraft, cheap and legal alternatives to drugs. This shit will sap your life away.
Minecraft, a kick-ass game that is being built slowly. The creator is notch and he programs the
game. Not anymore, bitch. I specifically like the words here. Person one, hey. Person two,
shut the fuck up. I'm playing Minecraft. There's like five different ones about it being a drug.
You get the point. It's a fucking video game. I went to knowyourmeme.com and that has a vastly
superior definition. It's just Minecraft is an indie Java video game created by Marcus Persson.
It is a sandbox mining slash building game which the players gather, blah, blah, blah,
various resources combine them, blah, blah, blah, developed a lot of online following, blah,
blah, blah, YouTube videos, blah, blah, blah. It was released during Minecraft, 2000.
Mate, shut the fuck up. I'm playing Minecraft.
A video game. The video game. We need to lay down some fucking groundwork here. We need to lay
down what the fuck is going on. We need to have some frame of reference going on and there's no
better frame of reference than how much of a new fag are you. What update did you guys join on?
Oh, Jesus. If I'm not mistaken, you literally first played Minecraft on a stream, right?
If you go into... Yeah, what channel can they find that video on? Where do those exist now?
Given Gaming, somewhere. One of the Minecraft streams there, Nate, tries to play Minecraft
and he learns about Redstone and he's really excited about various very mundane things and I
laugh at him. That's right. That was like a year ago or something. Yeah, fucking incredible. I have no
idea what that was. That was easily... That was a 1.10 or... Something like that.
It was pretty hilarious because I am a noob. I'm a Minecraft weakling and even I was rolling my
eyes at the things Nate found to be like, huh, it's really interesting how mine can do this and
I'm like, where have you been? It's 2017. When I learned that you could put obsidian in a block
and spark it with a flame and turn it into a portal, it literally devastated my soul on a
deep, fundamental level. I remember the specific update I joined on. It was beta 1.6 when they
added dogs and I played exclusively within a browser. I played only Minecraft in a browser,
which is extremely rampant at the time. You could just upload the files of Minecraft.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. A browser on your computer? Yeah, yeah. Well, hang on, I don't understand.
How did you do that? This is an exclusively 3DS game, as I understand it, and I was going to say
how impressive it was that all this stuff on 2B2T was built on a 3DS. That's really, you know,
that's impressive. That's impressive stuff. I think you're thinking of the mobile hit smash
game, Jurassic Park Alive, where you can go and run across your own GTS world and capture dinosaurs.
That's fine. Yeah, and I remember, I remember, I remember my first moments playing Minecraft
very vividly because it was like a nightmare. It was like a real-life nightmare where I joined
and then it turned night time and then just a skeleton appeared in my peripheral and I had no
idea there were monsters or that like night time was a feature. I was just walking around just
hanging out and then there were very, it was terrifying. It was fucking terrifying and I'll
never, I'll never forgive you, Notch. I'll never fucking forgive you.
I, I think I started playing Minecraft in a browser as well. I think I was in college or
something and I just like fucked around with it and I made no headway and I found it frustrating
and opaque, so I gave up really quick. And then like ever, like once or twice, like a friend of
mine would be like, hey, I play Minecraft, join my server, and then I would jump in for a little
bit, fuck around for like a day, and then give up and I'll play it again for like two years.
I played on, I played on Hippo's server for a little while, a while back, before I think the
server is dead now, but I made, I was very proud of myself. I made a little hut. I just like built
a little stone hut right next to Hippo's aquatic base and I hope it's still there. Sometimes I
think about it like, man, I hope that that little hut didn't get destroyed and taken apart for its
pieces. But I remember the one time that I almost was in danger of getting into Minecraft legit,
it was during the pony day. The extreme perilous danger that is. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. The sort
of Damocles was almost whatever. It was during the pony days when we were, it was in the, it was in
the heyday of the torrent of quality content that was t-bat plays. Oh no! I spent, no listen,
okay, because, because that was around the time that I had just gotten into a Shadow of Israfel
in the Yogscast and I had watched all of Shadow of Israfel and thought that it was the coolest
thing ever. Was it going to be those embarrassing podcasts we put up early?
Wait, shut up. So I, I spent like weeks, I spent like weeks trying to figure out a way
to get a modded version of Minecraft where we could be ponies, we could be phantom horn and keg
standard, and I thought that we could do like a, like a, like a Shadow of Israfel kind of thing.
I'm having, I'm having the flash, I'm having the key, so I'm slaying for views.
If I tried to Google and like there were some like pony mods of Minecraft, but they sucked
and like they didn't, I don't know, and I couldn't figure out how to make it work.
Do you remember? Oh yeah, it was the summer of 2010. I was just your typical college broham
and I was browsing V on 4chan and that's back when Notch himself was actually advertising on V.
I remember those days. Yeah, so he was posting some threads, so I decided to check the game out
and like I thought it was pretty sweet. I'd never played anything like it before.
I thought it was awesome. And then here I am, eight years later, God, literally the most powerful
Minecraft player of all time. Making that sweet bank.
Yeah. Holy shit. Oh my God, the return investment on that must be fucking insane.
It's because you're paying for a beta and stuff, you know, so yeah.
How much does Minecraft cost nowadays? $26.95. I just bought it. I think I paid $20 for it.
Yeah. Why is the price going up as opposed to down? I mean like, you know, I guess with the
update. Well, I think it's probably because when Microsoft bought it, they're like, hey guys,
let's jack this price up a little bit. I guess so. Well, whatever, whatever.
Also inflation question mark? Let's not open that. Let's not bring your fetishes into the
equation right now. Mage, when did you get into Minecraft? Oh gosh, when was Minecraft created
exactly? Like 2008, 2008? It went real in 2011. Because like, I think that's around the time I
got into it, 10 maybe, 2010, maybe nine, I'm not sure, because I remember a friend got it for me
because there was no way for me to buy it at that point. I was still living in no Athenian, no credit
cards, whatever. And yeah, he got it for me. It was like $17 ish at that time. And yeah,
and that's how I got into it. I remember I was the only one who could figure out how to host a
gosh darn Minecraft server with, what's that program? I hate that program. What's it called?
Windows Movie Maker. No, no, it was like...
Mine's over.
Hamachi, there we go.
I host my Minecraft server on my TI-83 calculator.
Yes. Got to launch that Mirage OS first.
Guys, no, no, no, no, guys, do you know Hamachi?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I try to set that up. Little did I do, it was way more complicated than just
doing it normally.
Back then, yeah, Hamachi was like the only way you could really do it, and it was awful,
and I was the only one who could figure it out.
I tried fucking with Hamachi to post brutal doom with some of my friends, like to play
cooperative online, and that was hell on earth, and I hate it.
I'm never touching how much you can get no more.
Well, well, Mirage, that's interesting to know when you got into Minecraft,
but when did you then upgrade your life from Minecraft into one of the many shittier version
clones that you love so dearly?
Yeah, that's shitty, oh my gosh.
I think I've played one with you. It was almost like a weird hybrid, like,
terraria Minecraft weird fantasy fucking...
Wait, pets.
Oh, yeah, like pets.
It was just the pets.
And Mirage, aren't you also big into paladins?
You were the one telling me I was trying to get into paladins.
Oh my god!
No, no, no, no, no, no. I didn't like paladins anymore.
They changed the name.
Mirage, are you the one into angry birds?
Always talking about angry birds this and angry birds that.
I'm frankly sick of hearing about it.
Are you the person who's always trying to advertise Jurassic Park alive or all my friends?
That's a classic. A classic is a classic, my dude.
You guys need to stop.
Mirage, tell us about some of the many fine Minecraft alternatives out there.
Creative versus good.
I mean, like, vanilla, like in comparison to vanilla Minecraft, I much prefer great
gradeverse. It's a lot prettier looking, at least for me.
I like the building aspect. I like the pets I can have.
Like, every single creature can be turned into a pet and I love that.
It's a favorite thing to do.
And I honestly don't know how to sell the game.
Just like, check it out. It's free. There we go.
That's the best seller.
That's a good one.
It's Minecraft, but free.
That's pretty good.
Minecraft, but does everything Minecraft can do, but better than for free.
But better than for free.
Yeah.
And it can host servers so easily, you just make a world and like you host it and there you go.
It's up forever and everyone can join.
Do you offline or online?
You don't have to host it yourself.
I mean, you can host the servers really easily, but you know, there's no one to play with.
You can play it.
Hello.
All right. Who else we got?
Tom.
Tom, what did you first play the game?
Yeah. Oh God.
So I first played Minecraft in 2014.
And I was playing...
All these fucking new fags. Jesus Christ.
I started in 10, so...
So I, my friends were like,
yo, we're going to play Minecraft.
Do you want to play with us?
And I'm like, I've never played Minecraft in my life.
And they're like, well, you need to fix that immediately.
And I was like, uh, fuck.
So they made me buy Minecraft for $20 when it was 20 bucks, which sucked.
We made you a fucking knife point.
Yeah, they're like, dude, you're being...
But we're going to stream, we're going to play weekly.
It's going to be a thing.
It's going to be awesome.
And you're going to be part of it.
Like, okay.
So I started playing Minecraft.
And those friends would go on to become the Yogscast.
If only, yes.
Exactly.
Oh, oh, they wanted to get you in.
Tom, you're like, no, I don't see a future in this.
I don't think it's going to go anywhere.
They're like, well, suit yourself, dude.
My business savvy continues to be impeccable.
So we were going to play, and I was very confused when I started playing the game,
because I'm like, why is everything so confusing?
Like, why does everything look so shit?
And they were just like, no, that's like...
They're like, that's like...
This is not even real life.
Like, what the hell?
What are these pixels?
They're like, no, like, no, dude, that's the aesthetic.
I'm like, but like, there's like these weird, just like,
everything's so patchy and weird.
I don't understand.
And we were playing for like two hours.
And I was just very confused.
We learned to find out later that there was like a glitch with my computer,
and like half the textures weren't displaying.
And that's why I was so utterly bamboozled.
That's why everything looked...
Because I knew it was supposed to look shit,
but I'm like, is it supposed to look this shit?
Like half the textures just weren't loading.
So they're just like, you just have to combine these two things.
And I'm just like, but they look the same.
And they're like, what are you, retarded?
I'm like, I guess.
So that was my one and only experience with Minecraft,
because I could never get it to work my computer.
And I haven't tried since.
And I guess I still have a license floating around somewhere,
but I don't even know how I would access it at this point.
What kind of computer do you have,
where you can't fucking run Minecraft?
Well, that's the thing.
The computer was a quad-core i7, a GeForce GTX,
like 650 at the time, like 16 gigs of RAM.
It should have crushed Minecraft,
but no, it was not meant to be.
How bizarre.
How mistake.
Hey, remember when we got into Terraria for a little while there?
Terraria is like Minecraft, but just better.
That's, there you go.
There you go.
Better than for 9.99.
I'll just say, let's just do the Terraria real quick.
Terraria is just 2D, and it's more fun to play.
At least it was the vanilla Terraria.
It's more of a game game.
That's what I'm trying to say.
It's more of a game, but that's fine.
Okay, whatever.
Let's get this right one later.
I don't like it.
Wait, do we hear about Gibbs Origins?
Yeah, I don't think so.
Oh, yeah.
I saw Minecraft over my little brother's shoulder.
He was playing the Alpha, and he was putting cobblestone blocks around,
and I was like, what's that?
And he said, it's Minecraft.
You should get it.
It's really fun.
You can build.
And I'm like, oh, okay, yeah.
Look, you know, brushing it off, because, you know,
my little brother is playing it.
Therefore, I must be gay, so I'm not going to get into this.
Then I continue to see it, and I'm like, you know what?
That looks pretty fun.
And I could hear the Minecraft music,
because that was from an era where people, you know,
they still just listened to the music in the game.
And I got it in the beta, and I played it forever,
and I love it.
And it's my favorite thing, and I still love it.
And my biggest, like, Minecraft YouTube thing
was always X's Adventures in Minecraft.
That really got me into, like, do you remember that?
Me too.
Me fucking too.
Dude, I remember X-Base.
I remember fucking X's Adventure.
I love fucking X's Adventure.
X's Adventures in Minecraft.
I had already been following him,
because he made, like, World of Warcraft,
like, how-to-tank videos, and I was like, I need to know that.
And I just liked the way he talked and his voice.
And then his Minecraft series started,
and I was like, you know, he was in there on the ground floor,
but he sort of didn't blow up because of Minecraft,
unfortunately.
But his, like, journey through exploring Minecraft
in the early days and figuring stuff out and building X-Base,
it was... it is my favorite.
Hey, I just want to...
Starting to interrupt, I just want to let you know,
I just paid for...
I've been stealing Minecraft for a very long time.
Before this stream, I decided I would finally buy it.
I have just logged in to 2B2T for the very first time,
and looking around at this gigantic hellscape,
and it is... I see Swastikas.
I see Rachel Slurs.
Should we transition?
Should fit give us the rundown of 2B2T?
Well, let's take a little...
I feel like we all...
We can all get into the nitty-gritty of what we like about Minecraft.
I think it's time to transition over to Minecraft Server,
because that's where I spent the bulk of my time.
It's time to transition to Minecraft.
We've been waiting for this for a while.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think all of us can agree that Minecraft Servers
is where we spend most of our time.
I'm not going to play some fucking shitty ass single-player game.
I love the single-player of Minecraft.
There's a single-player game?
It is so fun.
What the fuck?
But multiplayer is obviously where we go,
and Servers are fucking great.
I spend most of my time.
And there's very one particular server
that my friend Mark showed me many moons ago
called 2Builders2Tools.org.
And that's why I found this boy here, Finn MC.
Finn MC, I think you are like a professor.
You have like a PhD in this server.
So please, please explain it to us in the way that you do.
Okay.
Well, if there's any listeners that are not too familiar with Minecraft,
basically 90% of players, if you play through single-player,
you're going to have the same kind of experience.
You're going to build a base, make some food for yourself,
and then eventually kill the dragon.
Well, he has 90% of single-player for most people.
But when you get to multiplayer servers, there's a no pun intended.
There's a huge spectrum of different multiplayer servers
you can play on.
On the one hand, you've got like the kid-friendly mini-game servers
where you're like playing with your friends
and talking about it the next day at school.
And then you've got my side, all right.
Yeah.
The side that is actually really-
The heavier side of the spectrum, if you will.
So for those of you that don't know,
2Builders2Tools or 2B2T.org is the oldest anarchy server in Minecraft.
And I believe the second oldest server overall.
And it's-
Holy shit.
It's a server that has no rules, which means you can hack,
you can cheat, you can steal.
There's no censorship.
There's no admins at all.
It's just survival Minecraft.
But the map is like almost eight years old at this point.
And it is just insane.
Well, hey, I've got a question fit.
I mean, okay, so if that's the case, how did they make money off of it?
I mean, we got how someone's got to be-
If there's no profit motive, why would anyone ever be interested
in doing anything?
I don't understand.
Please explain.
Oh, yeah.
Well, for the first few years of the server, I mean, it was a very small server.
I'd say the most players that ever had, like as an active player base,
was about 100.
And the entire server ran off player donations.
The admin of 2B2T, his name is Housemaster.
He's this really mysterious guy that no one really knows much about,
except that he's from Sweden.
He never intervenes and it only will do it on the most extreme circumstances.
He's just this like bizarre shadow figure that like, I don't,
like how many people have ever even seen him, like in the world?
I have, I've seen a like a small leaked picture of him and that's about it.
Just a picture of the gray.
He's just like, he's like Bigfoot.
You know, I'm sorry to interrupt again, but I'm just,
I am currently exploring 2B2T for the first time here.
I've walked up to a skybridge and there was just a towering wall of lava
as far as the eye can see on either side.
That's just, it's impenetrable.
I have to go back.
I have to kill myself.
Fascinating.
You're going through the stereotypical first night on 2B2T.
You're a new player.
I guarantee you, just wait a couple minutes.
Someone will be by in Diamond Armor, running 100 miles an hour.
I can't wait to get demolished instantly.
I really look forward to it.
Oh, that sounds great.
Nate, I want, it needs to sink in for you.
You are not playing against like the best Minecraft server.
Like, you know, you don't, like, they have Diamond Armor fully enchanted.
That's not the problem here.
The problem is speed hacks and like one of the hills and like running across the map
at like insane speeds where you can't even fucking process them.
Oh, and when you go into the nether, like, like, like people will just be like
right up to you with fucking beds placed in the middle of your sleeping
and like just blowing you up instantaneously.
Well, listen, Munchie, I'm sure, I'm sure that's going to be really effective,
but I've got my own life hack right here.
No, the steak weed, bro.
I'm going to fucking blitz the fuck out.
Nobody can keep up with me.
Okay, that's, that's my joke.
I do weed.
The only way to like see speed hacks properly is to smoke weed.
That's slow down time.
That's right.
My viewers, I get this and I've explained 2B2T to many people before
and they've seen less than press than they should be.
So I just want to hammer this home for the normies in the audience.
You may be thinking, what's the deal?
Eight years?
That's fine.
I'm more than eight years old.
Okay, but you have to understand this.
Minecraft is a game where you can like, you can destroy and you can,
you can build anything.
You have complete like control to like tear form your reality.
And because it's no rules, you can tear form anything.
So just imagine the abuse that these four chain freaks and geeks have done
to not just the spawn area.
The spawn area's got the worst, obviously,
but just like for millions upon millions of block outwards from spawn,
the amount of griefing and like dynamite and just fucking unholy concoction
see people have made over the course of eight fucking years.
It's fucking unbelievable.
There are entire there.
My favorite thing about about fucking 2B2T is because it's obviously like a cruel wasteland
where you'll get fucking sodomized for asking for a nickel.
And that's just the way things are.
Oh God, I got to the top of staircase.
There was an intentional hole.
You know, dude, exactly, exactly.
But my favorite thing is like there are people dedicated to just helping out new fags.
And the two things that are the most evident of that are near spawn,
there are just like patches of watermelon you pick up because
watermelons are the new fag food.
And my favorite thing are the never highways.
There there are near the top of the ceiling of in the nether.
There are just like like two by two hallways that stretch out for like thousands upon
thousands of millions of blocks that stretch out farther than you could ever like hope to
walk in a single set, you know, session.
And they will help you get away from spawn as fast as you can.
And those are like maintained.
Like there are there are people who like intentionally like,
you know, try and keep up the appearance of those and try and fix them
when people try and destroy them.
It's great.
It's a great community.
It's totally crazy.
Yeah, I mean, we even have it to the point where each cardinal direction,
if you're on the nether highway, it goes to the world border.
Millie.
Oh my god.
I haven't played in a while, but I remember they were working in that when I got this.
This is fascinating to me.
Like I'm not super interested in Minecraft as a game per se.
Maybe I just haven't tried it enough, you know, with like working graphics,
but like just the concept of there's a decade of just like culture and society and just like
like custom built around like like a virtual space and how it's just like slowly evolving
and the fact that like it's being done because it's different than something like World of
Warcraft where like, you know, people have been playing forever, but like that's like a static
world where like this is just like everything is entirely user generated and like susceptible
to be destroyed at a moment's notice.
And there's just like this undercurrent of just like some like underlying knowledge
that like the people who've been there forever just kind of understand.
It blows my mind.
It's so cool.
I just want to like listen to it forever.
When I first heard about it, it really, I haven't like looked into this either,
but like Eve online, as I understand it, has a completely organically generated like gigantic
factional system divided between like two huge organizations.
And that's just such a fascinating thing that that can exist in these virtual spaces
we've created and people like really give a shit about it and adhere to it and have
these kind of in groups that are completely separate from the real world.
They're only virtual dope, fucking dope.
Fit, I have a question.
How do you feel?
What are your thoughts on Dwarf Fortress?
Oh man, I have never actually played it, but I've seen it being played and I'm just like,
this game is not for me.
I can't, it's like fun losing, right?
That's the motto.
Like it's fun to lose.
Yeah, losing is fun.
Losing is fun.
I mean, I'm not great at Dwarf Fortress, but I've played, I've played some of it.
And all right, so since Munchy introduced me to your channel this past a little while ago,
I've listened to a bunch of your videos, especially like the ones that go into like,
you know, like the history and the lore of the server and stuff.
And listening to like, listening to like an account of like how like,
you know, the wars played out or, you know, how all these different like characters or people
had effects on the culture or whatever, it reminds me of something that I really like
about Dwarf Fortress, which I like even more than playing it.
Like, I really like listening to or like reading like, like stories of like,
how like a world played out and like how a Dwarven society fell.
Just like a procedurally generated like, story of like a world and stuff.
And like, the like a blow by blow of like how things, how things progressed in like a bizarre way.
Now, I don't, don't take this the wrong way, but bit to be to whatever the fuck this thing
his name is like, he fucking up is literally the Dark Souls of Minecraft.
Well, I'm sure that a lot of servers are like that.
But like, as I was watching your lore videos, I just kept thinking that this world is exactly
like what a Dark Souls setting is like.
It's like a ruined world where there are pockets of civilization that still exist,
and you can seek them out and find them.
And basically the fun of it is like exploring the lore and finding out what transpired here
to make the world into the twisted shell of itself that it is now.
And you're basically the Vati Vidya of B2BT.
Whatever the fuck it is.
What is the name of the server?
I don't know any of those.
Okay. Well, point is it's fucking awesome.
And it's super cool.
And it is Dark Souls.
And I like Dark Souls.
Please, I implore you all check out Fitzchannels.
He has a bunch of playlists.
He doesn't just do 2B2D, he does, you know, he does other stuff now.
But how I got into him, and I think a lot of people did, was 2B2D.
And they're fucking iconic videos.
I especially love, my absolute favorite is of course the Pop Bob video and the Valley of Wheat video.
I like the history of the super weapons.
That was definitely, my favorite by far of the ones I watched was the finally reaching the border wall.
That video legitimately brought me to tears.
Because it was so emotional and like seeing all these people, because like, okay guys,
just so you understand, it is over four million blocks or something.
It might have been four in the ether to get all the way into the final border of the server.
And to get there requires a month, months long real world investment of every day,
walking there with all the most biggest enhancements for speeds you can get.
And when you finally get there, and there's all these people waiting for you specifically fit
to have a celebration about you, this guy that they like love and respect.
All these people were willing to put in all this work to get all the way out there
in order to have a fucking party for you at this landmark event of you reaching the border wall.
That was like brotherhood.
It's fucking brotherhoods with that.
Nate, you know, that's gonna be every single day for Mexicans when they reach the border wall.
Brotherhood.
Walking across, you know, Vipitana, Patalinsa.
That's what they're gonna have every single day.
Incredible.
Just another great reason to build that wall.
Just another great one.
So that they could have that emotional fulfillment when they finally reach it.
We want to be able to let them nether orb hack past the border wall temporarily
and unlock their camera and see what's going on on the other side of that wall.
You know, why rob them of the joy?
We can't. We can't do it.
Yeah, so I mean, I think I'm the only one here besides Nate very recently who's actually played on 2P2T.
And I found out about it through a friend.
And we, like, here's how the 2P2T experience has gone for me.
Whereas, like, I'll join Spawn. I'll immediately be like, I'll have like whiplash.
Because this is unlike any other Minecraft server I've ever been in.
Like, you know, you'll have that pussy shit where like Spawn is like made out of Obsidian.
Like, hardcoded where you can't destroy Spawn.
This, you spawn in some like random fucking cobblestone tower, like 50 feet into the fucking sky.
With like lava surrounding all the sides.
And then, like, if you're lucky, like I was, your friend will show up
and it is fucking fully enchanted diamond armor, like on his horse.
And be like, hey, like, I've come to get you. We have to get out of here fast.
I've brought you watermelon. We have to run before they get us.
So, like, running through the night in this like fucking war-torn countryside,
you have to like search for the nearest Nether portal.
Like, hopefully your friend has brought Flint and like get it as fast as you can.
You have to vaid all these fucking bedbombing terrorists.
Like, like, like run a thousand miles in this fucking scorched hellhole.
And like hopping between Nether portals so you can like raid various bases on your way there so you can get supplies.
Because God knows, like, like he doesn't have the supplies, they can carry two people.
And finally you get you, finally you get to the base.
And his base, like, was like built at the top of this, like, like, how do I describe it?
Like, like, like a chunk loading wrong.
So it was just like ocean and then like very, like, like, hardly cut.
Just there was earth now, like, like, like low chud, uh, a chunk loading error.
And it was being like a giant, like, like Jerusalem, like, like cathedral type building.
It was fucking insane. It was absolutely fucking insane.
And, and oh my God, the feeling that you get, the feeling that you get when you fucking, when you see another player tag
and you can't tell who it is yet.
Oh, you don't know it's friend or foe.
Yeah, you just know someone's there.
And you instantly crouch, but it doesn't even matter because they all have like, like, tag, like trackers.
We can obviously tell where you are, but you just instantly crouch and you start to sweat in real life
and fear for your Minecraft possessions more than you've ever feared for your real life possessions.
Your entire fucking life.
This sounds fun. We should, we should definitely do like a procrastinator's like all go on the server at once and try to survive.
That's a slippery slope, Pipo. That's how you, that's how you get a new fag invasion.
That's how you get a, that's how you pollute and, you know, cancerize the society. That's a slippery slope.
Well, I guess there's an argument to be made that, uh, not to be mean or anything,
but I suppose you probably get a lot of detractors, you know, of the hardcore people, which I can sympathize with,
who aren't too fond of you popularizing, uh, fun, you know, like servers that they don't so much want the new fags to be exploring.
But, you know, you're a historian as I see it.
And so everything you've done is like a chronicling of the events here.
So, I mean, how do you deal with that?
What do you say to people who criticize it for that, if you even get that?
Well, it's, you know, it's totally understandable because 2B2T was born from 4chan culture,
which is very anti anything popular.
Yeah.
Secret clubs.
A lot of, yeah, it's like a secret club. So when a lot of players come on,
they try and act cool by saying like, oh, I hate YouTubers. I hate this, blah, blah.
But at the end of the day, whenever a YouTuber does invade, kind of like what's going on right now,
it's some of the most fun us old players have just by going to spawn and killing all these new players.
Makes sense.
Marsha was talking about bed bombing earlier, if you don't know.
So basically, in normal Minecraft, you fight with a sword and a shield and a bow.
On 2B2T, you fight with beds and end crystals.
Because since everyone is walking around in full protection for armor stacked,
and also they have what's called a totem of undying,
just like a fairy in a bottle from Zelda if you die and bring you back to life,
the only way to kill someone is to blow up a bed or a crystal next to them
and just deplete their totems until they are fully out.
It's just, I still have PTSD from the war of all these explosions going on around me.
And it's like whenever an eight year old comes up to me to start talking about Minecraft,
like I like pigs and stuff.
I just start thinking of my time in the trenches and all those explosions going on.
The bed bomb's going up left and right.
You haven't seen the shit that I've seen.
Have you been able to sleep in a bed after that?
He exclusively can sleep in race car beds because he has no negative associations with those.
Oh my god, there are so many times where I've seen someone race by in the nether
and I knew that my time was numbered and I had to reach fucking safety immediately.
Oh my god, because the nether highways are such tight corridors,
you'll just see an intersection up ahead but you can't properly see it.
So just imagine you're walking on this tight corridor, there's an intersection coming up.
You just see this guy with no diamond armor on, don't even fucking care about it, running at full speed.
You see his tracker come up and immediately disappear over the horizon.
And then you see him stop and look back at you and then you know you're going to start a great chase
unlike any fucking other.
Well hey listen, Minecraft's all fun and games, but it's time to get to the most important question here.
How exactly is Minecraft helping us make Starfleet real?
Like what are we doing here?
Nate, throw it in the garden.
You can fuck up.
I just want to model the Enterprise.
This is such a good episode.
Do you remember that one guy who built a one to one of the Starship Enterprise in Minecraft?
And then Inspector Gadget made fun of him on that mic.
Yeah, I remember that.
How fucking terrifying.
Fit, fit, fit. I want to know.
My first base was this watermelon castle thing I made.
What was your first base you made in 2B2D?
It was a dirt hut because I was surviving on zombie flesh and this was back in 2013.
And then I think I made like a little fishing hut next to a river and then I walked a hundred thousand blocks overworld
just to get established.
Why overworld?
Because you know when you're a noob and you're not familiar with like the nether and stuff
because when you're brand new you don't know about the nether highways,
you don't know where all the little secret shortcuts are that let you get in and out.
So you get that from just years of experience and sort of like mentally mapping out where things are on the server.
Is there like a, if one Minecraft block is one meter, how big is this server?
Like in terms of like real worlds.
Oh, okay. So, well first of all, to give you a real idea of how big this server is
I want to talk about how much disk space it takes up.
Most of the Minecraft worlds, if you plan it for a long time, it's probably going to be measured in gigabytes
like my original Minecraft world that I still have that I plan on is about four gigabytes.
2B2T is measured in terabytes.
It has been played on by I think 200,000 players at least once
and it's just, like I said, the highways go all the way to the world border in the nether.
Some players have walked millions of blocks overworld and it's just all this terrain has been generated
and what you can do is because it's such an old server, whenever Minecraft updates to add like new biomes and stuff
there's these violent chunk borders.
When you go from one Minecraft version to another and then following these chunk borders,
you can walk out hundreds of thousands of blocks to find people's bases.
It's crazy.
Yeah, damn.
It's not like those like 30 million blocks or whatever are like uninhabited.
After you get to a certain point, like, oh, there's just no civilization out there.
Like the top tier players, I'm forgetting, there was a giant city with a bunch of pro top tier players.
I'm forgetting if I can was that Jared found legendarily.
Oh, MC, yeah.
Yeah, MC, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was like millions of blocks out.
No matter where you go on the server, there will be someone who has tread before you
and that just makes it even more interesting because you can always find just little relics of like someone being there
or like a block misplaced or something.
Oh, this is the scariest 2B2.
Oh, actually, did you want to answer?
Do you know off the top of your head how big it is in real life, 2B2T?
Well, assuming, well, Minecraft world, I think isn't it at its biggest?
It's like 60 million by 60 million blocks.
I think so.
Yeah, so just honestly, 60 million by 60 million is what it is because there are players that have generated those chunks all the way out to the world border.
Hypothetically, yeah, so.
I don't know.
It's fucking crazy.
It's nuts, man.
But the scariest moment that I had in 2B2T was I had not played for a while.
You know, I just like left, you know, my base there, you know, I had not played for like a month or two.
Then I joined back.
I walk out, you know, I walk outside and there's a sign left by someone like, like, hello, it's me so and so, found this deserted base, just took what I could.
Nice, nice looking base here.
You know, I left on this date.
And like, I don't even know, like, like, like, imagine coming home to your house and like all of your furniture is just like slightly shifted.
And you know that someone's been there and they haven't done anything malicious.
You just know it's out of place.
That's what I felt.
This person, this person, like, invaded my Minecraft base, like, thanking it was deserted.
Like, they didn't blow it up or anything.
They just came in, they like, like, took some of my diamonds and shit, which was fine.
That's just, you know, the name of game.
But it was just so fucking terrifying knowing that, like, I could have been logged in and, like, he could have easily killed me, probably, because I'm shit.
Like, like, I nearly avoided death by, like, playing dead.
And, like, him thinking this was an abandoned base.
Well done, dude.
Like, like, yeah.
Hey, hey, I just did a quick calculation.
I looked online.
Apparently, a Minecraft block is one meter.
Is one meter is the cannon distance.
So 60 million meters is equal to 37,000 miles.
So I guess you could say that it's roughly, like, 37...
Fuck, let me do the fucking math here.
This times this, fucking times this.
It is one...
Wait, one billion...
Wait, fuck.
I gotta count the fucking places here.
Okay, one trillion.
Three hundred and eighty-nine billion.
Nine hundred and sixty-seven.
Seven hundred and seventy square feet.
Jesus fuck.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You said that it's, um...
How big is the Earth?
Well, the Earth...
I don't know.
The Earth surface area is almost two hundred million square miles.
Okay, well, this isn't me...
Wait, this isn't miles?
Fuck.
I don't fucking know.
Hold on, hold on.
It's really big, guys.
It's really, really big.
I'm figuring this out.
Everyone continue.
In like five minutes, I'll jump in with some factoids.
No one cares about it anymore.
Some mad facts.
Yo, let's talk about how else this game is literally Dark Souls.
Uh, how about, uh, how cool it is?
That's pretty Dark Souls, right?
Thank you, thank you.
That's my contribution.
Yeah, there you go.
Speaking of loading chunks, I remember, unlike, like a month...
I prefer blowing chunks, if you know what I'm saying.
Dab, dab, dab, go on.
But before I left, like a month or two, there was an Elytra hat going on where this guy
was like, like, staying in air with the Elytra perpetually.
And he was going so fast that he was constantly loading chunks.
And so the server would have, like, lag in order to accommodate him loading new chunks,
like, creating, like, generating new land.
And so the server was always on, like, one or two ticks, because there was just, like,
like, one or two guys just flying around at, like, like, like fucking, like, sonic speeds,
like, breaking the sound barrier and their fucking wings, creating new land to inhabit.
It was a fucking nightmare.
It was really incredible.
They're also, oh my god, lag.
Lag is so fucking integral to the history of 2B2T.
People alternatively, like, like, like, like, like, like, the newest and best lag machines
in order to crash the servers.
Yeah.
You made a pretty good lag machine.
Or were you showcasing, I remember there was a video where you were showing off a lag machine.
I think you were at Offtopia's base, maybe?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
And what's crazy is when you come across, like, the ruins of a lag machine, like, on 2B2T,
people consider that like an actual relic, like, whoa, this used to crash the server,
and now it's in ruins, and it's got vines growing on it.
Like, it's just this weird pseudo, like, lore thing going on.
I don't know.
It's just, it's so hard to describe 2B2T to fucking normies.
It's just.
Yeah.
The surface area of the Earth is 196 million square miles.
The surface area of this Minecraft server is 138 million square miles.
So it is smaller than the Earth, but not by that much.
Okay, all right.
It's like 70% of the Earth.
Do you remember that, like, most of the Earth is covered in water, so?
Well, yeah, so it's probably been.
How much of it that?
Most of it.
Oh, okay.
Was Gabe gonna say?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It sounded to be really cute that there were vines growing on it,
because vines don't just grow on stuff.
Somebody has to place them there.
Somebody has to, like, put them there.
Oh, somebody was like, ooh, I want to make these look really rustic.
I want to really make the souping look rustic.
Yeah, that's very possible.
I think they do grow on the south, but now.
I could be wrong.
Do they?
They do spread to a degree, and if they're hanging,
like, they will drop all the way down to whatever block they eat.
So, like, at spawn, you've got vines at sky limit growing all the way down to bedrock.
Fuck.
It fit.
I think I said my favorite story,
because these really are, like, Bible-esque parables that you have
of, like, legendary figures.
Like, they're, like, larger than life.
My favorite is Jang and the Valley of Wheat.
That's just, like, that's, like, literally a Bible story
where, like, this guy meets another guy in the nether,
and they, like, found, like, a city together.
Damn.
Please go watch the Jang and the Valley of Wheat fucking story
on Fit's channel.
What is your favorite story from 2B2T Fit?
My favorite story.
Oh, man.
I don't know.
I know.
There's so many.
There's so many, and it's just, um...
I honestly can't give you an answer right now
because there's just so much, and I have to, like, think back
because I've just put out so much 2B content
and just been on the server for so many years.
I don't know.
How about just a good one that's on top of your head?
I've got to think.
What's the most, like, tragic story you can think of?
Oh.
That's a good one.
That's a tragic story on this fucking set.
I'm going to open the old player vault for this one.
There was a player that joined 2B2T a long time ago,
and this player name was, it was Chris Leighton,
and he kept going around the server telling people,
I'm the king of 2B2T.
You mad?
And he would just scam it.
Yeah.
Well, turns out Chris Leighton used his real name
as his Minecraft username,
and so he was got so hard that he never returned to 2B2T.
And it's just, that's the thing about 2B2T,
it is a very toxic place.
I mean, people have, like, fucked with each other in real life
over a block game.
Like, it gets intense.
It gets intense.
If you join and you have, like, any sort of trace
to your real world identity, you're fucked.
Damn.
I guess they really were mad, after all.
Oh, god.
Oh, oh, this isn't on your channel fit,
but my favorite piece of, like, overall content
that you have produced was a dramatic reading you did
of a conversation between Pop Bob and Jared 2013.
Oh, yeah.
Where they just insulted each other back and forth.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
So it's, yeah.
It's hard to, like, explain this to outsiders
who don't know these people,
but 2B2T before it got, like, quote unquote, internet famous,
was just home to degenerates.
Like, you either played on it
because you had a sick curiosity like I did,
or it became your life if you had no life.
And the way these players would talk to each other,
just saying the most vile, fucked up shit to each other
and doxing each other, it was just...
It's all like the PCP in that way.
Yeah, from the sidelines, it was very amusing.
It was very amusing.
It was great.
And, okay, okay.
It's the 4 Chain community for you.
So there's two people.
Pop Bob and Jared 2013.
Pop Bob was, like, this, like, like, impfenous,
like, like, like, the fucking Griefer.
Like, like, Pop Bob's name is still, like, fucking,
like, ring throughout the cosmos as the Griefer.
He had a lightning hack where he can, like, you know,
like, like, understand where you are when lightning struck.
It was fucking, it was insane.
And I'm gonna show a little bit of my naivete
from what I can understand.
I have not looked into this person as much,
Jared 2013.
What I can tell is just, like, a huge asshole meme-er.
Sounds about right.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
He's just a fucking meme who, like, he's just, like,
yeah, he's just a meme-er.
He did some important stuff, like, basically,
like, I don't think about him as, like, a real person.
He's just a huge meme, which is fine.
And great.
But yeah, him and Pop Bob had this, like,
legendary conversation.
One line says,
Go sniff paint, you brain-dead kike.
I really like that one.
It's just fucking great.
I mean, I could stay here reminiscing about
all these fucking great times forever.
Like, the problem with 2B2D is, it's just so fucking big.
You can't talk about it in any, like, you know, reasonable way.
Like, we have not scratched the surface.
We've talked about, like, maybe, like, six stories here.
Like, that's literally nothing.
That is literally nothing.
There are countless stories that you could make.
You could be 2B2 famous if you really tried to.
You have the autonomy to do anything in this fucking game.
And you could make a name for yourself if you really fucking did.
I mean, that's the amazing thing.
I just, right now, just because I wanted to have a little experience
of playing it, just bought Minecraft,
even though I'd been resisting that for fucking years,
and just jumped right into the server,
and bam, there I am.
It's real.
The legends are all there.
I've done it.
Your contribution so far is probably, like, you know, like,
stepping on grass.
I ate shit and died is what I did.
Humble beginnings.
At the very least, Nate, you've added to that fucking terabyte,
you know, file size.
You are now a new player ID that the game has to keep track of.
There you go.
Your name is etched inside of there for fucking ever now.
What is it?
Memeboyblue will live on forever in those annals.
Memeboyblue.
There he is.
That's what's cool about 2B2T.
What I like about all fucking multiplayer games is just the ability to,
like, with your friends, like I played 2B2T with,
with your friends to just be able to bond over doing some of the game.
Video games, multiplayer video games are literally like World War I,
aka good.
There is no greater way to bond with your fucking friends
than having a common goal that unites you against an adversary
in order to fucking defeat it.
That's just common odds.
That's what you fucking do.
Watchmen was literally based on 2B2T in that respect.
Watchmen was.
Yeah.
Yeah, because ultimately they hold the unite against a fake opponent
so that they wouldn't kill each other, you know?
Having an external opponent is what unites people.
It brings people together.
Yes, basically.
And that's why all of my best friendships have been forged
in fucking Minecraft or fucking, you know, TAF2, all that shit.
It just, it just, it's the perfect, honestly, God, believe this.
It's like the perfect way to spend time with your friends.
Like having, like, like, like an understandable, like, realized goal
and like being able to talk about whatever you want,
just like in this pointed, directed conversation.
It's fucking beautiful.
I love multiplayer games.
I literally, I, multiplayer games are better than skill player games.
That's a real thing that I actually think.
These can be with your fucking real ass friends and doing share.
I, the moments I have playing fucking Terraria or TF2 or fucking, you know, CSGO for a while,
they're beautiful.
They will never be taken away from me.
I don't remember mining coal and mine.
I don't fucking care about that.
I care about, I care about finding old bases in 2B2T and destroying them completely.
That's kind of shit that I care about in games.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I want to know, like, like, who, who, Ben, you are, you are now officially 30 years old.
You are 30 years old.
Yes.
As of today.
Happy birthday, Ben.
Happy birthday.
Yes.
Splendid.
Do you have any memories playing online?
At all.
Or are they gone?
They're fading fast.
Yeah.
Wait, do I have any memories of what now?
Of, like, playing online is the difference because I get the impression that this is a fairly,
like, new person, you know, new age, Gen Z thing, to, like, want to spend time with your
friends in video games.
The multiplayer game I probably played the most of was Team Fortress 2 for a while.
Yeah.
But I didn't, I didn't play it with friends.
Like, I didn't have no anyone else that was playing it.
So I fell off.
I don't know.
Like, I had friends that tried to get me into Minecraft and I didn't stick to it.
I had friends one summer in college when I was home.
I, yeah, I played World of Warcraft for one summer because it was, like, just the way to
hang out with my friends.
So, and it was, and that was cool.
And then, so that was, like, like, playing through the game and, like, leveling up was
fun.
And then I got to the end and, like, I hit max level and it was, oh, time to start
raiding and I realized that I hate World of Warcraft and I stopped playing it.
But I didn't need it anymore because now...
You realize that you hate it once you beat it, yeah.
I mean, that was similar to my experience with League of Legends.
I just played it so I could stay in contact with my friends.
Yeah.
For the most part, yeah.
I played them, I played with friends, friends tried to get me into League of Legends as
well and I quickly realized that I just wanted none of it.
I remember very well.
You played Warwick and then you said, wait, there are other characters to learn besides
Warwick?
It's like, it's not enough for me to just kind of get good at using Warwick?
I have to, like, know them all?
Fuck this.
Understandable.
I played, I played a little bit of Halo 2.
That was my online game back in the day.
Me and my buddies would play Halo 2 because we played Halo 1 for a long time at my friend
Mike's house and we just played the same map, Hang'em High, Pistols Only.
It was the fucking best and then we moved to Halo 2 and we played that all the fucking
time and I hated that I had to keep buying Xbox Live because I'm cheap as fuck.
I couldn't understand.
I tried because I had like two groups of friends.
I had like my friends from like...
Where's the Xbox?
I had my buddies from the comic book store because I used to play like cards and shit
there all the time.
And we would play Halo and then my friends from like school would play Counter-Strike
and I hated Counter-Strike because it was hard and I don't like hard things because
it was...
My computer also sucked ass.
I had to run it like at the lowest setting.
So that was not fun.
So I played Halo all the time and I remember specifically my last time ever playing Halo
2 online because we were fucking garbage at Halo 2.
Like to this day, me and my buddy Mike, I just hung out with him yesterday.
We were terrible at games and despite the fact that we like to be good at games, no
matter how much effort and practice we put into it, we never get better.
And that started all the way back with Halo 2.
I remember the last day we both played Halo 2 was when we were just pubbing, being fucking
retarded, trying to get good, trying to maximize our rocket jumping and BXR and still couldn't
do it correctly.
And then we just joined this random match and these two little kids completely dominated
us and they just spoke Spanish the whole time it happened.
Yeah, it was munchy.
It was munchy.
Exactly.
And we had no idea it was going on.
And from that, we were so shamed forever.
We hung up our controllers for the rest of the time.
You know what?
It's good for a man to know when he's wasting his fucking time.
Yeah.
Tom, I want to let you know that I have PCSD when anyone even mentions the word Halo.
Like, the room fills with like a ball smell and all I can smell is balls because the only
person I ever played Halo with was my cousin who just always smelled like balls and whenever
he would kill me because he wouldn't teach me how to play would just say, ah, sick, you're
shit.
That was my only experience with it.
We learned a lot from it.
The word I would most associate with Halo is, this kid just screams Nate because my friend
Mike's brother, his Nate, because he would throw grenades, but yell Nate really obnoxiously.
Oh, Nate.
Lesson grenade.
Okay.
It's supposed to be Nate, but he would say Nate because he's a fucking idiot and we named
him Windo because at one point he got so mad that we beat him and hang him high he punched
the window of the house and shattered it and ran outside.
Oh my fucking God.
Hell yeah, Windo.
That sounds like my fucking kind of guy.
He's a fucking monster guy.
Oh my God.
The fucking dueling your friends in Team Fortress 2 is the most sadistic pleasure you can ever
derive from your fucking life.
It's worse than real life torture.
I have concluded.
There are many duels that I've done in one.
I have concluded that being your friend in Team Fortress 2 and them screaming at the top
of their lungs trying to fucking kill you is the worst thing you can possibly do to another
living being.
Like no matter the friend, no matter if your friend is short tempered or not, in Team Fortress
2 there's just something about it where they will just try so fucking hard to kill you
with all their might.
Like new friends, old friends, doesn't matter, all will fucking scream at you in Team Fortress
2 duels.
It's not really a similar experience to this fit.
TF2 is just nuts.
I mean, I am not one that is quick to violence, but when you hear that domination jingle
and then someone congas over your dead body, it's really hard to just stay calm.
You know, I've never been able to do that.
I always rage-quit every FPS, every single one.
My friends, I forget what game we were playing.
It was some game along these lines.
And so like the match was over and like one of my friends won and one of my friends lost.
And like the one who, like, so everything was like perfectly calm, like uncomfortably
calm after this like victory of one and the loss of the other.
And that just kind of went on for a minute or two until like a discussion began about
whether or not it was more cold-blooded to be like an up close and personal like soldier
who has to kill soldiers like Kloestrum or if it's more cold-blooded to be a sniper.
And this discussion-
What's more cold-blooded?
This discussion has gone down the annals of my friendship history as one of the most climactic
and earth-shattering moments of all time.
And you know-
I'm sure you must have concluded that snipers are pussies.
You must have concluded that, yes.
Well that they're like, well that they're like the more, okay, see one of the, the friend
who won kept saying like, nah dude, it's way more bass, like get up close and personal
and like fucking just shoot him right there.
But the other friend who had lost like slowly but began to emerge with this deep burning
rage, like it's obviously going to be the sniper because he has to like study him and
like learn about him and like know his family and friends and like intimate, like get intimate
with him.
So obviously he's the one who's more cold-blooded, you stupid motherfucker, it's obviously the
sniper.
If you're killing a million people, all your friends are dying, you're going to be, your
anxiety is going to be so high, you have to be the snipers, obviously the one who's
more fucking cold-blooded.
And then he like kicked the wall and like broke a lamp and ran away.
Not one, not one, not one, like which is cooler or more honorable, no, cold-blooded-
Yeah, it was cold-blooded.
He was more cold-blooded, that's right.
That's right.
These are serious questions, clearly.
Yeah, yeah.
But it all derives, the rage there obviously derived from the game.
I think it might have been legal legends or something, I can't remember.
I still, I said this before about how like I have met all of my like good friends over
like Cube Fortress 2 or Minecraft and I remember the first time that I met like a lifelong friend
that I still talk to to this day, I met him on an Australian furry server that I had just
like randomly joined and he and another person I know, yeah, randomly, they're both like
arguing about like the 2012 presidential election, like at the top of the lens, like
all of the furry add-ons were like telling them to stop, but they just wouldn't do anything
they made them angry.
And it was great, and that's why I met, there's just, it's beautiful, multiple video games
are just fucking beautiful, because all the things that you can do and all the things
that you can be, that's why you come to the Oasis, you know, that's what people say in
this Steven Spielberg hellhole, it's incredible.
In terms of like MMOs, I used to play a shit ton of MMOs, but like RPG MMOs are, MMORPG
is mostly fantasy ones, I would hop from one to another life within a month or so.
I played like, I probably played all of the old MMORPGs that are out there still, if you
have even closed, I think City of Heroes used to be a really good one, it's not a fantasy
one, it was a hero one that was like the best game ever, but they closed it, I'm so sad.
And another one was Shin Megami Tensei Imagine, which was based on the Shin Megami Tensei
series.
Oh, they made an MMO of that?
Is that official?
Yeah, yeah, it was, and like, they changed publishers at some point as well, and I didn't
even know about the Shin Megami Tensei series when I got into the game, everything was like
completely new to me, and it was like, it was amazing, I loved it, and then they closed
it as well, and I was like, sad.
What was that game, didn't like we all play some game with you one time, like we all got
in some MMO.
Whatever many MMO journeys, yeah.
Eatin' Eternal, I'm pretty sure that one was, it was really cute.
Eatin' Eternal, it was a eating simulator, just eatin' eternally, there you go, it's
an inflation, again, your inflation fetish comes raring again.
Stop this, no, do not, do not.
Try to flood this fucking server with inflation, I'm not gonna stand for it.
I know, I don't, stop, I don't have the courage to stop this abuse.
No meme.
No.
Well, hey.
Hey, should we use your questions or?
Hippo's good shit.
Okay.
That he's playing?
Yeah.
Oh, in terms of multiplayer, well, my multiplayer game experience was primarily when I was growing
up with just my brothers playing multiplayer PlayStation 2 games, two at a time.
Things like Worms 3D, which is the first three-dimensional Worms game where you're going around shooting
things and it's like really laggy and slow and terrible, but me and my brothers would
hang out in that and that would be like the way we hung out, kind of, instead of going
to the park and playing the B-ball or the football.
Yeah, fuck that shit.
It's all about the fucking Worms.
We got the Worms, we would build- Fuck basketball, Worms are good, fuck basketball, Worms are
good.
All right, enough of that, but we would spend hours in those like levels not killing each
other and instead using the girder tool to build fortresses, which we would then flood.
It never really became about the game, it was always just about, you know, fucking around.
We would invent this game called, I don't remember what it was called, but it was like
you have to kill yourself over and over and to try and minimize your score, like whoever
has the least points and it would go into minus points and we would just do that and
you can't win by getting minus points, so we just kept going forever.
With that- Yeah, sorry, go on, go on.
The reason I say that is that a lot of my like multiplayer experience was not with anyone
over the internet.
I never really liked talking to people in like RuneScape or World of Warcraft because,
you know, much against like the popular belief, people in RuneScape are actually retarded
and I don't like them.
Are they fucking super geniuses playing like the most advanced MMO?
No, they're actually very fucking stupid and I never liked anybody in RuneScape, I never
got along with anybody.
You need to buy a GF.
Yeah.
They are so expensive, I actually did go on a GF thing, but I didn't buy a GF, somebody
says, I'll be your GF and I was like, whoa, excuse me, for free, yes, and then we threw
snowballs at each other and she cried and ran away and I was like, I didn't know what
I- You didn't treat her right, man, you didn't treat her like a queen.
That was your problem.
I didn't use the right emotes, I don't think I had the right emotes.
Yeah, that was the problem.
Hey, uh, did you ever play the Ratchet and Clank 3 online multiplayer?
I would have, I didn't have- You needed that like extra box or whatever thing, yeah.
I think when Ben and I bought- Yeah, I didn't get the attachment, I played that with my
brothers as, again, it's like a multiplayer, I played with them and it was like even Minecraft,
like we would have our own server and we would like build our own individual towns and then
connect them with like mine cart, rails and create train stations, just the three of us.
Mine, comp, excellent.
And we would, yeah, very good.
And like when it comes to online stuff, like getting into like making friends and like
random people, meeting people, I've always shied away from it, I'm a very shy boy, I'm
a very like baby lad and I don't like talking to strangers on the internet, they may like
take me in their van and I don't like it.
It's only very recently that I've started to just, you know, well actually, I've never
done it in TF2 or Minecraft, making a friend, it's always been through something else like
fucking my YouTube channel or like associating with someone who is also a YouTuber, like
it's, I don't know, I have one person from World of Warcraft that I actually considered
a real friend and I could probably still talk to them.
I can relate, like with all the MMOs I've played throughout my whole life, I never really
made friends, like I think one time, twice maybe, I joined some guilds and made friends
there, but when I cut the game, the friendships just kind of sizzled out and yeah, I never
really, I usually play solo on MMOs as sad as that sounds.
I do too, I like soloing like lower level raids from earlier expansions by myself because
getting a group together is a hassle and nobody is good.
I remember when I first started playing World of Warcraft, I didn't know what I was doing
at a deep social anxiety about like trying to like be good at the game because I just
didn't understand it.
I mean, I played for like two weeks or something, but still, yes, deep fears, deep fears.
Oh, coming back to Minecraft, the only multiplayer server I've ever played on Minecraft was Pixelmon,
which was a Pokemon.
I trusted that I really wanted to do that, but I couldn't get to work.
It worked for me and it was like, I had a blast, it was really fun, it was like playing
Pokemon in Minecraft.
You could build stuff and catch Pokemon and you can like live outside and be surrounded
by like Shutenabu Saber Lies and that was perfect.
I loved it.
Damn.
Nice.
I remember when Minecraft was fun.
Sadly, Pixelmon got shut down because Pokemon people shut it down.
So all the good things in my life has been shut down, so.
Only your life remains.
It was the kids of death for all these things.
It's made shows up.
It's days and numbers.
So 2BPT going to get shut down soon.
I keep saying that you're like a second person that says that to me this week that like whatever
I touch is dead.
He's dead.
Can't wait for the PCP to get permanently demonetized.
Whatever Mage touches turns purple.
Yes.
Oh, God.
There's only one thing more I want to say on the subject of stories of multiplayer games.
Before we move on to questions here.
My earliest multiplayer game memory that I have is Ethan.
We all know Ethan.
We all know he's the legendary person of Best Boy here.
Pukiboy himself.
Yeah.
Before I knew what he looked like before I heard him, I was playing Minecraft with him
and he was like, hey, we should join a tiny chat and then we should like we should like
see what each other sounds like.
So I turn on my mic in this fucking tiny chat, which if you know tiny chat, fucking
press one for tiny chat.
And I was like, hello.
And he was like, ha, your voice sounds gay.
And then he turned on his voice and his voice was even higher.
And that was the beginning of our fucking friendship.
What was building Minecraft gay bath houses and you know, all the associated war.
It was fantastic.
And that's why I met fucking editor of the spicy row pack was through fucking Minecraft
and my best boy.
I love him with all shout out.
Yeah.
So fucking multiplayer games.
Good shit.
That's that's how I made most of my fucking friends.
What is the PCP but a real online multiplayer game?
Yeah.
Where are you going?
PCP MMO.
That's the real question here.
The fucking currency that you can buy stuff with will be the PCP and will be a real cryptocurrency.
It's going to start with the rowdy fuckers.
Once I fucking gamify the rowdy fuckers cop killers, that will be the beginning.
Yeah.
Day by day, you'll gamify it more and more until it is just a real video game.
That's the plan.
That is actually the plan.
It's just going to have so much feature creep.
Like the creature, the features are just going to creep in.
So they're just they're never going to stop creeping in.
Just like creepers, you could say from there.
You might, you might say just like that song about creepers that's like click, click, boom.
I play Minecraft every day, but not at night.
I love that.
I certainly love the radio.
There you go.
That's it.
All right.
We're done.
Jesus Christ.
We get to the fucking questions now, please.
I'm dying here.
I'm dying.
I mean that we're floundering is what I'm saying here.
That's what I'm saying.
Can I tell you a secret?
Okay.
Can I tell you?
Can I tell you a secret guys?
Okay.
No.
I once had a Minecraft channel.
Oh, no way.
What?
Oh my God.
Yes.
Is it called purpleminecraft.org?
No.
It is called Fiddim C.
I wish.
No.
It was terrible.
I think it has like eight subscribers right now.
Is it still up?
It was like terrible audio.
Yeah.
It had like six videos and then I quit.
Well, you tell us a little bit.
Or do you want to be a fun game to see who can get it first?
I won't say the name now because I want to review the videos to see if I reveal any personal
information on them.
Okay.
By the time the video goes up, if it's okay content, maybe you'll be linked in the description
if I remember.
Yeah.
All right.
Cool.
The hunt begins.
Whenever someone brings up that they have like a Minecraft YouTube channel, I always
feel really bad because it's like there's been tens of thousands of Minecraft YouTube
channels that have tried to get their feet off the ground and failed.
And then you got me some mid-twenties fuckboy that just comes along and makes a couple videos
and it just blows up randomly.
Hey man.
Well, that's life.
You're in the right place at the right time, I guess.
The whole Minecraft YouTube genre is like full of people who just make one thing that
suddenly it becomes a new trend like that fucking, the realistic Minecraft with the green
screen hands that we were looking at the other day.
And you know, furthermore, there's a whole genre of Minecraft videos where a guy just
green screens his hands and he pulls a realistic Minecraft.
I mean, if you're putting yourself up against like every individual Minecraft channel out
there, like you're putting yourself up against people who's just videos just like, I welcome
to number 25 Minecraft mining dirt, let's play it today, we're going to spend 25 days
mining dirt.
You know, it's just like...
That was basically my channel.
Yeah, there you go.
But you do real shit.
You do lore.
You did the deep web hacks and stuff.
That's just got a more, more panache, more style, plus you do a bunch of stuff.
Nate, will you please read the pity question from the Twitter, please?
Okay, let's let's let's shift over here, read a little pity question.
Um, what do we got here?
What do we got here?
Please pick a good one.
Okay.
Here's one that's not terrible.
At owl1373, this might be an obvious question, but bear with me here, asks, during the robot
uprising, which PCP member will be most likely to be mistaken for a robot?
Why do you always...
That's a good question.
You just insist.
You just insist on reading the worst fucking question.
That's not...
There possibly is.
That's the end.
Me.
Davoo.
We'll see.
There you go.
Davoo.
Yes, it's Davoo.
No one has seen me.
I could be just like an app on your phone.
Oh, yeah.
Mage could be essentially an AI.
Have you guys seen the new iMage?
The new update really fucks everything and destroys the feng shui.
It's called the touch of death.
Oh, jeez.
No.
That was terrible.
That was terrible, Nate.
That was a good question.
You just had a bad attitude.
That's your problem in life, my friend.
You got a bad attitude.
Happy to be...
Look at John Lennon says, final verdict.
Is it safe to mine at night?
A vastly superior question.
Oh, jeez.
It's not...
It's the most obvious question in the world.
Well, it's a complicated question.
It's not safe, but you should probably do it anyway.
Well, listen.
You know, it is your own mind at night on hardcore mode.
Mining at night is, in fact, against God's law.
But that being said, if you live in anarchy, if you live in a world of madness where you
are hidden from the light of God's love, like on 2P2B, or whatever, no, wait, I'm sorry,
whatever.
Did you actually make a mistake?
I thought that was a joke.
No, wait.
2P2T, right?
2P2T.
There you go.
If you're on there, you are hidden from the light of God's love.
And so, like, I'm not saying that you should do it, but I'm saying that you can get away
with it.
But you shouldn't do it anyway.
It is a sin.
It's, of course, a sin.
You probably should do it, though.
Oh, my God, that reminds me.
A few years ago, there was this troll account on 2P2T.
His name was Build Smash, and he basically masqueraded around as this in real life missionary
for God.
And you would constantly post Bible passages and try to correct people on their, like,
arrogant, sinful ways.
Oh, it's like me when I was, like, 13.
That's exactly what I used to do.
Do you remember Bible Bot?
Bible Bot was an offshoot of Build Smash, and it's like, it was the greatest troll of
all time because you've got all these Edgelord Fedoras, and you're trolling them with God.
It is.
It was the worst thing you've ever seen.
Oh, man.
They just can't resist the bait at that point.
Bible Bot is fucking legendary.
I fucking love Bible Bot.
Not Ethan.
He made a discord version of Bible Bot that's still in the works now, but you can do X-Mesh
Point Verse and shit like that.
It's fucking dope.
It's dope as hell.
I love Bible Bot.
Dude, that's sick.
I'm going to scroll up here.
I have a question.
Yeah, I do.
Okay.
By Giffy or Giffy, what do you miss most about old school Minecraft?
Good question.
The no hunger meter.
I miss the oof sound that Steve used to make.
Is that gone?
That's a classic.
Yeah.
Now it's just a cracking of a bone.
Oh, that sucks.
Oh, I hate that.
How old school are we talking about, though?
I miss, I mean, like early beta.
What I miss is the lack of choice.
There's too many blocks, too many colors.
I can't decide on how to like build my base and I always default to cobblestone and wood
because I'm just an idiot and I can't be able to like plan out how to find and get
all these fucking materials.
We didn't talk about Minecraft the actual game, but I want to put on the record that
I think Minecraft was like pretty shit and like not like fun is like a game.
I love to play.
I have to agree because I've never stuck with it whenever I tried to play it because
I just I would always get in there and then suddenly realize like, wait a minute, it's
I've done this before.
I just got to break some trees and build a hut.
That's why I don't want to do that.
I loved Minecraft.
I love the last time I sincerely and truthfully loved Minecraft like vanilla Minecraft.
I play when the horses came out and my biggest goal was like to make like the biggest stable
with all every single type of horse in it.
Oh, that's nice.
Beautiful.
It was so fun.
I distinctly remember the most fun I ever had playing Minecraft and it was I was like
I was playing single player because single player is superior to multiplayer.
That's gay.
It was just I was just dicking around and then I was just like on the wiki because I'm
a total noob learning about like various stuff you can do.
And I decided for myself, I want to build a sugar cane factory.
Once I decided upon that to then have to explore the labyrinthine system to get like all the
components necessary to make that happen.
To make that thing assemble, I needed like I needed like nether or whatever and like
I didn't even know what that is or that the nether even existed.
So I had to like learn about that and how to get there and construct like an obsidian
portal like having a goal for yourself like that and then doing what it takes to get there
and exploring the mechanics that way.
That is the most fun you can have playing Minecraft in my opinion.
Dwarf Fortress was the same like I never like I would like set up you got to make goals
for yourself.
You got to be like, okay, well, how do I build a farm and then you go and you look up how
to build a farm and you try to make it happen.
How do I set up an army?
You go and you look you do research and then you like try and make it happen.
Yeah.
I guess I never really set had like a goal for myself.
That's the big bump.
Once you get that, it gives you a sense of purpose.
I want to say a thing quickly.
I just I just remembered one single complaint I have on Minecraft still to this day.
Like, you know, Apple is a Minecraft, right?
They were like, they're from almost the very beginning.
If not the very beginning, right, we still don't have Apple pie.
That is I am upset if that's true.
Are there pies?
The community needs to answer for this.
Yeah.
Like pumpkins came out.
I think and there was pumpkin pie or something.
Right.
Wasn't there?
I haven't played.
Yeah.
Exactly.
See, well.
And there's cake.
That's true.
I said Minecraft is shit.
I had one very specific reason in my mind is because they keep adding shit that I don't
care about.
It just blots up the game as opposed to adding things that I actually care about.
Like, OK, back in the old days, there was just like dirt and there was just like, you
know, like stone in the underground, like those were your blocks.
Now there's like different types of stone, but they both look like shit.
Like they look absolutely awful and you would never want to use them.
And they're just like, I wouldn't be opposed to have like a different type of stone, but
just make it look like an actual human.
They're not like a weird AI.
It looks fucking abysmal.
They keep like weird, awful things that I just think are stupid.
Add good things and then I like it.
There's just too much choice.
When it comes to like designing a castle or designing an interior of a place, it's you
can do anything.
Anything now.
You can have multicolored carpets.
Can we all agree that there's not enough purple in Minecraft?
There's scant.
But you know what I will say.
There's not enough.
I will say.
There was another question that is relevant to this.
It was a fun bill asked, what is your favorite Minecraft block?
And my answer was definitely obsidian, even though it's like the edgy, like literal Sasuke
choice.
Obsidian too.
Yes.
Obsidian is purplish and it makes the purple port.
Old style cobblestone.
Old style cobblestone with the black lines.
Oh yeah.
What did you say, Fit?
What did Fit say?
My favorite is one thing you just are adding now for the next update, the Sea Pickle.
The Sea Pickle.
Is the greatest.
I'm not aware of this.
Okay, so they're adding so much new stuff in this update, but it's like too little, too
late because it's been eight years already, but they finally added spears and you can
do a fucking taboon jump in the rain and it's baller as fuck and I've been waiting for
it so long.
Dude, I saw the Trident.
I saw the Trident video.
It was nuts.
That's sick.
God damn.
It's like all this cool shit, but now Minecraft is like going way down a popularity.
It's just too little, too late.
Like they didn't get it yet.
Best block mossy cobblestone.
That's a good one.
Oh dude, I remember whenever me and my friends find like a dungeon and be like, take whatever
you want from the chest.
I don't care.
Just give me the mossy cobblestone.
I only ask for the mossy cobblestone, that's all I care about.
Please, sir, extends out his hands.
Please, sir, just one more mossy cobblestone to sustain me, please.
This cake kind of like a block.
I'm looking at the sea pickle and this looks fucking gross, but like really funny.
Okay, I also like cake.
Actually, I'm not sure if that counts, but whatever.
My favorite.
Well, it's my second favorite.
My favorite block and which I made, like my first 2B2D base was made entirely out of
this material was like melon brick.
I love the melon brick and you can like make your food into like a constructable material.
Well, hang on.
Question, question.
Is that a brick or I thought that those were just literally like melons, like they just
are cubes.
Yeah, they could be used as construction material.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, sure.
Okay, okay.
It's just when you said brick, I thought you had to go through a process to convert
a melon into a brick and that's all.
No, no, no.
Okay, all right.
Yeah, I'm just saying as opposed to like the edible thing.
So it's a literal edible house that you can just eat if you want to.
Exactly.
It's beautiful.
That's sick.
Cakes and melons are the only food sort of things that you can put down, right?
Yeah.
What's that?
Cables.
What's kind of cool about cakes is that on 2B2T when the lag is so severe that you can't
even eat, cakes are the only way to stop yourself from starving to death.
Why cake?
Unless they're a right click and you instantly fill up your hunger bar, whereas with the other
foods you have to have the eating animation.
And it takes like five minutes sometimes if the TPS is below.
So like you'll be trying to eat it, but your stamina will be like ticking down and you'll
just like die before you can actually get the thing in your face.
Yeah.
Okay, all right.
Cake is OP.
Word.
Cake is dead.
I changed my mind.
My actual favorite block is the sign, mostly because of like the history and the memories
that can invoke when you go back to a place that you remember writing a sign in and you're
like, oh.
Oh, yeah.
That happened upon a sign.
The literal words I wrote like five years ago.
I happened upon a sign just at the beginning of 2B2T, right?
Yeah.
All right.
We've come full circle that just said a little arrow not sucking dick 2018.
That was it.
That was a whole scene.
It was good.
Okay.
I feel like everything I said Minecraft is actually the best video game ever made because
of this.
That's what happened.
I remember distinctly saying to one of my friends, dude, you should be able to like write books
like like write.
Oh, yeah.
Wouldn't it be cool to do that?
And they're like, oh, that's never going to happen.
And I was like, yeah, you're right.
Next time you can write in books.
That is a game changer right there.
That is a game changer.
I just remembered with the books one time I had like I hosted a little server like it
was a bit of a role-play server between me and my friends and I wrote the whole story
and they had to follow the story and they had to find books to continue the story and
stuff.
It was really, really fun.
That's awesome.
That sounds fucking sick.
Hey, hey, somebody was just talking about a feature creep.
I just wanted to say that a feature creep is literally what completely broke Terraria
and made Terraria boring and shit because it no longer...
You literally have no fucking brain cells left in that game.
No.
No, Terraria originally had a very clear path line that went from like your base house
then you go to like Jungle Biome once you've built yourself up and you've mined some decent
ore from underground then you eventually get to like the...
I don't even remember like other stuff happens then you get like to the fantasy realm and
then there was a linear path that was fun.
The feature creep literally did not affect that.
It made it so bloated and clunky and annoying.
The features they added didn't add any new fucking biomes.
All they fucking added was more shit to do.
The fucking...
The beehive was a new one.
That's one.
I don't know.
That's just in...
That's just in the...
Okay.
That's just a small structure that is inside of the Jungle so you need to go there anyway.
Pasha.
You're fucking fag.
Terraria is perfect.
Okay, to be fair I haven't actually played Terraria since those updates but it just looks
shitty.
Just looks shitty.
You're fucking rude.
Oh yeah.
Oh, I log into Terraria.
Oh good.
I got like the Santa DLC in my fucking chow...
DLC!
Thank you Terraria.
You're fucking dead, Nate.
It's basically DLC.
Only spree.
You don't fucking know fucking shit.
Base Terraria was OP and GG to you, Munchie.
Speaking of Terraria, I think it's the same people who made a new game called Staxel which
is kind of like Stardew Valley and Minecraft had a baby and that's a game I like playing.
Didn't...
I didn't...
Behind babies.
Didn't the Terraria people make like some like...
Some like...
Starbound, my friend.
Starbound.
Yeah, some perpetually early access shit hole that I heard was like a big disaster.
Yeah, I don't know.
Hey, hey, fucking fucking Ethan himself asked a good question.
Oh shit.
Yeah, shout out.
But where do you see the future of 2B2T or more broadly if you prefer Minecraft heading?
Oh, great question.
From my perspective, I've seen several Minecraft slash 2B2T YouTubers switch from to other
forms of content altogether and it seems as though the server slash games decline as
of late due to the over-saturation of Minecraft based content.
Hmm.
What do you think, Fit?
This is a good ass question.
For 2B2T, as long as there's like at least 10 people playing on it and a couple people
pitching in for the server costs, I think it will end once Housemaster just gets bored
of running it.
But here's the thing, Housemaster has a cocaine addiction and he needs to fulfill this cocaine
addiction so he needs as many shekels as he can get with all the players on 2B2T.
He will run this as long as he can, but Minecraft itself, I actually think because it's just
a game that you can put on any platform at this point, I think I see it like still being
played by a somewhat relatively large player base for years to come, I would say.
I agree.
I don't think it's going anywhere.
I think that the decline of popularity is actually fucking great for specifically 2B2T
because no one wants to deal with the queues.
That's like the major thing, they like remove the veteran queue I think I haven't played
in a while.
But the main thing is, because 2B2T, a lot of people want to join it, but also it's
not a huge servering thing so you can't have any people on it at once, there's a queue
to get in so you can be put in a 100 player queue and eventually that will tick down and
then when it's your turn you can get inside the server and you can stay there for as
long as you want.
But anyway, the main thing that I think is good is that once 2B2T becomes a niche thing,
I think Minecraft is kind of heading like just generally, obviously it will still be
a big game but it's nowhere near the popularity it had and eventually it will die the death
just became like a niche game.
That will be great because then the community will be small again and you'll just be able
to have that rich, small, you know everyone on the server and you know what their deal
is.
That's great and I love that and I miss that because I joined before the Russia invasion
and stuff.
So I really miss that a small, you know like 30 players on at a time in the middle of the
night.
I miss that and I think it will be good.
Hey, I got two questions here to read, they're very important.
Okay, these won't take long.
First, meme manifest asks a question, do you agree that Minecraft sex mods should make the
boobs more seeable?
Fit?
Would you care to comment?
Like wait, I was reading a statistic, wasn't it like back in 2014 on point hub like Minecraft
was one of the most searched terms, like what the fuck?
It's incredible.
I think if this guy doesn't like the way the boobs look in the Minecraft sex mods, he needs
to get on it and fill that demand himself.
He should be the change he wants to see.
Well you know what, to be fair meme manifest is asking if they should be more seeable.
So I guess it's a taste question he's asking here.
I don't know, it's up to you man.
Why would you have a sex mod?
Have multiple mods man, make a boob slider, you know, let us choose.
Artificial Academy 2 mod for Minecraft.
For Minecraft, yeah.
Oh my god, you know what artificial academy is?
Of course.
What a legend.
Um, Mozilla Fennekin asks another question.
Do you even lift FitMC?
Do you even lift?
Oh god, well I mean Nate, you and I are both browsers of the infamous Fit board.
Infamous, that's right.
When I first made my channel a couple years back, I'm like well, I play Minecraft but
unlike most Minecraft players, I actually go to the fucking gym, I just call myself FitMC
and then like, at first my fans were like oh there's probably some fat guy in his forties,
like he's just playing Minecraft all day and then I did my face reveal and they were just
like flabbergasted.
Yep, yep.
Got him.
Dad's on those haters.
Like a true Fit boy, I have an Instagram account too so I have to.
Of course.
Yeah, you have to.
Congrats.
You know, there was the original title for this episode was going to be fitness and
Minecraft.
There's going to be a double topic, extravaganza for FitMC, unfortunately that's lost to the
wins of time.
But you might just be on the fitness and have FitMC back.
Oh, that would be legendary.
Yeah, if you're fucking lucky because you can play your cards right.
All these questions are true.
I have a question.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
By Smickelkun, which do you like more, mining or crafting?
For me, it's definitely crafting.
I love crafting.
I like making things.
But how does one craft without previously mining?
That's a chicken and an egg problem here.
No, no.
See, what do you like more?
It doesn't mean you can't do the other one.
I assume crafting includes building and architecture.
I prefer the crafting.
I think I lean more towards the mining personally because you know I'm a guy who loves grinding
in video games and mining is just like your death.
When you're mining, you can just be mindlessly doing that while listening to some Let's Play
or just content online or something, whatever, man, podcast.
Mining is just like some chill, just tune out and just start whacking blocks and then
with the occasional little dopamine rush when you find something good.
You're always mining for a purpose.
You've always got that.
But when you're in the eight hour grind of mining out your expansive underwater pleasure
dome, then it's nice to just zen out and do that.
I have listened to entire podcasts from beginning to end of an entire podcast while mining.
Sure, me too.
The problem with mining though is that you're doing the same repetitive task over and over
which means you have a lot of time to think and that usually leads to an existential crisis.
Crafting is infinitely better than mining.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
If you've got a lot of demons in your head, you're definitely going to lean on the crafting
side of this thing.
What's your suit?
I think it's those.
All right.
Is anything else here?
You want to say?
I think we're good.
I think I'm good.
All right.
Is there anything you would like to plug here at the end here?
In true fashion of being a fitness slash Minecraft YouTuber, follow my Instagram, Fittemps, Sippy
Cup, boy.
All right.
Sippy.
Hell yeah, dude.
It's been fucking great.
It's been fantastic.
What a great time to have you on here.
It's so nice that you like our content in general and you know, been watching what we're doing
and great to meet you.
Great to talk to you.
Yeah.
I was trying not to fan boy.
Same.
I still cannot believe we have fans.
I just can't.
One day.
Doesn't matter.
Here you go.
Yeah.
Oh, it's so true though.
Hashtags stay humble.
That meme with the woman being confused and those math problems around her.
Oh yeah.
Exactly.
Oh man.
So what should we get at the end of Mages OC with like the fans around it, like the names
and like the ads.
Just do.
Mages.
That's a good one.
All right, guys.
I think this is the end of this episode of the Procrastiners podcast.
It's time for plugs.
There's only one more thing you have to say and that is goodbye.
Actually, there are a couple things to say.
For example, if you like our bonus episodes, which I might be editing into this episode,
I can't remember.
We've got like 12 now, pledged fucking five cheap ass dollars, you cheap piece of shit
to our goddamn Patreon.
We've got, we've got to chill, my dude, Patreon people, five dollars, all the bonus episodes.
What was the last one?
I can't remember.
We just did it the other day.
We just did a Radcon 3 recap.
Right.
We went truly behind the scenes.
The Radcap.
That is what I was trying to say.
There's a little bit of private behind the scenes Radcon discussion in there.
That's good shit.
Plus all the other ones.
So it's a cornucopia of good shit.
And if you pledged as low as one dollar, you get into the Discord chat.
So give us as much money as you please and you get to hang out with us some more.
Hey, send us, follow us at TPCraftSnators on the Twitter.
We do the questions there for free and if you're not paying any money, then you probably
won't get your question picked.
But we put out updates in there stuff, so it's good to follow us there.
And subscribe and like.
Please buy our indie game that we just had developed.
It's called Minecraft.
It's a sandbox game, you know, Boxlebase.
But it's not just sand, there's dirt.
Yeah, it's time to go, everybody.
Thanks for listening and we will see you next week.
Bye bye.
Bye.
I'm supposed to be working right now, I'm supposed to be working right now, but I'm not working.
I'm doing nothing, my dick I'm jerking, myself I'm sucking, I am an asshole, I am a stupid,
I've got a deadline, don't want to do it.