Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be procrastinators.
You can't guarantee that.
The coolest thing about having sex with 28 year olds is that there's 20 of them.
Greatest hits guest medley going on today.
Now you're going to be demonetized.
That was part of the plan.
Is that a pun? Is that a pun about demons?
We were sent here by Nate Bestman to demonetize the PCP.
Defund the police? No, defund the PCP.
Defund the cop killer.
That was part of the cat cake.
Speaking of demons, I've watched Hell of a Boss. You've seen that show?
It's the other show by Vivzi Pop.
That's right, Vivzi Pop.
She did the has been hotel pilot, which is going to be turned into a real show on Netflix or something.
Hell of a Boss is in hell with imps and demons and killing and swearing and blood and gore and sex.
It's cool, but it's on YouTube and stuff.
It's actually really good. I would say it's not just good for an internet show, it's just a good show.
Somebody told me it's better than a has been hotel.
Yes, absolutely.
A has been hotel is kind of like a weird, confusing mess.
The pilot of Hell of a Boss is a bit similar, but episode one onwards, it's actually well written and good.
It's like a good show and it's like, wow, I want to have an imp sona now.
But I don't want to like it.
I think the premise in Hell of a Boss works better than in has been hotel.
Because having a hotel feels a little force.
Why do I give a fuck that these demons want to become good people?
There's really no emotional connection to that.
But in Hell of a Boss, it's like, you can explain again.
Hell of a Boss is a boss of a small team.
And he's the hell of a boss.
And their job is to go into the human world and assassinate people.
So it's like Monster's Inc.
Yeah, except with killing.
They go into the human world, assassinate humans on the request of dead, vengeful spirits in Hell who are like,
I hate my old boss.
That's why I, that's why, and he made me die or something.
So I want you to go fucking kill him.
Yeah, fuck yeah.
They go in through a portal.
They kill him.
That's their job.
But the show focuses on the characters.
Sounds like a great job.
It's a fun job.
It's a fun time.
And the characters are great.
There's at least two Vriskas.
So I like it.
Vriska count two.
Ding, ding.
It dings the Vriska meter twice.
If it gets to eight, then I'll be like, wow.
It's hit the Vriska minimum level.
To be acceptable media.
I didn't watch the Vriska lecture.
The fuck's a Vriska?
Well then you don't know.
Vriska is a character archetype of like a mean girl who is secretly good in intentions,
even if they fuck up a lot in real life.
And they just, you know, it's complicated, but that's generally it.
Is she a manic pixie dream girl?
Is that what a Vriska is?
No, no, no.
She's like Batman but a girl.
It's, it's more, I mean, it's closer to a, it's closer to a, what's the, what's the anime like girl that is mean to you?
Yandere?
That's what it's called.
It's closer to a Yandere, but it's not really that either.
It's a Sun Yandere.
Whatever.
I don't know the anime.
Those words don't mean anything to me.
Sun Dere is like, they, they don't like you at first and they do like you.
Vriska isn't always like that.
I think they just sort of, they have a cold outer shell where they put on like a,
a performance of being the best and being the coolest and being smarter than you.
And it's very like kind of mean, spirited and, but secretly they are like very fragile and emotional,
but they try to hide it.
Rainbow Dash is kind of a Vriska, you know?
Kind of like my mom.
A little.
A lot like my mom.
I could relate to this one.
Nice.
I think I had enough of Vriska in my life.
This is why we needed, we need a Nate here because,
Gotta do the Cheesy Man's mom lecture next.
Yeah.
That gave me, you could do that one.
Oh, you already did it.
Cool.
We needed a Nate here because he's an expert on Japanese.
Colloquialism.
Japanese stereotypes.
I know Sun Dere and Yandere and that's it.
I know what both of those are.
There's two.
Yeah.
But that's it.
I know there's like a bunch of other ones that like, there's like Q Dere, but I have
no idea what the fuck that means.
Q Q Anandere.
Yeah.
Q Anandere.
There's all these.
Q Dere is like QB, like Fox, right?
It's like the anime girl that's like Q Anandere.
It's like the Fox that loves you.
Speaking of anime, I feel like that's a great segue or before we get too deep into the
story.
I want to mention on the episode that Road to Radcon, the book is out.
Eleazar, show the picture.
Show the cover art by Michi Fossard.
Bam.
There it is.
The Road to Radcon book is out.
It's printed.
I have it.
I have a box of them here in my house and I made an announcement on Twitter and I want
everyone to be aware that if you are, if you were a $100 Radcon 4 backer, you must
if you've changed, we'll send them to you.
If you change your address, log in to your Kickstarter account and send us a Kickstarter
message saying here's my new address, send it here instead and then I'll send it because
it's been like a year and a half.
So I think a lot of people might have moved since then.
So I just want to put the message out to everyone so I don't end up sending a bunch of copies
to the wrong house.
Yeah.
I saw you announce that on Twitter and that means you finished the part that you wrote
yourself, right?
Yeah.
I finished, I wrote the fifth chapter which is the longest, it's the longest chapter
by far because it had to, you know, had to wrap up all the densely woven narrative threads
that were dangling.
The longest and best by far, right?
Absolutely.
Well, they're the same thing.
Those two words mean the same thing.
He goes good.
Yeah.
All you need to do is write screw Flanders a hundred times and any work becomes better.
I, yeah, I wrote it and also I guess I'll, I'll try to get a post on the website.
I think I want to post like the PDF version for people to read like the final chapter
because we never published the final chapter.
Oh, I'll post it.
I'll post the text version somewhere along with like the full resolution cover by Mishi.
I was like, I admire this cover.
I was just admiring this cover.
The full resolution that contains the full resolution to the story.
That's, it's, it's true and you get both, you get the, you get the double whammy.
I'll, I'll try, maybe I'll post that like on, maybe I'll post a link on that on Twitter.
I'll post it on the website.
I feel like that belongs on the website.
Okay.
Fuckin' backers, get me your fucking change of address.
Notice.
Okay.
Notices if you need to.
What's left on the Radcon for docket?
What's left to do?
Is it just the dojian and the music video?
The dojian and the music video and the OVA, the crown jewel, the crown jewel, the OVA
with the animated intro.
Oh my God.
It's, it's true.
It's have, it's real.
It's real.
Don't forget though.
All the pieces.
Don't forget about the Brony lecture.
Ah, yes.
Oh, how can we forget?
Who could forget the Brony lecture?
Well, luckily for us, that wasn't on like the guaranteed, this will happen.
So we are conscious, are clean.
It's, it technically, it by the, by the most literal reading of the rules, it is not a,
it is not a quote unquote broken promise.
So it's fine.
Yeah.
You two, you two did the best you could to try and get it out.
So none of the blame lows on you.
I mean, yeah.
I mean, even if it was, I mean, I fucking did everything, I did, we did everything.
I possibly could about that, but oh well, nothing, nothing to be done at this point.
Yes, the dojin is in the works.
We've got a script to look over.
Yeah.
We have a script written by the PCP dating sim people or some of them.
And we need to, we need to approve it.
Ah, yes.
The experts.
I've been, I've been busy this week because I've been moving, I've been moving again.
And I have, with the help of Munchy and Kazi and a bunch of their, their roommates, I,
I have moved into my new and theoretically, I mean not permanent, but like one year, theoretically
one year lease and it sucks.
It sucks so much.
It's, it's complete shit.
Oh no.
The lease or the place.
Oh, well, the lease is normal.
It's not great, but it's a, it's, but it's a mostly normal lease.
The places, I mean, I'm making the best of it, but like I get in here, I call it my landlord
and I'm like, Hey, you told me I can move in today.
She's like, no, you can't move until tomorrow.
I'm like, you told me I can move in today.
I got my moving van only for today.
And she's like, well, you can move in, but I haven't cleaned the floor and I'm like, fine,
I'm off the floor.
So I move in and it's like, the floor is like stained.
It's dirty.
It's gross.
The walls are a little bit uneven.
They're a little bit kind of like bowed out at places.
The paint, it's a little bit peeling.
The kitchen, the floor is pretty grimy.
The floor is grimy, dirty kitchen constantly smells like, like propane for some reason.
Uh, uh, you know, the windows are all kind of like, not tech, they're not falling apart,
but they look like they're falling apart.
Um, well, I don't know.
There's fucking like ceiling tiles missing.
The fucking property manager comes out and talks to us about like all the guns he has
and about like how he was like a sniper and a paratrooper in a bunch of wars that he can't
tell us about.
Cause he was like special ops, secret agent.
Uh, he's got, he's got the fucking POW, MIA flag flying from his, from his like office.
Did he show you his fat cock too?
I didn't ask, but I'm sure he would have.
You only heard about that.
Um, we, we, it went with the thing.
You only heard about that in legends.
Can't, can't tell you about that one too, uh, too much, uh, classified info.
So would you, would you in trouble?
So, you know, I mean, uh, it's, I mean, I cleaned it up a bit.
It's like, it's livable.
The kitchen, the kitchen sucks.
Uh, I don't, I don't like it.
Isn't that, uh, your normal living conditions?
It's, it's, it's a downgrade.
It's a downgrade, uh, the, the location is great.
It's right in the middle of Austin, which is like right in the middle of every bus
line, you know, it's like a good, it's a good location, but I don't know, I said what town
I'm in.
Um, but, uh, everything else is on every door, apparently the place, apparently the place
has bad reviews that I just didn't look into.
I don't know.
I don't, I don't remember, I don't remember it being this bad when I like
toward it.
Uh, I think, uh, yeah, I think it was, it was furnished when I saw it.
So it gave me the illusion that it was better.
I didn't pay that much attention to the kitchen.
I was mostly looking at the room.
So I like kind of didn't notice.
And also I was just desperate because I like, I have to find a place to move by the end
of this month.
And then I ended up not even being, yeah, so I think I just kind of had rose colored
glasses on when I looked at it.
I don't know.
I'm making the best of it.
Uh, worst case scenario, I mean, I think my gut feeling is that this place is run by
like a slumlord who will try to scam me for in whatever way she can.
So probably, I think there's probably no way I'm getting my security deposit back without
like a legal battle anyway, even if I do everything right.
So maybe I'll just say like fuck it and like find a different place and like just, just
say fuck the security deposit.
Fuck my lease.
I'll, I'll leave when I want to, uh, uh, uh, but I, I dunno, I'll have to be, I guess
I'll have to have some more, maybe, uh, if I can even muster the, the strength to go
on.
It must be fucking awful if it's too bad for you.
You do have, uh, you do have internet, right?
Cause that's the only thing that matters.
Actually, uh, actually no, actually I'm, uh, uh, I should, I should have internet or
like some, the other guy I live in here said that we do, but like it doesn't work and I
need to figure it out.
And at the moment I'm, I'm on the internet via a, uh, my, using my phone as a hotspot.
So I'm burning data.
No.
So I'm burning data like super fast, uh, that's, uh, that's not good.
No, it's terrible.
No, it's pretty bad.
You can even say that's, that's mad.
I might.
If I were so inclined.
Sounds like, sounds like the first two weeks on my last place, because I was doing something
very similar.
I was using my own phone data, just to use the internet cause my computer tower just
couldn't pick up the wifi and it was incredibly annoying and, yeah, well I, I, I, supposedly
there's supposed to be wifi and maybe there will be soon.
Um, I don't know.
But I gotta say the guy, the guy who's like on the same floor as me, I might have mentioned
this before, but like this, this place has another room that I also saw that is like
the most terrifying apartment I've ever seen.
It has no windows.
It is an entirely interior room with absolutely no windows.
Oh my God.
Isn't that against code or something?
I don't know.
I don't know the code.
There's no windows.
I don't know the building code, uh, but he's in there and he seems perfectly chipper about
it.
So, I mean, if he's happy, I'm happy for him.
Well, it does sound like it'd be perfect for you, somebody like you.
There is, there is, there is technically a window, but it's not a window to the outside.
It's a window into the kitchen.
So like from the kitchen, if he opens his window, you can like look into his room.
What's the fucking point?
I don't know.
That's, uh, I don't know.
Very interesting design.
It was the kitchen built on later, onto the side of his room.
It is horrifying.
It's the worst thing I've ever heard.
It's terrible.
Well, you see, this is, uh, when you're a landlord, these are like the useful life hacks
you can use to save money and building stuff.
It's, it's, it's too big to be a closet, so it must be a bedroom.
You need to take notes for the day that you become a landlord yourself.
One day.
Yeah.
I should be taking notes.
I should be taking, slumlord.
I'm, I'm, I'm, I think slumlord is the right, is the right word.
When are you going to become a comlord?
Am I right?
Uh, I know.
Unfortunately, I, I was standing on that, the, on the path of like, you know, you got
to, you got to go the dark path of the light path meme and there was slumlord or comlord
and I, I took the wrong.
I took the wrong turn.
You're the little kid in the middle.
You took the wrong turn.
Yep.
Ben St. slumlord or comlord?
It's, it's up to you.
I chose, I chose wrong.
Uh, I chose wrong.
Speaking of house horror, of horrible things happening in the house, I was a fucking, fucking
idiot today and I, and I'll never forgive myself.
Uh, we have a cupboard and all of our trays and, and baking trays and shit are stored
in there and in the middle of the pile was a plastic one and, uh, I was cooking sausages
and hash browns for breakfast this morning and I put the hash browns on a plastic tray
in the oven.
Oh no.
And I melt.
Oh God.
Did it, did it just.
Yep.
Well describe the fallout.
Describe the fallout.
Imagine just gray lava falling down onto the oven everywhere.
Oh, delicious.
My parents are coming back tomorrow.
Uh, I've, I've managed, I spent an hour ripping plastic off of the fucking, uh, shelves in
the oven.
You know, like the greater shelves, just fucking ripping it and I've cut my hands open.
I burned my fingers on it in panic.
My hands are just fucked at the moment and I don't know what to do.
It sounds like a, just a, like a typical Wednesday for me.
Exactly.
I mean, I would, I would say no, I was going to say just, just turn the oven back on and
like just melt it off, like let it drip off and melt off and burn off.
But then like, you'll, you'll kill yourself with toxic fumes.
Exactly.
That's why I'm going to do that.
So I've, I've taken as much off as possible and I'm going to have a go with a screwdriver
and a hammer and try and chisel the bits that are still stuck on later on.
If you have like a metal scrubbing pad, like a metal brillo pad or something that might
be what you need to scrape it off.
It's thick, full chunks of plastic.
It's like as thick as like a Lego brick, basically, just like surrounding the metal bars.
It's really bad.
Luckily, like there was a tray at the bottom with like a heat proof sheet in it.
So like most of it, a lot of it dripped onto that.
So I just peel it off and stuck it in the bin, but can you, can you just take the grate
off?
You put the plate on a grate and then it dripped through the bars onto the tray.
So can you just take that grate out and maybe replace it with another one?
Yeah.
That's what I'm going to do when my parents get back, I'm going to be like, I'll pay
for it.
I fucked up.
Yeah.
If I, if I can't sort it.
Just don't even mention it to him, just like, just clean it.
Make sure there's no evidence of it.
Don't even tell him.
Yeah, but I don't know if I'm physically capable of cleaning it enough.
I'm not strong enough.
It sounds hard enough that I would consider like, fuck it.
Like, like the grate is dead.
I just got to get a new one.
Has the plastic, like when it drooped down, did it curl around the metal bars?
Yeah, exactly.
That's what it is.
There's plastic shell casing.
So there's no way to like lever it off.
Some of them were like half done and I managed to lever it off and like pop it and it was
quite satisfying to do it, but it's just fucked.
It's like gripping.
Yeah.
Let me see if I got a photo of it.
I got a photo of the one that is slightly better and there's just like little bits of
plastic.
This is after an hour's work of ripping shit off of it.
Oh, crunchy.
I think it's just easier to buy a new one.
Yeah.
Yeah, probably.
They're like 20 quid.
It's fine.
Yeah.
It's like what?
Like one big titty commission.
Okay.
You got the bag.
The one thing that I would maybe say might help in this situation other than buying
is if you have an outdoor like fire pit, if you like put it over the fire pit in the
in the in the like the same idea melted off, but like in the outdoors.
So the fucking flat burning plastic gases could dissipate.
I don't know.
Yeah.
So you just you damage the ozone layer instead of your health.
And my neighbors just look over the fence and they see me fucking cooking plastic off
of a sheet on the barbecue.
It's my own goddamn business.
God damn business.
Absolutely.
You could just wave the toxic fumes at them.
Like a big fan.
It's melted plastic.
Get away.
Castle doctrine.
If they look over your fence, you're allowed to shoot them.
It was a complete morning moment.
Like, you know, when you wake up in your dozing, you're not thinking because I went through
like three sheets and that one's too big.
That one's too small.
This one's plastic.
And then just didn't register that.
Just real, real morning moment.
Yeah, exactly.
You should have just done the Adam Ragusea just fucking throw your pizza dough right
on the grate and let it fucking like droop through the bars and just cook your fucking
zig, cook a zigzag pizza, man.
Yeah, I should have just done that.
The hash browns would have been fine.
I ate them.
I ate them anyway.
There was a slight plastic, plastic taste, but.
Oh God.
Oh my God.
So what are you even worried about fumes for then?
Fuck it.
Yeah, I guess.
This is going to be the last Simsies podcast.
Now you're going to be radioactive.
You're going to gain superpowers.
You're slowly dying from the plastic poison going into his veins.
I have wasted, I have wasted many a dish by cooking it and then immediately transferring
it onto a styrofoam plate, which it then melts.
And then I'm like, well, now it's got fucking melted styrofoam.
I just got to throw it in the fucking garbage.
Melted styrofoam is good for you.
I hear it build her immunity.
Why are you spoiling it?
Make it mean to us.
If you eat styrofoam as a kid, you can't get COVID.
I read that in an article.
I used to.
I read that.
That must be why I haven't got COVID.
Yeah, I heard this from infowars.com, so it's very reliable info.
Yeah, and he's on a war against info, so why would he lie?
Yes, yes.
I got my second vaccination.
Oh, finally.
Oh yeah.
Me too.
That's cool.
How long did you go between shots?
Longer than, well, I'm trying to think.
I got my first one in July and my second one a few days ago.
Damn, that's a pretty big break.
Is it because like the availability?
It's weird.
I made my first appointments.
Maybe it was in June.
Man, I can't even remember.
But for some reason, they're saying like in the UK, at least, they say at least seven
weeks between a jab or six weeks or something.
Told me three.
Yeah, I don't know.
I've heard conflicting reports about how long you're supposed to take in between.
Can you wait even longer than that?
I'm sure people would want to get it as soon as possible.
Maybe there's some scientific reason why you should wait.
Well, maybe people in the UK are weaker than Americans.
That's probably it.
They probably are weaker.
I mean, they did lose to Americans.
Mine was exactly two months between them.
The first one, I was completely fine.
The second one completely fucked me up for four days and I felt the worst of seven years.
No symptoms at all from either one.
So powerful.
So invincible.
Neither did I.
I had like a bit of an arm numbness the first time and then a bit of an arm numbness the
second time and that was it.
I had a bit of a bruise.
I had a little bit of a bruise where they jabbed me the first time and that was the end.
I woke up with a 40 degree fever and a migraine that lasted two whole days and couldn't eat
anything.
I had fucking weight.
I had an erection for like three hours after I got on mine.
I had an erection that lasted more than four hours.
I had to go to the hospital.
They complimented me on my massive erection I had.
This erection is COVID proof.
That's what they told me.
You went to the hospital.
They just complimented you and you like...
I wasn't there for treatment.
I was like, you check this out.
Sometimes the best medicine is reassurance.
You go in for cancer and they'll be like, oh, what a handsome life.
What a big strong boy and boom, cancer gone.
I prescribe you a high five, bro.
You're kind of an epic bro.
You're a brofist right now.
Don't leave me hanging, little guy.
Oh, you're going to get...
I'm going to leave you hanging.
COVID's no joke.
COVID's no joke, guys.
Let's get serious.
Oh, my bad.
I'm sorry.
I had a very vivid imagining of going to a doctor's
and you tell them, jeez, I think something's wrong with me.
And then they pog.
They just do a big old pog right in your face.
And it's so inappropriate.
And they're like, what?
You're supposed to help me.
It's like, oh, pog.
Oh, pog.
Cool.
It's the first time I've gone to treat this.
Fuck, yeah.
This is supposed to make you feel better.
I want to remind you of your favorite thing, streamers.
Pog medicine, perfect.
Secure for everything.
True.
Not wrong there.
I think German is the cure for everything.
That's what I did when I was ill.
I watched German for like 6,000 straights.
Yeah, how did the dollhouse go?
I saw some of the first stream of that.
Oh, it was wonderful.
It was really good.
It was beautiful.
It was good.
I liked it.
I jumped in to watch it, and I hadn't seen the intro, and I was like, how are these...
I didn't quite understand how the commands were working, but I got the gist of it.
They made a...
I thought it was pretty wacky.
They made a stream on the 30th of last month talking about behind the scenes of the set
and how everything worked.
That's interesting.
Yeah, it was really interesting.
They got all the people involved to come in.
I might be interested in watching that, actually.
They're doing the whole thing.
They're uploading full highlights of it on German's channel now, so you can watch cut-down versions of it without all the waiting for people to vote.
And then they're also doing a cut-down version of the behind-the-scenes, I think.
So, there's going to be a perfect four-hour playlist of just, oh, there it is.
All preserved in its history.
It's just such a weird concept that I might have to check it out.
I'm so glad we're watching it.
I want a cut-down version of the cut-down version, and then cut that one down.
It just gets better.
That's what they say.
That's the right writing advice.
Always got to cut it down.
I don't think so.
The shorter the better.
I don't think it will.
Yeah, always, always, always.
I thought the longer the better.
Are you contradicting yourself, Ben?
I love Moller.
I do love Moller so much.
Big Moller.
I wanted to Moll me.
He's so fucking smart.
I haven't thought about Moller in years.
I just happened, yeah, I just happened to see, last night I just happened to see someone be like Loll at Moller.
Moller and Rags, and some other guy I didn't recommend, doing an 11 hour stream where they dissect, I guess among other things,
but Jenny Nicholson's I Didn't Like the Joker video, which is like 20 minutes long.
I don't know.
Her video was 20 minutes, how long was their thing?
11 hours.
Was it word by word?
The name of their stream is Every Frame a Pause, so it's...
It's the worst name I ever fucking loved.
They lean into it.
They lean into the whole like, yeah.
I hate that.
Oh my god.
I hope, what's the name of the guy who did Every Frame a Painting?
His name is like, something.
Tony, Tony something.
Tony for Tony.
Tony is a dog or something, right?
Sure, maybe.
He's probably rolling in his grave.
He's probably not dead, but if he was, he probably would be rolling in his grave.
He's rolling in his grave.
Yeah, he's rolling in his grave.
No, the content.
He's rolling in his, yeah, he's rolling in his Sega's editor movie job he has now.
I just, I just, I checked out the comments on this one through, and like,
Asmad Moller fans are among the most annoying people I've ever seen on Twitter.
They are like, they are like a singularly despicable cohort.
They're like Elon, they're like Elon Musk fans, but like, even more petty.
They're like, they're just, they're just there, they're there to get in a fucking semantic argument with anyone
over like, what the definition of objective is, and they will fucking cite sources at you.
You're so bad.
Give me a fucking headache.
Yeah.
I was, I was watching Sean's video about Teal Deer, and I've, I'd watched that a while ago,
but I had forgotten quite how pedantic and insufferable that guy sounds.
Teal.
Teal Deer that is.
Yeah.
I'm not, I've seen that video.
I've seen him.
It's just so like surface level, like completely getting everything wrong and being so smug about it at the same time.
So snarky.
I have seen Patricia Taksin's video about rags.
The other guy who was in this mauler stream.
Uh, uh, they're, they're not good.
But is that, is that kind of like, I can't, I don't know how to describe, like, I think of fedora tippers,
but like, it doesn't really do their, their like annoyance, their insufferableness justice.
Yeah.
They're badly complicated way.
It's a monster sippers, not fedora tippers.
Monster sippers.
Enough of these fedora tippers.
Look at some monster strippers.
Yeah.
But, um, I got, I really hope that, um, they do an EFAT video on, on the one analysis video I made about, um, Amber from Vincible.
Do you guys know about this?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I've seen you get in some arguments of over that one.
Cause there's this like, black girl in invincible and that's a problem.
Right on its face.
We were off to a bad start.
Yep.
Yeah.
Cause she's black and she has like, um, I don't know, she sticks up for herself.
That's, that's terrible.
Oh God.
Can't, can't accept that.
Was it, was it your video that Miss Anthropony made a reference to?
Not, not really.
He mostly was talking about my tweet that I made, the one where I thought like, if you need this character,
you don't have that much really, you don't have that my relationship experience.
And I made that tweet like to purposely piss off people cause I love pissing off people on Twitter.
I think it's hilarious.
I tried to always make one like, one like mad worthy tweet every week cause it's, it fuels me.
You know?
Fuck you.
And then you, you must, uh, you must really love tweeting at Ben because he's always pissed off at Twitter.
No, me and Cheesy, if Cheesy ever made, Cheesy would never make me mad on Twitter.
Cheesy would never, would never do that to me.
I'll tweet out vapors.
Yeah.
Kind of shit.
And then it'll be like a picture of the vapors.
Cheesy knows that I am constantly walking a razor's edge.
And if I were to be disturbed in that, if I were, if my surface, if my delicate surface of the lake of my spirit were to be disturbed in such a way, I would never recover.
Um, yeah, fucking, it's a type, bro.
It's a, it's a back and forth if you want.
Oh God, you know, speaking of which, about like kind of like making people mad, you know what's like the worst kind of like people to like the worst kind of commenters are the ones who like reply back with a fucking essay.
Like with several tweets, like a fucking paragraphs of why your point is bad.
I literally do never read.
I never read anything beyond a one tweet.
They ever fucking reply.
Gabe, I, I, okay.
Obviously last month I talked a bunch about like the whole Chris Chan is trans thing and the whole debate with, with, with Dylan, Dylan Thomas.
Did I, did I mention that I looked into the, like the evidence that people use about why Chris is faking it?
You did talk a little bit about some of the evidence, like the, the, the, the, she said one time that she.
Okay.
Uh, was faking it.
And the evidence was that years ago she mentioned maybe the evidence was that maybe that one time 10 years ago before she was trans, she was like, I'd like to pretend to be a girl.
That's the evidence.
Yeah.
Uh, okay.
All right.
Then I won't, I've said it before that I won't get into a whole thing, but that's my worst kind of commentary is that guy of which there's a, they've started to slow down.
I've started to, I've started to not have to, um, I've started to not have to delete comments every day about that.
Uh, I had my policy.
I didn't, I didn't delete comments just because they like misgender, like casually, like, like, like thoughtlessly.
But I would if they posted a comment just to argue, like, actually you're wrong and Chris is faking it.
Here's why.
Like, no, not allowed, not allowed on my comment section.
Uh,
I can't believe, uh, you put so much effort into deleting comments.
Yeah.
A lot of work to me.
Well, you know how many, you know how many volumes of the vapors you could have done finished now?
So many.
Yeah.
Too busy focusing on, on people who are angry at you.
We could have had vapors 17 by now.
Uh, I wish.
Oh, you know what?
All right.
I could have sold, I could have sold so many copies of mini mice.
I, uh, that reminds me, I have not been listening to any episodes of the PCP except for the one that dropped two days ago.
And I listened to the segment where you talk about, um, going to mice, right?
Yeah.
And, uh, and it sounded, it sounded pretty rad and it got me, it wanted me to ask you.
It was pretty rad and I was totally vindicated because when, when I went to mice previously, I was like, I hate this.
I hate being an attendee.
I hate like being asked to buy stuff.
I don't want to buy stuff.
And I, when I got there, I was like, oh my God, what if I, what if I get there as a vendor and I'm selling and I'm like, this is just as bad.
I like every, like I'm just miserable no matter what.
No, I was totally right.
Being a vendor is cool and fun.
Although I did, I didn't get, I didn't get to like talk to that many other like, I was hoping to maybe get to socialize with more like tablers.
And I only got to do that like a bare little bit and just like the people right to the left and right of me because I was busy the whole time.
I didn't get to like walk around and meet people that much.
But other than that, I was, I was vindicated.
Anyway, what were you saying?
I wanted to ask, like, how do you, how do you feel about, how does that make you, do you feel like, do you have the energy now to make more fucking, do you feel like making more comics because of that experience?
Yeah.
You think like, like, yeah, maybe I should get Vapor's Tria out as soon as possible or something.
Well, it, well, it made me think, yes, but it specifically made me think something that I already thought, but even more strongly, which is I need to finish Phantom's Revenge so I can finish Slime and Punishment so I can print the book form of Slime and Punishment and sell, and maybe sell, maybe sell that at the next one.
Oy vey, you should look up if there's any other smaller conventions in your area.
There probably are Boston, pretty vibrant city.
There's not. Yeah.
Mice was like the main one that I was aware of.
There might be some smaller ones.
I mean, you know, even, even mice was significantly reduced, even, even, you know, this long into the whole COVID situation, you know, due to the COVID situation.
So smaller ones might not even be happening, even if they otherwise would.
But even, even smaller than mice, but mice are pretty small.
The gamer's got a point there.
We had, we had a running joke at my old house where one of my friends, the joke was just that you would mention blue mice at him and he would go, and he would get aggravated by the mention of blue mice.
That was a fucking great bit.
I don't even know where it came from.
Was it Manchurian candidate code word that activates his secret agent training?
Something like that. Yeah.
Blue mice.
Nobody likes blue collar workers, just like blue collar mice.
My housemate, Dan, we realized he was a shithead halfway through the year when I lived with him.
And we started calling him Crooked Daniel.
And he'd laugh it off all the time.
He was a very simple man.
Crooked Daniel.
Yeah, exactly.
And he wasn't the very, the cleverest guy, but it was tight.
Yeah, he was quite crooked.
Was he like cheated, like cheated, cheated cards?
No, he was just stupid and like morally not right in lots of ways.
He just didn't treat girls correctly.
Morally right, yeah.
That's the most British like insult nickname.
Crooked Daniel.
Well, that's a Trump insult.
That's what Trump would call you.
Oh, okay.
Crooked a Hillary.
Like he was so easy to trick on things.
Like we went to a nightclub once and as we were coming out, he was like, oh, that was a great night.
And I was like, yeah, apart from the bit where you kept spitting on that girl and calling her a pig.
And he went, what did I actually do that?
And I was like, no, of course he didn't.
You fucking moron.
And then we got back to the house.
He believed you.
Yeah, I know.
He believed me.
I don't understand.
He believed it.
Don't you remember?
Yeah, I went, don't you remember?
Don't you remember not doing that?
Well, I suppose I could have.
I did drink some alcohol.
That is exactly the kind of thing I would have done.
Exactly.
But we got back to the house and somebody had written Crooked Daniel in, like, fridge magnets on the fridge.
And he, like, ripped them off really angry.
It's the only time he ever got upset about it.
And, like, stormed out his room.
You should have convinced him that he's the one who put Crooked Daniel in the refrigerator.
Don't you remember writing this?
Did I?
Wait, wait, I have to.
Okay, this is a bizarre story about not remembering things.
And I'm sort of embarrassed to tell it, but, like, it doesn't even seem like it's about me.
I don't know what happened.
The first night I moved into this place, I go to sleep and I wake up in my kitchen, in the filthy kitchen, on the floor.
I'm lying on the kitchen floor and my new roommate, my Brazilian roommate, is like, hey, are you okay?
And I'm like, what?
Huh?
And I look around and I realize that, like, my head is on the welcome mat and there's a pair of, like, snow pants.
I don't know whose snow pants they are.
But there's a pair of, like, snow pants that I'm using as a pillow.
And I'm in my underwear, lying on the kitchen floor, and I'm like, no, yeah, I'm good, I'm good.
And I go back to my room and I go down to sleep.
Had you drunk anything?
And I don't know how I got there.
I was a little bit drunk, but I wasn't, like, because I remember coming home and going to sleep in my bed,
even though I was a bit drunk.
I guess I must have, like, sleepwalked into the kitchen and gone to sleep.
And I was just like, I've never done that before.
I'm not aware, ever having sleepwalked anyway.
I think that propane leak.
That's what happened, I think.
I think that propane leak in your apartment needs to get sorted soon, if that kind of shit's happening.
It does.
It smells a little bit.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you Crooked Daniel?
I was feeling very crooked that night.
Crooked Ben is what they called me.
Imagine you're my fucking, you're my new roommate and you walk into the kitchen and I am, like, asleep on the kitchen floor.
I feel bad.
Oh, no.
Yeah, literally the first night.
Perfect first impression.
Now he's asleep longer.
It could have gone smoother.
It's pretty accurate.
I don't know, dude.
Shit was really weird.
I was afraid.
Come back the second night, been sleeping across the, like, the grill.
I was afraid that the next night I would wake up in some other wacky place with no explanation.
It's a cursed house.
Yeah.
Moves you around without you knowing.
Some adventures at night.
It's fine.
Cool.
Jesus.
There was a crooked man who lived in a crooked house.
His name was Ben St.
My neighbors, I guess my neighbors, this house, like, across the parking lot from me, like, yesterday, Saturday.
Just this house was just having, like, this fucking block party.
It sounded, I couldn't really see over their fence, but it sounded like they were, it sounded like an arena full of people.
Just, like, blasting music that the entire block could hear.
Just, like, shit.
It was just some little backyard.
Like, I don't know how they must have packed so many people in there.
But it was, like, the loudest party I've ever heard.
I mean, it was far enough away that it wasn't, like, a huge problem for me or anything.
We almost got arrested for doing that during COVID.
That happened at our uni house.
My housemate was a nutter, and he'd get high and drunk and shit every single night.
And he had about, I think it was, I think the grand total was 39 people over.
And most of them in the garden, but a lot of people in the house.
And our house was fucking tiny.
And the-
This sounded like a hundred, hundreds of people.
It sounded like a stadium chair.
Listen, I had to sleep through these regular parties.
I think, like, 20 people can sound like a million, depending on the amount of alcohol and music.
Yeah, maybe.
It's funny, because, like, two months ago, we hosted, like, a punk show at my current place.
That's so awesome.
And it was fucking, it was crowded as fuck.
And, like, people told me after that, like, there's, like, an apartment complex.
Like, maybe a block away from where I live.
And people in that complex could hear the fucking band, including that fucking loud.
And-
That sounds like a punk band, yeah.
Yeah, we want to host another one, like, maybe a Halloween themed one.
Right?
That sounds pretty cool, actually, yeah.
Yeah, some people shot of it.
I posted this on the Ben St server, so if you're in there, you're missing all these exclusive content.
But, um, yeah, some people were there that kind of, like, recorded the whole thing.
They're kind of like, uh, what's it called, all gas, no brakes types of guys, you know?
You guys have ever seen those videos?
Kind of like a Yig Studio type of concert recording.
Okay, it's like Yig Studios, but good, if you will.
Uh, hard to imagine.
It could be such a thing.
Hard to imagine.
Hey, I'm Trixie the Golden Witch, and I'm interviewing people.
Oh fuck, what's my line?
Uh, the-
Wait, I thought, uh, I thought Yig Studio videos were good.
Yo, Trixie, um, she lives in Southern California now.
I should invite her to the next punk show.
Yeah, you should get her to rap for you.
Look, she could be the opener, like, look, we'll get you free.
You just gotta, like, take the vaccine first.
She'll do it, she'll do it at a loss.
She'll do it at a loss.
She'll drive, she'll pay for gas, and drive, like, 30 hours there and back.
It's not about the money, so.
Yeah, to do the song about Pikachu.
That one's funny.
She has to do-
Yeah, get her to do the Pikachu song.
Okay, she gotta do the Pikachu song.
I want her to do the-
Get her to do the Pikachu song, and the song about how she spends all her money on weed.
But it's okay for song-
Perfect.
Yeah.
That's perfect.
At the show, at the show, there was one band who did the cover of the Johnny Test opening theme song.
Awesome.
Bass.
Yeah, I remember I was, cause I was kinda like, I was the emcee of the night, so I was, like,
running around, making sure everyone's having a good time, make sure everything was fuckin'
organized and whatnot.
And then I heard the beginning of-
You were the producer.
Yeah, basically, I was the producer.
I was the Riley of the night, if you will.
Hell yeah, hell yeah.
Yeah, yeah, the code, my code name.
So, I was just running around, and I hear the opening of the next song, and I'm like,
oh, they're doing a cover of American Idiot, and-
But then, like, they'll probably hear it all.
Wait a second, does that sound hilarious to American Idiot?
This is Johnny Test theme.
I don't even know the Johnny Test theme song.
It sounds like American Idiot.
It's literally American Idiot.
It has, like, the same instrumental as American Idiot.
His best friend is a talking dog.
Johnny Test, the Chad, the Chad to Dexter's beta, if you will.
Yeah.
They have, like, the same posture, too, yeah.
I can see it so clearly, him doing, like, the Chad, the Chad beetle-like stride, and Dexter
just, like, his head down, like, his arm slump, just, like, it's a little squat.
The version Dexter.
Johnny, yeah, Johnny Test's sisters look exactly like older female versions of Dexter.
They have the orange hair.
They do.
They're, like, the labor-fed version.
In some way, or rip-off.
Yeah.
True.
Johnny Testies.
Suck on these Johnny Testies, if you will.
That's what I said.
Yeah, I know.
That is what you said.
But then I said it louder, so it was funnier.
Damn it.
Yeah, true.
Fucking dominant males.
It's technically iterated.
Yeah, get out of here.
It's a man's world.
Don't blame me.
This is a man's world.
Blame the patriarchy.
The real villain.
See, it's fine.
Rampant misogyny's fine if we say it's a joke.
What did I see?
I saw a screenshot of a TikTok of a girl, like, rolling her eyes in disgust, and the text was,
like, me, my face when men complain that the patriarchy they created doesn't let them, like,
be emotionally vulnerable.
True, true, true.
Get over it.
You did this.
You made your bed, and now you got to lie in it, alright?
You wanted this.
You can't complain about high male suicide rates if you're always calling everyone a manlet, dude.
That's not how that works.
True.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't care about high male suicide rates.
That's why I'm okay with calling everyone a manlet.
I just don't care.
That's, um, now that's, um...
Now that's base.
Now that's what you call aggressive.
Base?
That's what you call a cheesy moment.
Took the cheese.
A real cheesy moment.
So what took the cheese pill, finally?
Cheese pill.
What flavor it is.
Cheese pill does what Ben does for his diet.
Exactly.
That's his keto diet.
Cheese pill is like, when you, you know, it's like, you know, capitalism is bad because
we like capitalism keep happening.
A little goblin spaceman might show up and, like, murder everybody.
That would be a real problem.
That's end stage capitalism right there.
That's the real goal.
That's his name.
That's the goblin's name.
First name, end stage, last name, capitalism.
Capitalism?
End stage, capitalism.
That was like a great comic book character.
Yeah, it's, yeah, from a great comic.
Um, oh yeah, uh, let's talk about Villainverse now.
Sure.
Um, did you...
Oh, I gotta tell you my, I gotta tell you my new address for my copy.
Yeah, yeah.
That I bought like a year ago.
Yeah, I gotta send back to my PO box.
Um, you and like two other people.
I don't know why.
For some reason.
Um...
It should have, it should have just gone to my PO box.
Did you renew, did you renew your PO box?
Did you...
Yes, I did without meaning to.
Unfortunately.
So that's $80 down the drain.
You should, uh...
I guess I can get a transfer to a different location maybe.
You should, uh, do the, the items thing where people just send you random stuff to your
PO box and just open it in front of a camera.
I mean, by all means.
By all means, people.
Everybody loves, uh, unboxing videos.
Yeah, just send random crap to Ben St.
Uh, don't send Anne Frax.
Do not send Anne Frax to Ben St.
My PO box mainly exists to be a receptacle for undeliverable, uh, vape, vapors copies
and, uh, endless war pin cop shipments.
And now, and now Radcon, Road to Radcon books.
It just, it's where, it's just where the ones that don't make it to their destination arrive.
Like battered and like shredded and torn up.
If, uh, if somebody sends, uh, poop to your PO box, then it'll be more like a PU box.
A poop, a PU box.
If you got any poop to send, please send it to Gamers Tavern PO box, which is in the description
of every one of his videos.
He's the poop guy, not Ben.
Yeah, that's why I call it a PU box.
PU box.
Boom, there you go.
A poo box.
A poo po-o-p-o-p box.
There's a, there's a lot of different directions.
U-P-P-S.
Poop po-o-box, am I right?
You, they call it U-P-S because of U-P-S.
C-E-R-S.
U-U-P-P-S, am I right?
Hey, pee-pee poo-poo fecal funny, am I right?
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
Base, red held.
I just remembered, uh, Gib, uh, did you already talk about how you conquered Mario 1
on that stream, uh, the other day?
Oh, I didn't talk about that yet.
I played Mario and I beat it.
Legendary.
Mario.
Good, good.
Finally, real gamer moment.
Now, now beat the Lost Levels and then we'll talk.
Now beat Sonic the Hedgehog.
No.
Now try.
The, the, the process of beating Mario 1 was, uh, arduous.
I got all depressed.
I mean, for other reasons, but it was sort of like coincidental.
I couldn't beat Mario.
That didn't have anything to do with Mario.
It just happened.
It was just sort of like, I was sad at the time and it was just sort of like, uh, and
also I can't beat Mario 1.
Oh, you know, guys, I'm going to have to.
Will the horror never end?
Which one of those days?
I came back the next day and I beat it real quick.
Okay.
I was, I was there for the first stream and I gave you some advice because I'm kind of
the, the gamer.
You're a bit of a gamer.
He's kind of, he's kind of a gamer, um, and he owns Tavern, if you will.
What, how long did it take you to beat Mario 1?
Cause I've never beaten it.
The first stream, I'd beat the worlds one to seven and I think it was a four hour stream.
And then, uh, the second stream, I think I'd beat it in like an hour.
So maybe five or six hours, I guess.
World eight is really tough because there's no mushrooms for the majority of it.
So if you get hit once through any of the worlds, you will die and you only have three lives
if you game over.
So you've got to get through four worlds without getting.
There are a couple of mushrooms in world eight, but they're all hidden in, in this world.
Yeah.
Once I, once I knew where the places where they were hidden were, it was just a case
of dodging the hammer brothers to get to them, um, without taking a single hit and then
keeping the fire flower.
It was tough.
It was very stressful right at the end.
I think I got a little lucky with the final jump, but it was very pog.
The final jump over Bowser.
The final jump through the many hammers and fire of Bowser as he jumped towards me and I was losing space.
I could either accept my fate and die or jump and hope I didn't get hit and I didn't get hit.
So I did it.
Good job.
You're, you're now a better gamer than Ben St.
No.
Finally.
I, I, I beat, I made the sun.
I made the sun in Noida.
I made the sun.
No.
You're a polymorphine.
Yeah, but in that game.
That pales in comparison to beating Mario one.
Really does.
You know, Ben, you're pathetic.
You're an embarrassment.
Ben, you're kind of a fucking lame.
You kind of big version energy coming at you right now.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
I fall down the pit and get absorbed by the dark side.
Fall down.
That I also did, by the way.
I played more than to Undertale.
I played more than an hour of Xenoblade Chronicles 2 and didn't kill myself.
So I'm the true gamer here because that game is insufferably terrible and anyone who likes it is a moron.
I, a week.
Well, I guess it would have been maybe a week and a week and change ago.
I went down a big, huge rabbit hole where I was just listening to,
I was just going through all these different games, RPGs mostly,
just trying to find the perfect, the perfect background music to steal for Phantom's Revenge.
I, I, I kind of know that the demo used the cholera theme from Pokemon,
which is a good track and it fits that part of the game.
But I need, I need like, what do I need?
I need, I think I need like, sort of just a, something like that for like the main part of the game.
But then I need like a sad theme.
I need like a, I think I need like two different boss themes.
And then like kind of a sad, like melancholy theme, like fighting Gwyn at the end of Dark Souls.
And then sort of maybe like a happy kind of intro.
If you want the inspiration for good music, you should listen to the soundtracks of Chrono Trigger and Final Fantasy 6.
Those were, those were where I went initially.
I was like, because that's, that's the exact kind of music I'm thinking of, but it's too iconic.
And I don't want it to be like, I don't want you to be like, oh, this is Chrono Trigger music.
Like, like if no one had ever heard those tracks, I would probably just steal it.
Dude, to Chrono Cross.
Well, I think,
Can I get good music? You should go to Beethoven.
You should go to the real musicians.
I was, I was kind of, okay, because I was like, the Cholrest theme is good,
but like there's no, the other Pokemon songs don't really like, aren't really what I'm looking for.
So maybe I could just find one game, like a semi obscure game that just happens to have a few different tracks that like kind of do
fulfill what I'm looking for.
And then there will, it will have like a sense of like musical unity throughout all of them.
And I was, I was listening back to like the Xeno Saga soundtrack, which is very generic.
It's a little too generic, honestly. I'm not sure if it's, if it's good.
If you want a soundtrack to an obscure, old RPG, I have one.
Let me just look up the name because I reviewed the game a while ago.
I think it's called something arc.
It's for the Super Famicom.
Arc the Lad? No.
Shining Arc?
I forget exactly.
It was only released in Japan.
It wasn't released outside of Japan as far as I know.
I spent like, I spent like two days.
I spent like two days just kind of like, I was looking for like other RPGs that were scored by the same guy who made Xeno Saga.
Some of the Xeno Saga soundtracks are really good.
Like the final boss name of it is really good.
I just found the name. It's called Mystic Arc.
Mystic Arc. I'll check it out.
The final boss name is really good, but a lot of the other stuff is very generic.
And I'm like, I don't, I don't want to mix and match too much because like that one's very orchestral.
But other ones that I found were very like chiptune, like SNES stuff.
And I'm like, what, what's the, I guess I, I don't know.
I would rather not mix aesthetics too much.
I reviewed Mystic Arc on my website. It was published by Enex in Japan only.
I played this game back in 2014 and I was pretty impressed with the soundtrack.
It has, in my opinion, one of the best soundtracks for the Super Nintendo.
And pretty much nobody knows about this game.
So if you use music similar to it, nobody's going to recognize it as far as I can tell.
I was, I was the, the, the, the unicorn that I was hunting would be like a, like an NES or SNES era RPG with a kind of epic soundtrack,
but also like a sci-fi theme would be the best.
So, uh, uh, Star Ocean seemed like the closest, but like I listened through and I don't know, I wasn't super like the Star Ocean soundtracks weren't speaking to me.
Very big, very biggie.
Did you try the Fantasy Star series for the Genesis?
No, but that's a great suggest. I didn't even think of that. I will, you know what?
That's a great idea.
Fantasy, Fantasy Star 2, 3 and 4 were released for the Genesis and I think the first one was released for the Master System.
That is a thought right there. Okay.
Have you thought about doing nightcore versions of My Little Pony songs?
Actually, yes. Um, I was, I am, um, uh, what was it?
There were two that I was like, I, I was thinking that maybe like the final credits theme could be a, what was it, um, the unicorn song, the, um,
the one, the song that we parodied for Phantom Reviews, uh, hearth-swarming Eve.
Uh, let the grandma remind you.
I don't remember what it's called. That one.
I don't remember that one.
That was from the, each one of us has something special, has something different that makes us rare.
Um, I think it's from the like season three finale.
It's a good, it's a good song.
Um, I could, I could just, well, you know, if it's a YouTube artist, I wouldn't just steal it.
I would contact them and be like, hey, what's your use policy?
Do you mind if I use it? Do I need to pay you to use it or something?
Um, uh, uh, but I don't know.
Again, it's like, I found like an eight-bit remix of it that is good, but it would be weird if I used like an orchestral score,
but then I had like this one, like any, like Game Boy, like eight-bit mix in there in the mix and like, I don't know.
Uh, uh, there's, there's another one that I got really stuck in my head and I couldn't, but it's like, it's unpopular.
It's not one that got heavily remixed by the fandom because there's not even a single eight-bit remix of it.
There's not a single chiptune remix, which is the mark of whether people, whether the community likes something or not.
It's the song from when the Cutie Mark Crusaders get their marks.
It's, you know, they are mark one way or another.
That's, that song's so good. That song fucking rules.
Uh, uh, uh, the ultimate reward?
No, I think it's called We'll Make Our Mark.
Um, and there's just not that many remixes of it.
I mean, that's like devastated.
That, that's like a post-peak brony art stuff.
It's slightly, slightly post-peak.
Yeah, but not like post-fandom death or anything.
This is years, years, that was, that was years.
I mean, that was when I was still watching and I fell off like before a lot of people did.
Um, I don't know, I've had, I've had that song stuck in my head for at least a week now.
It's a masterpiece. It gives me goosebumps.
You can actually go from a serious style to like an eight-bit style because the final boss theme for Earthbound,
it starts off with like an intense complex rock tune and then it slowly morphs into like a eight-bit chiptune thing.
I always really liked that particular song for that reason.
I recommend stealing music from shitty licensed Game Boy Advance games.
Like this. Like robots.
Yeah, I just, I just listened to, yeah, listened to the robots theme. It's really, it's last.
Yeah, nobody's gonna recognize this.
The other, the other song that I was, the other eight-bit remix I was thinking,
maybe I should put this in the game, was the eight-bit mix of a, of a big iron.
Because I realized that the story of Phantom's Revenge is basically the story of Big Iron.
It's the story of a stranger come to down to do some business with a big iron on his hip.
Uh, I was like, it's perfect.
The iron is a katana.
The iron, the iron is a katana and it's called, it's named Platinum.
So it's like, it doesn't quite fit, but like it's, it's pretty, it's close enough.
And it's made of Japanese folded steel.
Kind of like.
Which contains iron.
So, you know.
Kind of like.
I play Dwarf Fortress. I know what iron, what iron makes.
Kind of like how in cowboy movies or rip-offs of samurai movies,
you are taking the cowboy and then you're ripping it off with your samurai pony.
That's right.
Great artist steel.
It's the logical progression.
From samurai to cowboy to pony samurai.
You know what they say, uh,
imitation is a sincerest form of flattery.
And that's why you should steal the robots.
There's only so many, there's only so many stories.
There's only seven stories that humans have ever told.
And one of them is, is big iron.
I don't want to think about that seven stories thing.
I had to write a dissertation for university and it was 8,000 words talking about that shit.
And it made me fucking miserable.
Just right, just right big iron.
I got two, I got two of those, I got two of those 8,000 words for you right now.
Big iron.
You're welcome.
Yeah, every story.
Yeah, it's called the Bible.
Just write that.
Actually it's the mono myth from Joseph Campbell's book,
The Hero of the Thousand Faces.
Thank you very much.
Mono.
Mono myth.
Mix yourself some bitches.
More like mono is a hoax to, I don't know, get COVID vaccines?
There's no mono vaccine.
There was the burgeoning of a joke there.
Somewhere in there.
You were getting close.
Oh man.
If you ever get sick with mono, just switch to stereo.
I rewatched the Noah Caldwell-Gervais video
where he goes through the Knights of the Old Republic games and talks.
He read the original mono myth essay by what's his name.
And then he, by Joseph Campbell, and he goes through the Knights of the Old Republic games
and he explains like, wow, it's not so much that the mono myth was a thing
that is just in all stories that Lucas used as a template for Star Wars.
It's that like, Lucas took the literal wording of that specific essay
just like outlining the mono myth and like literally made it into the movies.
And that's literally what Star Wars is.
That's why George Lucas is a genius.
I mean, he's rich and you're not, so you don't get to criticize.
But wealth is a sign of greatness, isn't it?
And it works in reverse too.
That's something sad, that's something sad that happened this week.
Me and my friend got drunk and we watched episode three.
And the saddest moment I've had in a few years was,
I was realizing that the prequels are nowhere near as funny as I thought they were.
They're just boring and bad.
Yeah.
If you watch the Plinkit reviews too many times,
you just sort of associate those funny moments with the thing
and you actually watch it and it's like, oh yeah.
He's not here with me.
Okay, speaking of, I watched, I watched this at the Munchie house,
aka the Munchhausen as I am calling it in my head.
I watched, not the original Pokemon movie,
but we watched the 3D remake of the Pokemon the first movie.
The fuck, I didn't know that was a 3D remake.
Yeah, I saw the ads for, or I saw that it was being made a while ago.
I didn't know it actually got made, but there it was, on Netflix.
And we were like, whoa, and we watched it.
And it's so fucking bad.
It's so fucking bad.
I can't believe it.
I felt so...
And what 3D, is it like Detective Pikachu 3D or CG video game?
I haven't seen that 3D.
It's very plasticky 3D.
Is it like a Berserk, the new Berserk anime?
No, it's...
Have you seen that loop in the third, like Traders to that loop in the third movie,
where it's like CG but like looks nice?
It's like that except the designs are terrible
because they're the original 2D Pokemon designs and they do not work in 3D.
Oh my god, alright.
Yes.
Even just the thumbnail on this.
They also, they're...
Yes.
That does look pretty bad.
But there's a thing.
You could tell that they bought the rights to some very expensive and high-end smoke and flame effects.
And there's this same, very similar smoke effect that every fire attack
and every time there's an explosion,
you can tell they're using the same plug-in to do the effect.
They were really proud of it and they lean on it really heavily.
This looks awful.
It does look pretty bad.
Those stupidly long Sugimori eyes.
Like where the eyes are really, really tall.
That just does not work in 3D.
They really don't.
But like...
Okay, they changed...
I know they changed some things because I know
that in the original,
they have the iconic scene where Ash makes the joke about the Minnesota Vikings.
And there's no...
And Jesse and James don't dress up as Vikings in this version.
So it's not like exactly one-to-one.
Yeah, I know.
It's a shame.
But it's mostly the same.
And it's just so funny how like Mewtwo...
Literally, the plot of the movie is
they get invited to a place
and they go there and there's a fight
and that's the movie.
That's the movie.
Mewtwo just builds...
There's no reason why Mewtwo builds a castle.
He just...
I guess he just felt like it.
He's like,
I'm gonna do this weird thing.
I'm gonna get some strong Pokemon
by like inviting just some random people to my island and cloning them.
And then we'll have a big slap fight.
He wants to build a kingdom of the clones
because he feels left out of the world, I guess.
Yeah, he wants Pokemon deserved to rule the world
and I'll get the strongest ones
and I'll kill the humans.
That's the...
No, it's not.
It's just sort of mostly fighting.
He could get and clone Pokemon so easily.
Like the whole beginning of the movie
is a montage of him...
I think this is new to the remake,
but there's a whole montage of him
basically stealing Pokemon for Team Rocket.
He kidnaps so many Pokemon.
So there's no problem for him
to just go out and get as many as he wants.
He's the strongest Pokemon.
He could get them,
but instead he does this stupid thing
where he does this fucking like,
oh, come to my fucking castle,
yee, yee trainers,
and behold my majesty.
So they can have a set in for that first Pokemon movie in 19...
He wants an army.
It's bizarre and he builds like an evil castle.
It's like, why did you do that?
Why did you have to make like a big evil castle?
Because he's a villain.
Who are you trying to impress?
They do do that.
Why did you put a windmill on your dark castle, Mewtwo?
Like what does the windmill power?
How is it...
It's the computer screens.
Oh my god.
Why is...
He's...
Is that Jerma?
Yeah.
He's doing the Jerma face.
He looks like that Dragon Quest movie except that rule.
Oh god, that fucking me and that movie,
oh god, we have history.
Yeah, not the ending of that movie, my god.
I just couldn't...
I just kept thinking like,
my parents, I think my mom,
took me to see that Pokemon movie in theaters as a little kid
and I just couldn't think,
she must have been so bored.
Like this is so boring.
The plot like...
I remember when...
Half the movie, wait, let me finish.
Half the movie is they're having a fucking slap fight in slow motion
and like the unimportant side characters are just observing being like,
oh, why are they fighting?
Watch someone slap each other.
Oh, living beings fight with each other.
Slow motion slap.
Oh, but why are they fighting?
They're both living beings.
Slow motion slap.
Oh, because living beings,
they compete.
Slow motion slap.
Oh, but don't they know that they live in the world together with one another
and are both living beings?
Can we just get along?
It's really just like,
why can't we just all get along the movie?
Well, it's a typical neoliberal propaganda.
It's you set up a conflict where a bunch of people are mind controlled
to fight each other
and then you opine philosophic on like,
oh, why must living beings fight each other?
Because you fucking mind controlled them to do that.
These are like hypnotized clones
that you made specifically to do this.
This doesn't make any point.
Once I had started playing the Pokemon games,
I went back on the movie
and I was like, why are they fighting their clones?
Shouldn't they team up against the ones they're super effective against?
What's the point of all this?
They just do it.
They just slow fight each other because it's symbolic.
The point of the movie is just that Mewtwo is cool
and they wanted to make a movie about him.
That's basically it.
I know, but...
I still like the first movie.
It was just a marketing thing.
Something about the atmosphere.
It's bad.
It's terrible,
but the atmosphere of some of the locations is like,
ah, cool.
Wouldn't that be cool if it was real?
I don't know if you remember this or if this happened,
but did they give you Mewtwo cards when you went to watch the movie?
Absolutely.
Ancient Mewcard.
100%.
I think I had one inside of the VHS copy of the movie.
Well, they gave it to me at the theater.
I watched it in theaters and they gave me an ancient Mewcard,
which I no longer have, but I did have for quite a while.
I have mine.
In fact, the other week I was going through my old Pokemon cards,
looking for any valuable ones that I might have.
I do have a Charizard and stuff,
which is not in the greatest condition.
It's not Shadowless and it's not First Edition,
but it might be worth...
I could maybe get a couple hundred for it if I wanted to sell it.
Is it still that valuable?
You just gotta hold until you're like a hundred years old
and sell it for a thousand.
The really rare ones in really great condition sell for like $10,000.
Oh, shit.
Well, I remember years ago I decided to sell my entire Pokemon card collection
and I went on eBay looking up prices and everything seemed like it was worthless,
like five, ten bucks for like fifty, a hundred cards.
I mean, it depends on the card.
How long ago was that?
There's been a bit of a bubble.
That was like ten years ago.
You should do it.
You should check it now because now it's like...
Now it's like so at the point that like locations like Target
will only sell you like one deck or one booster pack because they're...
Yeah, I think demand has risen.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe the prices went up now.
Yeah, it might be worthwhile to check right now.
But I only had Gen 1 cards anyways.
Because I stopped collecting after Gen 1.
I had a few Gen 2.
I had a few from after that, but not that many.
I had for some reason.
I think I actually did had a few Gen 2 cards,
but they were in Japanese weirdly enough.
I actually had a bunch of like...
From even before Pokemon cards were a thing,
I had books of hockey and football cards
that I think like an uncle or something gave me
thinking that they would eventually become valuable.
I think they just bought like an entire run of some random set
of like a few different like sports series of cards.
Just thinking like cards are a collectible item
and they become valuable eventually.
So just hold onto these until you're...
And then you'll have a bunch of money.
That was the boomer version of Bitcoin.
Yeah.
That was...
Oh my God.
I've already made collectors.
Monchi told me that his...
This is a funny story.
His 4chan uncle gave him $40 worth of Dogecoin
and said,
You're not allowed to sell this for a year
because this shit's going to the moon.
What do you mean by 4chan uncle?
Oh, you don't...
Monchi has an uncle that he lives in the 4chan.
He has a 4chan uncle.
I think he's talked about that on the PCP before.
Yeah, he has.
He has, yeah.
Monchi's famous 4chan uncle.
That's pretty fantastic.
Yeah, fake fan.
Fake fan confirmed.
Fake game and girl tabbed.
You know what Pokemon thing I like?
I like Destiny Deoxys.
That was a stupid movie,
but it was in a cool sci-fi scene.
And Munchlack was there.
And there was Plustrel and Miner
running around in bins.
And I was like, this is nice.
And Deoxys is scary.
I think...
I think first movie was the only one I ever saw.
I've seen some of the one with Entei
and the Anons.
But I watched that much later.
I just caught it on TV.
I just assumed that all the other Pokemon movies
were going to be bad.
And even the first one is not that good.
They are.
But most of them are better than the first one.
I would honestly be surprised
if the other ones weren't better than the first one.
I don't think it's just like normal kids movie bad.
I think it's like a spectacular failure.
I remember liking...
I think the second one was the one with Lugia, right?
Yes?
Yeah, I remember liking that one.
I think the third one might have been the one with Entei.
Is Pokemon 2000 the one with Lugia?
Yes.
And then Pokemon Forever is the one with Celery.
Is that the one with Celery?
That's Pokemon Forever.
Whatever the fucking little green one is.
Pokemon Forever is the one with Celery.
That's Pokemon Forever.
Yeah.
See, I only saw the fucking...
I think I caught the ending of that one somewhere
where Professor Oak is a young person
because they travel in time or something.
I remember the one joke in Pokemon 2000
where the fucking ancient prophecy is all like,
oh, if we can't calm down Moltres, Articuno, or Zapdos,
the world will turn to Ash,
which is basically saying the world is going to be destroyed, right?
But then Misty interprets it as like,
oh, that means Ash is the chosen one,
and then Ash is like,
oh, I wish my mom named me Richard instead of Ash,
because it doesn't want to be the chosen one.
That gets the official Gamer's Tavern Seal of Approval.
Who wrote this movie, Gamer's Tavern?
Because it sucks.
Probably.
They didn't even have...
The 3D remake doesn't even have the iconic scene
where Jesse and James are dressed up as Vikings
and Ash says,
I thought they were only in Minnesota.
It's the confirmation that Pokemon takes place in the real world.
I can't believe.
Mewtwo is from South America.
They know about Minnesota.
It's a huge deal.
I didn't know that the Japanese were such big fans of American football.
I don't know why the Japanese would write that in their script.
That's crazy.
It is crazy, but they were very, very faithful.
Mewtwo is basically just Sephiroth.
No.
Are they?
I never played a game.
He doesn't want to destroy everything with a big rock.
He's way worse.
He wants to make a clone so that he can have friends
and live in his own little kingdom, basically.
And then he flies off and he's never seen again.
Except in Mewtwo Returns.
Mewtwo strikes back.
I typical dark, broody, badass villain that hates everything.
He's basically Shadow the Hedgehog.
He's basically Eggman.
He's basically like a villain.
He's basically Stitch from Lilo and Stitch, the ultimate life form.
The Hedgehog.
Yeah.
That's what said, Stitch.
It's a high idea of you were an experiment by a government entity
or something and you're upset about that.
There's way more going on with Sephiroth.
Because Sephiroth is...
Obviously, Sephiroth is better than Mewtwo,
but Mewtwo is like a condensed version of that.
Babies for Sephiroth.
Very simplified version of it.
Yeah, he's babies for Sephiroth,
which is also a baby game for babies.
I enjoyed the first movie just because I was a big fan of Pokmon at the time
and I thought Mewtwo was pretty cool.
And it's cooler if you played the games first before you watched the movie.
I was thinking...
And if you read about Mewtwo's origins in the game, text files,
there's a lot of lore behind it.
So seeing the lore on the big screen was kind of cool.
It's true that the plot for the movie is bad.
Yeah.
I gotta read.
I gotta play a video game to know what's going on.
Damn it.
The Pokmon first movie might have been the first feature length anime I'd ever seen.
I guess that might be the truth for most people,
but that's probably true for me.
Yeah, probably it was for me.
I think mine was the Manafi movie because I'm a zoomer.
So that's the one that I saw.
Manafi?
What the fuck is that?
There's 150 Pokmon, god damn it.
Four?
I was on Gen 3, I think,
because Ruby version was the first Pokmon game I ever bought.
And I was like...
I can't believe the PCP is still talking about Pokmon in this era.
Mewtwo wants to create an army of strong Pokmon,
but only picks Gen 1 Pokmon.
Plot hole kind of cringe, really.
Sounds a little bit like a white supremacy to me.
True.
I liked the fairly recent one they did a few years ago called Pokmon,
The Power of Us.
That was a fun movie.
That one was just like a genuinely good anime movie.
Why would Power of Us?
What?
The Power of Us?
No, us.
As in like all of us.
Ass catcher.
No, us.
The Power of Us?
The Power of Us.
I think I...
Is that the one that's actually well-animated?
Yeah, it's well-animated and it's just like a cat.
It's just Ash and Pikachu and they go to a city and they meet all these really...
It's Ash and Pikachu.
You know what I think of when I hear that title The Power of Us
is how almost every anime and Japanese video game that is inspired by anime,
the plot always comes down to the power of friendship.
That's exactly what it's about.
Conquering everything.
That's exactly what that movie is about.
I kind of hate that.
Let's just really cliched and played out at this point.
Yeah.
Maybe it was actually The Power of Us.
And it was just...
The Power of the United States.
Yeah, because...
Propaganda.
Ash is from America.
You know.
You know what?
The Power of Us.
The prophecy says that if we don't calm the birds, the world will turn to us.
Oh, but it actually meant the US.
It meant there was supposed to be...
There's all these characters.
Periods there.
All these characters, and they all have different reasons for not liking Pokemon.
And Ash introduces them to like,
No, Pokemon are based, see?
And they're like,
Oh, oh, he's right.
Cool.
And then he turns to the camera and says,
Especially based when you go out and buy Pokemon-related stuff.
Isn't that right?
Exactly.
God.
See, all these movies are just the products of capitalism.
They're just...
True, true.
...might of products.
Oh my God.
I'm about to coom right now.
Game receiver, keep talking.
Then I better stop talking.
All right.
Have you guys...
And it was mentioned a couple of fucking minutes ago,
but have you seen the CGI Dragon Quest movie?
Yes.
Is it a CGI Dragon Quest movie?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's also on Netflix.
Is it good or bad?
It's awful.
If you wanted a fateful adaptation,
it's not really fateful to the game.
Well, I mean, it covers...
It's like a speedrun.
It's like watching a speedrun, basically.
It's the most unexpected metatwist I've ever experienced
in a piece of media.
I wish that the twist was done in the middle of the movie,
because then I felt that we made everything
10 times more interesting.
But like...
It's the twist.
Spoiler it.
But basically, it was a video game the whole time.
Dragon Quest is actually a video game the whole time.
That's the twist.
Oh, my...
Okay, so basically what they do is that
they just tell the whole story of that specific Dragon Quest game.
And then right at the end,
the final boss is about to show up like,
oh, I'm summoning my master through this portal.
And then our protagonist,
who has his chosen one son,
throws their destiny to the fucking portal,
and it stops the final boss.
And then out of nowhere, the game freezes.
And only our protagonist moves.
And this weird-looking virus guy shows up.
And he says,
yeah, this whole thing has been a simulation the whole time.
You're at some sort of like Dragon Quest theme amusement park.
And I'm a virus created by a troll.
And I just came here to tell you...
Oh, it became the Digimon movie.
I like this better when it was called Space Funeral.
And the virus basically says like,
yeah, so anyway, I just want to tell you,
Dragon Quest is kind of gay and lame,
and you're a loser for playing this game.
And then the guy...
Then, unironically...
But that is true.
Unironically, the message of the movie
is that you're actually a very special person
because you play Dragon Quest.
Oh, no.
I'm not joking.
He's very special.
No, he's not.
I'm not joking.
Because like, this flashback happens at the end of the movie,
at this part of the movie,
because he remembers that like,
oh, I love my fucking video game,
because you have a wife in the game, right?
Me too.
That's right.
Like, oh, I love my video game wife.
I love my video game children.
Even though in the movie,
he has played the same game like multiple times.
He has played every remake version of this game,
and now he's in the little simulation for it at amusement park.
And what's so weird is that in the flashback,
it shows him as his current age,
and then it shows him at every point of every remake,
and now he's at the amusement park version.
And he's just the same age.
So it's like, did he not age?
Has he just been the same age the whole time?
What is this movie trying to paint these people as?
When you play Dragon Quest, you don't age.
But what you said before,
this is a, the movie is a recreation
of a specific Dragon Quest game.
I forget which number.
Which game is it?
Is it full?
I think it's full.
I think so.
Wait.
I think it's Dragon Quest.
Isn't it five?
It's a...
Yeah, it's five.
It's five.
It's five, yeah.
Yeah, five is the one where you get married and have kids.
Yeah, yeah.
So it's gotta be that one.
I like that.
I played the DS remake of that game.
And in that version...
Yeah, I also played that.
Yeah, in that version of the game,
you have a third wife option,
because in the original, you only have two,
which is like,
does the blonde hair grow next door,
or like this rich guy's like blue-haired,
keeler daughter, right?
But in the DS remake,
they give you the third option.
They give you this spicy sister of the blue-haired girl.
And I was like,
oh, I like her because she actually has a personality,
unlike the other two girls
who are bland as fucking cardboard.
Personally, I prefer them not to have a personality.
Whoa.
Just like in real life.
Speaking of multiple romantic partners,
I've been playing Persona 5 Royal,
and I've successfully managed to date
every single woman in the game at the same time.
So I'm the biggest comeback on Earth.
And it feels fantastic.
Yeah, I've seen Let's Play
is where people have done that.
Yeah.
It's pretty wild that they let you do that.
I think that's required
if you want to 100% the game, right?
There's a challenge for doing it.
You get reward coins,
and you can unlock concept art and stuff with those.
And you get an achievement
for dating every single woman at the same time.
Do all the girls know
you're dating everybody else?
There's a scene on Valentine's Day
where you show up to where you live,
and there's 11 women standing in front of you
all with presents for you.
Yeah, and then they murder you.
Yeah, they all roast you,
and then it cuts the black
and you're all bruised and beaten up.
So they beat the shit out of you.
What's the name of that one anime?
That's a video game where it's a light novel
where you date every girl,
but they all murder you or something.
Is it called Yandere Simulator?
School days, right?
So you don't get a school days pulled on you?
No.
Yeah, the only thing...
Is that...
Go ahead, Gib.
Sorry, I was interrupting.
Okay.
The only thing I know about Persona 5
is this copypasta right here about this guy
who was convinced that Persona 5
helped him to cure his autism.
Was it Persona 5 or Persona 4?
Oh, God.
I think it's 5.
I've been playing 5.
Yeah, that's 5.
I would say the opposite.
Yeah, I was going to say the opposite.
I think Persona causes autism, doesn't cure it.
I know.
That's why this is really funny.
It is a funny copypasta.
This guy is clearly doing very autistic things
but believes that they are acting
similar to the main character
in a way that their life is being improved
by copying what he's doing.
He makes a social link chart
of all the people he knows in real life.
Well, if he's getting better,
then I guess that's good for him.
I hear people...
I don't think he is.
I think people actually do do like social...
Well, not a social link chart,
but I think people who are all about networking
have Excel sheets of everyone they know
with their business number and whatnot
but also have a little fact about
the last time they talked to them.
Oh, they had a dog.
So if I see them again,
I'll ask them about their dog or something.
So you mean the people that are really successful
in business are all autistic?
True.
100%.
He says,
I'm pretty far in my social link
with the girls in the apartment next door.
Probably six or seven with both of you.
I left a calling card too,
like in the game,
to let them know I was going to steal their hearts.
Oh, God.
How do you know this isn't a joke?
Because it's on 4chan, so it's true.
That's the funny thing about the 4chan.
I want to believe it's true.
You can believe it whether or not.
I like the one green tech story
about the guy who has a pocket watch.
He's at a bar,
and then a guy comes up to him
doing small little snickering.
Hey, buddy, you got the time.
And he pulls out his pocket watch,
and then he turns around to his group of table
and says, oh, I was right.
It was a pocket watch.
And then everyone laughs at him.
And then he ends as a green tech story saying,
why does everyone hate pocket watches?
What a good green tech.
Oh, my God.
I mean, just own it.
You got to just own it if you want to.
Just own it in a pocket watch.
Yeah.
But about the Dragon Quest movie,
that plot twist reminds me of,
you know, this is spoilers for Star Ocean 3,
but near the end of Star Ocean 3,
they reveal that the entire universe of Star Ocean
takes place in a video game.
And I remember at the time when this plot twist happened,
everybody hated it,
because there were Star Oceans 1 and 2,
and there was all this lore built up.
And then 3 came along and said,
oh, all that lore is basically fake,
because it doesn't exist.
Does it imply that all the other Star Oceans
also take place in a video game?
Yeah, because the third one is,
it's in the same universe as the first two.
I was going to say,
either they're all in a video game,
or maybe it would be a little cool
if there was one like that,
but instead of like, oh, all the games are in a video game,
it's like, no, just this one is a video game
that exists in the universe of all the other games.
I'm pretty sure it's all of them,
because the Star Ocean has its history.
Instead of using the regular date system,
they use like SD or Star Date, I think.
I'm not sure if it's Star Date,
but they have a timeline.
But the cool thing is,
when your characters discover this at the end of Star Ocean 3,
they eventually leave the video game world,
and they go into the real world,
and they fight the developers of the game.
You're joking.
I think they kill them.
They're fucking joking.
Yeah, that really happened.
The thing is, the developers have like...
Does the game end immediately when you do that?
The developers in the game have like god-like superpowers.
They gave themselves those powers with their game development skills.
That's pretty magic.
Yeah, they do this twist in Simpsons is a video game.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they have to go fight Matt Groening
before they fight god.
They mean that Simpsons is okay?
No, the one that came out for Xbox and PS3,
Simpsons is a video game.
The one that has like fully animated cutscenes.
It's just called the Simpsons game.
It's the EA1.
Well, there's a ton of games just called the Simpsons game.
Okay, the one that came out like the last Simpsons video game.
I'm pretty sure there was no other game made after this one.
That was the last one?
Yeah, I think so.
There's Simpsons games for the Super Nintendo, the Sega Genesis.
Yeah, I don't know that old shit.
I'm talking about the Xbox 360.
Look, you fucking boomer fuck.
It's called the Simpsons the game for PS3 or Xbox.
And it's not great.
And there's also a Simpsons hit and run, I think.
The Xbox 360.
That's my one.
Everybody knows hit and run.
Yeah, everybody knows hit and run.
Is there only one hit and run or is there multiple?
Wait, is the Simpsons game the one that has the Spore guy in it?
Yeah.
Will Wright.
Yeah, he's like a boss in one of the levels.
Yeah, I have seen those cutscenes.
That sounds pretty cool.
Matt Groening summons.
Isn't it like a GTA?
No, that's hit and run.
Well, there's like the Springfield is like the hub world and you can just roam around and walk around.
But you go to different places and activate levels.
Is it more like SpongeBob battle for the key bottom?
Yeah, you get the different family members.
I think they have different abilities that unlock different areas.
Yeah, because Bart finds out that they're in a video game.
He finds the guidebook for their game and then he's like,
Whoa, Rad, we live in a video game.
I'm going to use my Bartman powers to break into the museum with Homer.
Yeah, that sounds pretty cool.
He was great as a kid.
I'm not sure if it holds up.
I think it's fine.
This was like, I guess it came out during Zombie Simpsons era.
I mean, I think the game came out like around the time the movie came out.
I like that during the Matt Groening boss fight, he summoned Zoid Bergenbender to fight you.
That's funny.
And they spout like bad quotes about the Simpsons being worse than future armor and stuff like that.
It was true at the time.
There's a part of the game.
There's a part of the game where they go into another video.
There's a part where they go into several video games, but there's one part where they go into like a sewer system.
And there's like a Mario ripoff like walking around in the background.
There's like a Sonic ripoff on a hamster wheel.
There's whole levels parodying various things.
Like there's the Katamari parody level and stuff like that.
It sounds like a great game to play if you're a gamer expert.
Yeah, if you walk by, I remember the quote that if you walk by like the Sonic guy, you hear him say like,
I met the Shadow version of myself.
Turns out to be a nice guy.
You know, Mario and Sonic were in the Simpsons in the 90s.
They made a little cameo.
Yeah, when Bartz wants to steal a bone storm, was it?
Yeah, he wants to steal like some kind of Mortal Kombat clone game.
Oh, I talked about that in my dissertation.
Oh, I talked about that episode.
Oh my god.
Why?
That's one of the two of the seven stories that ever humans have ever told.
One big iron to the bone storm episode.
Only two stories.
Well, there's five.
Well, there's five more.
Exactly.
There's five more when nobody remembers them.
Those are the two best ones.
Those are the ones that work.
Yeah.
We have been going for almost two hours.
So we could move to voicemails anytime unless anyone has any objections.
I want to talk real quick about these new things I'm cooking up with Villainverse.
Tell me if you guys ever heard of, you guys know what a chick track is?
Yes.
No.
So it's basically like these mini comics created by this like crazy Christian artist.
And the way that like chick tracks would be...
Jack Chick.
Yeah, Jack Chick.
Jack Chick was the artist's name.
Yeah, and he...
Oh, wait.
I think I know those.
Yeah, the way that he...
I heard of this.
Jesus didn't believe him because he told him the truth.
Yeah.
Or is that something else?
It's these little things.
And the way these things are spread is that you would just find them randomly like on bus stations
or like in bathrooms or just be on the ground, right?
And that's kind of like the point.
You're supposed to just find them in random places, right?
So everyone has found one at least at one point in their life or like found like rip,
like just something similar.
There are comics that are supposed to convince you to come to Jesus.
Right, basically.
But they have...
It's very like...
I think even this guy was kind of like extreme for most Christians at the time.
Yeah.
Because he goes into very like bizarre places and he has a chick track for everything.
Like anything you could think of, he has made like his own like little Christian comic about it, right?
And so basically I have made my own chick track, my own villain verse chick tracks, right?
Bass.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
And what I'm going to do is I'm going to send them off to as many people as I can in hopes to spread it, right?
And I've made like a little...
Like coronavirus.
Yeah, like coronavirus.
So you're going to just randomly leave them out for people to find?
Well, I thought of like going into like Barnes and Nobles and like going into their manga section.
Oh, this is cute.
Yeah.
Picking out like certain manga that I think like are similar to villain verse and just stuffing one in there in the manga.
So when people like grab it, it comes down.
They're like, oh, what's this?
Right?
Like I just want people to find it.
Oh, this is great.
I like this a lot.
Yeah.
And for my patrons, I was going to like, I guess make it kind of like my equivalent of a sticker club.
Like, oh, if you're at this, if you're at this tier, I will mail you like five of these.
Although I think I'm going to switch it to only three of these because these motherfuckers really like they eat printer ink like a motherfucker.
They're not, they are not like nice to print.
They're kind of expensive to print.
Right.
Exactly.
But it's a tree like for the $5 amount, which actually, Ben, you get, you got some too because you're at the $5 amount.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Could you, I mean, could you photocopy them instead of printing them?
Is that an option?
Yeah.
I mean, doesn't photocopy and also use ink?
No.
Really?
Yes.
What about a laser printer?
Oh man, my printer is fucking ancient.
How does a photocopy not use ink?
Yeah.
What is on the paper then?
Uh, something, I don't know, something else.
Nah, it uses ink.
Nah, it does not.
It does not.
It's not like a receipt printer from a show.
It uses maybe a different kind of ink, but it surely uses something.
I know laser printers.
Okay, they use, right, they use toner, which is a, it's a different, it's a different thing and it's not as expensive as printer ink.
I know laser printers use a powder, but I'm not sure if it's more expensive or less expensive than ink.
Yeah, that's toner.
That's toner.
I've been trying to like look, cause I heard there's like, you could subscribe to like ink, like an ink subscription where they send you like a cartridge like every month.
Well, they send you, I don't know how much they fucking send you, but like, and it's way cheaper than like buying and buying ink yourself.
And I tried to look for a subscription and I think I found one and I typed in what type of printer I have.
And they're all like, yeah, your printer is not eligible for the subscription.
And I'm like, fuck.
Just, just, just buy a load of pens and then pour all the ink into the top of your printer.
It'll work.
Oh yeah.
Just like a cartoon.
Yeah.
I think what I was going to do is just buy a bunch of pens and draw it individually.
Trace it.
What am I a fucking cartoonist?
I ain't doing that shit.
You heard of tracing paint?
You heard of a light box?
That's how you used to do it.
That's how milk oil did it.
You bastard.
Just send it, just send it off to a monastery to be illuminated, illuminated like a manuscript.
I'm going to, I bought like that, you know, that there's like an ink refill kit that you can just grab a cartridge and just refill the ink in it.
And it seems to be way cheaper than just fucking buying cartridges.
Right.
So I found out how to.
I remember years ago I used to take cartridges to the mall to get refilled with ink.
But I haven't done that in a long time.
That's cool.
What store like refills your cartridges?
I don't remember exactly the store.
I guess some kind of office supply store.
It was a man behind the bin.
Office depot or something.
Interesting.
He just gets live squids and he squeezes them over the cartridges.
There'll be 50 dollars.
Yeah, like the squids from Mario Kart.
It's kind of like when people have to siphon gas out of a car, they like have to suck the squid a little bit.
So like the ink comes out and then they start pouring it.
Wow.
Squid sucking.
Dude just fucking banging my door and I don't know why.
Oh my god.
Yeah, so I'm making these little.
Never mind.
I'm making these little chick tracks.
Gonna be sending them around.
Hopefully you find them soon at your local whatever the fuck.
I wonder if you put these in books and stuff at a bookstore, would that be considered illegal?
Well as long as they don't get caught.
No, it's not illegal to get caught.
It'll be littering at most.
You'll be fucking shot.
And nobody will ever find you.
I've been thinking about because I need to get, I'm so like, there's like an urge in me of like, if I'm not in a costume, marketing a comic, am I really marketing the comic?
So I need to kind of like how I had.
So become a villain in real life.
Yeah, kind of how I had like pasta, the clown, marketing bungalow and I need like my own little marketing guy for villain version.
Oh, there are a couple of episodes back.
I mentioned clown vis.
Oh yeah.
How can I forget?
It's too bad Cheezy isn't here to appreciate this clown Elvis costume thing.
Oh, I follow him on Instagram now.
You should have.
Did you find out about him from Gamers Tavern?
Yeah, yeah, I found it out from that episode.
I think one of my friends commented on that episode saying like, oh, you guys talk about clown vis and Cheezy's not on.
Blast for me.
Yeah, exactly. You should have been there.
Well, I guess I can't go back in time gamers.
We're talking about it now.
But I'm thinking about this.
I'm thinking about making-
You should have your own costume like clown vis does.
I do. I have pasta with clowns.
Well, there you go. You should wear that all the time.
See Gamers Taverns, this is how I know you haven't read Bungalow and Luna.
Fucking got him.
Got him.
Are you sure? You got me.
I haven't read anything. I don't, I don't read.
It's a long going boomer.
I can only read things with pictures.
I can't read any fucking book.
I can't read words.
I can only read things with moving pictures and sound.
The only things I read are like little dialogue boxes and RPG games.
Yeah, exactly.
If anything beyond that, a little too complicated for my little brain.
But yeah, I'm just going to fucking sneak these bad boys into everything.
And I was thinking about making like a fucking costume like a villain marketer.
You just got it. You got a lower cost.
You got a lower printing cost by any means necessary.
Yeah, I mean, that's why I'm investing in the refilling kit and just doing that.
Like I watched the video and they said that yeah, you could like refill your ink cartridge at least like 30 times.
That's pretty good.
I think that's a cool fun way to like promote yourself is to just leave stuff like this in random places.
Like just go to a table in a courtyard somewhere and just leave this stuff on the table and somebody's going to find it.
I really just like making like kind of video content for marketing.
I was thinking about, I dressed up as like some sort, I make like a mask, right?
I wear like a suit and I run, I stand in front of like grocery stores giving out these little chick tracks, right?
Trying to convert people to the villain.
And then my friend was also in a villain costume will pop up and be like,
yo, don't get your chick tracks from this guy.
Get him from me.
I'm the real villain marketer.
Then we start fighting and we literally try to beat each other up in front of like public kind of like a mega 64 thing where they just do like ridiculous ass shit
in public.
Yeah.
And then people call the cops and you kill one of the cops.
Yes, exactly.
If there's footage of me like in a villain mask getting arrested, that'd be pretty rad.
That would go viral.
That's what you gotta do.
You gotta pull that thing with the better call Saul.
You fucking do the thing where you get on the news because you climb up the sign.
You fake saving someone.
Yeah.
But it said you fake killing someone.
You keep throwing someone off of a billboard.
I'm gonna get on top of a fucking billboard in my neighborhood and spray paint it with Reed Villain first.
What does this mean?
Well, as Ethan Ralph proved the best content is filming somebody getting arrested.
Base Ethan does it again.
Oh my god.
Okay.
I can't believe this, but you will never guess.
Sims, you might know.
You will never guess who responded to the Kickstarter message saying, hey, tell me where to send the Road to Radcon book.
You will never guess who was like, here's where to send my Road to Radcon book.
May.
Oh.
She's like, she's like, send it to my parents.
Here's the address.
I'm like, okay.
I guess I will.
The gunt wife herself.
She's back for the grade.
She's back and she wants, she wants a damn book.
Well, yeah, because I sent out a message to everyone saying like, if you, if you paid this much, you get the book.
She did.
She is a backer.
So she's entitled to it.
That's the rules.
I can't believe she wants it.
That's so funny.
I don't, I don't get it.
But whatever.
I mean, she still thinks she's friends with you, right?
No, she blocked me because I tweeted that thing about how she doesn't like black people.
I mean, where was the lie?
I guess.
Well, no, there's an uncomfortable truth that she just can't, she can't cope with.
That does confuse me then.
Like what?
Yeah.
Why would she ever want to see that?
I don't know.
Maybe she'll just shit on it.
I hope so.
I just don't, I don't think there's any.
She's obviously a, I don't think there's any.
I don't think there's any.
She's obviously a big fan of the PCP.
Maybe she.
I mean, who isn't?
Maybe she helped.
Maybe she helped Trixie with the writing and she wants to see like, I want to read my part.
The fruits of my labor and perhaps, perhaps.
Am I not entitled to the fruit of my labor?
That's true.
All right.
I feel like we should, we should be getting on to voicemails soon.
What do you, what do you dudes think?
Okay.
Cool.
Sweet.
Well, I'm good.
I'm good.
Here's the first one, the first one, which I will post in general.
Cybershell was here.
This would go on for another couple of hours before we got to voicemail.
Thank God that fucker is nowhere near this holy place.
The first one is called is water wet?
Three, two, one, go.
I'm going to revive a dead meme here.
Is water wet?
No.
That doesn't make any fucking sense.
Wetness is a property that water applies to other objects.
It doesn't make any, it contradicts our human sensibilities.
Yeah, if wetness means it has water on it, then water doesn't have water on it.
So it's not wet.
You say that water can be wet, right?
It's like, it's like saying, can fire be drunk?
Or like, can salt have water on each?
No.
It's like, if they're touching.
How many holes does a human body have?
I feel like I've seen a Vsauce-esque video about water is wet.
And it was actually interesting.
This isn't interesting.
Yeah, I get it.
Okay, on a purely technical level, I understand.
Thanks to the voicemail.
Next one is called Ben St. After He Learned.
Is it called half full or half empty kind of thing?
Ben St. After He Learned.
Yeah, it's a semantic argument.
There's 9,860.
Is water a sandwich?
Hot dog is a sandwich.
I fucking hate the whole sandwich argument.
I hate it so much.
Water is a sandwich because each molecule is sandwiched
between two other molecules.
Precisely.
Oh my god, I don't care.
Ben St. After He Learned.
There's 9,862 frames of low rent witch made.
Okay, three, two, one, go.
Like, Vegeta, the Scouter.
I liked how this voicemail was only 3 seconds long.
I liked that too.
That water question should have been 3 seconds long.
Yeah, exactly.
Maybe a voice grail that one.
What a king.
The only criteria is just be sure.
Yeah, the shorter the better.
The next voicemail is called
An Honest Review of Bee's New Album.
Three, two, one, go.
It's pretty good.
No, pretty good.
I don't think so.
A lot of the charm that was missing from like the Yig.
Because I listened to it and I thought it was embarrassing.
Yeah, the charm that are all that one.
I love Pikachu.
I thought it was pleasant to listen to.
I thought it was really embarrassing.
It sounded like a fucking middle schooler wrote the lyrics.
And she didn't write her own beats.
Solid.
There's six and a half or seven out of ten.
It's like something a high schooler might be a little proud of.
Well, Ben, you have to look at it.
Everything is relative.
It's like maybe this album is better than her previous work.
I think it's not even better than the Yig.
It's actually more embarrassing than the Yig stuff.
Because the lyrics are like so stupid and like something an idiot would write.
Pop culture references.
I read, oh my God, the tweet about can anyone decode my nerdcore bars?
It's like a reference to Pokemon.
Oh, God.
I can hate nerd.
Oh, shit.
Got it.
The Pikachu, I'm sorry, a functioning adult should not write those Pikachu lyrics.
I'm sorry.
Like you should fucking be ashamed of yourself.
Next.
I guess I'll just have to take your word for it.
Because I hadn't heard the Pikachu rap when you were talking about it earlier.
I was just imagining like a rap, but it's like from the perspective of Pikachu who could only say Pika and Chu.
That would have been fun.
Yeah, that'd be funny.
You have to be a funny, that could be a funny novelty song that's like 30 seconds long.
I did listen to a little bit of the Pikachu one and it was quite shocking, you could say.
Someone should get a picture of Anthony Fantano, turn his yellow shirt into purple,
photoshop Ben's face over Anthony Fantano.
You can make him bald too.
And in the background, add the cover art for Bee's last album.
I didn't listen to the whole thing.
I listened to the two track, the one about Pikachu and the one about how she spends all her money on weed.
And I was just like, I don't know.
I was like, sounds like shit.
There was something you already know about that, that's just a fact.
There was some lyric in one of the songs that was like a vague allusion to like burning bridges and throwing away her phone and losing all the contacts,
which I thought was funny just in the classic terms.
I think that's the, I don't know, that's in one of the, yeah, I heard that part.
It's like, yep, true.
I'm disappointed the Pikachu song didn't have the excellent joke of like, hey, do you like Pokemon?
Good, because I Pikachu in a shower.
It's, I mean, the rhymes are like literally like Dr. Seuss shit.
It's like Dr. Seuss shit with like a little bit of like, a little bit of like changes the meter up a little adds like some extra, an extra syllable here and there.
There's some twiring.
That's it.
You're right.
Sure.
Yeah, sure.
You should make a diss track then.
So you do it.
Here's what I'll say.
Here's how it's bad to the point that I think if I wrote a diss track, I think I could write bars about as good.
So that's how, that's how bad it is.
Well, I'll take your word for it because obviously you're the number one Yig Studio fan.
True.
Okay.
Next one is called additional note on B's album, something I just noticed.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh, and the first track is titled dollars falling out of my pockets, which I would personally like to believe as a reference to Ben St.
paying off her patrons in order to get them to unsubscribe.
I doubt it.
I think it's just an illusion to losing the money out of her pocket.
Yeah.
It's spending it all on me.
It's gone.
Loathe.
I don't understand.
I don't understand how she makes so much money from Patreon and Substack and I mean, she's probably got like two subs to her only fans or whatever.
And YouTube ad revenue and gets an allowance from her mom on top of it.
Parents just pay for everything and still is broke and has to fucking beg on Twitter and be like, guys, please buy my new album.
It's actually good.
I promise.
I'm broke and I don't know how do you even spend that much money on?
How do you do it?
She already covered that in the first song.
She spends it all on weed.
She's probably pulling it for the whole family.
How do you do it?
You get overcharged so you don't know what you're doing, probably.
God damn.
Okay, whatever.
Next voicemail is called...
I'll post it there.
It's called MFV.
Sorry, I just got to take a second to load.
Come on and load.
Come on and...
Okay.
Here comes the load.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey guys, this is my first voicemail.
Hope I'm doing it right.
Yeah.
This voicemail.
You're killing it.
I'm going to tell a joke.
It's my first time telling a joke so I hope you're going to do it right.
You can do it, buddy.
What does the rat say when meeting another rat?
Cheese to meet you.
Do you approve?
Yeah, it was pretty good.
That was the first joke he ever told in his entire life.
So I give him a lot of credit for that.
Well done, young man.
Here's to many more.
I thought that was Gamer's Tavern's message at first.
Why would he drop this joke here?
He could have just said it on the podcast already.
He didn't know it was going to be on the episode.
I didn't know.
Next one is called Oh How the Best Have Fallen.
Three bests and quotes.
Three, two, one, go.
Nate calling a woman ugly over Twitter because she doesn't look like an anime character.
I didn't expect that of him.
I wonder what kind of audience that cultivates a fucking based one.
Yeah, I saw his tweet about the Faye Valentine actress who he called Lagoblina.
Oh, no.
And then his follow-up tweet was like, he was like, we all knew this would happen.
Damn.
I can't believe Nate's a racist, holy shit.
It's just vegan.
I mean, I don't know what that means.
I genuinely don't know what that means.
Gablina or Gablina is like a joke about mixed-race people.
No, there's no way that's what he meant.
There's no way.
I've heard that used as just a meme to disparage a woman's appearance in general.
I've mostly seen it like Americans look like this.
They're Gablinas or Gablinas and they're mixed-race or something.
I don't think.
I remember seeing that joke on Poll a lot, which I guess makes sense.
Maybe he's just racist against women.
Why there was a word for that?
I've only used that term when posting drawings of my goblin girl character and saying El Gablina because she is a goblin.
Is that okay? Is that acceptable?
I'm gonna say yes.
No, it's anti-Semitic to draw goblins.
When have you drawn a goblin girl?
I'm gonna check your Twitter right now.
It's been a long time, not recently.
I usually retweet everything you draw.
Maybe I'm thinking one of the Saiyan characters you draw or something.
Would you say it?
I thought you had drawn one recently and maybe it was a Saiyan character.
Yeah, very goblin-adjacent is Saiyan.
It was green and it had long ears.
Well, that's not a fucking Saiyan then.
Well, I don't know.
Hang on, hang on.
Two seconds. Where's the last one I did?
Oh my god, it was like six months ago. Never mind.
There you go.
There's a goblin.
Well, let's call that a goblina.
That's kind of like a...
That's the Akira Toriyama art style, isn't it?
A little.
I'm big inspired by Toriyama, so I guess it might see through.
The hair reminds me of Bulma's mom.
Yeah, it's kind of based on that.
This reminds me of something across between Dragon Quest and Dragon Ball Z.
Yeah, I see that. I see a little tinge of Toriyama in there.
I like the picture you drew of Zelda with a fat ass and there's a tiny penis.
That was a fun commission.
That was pretty funny.
I thought that was funny.
People were kink-shaving the guy who commissioned it in the comments and I was like,
that's not cool. It gave me money.
It's not cool.
It's kind of funny, but it's not cool.
It's funny. It's fine.
Whatever, yeah.
Okay, next voicemail is called Grief Cliff.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, this is Grief Cliff here in the United States.
Government needs to make me a 420 star general.
This is my plan. Here's how we could have saved the exit.
The exit?
We knew the Taliban was coming in.
They had all the trucks and the jeeps and they're trying to take it over the airport.
So what we should have done is we take all the TNT in the world, just all the TNT in the world,
and we put it on the airport. We just put it under there.
Simple so far.
And then we put a little pressure plate on that and we fly the plane out.
And then they're like, ah, we won.
And they're like pew, pew, pew.
And they're firing their guns in the air and one of them steps on the pressure plate.
Yeah.
Then it's game over and then we win.
Then we go back in and then do it again.
Just repeating this problem.
After the first time, they might not fall for it.
And they go on and get on that.
They fall on it like three times.
Yeah, it's a little late now, but maybe we can...
This sounds like a Wiley Coyote.
That's rad too.
Peace out.
Pull me once.
Awesome. It would have worked.
It's like lemmings.
They'll just keep going onto the pressure plates.
The Taliban.
Just one after another.
Yeah.
Surely you would say landmine unless you were thinking of Minecraft.
We should have just...
Yeah, true.
We should have just banned the Taliban.
Yeah.
The word for TNT connected to a pressure plate is landmine.
Who that is?
We should have given the Taliban weapons.
Why the fuck did we do that?
Yeah.
Next voicemail is called...
What is it called?
It is called Red Five Rainbow Tommy J Call Out.
Three, two, one, go.
Oh my gosh.
I bet I can make a voicemail better than all this shit that comes in.
You know what though?
I don't.
Why?
Because I don't have anything to fucking say.
So I just don't say anything because I don't want to make you listen to my goddamn voice.
True.
Yeah.
Tommy J Call Outs are a genre unto themselves.
Give us more of those please.
Sorry.
I think so.
I gotta be excited.
Girls listen to the PCP.
I know that.
True.
Yeah, that's like...
I wonder if our demographics have shifted.
We don't know their pronouns.
Don't say anything.
Oh fuck, you're right.
I happen to know that Red Five Rainbow is a she, but that's just...
Wait, did I say something wrong?
She said, she's the assumed.
She's the assumed.
And you know what happens when you assume?
You make an ass out of you and me.
It makes a big ass.
That's how you spell the word.
It's pronounced.
It makes a big ass that you can't even fuck with your tiny dick.
Get out of here.
That's relatable.
Relatable.
Can't even reach.
Especially the tiny dick park.
You make an ass out of you and I actually is how it's said.
Out of you.
Oh fuck.
Ass-eye.
Yep.
No ass.
Not ass.
Ass is donkey, dumbass.
Wait, dumbass.
Okay, that was pretty mean.
I think I'm going to unfollow you on Twitter now.
Do it, do it, do it, do it.
I'm not going to do that.
Yeah, you're not even going to make a dent, boy.
No, I would never do that.
I would never do that.
Next one is called Ben After Every Workout.
Okay.
Processing.
There it is.
Three, two, one, go.
Get the pizza now.
I mean, I mean.
Yeah, that seems pretty accurate.
Do you get the pizza now after every workout, Ben?
I want to.
You want to see the pizza?
That will ruin the point of the workout, wouldn't it, if you get a pizza?
Is he calling me fat?
This guy's calling me fat.
He's calling you a pizza demon.
He's calling you a fat.
Get the pizza now.
He's calling you fat with a pH.
Not if you degrease your pizza before eating it.
It's a pizza with a pH.
Fat with a pizza.
I am fat, though.
I have to start working out again.
I have to go to the fucking hardware store and buy new bolts,
because I stripped the bolts trying to, Alan wrench my squat rack together.
So that's a whole fucking thing that I got to do.
Thanks for asking.
Just putting the squat rack together is a workout in and of itself.
Yeah, only it was bad for me.
Next one is called...
You do it like a workout, but you could do a work in when you work on your inside.
A work in is when I boycott working out to defeat capitalism.
Oh boy.
Works every time.
That'll show him.
That's what I've been doing.
That's what fatbin is.
That's what I've been doing this whole time.
Yeah, true.
Next voicemail is called...
Unlike some lectures, this one exists.
This is from fuck the golden witch bitch at kibagorf.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, PCP.
I just wanted to say that it's finally here.
A new big ol' fan lecture, Yu-Gi-Oh GX 101.
And I just wanted to say a big ol' thank you to all y'all, you know.
And my audience, which was most of the pro and on,
Rito, Jelly, Eleazar, Kajoro, Nonibra, Sital, Syamed, and Shinnisaba,
all quirky characters you may know.
As well as a bunch of artists I commissioned for various characters
for the lecture, Alexymillion, Asha in the AM, Sital, Doon Koon,
Jade Moro, Jelly Beaner, Chip Wiseman, Kaiju Koon, Kajoro Bitterthorn,
Michi, Never Paint, Nonibra, Syamed, Sporktown, and Sital for the thumbnail art.
Thank y'all again for inspiring creators and artists out there.
And link in the description for me, please, Eleazar. Thank you.
I recognize about half of those names.
That's Sean Don. I'm sure that's Sean.
Eleazar, if you... I'm sure you can find...
Yeah, put the link in the description.
What was the name of the video?
Well, I don't think he said... It's a Yu-Gi-Oh DX PCP fan lecture.
Yeah, Eleazar, put the link down there in the doobly-doo.
That could be interesting. I always liked those lectures.
Nah, I've never been a fan.
Not a fan. Yeah, I can't find one.
Not a fan. I hate learning. I hate learning.
Eleazar will probably know where it is.
That's why you're so smart.
I'm so smart that I can't learn anymore, and that's why I don't like it.
How Yu-Gi-Oh Dual Links is censored outside of Japan. What? No way.
Next... What? What's wrong with my fucking...
I'm okay, my mouse went weird.
Next voicemail is called Big Chicken's Egg of OK Tim Rogers Is David Foster Walla?
And then it cuts off. 3, 2, 1, go.
Alright, let's look at the cold, hard, objective facts here.
David Foster Wallas is a very self-conscious man, so after all the eyes went on him
after publishing Infinite Jest, everyone calling him a genius and stuff,
I don't blame him for wanting to fake his own death.
That was just a puppet that he hung in the attic.
And then he cut his hair, he learned how to wash his hair.
He shaved his jawbone down a little bit with some plastic surgery money that he got from Infinite Jest.
He got a job translating.
And if you look at both Tim Rogers and David Foster Wallas' writing, it's remarkably similar.
In Tim Rogers' action button reviews where he spends four hours out of the six hours of the video
talking about his personal life, they line up remarkably with David Foster Wallas' own life.
So, you know, you be the judge.
Wait, is this like the Alex Jones is Bill Hicks conspiracy?
I haven't heard that one.
Oh, really?
I mean, you haven't heard that popular, famed conspiracy?
That's a classic theory.
I think I might have heard someone mention it.
Yeah, it's that. It's like that.
I remember David Foster Wallas be now probably in his like sixties, right?
Maybe he wasn't he wasn't at all. I don't know.
I remember somebody told me that I sound like the action button review guy, but I don't know if that's accurate.
That you you absolutely do not.
That is the Tim Rogers is the action button review guy, but you don't sound anything like him.
And I don't think so.
No, you sound like Bismarck. You sound like the speedrun YouTuber Bismarck.
Yeah, I saw somebody mentioned that as well.
You are the same person.
I only watched one video of that guy and it was about Mario 64, I think.
I think I've watched their entire channel.
I eat that shit up. I eat that fucking speedrun YouTube video content up.
For some reason.
It's cool.
Yeah, that and the egg studio stuff. Those are your two main things.
Yeah, true. Yeah, true.
Dude, the latest, the latest what you're doing dropped and I drop whatever I'm doing and I go check it out.
Yeah, you drop whatever you're doing to see what you're doing.
I drop what I'm doing to see what you do.
I know we're in voicemails, but can I just say those are actually so hard to watch.
They're like, I watched. Yeah.
Gib, you mentioned one and I wasn't going to check it out, but I went and I looked and I watched the start where.
Yeah, where she literally can't fucking introduce herself and Riley needs to tell her what to say.
She leaves it in and it's not a funny outtake. It's embarrassing.
Jesus Christ.
It's like you're fucking struggling so much with the simplest thing. It's so bad.
Yeah, the other thing that kind of creeps me out is that there's no eye contact whatsoever.
Between them. Between the two of them.
Yeah, between who's talking.
Yeah, she doesn't look at them.
She's just staring off into the distance.
Yeah. It's weird.
Like she's not staring at the camera and she's not staring at them and she's just kind of looking off into the distance as they talk.
And they're not staring at her either. They're just staring into the distance.
Kind of to the side, into the middle distance.
I didn't watch the whole thing, but yeah, both of the bits that I've seen are the same.
There's just like very, very low level of like interaction.
It sounds like she's not at all interested or cares what they're saying.
She's just waiting for them to finish speaking.
That's what I've heard.
Next lesson.
That's what I've heard. She's like these days.
Lamal.
Next voicemail is called...
It's called Doid Gazers Again.
Okay, three, two, three, two, one, go.
Hi, this is the golden bitch, aka Doid Gazers.
Sorry I haven't made a voicemail in a while.
I just know something.
Ben, that jacket that you wear in the lectures, is that too small for you?
It's a half coat.
It looks incredibly tight and uncomfortable and it also comes down to about an inch and a half.
You're so fucking stupid.
So I was thinking maybe we all donate money to Ben Sings Patreon at Patreon.
Wait, I mean, yes it is too small. I can't afford a bigger one. Please help me.
So that Ben can afford a new jacket for his future endeavors.
It's like future trunks.
So wait, Doid Gazers is back? I thought they quit.
Well, they're out of retirement and they're apparently recording voicemails in what sounds like maybe a pool room at their local YMCA.
I'm a huge fan of the Doid Gazers.
What was the point of the Doid Gazers bit for that question?
I don't know, but the coat that I'm wearing...
I'm disappointed there was no crying baby in the background this morning.
The coat that I'm wearing in those videos, I think you would call it a half coat.
It's like a tuxedo coat. It has buttons on it, but it doesn't close. It doesn't button.
It stays open and you would wear like a shirt and like a cummerbund under it.
It's like future trunks.
Yes, but like a tuxedo of being future trunks.
It stays open because you're too fat to button it up.
Well, I am now. I wasn't at the time. I was lean. I was a lean mean 169.
If you want Ben to get a new button up for his fat, disgusting body, donate to his Patreon.
Yes, if you want me to be able to afford a third button to cover up my disgusting gut.
If you think Ben just looks disgusting and you want him to cover up, please donate money.
You just fucking hate Ben and how he looks and never want to see him again. That's where you gotta send money.
Donate money.
You gotta make sure he can't show that atrocity to anyone else.
I want the money.
Donate to Yig Studio's Patreon.
That's all around.
Well, it's, I mean, it's called The Golden Witch.
Oh, is it? I thought it was Yig Studio.
Let's see how much money they're making right now.
It dropped another 50 this month. It has dropped about 50 every month.
Wait, are you still getting a, are you still paying a dollar for every time it drops?
I would. If someone contacted me and told me I'm unpledging, I would get, I would pay them to do it.
But no, people, people are just doing it of their own free will. This isn't even on.
I've started a revolution. It's, it's grown, it's grown bigger than anything.
Ben, I am pledged six times. Can I have six dollars?
Yeah.
I hate how we talked about collaborative projects recently uploaded on The Golden Witch Patreon.
Only five bucks to see. What a deal.
I bet that's awesome. I bet that's really interesting.
I am going to become a patron right now.
No, no. Julian in my discord, just, just for fun, subscribed to her sub-stack just long enough to like download all of the, all of the private, you know, posts there and just post to them.
And they were just really boring. I don't know.
That one was just.
And the legendary Kiwi Farms leaker stole them all and put them on Kiwi Farms.
Oh yes. The legendary Kiwi Farms leaker.
Wherever you are.
He's a spy in my discord.
Who is this man of mystery?
Who is this, well, this, this, this woman of mystery because his, her thing is that you need, she takes a neutral stance on pronouns, obviously, but demands consistency.
So you just, you got to pick one and stick with it or else they get mad at you.
Yeah, yeah, she.
So, she, so I rolled the dice and then we landed on she.
So, neutral stance though. No, no skin in the game on that one.
There was, there was just, you know, a bunch of the posts were like, I don't know.
I don't know, they were annoying.
That one in particular was like, it was like, why do movies only get, why does everyone know the director of the movie and not all the other people that worked on the movie?
There's too many people to talk about.
True.
Did she upload something complaining about how a lot of music, mainstream music is made by large teams of people or something like that?
I think that was the same essay.
That one's a classic cope there.
It talks about like, but in music, it's a little bit different kind of.
Look at all these people I passionately interviewed, you can see.
Next voicemail is called, wait, no, that one's not a real voicemail.
This one, wait, is that one a real voicemail?
Wait, this was, fuck, this is one of the alternate.
This is one of the alternate.
They use the other website for some reason that I don't understand.
Okay, this one is called, thank you for playing my voicemails despite my ethnicity.
This one is loading.
We're loading.
We're almost there.
We're three quarters of the way there.
We are going to be, this is what I get for using my phone as a hotspot.
Here it is.
Here it comes.
You got text it.
Perfect.
Three, two, one, go.
I don't understand why some people submit a link to a different site where they upload
their audio.
I don't have a microphone and can't get voice meter to run correctly on Windows XP.
I sincerely apologize for the inconvenience.
How do you record a voicemail if you don't have a microphone?
It's so cute.
Do you have a phone?
This person still uses Windows XP just like I was doing a couple of years back.
Oh, this person must be doing, they must not be recording.
They're synthesizing it with their fucking voice modulator text to speech.
Yeah, that wasn't a real voice button.
Yeah, no one sounded like that.
Well, okay, but it's not every voicemail that uses the other website is like that, but
maybe for this person, that's why I guess that makes sense.
They hired Siri for this one.
The next voicemail is called Hype me up.
Hype me up.
Please do.
Sorry, it's loading.
Sorry.
It's just related to the hype.
We're bleeding hype.
Please.
Here we go.
I'm getting hype.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, fellas.
It's not too much of a spoiler to ask.
What are you guys projects after you're done with what you're doing now?
I think Gibbs to walking on a lot of ghosts in dance definitely still walking on that
that game.
Yeah.
And I would like to know so I can get excited about those because you know, currently, the
projects are reference to like a fucking discord forum game that I don't play.
Like four new reviews.
I didn't watch and shit.
Yeah, I'm going to do a pony review next.
I can really get happy about that shit, but the new new stuff, I think the thing that
I'm going to do, I'm not going to start anything new.
Now my plan is finish, finish phantoms revenge and then doing so finish slime and punishment.
And after that, probably I'll finish the Winnie the Pooh season one retrospective just because
I think I can bang that up pretty fast.
And then I want to finish Biscuits after that.
And so that's my first you have to be working on phantoms revenge for like five to six years.
No, I think it's I got a lot done last month and it's it's pretty close.
It's it's close to being done.
I'm not going to.
I don't know exactly how three years then.
Yeah, maybe maybe 20 early 2023 release for the alpha.
You guys you guys want to answer this?
I after a lot of ghosts after the the Lord of Ghost Kickstarter, then there's there's
a lot of things I could do.
And there's my secret project, which will be the hypest of all of them.
I think once I release that once I announce what that is.
Yeah, people will be like, oh, wow.
Then there's certain things I need to finish.
Obviously, the Lord of Ghosts needs a finished final chapter arc act.
Clarissa Gunsmoke and the Bandit King needs a proper release on my website need to finish that up.
There's another small comic that I was going to do for the Cato anthology that I didn't finish in time.
I could finish that.
Then there's another two or three different comic ideas that I want to start.
And then there's Bill J.
Two and then there's the Bill J.
Book.
There's a lot of things on my plate.
That's that's human.
That's too many things.
You can't do all these many things next.
I feel it.
No, no, I'm not going to do them next.
But there's like of them of the things to do next.
There's lots.
I just need to choose one at a time.
What about the Mario to a stream that you said you wanted to do?
Yeah, I could do that in a few days.
I could I could stream Mario to I haven't felt like streaming in a couple days.
That's basically content.
That is not actually that is wasted content though.
If you're not streaming your you should be screaming.
This money.
Sitting alone not streaming.
You should be streaming yourself screaming.
Yeah, ice cream on top of that scary games.
Like everybody you see on a YouTube video or a stream, they're not screaming because
they're streaming as soon as they hit.
As soon as they turn it off.
They start screaming.
I can't believe I'm not monetizing this.
You're either screaming or screaming.
There's never an in between.
Or both.
Scream.
Well, if you're screaming.
It's streaming.
Then you're creaming.
Willie.
Cheen teaming teaming.
Next voicemail is called more bell jpe type stuff.
Oh, a minute 30.
All right, I'll give it a chance.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, give a you said we're sad in the last episode because we have people demanding things
of you and ask who is going to demand things of you.
I find the thing that most that you ever did was bail jpe.
I love that it's like a funny adventure comic.
I love how it looks and how it's pleasing to the eye.
I know a lot of ghosts and Clarissa are also kind of kind of similar.
But Clarissa, I don't think you're that good drawing the human form yet.
And the colors.
I miss the colors.
I don't know if I agree with that.
Disagree.
J pass.
And the lot of ghosts.
I couldn't understand what the fuck was happening because I never read.
I never played.
You don't have to fucking read.
No.
But even then, I never read Homestuck, but I played bail jpe and I loved it.
And if you did more stuff like more like adventure, you know, humorous and charming.
Shit.
Like adventure time dragon ball bullshit like that.
I would be pleased.
I would like it.
I will share it.
I will print it and I will shove it up my ass.
Yeah.
I agree with all the things this guy likes about bail jpe.
I don't agree that like there's any problem with the way you draw the human form.
I think I thought your drawings.
I mean it's a little amateurish.
Well, I mean it generally.
The drawings in Clarissa were not going for like anatomical accuracy.
They were going for like, you know, an expressive cartoonish look.
And I thought it conveyed that very well.
Very gestural and momentum.
I really thought your drawings of specifically your drawings of the human form specifically
your drawings of the human form in Clarissa were like a big, a big like something that
was like, oh, wow, I didn't know Gibb could do this, but she's doing it.
So I like strongly disagree with that particular point actually.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's so nice, Ben.
It's nice to hear.
Yeah.
Fuck you.
And then.
No, you complimented me.
It's too late.
What was the other thing he said he didn't like about?
He misses the colors.
I mean, coloring is hard, but.
He said he couldn't read Lord of Ghosts.
You don't.
Oh yeah.
The RCK thing.
You have to read no RFCK to read Lord of Ghosts.
That's like fairy bait.
Whatever.
I don't know.
I try to make it like, I mean, I am biased in that I do know about RFCK and the history
of the Lord of Ghosts in RFCK.
I tried to condense it all down into the main little parts you need to know.
And like everything that you learn about like mud and blood in like the, in, you know, in
but second he is, is the same as what slime is in Endless Wars is not that.
The Lord of Ghosts.
It's just a parallel world.
Comic.
Of the same thing.
It does like start its initial setup is based in RFCK, but it very clearly and simply explains
what the setup is in a way that like you don't need to have read anything else beforehand.
So it was pretty comfy.
I think there's a misunderstanding there.
There might be people who know that it's of Endless War and will immediately assume they
don't know enough to get it.
It's just not true.
You should just read it.
Personally, I would like to see more red man comics.
Remember when you used to do those?
Yeah.
This is very easy to do.
It's just, I don't know.
I mean, it was, it's the same as that.
It's the same.
Slime and punishment is the same.
Like, yeah, it's set in RFCK, but the comic explains what's going on and explains what
you need.
You don't have to have played the game to, to, or at least that was my intention.
You don't have to have played the game to know what's going on because the comic explains
what's going on.
I'd say it's a lot easier to read Lord of Ghosts than it is.
Slime and punishment just because there's the extra layer of all the Christian lore and
the pony stuff and all that.
That's, that comes in later, but yeah, that's probably true.
Yeah, that's true.
That's fair.
Maybe I should read Lord of Ghosts.
Maybe.
Did you buy it?
Why not?
What do you have to lose?
I didn't buy it.
Oh.
I could read it.
Give it the cheesy, the cheesy.
You didn't, you didn't pluge?
No, I didn't.
You're not a plunger.
Oh my God.
I don't, I don't have it.
This, this non-pluger.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm not the common plunger.
I'm not a plunger like you guys are.
I am, I don't have money.
No one pledges to me.
What money am I supposed to give out?
What, I give you $5 a month.
What are you doing with that if not pluging?
I am printing out the most expensive.
You're spending it all on weed.
Yeah, you got me.
I'm spending it all on fucking weed.
You're, you're, you're blowing it all.
You're blowing it all on printer ink when you could be spending it on the cheaper toner
and spending the, the excess, spending the extra on weed.
You could have it all.
I'm bulging.
You can make a comic about how you spend all your money on weed.
All right, I'll do that.
Yes.
There we go.
Lord of the Ghost eventually.
I'll get to it.
I specifically saved as soon as I started reading Lord of the Ghost right before the kickstart
was announced and I was like, there we go.
I've read the very first like seven pages and then like two hours later the kickstart was
announced.
Okay.
I'll have it in my hands.
Yeah.
It'll be there soon.
I just need to wait for, uh, needs to do the artist.
Oh, God, me.
It's Ben.
It's Niko.
And, uh,
Goku.
Kaijukun.
Well, uh, then, then has to finish Phantoms of Revenge first before he does that.
Uh, I probably should take a break from Phantoms of Revenge and do the Lord of Ghost comic.
Uh, so you might be waiting a long time.
No, no, no, no, no.
The Lord of Ghost comic shouldn't take a million years.
Ben draws pretty quick.
Well, sometimes.
You're quicker than me.
I've seen you do like, like live streams and it's like, hey, it's pretty good.
Well, he's quick.
I can draw quick for some time.
The problem is he's a big procrastinator, if you know what I mean.
I'm, I'm, I'm, uh, yeah.
I mean, you've been moving, so I haven't expected you to get it done at this point anyway.
I haven't been getting anything done, um, but, uh, I'm, uh, I'm settled in my new fucking
shitty apartment that I need to get out of.
So, you know, I guess I'm good.
Yeah, that sounds good to me.
I'm reading the Lord of Ghost.
Problem solved.
I'm reading the Lord of Ghost right now.
I'm not gonna lie.
Oh my God.
I'm getting big villain-verse energy from it.
A lot of, a lot of, a lot of, a lot of, uh, callbacks.
That's what you're saying about everything.
Guys who have a red villain-verse.
Hmm.
I'm gonna get a lot of villain-verse energy from this.
Exactly what I was gonna say.
There's drawings on a page with words around them.
Villain-verse.
No color.
A prologue explaining the Lord before the main story.
Uh, her.
Very villain-verse, I see.
Very villain-verse, very much so.
I want to move on to the next voicemail, which is called
A Solution to My Problem.
Three, two, one, go.
You say that I drink my juice.
Price of my love for the price that you're willing to pay.
But I do not piss anymore.
I only fart.
And my farts smell like piss.
And as much as I would like to drink my blood,
I think I need to hold on to what little blood I still have.
But there is someone's blood who I can drink.
Tommy J.
Yeah.
Give me the body of Tommy J.
I will be able to survive this wasteland for a lifetime.
It's all yours.
It's not like the word that's currently controlling him
is doing a good job of using it anyways.
Give me Tommy J.
Take it, take it already.
Get it out of here.
This is a really good Dark Souls NPC.
He's got the slow speaking and the grossness.
Dark Souls NPC would do...
Give me the body of Tommy J.
I love how there's all this lore, deep lore,
that's exclusive to the voicemails that nobody is going to listen to.
Everyone loves the voicemails.
Some people only listen to the voicemails.
I'm getting a lot of Villainverse 5 from this voicemail.
That's true.
I need to.
Tommy...
I couldn't see it with Lord of Ghosts, but with Tommy J...
Tommy J is pretty high up on the villain index.
Yeah, true. He's high on that fucking ranking.
Not gonna lie, Tommy J is an infamous villain.
Something else that has a lot of Villainverse energy
is No More Heroes 1 through 3.
What? You cut out? Fuck.
No More Heroes. That has a lot of Villainverse energy.
Yeah, I bet it does.
I gotta play that.
I'll probably say that while I'm reading Villainverse.
Getting a lot of Villainverse vibes.
Villainverse Chapter 2 has a lot of Villainverse Chapter 1 energy.
You think the author of this has read Villainverse?
If it does, I'll add it to my Villainverse playlist on YouTube,
which is just a collection of things that just give me Villainverse energy.
Yeah, which is everything.
Next voicemail is just stuff.
Next voicemail is called Good Internet Aliases 321 Go.
Last week, BaystyleDai left a voicemail asking,
what are your favorite Internet aliases from people in the PCP
or PCP adjacent communities,
and you didn't even give a single one fucking New Pymers.
There's definitely some names that have stuck out to me as exceptional
because they're either, they roll off the tongue, look cool written,
are entirely unique to themselves,
or just sound fucking cool for starters, give and take.
Not to be a kiss-ass, but it's a solid name.
Good pun, fun to say, and Gib is even better.
Three letters, one syllable, yet wholly original, plus satisfying to say.
Yeah, true.
Pizza-chan, fucking Kino, super marketable,
Rita Torpedo, son's fucking Nido, Mosquito, them snakes, classic.
Nido Mosquito would be good too.
Kip and Nate, from RFCK, just look excellent written.
Cybershell, if you've ever heard him describe the lore behind it, it's brilliant.
I have.
No need, brah, it's a feel-good name, and it sounds cooler as no need.
And to top them off, Marenpan, rolls off the tongue, ends with an M.
You're just sucking off your friends.
He's just like, oh, my people I know have cool names.
Plus it's cute and adorable.
Nah, these all suck.
Just straight-up mean-a-cycle-arty.
Nah, these are fucking terrible.
Kawa'i.
Join the PCP Minecraft server, it's like a whole fucking Pokemon game.
Except good.
Yeah, do that.
No, those actually were all really good.
Yeah, definitely do that.
Hold all the babies on the PCP Minecraft server.
Patreon.com slash the procrastinators to join the Minecraft server,
and also to get bonus episodes, which I swear to God I will upload soon.
Yeah, I'm still waiting for the Cybershell.
It's not my fucking responsibility, but I guess it is now.
Oh well.
I mean, yeah, I could also do it, but I don't know what I would do.
I've been waiting for the five-hour Cybershell bonus episode.
It's so out of date now, but on the other hand, be complaining about it.
Trixie will never truly be out of date.
It's like wine.
I added her, just for fun, I added her in the announcement that Road to Radcon is up.
I think there's basically no chance that she didn't see the Road to Radcon is published now.
You mean she didn't block you on Twitter?
She did block me on Twitter, but she would have seen the replies to the posts that were not by me,
and she must surely have been like, what are these things adding me in reference to,
and must surely have logged out and taken a look, so.
She must have seen that Road to Radcon is out now, and I'm sure she will not acknowledge it anyway.
I mean, if she even uses the internet anymore.
She tweets once in a while.
Oh no, she does.
In fact, no, she tweeted something like that day, so no, she saw it.
I wonder what she thinks about it.
Probably nothing.
She's busy working on the anime alphabet videos thing.
She's busy making fucking grade school level raps.
Hey, I'm a Pikachu.
Hey, I got a Fu Manchu.
Hey, I'm gonna electroshock you.
Oh, that was pretty good.
That one was pretty good.
Hey, it's a metaphor for something.
Hey, it's me, Italian Pikachu.
Get over here.
I'm gonna hit you.
What?
I'm gonna hit you with my electrical shock.
Come here.
What the fuck are you talking about, boy?
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm walking here.
I don't care about rhyme.
Yeah, Digibro's a good-
It's the Raichu.
It's the fucking Raichu.
He was wearing a wire.
If you wore a wire, he would be grounded.
Yeah, Digibro is a good internet alias.
It is a good internet alias.
It's pretty good.
Who's Digibro?
Yeah, that's why it's not being used anymore.
Yeah, Dick Masterson's also a good internet alias.
I don't care what anyone says.
Too many syllables.
Sure.
Well, it's kind of like Gibbentake.
You can shorten it to Dick.
Yeah, exactly.
Once you establish who you're talking about, I guess.
Right.
Yeah, it's pretty decent.
Yeah, Monkey Joe's 10 out of 10 name, too.
What else?
I always liked Monkey, to say.
I think a lot of people have heard of Monkey
just because the name is so fun to say.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
My favorite internet alias is Ben Saint.
Disagree.
Mine, too.
Nah, it's just a regular name.
Mine is Simsie Fart because Simsie Art and Simsie Boy were both taken,
so I had to go with Simsie Fart.
I hate this conversation.
It sucks.
I got Cheesy Manfredo because Cheesy Alfredo was already taken.
That's it.
No more.
Next voicemail.
Now it looks voicemail.
It's called I Am Uneducated, but still Google these things.
She, they.
Thank God.
Three, two, one, go.
So Bitcoin has this cycle where once every four years,
they have the amount of Bitcoin that they give out to miners,
which then causes a boom in value some months later.
There's also an investment strategy called dollar cost averaging
that smooths out the effects of short-term market fluctuation
so your long-term investments are more reliable.
Now, I know basically nothing beyond a few research expeditions on this stuff,
but it sounds to me like this cycle makes long-term Bitcoin growth
a pretty safe bet, at least until they give out the maximum number of Bitcoin.
So using an investment strategy like that would be a pretty good idea.
Hopefully, if I'm actually wrong and stupid, other voicemailers will correct me
because I very well could be.
But I think I'm justified in saying that you people keep looking at the random short-term fluctuations
of Bitcoin and acting like they're the end of the world,
but that's just getting distracted by what's effectively white noise
when there are much larger patterns that you can more reliably take advantage of.
So stop it.
You're half right, but you're being, you know a little bit.
You've understood like a basic fact and assumed that it is relevant to like everything.
This guy just cares about being right.
This girl just cares about being right.
They specified, she they specified this time.
Let's not go back to the crypto case.
They all specify because I always get it wrong.
So now that people do their, now the only way,
the only way I can get it right ever is if people say it in their thing.
So I have it here for my benefit.
Bitcoin did rise a little bit more.
I sold it a little bit ago and then it rose a little bit.
So I lost out on a little bit of money, but whatever.
Everybody loves the crypto cash.
Bitcoin's the same, but Ethereum is blowing up more.
I wish I had held on to my Ethereum.
I mean Bitcoin is also, wait, what is Ethereum doing?
It went the same way as Bitcoin.
And then when Bitcoin was just sort of going normal,
like up and down the same level, Ethereum has now gone up even higher.
In a big old spike.
Really?
Mmm.
Look at the one month.
Oh yeah, it's up.
It's up.
It's up, baby.
It looks like it's hovering around 4k.
Well, good for Ethereum.
All right.
This person is wrong.
I was not looking at random short-term fluctuations.
I was looking at the pattern that had held for like a month and a half
where it was like steadily growing.
I mean, from like 30k to like 50.
That's not like a random short-term fluctuation.
That's like a serious trend.
I mean, I understand that like you might think that in the long term
it goes even higher.
But at the same time, say you're like, oh, I'm going to buy Bitcoin
in the hope that it's going to go to 100k.
Well, sure.
When do you buy?
Do you buy now when it's 50?
If you think it's going to go down to 30,
then you can get like 50% more of a return
if you wait for it to go down to 30 before you buy.
I don't know.
I think this is a...
Well, what I learned is that the exact wrong people to find this information about
are the people on Reddit, the Bitcoin Reddit section.
Yeah.
Because everybody on there is always extremely optimistic.
Yes, they're all true believers.
They're all like, it's going to be 100k in the next week or so.
And then it like dropped to 46k.
Yeah, everybody who like spends time on the subreddit
is like a fucking muskite.
Like, oh, it solves the general problem.
Nothing in history has ever solved the general problem before.
It's fucking...
Too many woke generals.
We could have just like, you know, socialism.
No, thanks.
All we needed to do to solve poverty was just if everyone had invested in Bitcoin
when it was new, then we'd all be rich now.
If you look at the posting history,
every single time Bitcoin goes up just a little bit,
they're like, it's going to hit 100k this month and then it doesn't.
You know, just an endless cycle of that over and over.
Yeah, I've never looked into anything about Bitcoin.
I just look at the number, I just look at the graph on Coinbase
and I'm like, hmm, I'll just assume things.
More like coin cringe.
It's worked out sometimes.
Well, that's what I was doing originally,
but then I went to the subreddits to see if I could like,
one-up things and then I realized that doesn't work.
It's better just to look at the numbers, honestly,
because that's what everybody else is doing.
I mean, fucking...
I thought they had secret knowledge, but they don't.
I mean, why would they be giving it out if they had secret knowledge?
They'd just be using it to get as much as possible.
Look, I looked at the pattern.
I looked at like, okay, earlier in the year,
it hit its biggest spike ever and then it kind of bounced down
and then it was going up again and I looked at that
and I was like, there's two possibilities.
One is that the first spike was just like an initial sort of spike
that's just going to be like the tip of the iceberg
of an even bigger spike that's coming.
The second possibility is that that was the spike
and that what we're seeing now is sort of like an echo,
a smaller spike that's coming afterwards.
And I was like, alright, if this is an echo bump,
then it's going to only go so high and it's going to peter out
and I won't lose that much.
And I might lose some.
But if this is like the tip of the iceberg and it's going to the moon,
then if I don't invest something, I will lose so much.
I will lose out like so hard.
So I was like, I feel like the risk of not investing
are higher than the risks of investing and that's why I did it.
And everyone is like, Ben, but you saw it go up,
so you should know that next it goes down.
Like you are, everyone is very, everyone's a critic.
Everyone is a fucking critic.
They think they're operating on a higher level.
They're not, they're all reddit level, they're all reddit tier.
When I go to like the tracking websites that have the graphs,
I'll see articles that are like, oh, Bitcoin is bullish,
but short term, it's bearish.
And then I look at the diagrams that supposedly demonstrate this
and it's literally just like they pick two random points on the diagram
and draw a line between them.
And then they'll be like, yeah, this is the trend,
but then they'll pick two different points and be like,
draw a line between them and then be like, or this could be the trend.
And then they'll just be like, yeah, it's one of these.
And it's literally just like pick two points and be like,
is this the trend?
I don't know.
Nobody actually knows what's going to happen.
They just pretend like they do.
Yeah, it's pretty much that.
It's for suckers like me who are just going to just see the numbers
and then we see a thing that's like Bitcoin going to 100 by the end of the year
and it gives me FOMO and I buy more.
That's what it's for.
Let the good times roll.
It's a little more consistent, safer way of gambling your money.
At the end of the day.
Because when you gamble at a casino, there's like no degree of predicting
what's going to happen, but at least with this you can predict a little bit.
So it's safer than gambling.
I think we have about eight left to go.
So let's let's move on.
We've got the next voicemail is called Ben.
It's your mother.
Why are you apostrophe?
Are you mother?
Three, two, one, go.
Hello, Ben.
It's your mother.
I really want you to call me back one of these days.
I'm really worried about you.
I can't have my little Ben say running around all across the country without his
clean underwear.
Or having his breakfast every morning.
Please.
Sounds like Dr. Dolphins.
Don't worry, mom.
I ate baby bells.
I ate baby bell for breakfast.
I found those dirty magazines underneath your bed.
Gross.
I'm not going to throw them out, but we need to talk about what you're reading.
We truly don't.
Okay, son.
Goodbye.
Oh, geez.
Well, that could have gone right.
They found slime and punishment.
Yes, they found the vapors under your bed like Ben.
We have to talk about this.
I sounded exactly like the police officer from German's Doha stream.
That's the exact same voice.
I said it.
She sounds like Dr. Goh from Venture Bros.
True.
Well, all those people are Ben's mom.
Whoa, no way.
Next one is called Hi, Honey.
Three, two, one, go.
What would you do with a death note?
Type in list of all the billionaires in the world.
Just run it down.
Yeah.
And then realize that it doesn't have a typewriter.
I would be...
You have to write it.
Man, I would be scared to do anything.
I might honestly not do a single thing with it.
Because I'm too much of a coward to set shit.
It is lame, but you're setting shit in motion.
Who knows what the consequences are.
He's going to be like, what if something bad happens?
You want that on my shoulders?
Bad things are going to happen if you don't do anything.
So it's kind of like...
Yeah.
Wouldn't the US have been able to win the war against the Taliban if they just had the
death note?
Just write down the name of everybody in the Taliban.
Yeah, I could just death note all the Taliban.
And then I also do it in the entire US military.
So it's even.
I'm not partisan.
You could just do it to people who are old and a heart attack would not be that out
of the ordinary.
So nobody would suspect anything.
Why?
I mean, it's a heart attack anyway.
You have to just like...
Well, you know, like get rid of Donald Trump.
Why does he need to be there?
It doesn't have to be a heart attack.
We don't want him to run again.
It could come up with weird actions.
True.
Can you write down in the death note, get COVID, like about someone?
So gets COVID.
Get COVID and die?
You definitely can.
Yeah.
That 100%.
COVID is already doing that.
It's already killing a lot of the old people.
No, but I would want it to kill specifically grifters, like right wing grifters.
Sure.
That would be pretty base.
It is basically killing them because they're not getting vaccinated.
I would feel...
Steering proud is still around.
I don't know if I...
I don't know if I have...
I don't know if I have like the gall to actually like write a person's name in the...
Even if I hate them.
Even if I think they're an objectively bad...
I don't know if I have it in me to be like, I'm going to end this person's life right now.
That's why you're...
Neither do I, but I also can't imagine such a thing existing.
So I'd probably write it thinking it doesn't work.
Ben, look, just give me the death note.
I'll do it.
Honestly.
I'm good.
I hand it and Cheesy immediately writes my name in it.
Yeah, Ben's saying that doesn't work because that's not your fucking name.
Nobody knows my real name.
Let's...
No, this is just they do.
I would put Elon Musk dies in a Tesla.
It blows up and kills him.
Yeah.
I would do every director, every Marvel Cinematic Universe movie, so it could just end.
It would be like...
That would not end it.
I would kill every member of Disney as a company.
That would maybe do it.
Robert Downey Jr. maybe.
When it comes to people who are just sort of stupid, like Elon Musk, I don't know whether
like him, his death is going to be a good thing necessarily.
They probably will.
If he could change his mind with a change mind note, that would be nice.
Who knowing would be cracking news though?
If you just...
Very interesting news.
If you killed...
Elon Musk blows up Tesla and Jeff Bezos.
Rocket blows up.
Wait, if you just kill...
Phil Gates gets COVID.
I think there are a lot of funny little creative ways for each one of them to die.
I could do that.
You could write...
Oh, okay.
I see how it is.
Bensate is totally fine with paying taxes to send drone strikes to kill brown children,
but he can't put one little rich white guy's name to the death note.
Oh, okay.
I see how it is.
Typical hypocrite Americans are okay with paying taxes to blow up brown children.
So Lara is going to commonly live in the comments for this.
I have morality now.
Now that I have control, you always had control.
Oh, yeah.
That's a pretty neo-lib take of you.
True.
It is a little bit.
I'm like, oh no, it's complicated though.
No, international conflicts are complicated.
Maybe some of them are good actually.
They're complicated.
There are just some that are less complicated than others.
I don't think...
Yeah, I said it.
I said it.
I kill Nate.
No, the possibility of like, say, like a second Trump term.
I'd rather just avoid that altogether.
Okay, let's be honest.
Mark Zuckerberg dying would be way better for the world.
Let's fucking not beat around the bush, please.
You gotta admit that.
But the thing with that, the thing with that, I guess the thing with anything is that if
you get rid of one figurehead, there's probably going to be another one.
And then you get rid of that one.
You have a death note.
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
If Trump doesn't run in 2024, they're going to just run someone else.
And it could be someone even worse, honestly.
Oh, darn.
I suppose.
It's just sort of like...
And there's only one page in the death note.
No more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, you know, yeah.
Bam, bam, bam.
What you got to do in...
You got to like...
You could probably set it up to make it think like...
You could probably convince conservatives it's like a curse or something.
And they'll probably fall for it.
I got a good one.
Okay, so Trump...
You write Trump dies, but before he dies, he writes down like QAnon.
Like you must protect QAnon.
And they'll throw people a lot of like, oh no, they're attacking QAnon members.
I killed a guy at Tesco who always IDs me when I'm buying energy drinks, even though I'm fat,
bold, six foot three and 22.
You have to show ID to buy energy drinks.
Yeah, you have to prove that you're over 16 to buy energy drinks.
That's fucking lame.
Bloody nanny state.
Tell you what.
That's true.
Does the Death Note ever run out of pages?
No.
It technically could, but like, you just write small.
Um, fuck it.
Aaron Hansen.
Look, unironically.
Yes.
I would put Alex Jones in it.
I don't care.
I'll do it.
No, he's too funny.
Yeah, he's real funny.
Like I give a fuck.
That's fair.
Okay.
Motherfucker be the funniest motherfucker in the world.
I don't care.
I think it's funny too.
I think, I think he's hilarious.
Like I don't think like, I don't think, um, just cause I was funny,
it doesn't mean they have the right to live.
That's a cheesy quote.
Just cause they're funny doesn't mean they have the right to live.
Yeah, that's a cheesy moment.
That's a cheesy moment.
Cheesy.
That's a real cheesy pill.
That's an absolute cheesy moment, brother.
Absolute cheesy moment.
Just cause they funny, they don't deserve to live.
What a right name of Death Note.
Yeah, for me, it would be like, can you measure the deaths that they cause
by being alive and doing whatever they're doing?
No.
Um, and I have to just be, just people have been positioned to-
I mean, you can to some extent, right?
Just people in position and power.
I don't know.
Maybe for some people.
If people don't catch on that, if people don't catch on that you have the Death Note,
people would just label it, oh no, the billionaire curse.
If you reach this amount of money, you just instantly die
and then people would just kind of accept it.
I would reserve it.
I would reserve it for the sort of person who has so much money and power
that you couldn't even assassinate them if you had like a nation's like military.
Yeah, James Corden, that's who I'd kill.
Yeah, I would definitely put James Corden.
Get that fucking guy, car crash.
What you do is that I don't even know who that is.
It's a very annoying British guy in America.
You could probably kill off a lot of very powerful people,
but then also kill a couple of celebrities
so no one talks about the like powerful people they just talk about.
Oh my God, they forgot.
He's a British actor.
Right in the Death Note, every single one of like the powerful evil guys in the world
slip on a banal appeal, hit their head, die instantly.
That's the way they die every time.
People just get really scared of banals.
It's ironic.
The Death Note is basically just the CIA that existed already.
Oh, what you do is that like, I don't know, maybe like,
you make one of them admit they're a pedophile before they die.
That would be pretty funny.
Or Epstein was right and then one of them dies.
Or like Epstein, like...
If you write something that like can't happen,
then it just does a heart attack, right?
It just defaults to like the normal.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Well, since no billionaires are pedophiles,
that could never happen, so it's impossible.
Okay, this is gonna fuck people over.
I will kill one of the main cast of The Simpsons just so the show ends.
I'll pick one at random.
I won't say which one.
I'll just like flip.
I'll like Power Generator with all their names and be like,
okay, whichever one pops up is gonna instantly die.
I don't care if I have an emotional attack.
Oh, but they never did nothing to nobody.
I'm sorry.
Isn't Bart's voice actress a Scientologist?
Okay, well, yeah, I guess I'll pick her.
Yeah, she is.
Yeah, she is, yeah.
Okay, that makes it easy.
Okay.
It makes me feel a little better.
I'll probably just like just kill off the guy ahead of sight.
Just like, you have to like kill off certain people that like
the whole system kind of breaks down,
but it probably won't happen like that overnight,
but I'm like, there's enough pages.
Like, I mean, in Death Note, like Light is killing so many people,
he must have at least run out of pages by the end,
but he seems to not, you know,
because it's kind of like low-key magical.
No, I feel like they must have addressed that at some point.
Like, surely you run out of pages.
Nah, it's just magic.
He, I think he just, I think he literally just writes really small.
Like, I think that's it.
I just think he just can't run out of pages.
The thing is, he does it for like 10 years, though.
He writes in like random criminals who just like do bad, like petty crimes.
He doesn't, he doesn't kill...
Which is his first mistake.
He doesn't kill that many people.
Yeah, I don't think they ever addressed it on the show.
He might kill like, he might kill like, maybe in the tens of thousands.
I mean, what about when he gets a potato chip and eats it?
Like, he kills a lot of people.
Yeah, but like, there's so many people.
Like, heads of like police unions, um, proud boy members.
There's like so many people out there that you potentially could off,
and then things would be a lot better.
Or you could just convince people.
Like, I feel like Superstition is going to convince a lot of people that,
oh man, something creepy is fucking going on.
Well, that's the thing.
You might want to keep Alex Jones alive for the longest,
just so you perpetrate this idea of the conspiracy and that froze people sent off.
If people really thought, if people really thought that like,
if I get like over a certain amount of wealth, I will die,
I feel like that would, like genuinely, that would genuinely improve the world.
Okay.
Like, if like anyone who has over a billion dollars instantly dies,
and suddenly everyone is like, like, I got to get rid of this money.
I would, I would probably like look for a list of all the...
Oh, they just lie about their net worth.
Congress members like over...
Yeah, they do.
I would just look up all the Congress members over like 80 or around 60,
and just anyone older than 60.
Oh, well, boom, boom, boom, just to clean the slate.
But then you...
Or get rid of all the like...
Get rid of all the like...
Yeah, sure.
But then get rid of all the like conservative judges.
Just one clean swoop.
So it just resets.
See, the thing, the thing I would not do is I would not do it
to a point where people can start seeing a pattern.
I would only do it for a few people, and then I would stop.
Here's the...
Because that's the thing that gets you caught.
No, you bro, you won't get caught because people see patterns when they're not there.
So anything that people like convince are a pattern,
they are going to be thrown off as conspiracy theories.
It's probably a lot more easier.
But that won't...
Just doing a few people won't accomplish anything.
I think that's why you got to kill a lot of people.
People accomplish enough.
Cheesy certainly has put a lot of thought into this.
I do, I think about this a lot actually.
Cheesy has a lot he would do.
Every Steam user in the world.
See, the reason why Leg gets caught, because he didn't fucking realize
there was a super genius, a Sherlock home motherfucker
that also lived in his universe, right?
There isn't an ours, as far as we're concerned.
Unless Hillary uses her heart attack gun on me,
but I'll just snipe Hillary.
Fuck, I'll probably do that.
You have to have a good balance of liberals and conservatives.
Hillary would be pretty high on the list.
Yeah, if you off Hillary, people would be so distracted
while you off a bunch of other conservatives.
You know, things would be way better if Mitch McConnell was gone.
You'd know that for a fact.
Yeah, sure.
Someone else would just do his job.
Then you off that motherfucker.
I don't run out of ammo ever.
I have an infinite heart attack gun on my side, just like Hillary.
Come on.
If we killed, whatever, yeah.
The CIA actually tried making a heart attack gun a while ago.
I think those were in documents that were declassified.
How hard could it be?
But the thing is, they failed.
They couldn't actually do it.
Guys, what if you death-noted Mario?
That would be so fucking wacky.
Everybody playing Mario at the time would lose a lot.
No, not Shigeru Miyamoto. Just Mario.
Every time you put up the game, Mario dies and people get really upset.
Everyone who's playing it at the exact moment you do it just loses one life.
Maybe you could off.
He just comes back.
Nobody notices anything wrong.
What killed me? And then life moves on.
But you have to write his full name of Mario Mario.
I'll probably death-not that.
Or his nephew, Luigi Mario.
I'll probably death-not all the Japanese legislators
are stopping, like, smoking weed in Japan.
Next voicemail?
Sure.
Next fucking voicemail.
Before the FBI knocks at my door.
Yeah, before we get on a list.
I feel like that three-second voicemail got a lot of mileage there.
I'm eating more baby bell, by the way.
Of course. Cheesy bastard.
I'm even cheesier than a certain clown.
Taking the real cheese pill right now.
Oh, yeah.
Next one is called The Final Solution.
Three, two, one, go.
She exists as an artist today.
You have to perform two games.
You've got the morals and you've got the aesthetics.
Morally, Sarah says she beats Andrew Hersey out of the park.
She is an ultra-inclusive, ultra-SJW,
pronouns on bio, X-tumbler, kid who-
Oh, I'm so impressed.
With Striga Walens and everything,
she should make sure she's not to hurt anyone.
While Andrew Hersey is like a lazy,
list-bag who explores his workers and
it's kind of a piece of shit.
But aesthetically, he made Homestuck.
That is a work of art that you guys value a lot.
While she makes, like, a fucking gospel video
that people are forgetting in three days.
So, I think that's where the conflict comes.
I mean, I-
And also, Ben hates women.
That's why he prefer Andrew Hersey.
Well, that's true.
I mean, it's strange to put it in a moral,
like, Sarah Zed doesn't do what Andrew Hersey does,
but her Tumblr stuff doesn't make her a better person.
Just because Sarah Zed does all the things-
Like, it's not-
Like, I guess it's good to do trigger warnings.
It's good to do-
Oh, yes.
It's pronouns and bio.
Like, sure, I agree with all that,
but, like, that doesn't make her, like, a great person
just because she does all those things.
Um, it doesn't make her, like-
Hussie-
You might think-
I don't know.
Whatever.
I don't care.
I don't care if Sarah Zed is a better person than Hussie.
Maybe she is.
It's-
I mean, from my perspective,
they're content creators.
And that's it.
Like, I don't know her.
Yeah.
Or him.
So, it's like, I'm just judging the content.
I like Andrew Hussie's comics.
Yeah, true.
Yeah, Sarah Zed didn't make Psycholonial,
so, you know, I respect it a little bit less.
Psycholonial is great.
And she didn't even mention Psycholonial
in her fucking Homestuck video.
What the fuck is up with that?
Kind of cringe.
Was it out at the time?
Yeah, it was.
She didn't even mention it.
I don't understand.
Next voicemail is called-
What is it called?
Uh, it's called-
There is only a name section.
If I put a name, it's not the title.
Uh, okay.
Three, two, one, go.
All right, it's Friday.
Podcast comes out, right?
Mm-hmm.
Now it's Monday.
I listen to the podcast.
I'm at work.
I'm killing time.
Now I get home from work.
I leave a voicemail.
I say-
Big mistake.
Or whatever happened.
I reply to you.
A few days later, new podcast comes out.
I'm not on it because it was already recorded.
Seven days later, the next podcast comes out.
It's fucked up.
My voicemail's in it, and I say,
Hey guys, last week this.
And you go, last week, that was two, three,
four, five weeks ago.
Ben, what the fuck?
Do you not understand your own schedule?
No.
You're gay.
Yeah.
The last part is true.
Very true.
Yeah, I understand why it's a bit weird,
but I don't want to think about it anymore than you do.
Just try to avoid saying last week.
I don't want to think about it anymore than you do.
So I know we're operating across a week and almost a week long temporal gap here.
I'm just going to pretend that it doesn't exist,
because it's fine for me,
and it doesn't cause me a problem,
and it's your problem.
You need to alter your life to better benefit this guy.
I could change my life to better suit your mood.
Okay.
Better work for the collective.
Nice.
Carlos Santana.
Okay, next one is called Untitled by Edward Edwards.
Three, two, one, go.
All right.
First off, whatever you said in reply to me, Ben, you're wrong.
Yeah.
And I just like to say L plus ratio, plus you fell off, plus you're white.
Anyway, Gib, you're cool.
And Tom, you're not dead.
What do you mean I fell off?
What does that mean?
Like I'm not making the hips like I used to be?
I think I'm not cranking out the bangers anymore.
I feel like to have fallen off the big money,
and now you're doing little baby jobs for babies.
I think that's what that means.
I always did little baby jobs.
It's like a disparaging thing for like,
ah, you used to be big, and now you're just frying burgers
and taking shit.
It's very specific.
It's a simple burger flipper, Ben's saying, how's it come?
Yeah, you used to be big with your Christian lecture,
but now my second one is...
Ben, he used to be big when you were friends with...
Ben, he used to be big when you were friends with Digi, bro.
Now you're enemies with Trixesis.
Yeah, I've definitely, that's a big downgrade for sure.
For sure, yep.
Next voicemail is called a message for Gib and take
from BerserkChip at gmail.com.
One, two, three, two, one, go.
So Gib, I just wanted to let you know that you're my favorite
PCP member, you're super cool and smart and really funny
and based and not cringe like it's whatever, dude.
And something that you said in an episode years ago
was actually what made me become a PCP fan,
because it made me laugh so much.
Somebody in one of the episodes was relating on
what sumo wrestlers eat to maintain their big weight
and you interrupted them and just said, chicken nuggets
and it was the funniest fucking thing I've ever done.
I don't even remember that.
So I just wanted to let you know that you're cool as fuck
and that you should know about yourself because you're awesome.
Chicken nuggets.
Come on, you're awesome, dude.
It's true.
Yeah, I agree.
I really fell off after that chicken nugget.
You fell off and you're white.
That was the peak of her career.
And ratio and the other one.
And L.
And you're British, huge L.
Oh yeah, it's a bonus stat, negative modifier.
British is a minority, you're being slurry at me.
I'm gonna fling and slurry at me.
I'm gonna put you in a blender and turn you into a slurry.
No, don't do that.
Oh, please don't do that.
Oh yeah, we're doing this.
Next voice.
Now I'm going to be chicken nuggets.
Chicken nuggets.
Next voicemail is called on Jesse.
Three, two, one, go.
So are you feeling like really like planned to be the beginning
some like pro wrestling storyline or did Jesse have like a vague idea
that he just improv tentatively came up with it later?
It wasn't supposed to be the beginning.
It was, he started it after Horseshoe Finale.
He did sort of start like another storyline that he abandoned.
Horseshoe Finale wasn't meant to be the beginning.
It was meant to be the end of the storyline.
Right?
I think, wait, well, is he asking whether Horseshoe Finale was planned
to be like the whole Horseshoe saga was planned to be a wrestling thing?
I think Jesse just likes wrestling and he wanted to cut a promo
because he likes doing that.
Yeah.
He definitely planned at some point.
I don't know.
Like it's hard to remember because it's a while ago.
But I get the sense that the first few things were just like
or at least the cantaloupe wedding was just like
fucking Brony's doing reviews.
It can do that.
Or maybe he just thought it was funny.
Wait, cantaloupe wedding.
Maybe he didn't even know about...
The one where he, where Colt Corona debuts, he comes out of the little My Little Pony tent.
I remember that.
And he talks about the cantaloupe wedding.
And I don't know whether he was like riffing on Pony reviewers yet.
But at some point he thought, wouldn't it be funny if I did a whole Pony reviewer thing?
And then it turned into a bigger project as it went.
Yeah.
I mean, if the question is like, was it planned from the beginning?
No.
The Horseshoe Saga definitely like evolved as it went on.
Yeah.
I think that answers the question, right?
Okay.
Oh, okay.
True.
Next one is an image post.
So I'll just post it here.
It's called Ben Gibb and the Pig.
Oh no.
Oh my God.
Come here, you.
Oh, wait a second.
Wait a second.
Come here, you.
He's apologizing for scaring you and you're so welcoming.
Why could I stay mad?
Why did they drop Ben with a receding hairline?
What do you mean?
Why?
That's what I look like.
Fuck you.
Oh, you look like that?
Oh, okay.
Wow.
Do you not know it?
That's the real Ben St.
I'm a.
Okay.
Fuck you.
I'm looking at that and I'm like, that's just a normal looking guy.
Yeah.
Look how bald that guy is.
Fuck you.
You're the one with the problem.
No, okay.
That looks like a full head of head.
Clearly, clearly I pushed the button here.
I am sorry.
This drawing has a receding hairline.
You don't.
It doesn't.
It looks just like a guy.
Fuck.
Okay.
I'll fucking end you.
Look, it's fine.
All right.
I'll fucking go to California.
No, you won't.
And kill you.
Okay.
You won't.
I'm not doing that because I'm afraid of flying.
So I'm not going to do that.
This is like that time that Maddux cropped the camera to take away his balding head from
the video.
Did he do that?
Well, somebody accused him of doing that, but he declined or refused the claim.
Gib has a Lord English fucking rainbow energy.
Yeah.
I was going to say.
It's like cyan, magenta, yellow, and the big spiky teeth.
You're so huge.
I don't know what I'm doing with my hands.
I'm some sort of monster out there.
You're like floating in.
You're like a Lisa mutant.
Yeah.
Pretty cool.
He's cool.
I like it.
I love the pig.
Bring back the pig.
You know, we were too hasty.
First voicemail.
This is the last one.
It's called can't afford the bus frowny face from Jamie Sims 99.
Jamie.sims99.
That gmail.com.
Three, two, one, go.
Hey, Ben.
Can I borrow six quid?
I need to get the bus home.
Six quid?
Was that Simsie?
Well, what's your answer?
Cost six quid for the bus?
Yeah.
That's like eight dollars.
Peak time in Bristol, man.
Peak time?
What the fuck?
It's like a buck 90.
It's like a buck 90 to take the bus here.
Oh, fucking yeah.
All right.
Here in communist America.
Yeah, in fucking miracle land or whatever the fuck it's called.
The fucking roads are paid with gold and you pay gold to get on the bus.
Wait, yeah.
That is really quite expensive, a London fare.
Look, if you need it for a bus ride.
If you need it for a bus ride, you got it.
But you got to buy me some what's like a stupid British slop you would eat over there.
You got to buy me some haggis or something.
The haggis.
Scottish.
You wouldn't find that in Bristol very easily.
Whatever.
Okay.
You got what you.
You got to buy me a, you got to buy me a smack bar and pee wet.
What?
I don't know what that is.
You got to buy me a smack bar and a Kimbo with the pee wet.
That sounds like a sex move.
It's when you put.
It's when you put a chicken pie between bread and then you put the water from the pea soup on it.
You put some pea soup on your sandwich, which is just a pie between bread.
Is that what you think we do?
I saw it.
I saw the video.
I've seen the proof.
What about a, what about a blood pudding?
I had Chinese food last night.
I actually like blood pudding.
I tried blood pudding once and I liked it.
Black pudding is good.
Or yeah, black, black pudding.
I had it for breakfast.
It was pretty decent actually.
It's good pudding.
Blood pudding.
There's a difference between blood pudding and black pudding.
Black pudding, paradoxically, black pudding is the one that is made out of blood.
It's a good one.
Yeah.
So what's blood pudding made out of then?
Black.
Probably also has some blood in it.
It's made out of black.
Yeah.
It's made out of a squid ink.
It's made out of the color black.
It's made out of condensed void energy.
Void, void, void, void, void.
Void, void, void.
I'm looking to, to avoid between two slices of bread and pee all over it.
Oh God.
Hey.
You Brits.
How are you?
I've got, I've got bad news.
I've got bad news.
We've actually got two more voicemails.
Oh my God.
No.
I'm sorry they arrived just now.
We have to, we have to end the episode before there are more voicemails.
This, this one is called a message for Simsies Balls and it's from Simsiefan333 at hotmail.com.
So I guess let's give this one a listen in three, two, one.
This one is me.
Go.
Hello Simsie.
You big smelly willy.
I'm going to suck the sweat out of your balls.
What the fuck?
Your balls are mine for the second Simsie.
How do they know I'm so sweaty?
What the fuck?
I don't think that's the thing.
It's obvious dude.
It's obvious.
Everybody knows.
You got a voice.
It's just in the voice.
We can tell.
Listen, who was that?
Oh no.
Come on.
It was you Simsie.
That one wasn't me.
Who else would do this?
I'm scared now.
I don't like this.
Just look up Simsiefan on Twitter.
They might not answer.
Simsiefan333, but it's spelled with one M.
One of your biggest fans on Kiwi Farms or something.
Because clearly Simsiefan333 with two M's was taken.
Yeah.
It's too popular.
Next one is called Apathetic Android.
This is the last one.
Three, two, one, go.
I hate for procrastinator's podcast.
I fucking hate it.
I can't stop listening.
A single point without literally every single host.
Constantly like vultures try and jump on me
and cannibalize my point to the point where it's
unrecognizable.
I like the idea of a robot listening to a podcast for some reason.
It was really funny.
Sounds more like a demon.
Why is he listening if he doesn't even like it?
He's a robot.
He can do anything.
Well, there's plenty of people in the comments that listen all the time and they hate it.
Yo, it's true.
Shoutouts to you guys.
Shoutouts to the commenters.
Sorry, the podcast is what it is.
I know none of us are happy about it.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
We've all got to deal with the hand we're dealt in life.
This is what we got.
This is what you've got.
When life gives you the procrastinator's podcast, what do you do?
You make the gamer's zone.
You make gamer's zone out of it.
You make wasted content out of it.
Oh, finally.
You make a better podcast.
You're right.
You make voicemails.
You make comments.
You make the best.
You make band camp albums.
Well, guys, this is the end of the Pizza Party podcast.
Finally, we found it and we ended it.
We better end it before we get more voicemails.
Yeah.
No more voicemails.
No more.
That's it.
That's the cutoff point.
Thepatreon.com slash the procrastinator's podcast for something.
I don't know.
I'm sure there's something there that is money to eat Minecraft server.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Sure.
Whatever.
And speakcribe.com slash PCB voicemail.
If you want to be one of these fine fellows, fellows or fellows, it's gender neutral.
It's either, either or.
Yeah.
In the, in the, these fucking part of the show.
Road to Radcon backers.
Remember to send your change of address if necessary to the Kickstarter.
If you didn't order the book, but you want it, I will be selling the extra.
I probably have like 20 extra copies at the end.
So I will make another post.
If you're, if you're a late comer, you're like, I want the book.
I'll be selling the book over at Patreon.
I'm going to get a quick tweet about it at some point in the future, but there's limited
supply, very limited, very limited.
Didn't get that many extras.
So, okay.
Just putting that out there.
And I think that's all.
I think that's all I have to say about that.
Any, any, any final words?
Rose.
Read Villainverse.
Okay.
Yeah.
Read Villainverse.
This podcast really reminds me of Villainverse.
You ever seen the Zimzies?
There aren't big Villainverse flags from that.
Yeah.
I'm getting, I'm getting a new microphone tomorrow.
So I'm probably going to start live streaming regularly now that my audio won't be pooh-pooh
die-rear.
You're going to live stream.
You're going to live stream yourself reading Villainverse, guys.
So.
Yeah, exactly.
That's the first.
Exciting stuff.
That's the first stream that I'm just going to be tracing all the art from Villainverse.
Yeah.
Making their boobs smaller.
Smaller.
No, bigger.
Wait.
Wait, what?
Who even is, who is even happening anymore?
Okay, I guess that's the end of the show.
And that's the end of the show.
And goodbye and see you next week.
Goodbye.
Love you.
Bye.