The great thing about the ancient alien theory is the fact that we can compare modern achievements with stories from our ancient past.
And so if today we're able to create a two-headed dog with six legs,
is it possible that a similar creature existed thousands of years ago?
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of the PCP.
I'm the best guy ever and welcome to my unidentified podcast. No one knows what it is. I am here with Tom Oliver.
Aliens built the pyramids. They genetically engineered us human beings. They crashed in Roswell.
We use their down ship to create microprocessors, and that's why Intel is the thing.
Alienware computers are actually alienwares.
The proof is in the pudding. Hippocrit is here.
Nate.
Wait, you said something. Cut the whole podcast out. I made a mistake with what I said.
I was going to make a joke, but I said the whole thing wrong three times in a row. Just kill me.
Cut myself out of the podcast and put a beep boop noise.
We'll get back to that. Lethal Aurora Mage is here.
Do we have ghost aliens? That is the question.
I think they might be the same thing. And of course, Munchy wears tiny hats.
Guys, I'm in a signal from outer space right now. Oh my God, I'm going to type down wow on my paper because they like World of Warcraft.
This is the wow signal, but that's World of Warcraft now.
We really have evolved since we were those aliens long ago.
Well, everybody, we're talking about aliens today.
The most powerful race on the planet Earth.
The most benevolent beings with their compassionate eyes.
I am Paradot. I love Steven Universe. I am everything to me.
I just want to go on record as saying my absolute favorite emoji is without a doubt the alien face emoji.
I copyright it. It is my property. Every time you use it, you owe me one American dollar.
Let's actually check out these Urban Dictionary definitions.
We've got a double for you, everybody. So number one, we've got aliens.
Wait, did we explain what the PCP is?
Oh, we totally forgot. Thank you for reminding me.
So the PCP, everybody, is a podcast of a bunch of internet content creators who got together and they just have fun.
They just love goofing. And we love aliens. We love aliens.
It's a big proponent of alien culture.
We feel more related to aliens than you fucking disgusting, normie humans out there listening to it.
So that's why we decided to talk about our spirit brethren today.
People always say, does morality come from within the soul of man?
Or does it come from a higher being? Or does it come from God?
Or the third option, did it come from aliens? That's what I want to get into.
Okay, but here, Urban Dictionary, give us some information about what the fucking aliens even is.
Okay, here we go. Top definition, people from outer space.
Generally, peace, loving, and wise, they've come to Earth because we've got Velcro and they love that shit.
That's the thing. The example is terrible, so I'm not going to read it.
But then our other definition here is UFO.
Okay, UFO, abbreviation for unidentified flying object.
The USAF defines a UFO as anything that relates to any airborne object,
which by performance, aerodynamic characteristics, or unusual features,
does not conform to any currently known aircraft or missile type,
or which cannot be identified as a familiar object.
Okay, well thanks point, Dexter, for the textual definition.
So the United States Air Force just confirmed the existence of aliens if they have a definition on record.
Is that true? How so?
Because you just said the USAF, right?
If they have a definition for it, they must acknowledge that it's a thing that can happen.
If it can happen, that means it's real.
If it can happen, it is real.
It sounds like...
I watched Ancient Aliens, alright?
I know exactly how you have to do this logical chain of how aliens work.
I never once watched Ancient Aliens.
Yeah, like when in Google Docs, when I type teleport, it corrects it as if it's not a word,
but when I type aliens, it's a word.
Therefore, it exists.
Oh shit!
It's in the database, it's real, probably built by aliens, manipulating us right now.
I fucked it up again.
Oh, there's a static that cut into my...
I'm back now, I'm fine.
Aliens are interrupting your thought process.
They're scrambling my brain, making me not funny, and the audience is just hearing static, so it's fine.
Do you don't want to let you talk?
Let's just cut to the chase here. Aliens are real.
Okay, okay, they may be real. Have they visited the Earth?
Yes, they've seen Steven Universe.
Oh, yeah.
The sneakle are here, and they're going to fuck us up.
My opinion is that the aliens are objectively real, but the only ones we've seen have been really funny,
and the other ones that we haven't seen since.
We're just waiting for that.
The fact of the matter is that aliens are real, and they're illegal, and they're crossing the border every day,
and Trump's going to fix that shit. Stop making fun of him.
Is alien like a mean to use as a word? I don't know, is that like a negative implication there?
No, it's not.
Because now it's undocumented immigrants, you know how that's changed?
Yeah, they keep changing it.
I guess it's just like Judge Collins talked about the softening of language every time.
It's only the legal alien that's sick, because an alien in that terms is just someone who is living in the country,
but it's not a resident of that country.
Like Phil Collins' famous song, Legal Alien.
Like all of the fucking aliens that crashed here in Roswell are now being held prisoner in Area 51, as we reverse-
I think they were a diet of old age.
I think they were forcibly bred to reproduce so we could continue to study them.
I wouldn't put it past us.
Maybe aliens are like space elves, and they're undying. It's very possible.
Who do you think produces more precom? Alph or ET?
Alph.
Definitely Alph.
Alph gets around.
No.
I mean, have you seen his nose? I mean, come on.
That's not his nose.
So the universe is really big, right? It's really, really, really big.
I don't know about that.
It's really, really, really fun.
Okay, well take my word for it.
I've looked into this a bit.
I've watched Star Trek. It's hilarious.
I've seen that. It's really goofy out there.
Okay, because the universe is so big, and human beings have explored and can see such a tiny little baby-sized percentage of it.
So as the discussion goes, as the argument goes, there's so many opportunities for life out in the cosmos.
When you get into this stuff, immediately religious people think that there's something magical and special about Earth
that God created man in his own image and made us here and shaped the universe around us.
So yeah, God created the entire fucking universe to house one little basically insignificant planet here
that nobody gives a fuck about that we can't do anything with, just like a goof.
Well, I'd say that was the inefficient answer.
I don't think anyone here is doubting the possibility of humanoid aliens in the universe in general.
I just want to make the point for the listeners out there.
For any doubting Thomases, they will be deleted as will Tom from this podcast immediately.
This was my topic idea! You can't delete me!
That's true.
Did you know-
Actually, the opposite of a doubting Thomas. You're the woke Thomas.
I'm taking that term back. I'm fucking- I'm suing the federal government to get custody of that term.
Bastards.
Again, what were you saying?
Here's an article thing that I read, and I have no idea whether it's true.
But did you know, guys, that there's life in our solar system on Mars?
In, like, the under-under-the-surface oceans on Mars, people have found small little bacteria.
It's much of getting invaded by aliens right now.
Stop! Please!
Is that what's happening?
Please stop them! Please!
They're trying to- they're doing everything they can to disrupt this podcast so that the word does not get out,
that we're under their shit, and we know they're among us every fucking day.
Yeah, I was about to- I was about to announce something, but, you know, I was interrupted,
and now my brain is, like, scrambled, like I remember what I was gonna say.
Here, maybe this image will help you out, check out this.
I'm just a thing.
Something cool.
That's a good one.
Just so everyone knows, we are constantly, like, in our chat dumping more alien images
just to keep us woke as possible while we're at it.
I just Google searched funny cartoon aliens, and I'm just posting all of the cool images
that I found scrolling down at Google Image Search.
Maybe we'll remember to post a link to all of these images.
No, you can play along. Just type in funny cartoon aliens and just laugh at them while we're laughing.
Yeah.
All right, continue.
Okay, you know, Tom posts a picture here that makes it a good argument.
It's like, okay, if aliens weren't real and didn't visit Earth, how did they build everything in prehistoric Earth?
Why were they responsible for every major achievement of humanity, you know, up to the invention of the cuckold?
The blocks of the pyramids cannot be carried by men on their shoulders.
They just couldn't do it. It was just too heavy.
You really think that a bunch of fucking people dragged multiple ton blocks across the sand?
No, aliens did it. The amount of precision that the pyramids are built with, you can't even do that today with modern technology.
Do you think a bunch of life, do you think a bunch of fucking monkeys with sticks can make that shit?
Do you think a bunch of Minecraft characters built those?
The true facts all point to aliens just being really swole and they carried them on their shoulders because they're really strong.
And then instead, they didn't have spaceships, they just jumped away from our planet to another one.
They just had very strong legs.
Okay, let me ask you this. Does anyone have any good reason to believe that aliens were actually on Earth ever?
Is there any justification other than like, oh, they must have been here.
Google search the Anunnaki, god damn it.
What is it?
The Anunnaki that shit's fucking real, dude.
All of the ancient creation myths are actually just misinterpretations of alien visitation.
Look, watch ancient aliens. It lays it all out. Shit's fucking real as fuck, alright?
Everything that happened in the world is aliens.
Have you seen all of ancient aliens? I don't know how much there is.
I've seen quite a bit.
And I've seen it all.
Is it always that guy? Is it that one dude?
It's not always that guy. You know what the interesting thing is?
Okay, I'm gonna blow your fucking mind right now.
This is how I know that ancient aliens is legit.
Alright, so I just linked...
No, no, no. Listen, this is some real fucking shit right now, okay?
This is a conspiracy theory that's gonna blow your mind to shit.
Alright, so everybody knows what the ancient aliens guy looks like, right?
Everybody knows that.
Alright, people at home, play along with me here.
Alright, you're about to have your fucking brain expanded.
You're gonna be like, blow.
You're about to reach level 7 Christ consciousness.
Exactly, this is good. You're gonna get at least two levels of Christ consciousness.
Expansion here.
So, Google, ancient aliens guy, go to images, put that in your brain.
Now, go to Google Images and Google search Babylon 5.
Alright, that's a television show, okay?
Babylon 5 Centauri.
And then, be amazed that the Centauri aliens look exactly like the ancient aliens guy.
It's the exact same thing. They're literally the same.
Oh no.
These fucking guys.
Is that a fucking coincidence? No, it's not!
I even see pictures of him posing with pictures of them.
He's trying to tell us something. He knows shit, alright?
Ancient aliens is 100% legit.
Babylon 5 is a realistic account of aliens and how it's going to go down in the future.
This shit is real. It's all fucking real.
He's not the only one. Look at this shit.
I'm seeing some major similarities here.
Kim Jong-un or whatever.
They're among us, dude.
And you know what the fun in Babylon 5?
The Centauri are the closest alien species to humans because they live in Alpha Centauri.
They're their star. That's how it's good.
It's all coming together, dude. The shit is fucking real.
I mean, mathematically speaking, they're the most likely to be the real aliens
that fucking steal my parking spot every day at work.
These are other fuckers.
What are you gonna do, man?
Sometimes you just gotta let the aliens have their way before they fucking kill you.
My favorite alien is the guy from Doctor Who.
He wears a suit.
No, not that guy.
He wears a suit and if you look at him, you're like, oh, god, it's a scary guy.
But then if you turn around, if you're not looking at him, you completely forget his entire existence
and the fact that he was just there.
And if you turn around, you're like, oh, my god, it's a scary guy.
And then you turn around again, you're like, wait a minute.
Why am I here? Oh, my god, it's a scary guy.
Oh, no, there's nothing there.
Ben Sane.
Exactly.
Mike, if anyone knows that Doctor Who alien, that's like a real cool one.
Wait, is that the one that's the one that teleports?
Like the weeping statues or whatever?
No, no, no.
Those are like angels or something.
I'm gonna type in Doctor Who.
The Europeans immediately jump in and correct us on our lack of Doctor Who lore knowledge.
My favorite aliens are the alien kids.
And the reason I like them so much is their debut album, Alien Rap,
songs that lie from Planet Lump by the alien kids,
where they wrap it up their alien food and the ways which they process it.
Also about education reform.
Yeah, I'm with you on that.
My favorite aliens, I'm quite partial to, you know that blue guy,
who like a whole narrative was built around him from that like,
I'm blue, I'm blue, I'm blue, I'm blue.
No, I was gonna say that.
Oh, you like, okay, well that guy's got like a name and a lore and a huge back story
and like all kinds of tie-ins.
Can we just go on record though that as cool as that guy is,
the best blue aliens to ever exist are the aliens from Interstellar 555.
Come on.
I do love them intensely.
They got a bit more depth to them, all right?
There's a lot of fan and lore around this blue dude,
but I like going direct to the source with the canon lore.
That's where I like to live.
Yeah, Gib, go on.
I was trying to remember the name of this 80s alien kid movie,
kid alien movie, and I can't remember what it is.
It's like a group of kids and there's a cool one and there's a nerdy one
and he has a computer and he types on the computer
and he makes like an anti-gravity bubble
and then they build a spaceship and they use the computer and make a bubble
and they go into space because the kid was like getting dreams of like alien technology
and then they go into space and then they get to the spaceship
and the aliens does a goofy fucking plastic weirdo in a suit
and they have a fun time and then the alien's dad comes back
and he said, have you been talking to the humans again?
And he's like, I'm sorry dad, but in aliens,
so you don't know that that's exactly what they're saying,
but it's probably, it's like you can infer.
And then the kids go home and what the fuck is that movie?
I really like it.
Home Alone 3, Journey to Big Water, I don't know.
Guys, I have something really fucking important.
Go search media aliens and you will see some crazy fucking images.
Do that to viewers.
Media aliens.
You see a picture of Bill O'Reilly?
You see like a movie toaster?
I don't see Bill O'Reilly.
Cowboys and aliens.
Dude, the aliens from Cowboys and Aliens are so fucking scary
because they're with cowboys.
I like this extreme UFOs and aliens ones.
Okay, well, this is all great and all,
but I wanted to ask you guys a specific question.
And it's that, okay, if aliens are real and they visit Earth,
should they be allowed to kill human beings?
Should they be allowed to wipe out humanity
if they deem that we are inferior and not worthy
of ascending to a galactic civilization?
Explorers, 1985.
Okay, that's the one, that's the one.
Anyway, why would they be able to?
What if they are able to assess that humanity will advance
to some like stage where it could be a threat?
Like, you know, like in Mass Effect, right?
The Reapers may or may not be some sort of like white blood cell
that wipes out, you know, like civilizations that advance too far
or something like in Die Buster and Gun Buster.
That same idea is present where like humanity is growing
and reaching out to the stars and whatnot
and the space monsters are thought to maybe be some sort of like
white blood cell that wipes out like civilizations
when they get to advanced.
And they don't really explore why that happens,
but perhaps one possible reason could be too much stuff happening.
Out in the real world, could fuck some shit up.
Could maybe, I don't know, cause problems.
I'm thinking from the perspective of humanity,
fuck that entirely, that's just a cock mentality
to just bend over and not expand throughout the universe
because oh, maybe would kill some things and do some bad stuff.
Fuck you.
I mean, it would be very hypocritical of them considering
that they're out in space and now killing stuff.
Well, it's, you know, it really is just like
the whole anti-spiral argument from Gern-Lagan
that the anti-spirals-
What's this about white blood cells?
I mean, seriously.
The aliens have green blood.
This doesn't even make sense to them.
They're about the black blood cells.
But, yeah, so like the anti-spirals and Gern-Lagan,
like their whole deal is they stopped like the spiral guys.
You know, the spiral just represents like evolution
and growth of humanity and whatnot.
And the anti-spirals like they deliberately put a cap on themselves
so they cannot go any higher and they gave themselves the job
to like squash, you know, like anything out there that gets too,
that starts growing too much and could get out of control.
And they were proven wrong and they were doing the bad thing
and it was done.
Well, I mean, to be fair, to be fair,
one of the things I like about Gern-Lagan
is it doesn't actually tell you that they were in fact wrong,
but what it gives you is it-
I don't know.
You got punched in the face pretty good at the end.
He did get punched real hard.
I thought that was definitely some subtextual thing there.
You're not wrong.
A little bit of subtext.
It's clear where the intense lie,
but like it allows a degree of ambiguity
where it is true that the human beings may in fact fuck some shit up,
but I actually prefer that they don't confirm
that everything works out perfectly.
Yes, we agree.
Instead, it leaves you on this note of that everyone like agrees
that like, okay, we are all going to work specifically
to maximize happiness, freedom, and avoid this catastrophic thing
that could come with too much of either of those first ones.
Well, I would not let any aliens fucking tell me what to do
or my buddy's here on earth because that's thought crime.
I think it's bullshit.
You can instead, if you were an alien race
full of advanced technology and you were able to travel
through the stars and all this shit
and you could make some sort of calculated sort of projection
on the future of humanity and you thought that it was going bad.
Instead of being like, well, you guys are going to fuck up
in a couple centuries, so you're dead now.
I'd be like, this is an opportunity to kind of guide this society
towards a better understanding.
I think just the act of interstellar contact
would fundamentally shift the progression
and trajectory of human interest dramatically.
So I think just by being introduced to the concept of aliens
we would change our priorities
and the way society interacts in general, simply from that fact.
And I think it would be hoovan upon aliens
if they thought that we're going bad to use their position
to try and help.
Basically, they need to be the America of the galaxy
and intercede and spread space democracy everywhere
and do nation building.
That's interesting because Star Trek deals, as you know,
with this very issue and it's the Prime Directive.
And of course, in Star Trek First Contact,
the movie based from the next generation
in which they go back in time to the moment where
human beings and Star Trek develop their own warp drive,
which is the technology you really need for faster than light travel
in order to be a force in the galaxy and in the universe
outside of just your own little solar system.
And as soon as they activated their warp drive,
they were detected by some nearby Vulcans
who don't live too far away.
And then they came down and were like,
oh, hey humans, let's be friends now.
And it was through that that they developed the Federation
and grew into Starfleet and all that good stuff
that happened afterward.
So the best case scenario is Star Trek.
Star Trek and Starfleet and all that cool stuff.
That's the best case scenario.
But it is entirely possible that what if the humans
just met the Klingons first or something?
Not even the Klingons, but something even worse,
like the fucking Borg.
And it fucks them up real bad.
And they get whatever kind of bad things happen to them.
I'm not even advocating for anything here.
I'm just expressing alien issues.
Hashtag alien issues.
Relatable alien problems.
Stealing our jobs, crushing the working class, alien issues.
I think it's retarded and stupid
and frankly you should feel bad
for even suggesting anything like that.
Because aliens are probably not going to have any...
Well, I'm not saying they won't at all,
but they might not have any philosophical insights whatsoever.
It's possible they might just be like fucking like a dog or something.
And they'll just be beasts of the land.
No, that's silly.
An alien couldn't get here
without a certain level of development.
Sociological and technological.
I'm not saying that if we meet aliens,
if we meet aliens,
then it's very possible that there are just like thousands of planets
that are just full of just bum-fuck-retard dominant species
that have no real abilities whatsoever.
And so, I don't know.
And even if there is a highly developed species
that gets to us first,
it's not guaranteed that they will have any sort of the same sort of like,
you know, democracy or ideas such as that.
There's absolutely no way to tell that they will have anything
even resembling that whatsoever.
And so, I don't think...
If an alien species does meet us,
there's no way to tell if it will even know what killing is,
because life just might work so different on that planet.
Because, you know, all of our ideas is built on how life is on Earth.
But if there's just some weird fucking crazy planet,
there's no way to know what its needs or wants are,
everything will have needs or wants.
I hear what you're saying,
but I think there are some basic biological foundations
that make a lot of things like life versus death.
Well, life versus death, for example,
I think is a pretty clear cut one
that any alien that advances to the point
where like they can, you know, travel through the stars and whatnot,
I think we'll have some fundamental understanding of like what life is
and probably respect it.
I mean, they might operate in a society that just like works on total enslavement.
Trolls. Trolls.
Or trolls, there you go.
Alternate trolls, yeah.
Were alternative trolls even that different from normal humans?
What were their distinguishing characteristics?
They were super fucking strong.
They had crazy like, like PSI powers.
And they were super fucking violent.
They like killed everyone for like looking at the bad.
And there was a really rigid like, like India caste system.
But then Carcat just like was best friends with Dave.
How come he didn't just like kill Dave?
That was after like, that was after a while.
That was after a lot of homosexual propaganda.
So what you're telling me is hashtag not all trolls.
Yeah, hashtag not all trolls.
Okay, all right, there we go.
Yeah, it's all trolls.
Fuck all trolls.
You can all burn.
Every troll was an MMM.
And fucking one of them had a bullet in them.
You bite the bullet, asshole.
Die.
I'm gonna say yes.
I'm very happy that Homestuck is part of this conversation.
I just want to say that.
I don't really have like a point.
I'm just, I just remembered.
What's your favorite Homestuck alien?
Oh, John Egbert.
Yeah, it's mine as well.
Hey, so, okay.
So does anyone have any personal experience?
Like, has anyone ever come up to you and said like,
check me out of a fucking alien
and then directly annihilated you?
You know, like a story like that.
I'm interested in that sort of thing.
Do you want to know about the story of the alien that got away?
Yes, absolutely.
So when I was a little kid,
I loved, I loved aliens.
I loved space.
I loved science class.
We were talking about like the solar system
and astronomy and all that shit.
And it was really cool.
And I loved science.
Then I was like...
So I was at the carnival.
The carnival was in town.
And so I was,
and I was all about aliens.
And this was back like in 1990,
whatever, old, olden times
before Munchie was even a twinkle in his dad's eye.
And I wasn't a twinkle in my dad's eyes ever since.
Exactly.
He explains everything.
So I'm at this carnival
and I'm playing the games and stuff
and I decide there's this big alien prize.
And I was like, that's what I want.
So it's typical like little green alien
but you were like, I had like a hoodie on
and it was a cool thing.
And I was like, that's what I want.
And I spent all day trying to win this alien prize at this game.
I don't remember what game it was.
And I got it.
And I felt like the coolest guy in the entire world.
It was big.
It was like 18 inches tall.
It was one of those big, hard to get prizes.
You are literally paradigm.
Exactly.
I resonated with that scene a lot.
And this story takes a tragic turn here though.
Because I brought it home
and I brought it to my mom
and my grandmother.
And they're both very religious.
And they thought aliens were the devil.
So they refused to let me have it.
And I was like, no.
I worked for this.
This is the result of my labor.
This taught me a lesson about capitalism
in the world.
How dare you take this from me.
But they bribed me.
They bribed me.
They were like, alright, you capitalist pig.
We will give you
that toy from Lost in Space.
That other space movie that you really like right now.
If you give us this.
And I was like,
But
I won this and they're like, yes.
But we're going to be the government incentives
giving you things for free.
If you vote
Democrat.
So I voted Democrat.
I got rid of it.
And they made me feel bad because
I thought my soul was going to burn in health forever
for having this alien toy that I won.
And I never saw it again.
And every time I see the alien
wear logo, I'm like,
There he is.
I'm going on to bigger things.
I'm so happy.
I'm CEO of a computer parts company.
We can all just agree
that the little stereotypical
green alien guy with the big ass eyes
is the pinnacle of graphic design.
I agree.
Completely.
Do you guys ever see that post?
There was a post of some photos
of a claimed real photo
of a gray alien with the big
eyes and like, you know, like the small lips
and everything, whatever. And then someone drew over it
quickly as a sketch.
And then again, it was the perfect proportions
of an anime girl.
I'm just saying, dude.
It's a conspiracy.
Anime girls.
I'll try and find it.
I'll try and look for it.
Actually, you know what that exactly reminds me?
There was a chapter in Frank and Fran
where there is a, which is this horror
like monster surgery.
This particular chapter is about
the main character, Matarake Fran.
Matarake Fran.
People just come to her and ask for crazy surgeries
because she's like a god of surgery.
And she can literally do anything, including bring the dead back to life sometimes.
She's just nuts.
In this case,
a famous actress approaches her
and is like, Fran, you're famous, help me.
I, okay, there's a guy
that I love, that I want to marry, date, etc.
The thing is though,
he's only into that fucking 2D shit.
He's not into 3D pig disgusting.
He's not into that.
So what I need you to do,
okay, there's the image he posted.
It's fucking awesome.
So what I need you to do, Fran,
is make me look like a fucking anime girl.
I-R-L.
Do whatever you gotta do
to my fucking body to make it happen.
So like, she like shortens her limbs.
She like, okay, so what she does with her brain
is this is fascinating.
So the anime babes have big old heads.
She replaced her skull
with a gigantic dome thing
and then has her brain suspended
by wires inside the thing
with a big cavern.
I know, it's fucked up.
Like, Frank & Fran is a fucked up series, but I love it.
But the culmination of this
is that slowly, when she becomes more and more anime,
she-
her eyes getting big in all kinds of crazy shit.
Increase anime!
There was just a knob.
Yes, there was a knob.
I'm talking overdrive here.
So like, Nia's to say her body was getting
super fucked up the whole time.
She has to wear a wig now
and she has to do maintenance
on her body and shit because she's a fucking freak now.
But ultimately, what happens is
the guy does start to love her
because she is like his anime babes.
Yeah, he's doing it.
So that happens and then like, I think they either get married
or they're like, I don't know, they're together for a night
and so the guy's laying in bed
and she's like, yeah, I'm coming out to come fuck you
and then as she
as he turns, see her climbing onto the bed,
there's like a light shining from outside the window
and her wig has fallen off
and all her clothes are off and you can see her body
and she just looks exactly like one of these
fucking gray aliens.
Exactly the fucking same.
And it's pretty much like the climax of the whole arc.
You know what this means, dude?
This means that anime is an alien plot
to make us want to fuck them
to make us sympathetic to the alien cause.
Exactly.
The Japanese have been taken over by aliens.
By the way, I just want to say
When did like fucking
Astro Boy come out and shit?
What year was that?
The 30s, the 20s, I can't remember.
The 40s? A while ago.
Not the 20s.
Wasn't that long ago, was it?
No, cause Disney started like the 10s of the 20s
so it was later than that.
I think it was like 50s.
I'd say like the 40s or something.
I don't know, whatever. Around there, around there.
In the background of my audio
is like a very like consistently
weird booming base.
That's just my alien spaceship.
Don't worry about it.
Wait, wait, no, no, no.
Okay, this is some real shit right now, okay?
So, I'm going to drop a conspiracy theory.
Christ conscious of the other level.
Roswell, Roswell at the UFO incident
in mid-1947
at United States Air Force's balloon
crashed in a ranch near Roswell, New Mexico.
Yeah, okay, Wikipedia, keep telling us that.
1947,
Roswell, five years later
in 1952, Astro Boy
is released. Oh my god.
What do you think it is?
Mega Man came out that pod.
Wow. He came out.
Guys, my favorite monster,
no, I'm sorry, my favorite alien
of all time.
I can't decide if it's the Flatwoods monster
or it's the Hopkinsville's goblin.
They're both a goblin.
Those are excellent choices.
Here's the original
depiction of the Flatwoods monster,
by the way.
Okay, I dig it. He's impressive.
Whoa.
This is Waluigi.
He's Waluigi
in a wedding dress.
He just wants to be loved.
No, but the
canonical version is
fucking dope. Look how cool it is.
Holy shit.
Yeah, the Flatwoods monster.
I don't want to go to the Hopkinsville's goblin
because he's just a little fucking guy who's an asshole.
Fuck you.
Dude, do you know
the story of the Hopkinsville's goblin?
I have no idea. Okay, so fucking
basically
these two fucking
in the middle of fucking nowhere,
I forget where, like New Jersey
I think, anywhere.
Anywhere in the world
can happen to you. Okay.
Um, you know, just these fucking
hillbilly fucking retards,
you know, fuck you if you farm.
We're in their house.
And just these fucking, like, little, like, gray,
like, like fucking, like, goblin
fucking asshole, like, sable eyes.
These fucking sable eyes came out.
And they started, like,
popping in and out of windows, like, playing
playing peek-a-boo and shit and, like, making fun of these people.
Making fun of them, they're, like, waiting
shit, being real assholes and
playing pranks. Playing mean pranks.
One of the dads would walk out and, like,
the door was slightly open and he walked in the other room
and then a bucket fell on his head.
Fucking mean. That's what they were.
They're just pranksters. They're just mean people.
They're jerks and fuck you.
Goblin, you're mean.
That's why I like them, because they're really prank.
Alright. That sounds good.
I think Mage was trying to say something before. Mage?
Um, I wasn't,
but I had something in mind, so you maybe
you read my mind. Okay.
Okay.
But first, I have to open the door for my cat.
Sorry.
Well, in the meantime, everyone, I just,
while she's doing that for a second, everyone look at
the greatest alien who ever lived. His name is
Jiren. He is from Dragon Ball Super
and he is canonically stronger than God,
proving that aliens are superior to God
and my God. He is
the best of all time. Also, he looks
exactly like me in every way.
Alright. Alright. He is me.
He is me. Okay. Now we're just projecting.
I'm serious. Look at my newest
video where I'm talking about Star Trek. I put
a picture of him up. It looks exactly like me
wearing my sunglasses. I'm just saying.
Okay, mate. Lay it on us.
Okay. Well, it's not
that big of a story, but, you know, when you
asked, like, if anyone had some sort
of experiences or whatever. So
one time, I was around
10 to 12 or so,
just a little, little Mage
running around late in the evening
without supervision.
I was with a friend at that time. It was
really late in the evening and it was almost
dark. I think, like, the sun was almost
completely down.
We were both going home and we were
near his house and just at the corner
of my eye, I spotted something and then I
looked up at the sky, not, like, directly
above me, but, like, in the horizon.
They were, like,
several lights sort of flashing and something
was flying by before disappearing behind
a building. And
I didn't know
what it was because it was very, well, I mean,
literally a UFO. I'm not
implying it was an alien UFO, but, like...
Sure, sure.
We both saw it and we didn't know what
it was and we ran towards the horizon to see
if we could, you know, see it behind the
building. But by the time we got to the building
it was already out of sight.
And, like,
I told my parents about it and they said,
oh, it could have been a plane or something because
planes have, like, you know, lights on when they're
flying in darkness and stuff.
But, like, it looked too
close to the ground and, like, the lights
were too big and spaced a bit differently
from the planes.
And also, like, the plane had, like,
no real reason to
be flying over there because we didn't
have an airport in my city and we never
saw planes ever fly.
Like, now we do, but back in those
days when I was a little...
We never got planes flying over
our places, like...
You know, Major, I'm glad you brought that up.
What year was this? It was, like,
over ten years ago.
Uh, I think...
Was it on September 11th?
One by any chance?
I'm just saying.
Just checking in.
You know, I was gonna say, depending on how old
you are, but if it's only, like, ten years ago
probably not, it might have been some sort of Russian
thing, possibly, since I know you were
close to there.
And, I mean, it could have been,
like, you think you only got independence
from Russia, like, one year
before I was born.
Oh, really? Are the Russians
aliens?
Basically. Maybe.
Putin is superior to all the life forms on the planet,
so it's probably true. I need to interject here
because I'm on thealiens.wikia.com
fandom page
and I'm looking at the Anunnaki
and I'm in some deep shit right now.
Alright, check it out.
He's in hot water right now.
Check the shit out.
Anunnaki, general information,
whole world,
Aldebaran,
habitat, earth,
body type, vagina humanoid,
sapience level,
super,
behind the scenes
information,
universe, real.
What?
This is some real stuff.
There's a lot of aliens. I mean, we aren't even
gonna get into the aliens that populate the
imaginary universes out there. There's just
too many to go into.
The accompanying picture really sells this whole
thing. It's
some great a shit.
Let me tell you.
Oh, shit.
Wow.
Are those the aliens, those big bearded
motherfuckers? Figures
believe to be the Anunnaki. I believe it's some sort
of sculpture or artistic representation.
Viewers, if you want to understand
what this looks like, if nobody edits this in
cough then. You know what's great though?
The main figure is basically
just, imagine like the
representation of Sargon of Akkad with
googly eyes. That's pretty much what we're looking at right here.
Right. Confirm.
By the way, I just want to point out how amazing
it is that there is a category for
universe, real versus not real.
Think of how many entries there are
in here that depict universes that are
not real. This is why you gotta watch
Ancient Aliens. That's just the beginning of the
fucking rabbit hole for all of this shit.
This is a huge arc. It goes on forever.
Let's just throw out the concept of real versus not real
because that's garbage anyway. It never meant anything.
Once we get that out of the way, then we can
get into the real shit where you are
right now.
When I was a young lad,
I was a very smart boy.
I hadn't actually read The Great Gatsby.
I hadn't actually read The Great Gatsby
but I imagined that I had.
I was a smart
cookie. Anytime
aliens were brought up, I would immediately be
like, that's probably not true.
It's probably like this and that.
Every time my little brothers would
say, whoa, what's that? That's a blink
and light moving across the sky. It's an airplane.
It's not real. It's not alien.
I never had
a time in my childhood
where I believed anything because
I think I was told they weren't real
before I had an experience like
that.
I thought I was real smart
and stuff.
I would love rationalizing things in my head
like, I don't know
how that could be but
let me think of the ways that it could be fake
and I would be that kid.
So that
yeah, I ruined
my little brothers' lives.
They now don't believe.
You know what the most important aliens in my life
are? The aliens from Chicken Little.
Because they were so fucking gay
and they're like, you destroy...
they mess up that guy's fucking baseball
game.
No, I can raise you one better, dude.
You know what the most important aliens
are? The Fleblings
from ChexQuest. Those guys
were fucking around.
Hell yeah.
Do you remember the
weapon you had when you ran out of ammo? You had a spoon
and you scooped them up because they were
goo. I do remember that.
That was some real shit, dude. It was absolutely devastating.
It deeply impacted the way I eat cereal to this fucking day.
I remember something.
My favorite alien
is not whatever I said.
It is, in fact, a very specific
comic
in the Xenomorph
whatever comic universe.
The first movie's pretty good,
but this comic is like the best
alien story ever.
And if you type in Alien Comic
Saxophone, you will see the image I'm talking about.
You've sold me on this.
It's not actually funny. It's just like really cool.
It's the ending of the comic. The saxophone
is like one of the marines is like
precious items and he has to throw it.
I just want to say, just searching Alien Saxophone in general
is leading to fantastic results.
Whoa. That doesn't dope as shit.
Oh my fucking god. This is sick.
He's so aesthetic with that thing.
It looks incredible.
I don't know what that comic is.
I am hard.
But if anyone wants
a really good Alien Xenomorph
comic experience, that is probably
the best one I've ever read and it's probably better
than the movie and I like it a lot.
Shit, dude.
Alien Saxophone.
I like it.
Incredible. Oh my god, guys. I figured it out.
I got our guy.
I locked up and got a handcuff right here. Here he is.
That's a real jazz for your soul mother
right there.
I just cannot believe how much I love
Aliens.
I couldn't agree more.
But have we run the gamut for our deep
discussion about the realism
and the 100% confirmation that they are
real aliens?
We have met them on multiple occasions.
I'm thinking it's like a
they live situation mostly.
They're hidden in plain sight with all kinds of
bizarre gay filters.
We have some solid proof
that Obama is a lizard person.
We've got some real shit.
Hillary too. Hillary too.
We could have been ruled by aliens
but we fucked it up.
What are we going to do?
Humans making mistakes. That's probably the best
case aliens could make for wiping us out
is like, look, we could have ruled you
but you didn't vote with her.
So fuck you.
You work with her, you massage in his
piece of shit.
The aliens are super liberal cooks.
They invented it.
Dude, the first thing they went to
when they got here was Seattle.
That's when they got here.
I want to say that if you don't think
aliens are real, first of all
how dare you. Second of all
look no further
than the
I mean if you believe that there's a love
battleship underneath the pyramids of Giza
which you should because it's completely
feasible and I've been there myself.
Isn't it less than a millimeter thick?
It's like one atom thick.
And like two miles wide.
It's the love battleship.
And if you think yourself, well what's it
used for? I'll fucking tell you.
Back in the 1950s when the grays were getting
heated up and they're getting super mad
at the United States government because they
wouldn't give them weed.
That's all they wanted. That's the way they came
to earth for that dank kush bro.
They wouldn't give it from the United States government
because they were fucking prudes.
So some women from South America went over
I need to give them the weed so they'll
know they'll fuck off. So she went to the pyramid
of Giza and she went inside the love battleship
and she wished with all of her heart that they
would get so much weed that they would fucking
bark. You know what they did. They all got
sick and they ran away. So thank you women
from South America for powering the love battleship
and proving that aliens are fucking real.
Shit.
I am 100% convinced. Oh by the way
unlike ghosts, unlike ghosts
aliens are incredibly eco-friendly.
They're known for their hacky
sacks and general peace-loving nature
and have incredible taste and rap.
They're dykes.
I think I would take
an alien over a ghost any day of the week.
Who do you think would win an alien or a ghost?
What about an alien ghost?
That's what I said in the beginning.
But if aliens die
they have ghosts too don't they?
How do you know? We know that we have ghosts.
That's like the concept of interracial marriage.
It's never happened so let's stop discussing it.
It's not going to happen. We know because of the
dream bubbles that ghosts are real.
Yeah.
It's like
we don't know if they're going to have the concept of ghosts
because they might not have ghosts. We know we have ghosts
because we've grown up and evolved to have them
on the planet Earth. God has only
given human souls.
Those lowly aliens
are not superior beings enough.
The aliens might have their own gods.
They could have their own gods.
Guys, you know
like the saint when in Rome do what Romans do
if an alien dies on Earth
maybe it gains a ghost.
That's pretty good.
All right.
What if the alien comes to Earth
and is enraptured in our culture
and is born again a Christian?
Does he gain a soul?
Here guys, let me ask you this.
Ginger.
Let me ask you this.
If an alien lands in
the United Arab Emirates
and actually lands in an American airport
particularly United States soil
can he still get legally same sex married
because he's on American soil
but he's also in Saudi Arabia
so two conflicting laws.
Which law overrides for an alien?
What if he doesn't conform to human
gender binary things?
Can he get gay married at all?
The most common forms
of monsters are these vagina
alien types. Where does that exactly
fall on the spectrum? It seems female
at a glance. But they're all vagina
monsters.
Maybe all the aliens
in the real universe are all vagina
humanoids.
And the ones in the fake universe are the penis.
Of course.
Men, the patriarch is not real.
It's a social course.
It all comes together.
Little bit column A, little bit column B
motherfucker.
Well team
I think we did it.
What would you want to be in your UFO?
What's the sick UFO?
What UFO do you want to buy from your UFO car
dealership?
Jimmy Neutron's
spaceship.
What about the show called Rick and Morty though?
No.
It's really smart.
Seriously for real, the Jimmy Neutron
movie of them all turning like the
Ferris wheel and stuff into spaceships
is like the coolest thing I've ever
seen in my whole life.
Why?
I fantasized about turning stuff into
a spaceship and just going.
And just going up there.
Also that eighties movie I mentioned.
Anything like that. Anything that's like
real.
Like Jimmy Neutron.
I want the spaceship.
Is Jimmy Neutron
the real universe or is he in the fake
universe?
Maybe we're in the fake universe.
He's a genius. He can travel between the
universes. He's not limited
by such things like the rest of us.
I want a purple sparkly spaceship.
Well, age post is a very dank looking
spaceship in there.
It's shining bright.
You guys ever seen Spaceballs?
Of course.
I want the spaceship they have
that's just the RV
but it has engines on the back.
That's a good one. I thought you were
going to go with Mega Maid.
Like Van the rest of my life anyways.
It's going to be perpetually poor. So it'll feel like home.
You know?
Alright.
Is this one?
Oh my god!
Yes!
You win. This is the best one.
That's the one.
That shit. Oh god. That was in Lego Magazine
every month and I was like I want it so bad.
I had it.
I lost all the pieces
that I have no clue.
Oh my god. We have to go on a quest
to find all the pieces of the Master Emerald.
We have to go back.
I remade that UFO in like a million
different ways. It was so fucking fun.
We got a...
When we all do Radcon
Lego Land, there will be
great research.
Those were the coolest aliens.
Radcon Lego Land
We have to.
Lego Con? I don't know. I got nothing.
Alright.
I feel like my thoughts can be summed up
in this image.
Fucking drag and drop. Please.
Please. My computer is freezing up
because they know.
Okay.
Nothing in this book is true
but it's exactly how things are.
With a bunch of just fucking
aliens. I like how
this is the third edition revise that
explains it.
You know what?
Real serious question. This is the last thing
I've got to say on this topic.
What's the deal with fucking crop circles
if aliens aren't making them?
I actually had a thought about this
that I forgot to bring up.
The aliens put crop circles down
because we have constantly been making
crop rectangles and they get confused.
They think we're talking to them.
So they reply with the crop circles.
They hear the rectangles and they're like
oh, okay, a circle.
And they're like, oh.
They don't get it.
Maybe the square in alien language
means DTF this whole time.
Yeah, yeah.
And that's why they abduct us and give us anal probes.
They think that we consented already.
That makes sense.
Oh, we're going to press charges super fucking hard.
We need alien safe spaces.
Final question guys.
Are skeletons aliens?
Think about it. They aren't human.
They aren't alive.
Okay.
Agreed.
Yeah, okay.
We wrapped it up guys. We did it.
Yeah, okay, that's done.
All right, everybody.
If anyone doesn't have any final points,
let's just take a look at these fucking questions over here.
Yeah.
Did anyone, by the way, do the thing on the fan discord?
No.
Ask the questions.
Go submit it right now.
We'll get some while I butter us up
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, what do you got with this one?
At LibRplex, I guess,
asks
tips on winning arguments
slash being more persuasive.
How do you get people to be persuaded?
Munchy, what do you do when you want people to believe you?
When I want people to believe me,
I just don't,
like when I want people to believe me,
I don't know if I necessarily want that a lot.
I will like, the point of the conversation
is that I won't be to spread my ideology
most of the time, if ever.
It will just be to explain myself
and then come to my own conclusions after everything is said
and done.
Well, if I explicitly want someone to conform
to what I like, because I don't know,
I just want to emotionally manipulate them for any reason,
then I'll just act
like a really good person,
they'll feel bad for not agreeing with me.
I'm really cranking up at
your like straight-faced
answer as you posted
a picture of a cobra with a fucking cigarette in it.
I just got
really, really
without comment.
No human could ever conceive of this.
It had to be external forces.
It's the only explanation.
I love that snake.
What's the guy fucking doing?
What's his angle here?
His angle is getting turned
as fuck.
Alright, I'm going to have to say,
there's so many images.
I want to edit this just so that I can make sure
that all the images get put in the
thing. So if you've just been listening,
the video version of this podcast
will have images on.
So, there you go.
Hey, so on the thing of
how to win an argument, I would say
that somebody who's great at winning arguments,
whether you like the guy or not,
is like Donald Trump.
Because what Donald Trump does,
more like Donald Trump, am I right?
Got him.
What Trump does
is the classic
debate tactic of just
not giving a fuck with a question
you were just asked and just making up
an answer to some other question.
It's extremely high level.
But if you're in a debate,
I don't know, maybe there's
a formal setting or whatever,
but if you just want people to be on your side,
if you just want to win overall,
eventually, and there's no autistic rules
going on or anything,
just ignore attacks
and ignore things
that are about the substance of what's wrong
with your position. Just focus on
what's wrong with their position
and hammer away at it incessantly
and discard all decorum
and all semblance of trying to be
acting in good faith
or take the other person's argument at its face value.
If your only goal is to win,
just find a point
that you think they're vulnerable at
and hammer them over and over again.
Exactly how people do it.
My two suggestions would be first.
If you just want to win the argument,
always appeal to emotion.
Yeah, that's a good one.
The limbic brain is what's responsible for decision making
and that's the emotional part
of the brain. The neocortex does not
have anything to do with decision making.
So if you want to sway somebody quickly, appeal to their emotions,
not logic, because logic is not very
persuasive. You use logic after
the fact to justify your emotional responses.
But if you actually want to change somebody's
mind, I highly recommend the Socratic method
of arguing where you present
your points as questions.
So you ask them questions
and you basically back them into a corner
to basically make your points for you.
Because that way they're coming to the conclusions
themselves and it feels like it's their ideas
and their learning as opposed to you beating them
over the head with what the right answer is.
Yeah.
I have a suggestion.
This is kind of a bit of a tip here, guys.
So if you're arguing with
someone, the best thing you can do
is not to make the other person
feel attacked by your side.
Because as soon as a person
feels attacked, they get defensive
and as soon as a person gets defensive
it's shut off.
The conversation is shut off. You're no longer going to be
able to persuade them because
they're locked in and they're not
going to be budging and they're going to be stubborn.
So don't make them feel
attacked.
Nate, your argument about ignoring
the
question you were asked or whatever is depressing.
That's good if you're on a debate
and you're trying to convince the audience
but not the person you're debating.
Conduct is important here.
Entirely true.
And failing all that
puts an image of a snake with a cigarette in it's mouth.
I don't know if that will win
every argument.
By the way, just on the subject
of debates or arguments, this always gets me.
Considering Tom's
emotional argument point there.
It's so true.
Let's say, for example,
you've got some debate going on
between a mom
whose kid was
kidnapped by a pedophile and raised
or something.
What was he wearing?
You have the mom here
who's experienced this.
Let's say that the ideas, her and her organization
are pushing for stricter legalization
laws to outlaw
and let's say
Lollicon porn, for example.
So he's very near and dear to Nate's heart.
Indeed, indeed.
And then on the other side,
you've got a fucking scientist
who's saying, I have studied this
and I am telling you, there is no connection
between this particular art
or whatever and increased rates
of pedophilia. If you've got those two people,
even if the dude is correct
and can demonstrate that he is correct,
nobody's going to give a shit
what they care about is making the other person feel good
because something bad happened to them.
That is how it works every fucking time.
You cannot deal with these kinds of things.
It's totally illogical, but you see it
all the fucking time.
It's the worst. Which is why I so
hate all these
advocates
for all these causes that people
individually may have experienced the particular
crime, but then they go on to try
to advocate policies
to change things for everybody.
These people are looking at anecdotal evidence.
It's your own experience, sure,
but it's completely anecdotal.
It's the mass studies that actually matter
when it comes to making decisions on a large scale.
People can't emotionally quantify statistics.
That's why we're all fucking retarded.
That's why the aliens come.
They're going to kill us and I change my mind.
They should do it.
I want a meteor to kill us rather than aliens.
It's my religion, you know.
What if the meteor was
brought here by aliens?
Would you rather be
a ghost, skeleton, or alien?
Huh?
Aliens are gentle. Aliens are compassionate.
They understand what I want.
They don't indicate it to my needs.
If an alien kills you, you'd be
euthanized. If a skeleton kills you, you'd be
butchered.
You're right about that.
Skeletons can really get under your skin enough.
I haven't been listening to this
entire question because I'm looking at this
making them laugh so much.
You have to have the snake
up the entire Q&A session
so nobody hears any of this.
Good idea. Good idea.
Alright, let's get to the question.
Wait, wait, Maja was going to say something.
I said it fun, but now the moment's over.
Dammit. Well, shit.
If an alien kills you,
you'd be euthanized.
If a skeleton kills you, you'd be butchered.
You're right about that.
Skeletons can really get under your skin,
you know?
Okay, what do we got here?
Here's one.
Hey, what's up, you imitating mother fuckers.
They ask,
do you lock your windows at night?
I think they want to get into your house, Munchie,
so be careful how you answer this question.
Yeah, I fucking...
I do not, in fact.
I always have my windows open and with a fan
blasting as loud as fucking humanly possible.
If you ever come up with a little of my streams
of video quality,
or sometimes arm retrieval because fuck arm retrieval,
then you'll hear my fan.
It's legendary, it's powerful,
and it's throbbing constantly.
I would say that I, yeah,
when it was hot during the summer,
I've got a little AC unit that I just left the window open
and I just didn't give a fuck about it.
I would just leave it open for days
and give a shit.
I'm on the second story, though, so that we'll probably...
I am...
I'm not going to answer this, actually.
Yeah, definitely.
Whenever I can.
This won't matter because he's not at this house anymore.
But Digi used to not lock his doors,
and it was the scariest fucking thing
of my entire life.
You know what I... I always think
about this scene from Full Metal Jacket,
which is where, you know,
Private Pile at Fat Motherfucker piece of shit,
like he...
Whatever, Sergeant Gunnery, whatever,
is reviewing there like...
He's just reviewing the troops and whatever
bootcamp for joining the Marines.
And he sees this fat piece of shit
did not lock his footlocker.
And he just says, so matter of factly,
like Private Pile,
you stupid, stupid motherfucker,
there is nothing I hate more in this world
than an unlocked footlocker
because if it weren't for people like you,
there would be no thievery in this world.
Didn't you already say that in a different podcast?
Did I?
I probably did. It's one of my favorite lines ever, though,
because I had not even considered the idea
that like, what?
People should be responsible for protecting their own things
and we should accept the reality
that human beings are generally self-interested
so it's our responsibility to account for that
and to manage our ways through life
considering that and facing fucking reality
instead of a utopian ideal
that isn't fucking real and never will be
and is a waste of time to imagine
is the real way, where, where, where, where works?
What the fuck?
And that's why Starfleet will never happen.
Starfleet could happen, we'll see.
It's not as utopian as it seems, but okay.
All right.
What was the question again?
Do you lock your windows at night?
Yeah, I always lock my door extensively.
I have, I have like three different locks
on my fucking door.
I have a dead bull and I have the fucking normal lock
and then I have like that fucking
Shoryu thing at the top.
I hear you.
I don't want anyone to be able to get in or out.
I'm going to protect this really
by not allowing myself to come out at night
because I know I'm not going to be responsible.
My, my doors and windows
are all locked by elaborate
point-and-click adventure game puzzles
that I have to solve every time I leave
and enter.
Keeps me on my toes.
Check out this guy, this like pizza guy
and this pizza box coffin I posted by the way.
Oh my god, Sans with boobs also.
I know, I love that.
Just to show people images.
Okay.
Yeah, let's save this image.
I'm going to put it on the screen.
Ben's not going to fucking do that.
No, I'll do it.
I'll edit, I'll edit the thing.
Sounds good to me.
There's too many images for it to be found.
We really, we really have gone overboard
with the fucking image posting this episode.
I didn't expect the images to be in the video.
It's just we just started posting aliens
ahead of time to get ourselves psyched up
for the right views.
Oh, how psyched we were.
Just to help you out.
We're going to post our time stamp
so you can kind of sync that up with the podcast
and help you find where they are.
That'll save you some work.
Maybe.
Good thinking.
Okay, do you have a question from the...
Actually, wait, no, we didn't hear Tom and Mage's answers.
I'm curious.
Do you guys lock your doors at windows at night?
I have so much shit down here.
I don't trust anybody.
I don't trust the people I have to live with.
I don't trust any of you motherfuckers.
Agreed, neither do I. Very smart. What about you, Mage?
I trust people so much that I'm not going to answer this question
because if anyone
goes out at night
and sees windows
and if they see locked windows and open windows
if they knew my answer
they could narrow down which windows
could potentially be mine.
So I'm not going to say.
That does reduce the significant amount of windows
from the list of Mage's windows.
Oh, but now I know that you have windows.
That's already narrowing down.
Well, that's a given.
We all gave our answers and you're the most mysterious
PCP member of all time
even to other members.
That's definitely true.
I like it. I think it's great.
Check out this question.
Here's a good one.
If you're 15 to 16
year old self
saw how you look and act now
where you are now, what would they say?
Let's start with Munchy.
What if you were 16 years old again?
What would you do?
I think the question was
what would they say about where you are now?
They'd probably say, wow, in two months
I'm going to be fucking rolling in it, bro.
Yeah.
They'd probably be like, wow, nothing's changed.
He'd be so disappointed.
He'd be so distraught.
You didn't even get that dank cyborg eye
you've been hyping up your whole fucking civilization.
I didn't even get turned into a crystal skeleton
and get to weeping legs.
How about you, Gib?
If you're 15 to 16 year old self saw you
what would you think?
How you look, how you act, what you're doing?
He'd probably, well, let me think
was I interested in like
internet game review type people
at the time, like 15, 16,
maybe.
But I'd probably just be like
unimpressed because I'm not like
a super rock star at the time.
What the fuck? The Beatles
got big when in the 20s
halfway through yet, bitch.
Kill yourself.
That's what he would say.
But then I would say, grow up.
Jesus.
It's not all about doing it immediately.
Yeah, silly boy. And then I would kill him
and then I would start disappearing.
I know when I was
15 to 16 I mostly
spent all my time watching anime.
Specifically one, specifically
like big long running shounens.
I just did that all day every day.
And I would definitely
be happy about where
I am now, I think.
I mean, I'm saying this from the perspective of what I think that guy
would say, but even back then
I wanted, I'm not that swole, but I wanted
to be somewhat, so you know what, I'd be disappointed
that I wasn't more fit, but I'm working on it.
I'm working on it.
But he would be happy
that I found my path in life
and am financially secure
and independent
and am achieving
my personal dreams.
I think he would be very happy. I think he'd be happy about all those things.
I certainly am.
Let's look at some
Patreon questions.
Wait, after Mage and Tom made the question.
Keep forgetting them.
I'm trying to read these
and listen to you
and also read these questions. Some of them are just
like, I don't care.
Okay, hang on to that one.
Tom, Mage, what do you think?
I think
my 16-year-old self would be like,
good job losing the weight. I'm pretty fat.
Now you're not.
I cannot even imagine you being fat.
I know, it's crazy to think about.
It was a crazy time.
Let me tell you.
Those stairs, man.
They scared me.
I told you.
I'd be like, why the fuck haven't you
finished your comic yet? You fuck.
But then I'd be like, oh, I can do 3D
and I'd be like, whoa, holy shit, I want to do that
but it seems so impossible right now.
Now you're doing it and I'd be like, I know.
You've finished a bunch of comics since then, though.
You finished a bunch of shit.
Scootaloo!
To me, my comic is like
a Shonen manga start to finish.
That's all my ideas are.
I haven't done any yet.
So it'd be like, you fucking hack.
Joan Vasquez never even had a real job
right out of high school. He got J.T.H.M. published
and we got famous. What the fuck is wrong with you?
Joan Vasquez is the guy who did all those
weird puppet things you made
to review about 100 years ago, right?
No.
No, he's the guy who did
J.T.H.M. and Invader Zim.
Yeah, that's right.
No, that was M.Strange and he's a cool guy.
He's what got me into 3D.
So I would be him.
He's what converted me from a 2D
being to a 3D being.
It was a big influence.
I'm waiting to find my idol that converts me
to a 4D being.
I don't really transcend this mortal coil.
How about you, Mage?
What would your 15 to 16 year old self say?
Look at it now.
Well, immediately it would be the opposite
of what Tom says. It would be like,
oh, do you let yourself go, didn't you?
Oh, no!
I mean, not too much,
but I would have preferred to be
a different body type than I am now.
Still would.
Hit the squats, fam. Hit the squats.
Yeah.
She would probably be quite happy
with what I'm doing right now
and would be slightly disappointed
that I still haven't finished
any comics yet, as well.
Because I actually did start a comic
when I was 14 or so
and I sort of stopped doing it.
Maybe one day you and Phantom Horn
will get back together and finish
that old comic.
We got to leap around.
That was a hard no right there.
I know.
Right, here's a question
from the Patreon Discord.
Patreon.com
Donate as we talk to you, for real.
It's true, we do.
Even Bin Saint is here, unfortunately.
Don't tell them that.
They'll leave.
Water says,
what is your favorite thing
another member on the PCP has created?
Oh, good question.
That is a fantastic question.
The Vapors.
Excellent choice.
Chapter 2, specifically.
Chapter 2 is...
I like Chapter 1 better, I think.
It's shorter but denser with good content, I think.
I don't know.
I gotta think. This is a tough one.
Who am I even going to pick?
I like a lot of old Digi contents.
Project Awesomeness.
I like a lot of that.
Dude, what the freak!
My favorite line.
It's my favorite line of all time.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Yeah, I like old Digi Bros.
The Dark Souls playthrough of Digi Bros. was nice.
But that's not my favorite thing of all time.
That's just pretty good.
I guess like Horseshoe Finale
and the One Year Later Horseshoe Finale thing
by Jesse Endless.
Jesse Endless.
Horseshoe Finale was great.
Yeah, okay. Horseshoe Finale is definitely great.
The first thing I ever saw of Jesse's
was kind of the most
mind-blowing out of all.
Just because it was the first time I ever saw Jesse's
shit and
really fucked me up.
It was the
review of the Crystal Castle,
Crystal Kingdom review,
whatever. It's like it's Colt Corona
doing a review of whatever. Crystal Empire.
Thank you. Thank you.
Brony Curious. Always good to have you on an episode.
I had another pony moment
this morning too. I felt hot.
What was it? Tell me about it.
I was in a chat
and I have some art people
in the chat and Cece was there. She was talking about
the next season of RuPaul's Drag Race
and one of the people on there was Trixie.
I just thought Trixie, Pony, because I didn't see
the context of the conversation. Hell yeah.
I'm never going to be cured. It's terminal.
Yeah. Whenever I hear of President
or First Lady Fluttershy, I'm always like
oh wait, fuck it's not the pony. Shit.
I fucked it up again. She's not hot.
Dammit.
I was always confused
when I type in rule 34
Trixie and I would get like Timmy Turner.
I didn't understand.
Now we're talking.
Now we're cooking with jazz.
What else is great? I love
Brunswick that Ben made.
Brunswick is great.
Yeah, like Brunswick a lot.
I just love Gibbs content in general.
Yeah, I was going to say my favorite
content is like the one little animation
Gibbs did with the glass of water.
Oh, the fish one.
Oh, of course.
There's a fish at the door.
I watch both You've Got Chainmail
and Pokemon Go miniscule review
like every single day of my life.
You've Got Chainmail is a masterpiece.
You've Got Chainmail is the best thing you've ever made.
I'm going to have a
sequel at some point. You've got Platemail.
Oh, yeah.
Please. I can't wait.
I'm dying for it.
I like it all.
I like it all. It's all pretty good.
I don't know. I can't think of any
specifics. I like Topten trampolines.
Topten reasons like a trampoline.
That is a good one. The trampolines one is great.
I mean, one of my favorite videos
of all time is like Anthony C's
review of cancel out wedding.
He's not up. Oh, I see.
Yeah, like they work together on it.
Invite Anthony C
to the PCP. Press one if you want
Anthony C in the PCP member.
And press two
if you want Anthony C to be the only remaining
PCP member immediately
afterward.
Incredible.
We couldn't have Anthony C in the PCP
because every episode would be scripted.
There would be a whole script that he would write. We'd all have to do.
And that would be each episode.
Oh, is that a dig? Are you digging at him?
That's funny. No, that wasn't a dig.
That was a compliment to his
insane work ethic. Oh, of course.
OK, OK. Tom, I fucking love
your low-poly 3D models
you make of like stuff
like the sushi you did
and I think you did the sushi.
The Cuphead famous.
Yeah, Cuphead was recent.
Like all the little cute
PlayStation-y, PlayStation 1
sort of things.
I love that. Tom, I
have recently procured
a desire to have sex with Cuphead.
So I was hoping you could
give me that model for my
disgusting animations that I must do.
Frinter.
Exactly.
Fantastic.
I think some of my favorite stuff. I was going to say
Fisher the Door. That's definitely one of my favorite things.
There's a legend. So fucking good.
Animate more hippo.
Fuck.
Yeah, just do all this work. I demand it for free.
That's just the kind of guy I am.
I'll give you exposure.
I really
liked best game ever. To the elements.
When I strip you naked and put you on the fucking cold
and then you'll be dead. There's your exposure.
Dumbass. Okay.
I'm calming down. I'm settling down.
I just tweeted something like that. There was like a comic strip
that someone retweeted. It was like, hey, can I
use this on my website? Oh, that's right.
And it's just like, my dad told me about exposure.
That's what you die from in the desert.
Yeah, that's probably where I got the idea to
steal it. Loki's stealing some jokes here.
Loki.
I like best game ever, Undertale. I thought that was really good.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, Tom. What have you done?
I love it. It actually is pretty good.
It is pretty good for what it is. I just like how
you've ruined the game at the end. It's fantastic.
If you fucking watch this
and you play the game, guess what? I've ruined everything for you.
You'll never experience your fag
and kill yourself. That's the good part.
Because the reason I like that so much
is like, I almost did
watch it. But I'm like, no, I think I'm going to play Undertale
at some point. So I'm not going to watch it. So I saved
myself. I saved myself
the horrible fate. And so it had
some personal weight for me.
The video is an interactive experience.
It is. It is.
I like your
Gurren Lagoon Part 1
and
what was that other one?
There's only a few. I'm trying to think of
what it was. I know. I know. There's not that many.
We Agua Episode 1
about speed running
is a masterpiece
of vlog technology.
No, there's nothing else. I've never done anything.
It's nothing else.
Something that's kind of recent
that I really like. Phantom Reviews.
Phantom Reviews is great.
I agree. Mage, I was going to say
something I liked from you was
the transformation animation
you did with your character.
Oh, the map fight.
Fucking great. The keyframing
on that is so good.
It's got punch to it. I like it.
Thank you.
When you post that, I was like
fuck, that's what I wanted.
That's what I want.
I think
the problem with Nightmare Moon Ark,
the greatest video series
ever made.
Pretty keen on that.
Oh, and my favorite thing
from you, Munchy, is
arm retrieval.
Oh, no!
My favorite thing is Investigate.
Wait a minute.
I'm so sorry.
I go, like, three people here.
It's like, we'll do comics someday.
Someday.
Hey, man, they're tough.
I think we all know what the best creation
of everybody in here is.
And it's clearly the Undertailer.
The best creation any of us has ever made.
I got to give props to
known member of the PCP, Toby Fox,
for his creation of a little game you might know called Undertail.
It's really gotten a lot of mileage
here on this podcast.
Yeah, Toby isn't a member of the PCP,
but Undertail is.
That's true. You're not wrong.
You're not wrong.
Also, like,
a while ago,
you guys made the silly parody
with the ponies
where you all guys, like, switch cutie masters
or something like that.
Oh, the cutie marker fossil.
That's the stuff I was thinking about. It was because it was pony stuff.
Oh, right.
I forgot about those. That was, like, my passion project.
Yeah, it was pretty good.
And what a passion project was.
It's not bad.
Anything involving
T-Bap was incredible.
It is and slash was incredible.
Can you just define
for me what it is?
You always talk about how you, like, like, define that for me.
No, it's like, you always said
that you like the aesthetic of T-Bap,
or, like, you like the chemistry
that was, like, that good.
I've never known what the fuck that means,
because I'm like an idiot on the piece,
you know, because, like,
before I learned how to fucking talk,
well, the piece of me as well, but on T-Bap.
Like, I listen back to, like, the things I used to say
and the arguments I would make about the show,
and I'm just like, Jesus Christ, none of this is good.
I disagree with that.
I think there was some good shit there.
First of all, I think there was good shit,
but that's not the reason.
I don't care about the actual subject matter
or the actual conversation going on.
I care about the meta elements
at play within T-Bap,
the most important thing
in my entire life.
I care about the professionality
and, like, how much effort was put
into this, like, thing that does not need
any effort put into it.
Just, like, a basic podcast made about the show.
But the way there was a lot of, you know,
pony expressions been made
far more than it was usually made
for those types of things,
as well as just custom things made for each episode.
There's that one where you guys were fucking
in the night uniforms.
All this different sort of shit going on
that didn't have to be made whatsoever.
And it all added to the experience,
as well as intros, which were so far and above
beyond what anyone was saying.
It's just perfect, because it's so easily digestible,
because there are just, like, keynotes and stuff.
And everyone's on this, like,
this, like, pre-planned path.
That's super easy. There's a table of contents for everything.
It's super easy to digest.
However, it's so fluthy.
It's just, like...
It's just, like, you're on a bus stop, and you're going to each stop.
You don't know exactly what's at stop,
but you have, like, a basic plan for each one.
So you're still, like, free-flowing,
and you can, like, kind of decide what to do
at each given moment.
And the conversation is still, like, natural and free-flowing,
but it's still easily digestible.
And just the entire aesthetic of it being,
you know, this fucking cool thing
that you have to put actual effort into
moving the pony. And it's not a lot of work,
but you just have to move the pony mouths and stuff.
And there's just a lot of stuff going on.
And Phantom Reviews and Keg Reviews are fucking incredible.
And they have so much work in problem
with fucking, like, musical segments. It's incredible.
That's right. They're legendary.
There's so much lore, too, driven in to just these simple reviews.
It's just, like, you and Ben have a really good dynamic
just in general. Yeah, too.
Because, like, when we would drive to BronyCon,
you guys would just get into these heated discussions
about everything, and I'd just be in the backseat listening,
and I'd just be like, I just got a bonus episode of T-Bab.
That's just how you talk.
And it's a good dynamic.
Well, that's cool. Thanks for sucking my dicks, fam.
Yeah, no problem. All my myriad dicks.
That'll be 50 bucks.
Pay Pal now, please.
Hey, here we go.
AtBelity998 asks,
if you could create one new law for America,
what would it be?
Munchy?
No more ghosts.
I'm tired of them.
We got to get them all out.
Like, whenever someone dies, just get, like, a vacuum near them.
Just suck them all up and send them off
to us, outsource them to China, do something with them.
I'm tired of bumping into them on the streets.
I'm trying to, I'm sorry.
I'm so getting sick and tired of my Indian
drink catcher being clogged up
with all the spirits and ghouls constantly
after change every single day.
I hate it. No more ghosts.
We got to give ICE the necessary tools
they need to deport all these fucking ghosts
back to where they came from. The fucking, the fucking grave.
Right back to the fucking...
Well, we have to give ICE the necessary tools
to get all these ghosts out of our fucking property.
No, they need, we need to give ICE
the necessary tools to get these ghosts out of our fucking bodies
by killing all of us.
Yeah.
Hashtag give ISIS nukes.
Let's make it happen everybody.
Official sponsor of the PCP ISIS.
Official PCP partner
of ISIS.
Fucking ISIS.
PCP ISIS, they're both letters.
Oh no!
He did it. It's so true.
It's so true.
What even was the question?
What law would you make?
What law would you make real, if you could?
A Trafalgar Dealer.
Oh no, that's the worst one.
By the way, I don't know if I mentioned this,
but it just so happens that my guy
work with at work,
he has like, whatever,
he just joined, he's like an intern or something,
but he has a little heart pirates logo
as his chat icon
in our work chat, and it just every day
it makes me want to die.
He's a cool guy though, and we talk about one piece,
so he's an idiot, and he should be
purged from existence, he should be
eviscerated.
Indeed, hopefully he doesn't listen to this.
We'll see.
I will be fired, I will be fired.
It will be all up to me.
If that's what gets you fired from the PCP,
I know right, I know right.
Out of everything that's been said,
you have some good job security.
I think we've had the name
Washington DC for too long.
Here's my new proposal, Mecca 2.
The second, the second Mecca 2.
I think that's kind of what we like it or not.
Aka London, London Mecca 2.
It's happening.
Okay, hang on, I want to read,
a quick shout out to
hashtag worst question of the week
at Gabriel underscore freak.
You're getting a shout out, my dude.
What is the best thing for the members
of the TPC?
First of all, he said the TPC.
So you fucked up right there, my dude.
And what's the best thing?
That question is too fucking vague.
Otaku freak Gabriel
to use your full name.
Oh, you should feel ashamed of yourself.
This is a disappointment.
I'm sorry, I'm just kidding dude, you're fine.
He was about to pledge us $50.
Oh, I fucked up. Gabriel, forgive me.
The best thing about the PCP
is spending time with all my buddies.
No, that's...
This gay is not allowed.
The best thing about it is
the paycheck.
He's right.
Can't argue with that.
Speaking of paycheck, why are you asking that?
I thought the question was
what is the best thing
for members of the...
It's not even about the PCB.
What is the best thing for each of us?
The best thing for me...
A very small...
Okay, Lego.
Lego and Minecraft combined.
A very small roll.
You get rolled up.
You get rolled up hardcore.
You get twisted.
That's the best thing to happen.
Dude, how many times have you rolled into your duvet
and become a worm?
Many, many times.
Dude, it's a tradition.
I think I said this before, everyone in Thanksgiving
I turn my shirt into pants
and I wear my pants as a shirt.
That's the best thing for me.
Tom, were you saying something?
No, I was just confirming
that that story is indeed on the books.
Oh, yes.
I don't know what the fuck is the best thing.
I love my...
My Nintendo Switch.
See, I hate this question.
I fucking hate you, Gabriel.
My favorite thing is my Surface Pro
because it's a computer and a tablet
at the same time, so you can draw on it,
you can read manga on it really easy,
you can do actual work,
computer work with it,
and it's like a pound and a half,
so it's super light, you can take it anywhere.
Oh, wait, I got it.
It's the best computing device of all time.
Excellent.
My actual best thing,
the best thing for me is
when my computer does not just blue screen and turn off.
It's all the times it's not doing that.
It's the best thing for me, without a doubt.
Guy ever!
Oh!
It's been saved.
Oh, no.
Munchie's out of the piece.
Even though I said it.
Any other questions to the fan chat?
We're getting close to the end here.
The fan chat questions are all terrible.
I have a question for you, fan chat.
Can you make better questions?
You're paying money for this.
Who's the best dancer in the PCP?
They have money, but they don't have wit.
That's for sure.
They replace it.
How all women who are attractive are 0 out of 10 intelligence,
by default.
Dude, I know that. Hardcore.
It's okay, we like it that way.
If you had to choose between money and wit,
we'd definitely appreciate your money.
Agreed.
Tell you what, here's one more question.
At Ramon1234 asks,
what is the most time-consuming element
of each of your jobs?
I don't know if it means like PCP,
or getting ice,
or the fact that ice tries to deport you all the time
for being an alien,
an illegal alien,
violating the sanctity of the American Constitution
by being here.
I'm assuming it's that.
I would say that the most time-consuming
part of my job
is the writing of the script,
because
it takes a while to decide
on when it's done
and how good it is.
Recording and editing.
Actually, no, it's writing slash recording.
Editing is fine.
I can do that fine.
It may take longer,
but there's less time where I'm just fucking around.
Like, I can just do it when I do it.
And for writing, a lot of the time,
I'm just sitting there and I don't know what I'm doing.
And I'm clicking, clacking at the keyboard
and I'm deleting my, you know, my
Internet system 32,
you know, some 64, whatever.
The most time-consuming thing about my job
is whenever I have to press keys
on my keyboard.
When I record and when I draw, it's super easy
and I can't get it done really fast.
But if I have to, like, press down letters
or accumulate
exclamation points,
then we're going to have real problems.
We're going to have some real major problems.
That's going to be the end of my band
by, like, accumulate exclamation points.
That's not bad.
The most time-consuming thing
is editing. I hate it.
And it's doubly time-consuming because it takes
long time and I also hate it.
So I procrastinate on doing it.
That sucks balls.
The most time-consuming thing with 3D
is UV unwrapping.
That's the most time-consuming thing ever.
It's when you take the 3D model once it's done
and you have to, like, put seams in it
and flatten it out like a paper-craft doll
kind of flattens out so you can put the texture on it.
It's really hard because I'm stupid.
Interesting.
Yeah, those both suck balls and I hate it.
That's not just really hard because you're stupid.
That's just really hard because I can't wrap my head
around it when I try to do it.
You can't wrap your head around unwrapping
the...
That's why I said that.
That was very good.
I think that would agree with Gib.
Oh, Midge, go ahead.
Yeah, the most time-consuming thing for me though
is drawing everything out
because I do the animation.
No, no, no, like drawing everything,
every single panel, stuff like that.
Midge, how about that foreshortening, though?
Foreshortening.
Foreshortening's fun.
Guys, I gotta tell you, foreshortening
is a pain for sure.
That's a wrap, guys.
Someone made that joke like a week ago
and I've been wanting to use it ever since.
Do you feel like Midge just steals jokes
and that's what he does and that's why he's famous?
No, no, no. I misspoke.
Like, someone said the word foreshortening
and I've been wanting to make that joke.
That's my story and I'm sticking to it.
That's the truth for sure.
See, I just did what you did.
I stole your joke.
You stole my fucking...
Okay, well, I agree with Gib here
so it might not even be the longest process
because editing does take me a long time,
but specifically,
and I've worked on improving that,
but the writing process,
okay, well with Weagua, which is what I'm doing now,
nothing takes any time
and the thing that takes the most time with that
is just once I've recorded, I have to edit it
and that, for sure, takes the majority of the time.
Once all the footage is captured,
putting it down, putting in the timelines,
doing the color correction, syncing up the audio,
et cetera, et cetera.
That's not Weagua, but the real
bane of my existence is not Weagua
because I can bust that out fairly simple.
In the bigger videos,
my larger projects,
it's the phase
to get the script together.
So all the research,
all the planning, all that kind of stuff
in order to produce the script.
Once I have the script, which I do now, incidentally,
then it's easy mode.
Then I just record it, edit,
oh, it's fucking, it's simple.
It's not required anymore. It just happens.
Like a Weagua does.
It's everything about preparing the project.
It's where both the time investment,
because A, procrastinating,
and the combination with not knowing what the fuck to say
and having to sit there and think about it,
that's the hard shit.
And I'm hoping to get better at it as I go along.
But that's my bane of my existence,
for sure.
I'm pissing into my own rug right now.
My dude, Elias.
You're on me.
What do you got, Munch?
I've said enough about aliens.
I love them.
I love them too.
They are my friends. They are my friends.
Is there a person in here who doesn't believe
that aliens are friends?
Right now, we're gonna decide the PCP,
we're gonna contact Nasta.
Are aliens friends or foes?
We decide right now. I vote friends.
Dude, why the fuck is there not an alien
type in Pokemon?
Oh, that's...
Actually, there's deoxys.
There's Clefairy.
What else do we got?
Jirachi, I think, is from the stars.
Yeah, Jirachi.
Requies us from outside the atmosphere, I think.
That counts. He's green.
Yeah, he's green.
All aliens are Pokemon.
Wait, isn't Starmie canonically
from Outer Space or something?
I think he is.
Alright, that's enough right there.
Maybe Pokemon Uranium addresses this massive flaw.
I think Pokemon Uranium should get annihilated
because it wasn't made by Nintendo
or it shouldn't exist.
Hashtag DCMA, or have you say it,
is perfect.
My favorite thing.
Hashtag legalized DCMA.
We gotta legalize it, everybody.
Make it happen.
I think we're all set.
Anybody final points or anybody?
Kirby's my best alien friend.
Oh, he's a good alien.
He is. And the most powerful.
If you plant it in half, if you look at him sideways,
he doesn't give a fuck about anything.
Lilo and Stitch,
don't let Hawaii
be abducted.
Stop it!
Okay.
Yeah, just letting it happen.
It's very irresponsible.
I don't know what's their
angle.
My closing.
Oh yeah, go ahead, Mage.
What if we are descendants of aliens?
Oh, I was gonna talk about that.
There was a great episode of Ancient Aliens.
It was a great episode of Ancient Aliens
where they're talking about aliens and Bigfoot.
Because that's the thrust of the show.
It's always aliens and something.
And so there was an episode, Aliens and Bigfoot,
and they're talking about how Bigfoot was an alien.
But then they're like, no.
What if, okay,
that aliens, they're never depicted
with any fur.
Bigfoot has fur.
What if Bigfoot was like
a species that existed on Earth
and then they genetically modified them
and they became humans.
So we're genetically modified Bigfoot's.
And the Bigfoot's that exist now
are the natural evolution of species on this planet.
And we've been modified by aliens.
Of course. That makes sense.
And they're like, is it possible?
Maybe!
Why the fuck couldn't they just say,
instead of Bigfoot, just say Gorillaz?
Because Bigfoot is
the missing link between
between Gorillaz
and humans.
Everyone needs to watch the Aliens.
It's going to elevate your Christ consciousness.
You're going to become aware of everything.
Do I need to watch?
Do I need to see Indiana Jones
in the fourth one?
That's like their movie.
And they gave it a budget.
Things got weird.
It definitely has its charm on TV instead.
As we all know,
this is not to discriminate or discredit.
But as we all know,
the Hebrews are aliens and they came
to Limeria
in our mid-evolution cycle.
And they sort of assimilated themselves.
But technically,
all Jews are aliens.
Just throwing that out there.
The Jews are the ultimate vagina aliens.
You know, to drop a little
truth bomb here,
the current science
is inconclusive
as to exactly how
the Jews are human.
No, it's okay.
To whoever's point it was,
maybe it was a major.
I took a geology class
to finish my degree last year
or something.
There was currently
biology.
There was no known way
that the base amino acids
that make up the proteins
that cells in most species
all organisms depend on
in order to function.
The thought right now is that amino acids
were synthesized outside of the planet
and then arrived here later
after it had already turned into
a fucking planet toyed with shit.
And then it just from that collision
as meteors hit here and brought the amino acids here,
they slowly collected and eventually
formed life.
Technically, you can say
everything in the universe is from space
because we're all in space.
We're all from space rocks and shit.
The theory is we're all technically Martians
because they believe it came from Mars.
How did they get here from Mars though?
Was there like an explosion or something?
Like a meteor impact or something like that.
There was a whole big presentation
on it because
I guess Mars at the time
had the conditions necessary
to create those amino acids.
That would explain the dafty duck
with no mouth guide for Mars
in Looney Tunes.
Yeah.
He totally explained him.
Dude, what if the planet of the apes
was an Earth
and the apes were on a different planet
and that was their planet of the apes
and then they continued to be apes in charge
and then they grew their technology
and they made spaceships, they came to Earth
and then they turned into humans over many years.
You're describing literally
the plot of Final Fantasy X.
That is literally what happens
in Final Fantasy X.
Spoiler.
That's what happens in Final Fantasy X too
I should clarify.
That's where the shit gets real.
Alright everybody.
I assume they don't offer that one as well.
Of course, that's the only way they know how.
Alright everybody, that's it. Thank God.
Okay, let's do our plugs here everybody.
Alright, everybody.
Don't smoke.
Don't smoke but go to patreon.com
the procrastinators.
If you've got discords,
pledge some money, be in our discords
where we actually hang out and talk to people.
We do.
You'll get the fuck right in there if you pledge
one fucking dollar.
Slide right the fuck in bro.
If you pledge $5 though,
that's $5 per episode of the PCP
you get access to the bonus episodes
of which I believe there are seven now.
There are seven that exist now, I think.
And the last one is a fucking doozy.
We're getting ready to record another one
that's coming up. It'll be out.
We're trying to get out the first of the month
and so that's when you see that shit
a couple days.
We got some merch.
We got some PCP merch down below.
We actually just added some more to our red bubble page
with a bunch of fucking stickers.
You goddamn cheap motherfucker.
Buy them all.
Stop advertising that corporate
bullshitcompanyapple.com
on the front of your MacBook.
Slap a PCP logo
PCP member.
This machine kills fascists.
This machine promotes fascism
with the PCP sticker on it.
Hell yeah, go on Gil.
There's a sticker for each of us.
They're all drawn by Mage.
Me and Tom are kind of stuck together though.
We're going to be keeping track
of all the ones you buy
so we'll know who the most popular PCP member is
and then we'll kill that person
so I can be the most pop.
What if you're the most?
Tom, we're stuck together
so we'll never know who is the most.
It'll be me and Mage the podcast.
The best podcast of all time.
And also, there is a t-shirt as well.
A t-shirt designed
by someone.
I forget his name.
Edward D. Al.
That's the guy.
Guys, I just realized.
I confirm the aliens are real.
The procrastinators, TPC,
the podcast creators
that's also the same
initial TPC
the podcast creators.
Get it? Because we create podcasts.
What's that going to do with aliens?
I don't know anything
about what the fuck you're talking about right now.
Because they're the same letters?
What are letters?
We need to go back to square one here.
Dumb podcast creators.
When we made
when you said the name.
You fucked it up dude.
You had to say the people creators.
No!
See, that would have made sense.
That would have made sense.
Well, so we got, is there anything else to shill?
Follow us at TPCrastinators on Twitter
so that you can send me your questions.
We mostly look at the fan chat these days.
But if you also want to just send questions
on the Twitter as well and we record on Saturdays
you can do that too.
So keep an eye out for that.
Can I show my Patreon?
Can you show your Patreon?
No, absolutely not. That's not what this is for.
None of us shill our Patreon.
God damn it.
Well, maybe you should.
Well, okay, let's re-evaluate this policy.
Okay, everyone, Mage has a Patreon.
Now you know.
If you want to be a dirty bent saint.
I just want everyone to look
at the tears because I made some cute doodles
for the tears.
Okay, duly noted.
Go to her Patreon if you're gay
and you like that shit.
Also, mypatreon
at patreon.com
and go to
mypatreon
at patreon.com
That's my one.
Oh, Ben's actually going to get money from this.
Fuck you, Ben. Alright, that's it.
We're done, everybody.
Thank you for listening. We will see you
next week with another
dank ass meme story
just like this one.
Everyone, it's time to say
what the aliens, how do aliens say goodbye?
And say a...
a-la-mo.
Heidelberg.
Yeah.
I'm
supposed to be
working right now.
I'm supposed
to be working
right now.
But I'm not working, I'm doing nothing
Why did I'm jerking?