Rise and shine gamers and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
I, as you know, am the best morning boy and we've got Ben Saint.
Who?
I, I, I, that's a name I haven't heard in years, Vapes.
We've got Tom Oliver.
I'm the worst morning boy because the mornings are shit.
It's all about hardcore nighttime nocturnal power.
Guys, it's 1pm and it's, it's not the morning and second of all, Tom, you're wrong because
time zones just changed.
That thing happened or and what's what happens when the clock, the clock, yeah, and now it
gets dark at like 4pm.
It's dark for like 18 hours of the day now.
Right.
I'm in my element.
Far longer.
Oh, you know, it's too much.
Let's get back to this.
That's a good topic, but also Mages here.
Hello.
I hate the cold.
Speaking of time zones.
Yeah.
I hate the cold.
That we all agree on, I hope.
I, I do like coats.
I do like winter coats.
Oh, God.
Ben, your politics are one thing, but liking the cold is, is something I cannot stand
for.
No, no, I don't, I don't, I don't like the cold.
I don't like the cold, but I do like wearing big coats.
Well, surely we could all agree that being inside, while there's perhaps a layer of snow
and it's lightly snowing, but you're warm inside with a blanket and perhaps a cup of
warm beverage can be a very enjoyable experience.
It's the juxtaposition you see, the, the, the contradiction in terms that leads to ultimate
pleasure.
As you cast your gaze outside at the fucking broken homeless freezing and you in your gated
castle.
It just makes me feel great.
Yes.
It just makes her plus capital.
It just makes me feel so warm and happy inside.
Nate, I, I went to the parents place for Thanksgiving and was it nice?
Everyone have a good time?
It was fine.
It was good.
And, and they, mom was like here, you know, he got some stuff and here's, you know, Nate
said he didn't want this and it was, he was like a black.
It wasn't my shoes was it?
She's not giving away more shoes.
No, it was like a black coat with like a furry hood.
Okay.
All right.
You know what?
This is a perfect example of what happened with the shoes because when I spoke to mom,
I remember this explicitly.
I said, when I come to visit at Christmas, I will decide whether it fits or not.
If it doesn't fit, mom, I told her this, then we will decide about what to do with it.
She told me it didn't fit.
She was like here.
She is a fucking liar.
She was like Nate said, she said, Nate said this doesn't fit.
It didn't fit him anymore.
Do you want it?
And I was like, I guess.
Yeah.
Okay.
There's, there's some confusion going on in mom's head as usual, I guess, because we
just spoke about this.
I get why it was undermined.
I said, I suspect it doesn't fit, but I will try it on when I'm there in like 25 days,
mom, for Christmas.
Don't give it away until then.
I like that coat.
It may be too small, but I guess I'll find if it fits Ben, it probably fits me.
So there you go, mom.
The fuck.
This is exactly what happened with the shoes.
I have no doubt this confirms it in my mind.
Mom is just looking to fuck me over as many ways as possible.
Yes.
Absolutely.
You see what she's trying to do?
She's trying to force me to take drastic action.
That woman's vindictive.
There's no doubt in my mind.
Well, this Christmas, she's going to get the gift of a lifetime.
This is going to be prisoner Christmas.
Boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo, boo.
Yeah, that's how I feel right now.
I'm thinking of buying a tree, though.
I think of buying a tree for the apart.
Like a little small, fake tree.
We can be allowed.
I just want to look at it and feel happy, you know, Christmas spirit.
I hate feeling happy.
I see. I see in the in the stores, like these little tiny potted, fake Christmas
trees, I was like, maybe, maybe this year will be the year I'll get a little tiny
tree. Why not?
Just, just, just it makes me happy.
I agree.
That's the whole point.
That's what these things are supposed to do.
And I don't know, out here, being on our own, out here, not live on their
families anymore, there's none of this like group family camaraderie or spirit.
Like when you're, when you're like in school and like everyone around you is
talking about it and like all the teachers and all the events are like, you
know, holiday oriented, it really instills that spirit in you.
But once you're on your own, you kind of got to, you got to force yourself
into that mindset.
And I think that it's, it's well worth the slight amount of effort and money.
It just, it gives you a stat buff of happiness temporarily.
I love Christmas just because like, uh, yeah, winter is so dreary and depressing
and sad and dark and cold.
But then like, well, well, Christmas comes around, uh, or just before like a
month or two before Christmas rolls around, uh, everything, all the stores
and people sometimes like decorate and shiny, sparkly, glittery things.
And it's like, oh, it looks so nice and bright and cheerful and colorful.
And I like it.
It's like after New Year's ends though, everything just goes so dark and it's
sad when like real winter begins.
Like I never feel that cold in December because of these things, I think, but
in January, that's when hell has begun.
I think January and February are technically the cold this month just
because of how we are rotates.
It's because you have something to look forward to.
So you ignore the cold, but as soon as it's all over, you're like, wait a minute,
this fucking sucks.
And I guess, I mean, what's the next like holiday?
Easter?
Valentine's Day, I guess.
I mean, yeah, Easter, I suppose.
Boring love and God.
No, thanks.
I don't believe in either of those, sir.
So speaking of holidays, did you buy anything for the Black Friday sales and stuff?
I totally skipped it.
I don't give a shit.
Oh, you know, tomorrow's Cyber Monday, though.
So I probably will just, you know, do the easy thing and go to Amazon.
I need it.
It's like the online equivalent of Black Friday.
I need a fucking cord for my charger, my mobile charger that I got for Pokemon Go.
I bought a fucking good cord to charge my phone and then it disappeared like a week later.
I was like, I'm going to still like, I finally, I finally committed to accepting
that all my previous chords had been lost and I would never find them again.
I swallowed my pride.
I bought a new one and then it was gone.
I almost bought something for Black Friday, but I was I was
bamboozled.
I wanted I wanted to get a new power supply for my for the streaming computer
because I'm getting a new streaming setup to do more I am game streams.
And I was like, this power supply is shit.
I don't want this computer running 24 seven with like a budget power supply
that came from like some crazy Chinese case I got like 10 years ago.
It'll probably explode.
So I found a sick power supply like on sale.
I was like, oh, dope.
I'm buying this sick.
Good Black Friday went to grab my debit card, came back downstairs, sale over.
I'm like, what the fuck?
It's 1230.
What the fuck?
It's still there.
It's not out of stock.
It's just now three times as expensive for some reason in like the 20 seconds
between I'm going to buy that and man, dude, the worst.
So fuck you, new egg, you piece of shit.
You lost the sale.
Trust muncher.
I bought like two games.
That reminds me it's on Thanksgiving.
We give thanks for things that we appreciate right now.
I thought of something that I'm thankful for and I'm thankful
for the continual movement I'm seeing towards this.
I believe it's called, do we call it the Type C charger?
USB Type C.
Yeah, USB.
Yes.
This, the fact that the whole world, it's the oval.
Yeah.
It's the one that's reversible.
And it works on both sides.
It's reversible.
The fact that we're getting this technology, look, the round ones were shit.
Type C, this is the way to go.
The fact that it's becoming more and more universally adopted
in things brings me such joy.
And once we just all are using one type of board, I don't like it
because my phone doesn't take it.
Well, OK, we'll get a new phone, Ben, 10 years.
And we'll all, well, the sick thing about USB Type C is the dope.
The dopest thing about Type C is it's not even just like phone connectors.
Type C does everything.
It does display how it does USB.
So like, assumedly, like 10 years from now, literally, you'll just go
like on your computer and it'll just be Type C, everything
because every port will do anything you want it to.
Oh, fantastic.
Well, yeah, it's exactly what we should be doing.
We'll all be like birds with just one hole that does everything.
Oh, yeah.
I look forward to our avian future.
But yeah.
Simple, efficient, elegant.
The cloaca.
Speaking of speaking of things that are literally lighter than air, such as birds,
I wanted to give everyone a life update on a little beast named Lord Sashomaru.
And it's that everyone's been mocking Sashomaru, been talking shit
about how fat my dog is.
So you're fine.
You starved him for months and now he's skin and bones.
He's been on a little diet toe and he has in fact lost three pounds.
He went from 28 pounds to 25 pounds.
And that's a hell of a loss.
That's like over 10 percent.
That's pretty good.
I took a sword.
I just cleaved his fucking head off.
Just instantly, three pounds were gone.
Just cut his tail off.
You know, that was like two pounds of extra weight that he didn't need.
Now it's gone.
But even after losing the weight, the thing is he I was I'm vindicated
because he looks exactly the same.
He's just got a weird corgi body and it's not his fault that he's big
boned and wide and a strange creature that no one will ever love.
Oh, you know, that's the same curse I have.
No matter how much weight I lose, I still am somehow still fat.
It just doesn't matter.
It just comes from mystery areas.
I don't I look to say I've lost like 10 pounds.
I look fucking exactly the same.
But, you know, Sessha was at like a doggy daycare thing.
We were just like testing a new one because when we go to Christmas,
he's got to stay at a daycare place and there is a what we call the Beagle Brigade.
There's just a squad of Beagles and Sessha is half Beagle.
So, you know, the Beagle Brigade now that the Beagle Brigade, to be fair,
is somewhat exclusive.
They don't just let any Beagle join their ranks.
You have to be up to a certain snuff.
But when Sessha attempted to ooze his way into their ranks, as he does,
there was an immediate harsh rejection of flagrant racism.
Flagrant, you know, this is like the canine equivalent of like a half elf
just sparred by both by both fucking cultures.
He has nowhere to be. Exactly.
It's it's deeply fucked up and it's it's unacceptable.
It sounds like some shonen protag material.
He can rise above the the spurs of his peers
and unite the races once and for all.
I, you know, I can't get down with this multiracial interbreeding bullshit,
though, because I mean, they told us over and over again
that human Saiyan hybrids were quote unquote better than pure blood
Saiyans in Dragon Ball Z.
Why did Gohan lose every fight he ever fought in, except the one during
the Cell Saga that obviously was cheating?
The only one that the ghost of Goku won.
Yeah, he needed the ghost of a pure Saiyan to help him out.
That's exactly right.
So, you know, you're I don't know,
Future Trunks was a badass like through and through a hundred percent.
You're not wrong.
I mean, I mean, is anyone more badass than Trunks
when he like fucking trains hardcore, goes back to his timeline
and just immediately mercs everybody, even though he knows
that these androids could be like good people deep down.
But no, it's immediately murders regardless.
No consideration about this fucking incredible down.
You touch on the larger question of what is morality?
Sure, sure, sure, sure, you know, different timelines.
But I'm just saying if I was in that if I was in that situation,
I would have a little like maybe like seven seconds of pause.
Our boy Trunks, zero.
No, just immediately murdered, like taking great joy in doing so.
And then tracks down Cell, mocks him and then immediately kills him.
Greatest, greatest character ever.
Just to find goodness as not vulnerable to the tip of my sword.
Indeed, you're done.
Speaking of which, did you guys ever watch like the Future Trunks
there had like his own saga in Dragon Ball Super
that they tell me is like the best one in Dragon Ball Super?
Does anybody go watch that?
I've seen like one episode of Dragon Ball Super.
And I saw one clip from the Super with like with where
Mr. Satan sort of punches Goku, but not really.
And Goku's like, oh, no, I'm falling.
I forgot my tractor.
I got my tractor. Yeah, that was making the rounds on Twitter.
Yep, that's the only thing I saw.
I mean, I just I just referred to the God of Dragon Ball
that I know Jax played on Twitter.
And he's always saying that Super is garbage
except for the slice of life stuff.
So I just take his word for it.
Yeah, you know, just out of curiosity,
is Jax a fan of like Dragon Ball Classic?
Yes, that's the mark of like a true.
He's he's he's on record, I believe, saying that it is better than Z.
It's better than. Oh, my God, that's unusual.
But OK, I mean, I agree.
I think original Dragon Ball is better than Z as well.
So I mean, it's got to be more.
It's just, I mean, have you seen it as a classic, obviously,
but there's tons of bullshit that we've all just kind of accepted and moved past
have you watched Dragon Ball? It's definitely there.
I've you know, I've read the manga up to, like, I don't know.
I remember I think right when like he started to fight that guy,
he throws logs, lousy and like stands on him or whatever,
which is where things get really crunk, as I recall.
I just gave up of speaking of reading manga.
I started reading one piece again.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I'm up to
actually, it's been this is like last week I did, but I'm up to chapter eight,
fifty five. What's happening?
Jesus, we are at.
Oh, fuck, they.
Well, it would be kind of spoilery to say, but they are.
I mean, you're in the so you're in Big Mom Ark, I assume.
Yeah, I'm pretty well into Big Mom Ark.
The girl, she's putting putting.
Yeah, we saw putting's thing.
You know, OK, I believe I do know.
The things you were saying, yes, he understood.
OK, that's cool. That's cool.
Well, great. It's really cool.
It's great. It is great.
And perhaps this, the the Whole Cake Island Ark is is is quite
luscious and delicious and excellent overall.
I'm happy to say.
And if you get caught up, hey, maybe this legendary appearance
on the Padi cast could happen.
Yeah, what is what chapter is as one piece at currently?
Like how is it nine hundred something, right?
Oh, you're right around nine hundred sixty five or so.
So he's got a hundred chapters together.
I like I like how you have like barely any you're almost caught up
with a hundred something chapters.
Meanwhile, I'm reading more than most stars,
which is like a hundred and fifty chapters in total.
Yeah, I read like a hundred and I read like a hundred and twenty
chapters the other day. And oh, there you go.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
I wasn't doing anything.
Yeah, that's cool.
Did you read through all of zoe in doing that zoe?
Wait, on the island on the big elephants, man.
Yes. Yes.
He's got to love that arc, man.
Oh, the fucking rhizo arc with the manker.
Oh, my God, it's one of my favorite moments in the whole fucking series.
Oh, wait, they still have carrot.
Carrot is still around from everyone's favorite character.
Fucking carrot. Oh, she's going to join the crew.
I mean, she is pretty cute.
She's not going to.
She doesn't seem only positive quality.
Yeah, yeah. I mean, you're right, of course.
She's literally like the female chopper.
Chopper has done nothing for a thousand chapters like the female chopper.
Even though there is literally a female chopper, there's like a reindeer nurse lady.
Oh, yeah. But that's not the female chopper.
Carrot is a female chopper.
You know, I'll just we'll move on from one piece, guys, I promise.
But I just want to say that on the subject of chopper,
chopper is the one piece member who has been the most forgotten as a real
character by a huge margin.
I mean, guys like Brooke get some stupendous moments
in at various times, Frankie once in a while gets a little cool flight
and dress Rosa, but chopper, nothing, absolutely nothing.
But there there is a great opportunity.
Wano is kind of like the Zoan Ark and chopper is the Zoan guy on the crew
and the fucking monster balls or the rumble balls are like a unique thing
that tie into like Zoan powers.
If Odit doesn't capitalize on that, I will be so deeply disappointed,
but I have almost no faith that anything interesting will be done with
chopper ever again until the end of the series.
There's just too many characters.
I just say I still I still like Jinbei that much.
Oh, brother, you're preaching the choir over here, man.
I'm just not I'm just not that interested in Jinbei.
I'm not that interested.
I'm not I'm not interested in law.
Like it's just all the right things, Ben.
You're doing it well.
It's just that I feel like Oda made a really makes a really big deal out
of like Jinbei coming back and I'm just like, yeah, OK, all right.
You know, it's a funny thing because when you realistically think about it,
Jinbei has done some truly stupendous things to help the straw hats.
Like he's saved Luffy at Marine for it.
He did that. He joined the rebellion like to leave the jail.
Well, so did a bond.
Like a fishman.
So did bond Clay.
Nobody's going wild about bond Clay over here.
Yes, I had to look up here because I wanted to see how cute she is.
And I like this form of her.
It's in the gross discussing.
Oh, it's going to be a spoiler.
Don't show Ben. Don't show Ben.
Oh, OK.
Sorry, I'm not reading it so I'll check it out.
I mean, you know, I don't care.
I'm looking. I'm fucking looking.
Oh, shit.
Wait, is that?
Is that real?
Yeah, I mean, that's it's a thing that happens.
Well, it's a that is a whole thing made for it.
Oh, yeah, you're not.
You're not wrong.
Is that does she either rumble ball and that happens?
No, I mean, it's all the minks have this thing that under a full moon,
they turn to the Zulong, which is actually exactly like Goku from Dragon Ball.
He also becomes the Zulong Monkey Man form.
They just go like super powerful.
I don't feel like I've ruined anything by knowing that.
Yeah, there's it's yeah.
She just gets extra fluffy and I like it.
And she basically goes into mega Ampharos form.
Yes, that. Yes, yes.
Anyway, one piece is wicked cool.
Indeed, indeed.
For all those haters out there, for all the bullies who tell me, like,
no, Nate, you know, law is cool.
Gene Bay is cool.
I just want to point out to the record.
Here's a guy who just got cut up and feels very similar to me.
I'm not a crazy person.
The one thing about my fucking mind here that I like, like, laws fine.
He he's not he has not doing very much these days.
Like, he'll just kind of like, yeah, his over.
Yeah, he'll just kind of be standing behind Luffy and like make a comment here
and there and like, that's cool.
That's fine.
When the fights are like about him, his power is not interesting.
His power is dumb.
I mean, it's it's complicated.
It's kind of cool.
There's kind of like Robin's power.
It's a little too open ended.
I don't think it's fun shown in fights.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, right.
And, you know, the only thing I'll say is that I definitely agree with you.
And I I really feel the guys like, like, I mean, Ace is dead,
but like to a degree like Ace,
Ace actually has his own bunch of like side novels
that they're writing about Ace specifically in his adventures.
I mean, sounds fine.
But we know how that journey ends.
So how interesting could they really be?
Well, I mean, hey, I know it's about the adventure,
not the destination, blah, blah, blah.
Hey, question.
Do you think do you think that Marco the Phoenix could hurt Ace?
I think yes, because if Magma could hurt Ace's fire because it's hotter.
Marco's Phoenix fire has to be hotter than Ace's regular fire, right?
It is explicitly stated somewhere
that Marco's flames actually do not produce heat.
They're a magical, special kind of fire
that is totally unique and distinct from normal fire.
Never mind.
Never fucking mind.
It's that's that's what it is.
I don't fucking know.
Excellent.
Oh, and I was just going to say that I feel like characters
like like law are literally like only consistently in the narrative still.
Like, we all know that it was part of his plot,
like fight kind of so it makes sense.
He's involved, but he doesn't have to be on screen,
except that he places so unbelievably high in the character poll rankings
that it's almost it'd be like it'd be a bad move to not continually have him there.
And I really feel that drives why he takes up the screen time he does to.
What? I mean, I feel I like what it is.
Oda will basically just have him like sort of looking grumpy
and like saying something kind of like annoyed lately.
And like, I think that's fine and good.
And it is what he should be doing.
Well, you know, to like Kinemon was with the boys for a long time.
And I like never got annoyed by Kinemon.
I just would be like, I mean, what's this guy do?
When's he going to get his thing?
And he finally has in Wano.
So like, that's cool.
But last to say about all these things.
Go listen to the putty cast. Good stuff. Good stuff.
Boy, I have a question.
Sure. Have you guys like seen any discourse about Naruto,
like Sakura versus Hinata and stuff on your Twitter?
Because I've seen loads of it.
Not particularly.
No, I think it comes from one source, particularly.
But like, they're very.
Is this Boruto related or classic Naruto?
And just in general, I think it might span the whole
Naruto verse or whatever.
People still hate Sakura and but they like Hinata apparently
for the same things they hate Sakura for.
Or at least that's the claim people.
They hate Hinata. Who hates Hinata?
No, no, no. She said they like Hinata.
They don't like Sakura.
Yeah. But like, people who like Sakura just as a backlash
start hating on Hinata just because people don't hate Hinata.
And it's just such a weird stupid mess.
Do you have any feelings on either of the characters?
I'm interested to hear.
I mean, no, nothing, nothing much, not really.
I don't know. I mean, I've thought about this plenty
as as as I was a reader of Naruto and whatnot.
It just seems that like, I mean, Hinata is kind of
she was just the what's the word?
She was kind of the grassroots favorite girl
that like obviously not a lot of emphasis was put on her at
front at first, but like her just quiet like liking of Naruto
and appreciation of the character the same way the audience did.
I think just like the lack of being annoying in any way.
It's so it's so easy to like Hinata.
Yeah, it's so easy. I get it.
Yeah, it makes sense to be fair.
I cannot. I used to be my favorite back when I was watching
just because I could sort of relate to her because shy, quiet.
Yeah, it's it's in dear.
It's endearing. Yeah, Sakura.
I would hate I hated her.
I like the woman to know her place.
You know what I'm saying? It really does a lot for me.
I hate it, Sakura, just because like she was very loud, obnoxious, mean
and violent. Yeah, like it's not so we all aspire to be.
I still don't like Sakura to this age,
but just because they're still like lingering feelings from those times
when I actually used to watch Naruto, but I haven't seen her in the new,
you know, like I haven't really watched Shippuden and I haven't really watched
Boruto. Well, I don't know.
I got one good fight in Shippuden as the show goes on.
Yeah, I know she does not.
Sakura sucks. She never does anything cool.
She has she has some cool scenes.
Like when she fights, what's his name? All the puppet guy.
I was going to say, let's not forget that in that fight,
look, I watched that fight again.
It's not even really her doing the fight.
But she's the old lady.
But it's her super strength.
Like she like she legitimately
brings her own super strength to contribute to that battle.
OK, you're not wrong.
And that's not like a nod.
Well, as the fight goes on, though, she has the best thing Sakura ever did.
As the fight goes on, she has to fight by herself as well, too.
If that's OK, if that's the best thing Sakura ever did,
then I guess I'm glad I stopped reading when I did.
I think that was a wise move.
But compared that to at the very end of of Shippuden during the final battle,
they of course give the like when Sasuke final is like, OK,
I'll help you guys fight the final battle.
They do the like Team Seven has reunited Naruto, Sakura and Sasuke.
I actually just happened to see this the other day and like they give
they give Sakura like they just like give her a token punch.
Agreed. And then Naruto looks over and goes like,
oh, wow, Sakura's really come a long way.
Naruto is a billion times stronger than this girl.
Sasuke is 10 billion times stronger than her.
OK, but it's so pandering.
OK, OK, OK, but like no, no, listen, but like Sasuke has like his eyes thing.
And Naruto has like a demon in him.
Sakura is just a normal girl that just became super strong.
I know. Boring.
She also didn't she also become like a doctor?
That's pretty cool.
Well, she got trained by what's her face?
To not. And so she gets like like her.
And you know what?
Tsunade sucks, too.
Tsunade never did anything cool.
She punches hard sometimes and summons a snail.
These are the two things she ever does.
Punching hard is kind of cool. Boring.
If I could punch hard, I'd do it.
Snails are pretty epic.
In a series like Naruto.
Just OK, the problem is in a series like Dragon Ball Z,
punching hard matters is important.
Like technical fighting techniques matter in Naruto.
Like Taijutsu and stuff is like never developed at all.
It's just either you can punch really hard or you can't.
You've got one card to play and like that's she plays that card
and it's boring every single time it's played.
The punching hard card is so one note in Naruto
because the series isn't designed for it.
I somehow have both feelings that that Sakura is cool,
but she also got totally cucked by the show and should have done more.
A bit. Yeah, I mean, I don't know how those are
both in my head at the same time, but they are.
Yeah, I think Sakura does have potential, at least from what I know of her
and all the things is just, yeah, the show doesn't.
It's not about her, the show, sadly, and she doesn't get a lot of screen time.
She gets token screen time.
Yes, she does.
Which is what you said, her fault.
I mean, no, but is it her fault that she has the worst thing?
The worst thing Sakura does is forgive Sasuke.
I'm sorry. That was.
Oh, my God, after all he did to her, it's funny, hilarious.
And Rockley is there the whole time being the coolest guy in the entire show.
Disgusting, disgusting.
That Sakura's why I hate women. Confirmed.
Yeah, yeah, let's all simmer down and just watch a good,
a good old Naruto AMV set to Linkin Park.
Yes, do you see into the.
Got to watch Naruto versus Gaara set to disturb circa 2003.
Yeah, that's my shit.
That's my shit, Tom. Fucking aesthetic.
I had once made like an R2MV set to like
have an essence bring me to life.
Oh, is it so on YouTube?
You were one of the billions, one of the billions to do so.
That was the primary currency of the realm at that time.
Little to do, you know, me and Ben both like got off to the to the AMV
mage made back in the day before we even knew who mage was.
Our paths cross much like Team Seven themselves.
We all we were we had a bond all this way back back in action.
But OK, to be fair to Sakura and, you know,
like Hinata doesn't get much development either.
But I think like people just shit on Sakura a lot more than they do
on Hinata for the same reasons.
And but do you think it's because Hinata has big tits and Sakura doesn't.
Big tits blinds you to all character flaws.
And it's I mean, that's part of it.
I mean, let's not fool ourselves.
That's definitely part of it.
It's anyway, I guess like it's a little and I think it's a little unfair.
I like Hinata just because the way she is.
I don't need her to be strong.
And I don't necessarily, I guess, need Sakura to be strong.
My issue with Sakura is her personality or was used to be her personality.
It probably changed since she was like 12 or something.
I don't even I don't even have like a quote unquote problem with her personality.
I just think it's so justified to just like Hinata more
because she's way more likable, generalist and does more interesting things.
Hinata's got like a cooler power.
She's got that is it Ryuga clan?
Ryuga clan, Ryuga clan like the Biakugan, which is awesome.
And look, it's not anyone's fault that some people have magic powers inborn.
It's Kishimoto's fault for writing the series that way,
that some people are just way cooler than other people.
I kind of the thing that I kind of liked is like they had Rock Lee kind of like
overcoming that with pure effort.
And like they have this kind of setup with Sakura saying
like she wants to catch up to Naruto and Sasuke and like getting her training
kind of like sets that up, but it never really finishes.
Like it doesn't go anywhere.
Like she gets like stronger, but never to like the same degree.
And she never gets any moments like Rock Lee does.
And you're just like, you know what, I just realized.
And so and there's remember that moment where Rock Lee is fighting that bone guy
and like he's going to lose.
He tries the drunken technique.
It doesn't, you know, let him win.
And then Gara shows up and he's the one who defeats that bone guy.
And you know why?
You know what the key advantage Gara had over Rock Lee as we see later?
Rock Lee only had a dad who was like a weird deadbeat, the eternal
Ganyne or whatever.
But but fucking Gara had a loving mother who died loving him.
So it's the it's the advantage of a two parent household.
Gara is like Gara that pushed him over the edge.
Gara is like evil Harry Potter.
He's like evil Harry Potter because his mom died and gave him like magic protection.
That's true. Only it turned him into a fucking demon instead of.
Oh, it all worked out eventually.
And that was great.
OK, you want to know the thing.
OK, this is this is such a perfect example of the thing I hate most about
like writing in general, how like memes of characters can become more
than they were ever supposed to be.
And it's that, OK, we all know Gara.
Gara has like those really deep like black things around his eyes.
And like it's discussed in early Naruto, why that is.
He cannot sleep because he's possessed by a demon.
He like has terrible insomnia.
It gives him these like ridges around his eyes.
OK, Gara, this is the most retarded thing of all time.
It's when way later at the end of Shippuden, Gara's dad, like the third,
what do you call it, the Wind Kage, Kaze Kage gets revived or whatever.
Yeah, for like the final battle.
Like, of course, like we've seen with that guy looks like he looks like Gara,
but without the bags in his eyes, red hair, whatever.
And he fights with gold dust. OK, that's all fine.
But then he's like, oh, shit, I got a power up to fight my tongue, my fucking son.
Here I go, ninja art, like I power.
And he fucking activates like a ninja technique to get the like
black lines around his eyes, as if that's some sort of advantage.
Wait, does this happen? I don't even remember this.
I'm telling you right now.
I was just like six months ago.
Look like my son knows you.
Was this cut from them?
Fucking. No, what?
This can't be right. It's in there.
I'm telling you, at the very least, it's in the anime.
And I mean, I mean, I remember them saying that he has those because he can't sleep.
But like, I thought that later it was just like,
because, like, obviously he loses the demon later, too.
So why does he keep that?
That's my point. That was what I was wondering.
And I thought it was just like Naruto has like the marks on his face
because he has the demon fox.
So I figured I think he had those
when he was born before he had the demon in him, though.
That's that's so it's so fucking strange.
He was like put it in the right when he was born.
Things over his eyes.
And like that's because he's a raccoon, right?
It's the raccoon demon that he had.
So I was like, oh, it's like they have like facial markings to represent
the the the beast that they had.
And maybe that's what Kishimoto was going for with the initial design.
And then tried to justify it later or whatever.
It was dumb. It was stupid.
Yep. Keep your story straight.
Look at this fucking chud.
Look at this fucking look at this fucking Melvin.
Oh, yeah, that's him activating the secret art.
I power Garajutsu.
It's just a fucking consequence of insomnia.
That's not a real power.
See, and maybe insomnia is a power and we're all fools.
I mean, we're all wasting how many hours of our day.
All right, could be, you know, I'm going to stop sleeping and see if I get stronger
or report back next week.
It's just OK.
And for those who aren't obvious, this is an obvious.
It's just that like they just made like a character design trope into like a power
because I don't know.
It looks cool, I guess.
It doesn't even make sense. Epic.
Oh, it's simply because he looks like a boy band.
It's dumb.
But they do this shit all the time.
Mage and honestly, this is the exact same logic as where hockey came from in one
piece, like it is that same thing.
And you can do it better or worse.
Hockey is generally OK.
There's some problems with it, but it's this same thing that's happening here.
I'm trying to read the text in this these like series of screenshots that
Mage posted, but I'm just distracted by the fact that in the two close-ups
of Gara, his facial like proportions completely change.
And there was no reason you just recycle that frame.
It's very bizarre.
It is.
Well, what can you do?
Sometimes things are shit.
And by the way, I googled it.
I'm like pretty sure Naruto had the lines on his face before he had the demon stuck in him.
But I could be wrong.
So I won't I won't die on that.
Didn't they put the thing in in like the moment he was born?
Yeah, I mean, no, very closely.
And there was some amount of time.
Oh, OK, well, it's like a matter of like maybe an hour or two tops
because like he's born in secret because they have to like keep him locked away and shit
because they're and then immediately what's his face attacks them?
I forget everybody's names.
You know, it's all wait a minute.
You know what?
There is one thing that I think is maybe kind of reasonable.
Am I correct in in thinking that his mom was the genturiki of the Fox before him?
And OK, so the fact that the Fox was in up in his mom while he was born,
suddenly it seems a bit more reasonable.
He might have Fox markings on his face.
Because, you know, that's the real father.
The Fox is the father is my point.
So, OK, fair enough, at least half the father.
OK, that one's fine.
But this Garai shit is the most retarded thing I've ever seen in my life.
A blatant retcon or just ignoring your established canon.
It's not even a retcon.
It's simply a misunderstanding of his own series.
Oh, that makes me mad.
I remember fan art of Garai applying mascara like the emo boy that he was.
Yes, good one.
Thanks for the two thousands internet.
You shaped me into who I am today.
So, OK, we we've dismantled Naruto fundamentally at an ideological level.
What else is on the table?
Boys, well, everyone's telling me I got to get off Twitter.
And I should probably get off Twitter.
I mean, yeah, I can I can I recommend after this whole unpleasantness
with me and Digi and Mr.
Medicare, Mr. Medicare got involved.
Yeah, did you see what I tell this?
Should I tell this story a little bit?
It's an interesting story. It's amusing.
It's I feel I feel pretty you have to.
If you don't want to, we know it's fine.
I just I don't like how it went.
I don't like how the tone of it evolved.
But like, OK, all right, I guess I got to talk about.
OK, you guys see that video that Medeker did about how the sausage is made?
It's horrible. I tried to watch it.
I could not sit through.
I mean, you know, it's don't know this video.
I mean, OK, it's it's terrible.
I always say that because surgery looks gross no matter what it is.
So that's not a criticism.
Yeah, I mean, it's an unpleasant video, no matter how you slice it.
But like, yeah, yeah, it's like a pretty long video of like graphics.
Like, like bottom surgery footage,
like people getting their dicks inverted and stuff.
Oh, dear. And so it's that.
I want to watch that.
And and Medeker, he just like he just like snarks over the whole time.
Like, it's not educational.
It's for it's he's there to like make fun of it.
And it's really gross, like on every level.
And he got deep flat and he says drops the fucking N word like a bunch of times.
And it's I don't know why it's not it's not it's not even like a joke.
He just says it.
OK, he's fucking says it for no reason.
I it's yeah, OK, I don't like sure.
But he got deep platformed.
Did you didn't agree with him getting deep platformed, which is one thing.
But then he defended the video and I think the video is indefensible.
So I was like, no.
And then and then some shit happened.
And then also at the same time, coincidentally,
I made some comments on May's sexy Greta Thunberg, which I didn't really care for.
But then other people jumped into that conversation.
And that turned way uglier than I meant to say.
The worst thing about that conversation was some people said,
are you cosplaying sans with her blue hoodie?
Well, I was literally there cosplaying sans.
Yes, I had a black hoodie, but I was still sans.
That's the real crime being committed here.
It's a shame. What a shame.
Why don't you get in there?
Why don't you get in the photo? I should have.
I should have called him out.
OK, but so but so.
So I say like this, you know, this.
Oh, God, how do the kind? It doesn't matter.
I mean, did you just agree?
Did you seem to get pretty annoyed with me over over this stuff?
There were some fairly strong accusations made.
I don't think I made any accusations that strong.
Somebody asked me.
Somebody asked me, is Digi on the alt right pipeline?
And I thought the question was, is he on it?
Like, is he going down it?
And I think that Dick, I think that Dick Masterson is absolutely someone
who's part of the pipeline.
So I said, yes.
But it was interpreted.
I think the guy meant to ask is Digi part of the pipeline.
And I don't know. I don't I don't not sure.
So I. So that was that was dumb.
It wasn't dumb, but it was we were talking about two different things.
So there's certainly some degree of miscommunication
on exactly the nature of.
But did but did you got mad?
Did you got mad at me because he said that I would I would defend
Monkey Jones while I was while I would not do this.
Well, I would like attack like someone like
Medicare. And I was like, yeah, you know, I guess I guess it's it's true.
Monkey has some of the same problems here that I would object to.
Is he kind of the same?
And I said and I said that Dick Masterson,
Medicare and Monkey are all cut from the same cloth.
They're all privileged popcorn, nihilists will hand wave away
problems that don't affect them personally.
And I think that's true.
And Medicare saw that and he
he made it his fucking Twitter bio,
but he didn't understand what I meant.
He didn't know the phrase popcorn nihilist,
as in Charlie Brown is a popcorn nihilist.
And he thought I was calling him privileged popcorn.
Like he thought that was the phrase I was trying to say.
And so he said he was like, I can't wait for the next
popcorn privilege party.
And I'm very upset.
I was misinterpreted, misunderstood.
I don't mind that he was like, make fun of my tweet.
But I'm but I do mind that he got it backwards
and is making fun of a misunderstood version of it.
I don't even understand.
Misunderstanding seems to seems to be the root of all your Twitter problems, Ben.
It's almost like everyone's Twitter problem doesn't allow for
for a great degree of clarity and communication.
I maybe maybe you shouldn't use it like that.
Then I don't know.
Popcorn nihilist, Ben, you just have to do it.
You just have to become a breadtuber.
Like you have like like you're just at that point.
You're just at that point as much as I don't even want to encourage it.
Like it's better to like have a video where you can actually explain your point
as opposed to going on these Twitter escapades that get literally nowhere.
I guess so.
I mean, I mean, comparing the two things.
It's time to graduate from the new adventures of Winnie the Pooh analysis
into something truly evil.
Among the two, that's true.
And I'm sure it happens less.
But people can still pick and choose pieces of statements made and even
not like willfully misinterpret, but like people just inherently read
what they want to into what other people say and don't always, you know,
get down to the exact meaning the other person was saying or take a little clip.
And sure, maybe they legitimately only heard the little clip or something.
But then it sounds worse.
I just it's all bad.
It's all bad.
As a person who has long breaks from Twitter, I would highly recommend
to sometimes just take long breaks from Twitter.
It's not healthy.
Honestly, I feel a lot better from taking breaks like today.
I scroll through Twitter and, you know, I saw a lot of that Sakura Hinata discourse.
Like, who cares?
I wish I wish my time line had that on it.
That's much better than what I usually see when it comes to drama.
I mean, there's a lot of other stuff.
But I just like I just look at it.
I'm like, oh, I don't want this anymore.
So I shut off Twitter and I want to play banished.
Understandable, understandable.
This is part of why I just decided a while ago.
I just I just am not I don't want to do this stuff.
So I pretty much just follow like anime girl accounts on Twitter.
That's pretty much all I follow.
Getting into arguments on Twitter is very pointless.
If you ask, it's very it's very pointless.
Nobody is understanding each other.
We're talking to each other if you want to.
If you're current, if the currency of your realm,
I don't know why I keep using that phrase, but like if the thing that you like
profit off of is like, I mean, if you're like, for example,
like a drama YouTuber or like a even like some kind of like political person
and people like and you have like an ideological bent and people just like
to see fighting going like seemingly, quote unquote, productive fighting
against the other side, not I mean, you know, but everybody does this.
Does engage this to any degree.
Like it's useful and beneficial to have more of that happening.
So you can capitalize on it.
Yeah, but that's not me every time.
Like I lose followers every time I get in an argument on Twitter,
like every single time.
If you really want to like discuss or argue with a person,
just like ask them if you can take it to DMs or add them on on on like
discord or something.
I don't know.
I just don't think Twitter is a good platform for arguing and everyone suffers for it.
You know, you know, a lot of I heard I heard quite a few people
shitting on you, Ben, for these things.
But I must say, I feel sympathetic because the nature of Twitter is so seductive.
Like, you know, I heard some people just being like, you know, why is Ben,
you know, like being a jerk about this thing?
But I just thought, well, I mean, he's just using Twitter as intended.
He's just saying the thing he thinks about the thing that was posted.
Is that not exactly the funny thing is that I don't really think that I said
anything all that inflammatory, except for maybe the pipeline thing,
which was I was I was misunderstood in what I was saying.
Sure, that's exactly true.
Because like, I heard some people mad at like your response to May, for example.
And I just thought I actually looked at your message.
I was like, Ben seems pretty tepid here.
It doesn't seem particularly mean.
So yeah, I was just surprised that people were so.
I people like, why do you have things from the past?
But I just didn't seem that, you know, death.
I don't know.
OK, you can say how you want that that tweet was a month old.
But like, they had just discussed it on a podcast like a couple days before
and had been talking about that podcast recently, so it's not dragging up old shit.
It's not. Yeah, it's not.
It feels like if you're if you're just on Twitter, but if you watch that podcast,
as I did, like, I think the day this happened, I was like, ah,
I see where this discussion came from and it is not.
Yeah, I listen to it.
Shit. Yeah.
And I don't know.
We probably don't quite agree.
More of the story.
Follow everybody on everything.
Watch all the content and you'll always know exactly what's going on,
even if you don't want to.
Yeah, well,
there's just very annoyed, very annoyed about every every aspect of what
it's pretty funny that Twitter bills itself as a communication platform.
And yet it's the worst opposite.
It's like like more like the anti social network.
I'll say, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, dude.
Got him.
Bravo.
Shut it all down.
Destroyed.
Oh, dude, what if what if at the end of the movie, the social network,
they like reveal that word was hidden there?
Like, oh, like under a sign, there's like a piece of cardboard
like falls and does that like swing off of it?
You know, in front of the front of the sign out front of the building or whatever.
OK, got him.
Final note on that.
Fuck, Mr. Medeker, he's a Nazi.
There you go.
A Nazi.
I think he is definitely that word.
Definitely.
He's definitely he's a fascist who hates the Jews.
OK, hang on.
What if you are that but you don't you aren't willing to kill anyone?
Is that still a Nazi?
Yeah, yeah, I would say.
As long as we're clear, I would say pretty much.
I would say pretty much fair enough, fair enough.
All right, good.
Well, that's my story.
I'm sure everyone has their own interpretation of events and whatnot.
Also, this art of Hinata in different art styles is very cute.
I like it, Mage.
I've seen things like that recently.
I like this idea way better.
Yeah, it's good.
Also, look at how can you not like Hinata?
She's just she's just a lovely on the eyes.
She's easy.
She's easy to like.
Yeah, she's designed.
She's unchallenging.
Unvirginally.
She's the beloved Hinata.
She's she's she's unclouded by normal cognition.
You know what I'm talking about?
You know what I'm referencing there?
I don't.
I don't know that one.
Well, it's a spoiler, but in in Midsommar, there's a guy there, like,
profit is like the guy who's like a product of inbreeding.
And he's like all messed up and shit.
And like, they have him like finger paint in a book and then they like
interpret what the finger paintings mean.
And they say that he's unclouded by normal cognition.
So me and Munchy have been saying that all the time.
My reference was I'm feeling so unclouded right now.
What's his face?
The Candyland guy for a Leonardo DiCaprio's character from Jango Unchained
when he describes the old Joe Ben who was unclouded, no, unburdened by genius,
unburdened by genius, shaved his daddy's straight razor for 50 years.
And if it was him there, he would have cut his daddy's throat and it wouldn't
have taken him no 50 years, neither.
Great lines, great delivery, great characters.
Task support of slavery.
Man, we did it.
This Joe Joe version.
I don't like the Joe Joe ones.
People always fuck up Joe Joe artwork.
That's too. That's fucked up.
That looks terrible. Yeah, it's not quite.
It's not quite it, fam.
Heels are just a little bit softer looking than that.
Just a little bit.
Oh, and this is not everybody fucks up Joe Joe art.
And also it's people have a lot of trouble adapting to one piece art, too.
Like this kind of looks like Hinata, but like, I mean, like just for example,
like Nico Robin literally had Hinata's exact haircut.
And yet this looks way worse than like Robin's because they give it
like the rounded thing on the I don't know why they did that.
They just thought that's what one piece characters look like, I guess.
People fuck up one piece art so bad.
It's hard to interpret someone else's art style perfectly.
There are subtle.
That's what we all need.
Generic anime art style is the peak.
We need to all convene the house style.
If you type of drawing, I like the demon slayer one.
I like the hair just like it all swishy.
I like the My Hair Academia one.
Yeah, they're both good.
They're both good.
I like the Dragon Ball Z one because it's purple.
It's like literally just literally.
No, she had purple hair and blue sometimes.
So she changes.
It's true.
OK, what else is going on?
I've got nothing. I'm out.
I bought I bought games on the Black Friday sale.
And one of them is, you know, Cooney, Raffa the White Witch.
And they played. Oh, how is it?
I've heard many things about it.
It's so cute. I love it.
There's so many puns and it's so whimsical.
And I've been bothering Byter about how whimsy it is.
And she's like, oh, so much.
We did that too, right?
But yeah, the first one.
Yeah, yeah.
And I actually bought the sequel on the PC as well because sales.
And I've been wanting both.
I didn't even open Steam on Black Friday.
A small mercy.
I didn't even realize I granted myself.
Oh, yeah, you know, that's smart.
You know, I on Digi's recommendation, it wasn't a recommend,
but like Digi in some podcast or something recently was just talking so
glowingly about, he's like, every RPG sucks in the world lately,
except for cross code.
And I was like, oh, what's Digi likes in RPG that he found was like worth his time.
What is that?
That podcast was the content on Pokmon that you just posted a few days ago.
That's that's correct.
That's that you were on.
I, you know, these things just they roll off my back.
I can't remember anything.
But I played that game.
I've been playing it and probably five, six hours in.
It's great. I fucking love it.
It's fantastic.
I've heard I was I was with Digi when I was playing it and I'm mad
because he was like, all right, I'm going to play cross code.
I'm going to devote like 80 hours to playing this game
so I can be the first one to make a fucking massive video for I am games about it.
I'm like, all right, cool, that's sick.
And then he beat it.
He's like, I don't feel like it.
And I was like, you fucking didn't get 20 hours in and gave up.
He gave up people are now hungry for more content.
Jump. I do it.
I played the cross code demo on like new grounds when it was new.
Yeah, it was you ever play phenotopia?
I don't know. I don't know.
Phenotopia was like a site.
It was sort of cave story-esque, but like not as actiony,
but it was like a side scrolling action RPG.
And it was it was it was like a new grounds release, like five or six,
maybe more years ago.
And just I played that and it was it was really great.
And like the developer has been working on remaking it ever since for the last
like six years. Oh my god. OK.
And yeah, and also making the sequel like at the same time.
And but just at that very moment,
cross code also released its demo and I played it.
And I didn't like it that much.
I didn't care. I didn't see what the all the hype was.
Yeah. Well, maybe it's evolved since then.
OK, it's feel like it must have because like the demo I played was like very bare
bones. Oh, this I mean, I would definitely say this is not bare bones.
This is. Yeah. I mean, I feel like there's a lot going on.
It's like, but I mean, you know, now's a good chance for me to talk about
because I don't I don't maybe I'll make a video on it someday.
But like it's it's got just such satisfying
gameplay of it's it's 16 bit graphics.
You're moving around this world.
You're grinding. It's like every action you do.
It's it's satisfying in the like the the like the egovania style.
Or I don't know. I get like Secret of Mana kind of.
We're running around.
You're doing melee stuff.
But you've also got this very satisfying long range combat that, to be honest,
is a little hard to do with a thumbstick.
It's a little bit imprecise.
I feel like it maybe is better played with a with a mouse.
But nonetheless, it it's really fun and you get party members are grinding.
And there's this story that actually it's it's very much like a dot hack.
That one dot hack show, there's like a million shows.
But the one with that guy who's like in the world
and they forget how Amnesia is like as a part of the narrative.
But it's also very much it's like Greed Island.
It's actually it's exactly like the Hunter Hunter Ark Greed Island
that I just made a wee Agua about because it's about like a
a real world place where people like warp in digital avatars to go explore.
Like kind of in a in a kind of like in Avatar, the movie, how you like
are to your consciousness like in Bade, something else you can possess or whatever.
And you play as like a magical avatar sword art online.
Well, only this is a real space or online's digital.
But but nonetheless, it's super cool.
And like it's got this this is the real hook.
This is the real hook.
It's just that you start the game, you get these mechanics, but there's a big
there's the big hook I have as a player is just that at the very you're told
that you start off with like normal like a normal neutral attacks
that don't have any elemental properties.
But like the main quest is to go and collect like the four elemental things
kind of like Final Fantasy style, but like they actually give 10 like tangible
gameplay bonuses because each new like elemental thing you get
augments, your fighting like permanently, or it's just like a new
it's kind of like a new beam you get in Metroid or whatever.
You can just like activate them and you switch between them.
And just like the aspect of being on a quest where I know I'm going to get
like new ways to play and like new powers I'll be able to use in like creative
ways against enemies with like elemental weaknesses and stuff.
And the game like looks so good and is great.
I don't know.
The dialogue isn't like amazing or anything, but I don't know.
The world's it's good enough.
It's just it's everything about it just feels so appealing on just like on a
gameplay level and the story is also pretty cool too.
So I'm just I'm way into it.
What do you describe me with the, you know, you know, you play you unlock
more powers and stuff like that.
Like that's just like most RPGs aren't aren't isn't it?
It's just like it's different because this is actually, you know what?
You're right.
It's like it's like a fundamental thing, but it's really presented it in a
very appealing way and they feel like really big landmarks and big
achievements and I don't know.
It's hard to describe, but just the way it's presented seems very, it's
very appealing and very satisfying to pursue.
I mean, like in a lot of RPGs, you just sort of unlock it on level up and stuff.
Like, but if it's like, exactly, and I guess it's sort of neat, it's more
satisfying.
It's pretty Zelda like and stuff, but it just I'm watching the trailer and
it looks like there's way more going on here.
Also, there's a, there's a Saitama in it.
I posted a screenshot in the thing in the chat.
Oh, did you?
Uh, let me see.
A gross disgusting audio files.
Oh, yeah.
That's true.
There he is.
It's it's a indie game.
So there's, you know, there's memes.
There's I don't not like the portrait art style.
The art is not amazing.
You're absolutely right.
It is not amazing.
The sprites are nice though.
So I'm just the little sprites are fine.
How can you fuck those up?
I like that.
I sort of like all gets in tight.
Thank you.
I like the, I like the portrait of the girl though.
It's fine enough.
It has extra shading inside.
Look, the story, the characters, the art, it's all bullshit.
Who cares?
The point is, it's a really satisfying game to play.
And I'm having a great time.
That's, that's satisfying games.
Other than, you know, also, I bought Divina your drills and two, which
I've been craving to buy for a while and I did.
I only played a little bit.
I just got off the ship and I barely did anything.
But I stole eight buckets or I rather I took eight buckets.
I put one on my head.
It's a helmet now.
Wait, what is this?
Divina your drills and two.
I, I, I, I, I regret not taking the skill to talk to animals
because I missed out on talking to sheep, to two sheep and one squirrel
riding a skeleton cat.
So sex to be me.
There's definitely a story there for sure.
There's, yes.
Maybe next time.
It's fun.
It's pretty fun.
I hate the fact that the way you control the camera is a little bit clunky
and it takes getting used to because I'm used to like moving the
camera around with my right mouse button, but no, that's not how you do it.
I have to assign a different button.
I mean, like, I think there's a default button.
Yeah, there's a default button, but I signed it to a different button
just because it's more comfortable for me to have it on the mouse.
But it's still, it's still just so, so annoying.
If I forget how to do it, I just mess up the camera work.
But thankfully it's a trend based game.
So if I get into a battle, I don't, I'm not losing out on any time
to readjust my camera and stuff.
And I'm not like the old RPGs of like, like Baldur's Gate and stuff, right?
He thinks I haven't played Baldur's Gate, so I wouldn't know.
But yeah, it's very, it's very RPG, like with with nice enough graphics
and not super quality ones.
But I mean, they're good enough.
They're quite neat.
There's a skeleton dude that I may or may not romance.
Who knows?
I am a tall elf lady.
I'm glad to see the flash to gain the memories of the dead, which is really cool.
I just like that comic Chew.
It's just Chew. No, no, no.
He has no he can he's like a detective who can like eat something.
And if he eats something, he can like it's sort of like Bruce Willis
and unbreakable.
He can just sort of like sense like where a thing was.
And if he has to eat something to get it's like not its memories,
but like its history.
I think I've seen the concept thrown around.
But yeah, like with these elves, the one elf I met on the ship,
she all like she's a lot better at telling like reading memories of people.
So like all she had to do was like my arm and you can let her look
or your arm or not.
And I let her let her look my arm and she could tell memories
from my character's past, apparently.
So that's neat. I like it.
I like that's cool.
Yeah, I accidentally became a slave to a red lizard.
But I hate when that happens.
Yeah, but I met up with him afterwards
and he was like, I never mind being the slave.
You saved me, so you earned your freedom.
So I was like, OK, cool.
You know, I happen to watch that.
What's his fucking like Seth Cezniak or whatever that fucking YouTube guy
with the weird name.
I watched his video on Vampire, the Masquerades.
You guys ever play that game because it looked pretty dope.
I played the online one when I was younger.
I tried playing it, but my computer couldn't run it.
But it was kind of fun, but I didn't understand anything.
I was just too stupid, I guess.
It seems like a fairly large brain game.
It was.
I remember people talking about one of the Vampire Girls looking
sort of like a trashy Harley Quinn version or something.
Yes, that's right. That's right.
There's a new there's a sequel of that game coming out.
It's in there.
They're working on it now.
Yeah, but people are pretty, pretty hyped as I understand it.
Right, right.
It was sort of on sale the game, but wasn't on a big enough sale
for me to justify buying the Masquerade game.
Well, perhaps what I was just curious
if you guys played this.
Seth is a big fan, as it seems.
I liked it.
Yeah, I like I remember.
I remember liking it.
I just don't remember anything other than anything else about it.
Well, that's it.
That's that's my whole thought on that matter.
Philosophy Tube.
Philosophy Tube just did a video.
It's really good.
It's about I guess it's it's about the video game industry,
but it's in particular about like the work of Jim Sterling.
Yeah, I saw that thumbnail and you just dressed up as him.
It's very interesting.
Yeah, it's good.
It's about how like it's about how like the tendency toward monopoly
in in particular in the video game industry can can let like companies
like basically buy their way out of the supposed advantages
offered by the the free market.
Monopolies of which companies?
The developers or the distributors or publishers, right?
Both, I guess.
Wherever the money is.
I know just Jim Sterling usually has issues with publishers
more than anything else.
That's like his go to to make money.
I would think so.
Piss off the publishers, which is usually justified.
Not the developers, in particular, so much.
OK, OK.
You know, stuff like loot boxes and what I say,
though, what ways that like like like moves that the video game
industry makes towards like extracting more value without
providing a better product or like providing a service to more people
or anything like that. Sure.
I think we can all get behind that.
And the rent the rent to your economy where you make money
not by producing anything, but just by owning something,
whether it's like a building that you rent or just like intellectual
property rights that you just have.
I'm sending a certain ideological bent to to some of these points.
No, no kidding.
All right.
Well, I mean, those those are those are good things to talk.
I mean, fucking, I wish that I was just thinking about a game
that Oh, Metal Gear Rising, too.
Metal Gear Revengeance will never get made because Konami has
the fucking lockdown on and I mean, there's nothing to be done.
Sometimes I think about that and I die a little bit more inside every time.
I yeah, yeah, you know, I just saw a guy on 4chan who just had a thread
with a picture of of Jack about to let her rip.
I just beat Revengeance.
Wasn't it sick?
It it was sick.
It was dope. And you know what? I was I didn't expect to.
But the senator was making.
OK, dude, don't say he was making some strong red pill.
Is it not?
He was making some good points and many terrible ones.
I mean, surely, you know, this is a sure reason.
Yeah, sure. You got a pepper is some true some truth in there.
Of course.
Like his the whole premise of this thing was like, I want America
and Americans to be great again from the war economy and to be free
to fight for things they believe in, not be slaves of this like weird,
fucked up, you know, fucking thing where they're fighting for values.
They don't give a shit about it.
They don't understand what it's basically like a criticism of neoliberalism.
I understand as I understand it.
But like I'm noticing that we saying is we want this for Americans
and we will start wars to get there.
Fuck everybody else.
Well, OK, I mean, I don't know if I'm for starting many, many wars
for the benefit of the Americans that survive at the end of the day.
Is the idea is the idea that just America's got to like fucking
conquer everything so we don't have to fight anymore?
Is that the plan?
I'm not going to lie.
I need to see it again to fully digest his point because I he makes
this rousing speech while he's beating the shit out of you.
So there's a couple of things going on in the scene at once.
I was I get the feeling that he's just like Luffy.
He's just like, you know, the the like the king of the pirates
is the is the one who's the most free.
So America's got to be king of the pirates.
I mean, he comes in and and you know, Ryden's fighting him
and Ryden's like, oh, I know what you're up to, Senator.
Like you're a selfish crook politician, just like everybody else.
You just want to like start war to personally profit off of it.
And then Armstrong comes.
He's like, no, no, no, foolish child.
You don't understand anything like he actually has sincere beliefs.
But his sincere beliefs are like, first of all, you know,
he literally says make America great again.
It's fucking insane.
The best the best moment in that epic in video games.
Oh, my God, Trump ever fucking around.
I mean, I think Reagan had said it.
So like maybe they lifted from Reagan or whatever. It doesn't matter.
No, he never said make America great.
And that's why Trump used make America great again.
It was like a callback.
I'm sure someone in the past used the phrase make America great.
I was just wondering if this was lifting something.
It was Senator Armstrong, the legend.
All right, of course.
So what was the point I was making?
Just so like Ryden assumes he's just an evil corrupt politician.
Like in actuality, it's a bit more complicated.
The senator, he actually wants like America to be free.
He actually does seem to have this like libertarian mindset.
He wants to be king of the pirates.
I assume because free.
Yeah, because he doesn't want to.
He's he's not a fascist.
He's just willing to engage in war to like destroy.
He wants to like break down America.
He I guess you'd call it accelerationism or whatever.
He wants massive wars to like just to literally drain the swamp
and shatter like the current existing status quo
and then impose, as I understand it, like basically a narco capitalism
or something where people are just on their own.
Like the weak will be subjugated by the strong
because that's how it should be, you know, things, things of this nature.
OK, I see. I see. Yeah, that's some some randy and shit.
Yeah, pretty much, pretty much. Yeah.
And you know what? There's a lot of appeal.
There's a lot of appeal.
Epic. Like a banana.
There's a lot of appeal going on here.
See, Ben, it all works out for you
because Ryden like slices his chest open and crushes his still beating heart
as you was like it to be. It was fucking sick.
It was fucking dope.
I have seen I like I don't really
I'm not a metal gear guy.
I've like barely played any metal.
So I haven't played Revengeance,
but I've seen Matthew Matosis's video about Revengeance.
So I know about the battle with Armstrong and it does look sick.
Oh, you know, some people were saying that like Nate,
a lot of people think this is the best final boss of all time.
Like, what do you think?
And I was like, it's definitely up there.
I still, you know, Zemnas and Kmartz, too.
What can I say?
I mean, I mean, Armstrong is cool as hell.
Yeah, no doubt. No fucking doubt.
He is undeniably a bad man.
I mean, after this point, he's just a fucking politician
who then you think is just piloting a metal gear.
But no, he's also a nanomachine powered monster, man.
I was so happy.
I played that game way late, but I didn't spoil myself on anything.
So all of it was just like pure fucking hype.
Holy shit.
The amazing fucking cheesy line when Jack's like, you know, it's like,
you know, I thought my sword was a tool for justice, but I might have been wrong.
Besides, this isn't my sword.
And I was like, oh, that's a great fucking line.
Do this shit.
That's a great fucking line. Oh, my God.
You know, Ben, there's one other point.
Speaking of one piece, as we were saying before, I was curious.
Here, I'm going to post an image that apparently this came afterward,
but I can't help but feel like there are a lot of similarities
between like hockey in general and like the senator.
Now, I don't know which came from which.
Doesn't he turn his arms black with his whole body becomes black at various points.
And my boy Virgo here is just, first of all, problematic black face,
not appreciating that Virgo.
Although I still argue he's black.
I appreciate it.
And I'm just saying, there's a lot of similarities between these two characters.
And I believe one piece did invent hockey first,
like a couple of years before Revengeance came out.
So I'm wondering if perhaps Revengeance decided to crib a little bit from one piece.
I don't know.
These things are fairly similar.
I'll never know.
I mean, I'll never know.
I saw who was it?
There was a, it wasn't Renegade cut.
It was super bunny hop.
Super bunny hop made a video.
I was rewatching some super bunny.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Just look at this.
You might not like it, but this is what peak male form looks like.
Fuck yeah, Virgo.
Oh my God.
What a legend.
He's beautiful.
He's nice.
He needs to hang out with Tagorell immediately.
They would be bros forever.
Bundle.
He's just a big bundle of ropes.
That's correct.
Also, he got so much bigger.
It's just just for comparison sake.
Look at him in the manga.
Like he's he's still huge, but not on this level in the in the fucking anime.
Well done, boys.
Well done.
I'm glad they dial it up to 11.
That's incredible.
Me too.
But the super bunny hop did a video about
Evangelion and Metal Gear Solid.
Yeah.
And, you know, there's a bunch to say about that.
But like in particular, like, like Evangelion is like culturally ubiquitous over there.
It's like it's like known in the way that like Star Wars is is is like widely known over here,
which is incredible.
I didn't I didn't really know that it was like to that extent.
But I imagine one piece is probably like kind of the same.
Like everybody knows one piece at least to a degree.
They'll know Luffy.
They'll know Chopper probably.
Things like that.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. So like I'd be I'd be kind of it wouldn't be surprising
if like some concepts from one piece had bled into someone like someone like
Oh, fuck, what's the what's the Metal Gear Solid guy's name?
Raiden Raiden.
No, the guy Kojima Kojima.
Yeah, it wouldn't be surprising if some had bled into it.
Like just from such like a hugely popular, culturally ubiquitous.
Yeah, it's not crazy to think.
And he's the kind of guy like like Metal Gear Solid is a fucking cultural
mishmash that he just made up from shit that he'd seen like like any work of art is.
Did you know that out of every five Japanese citizens,
one of them has a one piece podcast?
You know, it's just, you know, the podcast is just is just wrote daily life over there.
So much. Yeah, there's you'll never run out of content to consume.
Learn Japanese right now.
It's wise, it's wise. Yeah.
What?
Munchie just called me.
Munchie.
Why did he call you?
Munchie, if you have time to call back, you have time to be on the podcast.
Into the show, why don't you?
Yeah, disgusting.
Well, he's typing.
Let's let's let's let's get an explanation for this.
Yeah, OK, well, I mean, I'll be happy.
You don't have to say.
But we don't have to wait for I don't know how long it'll be.
We could go to the fucking.
The whole novel.
Oh, yeah, voicemails.
I mean, I got we've only got a couple here.
But there's I think there's four total today.
So not nothing, nothing too brutal.
Yeah, all right, fuck you guys.
We're good. Go to voicemails.
I'm ready. Good, good.
OK, let me see.
Of course, everybody leave down below in the description.
There's a link to the speak pipe.
Leave us voicemails so we can play them on the show if they are of a quality
persuasion. OK, let's let's go to first one.
First up is let me see.
Oh, yes, here we go.
This is the no nut November comrade as in comrade.
But C U M sends message to enemy Comers.
OK, it's December 1st today.
So the walls are splattered white across the nation, across the world.
So let's let's see what he has to say for himself.
30 of November 2019.
T minus seven hours till the big nut.
In a couple of hours, I will finally complete.
No, not November and show all of you disgusting comers.
That's how superior I am.
It shows my willpower is so fucking strong
that I can resist the urge to nut.
You disgust me, you lowly peasants, who cannot handle your dick.
You cannot handle to not handle your little dicks.
Fuck off, die, Comers.
I can't handle the responsibility.
Damn, got me good.
Oh, thank God.
No, not November's over today.
When we are recording this.
Indeed, indeed.
It feels good.
I am sure this the our mighty comrade here has done just fine
and is currently enjoying the fruits of his life.
Yes, congratulations, sir.
Bless bless.
All right, that's that.
Blessed be.
Let's go to the next one.
What do we got?
This is OK.
I don't know.
I don't actually know what this stands for.
Any idea what it's called?
U G W G E girl.
No united gamers with girlfriends.
I don't know.
Maybe it's a Gwee, a Gwee E girl, a Gwee.
I see, you know, I just don't know.
OK, well, let's come clear.
I don't know.
OK, here we go.
And here they go play.
So I had a girl who was a big tinny got girlfriend.
And she says, I should drink more.
My own do tells me I should say the N word more.
Who trash talks and gets in deep with face clan.
One day, the 360 no scope silent shot her.
She's in MLG.
Quick scoping montage is all over the internet.
I just want to see your game again.
I just want to let her know that I don't care that she got pwned.
So I joined the public lobby and go AFK.
So my Katie ratio drops.
And you know what?
She calls me a noob.
She unfriends me on Xbox Live.
Now I see the full set.
Now I'm always saying the N word, Nick.
He finally sees the sunny side.
I mean, wait, the funny side of life.
Right. Right. Yeah, good.
I've I've learned my new favorite euphemism is the gamer word.
Yes. Yeah, that's good.
I learned that recently.
And sometimes you have a gamer moment
when you say the gamer word happens to the best of us.
What what is OK?
What exactly is an e girl?
Is it just a girl, you know, on the internet?
I would argue it's a more specific thing than that.
Like it's I mean, I thought that it was like a Titty streamer
or like a like a male is a celeb.
Right. I would think it's merely defamatory
to just call any girl online an e girl.
That doesn't seem. I thought it was like there's no distinction.
We had some sort of like presence
or trying to do something on the internet.
Yeah. Right. Yeah.
Like you're not just on the internet.
That's passively.
Nate, Nate, you're trying to have an urban dictionary.
Yes, she's right. Oh, you're right.
She's right. Let's let's go.
Why guess from the beginning?
Well, because I thought it was like a female e celeb.
But then I feel like people toss the word around
in a way that it just means any girl on the internet.
You know, I think it's it's kind of a nebula.
Or it's got fuzzy and I just like everything on social media.
It has multiple definitions, depending on who you are.
OK, well, here's the top one on Urban Dictionary.
E girl. Finally, we've got the authority way.
And OK, here we go.
E girl, an e girl is a species of emo usually found on TikTok.
No, but commonly spends time on Tumblr.
All right. I don't give a shit about the definition.
I don't know what an adult has to say on the matter.
I mean, you commonly found doing the me, me, me, meme dance,
but has probably never seen it before.
OK, some of these things do not have to be emo to be an e girl.
OK, all right. Let's go to definition two here.
This second definition is better, I think.
OK, here we go. So definition one of section two here is OK.
E girls are usually girls who play games online
and can be found on either Twitter or Discord.
They send nudes slash thirst traps or even sell them.
They can also be found on Twitch.
But the difference between a normal girl who plays video games
and an e girl. OK, good.
To make the distinction is that an e girl begs for money
or sells herself for it.
You can theoretically beg for money and not be an e girl.
But if you're like selling sexy picks, that's definitely e girl.
That seems much closer to my general understanding of I've seen.
I've seen Discord servers
like say that like we have e girls in our Discord server as like a selling point.
But it sounds like a derogative.
Yeah, I mean, I thought it was going to be a negative like stay away.
We've got e girls in our ranks.
Don't come in here, boys. Protect.
No, like when I when I went on like various
there are sites that like you can like search and find
Discord servers on and I put endless war on a couple of them.
Like, just to know Ben was googling how to meet.
Someone tell me I saw and I would see the term ego.
So I was like, like join our server.
You know, we're a we're a cute, comfy community community based server.
You know, we got custom roles.
We got e girls. We got e boys.
And I'm like, do we want those things?
Are those good things? I don't.
What? What's what's what happened?
It depends on the perspective.
But I'll be spending my evenings at the opera.
Thank you. Not on your Discord server.
I think when you call a girl and you girl,
usually you could be taking as a bad thing to be called.
But some people just wear it was unless you're pro slut.
Pro slut.
It really depends on the perspective and the person.
We call it we call it sex positive.
These days, you're right.
I prefer my ancient term pro slut.
But yeah, you're right. You're right.
I don't know. It's open to interpretation.
If you like it, great.
Well, as a father or a mother,
would you want your daughter to be an e girl?
Perhaps that's the operative question to ask.
Probably not in the strictest definition of the term.
No, indeed, indeed.
Oh, but, you know, like, you know, I was thinking that, like,
if someone if like a girl is in a,
you know, these, these Discord chat girls will come in there
and they'll they'll start to throw around some oo-woos.
They'll start to throw around some oh woes.
Yeah, you know what they're doing.
They're baiting me. I can't resist an oo-wooh.
Especially capitalized, bolded, italicized.
I'm putty in their hands.
And this is female power and frankly, it's toxic.
It has to be changed.
Mages oolooing right now.
It's not oolooing, it's nyoron.
Okay, that's the I apologize.
That's a whole other level.
Mages advanced here.
I'm not even ready to face that kind of demon.
You know, I just thought I'd play this one briefly
as an example.
This seemed like a good voicemail,
but just listen to how unintelligible this voicemail is
from the ghost of scumbag, Chris.
If you want to go listen to it,
it's on the fucking SoundCloud.
Just give this a listen for one second.
Oh, oh shit, it didn't work.
Wait, hang on.
This is pretty bad.
I got it, I got it.
Okay.
Totally in auto.
Go.
I just wanted to point out
that personally, if you're applying for this November,
it will only become the 20th of November.
See, can you make out any of this?
Hmm.
I see the problem.
Bits and pieces.
Stop, stop, disconnecting.
I heard the word November.
I heard November.
Yeah, no, not November was being discussed.
I just, guys, you should listen back to your own shit
if you listen, because that I just cannot fucking tell.
Okay, no, no, no, no, listening back,
no, no, listening back isn't gonna work
because you know what it's supposed to say,
so you hear it, ask someone else to listen it for you.
You know, that's a better suggestion.
If you're not sure, yeah, get a second opinion.
Because some people I know,
they'll like play something on a speaker
and hold it up to their microphone
and it gets more distorted or things of this nature.
I know there are some ways around it
that some people around here discuss.
So this is just one of these public service announcements.
If it's unintelligible, even if it sounds potentially good,
obviously it's gonna be an issue for playing on the show.
It's actually bad.
It's actually not quality.
Well, I mean, that's it, that's our last voicemail.
Wait, really?
Yeah, I mean, there was just a couple today.
We've only gone, we're only on an hour and 18.
Uh-oh, stall for time, stall for time.
Only an hour.
Oh, wait a minute, I'm sorry, I skipped one.
I did actually skip one, now that I look at it, whoops.
Oh, it better be a good one.
It's gonna be a 40 minute voicemail.
Save us.
Oh, it's 100% not, it's, no, it's not.
This is another kind of, okay,
let me just fucking play it, all right, here you go.
It's voicemail guide redemption, go.
What's up, voicemail guide, try to make it quick.
Okay, look, I don't think it's very fair
that you're giving other people a chance
to start arcs and finish their arcs
when you're not willing to finish mine.
If I just want some redemption,
can you please finish my arc?
Guess who I am, Hippo, Nate, Ben.
Oh my God.
The most you guys could know me.
Your other hint is Kingdom Hearts, Kingdom Hearts, okay?
It'll all make sense in due time.
Are you Keyblade Spirit?
I don't fucking know, that could be you.
It definitely could be you, but listen to the entitlement.
Once again, it's not fair you finish other people's arcs.
Okay, you know what?
I'll give you that.
Keyblade Spirit is a good guess,
like I have no other guess beside that,
so I'm just gonna go with it.
Are you Keyblade Spirit?
There you go, but, I mean,
you must certainly understand a fair voicemail guide.
Oh, hey, you know what?
You know what happened?
Yeah.
Something funny happened in, it was during slime fest.
Oh, wait, you know what, I wanna say something.
People don't know.
Rowdyfuckers Cop Killers is on a new channel.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
And the newest episode, like the full, like real episode,
not a Twitch VOD re-uploaded,
but like an actual, like me and Munchy sit down
and make like a three hour long actual RFCK episode
is up and is the most recent video
on the Rowdyfuckers Cop Killers channel.
And it's only got like 400 views,
and I think a lot of people just don't know it's there.
But it is.
Yeah, I think you're right.
We've moved to a new channel,
link in the description for that.
Okay, actually.
Speaking of Munchy, did he ever explain himself to you
why he called you?
Oh, yes, he did.
He said, oops, I didn't mean to call you,
but I did mean to ask if I got clearance
to listen to Storm Before the Storm,
which is a book we were talking about
that I did listen to on Audible,
but I was gonna listen to it again,
but I think he wants to do it.
And yeah, I'm not re-listening to this.
So the answer was yes.
Word.
Yes, been listening to books.
So it was streaming.
We were streaming Slime Fest yesterday.
And at the end, at the very end of it, spoiler alert,
I won the moral victory, as always.
Way to go, which is another way of saying
of losing the actual competition.
That's not true.
That's just not true.
It's all in how you look at it.
Okay, understood.
Victory is a social construct.
And so at the very end,
we were talking about what the next contest would be,
and I said a karaoke contest,
and I was reminded of the karaoke contest
between Christine Weston-Chandler and Solid Chris
and Liquid Chris, when Chris challenged Liquid
to a Singstar karaoke contest
to determine who was the real Chris.
And I said this, and then I went back to record,
what's the word, to make the VOD,
to highlight the VOD, so it'd be saved.
And I see at the very end, after I said that,
Chris appears in chat to say,
like, hmm, a karaoke contest is to say,
who's who, sounds a little too familiar.
Lol.
And I was like, lol, she heard me say the whole thing.
That's hilarious.
I think that was the only comment she made.
She just shows up to my streams now.
It's pretty funny.
I mean, yeah, clearly invested in the narrative
to some degree.
It's pretty funny.
I've been a little slower
on the slime and punishment updates lately,
but I've got a couple in the can ready to go,
maybe later today or tomorrow.
Sick, sick.
I've been checking your feed, looking for him regularly,
so you've got at least one person.
You've got at least one person who gives the fuck.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I mean, I'm not gonna lie,
I'm held in out for that keg standard cameo.
Although I did see him in, what was it,
Phantom Point was like thinking about something,
and then he had a little thought bubble of a...
Yeah, he's talking to Dupati and Tupati,
and he's talking about the importance of,
today I learned about the importance of loving your brother,
even when you don't always get a long line crib
directly from Friendship is Witchcraft.
Oh yeah.
I think, I guess it won't spoil too much.
I think there will probably be a keg cameo in the epilogue.
Sure, seems understandable.
I think that would be an appropriate time for it.
Hey, as long as it's appropriate.
Yeah.
No interference here with the artistic process.
Yeah, and I won't say in what context,
but that's a tentative plan.
So guys, you can all put down your pitchforks,
your favorite character, just give it a little time.
All these bullshit meme side characters,
they'll get out of the way soon.
I'm really looking forward to having it done,
because I feel like when I say, guys, it's done, it's finished.
I feel like that's the point when a lot of people will be like,
oh, okay, if it's actually done,
then maybe I'll go back and read it.
Because that's what I did with Balejap.
Like when Hippo said, like, oh yeah,
I just released the finale, it's over.
I was like, oh shit, I guess I gotta read it now.
And I did.
People love a finished product.
Yeah.
Speaking of finished products,
we should show them the new bonus episode,
because it's good or so.
Oh, you know, I'm so glad you mentioned that.
Yeah, maybe I would remember it at the end.
But yeah, the new bonus episode is,
the day of recording, I'll be releasing it after we're done.
And it's game development,
and there's a whole bunch of links to games we've made,
including the ones we mentioned before.
There's my little demo, I made it with my buddy John.
I've untitled Music Jumper, featuring QT Bass Drop.
There's the, of course, the Izumi game stuff
is linked in there.
Mage has some works,
some artwork from various projects.
Other things too.
The Saint Comics, the champion game,
which has just been up on SaintComics.com the whole time.
But I linked that too, I guess.
Indeed, indeed.
Also a game.
A world game bell I made with my buddy Rich back in the day
in college, that was a good time too.
An endless war.
Slime game.
If you could call it a game.
Slime game, not a lifestyle.
It's more of a lifestyle choice, yeah.
All right, we've delayed long enough.
We can wrap it up here, I think, boys and girls.
That's, we've done our due diligence.
We won't torment you any longer.
So let's see what's going on.
Of course, patreon.com slash the procrastinators
is always going on.
It's the hip-hoppin' in place
for all your social media updates
and currency draining exchanges.
If you're on the Discord server,
you don't even need Twitter anymore.
It's just outdated that.
Yeah, get off Twitter and get in the PCP Discord.
That's it.
Very true.
That's what it's about.
It's better, anyway.
Oh, you know, the other day, someone in your Discord bed,
first of all, they added me.
They added me specifically.
I just said like some, I mean, in my opinion,
it was horrific bullshit, but I mean,
the way that I read it, I won't say their name
because we made peace.
But it sounded like what this person's point was,
like, hey, Nate, just so you know,
like everything you've ever done
is like a pale shadow of Digi and you're pathetic
and I don't respect you.
Oh, wow.
I mean, okay.
I'm exaggerating for comedic effect right now,
but that was kind of the gist of what I read into it.
What actually, as we, so I got very angry,
but as we teased it out, their point seemed more to be,
hey, Nate, I don't actually think content
is the best use of your time
and would prefer you to do like your big videos.
And well, okay, just say that then.
Yeah, that's a very different statement, right?
But if they just said that,
they wouldn't make you mad and get a response out of you.
Oh my God, you've cracked the code.
That's very true.
That's, you know, that's true.
Well, it's all right.
It's all right.
Interpreted better and all is well.
What were we talking about?
Oh yes, of course, money, patreon.com
slash the procrastinators, $5 bonus episodes,
game dev one, actually a good bonus episode, guys.
Actually a good one.
What do you mean?
They're all gems.
I don't know what you're talking about.
They're all gems, but some sparkle more than others.
Well, most of them are gems in the rough,
so just lumps of coal,
but this one is actually a semi-formed one.
This one's particularly good.
So we all have experience projects to share.
Indeed, indeed.
And go listen to that.
End of the 31 other episodes,
32 total of the bonus episodes
for the low, low fee of $5 on the Patreon.
$1, you're in the bonus, not the bonus,
the PCB discord, the patron discord.
Good times, be there, obviously, as you said before.
And more, hey, as much as you want.
You could also go give $5 a month
to the PCP Minecraft server if you want as well.
Play Minecraft with us.
We got a stream coming up.
I think right now we have it scheduled
for Friday, December the 13th.
So keep an eye out for that if you wanna play,
so we will be there around then sometime in December.
And what else is going on?
At TPCrasnators on Twitter,
updates and whatnot, retweets, et cetera, et cetera.
And, of course, Speakpipe, leave more voicemails
so that we can respond to them here on the show.
Thanks, everybody for doing that.
Voicemail God, I forgive you.
All right, we'll see you next week, everybody.
And there it is, character art concluded.
Forgiveness, redemption.
All right, see you next week, everybody.
Bye.
Bye, thank you.