Hello everybody and welcome back to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm
the best guy ever, and I'm about $20,000 richer off of this Kickstarter.
Hey everybody, this episode of The Pro Crastinator is brought to you by Mike Bloomberg for President
2020, depositing $20,000 directly into our Kickstarter account, and now we're bought
and paid for, baby. Mike, he's the cool candidate. Bill, Mike, love that guy. Did you hear as well?
This message is sponsored by Pete Buttigieg's dog, who he roleplays as on Twitter.
Yeah? It's true. Much like Spoonie, Pete Buttigieg also has dog roleplay accounts on Twitter,
where he roleplays some dogs. Well, I'm gonna have to look into that. I mean, the joke about Pete is
that he strangles dogs in the studio. So I don't know if that's a deliberate attempt to get ahead of
that message. He roleplays the dog being into it. That's what he does. Every day he strangles dog
after dog, but one day there was a dog whose neck was so strong he just couldn't ring it, and he
thought, you know what, this one comes with me. Yes, that's right. Hey guys, in case you haven't
seen it, of course, you should definitely go check out the now concluded Radcon 4 Paradise
Kickstarter page. Obviously, it was a success as of several weeks ago. When you hear this,
it'll be closed. For us, we've got like two days left, and we are right on the cusp of 20,000,
as we speak. Incredible. As we speak, we are almost there, with about, what, 40 hours to go? 45?
That's right. And I'm talking like $150 to get their give or take. So it's looking good. It's
looking good. Oh, well, well, well, well, well, well, well. Here we are. Hot fuck.
I mean, when we started, so, man, it's funny to look back on it. When we started, there was all
this debate and ringing of teeth and gnashing of nails about how much to charge. And I mean,
you know, it was all understandable that we not try to overcharge people based on like how much
we earned last time. We undercharged them. As a matter of business, we 100% undercharged,
because we just lost money on the whole operation. This time, oh, praise God. Oh, the first time.
No, no, no, no. Listen, we've lesson learned again. You can never gouge hard. And we have just
at the, wait, oh my God, I just saw the tally on the Kickstarter tick up. Let me refresh the,
what the fuck? It went over 20,000 and then it dipped back down. I think someone pledged and
then immediately unpledged. Oh, wait, no, there it goes. Boom. There it goes. It's going back over.
I'm going to die. 20,000. I'm seeing 19,831 for me. I did. I'll refresh the damn page. Okay. I got
it. I got it. I'm going to die. Oh, no. Help. Oh, please. I'm seeing the page go above it. No,
okay. It keeps like cycling over 20,000. Okay. Well, I have no doubt it will make over 20,000.
Yeah, it says 20K for me. I just want to see the number. I just want to see the number.
20,081. And $81.77. I'm going to put a link in the show. For me, it says 19. Okay. Now I'm
seeing 20,000. It updated actually without me having to reload the page. For me, it says
19,831. It'll do in a second. I'm seeing 20,080. Give it a minute. My internet is being shit today.
Well, that means I'm writing chapter five, I guess. Chapter five. And a physical release.
Print that shit. Yep. So let's talk about that. 20,001. Oh, 081 actually, but close enough.
Ben, you've done some physical printings of comics before. Yeah. How has that gone for you?
Pretty easy. Yeah, yeah. Well, actually, I've been thinking about this. Yeah, I printed
vapors one and vapors two. It was pretty easy. I used a website or a printing service called
Blam, with a dash between Ka and Blam. I mean, yeah, you just like saved your, you get like
high res image files. Okay. Yeah, I, this, this service was for like comic printing.
There would probably be cheaper ways to print like a text thing. I imagine like,
yeah, people say Amazon publishing is good for that. So you don't even have to submit like a
PDF, but just actually image files. And they like, I mean, they wanted me to save them as this,
like a TNG file or something, but like, whatever it was. The next generation Star Trek.
I don't think that was, it was something, it was some weird format, but yeah, they were just like,
save all your files in high resolution as this file, like send them to us in a zip file, and we'll
just, we'll send you the fucking thing when it's ready, which, um, yeah, can't wait to do that
again for papers too. Once all my guests artists get their pages in, hint, hint, hint, if you are
listening, I was planning to use the same website to print my book just because there's going to
be a bunch of comic pages, manga pages in my book. And, uh, they have the option on that website to
get the book manga sized as a paperback. Like, yeah, you can get it a little book. That sounds nice.
So yeah, I think that would be sick.
You know, I don't know, I got recommended that service by another comic maker.
You might want to maybe ask around other like book writers about whether it's the cheapest
way to go about printing a text novel. I mean, again, I've heard that the Amazon service is good
for, even for printing, so I don't know, I had to look into that as well, but if...
Call up our old friend, ask him with that experience as well.
He's Lulu, he didn't use it.
Oh, okay, okay.
I was, uh, I was fucking around the other night. I was feeling like too probably, probably in the
wake of like the New Hampshire, the New Hampshire primaries or something. I was too emotionally
drained. I was too, I had gone through too much turmoil and I couldn't think anymore.
So I was like, man, I'm not, I gotta, I gotta do some shit. I gotta do some work, but I can't think.
So I was like, I'll do some thoughtless work and I'll just, for no, no particular reason at all,
like just, just because maybe. I'll just, I'll just take slime and punishment and arrange it into
pages as though it were to be printed in a book or something at some future date. And I'll just do,
I don't know why. I don't know, just, just fucking around. So, so I was doing that and then I was
looking around for like printers, because Ka-Blam will not, I was thinking if it were going to be
printed, it would be in like, I was imagining it like the Homestuck book, you know, basically
landscape style, like four panels like that. But Ka-Blam won't print in landscape. It only does
formats that are portrait arrangement. So I was like, fuck. So I briefly started looking around
for like alternatives and I didn't find anything, but I'm sure there's, maybe I should look at Amazon
for, I don't know, because thing about slime and punishment is that it's like full color and like,
if there were like any limitations on color in like, in like the physical printing, it would
look like complete shit, right? Because it's got so many like fully saturated, like crushed
collies and stuff. So the, it must be robust. Anyway, I don't know. That's, that's, I'll, I'll,
I'll look at it. I'll take a look at Amazon might, might be worth it. Fucking Ka-Blam,
fucking Ka-Blam will only print comics that look like comic books or manga. It will do like,
because slime and punishment printed physically would be like, well over 100 pages. And if you
get over 64 pages, it doesn't, it won't print it as a comic. It will, it has to print it as a,
like a quote unquote paperback. And I guess that means, you know, it has a spine and everything.
But it still won't change the, it still won't, it still won't landscape.
I need it landscape. I don't want to print it vertically. That's dumb. It was published on
Twitter in a, in a four, in a four image, an update, layout. I want to preserve that.
That's important.
Makes sense, makes sense. Yeah, I was wondering about the, the whole like amount of pages,
because the Vapors chapters have only been, what, like, 20, 20 pages? Vapors one was 40 something.
The Lord of Ghost comic, I was thinking of, of making a thing as well. Chapter three is out,
by the way. Yeah, that's right. Chapter three, link in the description. It just came out, right?
Just came out. Minutes ago.
As soon as I entered the call. Minutes ago for us.
For us. Right. It's been out since.
Sunday for you listening, folks.
Yeah, but the final thing will be about 100 pages almost. So I'm thinking,
is that, would that be a problem? But I guess not. Yeah, yeah.
I'm sure there's a way to do it.
Guys, and we got to talk about this, because I'm here with the two of you, Ben and Gibbon,
who draw comics. And that's all I've been doing for the last couple weeks.
Yeah. And it's, it's pretty great. Drawing comics is better than drawing regular illustrations.
IMO. You think so? How do you figure?
Let me put it to you like this. In a similar sense that, I think that the more complex a medium is,
at the same time, there are more ways that you can fail, but also the failures are kind of muted
by the successes of other areas. I saw a great tweet yesterday. And I was like, I was like,
yes, I am living for this tweet. So relatable. I said, drawing comics is about accepting your
ugly panels and moving on. And I was like, that's so true. Ben, I have a new catchphrase, and this
is kind of going to be the overall like linchpin arc words of the book, Cus Omega, which is,
it's not about being clever. It's about pushing forward. And in so many ways, you know, yeah,
basically, AKA, please excuse my bad project, but I had to make something. So here it is.
Anything finished is like Brian Leo Malley said, anything finished is automatically better than
anything unfinished. Whatever it takes to get it done. The perfect is the enemy of the good. I
completely agree. The arc that the character goes through in the story is that like he had killed
himself because of the fact that he was writing nothing but bullshit for so long and never got
around to writing his ideas for stuff that would be like really great works of literature because
he didn't think he was good enough to actually write them. And so he just didn't. And then
ultimately ends up killing himself. And when he reflects on it, he's like, well, you know,
even if those stories hadn't come out the way I wanted, it would have been better to try than to
kill myself, you know, indeed, since it puts him into the situation and all. But but did you don't
you know that being born is inherently abuse? Our parents didn't get our consent to be born to
have to carry these burdens in this world. I think the character possibly could have made that
argument if not for the fact that killing himself just didn't bring him any release at all. It's
simply trapped him in a narrative of how I would argue it would for us, though. It would bring us
relief, ladies and gentlemen. We don't know that, though. You don't know. That's the mistake that
he made. You never see it coming. So so with regards to the comics, like more so than just
like bad panels being held up by good ones, but even just when we think about one punch man,
right, the original release, the strength of it was not just that it had a great concept,
which is already the biggest strength of one punch man, but also that one sincerely has
great compositions in his imagery. They're just not well drawn, you know, and so like I kind of
looked at it like as long as I can communicate the story through the facial expressions and poses
to a degree where you understand what this is supposed to look like, then it kind of can carry
itself. That's it. You've got it. You've got it. You activate the imagination. It's just about like
my, especially with slime and punishment. I mean, in particular with slime and punishment. It's just
about get a page done and done means it conveys the thing I wanted to convey. Right. Yeah. And then
it's done. I mean, it's funny because I'm already used to doing that in other forms of art, so it
kind of comes naturally to me to transition that mode of thinking into comics. I just had never
really tried it before, but because of the fact that I'm doing this physical release of Cusomega,
and I decided to hire a bunch of artists to work on it, and I storyboarded all the comics
that are going to be in it. So I did 18 pages of comics and then another 12 for... Did you ever
giggle to yourself thinking like, hey, I'm just like that guy from Bakuman, you know, the one who...
Yes. The writer. Exactly. That's what I would do. You mean the blonde guy? The glasses guy. Yeah,
that guy. I mean the author himself, because like in Bakuman, they sometimes will show the
storyboards that Tsugumi Oba does for Bakuman, and then show Takeshi Obata's redone storyboards,
where he like, you know, he redraws it and makes it more dynamic and like changes the
structure of all the boxes before he goes in and draws it, you know, which is exactly what
some of these artists did who are working on... Like, some of my comics, they took it and really
re-adapted it into something very different, whereas there's one guy who is the one who kind of gave
me the idea to do this project, who really just wants to draw comics written by me. Like, that
was his goal. He was like, I will just... He didn't even want payment. He was just like, I just want
to draw comics, you write, right? Based on this story. So I've got him doing like a 12 page comic.
Kind of fucked that guy a little bit. For bringing down everyone else's potential
earning, potential buy. A little bit of a scab, a little bit of a pick and line crossing.
They need a union. No, for what it's worth, I'm not having him do anything for free. I told him...
There you go. I will not accept that. But uh, unless it was for no profit, but this particular
profit is... Sure, sure. If nobody's... If nobody's... If nobody's making any money, then sure.
But it's fascinating because he has been adapting my storyboards like
almost exactly to where it's basically just the same images, but with that level of detail that
I am just not capable of, you know? That's what you want. But it's funny, it's not exactly what
I want the most because I don't think my storyboards are necessarily amazing. So if they can be
improved, then by all means go for it, you know, which a lot of the other artists have done. But
it is... It's good in a sense that I can say, okay, well, like, this will let me see exactly
what this would look like fully realized. And then I can truly understand, like,
what am I doing right and wrong in my storyboarding? You know, this is a fascinating
point because not to be an asshole to that guy, but it sounds like he might be the kind of guy
who's such a big fan of yours that he might be afraid to tweak anything that you put. So he
wants to just stick to it. Whereas if you have somebody who... Let's say like you just reach out
to like a true pro and you pay him a million dollars, and they're like, yeah, I know what I'm
doing, I'll adapt your ideas, then they'll add some of their own expertise and artistic flair.
I mean, for what it's worth... I don't want to downplay how much he adds to it just because
the quality of my drawing is so low that the fact that he could extrapolate it into something that
looks correct is like, oh, wow, this is what you would need to add. Like, it's significantly
different, you know, in spite of the fact of being the same pose-wise.
You posted some of these redrawn stuff on Twitter, right?
I posted the two-page comic that he did. Link that.
Oh, that's his? I thought that was pretty good. The one with... Yes. Yeah, I saw that. It looks good.
Yeah, it looks real good. I agree. That's why I'm excited about this project.
But yeah, I'll link... I will post in the gross audio links the original storyboards as well,
so you can prepare them. Oh, this one. Oh, yeah, this does... This is excellent.
That's solid. By the way, the thing about... I like about the comic vibrations with numbers for
letters. This link is to the storyboards. These are probably available, so it's no big...
Yeah, the thing I like about the drawing of comics, and it is kind of like a storyboard
for animation a lot of the time, where you can imply a lot of movement by just having the same
thing shot like a few seconds after what it looks like. You're basically doing keyframes,
but really with no in-betweens whatsoever, and then that way you can convey so much more movement
than... Well, I mean, traditional illustration, just one image, it's always just felt like
there's not enough going on, because nothing can happen. It's a still moment in time. It's a photograph.
I mean, I wrote a piece on this before, but I actually had a website for Cusomega that got
taken down today because it exceeded its bandwidth limit from a fucking 3-note or whatever the...
They give you very low bandwidth limit. That or it was taken down because it had adult content on
it. I'm not sure which, because they didn't tell me anything, and it's just gone, so I might have
to build a whole new website, which is really annoying, because there's a lot of content on...
Like, I literally wrote a fucking massive thing that I only posted there and do not have backup of,
so let's hope I get that back. But in there, I was talking about how part of what inspired
all these comics and illustrations is that in the book, these two characters, Crom and Baila,
do not get really described in all that much detail. They're briefly touched on. Baila is not
described enough that you could even draw a picture of her. She didn't get any fan art.
So I was thinking just, what is the maximum amount I can convey about these characters
with images in the span of a couple pages? And it's like, even just seeing the range of facial
expressions that a character would make, even just seeing three of them tells you so much about
the character, just because it's like, you only would imagine them making so many faces.
So in this comic, Baila's got the really intense... She's having a ton of fun casting magic,
almost like sadistic in the first page, and then it's more relaxed on the second page,
whereas her dad mostly looks kind of serious. And in the book, he never jokes about anything,
but because I have a comic, I can do a thought bubble on him and give him kind of a snarky thing
to say. And the last face is like, this really expressive anime face really only makes sense
visually. I don't know how I would describe it in text. So it's like... I know that face well.
Just being able to add that in and give you that mental image, going back to read the story,
will change your impression of the story. Now you have these anime characters in your mind,
and this range of expressions they're capable of. So when I describe the expressions that these
characters are showing, you are more likely to think about other anime you've seen with
characters who look kind of similar, and kind of just plug in those expressions. And I think
that's why light novels exist, basically. That's my theory. The theory is to make quick cash with
one good picture of an anime girl. Is there even any other medians where speech bubble or thought
bubbles can even be a thing that isn't weird? Anime does it, but it is weird. But they speak
sort of like in their head, because it's motion and it's movement. If somebody's thinking something,
the amount of time it takes for them to say the words that they're thinking is a lot longer than
it would actually take to think those thoughts. So it's like, it's a disconnect. Maybe this is
just because of the fact that I do this kind of analysis, and I'm always thinking about these
things. But what brings... I feel like I'm fucking trying to say, oh, I'm fucking, I just started
making comics, and they're already good. But the theory behind what I'm approaching these
comics with is, what can I do in comics that I couldn't do in writing, and couldn't do in these
other mediums? Because that's what excites me the most about the idea of making them is, oh,
this is a whole different angle. These are stories that... This story in text is not interesting
in any way, but as a visual guide to the characters, there's a fun snappiness to it.
It got me really excited, because after drawing all these comics, none of which I planned at all.
I did not write anything. I just started drawing and let it develop, and it was so much fun,
I couldn't stop. And now it's a problem, because...
You should just stop the whole YouTube thing. Be like a creator boy, like me and Ben. Make comics.
I'm implying that YouTube is not creation in any way. I mean, okay, for many people it's not, but
okay. It's literally the dumbest thing you could ever do.
That's not true. Frank Yang is an artist who makes weird fitness slash art piece videos that are
about the perfect sprinter, Tom Cruise, how I will obtain. It's Andrew Yang's younger, more
muscly brother. Definitely, yeah. By the way, I just let me just say, fuck comics, all trash,
put them into the garbage, and thank God that on today's episode we have an announcement of
a happy time from a guy who has abandoned comics for all time and become an exclusive video man,
one Munchyshatsky, who has destroyed Investigator and is releasing today, the day we are recording
this, three new episodes of Stealing Your Dad have just dropped. I can't believe it. They're all
out right now. No, they're not. Oh, you're right, you're right. They are at the time of you listening
to this, but they are coming out every three hours over the course of the whole day. Episode
one is out though. Are they on his channel? Yes, they're on Munchy on his channel. So I just
linked his channel, we'll put it in the show notes there. To clarify, because nobody actually has any
idea what Stealing Your Dad's is. I was on it and I still don't. Let me explain. So Stealing
Your Dad's is originally a podcast that me and Munchy were doing in which we review fast food
by both of us going and getting the same fast food, because obviously fast food exists all around
the country. We would buy the same fast food and then record a podcast of us eating and reviewing
it. But also, because we were describing the setting of the world that we were in,
which is extremely, we would say it's basically the prototype of the world in
Ratty Fockers' Comkillers. Yeah, endless war. There is fear eyes that they're located in the same
along the same time. They are similar enough, fallout-esque super apocalypses that they can
feasibly exist in the same universe. They're both highly fast food-based. Yeah. The thing about
the show, though, is that for the most part, it was highly experimental. The audio quality is
not good. It is experimental audio quality. The experiment is, what if I turned it down?
What if I made it worse? So most of these only have a couple hundred views. I don't know that
there was any expectation from any audience that this would continue or that they wanted it in
any way. Well, clearly there was a small but dedicated audience. Well, because the thing is that
the three that we recorded at Radcon were videos, live-action videos, which were meant to be fully
edited by Ethan, I think, who also edited the Spicy Bro Pack video, which there's also a Spicy Bro
Packed from Radcon 3 that also has still not come out. But the one from Radcon 2 took a whole year,
so that's not a surprise. But yeah, these three have just been waiting in Limbo for the last
fucking literally nearly two years since we fucking did it. That's right. Is that how long it's
been? Wait, when did we do Radcon 3? Yeah, it took T-Bap Resurrection one full year to get done,
and it's been over a year since that. Oh my god. I was going to say these were the last Radcontent,
but no, I guess that Spicy Bro Packed is still... Oh wait, technically it was in March, so it's
technically been just under two years. That's the time for me. Yeah, sure. Which by the way,
the original Spicy Bro Packed video was like one of my favorite videos. It was fucking just
legendary. It was sick. And so that's why I've been nauseating. That's the reason like my excitement
over stealing your dad's has... I mean, I'm looking at people have screencapped some incredible
moments from the first episode in my Discord. Yeah, I'll go ahead and I'm going to have the...
Yeah, I haven't watched any of them, obviously. They just came out like minutes ago.
You know, we need to call this episode. We need to call this episode We Did It.
Munchie did it. Gib did it. Ben did it. Did you. Nate did it. The Radcon's a huge success. We did
it. They're on Munchie's channel, right? Yeah, they are. They're all there. Okay. Ew, gross.
Why is that happening? How unfortunate.
Let me bathe you in my meal. That might have to be my new avatar on Twitter or something.
That's pretty good. Ew, it's so gross. Oh, I don't like that at all. It's a Wendy's ice cream.
It's in Gross Disgusting. Gross Disgusting is right.
We did it. So true. So true. Click the link, everybody. God, I'm so glad those videos are
out. We did it. There it is. They did it. We did nothing. No. We were in the vicinity.
We were on the right side of history. Oh, they're from here. You know, the only issue I have,
or the one thing I'm concerned about with Radcon, not really, but I just want to,
we've got a bunch of stuff we've got to do. I want to leave those precious spaces in
between things to do whatever the fuck we feel like, you know? So maybe we can just
smash everything out really fast and then just do whatever we want for like the last bit of time.
Oh, oh, I'm sorry. And then I saw on Twitter the thing, I saw one individual whose name I forget
say the thing that gets tossed around here and there. And this guy is just like,
y'all nibbaz really paid these guys $20,000 to go on vacation, which is hilarious, which is a
hilarious thing to say. And entirely true. 100% true. That's definitely a major component of the
story. But hey, voluntary exchanges of currency for products and services. Good stuff. Good stuff.
Very excited. We've got like three weeks until we're out there doing shit. When you hear this,
it'll be like two weeks. So incredible. What a world. By the way, this is episode 199.
Next episode is 200. That's right. So I don't know what that means, but it means.
Oh yeah. Shall we talk about our plan to like do episode 200 at Redcon 4 regardless and just
skip. Just skip it. Skip it. Skip it for the meantime. Just do it. Well, when we're there.
We could, we could, we could role play for the next two episodes from the post-apocalypse
episode. Like it's a flash forward in the narrative. The post-apocalypse with the word,
with the number 200 doesn't exist. And we have to skip to 201 instead. We have to find it.
We're recording them from the future after like, oh, okay, just here's a thought. We record next
episode, episode 201. It's us. Maybe I shouldn't even say it, but it's us responding to the reaction
to Radcon 3 from the future narratively and the cataclysmic failure that it was and how everything
went wrong and we lost all the money, you know, et cetera, et cetera. It was all embezzled by,
was that company that stole all of Hussie's money when he was trying to make that game?
We partnered with them. The King's Crab, Darling House. No, the, the, the, the, the something
gentleman. The odd gentleman. The odd gentleman. Yeah, we partnered with them for distribution
and that turned out to be a bad idea. But you know, we were rolling with the punches.
We got to ask Daddy Mike Bloomberg for some more funding. We got, we got to go dip back into that
well. You know, speaking of corporate investment, I, I was looking at a couple of the, after our
stunning success with the Garling House Industries people, we still don't have our channel back,
by the way. That's pretty cool. Hopefully that'll be fixed soon. They seem to be really nice. It'd
be really nice if we had it back, which it seems, well, YouTube said they were on the cusp, but
YouTube said we were on the cusp of getting it back. They seem to be preparing to give it back
to us. They're just edging. They're edging us for sure. It would be really nice if we could have
it back by the time that the Kickstarter ends, because we're going to do that, like on the day
it ends, we're going to like stream for a few hours beforehand, like count down the hours,
probably like shout out like big doughnose and stuff. Let me just say for fun that like the,
the last message of substance I got on like the PCPA account was them saying like, hey,
hey bro, like we're working on your thing. We are going to move your account to like a new brand
account. So like they seem to have identified the problem. They're like, make a new brand
account, which is just like a new type of YouTube channel. We will like move the PCP onto the account,
give us the link, bro. I'm like instantly, okay, provide them the link. And then I'm also like,
Hey, also, should I make more for like the other channels? They have that. And they just have not
fixed the problem. And it's been like four days. I don't know why, maybe because the weekend is
happening now. But they have everything they need to restore the channel and seem to be waiting
and willing to do so instantly. They just have not let alone. This makes me really,
this makes me really depressed about the potential about the future of the other channels like the
PODcast and TBAP and a little bit. Yeah, like the fact that they are so lazy about it. Like,
I mean, I guess TBAP and PODcast have like, I mean, best guy ever is obviously the biggest channel.
The other ones are all like that. How many how many subs did the PODcast have?
Like 5,000 to 5,000, 6,000 something like that. So not a high priority thing.
In theory, I think the PCP should be next and then TBAP's got like 13k. So that should be that
should be next, right? Yeah, I'm glad that to my knowledge, nobody's been like uploading
shit or fucking around with that one other than changing the description to some weird
cryptic Russian shit. I would feel so violated if the stuff that was going on on these other
channels were happening on TBAP. I would be I would feel I would be sick. Well, now's a great
time to mention what is happening right now on CanTent, which is legitimately fascinating.
As Digi pointed out on Twitter, and I had also noticed that on CanTent right now,
let me I'll link you guys to the channel down below, we do not have control. The last two,
no, I think three videos now, what they are, are re-edits of me and Digi's old
Eremaga Sensei podcast. That's correct, Gib. They have specifically re-edited the full content
and made new thumbnails and new titles for them. We have never given them. Someone's working on
this shit. What's crazy is they're doing a good job. It's not a bad job. Yeah, better than us.
They took the episodes. I think what they did is they downloaded the ones that are on After Dark
because they're uploaded as individual episodes with the images. They used the same images that
were in the After Dark uploads, but then they add an episode one big splash on it. And then the
thumbnails, they cut together three different screen caps from the episode, it seems like,
and bleed them together. Which is your style of editing on CanTent now. It looks like shit the
way they do it, but it also is good. I look at it and I go, that looks like shit, but I bet
everybody would click on that. It's like a missing connection. I would never do, but I'm aware that
people who watch the video won't give a shit and will click on it anyway. They're doing a better
job because they're more cutthroat. The titles and descriptions and everything are like,
they use the actual titles of the episodes, which what they're probably trying to do,
and this might work, is so one of the problems we've had on the PCP channel and on DigiBro is
the Ghibli cast has a shit ton of views, but it's because somebody has taken them and plugged them
in on some like watch cartoon online website as the movies because they're about the same length.
They have the titles of the movie and the date, the year, which I think is really what makes them
think it's real. All of them have like 60% dislikes and just tons of angry comments that it's not
the movie, which is annoying and probably not good, healthy for the video, but I wonder if that's
what they're going for, which also happened to Rixity Minutes. Every episode had the same problem.
It's too bad. That's too bad. I'm really excited guys because let me see. Tonight at 7 p.m. I'm
really excited because Aramunga Sensei Anime Discussed Season 1 Episode 4 premieres on the
content channel. I'm really excited to watch that and see what these guys have to say.
By the way, these all have like hundreds of views. What are they doing in the video edit wise?
Are they just like cutting bits or moving things around? They just loop a gif over the video mostly
and just let our audio play. Looking at the first episode, it's just the exact same one image that
I had. Oh wait, Episode 2? Yeah, they do loop a gif the whole time. That's even more advanced.
What the fuck? Is it? This is advanced. I like how it works.
They literally improved it. I know.
On whatever black market, as what I was thinking, the black market of YouTube sites, we could just
buy free subs, you can buy YouTube channels from Russian hackers. Somebody who knows,
who Canton or Digibro or Nate is, was on this site and would be like, what,
Canton? Yeah, I'll buy it. And they know a little bit about something.
Did you mention the original title that it was premiered with?
Whoa. When the first re-upload went up and premiered, it was called He-He-It's-Dakanton, right?
Oh, okay. Well, that's because that's the default title on the channel, so that's not...
That's like a... They just haven't fixed it yet.
That makes a little more sense and it's slightly less creepy.
It's weird. I don't know why would anyone use a channel? I guess they just hope for...
I mean, this channel has been moved to some thieves' Google account,
and they are now earning all the ad revenue generated by all videos on the channel.
I just wonder if there's some troll who knows what they have.
Someone knows something about how this works.
Well, whether it just so happens to be someone who knows a little bit about anime YouTube videos
enough to edit and re-upload the same thing.
If they know about anime YouTube videos, they must know who Digibro is.
Very likely. It's all very curious and I don't understand.
I got to say, my favorite thing about this is that the thumbnails themselves,
they made thumbnails, they added more images.
I got to say, they're doing a good job with the thumbnails.
They are shitty, but they're clickable shitty.
Shout out to Brad Garlinghouse.
A cutthroat businessman. I've got a lot to learn.
I'm learning a lot here.
Here's what I want to know, because again, these videos, these re-uploads,
are getting pretty good views.
For our channel, not bad.
Probably a lot of its curiosity clicks just like, what the fuck?
Maybe some people sincerely haven't listened to it and are listening to it for the first time.
I want to know what the sub count looks like, because they hide that shit when they take over
your channel.
Yeah, we might be gaining from them sometimes.
It would be so fucking funny.
That would be fascinating.
This is a new channel with you and me, so there's definitely growing going on in general.
But I mean, the upload rate is basically every half a day.
They're posting another episode.
It is our content.
It's good content.
They're marketing it well.
I just don't know if this would even cost us any subscribers.
The only thing it's costing us right now, if we never get the channel back, that's bad.
If we get it back even now, we'll have lost some ad revenue.
But we gained some subs.
I mean, hey, I'll call that one a wash, I guess, a month of ad revenue loss.
I mean, we weren't posting videos on the channel, so if any...
I mean, we were going to post the Pat LeBour, Pat Labor video on there.
I'm saying we can't post anything there right now.
So at least they're posting for us.
Oh, so they're helping.
Right, right.
They're keeping the algorithm happy.
My favorite thing is that they've kept the can-tent logo,
like editing scheme for thumbnails that we were doing, the KH.
But because no one except you and I has access to the can-tent logo without the background,
they've shittily cropped out the edges from our channel logo and slapped.
You can see that a lower editing skill level is making these,
but this is absolutely fascinating what's going on in this channel.
Please give it back, though, YouTube.
I'm dying here.
We just only got the channel up and running and actually making some money and then this shit.
We are up to $20,182 on the Kickstarter.
It just keeps going.
It just keeps charging along.
44 hours to go.
We did it.
Yeah.
That's the meme this episode.
We're doing it.
At this very moment.
Man, Wrecked Hunt 4 is going to be so fucking cool.
It's going to be a great time.
It's going to be so lit.
Holy shit.
Oh, lit.
I'm excited.
It's going to be the shit.
I got the fucking anime wig in the mail the other day.
Oh, you did?
Do you want to tell us what any details?
Because I'm fascinated.
I'm going to save mine for the video when it comes out, I think,
but I'm curious about everybody else.
All right, it's just a long black girl hair wig for cosplay and you just put it on.
But it made, it was like, huh, this is sort of, this is sort of punk like,
you know, I could almost pass myself off as punk.
So I was thinking of buying clothes.
Kind of like in Radcon, The Road to Radcon 3 Chapter 3.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
And I was looking at myself in the mirror with this fucking punk wig on my head.
And I was like, hmm, this feels right.
I have a very masculine jawline.
I've just realized.
You do.
That's true.
In my, in my head, like putting on a wig would make me look like a girl.
And then that would be that.
And I would look like a girl on the screen.
It's me, the anime girl.
Yeah.
But instead I looked like a 70s rocker.
And I was like, oh, well, that's still cool, I suppose.
And it's on special way.
So you guys, have you all listened to The Road to Radcon 4?
I have listened, yes.
I have not gotten around to listening to any of The Road to Radcon.
I'm sorry.
Go men aside.
Yeah, I just haven't finished it yet.
I want to know everybody's perspective on how you feel about your portrayal in the story.
Oh, great.
Yeah, let's talk about that.
All right.
I love ripped jacked punk.
I hope so.
Ripped, ripped jacked punk.
Oh, ripped jacked punk is so, I mean, as soon as I saw the thumbnail, I was like, oh.
Oh, no, what is this?
And it just got, it was cropped at like the abs.
When you click on the video, you can see the abs.
And they're just like, it's like a fucking accordion.
Well, it says she still has the stick legs of normal punk.
But yes, they just connect straight to the abs.
So, or he, I should say, because it's you.
You are jacked punk.
I am jacked punk with J-Pump tits.
Yes.
The little bit of boob popping out below the shirt is by a.
They got under boob.
Yeah, under boob.
There is massive under boob going on.
Are those two pumpkins in there?
That's gotta be what's going on.
That's hilarious.
Two, three, three more.
I think jacked pump and also the even more so possibly the
illustration of Ben in episode two are my two favorite things
I've ever drawn in my whole life.
Oh, yeah.
I would put them both on t-shirts.
Absolutely.
I want people to draw a fan art of jacked punk.
I think that like, I mean, punk is a very easy to draw sort of face.
So it sort of works well.
Oh, you know what I'm saying already.
I'm very upset about my portrayal in this image.
You are vaping from the exhaust pipe of the of the Gravedigger monster truck.
I thought it was like, yeah, hooked up a hose to the to the tail.
You reside at the bottom of a basically the Goron city from Ocarina of Time,
except that it's full of antifa and smoke from your vape.
And that's basically cop kill town is what you describe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Regarding my portrayal in the second part of chapter two,
to me, now I hate that I don't mean to overstate the case,
but I really feel like you were like, I did all the work with Ben.
Let's just get this Nate part done and move on to.
Well, have you heard part three yet?
I did not finish part three yet.
When you get to parts three and four, you'll truly appreciate what I have done with you.
Because the joke is that you are a shockingly accurate portrayal of you.
All the commenters agree that my Nate is spot on,
because everybody else is over the top and ridiculous.
I was crying for personality.
I'm like, I'm so boring in this, but if that is the joke.
The joke is that nothing has changed about you.
You are exactly the same.
And you are so predictable that I can write you to a level of accuracy that is
makes it feel weird even for me.
Did she knows you better than you know yourself?
But yeah, you're kind of like the main character,
because Brad fucked you over.
So you get a lot of dialogue in parts three and four.
Well, shit, I gotta get to it.
There's a lot of Ben and Nate back and forth banter, especially in chapter four.
I really tried to capture the feel of the PCP anytime there's a conversation.
I wanted it to feel like you are listening to an episode.
Yeah, I can get that a lot.
Never mind, I'm not listening to this.
I mean, I'll just read the record.
I loved the description.
I mean, your start at the beginning, Digi, of being a broken,
basically like a hollow from Undertale.
From doing too much.
Just being a waste rule of a man,
but some precious passerby just bringing the essence of life,
that piss that went straight into your mouth and revived you from the grave.
Munchy's piss is what literally I've been living on for God knows how long.
Munchy's piss and crack, which in chapter four,
you will learn the truth about the crack,
the true nature of Digi Bro's crack addiction, and what it really is.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
What could it mean?
Now we've got all the five parts, the whole thing, it's all funded.
Yeah, five is funded, so I gotta make the epic finale.
It's gonna have to be, I mean, these are part five,
I don't have to rush it because it's already done.
So like, it's not advertising the Kickstarter anymore,
but it'll probably be a lot longer.
I was so sure we would not hit 20k.
Yeah, let's talk about that for a second.
I was positive it was like a complete pie in the sky.
Like, this is a promise that will never have to be.
We thought 10k might have been unreachable at the very beginning.
I was pretty confident we had 10k.
But like, once the really good start happened, and then it sort of slowed down,
there was a lot of talk of like, at this rate, at this rate,
we're not gonna get to 20k or anything like that.
And I was like, yeah, but there's always a bump.
There's always a bump near the end.
There is always a bump, but it's not always-
There's always people, there's definitely people
who are like holding off on getting a paycheck.
It's not like doom and gloom just because it's at a certain rate,
because the rate changes every day.
I've heard tales around that there is at least one person
who I believe is planning to donate $1,000 to this day.
I don't know that for sure, but that's what I heard, Taylor.
That would be crazy.
Listener, that could be you.
It could be all of you.
It could be you every day.
You can do that any time you want.
You don't have to wait for a paycheck later.
That's true.
Just go to $70,000, please.
I mean, this is in the past now, so we won't know the final total that they will.
Well, that's true, that's true.
After the tragedy of having one more thousand boys
drop down- It's never too late to send us money.
Somebody actually has one time sent me $1,000.
That has happened before, so that was pretty sick.
That's pretty sick.
Disgusting.
The clothes, I mean-
It's disgusting because it happened to you and not me.
Exactly.
Arthur Mus gave me the Cintiq that he had liner,
which is probably valued at $1,000 plus.
It is, yeah.
Closest enough.
That's sick.
That's great.
$800 something.
Let me just review real quick.
All the things that's going to come to you.
So people have pledged, you get pins.
I mean, I know I've said it a million times,
I've got my Rad Country pin.
The pin brings me probably more joy,
like my shirts are in the closet.
I wear them all the time, sporadically, they give me joy.
Every day I sit down at my computer,
I look over in my purple and blue
Rad Country pin on the starry background,
and it just makes me happy.
It sparks joy is what it does.
I don't know if everybody else feels the same way,
but it does for me.
I have no purpose for pins,
so I don't know where to be tomorrow.
Well, in this case,
I kind of just have a little spot
on my printer to my right,
where I have my Puba pin,
my Rad Country pin,
and my little Slime Corp logo pins.
It's just my pin spot, I guess.
There's not on anything.
Michelle is hers on her bag or whatever.
But I'm not losing these,
I just want them to be there and make me happy.
But I mean, I've got walls here.
You're going to get a poster
if you pledge to a certain degree.
I'm going to slap down on my wall as well.
That will also spark joy.
And you know what, I'm just thinking now
about the fan arch that we're likely to get
from this OVA at some point.
It's going to be nuts.
Oh, hell yeah.
Like, remember Nexus's amazing art of us
like during the...
Yes, yes.
That was the fucking sickest shit,
and there will likely be more.
Holy shit, I can't wait.
I mean, what do we got?
We got all the lectures are coming.
We've got the fucking shirts and the PTA.
The rumble is happening.
The Tiki Bar, the OVA,
which we're packing so many fucking ideas in this OVA.
Have we explained what the idea for the Tiki Bar is?
We have explained.
Well, we definitely did in the Kickstarter video.
If you want to restate it, feel free.
It's just going to have drinks.
The general idea is like certain streams that we do
will be controlled by the PTA members, I think,
just them or just people in the chat.
Well, we can give the PTA...
You get people to drink on stream for various reasons.
My thought is that we can give the PTA
amount of control, but it should be open to the public.
And anyone at any time in the YouTube chat or whatever
will be able to...
If you donate...
There will be a menu.
Probably put a menu on screen.
If you donate an amount for a drink
and specify who has to drink, you can buy drinks for us
and force us to drink.
And I think that probably there should be some...
If someone's like, I can't drink anymore,
I'm going to die or I'm going to throw up or I'm too drunk,
you can tap out.
But maybe there'll be some kind of like penalty
associated with it.
I think that'd be funny.
Okay, I don't know what that would be exactly.
I don't know how legal that is, but...
Well, we're all...
Well, I mean, you can't make munchy drink.
Well, you also...
I don't know if you can legally pay someone to drink.
Like, can you...
I mean, you're buying the drink?
I don't know.
Well, if you have the option to...
If you have the option...
That's what I'm saying.
It's like...
If you have the option to say no.
You have the option to say no and then we kick your ass.
I don't know.
Or we throw you into the sea.
Just kick my ass right now.
I'm going to destroy that.
Yeah.
Oh, of course, it's the calendar, the Brad lecture.
Brad's going to be the diss track that we will have to start working on imminently.
And then the music video that we will produce.
I mean, we got to get the song out, I guess, before Radcon,
so that we can make the music video at Radcon.
And so we'll be working on that.
And the fucking light novel, funded, physical release,
coming to all 100 and plus backers.
So I hope that you made it in time.
That's going to be that.
Maybe we'll fucking sell copies after separately or something.
If people want them.
If they want them.
We could easily just sell it like through Amazon.
Like the Amazon printing service or whatever it is that you ever requested.
Yeah, god.
I really love internet creators with physical products that they're selling.
Not like t-shirts and stuff, but like, you know, comics, books.
It's fucking sick, dude.
Things that you could put on your bookshelf and say that came from an internet guy
that would otherwise not exist because it's hard to get published.
It makes it feel real so that mom and dad can finally get it after all.
I definitely want to get the Digi's light novel
and the Rotoradcon novel when I have those for real.
I have no idea what the Rotoradcon is going to look like,
because it's not long.
So I don't know if it's going to be like a pamphlet or...
It'll be a little thing.
It's short and sweet.
Like Common Sense by Thomas Paine.
We will secede from the union and become our own nation at Rotoradcon for Paradise.
It's just a bad time.
All right.
Did we say, was there like an agreement that Tom would do like the artwork if...
For what?
He did say he would do that, yeah.
Yeah, so you'll have to draw Jacked Punk.
That's really funny.
Yes.
I mean, I don't know if he's, it's exclusively going to redo the art that I've done
or do original art for it.
I have no idea.
We probably need some more art.
I don't know.
I don't know how it's going to work.
Whatever.
We can figure it out.
We got, we got options here.
And we've got money to do things with to make it nice.
Oh my God.
Imagine that.
Oh, by the way, we're at $20,294.
It went up again.
Oh my God.
This is like the, this is like the, the, the, remember the first time we recorded the podcast
after we launched the kicks.
Oh yeah, that's right.
During the stream, we were like, oh, we're up another 100.
Oh, we're up another 200.
Holy shit.
By the way, we are, we are, we might pass.
I was worried because for a while, like even though we exceeded the amount raised in the first one,
the number of backers was actually trailing behind the first one.
We had fewer for a while, but now we're catching up.
We had 308 the first time now.
That's right.
We're up to 291, do 292.
So yeah, we might end up with at least as many backers.
It would make me very happy to break the number of backers, just to feel like,
hooray, our audience has grown, even though like we are charging more.
I really think, yeah, the fact that we made it with literally like less backers,
more than twice as much money.
It must mean that people really liked Radcon 3.
Like, it was such a triumph.
We did everything we promised and they were all pretty great.
I mean, it's kind of like, it's hard to understand when it's, when it actually happens,
because like you do the Radcon and none of the videos get more than 5000 views.
And they, you know, some of them take an eternity to come out and the response is like,
it's a positive response.
But when you just see like, you know, one day worth of comments and they're just kind of like,
good job guys.
It's just like, all right, well, there it is.
The Radcon 3, the arena video that I slaved over with all the different GoPro footage things.
And like, we go around shooting each other.
It was really fun, really cool.
It's an amazing video.
Legitimately.
It didn't get much of a response though.
It's just sort of like, yeah, cool.
Oh, yeah.
It's like, yeah.
I mean, look at them, like we've got a few thousand views, like, all right.
The numbers don't lie when it comes to the Kickstarter.
You know, clearly those few people were into it.
You know what's interesting?
Like during this Kickstarter, I also noticed, maybe you guys know this as well,
that like another Kickstarter launched during this time.
The Matthew Matosis just made a video about, which is the Wonderful 101.
And that's already, I think it's shot past, but at a $1.5 million already.
And they were looking for like 90,000 to just make it happen or like 100,000 or something.
But then they had all these crazy tiers above that, some of which were like,
if they got like 2 million, then Hideki Kamiya will clear his block list on Twitter.
And you know, like, by the way, the lower tier was like, if you pledge like $100,
whatever, he will block you on Twitter.
That's like one of the rewards.
So like they're working the memes, which I respect in a big way.
Yeah.
But like that product, I think, has far more like, okay, they'll be making a game
that everyone can buy and everyone can play.
Whereas like with our thing, it's a different animal,
which I think just inherently has this like niche community.
Like people are high pledgers, are pledging to be like part of the experience
by being in the PTA to like shape and like the dark, the fucking dark PTA guys who are
going to help make like a fighter.
And then of course the thousand boys who are going to be in the Royal Rumble,
like personally or whatever.
That's a very different experience, I think, than just like, I don't know,
helping a game exist.
And sure you'll get a copy, but that you'd have to buy otherwise.
I think that there's two reasons that contributed to the high like average
pledge amount.
One, yes, people really loved Rad Country and like the people that were into it were
happy with the results and are looking for more of that.
Imagine your audience was just bigger with the same level of passion.
Ooh, that's a recipe for money right there.
Well, the other thing is that like.
It would require the PCP to be good at any time other than Rad Country.
Damn, you're right.
You're right about that.
The other thing I think is real is that like it's two years later.
Probably a lot of our audience has aged by two years and like probably a lot of them
that were like in college before are now like working.
Like a lot of the audience has probably grown by two years, aged up from like college
and entered the workforce or whatever.
Probably just a lot of them just have more money now.
Now that they have those precious Yang Bucks.
Now a lot of them probably have disposable income that didn't have it before.
That's an interesting thought.
Yeah.
Maybe some of them have just been saving with anticipation of Rad Country eventually.
I don't know if I would flatter myself to think that these people have been saving up for two years
for the specific purpose.
Well, we also think.
Fair enough.
But they've probably been getting their shit in order at least to some of them.
Audience, I'm proud of you.
I'm proud of you that you've got your shit well enough in line to back Rad Country for.
Even proud a little bit of that guy at the beginning who pledged a thousand dollars
and had to drop down because he just like realized he was too much money.
You know, it's unfortunate that to us that looked like a dip.
But that's just life.
Good for you.
He provided a valuable service of getting people hype about it succeeding easily.
That's true.
In a way, it helped because it was like seed money.
Now we're.
Some Kickstarter's will launch and then the creator will just like put like
a hundred or a thousand dollars into the project at the very beginning as like seed money.
And not to mention when he pulled that, we then got to play the victim card in a big way.
And it was wonderful.
I love it every time.
I didn't phrase the tweet to sound like too victimized.
But more like, oh, we've had a little setback, but we can.
But we're still going to make it.
And hey, look at this.
We fucking did.
Take a look at this.
Okay.
Take a look at what?
Are you linking something?
No.
Oh, it's just recording Resident Evil.
Well, that's how I feel.
We should do like a spooky mansion rad con one of these days, you know.
I think the next rad con should be we should do it next summer and it should be Christmas or like
snow themed in the summer.
Why do you think what do you think would be in like a new a Christmas themed?
I mean, I want to bring up again the idea I had for of us doing like a cabin.
Out in the mountains and rad conning from a cabin doable.
Also, let me just throw this at you, everybody.
We talked about this amount of money.
There is a 100% chance we could find a reasonably priced air and be and get tickets to somewhere
like, oh, I don't know, Tokyo, Japan and do one there.
That is possible.
That is 100% to go to the no question.
Like we have to consider now like we have to level up our understanding of what we're capable of.
Part of what why I thought we could reach 20k with this Kickstarter was that Ben's
Vapors 2 Kickstarter made so much money because Vapors 2 I think made more than twice what
Vapors 1 did as well, right?
Something like that.
When I had seen that and it was more than the it made more than rad con 3, right?
Yes, it did.
Redcon 3 made $9,000.
Redcon 2 made exactly $12,000.
So, yeah, like when I was looking at not pure not pure profit, by the way,
that's just the number.
When I was looking at how much the Vapors had made, I was like, well,
like Ben's making this much off of this like relatively obscure comic.
Part of it is a lot of it is the promotion and the stretch goals and the fact that you
created this like sort of meta narrative with the continuing stretch goals,
just like giving people something to do essentially.
And I was like, yeah, this kind of seems like representing like the full potential.
If Ben were to go all out on something like on a project,
what's the most money he could make on that?
And that felt like it represented that.
And so I looked at it and I said, okay, well, I know that my audience is way
the fuck bigger than Ben.
So like if I did something with this level of push,
it should be able to get even bigger numbers.
And like I never promoted Redcon 3 at all,
because I was just like lost in a whole other world while Redcon 3 was being planned.
But with this one, I was just like, as soon as I throw my hat in,
I know it will do something to bump this.
And since it already hit the goal right away in the first couple of days at first,
I was like, well, maybe I don't have to do anything.
And then I was like, well, like I looked over the numbers and I was like,
nobody wrote in, we get paid.
Nobody wrote that in.
How did that happen?
How did I not notice?
It was there for a bit.
And then we like with like anxiety of not getting that amount.
But we didn't want to ask for too much for the initial.
So we said, okay, what is completely necessary?
And we here's the dirty secret.
And the getting extra like paid for the time we were spending was like something we cut.
Here's the dirty secret that I would never have admitted until that had been funded.
And now you can't take your money back.
So you can't know that we made a bad business decision,
which was because we were so jazzed to it.
We committed our plane flights and the money to getting the Airbnb.
So if we hadn't done it, we would have been purely out of pocket.
So we had to make sure we hit that goal by any means necessary.
If they had launched the Kickstarter and it had made zero dollars,
we would be like three or like five grand in the hole.
Yeah.
It wasn't like a stupid.
That will never happen again.
I will never do that again.
It wasn't a stupid idea to buy the Airbnb early.
Because we were worried that, you know,
there's only so many Airbnbs that completely fit the criteria.
If we didn't put the money down, we would have lost it or not gotten it.
And then everything would have been ruined anyway.
So we had to get that first.
Not to fearmonger.
But like when we did RFCConK the last time, we had the B&B.
Munchy had the B&B all sorted out.
And then the guy just canceled like the day before.
Well, okay.
So I guess I sure hope that doesn't happen.
Surely you've got your money back at least, right?
Yeah.
But then we had 24 hours to scramble to find a new place.
You know what?
We'll roll with it.
We'll figure it out.
But I mean, we can't control for such a thing.
There's nothing we can do to prevent it.
This is like a business and they seem to know their shit.
So I'm pretty confident.
But nonetheless, nonetheless, always a fear to be...
Like, you see, that's the thing.
Terrifying.
But like the fact that we've now...
I mean, I'm much more worried about the fact that
what if the coronavirus airport,
yeah, what if they don't let given come into the country
by the time this happens?
They'll just scan me.
I'm not that worried about that.
They'll scan me like, are you gay?
No.
If he was coming from China, I'd be a little worried.
Are there any coronavirus reports from the UK?
There's...
Yeah, there's like one in all the countries.
There's eight confirmed cases.
No one's serious.
I was probably higher than that by now.
It's the last time I checked.
I know China is a big place,
but I know that Econ was planning to go to China.
Is that happen or...
That has not happened yet and I don't think it will.
Unless they open the country back up by then.
I was gonna say, isn't half of China in quarantine mode?
Yes, most of it is locked down
to the point that they're not allowed to leave their houses
and they got drones yelling at old ladies in the street to go home.
It's fucking hilarious and crazy.
That does sound really funny.
They're also mass burning bodies somewhere in the...
Yeah, that's right.
Somewhere out in the fields.
But yeah, China's a mad house right now.
I don't know if Econ will be able to go by, you know,
if it'll be reopened by the time he's gonna leave,
but he had said something about coming to Radcon 4.
Oh yeah, right, right.
I was having some interest in that,
so I assume he was gonna leave after that.
I'll give you one hour of our time, Econ.
That's how much I'll budget.
Then you have to be out the door.
Maybe we could invite Christian at the same time.
That sounds like a great idea.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Econ and Christian would...
My two favorite people.
They would really play off each other.
They would have great chemistry together.
I'm sure Econ would be interested in meeting Chris Chan, right?
I suppose that's true.
The funny thing is that meeting Chris is not that interesting.
She doesn't like...
Well, I mean, what do you expect?
She doesn't do anything.
Yeah, she doesn't...
She's funny to think about,
and she says funny stuff online,
but she doesn't do anything interesting in person.
It's just what you're describing.
It's like you're describing a toy that you bought
that's not that interesting.
Yeah, I brought it home,
but it's just like it doesn't really do anything.
It's just kind of looks funny.
It's like you go to the zoo,
and you're like, oh, I want to see the lions,
but then you go to the...
And there's just one,
and it's sitting there behind the bush,
and you tap on the glass, and you're like, hey, move.
It doesn't hold anything.
It doesn't live up to the shape.
But it just doesn't.
But it means about the stories that are told.
It's about the experiences.
A lot of it's been mythologized,
like the man in the pickle suit and whatnot.
That event was probably less entertaining
to see as it is to think about and just mull over.
I don't know.
A full-on pickle man costume?
I mean, it sounds pretty spectacular.
It's full of that one, maybe.
But like Chris probably didn't do it.
Chris probably just kind of froze up
and stood there in confusion.
Yeah, I would probably do the same to be fair, but yeah.
It reminds me of lectures.
I was thinking about doing a lecture or two or something,
and I was racking my brain trying to think,
what do I know that's also like a lectureable subject?
And I kind of came to the conclusion that
in order to make it a lectureable subject,
I would need to do an amount of research
that is essentially, I don't, you know.
That's kind of where I'm at.
I would need to do so much more research
than what is already in my brain.
And if it's not in my brain,
it's going to be a fucking nightmare.
And I kind of don't want to bother.
Let me give you an example of something.
Yesterday in my stream,
this is why I was the right man
to do the Kingdom Hearts lecture.
And it is because when I was playing Kingdom Hearts,
or I was doing my stream,
I was talking about my experience
of playing through the new Kingdom Hearts III DLC,
I went on a rant about something
that deeply offended me in Kingdom Hearts III's DLC.
And it's that, oh, these so-called scholars,
that, oh, they've got all this lore.
They know everything about the series.
They're such geniuses making this DLC
that is literally just a canon retcon
because they fucked up the story the first time
and they had to fix it with DLC.
These geniuses, such as Nomura,
in Kingdom Hearts III,
there's a section in the DLC
you can play as Roxas briefly.
And what they did was they gave Roxas
the special power from Kingdom Hearts II called reversal.
But here's the thing,
reversal was a reaction command in Kingdom Hearts II,
emphasis on the word reaction.
Because in that game,
reaction commands relate to the specific enemy
you are fighting,
not the character you are fucking playing
as, you idiot Nomura.
And so what he does is he makes it
so that when you play as Roxas,
you can use this reversal power,
which puts you behind the enemy.
It kind of swoos around behind him.
But the problem is, in Kingdom Hearts II,
you could do it to Dusks, to Xemnas,
and I believe the Twilight Thorn as well.
Those were the only enemies
with the reversal reaction command.
And in Kingdom Hearts III,
they act like it was an intrinsic power that Roxas had
and you could use it on enemies like Luxord
and Larzin, which you could never do it.
And it shows a fundamental misunderstanding
of what a reaction command is
and what the fucking reversal power is.
And that kind of knowledge.
And even Keyblade Spirit says,
wow, Nate, even I'm not this autistic about Kingdom Hearts.
That's why I'm the right man for the job
to do that lecture.
It's like, I don't have,
maybe I do,
but I don't have anything that,
like I could really make a big old lecture about
that would also be an interesting topping
that anyone would want to listen to.
I feel you.
That's where I'm stuck because...
I've got very few things to be fair.
My first idea was,
I wanted to talk about the five album narrative
of the Coheed and Cambria albums.
And there's a ton of comics
and supplementary material to read,
to study for that that I haven't read.
But like, I thought about it and I was like,
well, the main appeal of explaining
the Coheed album narrative would be
that I could say like,
all right, this song, this is what it's about.
You know, like this song that you've heard
and you know, here's what it's about.
But no, I don't think anybody in the PCP
listens to Coheed and Cambria at all.
So it'd be me lecturing you guys and being like,
okay, well, when he says this lyric,
it's like, you don't know what the fuck I'm talking about.
So I was like, maybe that's not such a good idea
for this context.
It could be because I knew nothing about guilty gear
and Tom's lecture was engaging just for the...
It was good.
For the things he was explaining as he went.
The thing about it is that like,
you know, the actual...
It's that the actual experience of the Coheed and Cambria albums
is not the same as the story.
And so what makes the story interesting as a deep dive
is that you can have a different experience than the albums.
So like, you won't get a sense of what this music sounds like
or what the actual lyrics are or...
No doubt, no doubt.
Any of that if I just tell you the story.
And the story isn't inherently interesting.
It's interesting that this story is being told
in this incredibly bizarre way through these lyrics and music.
You know?
Yeah, you're right.
That doesn't sound like a great format for...
It has to be a wacky, crazy story told in a wacky, crazy way.
Yeah, I mean, the story is...
That's what made the Guilty Gear lecture,
because like, yeah, the story of Guilty Gear
is not analogous to playing the games,
but it is just weird in its own right.
The story of the Cohed Albums is also insane.
It's completely fucked up.
Oh, well, sure.
Okay, then fair enough.
So it would be entertaining in that sense,
but like, to me, the intrigue of the story is like,
you hear these lyrics that mean ostensibly nothing,
and then you look into them,
and it's like this massive sci-fi fucking war story,
and you're like, what the fuck?
Like, this is what you were talking about.
This seems like it would be best told in like,
YouTube video format to me, where you clip.
This reminds me of, okay.
I think it would be a good lecture.
It just would have to be in front of people
who know the music.
I might be exposing my ignorance here,
because I don't know anything about K-Pop,
except that I see it on Twitter all the fucking time,
and I'll be looking at a seemingly normal thread,
and then suddenly K-Pop gifts start getting posted,
and I check out because I'm like,
I'm not gonna understand anything that's being said from now on.
When I posted about how my grandma just died,
and that guy replied with,
should've stand Bu Jung Po, or whatever,
I was like, I mean, fair enough,
she did not stand that guy.
Maybe that would've done it, as they usually post.
I don't know why, but I clicked on the Wikipedia article
for BTS the other day,
and apparently they also have like,
a alternate reality storyline going on.
Okay, that sounds kind of interesting.
There's tons and tons of stuff
that I think would fit the lecture format well.
It's just like a matter of,
will this be interesting to people
who don't know what it is already?
And in the case of Coheed, I think it could be,
there's an entertaining lecture
that could be done just about the story,
but it would not be as interesting
as comparing it to the lyrics
and being able to mind expansion people who know them.
The other idea I had, and the problem with this one
is it would require even more research on my part,
but it wouldn't be too hard to do, is Toho.
Oh, that's a great idea.
Great idea.
That is a good one, yeah.
But the problem with Toho is that there's not really
a ton of official narrative that's that interesting
to dive into.
Mostly it's about the characters,
and I mean, there are a ton of official stories
and weird details about them,
but it would be like, when it comes to the fan content,
it's like there's nowhere to start.
It's endless.
There's more fan content for Toho
than anything else on the planet.
So yeah, I don't know.
I think someone could work in,
someone could definitely make a good Toho lecture
that would probably be skeleton around.
You go through the games from start to finish.
You talk about Zune's life and stuff,
and then as relevant characters come up,
you just tell anecdotes about what this character has done.
That one seems like a really, really strong idea for a lecture.
Yes.
The only problem with it is that I have no fucking idea
about Toho lecture, and I'm in these circles personally.
That's just guilty gear.
Everybody knows it, but probably how many people
actually know what the fuck it's about.
And here's the thing.
When it comes to these lectures,
I like when we do them about these super autistic things
because most of their fans can't explain that all.
True.
They're so into it that they don't know
how to communicate about it,
and if you go to Toho panels at Otacon or something,
they're fucking incomprehensible.
Even for me, with a surface-level understanding,
because the people at them know everything,
it's just constant references and obscure left hooks
and just rambling, incoherent,
nonsense and shouting about the characters.
Just a bunch of people who are really excited about Toho
spurring the fuck out about Toho.
And there's no way to get a grasp
on what the hell you're experiencing in that context.
Yeah.
And even if you do know Toho, for someone like me,
and this is why I would have to do a lot of research to do it,
there's always new games and new characters coming out.
So like most people probably know the main characters
from like Imperishable Knight.
From Reimu's upcoming inclusion in Super Smash Brothers
and the new DLC pack, that's going to be the one.
But like there's just fucking hundreds of characters,
you know, there's so many to go through
and so many side stories and manga and all that extra shit.
So I don't know.
Monkey's Pod choice.
All right, you get your PCP lecture about Toho,
ladies and gentlemen, listening at home,
but it's done by a man who I know could do it,
who has the skills, Econ.
Guest lecture from Econ about Toho.
I honestly don't even think Econ would be willing to
because of how much research he would think he would have to do.
I think he has the knowledge to do it,
but I mean, no, he's not going to do it.
He wouldn't, unlike, the reason that,
okay, this is why I'm so worried about me doing it,
is that like there is a standard of research
that I would approach it with,
which is enough to tell somebody who doesn't know about Toho
as much as they need to know to become interested.
Anybody who already knows about Toho will look at me and say,
you motherfucker, you got this wrong, this wrong,
you didn't go into this,
like there's all these extra details you could have talked about.
Toho is exactly that kind of community.
It's exactly that kind of community.
They're extremely hardcore, they're very opinionated.
So like, that's scary.
If you started something like that,
that's a very real possibility,
but if you started with, like, this is designed to be,
look, this is Toho 101.
It doesn't matter if you say that.
If we get the 50,000 Kickstarter, we'll do Toho 102,
and that's the advanced course.
I would probably keep it to just official canon.
That would be the easiest way to have...
Honestly, dude, the best way to get the most views,
you have like an hour long, maybe two hour long lecture on Toho,
and you include shit like,
why is Chirono associated with Nine?
Why is she a baka?
And then you'll explain that kind of shit.
That's all the stuff, yeah.
Basically what I would probably do is go through each game,
explain each character,
all the like, most famous lore pieces
and where they came from about those characters
that are like, tied to the actual narrative.
That's a million view video right there is what that is.
Somebody making that, I think.
If the Christian, well, maybe 500,000, I don't know,
but that one's got legs.
That one's got legs.
I might do it, but that's probably the best idea I've had
other than the co-heed lectures so far.
So, and I'm also curious if anybody listening
or if any of you guys just has ideas for things
that you know I know about that you would want to lecture.
What spawned this whole lecture series
was literally that Ben would just tell stories
about Christian all the time.
And I said, you need to lecture us about,
I really want you to just sit us down
and like blackpill me on Christian
because I don't know enough to have context
for what the hell you're talking about.
So, I don't know, because you do.
So I educated the whole world.
I do talk about a lot of the things that you,
you know, like at length in videos and stuff.
So like, is there really even that much stuff
that you haven't talked about that you could do in a lecture?
It's hard to say because it's hard to know what stuff like,
maybe there's something that I have talked about it,
but not nearly at the depth I could, you know,
or just haven't at all like, there's certain subjects.
I mean, again, like say the co-heed and Cambria album narrative,
like I haven't talked about that.
Well, you know about a lot of music stuff.
I don't know really anything about rap.
What is rap?
Death Grips is not a bad one.
Death Grips, I do have a video about,
and there's not that much to go into
because a lot of their thing is that
they're just very mysterious.
So, you know, they don't have like a,
there's like all the little legendary things
they did at the start of their career,
but at this point, they basically just,
every year a new album drops out of nowhere
and you go, oh shit, new Death Grips.
You know, this would be redundant
because I actually just watched a video about it,
but it does strike me as a story
that would work well for the formula,
which is just the life and times of one John McAfee
and all the adventures that he's been up to.
I mean, that's a perfect story.
I want to watch a video about it.
I watched that four part by that one dude
who interviewed him after it was done.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know his name, Michelle pulled it up for me,
but I mean, it was really funny.
And actually that guy clearly was biased against John McAfee.
And the whole time I couldn't help but be like,
you know, John McAfee may be responsible
for a few people dying and stuff,
but like, at least he's not a pussy like you, dude.
At least he's like not a little bitch, you know.
I, McAfee is definitely one of my, one of my heroes.
He's a libertarian God on this earth, no doubt about it.
I will be writing him in on the ballot
if Pete Buttigieg is the pick for the Democratic Party.
It's looking pretty unlikely that Pete's gone.
We don't know about it, we have no idea.
We don't.
Well, like fucking Bloomberg keeps rising in the, in the bedding odds.
Super Tuesday, baby.
He hasn't, he hasn't, he hasn't even been on a single ballot yet.
So like it remains a complete like hypothetical at this point.
Nobody knows.
Is he trying to, so is he running independent or for the DNC?
No, he's running, literal Democrat, Pete Bloomberg
is running as a Democrat.
And then all these people were like, Bernie's not even a,
Bernie's not even a real Democrat.
He hasn't been vetted.
Bloomberg, literal Republican comes in, runs on a Democratic ticket
and everyone's like, yes.
All the media shows are like, yes, let's get behind fucking Bloomberg.
I mean, Bloomberg, the fact that they, they,
he clearly pays people to talk about him.
Like even in the debates, they've brought him up.
Admittedly, admittedly.
Like it was obvious that they had been paid to bring him up
because they like quote him like in a, it was ridiculous.
But how does he, how could he get the Democratic candidacy?
Like who's, he hasn't been voted on anywhere.
Like how does one become this position without participating?
I mean, I think the idea is just to saturate the media
and saturate the mainstream media and the airwaves and commercials
with like Bloomberg propaganda
and then hopefully like win big on Super Tuesday.
I think that's his plan.
Is he even included in the polls that they do?
Like he will be.
Was he in the Iowa pockets at all?
He's waiting for it.
He was.
Well look, like the reason why the early states matter
is because it sets the tone for who's going to win.
But if you can just manufacture good tone
for the upcoming states that truly do matter,
you like theoretically you could bypass it.
It hasn't really been done much,
but it's, you know, in theory it's possible.
And that's what he's banking on, I think.
Although some people think he's not actually trying to win,
but it's just trying to, I don't know, fuck shit up in a good way.
Word is going around that he might name Hillary as his VP.
I heard about that.
Which, yeah.
Oh, what if he then retires?
He then gives up the mantle of president at last.
Retires immediately.
Immediately.
He's like, yeah, Rizan.
That's probably exactly what would happen.
She's going in the back door.
Holy shit.
And even please make it happen, Mike.
I guess now might be a time to briefly mention
that yes, Bernie won New Hampshire.
Very exciting.
If you're hearing this on Friday,
tomorrow, Saturday, is the day of the Nevada caucuses.
So if you're in Nevada, get out and vote for Bernie.
Good night, sweet yang.
Good night.
Do not realign yourself to any other candidate.
If Bernie is unviable, unlikely, but a possibility,
just go home.
I mean, I've been hearing these things
about clobementum going on, though.
And I gotta say, I'm liking what I'm hearing.
The purple shirt.
It is, in fact, clober in time.
Clober in time.
Shout out to Bevan for his incredible image.
Oh, because she looks like the Hulk.
She's tiny.
But she's sturdy, though.
She's stout.
She's sturdily built.
Like a female dwarf.
We're talking about a quivering a little bit.
Yeah.
Yeah, she's always quivering a little bit
on the debate stage.
Sometimes she's just vibrating, like a hummingbird.
That's that clobementum.
She's just raring to go.
She's got to hit gas.
She could barely contain the forward motion.
All right.
Vote for Bernie, everybody.
There you go.
There's the message.
Are we ready to move to voicemails then?
Oh, wait, before we do that,
let's talk about my problematic tweet
where I insinuate that right people don't think.
Okay, sure.
Oh, there is the response to my tweet.
Yeah.
She also tells what it said, first of all.
Great tweet.
My tweet.
All right.
Well, my tweet was a retweet from Rational Disconnect
with a screenshot of a Louder with Crowder video
called Exposed, Buttigieg's leftist extremism, 108K views.
And I said, there is no skill floor for being conservative,
meaning that you can be as dumb and as wrong
and as thoughtless as you want.
And nobody on the right cares
as long as you are appealing to their basic sense of fear
and disgust, and they will eat it up
and you will make a million dollars.
And that was my tweet.
How could someone say something so brave?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Controversial.
Yeah, I have no issue with that.
Certainly.
Yeah.
Within the Rational Disconnect.
But then I follow it up with a thought I had been having,
which is what I say is it literally does seem to be
that the difference between the left and right political
persuasion is the amount of thinking you do.
It's not even that all people on the right are stupid.
They just don't bother thinking about things.
First impressions.
Well, hang on.
Your first tweet was just that first sentence.
No.
All this is...
No, it was the whole...
No, he's still...
This is the tweet.
First impressions and gut reactions are often wrong.
And that was my tweet.
And the...
Oh, did you not read it?
Did you get triggered?
I thought I only saw the first half.
No, I just didn't realize.
Okay, whoops.
Yeah, well, I agree.
You don't...
It's a gut reaction to be a reactionary conservative.
It's like, oh, I don't like this.
Yeah, it's literally the exact same on both sides.
It is kind of the...
Yeah, that was the thing I realized off the board.
All of it is the exact same.
There's no difference at all.
I will admit that you can be a liberal,
that you can be a shit-lib without thinking about anything.
I mean, you just like, oh, Trump's mean online.
You can be good or bad of either.
It is the case.
The left, the real left is data-driven.
The thing that I was trying to get at was...
We love data.
We love facts.
We love logic.
We love rational...
Oh, R-L-Y.
Yes, one hundo.
The thing...
All right, I have been getting really into...
Last time I talked about bread tube and philosophy tube
and country points and stuff, and I've been feeling really left,
really cuck-lib, cuck-loser.
Like, I played Dark Souls 2, and I liked it.
You got to take a little of each medicine.
You got to mix some up.
I watched the ladder with Crowder video.
I watched a full-on ladder with Crowder video.
You don't need to watch Stephen Crowder.
All right, fucking...
Could you let me finish the thing I was saying?
Yeah.
All right, so I've been getting more left, just ideas in my brain
that I didn't have before.
And what I was realizing was that a lot of social justice stuff,
when presented not as stark, raving, mad, crazy, feminist, screeching,
it actually...
Like, a lot of the things make sense.
Things like white privilege that I would have assumed.
Oh, that's complete bullshit, because it's said by people who are crazy.
The people who I see in videos by Thunderfoot and stuff like that.
And I still like Thunderfoot.
I like his videos.
I like the Amazing Atheist.
I like the Razor Fist, the Rageaholic.
But these new ideas, which I previously dismissed out of hand,
it was sort of a revelation to me that I thought this whole time...
I had the same revelation.
I had the same one.
It's so funny to hear you guys say this because of the fact
that I come from this and have moved in the direction of appreciating the other side,
and being like, oh, these guys aren't slobbering morons on this other side.
It really just depends on where you started.
Like, I started with the Amazing Atheist, and he'd made fun of feminists and Christians and all that.
So it's like, this is my default position.
I believed it because I didn't have any reason to doubt it, and I thought it was funny.
And then in the future, there's this conflict, and I choose a side.
And now I realize that there's no point choosing a side.
You're stupid if you stick with the side that you first went into,
instead of exploring the other one with genuine curiosity and open-mindedness.
Because I used to think I was open-minded,
but I would dismiss things that are like, oh, that's stupid.
You know, I've got an open mind, but only if they have a good idea.
But they don't have any good ideas, because I saw them as screeching idiots.
So really, what I was was not open-minded, because I hadn't looked at what they were
actually saying before casting my judgment.
I had believed I was open-minded just because I wasn't, you know,
I assumed that because some of it told me that this is stupid, I was like, yeah,
okay, I get it now.
And I didn't get it.
And it's just a cool to be a person who takes all the pieces and puts them together
and then makes a decision.
I was having a Twitter discussion, I think it was yesterday, about South Park.
Someone made a tweet about the damage to the discourse that South Park had done,
or something, and I agreed with it.
And someone disagreed, and we had a pretty civil discussion about it.
And my point was just that, yeah, I'm pretty sure.
I remember being influenced by media-like, media-like,
centrist media like South Park that says both sides are dumb.
And I didn't mention these, but also like, yeah, like a reaction channel.
It's not centrist to say both sides are dumb.
It is, though.
That's what centrism is.
I feel like we've been over this, but...
We had a whole fucking video, YouTube discussion on it, over on StComics.
What'scentrum.com?
What's centrism?
Maybe I should look into this, this new way of thinking.
It's just that there's, to say that it is center, I don't want to get into it.
That's a good definition.
It's like, oh, left, right?
No, they're both dumb.
Well, yeah, the thing, you know, it's silly and reductive,
but it's kind of unavoidable to contain all of the policies considered left
and considered right and call them one thing, and you are on one side or the other.
Absolutely.
So that's the real issue there.
Someone was talking about, I think Tom said a thing about like gun control,
like two, at least something, something gun control.
And I said, well, I know that gun rights are generally considered a right-wing thing,
but like Marx himself was super high on like that.
You already broke it.
It already makes no sense, right?
Left and right makes no sense.
You don't even have to finish the sentence.
They don't make no sense.
They have a general sense.
They have a logic behind them.
I'm saying that there is, yeah, they're in some issues, there is crossover,
because if you're a hardcore lefty, Marx himself was very pro-gun.
If you find yourself in a position of, I agree with, like half of my stances are left-wing,
and half of them are right-wing, by the way, they're constructed currently.
This somehow makes me a centrist for thinking that people on either extreme are wrong,
even though I'm not in between the two.
I feel strongly one way or another about each issue.
I'm not in the center, you know?
I just think in practice, such a person is like
fantastically unlikely.
There are some issues that I think the figure of.
No, I think that such a person is almost everybody,
and that all of us just make tons of compromises on shit that we're not sure about,
or don't care that much about, because we want the issues we actually care about.
I think that most people are single-topic votes.
I think that if you really have put a lot of introspection into these things,
you will find that you have a tendency in one direction or another.
I think there's a general...
And you might not agree with everyone who shares your tendencies on everything.
The policies that you hold, the things you agree with could be on one side or the other,
and then there's the level to which you are engaged in politics in general.
I feel like people who are like, what's the word for somewhat radical?
If you are radically on the left or the right,
that doesn't necessarily mean that you are with all of these specific policies,
but some of them you are very far on that side.
Let me put it this way.
You can be, to be a centrist, I think is implied that you're not heavily one way
or the other in terms of a political direction that you're trying to go for.
The reason this is so confusing.
The policy is separate, I think.
Okay. It can't be separate, because policy is what defines the parties are.
I guess it can't be separate, but I feel like there maybe is a trend.
I don't have a position on what centrism is. I'm just trying to figure it out.
Well, that's what I'm trying to say. It doesn't make sense, because the problem is,
if I were retreading the argument I had with Ben, but if I were to say that I felt
very passionately pro-gun ownership rights, which is considered a right-wing position in America,
and also I'm extremely pro-abortion rights, which is considered an extremely left-wing
issue in America, then I now cannot wholesale throw my hat in with either of those parties,
each of which is going to take away something I care about. If I sincerely cared about both
these things, I am now in a third party, because I want them both. To call that a center party,
the only reason that those things are construed as left or right is that they just so happen
to fall into the bubble of people who tend to have certain other beliefs, but there's no
real correlation between them other than that. People by and large are willing to throw some
things under the bus, or they just don't care, because they care more about other issues. In
my case, growing up, I was very... I'm a freedom of speech person, and that's the reason I'm in
such a weird position, because growing up, liberal meant freedom of speech protector. That was a big
part of the party's identity. The conservatives were always trying to take shit away from us,
take away what we could say. Now, I don't know if it actually is the opposite now, but it feels
that way, because it feels like the liberals are the ones taking away what we can say.
The shit-lives and their id-pole shit is very anti-free speech. I agree that it is a big problem.
I think that that's what leads. I think that that identitarianism is what leads to this,
because people so badly want to have an identity of being with this party. As long as this party
supports the one issue they care about, they will tow the party line on all the other shit
and just assume that what the party thinks is true and correct. The way that people talk about
the whole AR-15, the automatic rifle with 15 rounds information, it's so easy for that to
spread through democratic circles, because they will just lap up anything that their side says
with just, they just don't care about gun rights, so they just say, oh, the Dems hate it, so I hate
it too. Their arguments make sense, ergo, I agree, but then you actually go listen to some Republican
voters who really care about gun rights, who do not care about abortion. They're like, yeah,
that should be legal, whatever. I don't care, but I'm voting Republican because they're not
taking my guns. When you talk to somebody like that, you think, okay, so most of these people
voting, they don't really have an opinion on most of these issues that are getting thrown in with
their party, and I think that if more people were, if we had something like alternative vote,
as I'm always saying, and we could have third parties that were viable, I think more people
would gravitate towards third parties that strip away the things that you don't like about
neither of the main parties, and just focus on a coalition of things that creates you in your
perspective. It is definitely stupid to have left and right. The only reason it has any value,
quote unquote value, is that at the moment we're in a two-party system, which generally goes left,
right. Well, I don't think that's the only reason. Well, yeah, I mean, the thought that generally
people of a certain persuasion think certain different policies are like, I like that section
of policies. Here's what I think about the hypothetical of a person who's very pro-gun,
very pro-abortion. I think if you are someone who, those are the only two opinions you have,
and you don't interrogate why you have them any further than that, sure. Then it would be
impossible for you to draw any ideological line for yourself and be like, oh, these are my,
these are my overarching beliefs. But if you think about, you could have those things,
and then you might think about why do you have them, and if you think about your underlying
beliefs that underpin those and cause you to think that way, I think what generally what you find is
people are inclined to one of two lines of thought. You either favor egalitarianism or you're in
favor of hierarchy. People tend to fall into these two camps. People have these two patterns of
thought that are diverged from each other. Causing everybody to fall. For me,
as a voter, I have nothing that draws me to either the Democrat or Republican side as like,
oh, this makes them better than the other one, so I need to vote for them. There's nothing I feel
that they are saying that makes me feel that way. I was arguing with a hashtag still voting
Yang. Those people, I don't understand that. I don't. It's kind of disappointing, but I think a
lot of them are probably like former Republicans or libertarians who went Yang, so I'm like, I'm
not too sorry to lose their vote. But anyway, I was arguing with one and she was sent, she was,
you know, no, actually, no, this was a Bernie or Buster. I had, it doesn't matter. But I said like,
like, I won't, I won't vote for Bloomberg, but, but I would probably vote for most of the Dems
if they got, I'm not, I'm not full on Bernie or Buster, but I'm also not full on vote no matter
who. I'm a centrist about it. But, but I was saying, I was saying, she was, I said, like, you know,
I know I hate Hillary, everybody hates Hillary, but like the fact of the matter is like, for example,
if we'd had Hillary for the last four years, it wouldn't have been great, but we would probably
be closer to Medicare for all or a decent public option, like, and we would have a better like,
we would have gotten better picks for the, for the Supreme Court and stuff like this.
See, I don't know all that stuff. We wouldn't have been happy about it, but we would have been,
we would be, we would be materially better off. That's the kind of thing that I view as like this
weird party think mind poison, because it's like, we could have got better seats. I don't know who
the fuck Hillary would have picked. Like, yeah, maybe they would have been Democrats, maybe in
some vague way that would get us closer to some ideals that I don't even really care about or
believe in anyways, but like, I just can't, I can't visualize in my mind this world in which
things were better because Hillary became president. Like, I, Hillary, for all her faults,
she was running on a platform of like expanding on the Affordable Care Act and stuff. For all
her faults, Hillary was pushing a, she was pro like expansion of the Affordable Care Act and like a
strong public health care option, which is a thing that I agree with. See, that's a topic that I
have no particular stance on. I feel like both arguments have a lot of strength and water.
Like, I've heard, I've heard both sides talk about it and I go, okay, I understand the issues.
Like, neither solution sounds like obvious to me. Neither one is like, oh, this will definitely
make things better, might make things different, could be interesting, might be worth a shake up.
But you know, like the level of like confidence that people feel and like, oh, if my guy wins,
things will get better. And it's like, if your guy wins, things will move very marginally in a
direction that will likely be counterbalanced in the next cycle as it usually is. Like,
this is, this is what I say. This is what I say to people that like scoff at Bernie and say like,
oh, well, you know, Medicare for all is too hard. It'll never get passed. And it's like, okay,
you even, let's assume you're right. Let's assume you're correct about that. And Bernie will not
will not be able to fully deliver on everything he says he wants to do, which,
you know, is the case for most presidents because they get thwarted by Congress because
separation of powers, this is how it's designed. And that's fine. I just, the reason I'm, I don't
care about that is because, sure, but at least he's a guy who will be pushing things in the,
he will at least be pushing in the direction that I want things to go in, even if we don't get all
the way there. It's better than having someone like Trump or like Buttigieg or even Biden or
someone who is going to be like way more, even if like, even if someone like Biden like wants,
like, I know that he would prefer that like more people be insured, right? Like, even though I
like expanding the American, the affordable character, I don't think is the best way we should
just go full on fucking socialized medicine. But even if like, he's not going to be pushing as hard,
right? Even if he's generally going the way I want, Bernie, Bernie goes harder for it.
We're going so far into the weeds and that's what I want, ideologically and materially discussion
than usual though. Yeah. But where I kind of want to back it out to is, I guess what frustrates
me about political discourse is that people have a tendency to look at things within the framework
of how they operate currently. People look at it like, like the Iowa caucuses, they matter because
of these like precedents of what they mean, you know? And so everybody gets excited about it and
we talk about it. But then particularly this year, like the Iowa caucus was a complete fucking joke
the results essentially mean nothing because of how badly it was cocked up.
Incidentally, I didn't know this, but apparently in 2016, Nevada was like an equally big debacle.
I didn't know this, but apparently in 2016, the Nevada caucus, the one that's coming out
this Saturday, the ones happening this Saturday, was an equally huge debacle and a nightmare rigged
by the fucking DNC. They stole it from Bernie. But less people were paying attention at that point.
Probably yes. So anyway, that's the one that's happening this Saturday, so I'm looking forward
to another night. When it comes to these caucuses and everything, people are paying all this attention
to it and like saying all this stuff about like what it means. And it's like, that all assumes
that the precedent will be kept to, but the precedent doesn't have to be kept to, it could
be completely subverted. Like Bloomberg currently is trying to completely subvert the precedent.
He's just using money to try and put his name in front of people and just get in. And Trump,
in many ways, what made Trump succeed was that he went outside the boundaries of what other
candidates were doing. He was using the internet. He was using memes. He is just way more blunt and
upfront than other presidents. He does not care about like maintaining this uber professional,
sanitary presentation that recent presidents, particularly Obama, have had. He rejected
all that because his thought process is, well, this may be the way that everyone's doing it,
but it's not the only way it can be done. And I can prove that. And he was so controversial for
that or for everything about it and that the mainstream media just fell all over themselves
to cover him. And he got billions and billions of dollars worth in free advertising.
He gets tons and tons of advertising because he is popular content. He will always show up on TV
and he knows how to be popular content. So, and there was that, have you seen the
Emplemen video about Trump, about how he memed this way into presidency? You should definitely
check it out. It's a great video. It just basically goes through Trump's whole history and how he has
always basically propagated himself as a human meme to get into, you know, eventually into the
presidency. But like, I think that the way that Trump looks at the world, he just says like,
I know that this will work. I'm not going to listen to anybody telling me otherwise because I already
see how this will work. And that tends to be the way that I look at things, which is like,
all right, I know that like, for instance, getting into the industry as a writer, you know, like,
all of us knew at some point in the past, oh, we could try to get published traditionally. Like,
we could try to work for a company, get some kind of pro gig. But like, we saw that there was this
alternative path of YouTube. And we went, okay, like, it seems like this is a way you can do it.
So let's figure out like how we can experiment with this and find another way forward. And like,
when we think about politics, I think people tend to think about it inside the box of what we
expect to be the way things work. Instead of going, how do we rebuild this box? Like,
how do we reshape this? Where can we start? What moves can we make? And there are certain things
like the reason I hammer on about the alternative vote so much is not that I think it would like
magically change the system or anything. It's just that it's such an obvious step in the right
direction that would have so much power. And it's so easy to do. Because all we have to do
is demand it as a people. Like, if everyone in America decided, hey, alternative vote is a
better way than first pass the post because it means third parties have a chance of existing,
then like, that's all it takes to change that. And I look at it and I just think this is so
obviously a good solution, even if it does nothing in the long run, it would be worth
having changed it because it's better as a system. Why aren't we doing it? Why aren't we
doing it? Why aren't we making a big fuss about it? And it's because nobody thinks it can happen.
Like, people don't convince themselves that those kind of changes can happen because they just think,
well, how do you even change something like that? Well, you just ask. You just tell the government
to do it. You are the government, ultimately. So it's like everybody gets so caught up in
participating in the political game instead of thinking outside of it. And like, obviously
Bloomberg is thinking outside of it, but the way he's doing it is so cynical and so
transparent that everybody who looks at it goes, oh, well, this is like gross, you know.
Guys, can I get in for a second here? Because, okay, this whole discussion has been very interesting
to listen to. But every single thing all of you guys have said so far doesn't vibe with me because
it is all inherently, and I know these words have tons of meanings and, you know, whatever,
to me, everything you're saying, including you did, seems super left-wing. And by that I mean,
you guys are all talking about what the government should be doing. Whereas, as you were saying,
Ben, what does it mean to be left versus right? I definitely just approached this whole conversation
from a different perspective because I have the one fundamental belief I have that people
just basically do everything better than the government, and we should not expect them to
solve our problems because they're just shitty at it and worse.
Wait, nothing I was saying was implying that the government should do anything.
Everything you were saying is about how we need to change the system politically. Now,
maybe you're saying by destroying the government or minimizing it, is that what you meant?
I'm an anarchist. I'm all for destroying the government.
Oh, okay, okay, fair enough.
Let everybody do what they want. I would say that my...
Kind of not exactly how I would define anarchism, but...
Well, what I think would be ideal would be to just have,
you know, we don't need a government. We just need everybody to not fuck with each other, you
know? I mean, I agree, but how do you enforce that? That's the question.
Let me throw this at you and see if it sticks. All right. Now, I agree that it is bad for the
government to control people. I agree that if the government is stepping in and telling you
what to do and they are a force, if they are a totalitarian force that is in control of everything,
that is bad. However, my issue is that power can accrete anywhere, and it is theoretically possible
that individuals, such as like a private ownership of a business, Amazon, for example,
or any other big corporation, or corporations in general, they have the potential to accrue
power, and that is basically becomes oppressive just like a government does.
So, while I agree that it's bad for the government to be too powerful, I think it is totally possible,
and I would say that it is probably happening now, that private corporations and individuals are
becoming authoritarian in their own, right, and exerting undue influence over the public.
And the only way to fight back at them, I think, would be through government regulation,
because if private industry, private interests are all aligned with each other against the public,
then what instrument does the public have to fight? I mean, strikes?
Ideally, not buying things from bad companies would help.
I understand that. I understand that, but like...
It's hard. It's very difficult.
People use our goods.
I mean, the reason we have government is...
When you vote with your wallets, when you vote with your wallet, people with bigger wallets get
more votes. And the people with big wallets all have class solidarity with each other.
All the rich are ideologically aligned with each other against everyone else.
I mean, the biggest threat, I think, to the ability to not have a government is the lack of
education, the lack of the ease with which those who have power can control the upbringing and
the knowledge that is had by those who are, you know, grow up in the system.
They can control how we think about the world, what power we think we have.
They teach us to be docile and to follow the script and follow society by their rules,
so that they can keep it organized.
And I think that whether you find comfort in that or not depends on, A,
how happy are you in this system, which the average person obviously is, and to at least
enough of an extent that they participate. And also, like, how brave are you? Because
those of us who don't like the system, we don't like it because of the limitations it puts on us
in what we can do with our lives. And there's a lot of people who would probably say,
I don't want to be able to do those things. I would happily forego my ability to do these
things in order to be safer, to have the government have more control over my life,
because I trust them, they are better at keeping me safe than I am. And for me,
I don't feel that way, because the government makes the lifestyle that I want to lead
put me in danger. A lifestyle that would not be dangerous if not for the fact that it's illegal.
Like smoking, buying drugs or something. Like buying drugs, like A-Cab.
Yeah, just, I mean, that's the perfect example just on its own. I can't legally,
can't buy weed here. There's no harm in me smoking it and consuming it and buying it because it's,
I mean, it's legal in tons of places, but they make me a criminal. They make my actions dangerous.
Look, even somebody like me, despite what I've said before, I am absolutely prepared to discuss,
I do not believe in no government, I am not an anarchist. I am in favor of a small force that
just like, the society doesn't completely collapse and fall in on itself. And potentially,
just as an example, maybe if we legalized heroin or some magic super drug of fantasy,
like maybe that would cause all of society to collapse because everyone just does that.
That's what Pete wants to do. He wants to legalize all drugs.
I mean, I am not convinced that such a thing exists, but like if we knew that would happen,
I would be for the government preventing that happening personally, because I don't want
society to collapse. That is a net bad, I would say. So for things like that, like I'm totally
on board, but like there's other things, like the whole idea of businesses being overly powerful
and stuff, that's probably true in many ways, and we should fix those things. But I mean,
there are definitely fundamental disagreements. I know we've previously discussed about just the
existence of billionaires, and I guess giant corporations as well, being inherently immoral,
whereas I just don't agree that just the, I need tangible examples of what they're doing to police
and could someone go to the point? Could someone reach the point where like this
company has done so many bad things, it needs to cease existing, because I also believe that with
criminals, I'm for execution if they do enough bad stuff. Same thing with businesses. If they do
enough bad stuff, break it down. But until that, like Amazon has Amazon, for example,
to so much bad, we should destroy it. I would argue that their profits alone constitute a,
what should be a crime. Maybe. I think. I would need to see some data. It's not so much like
having a lot of money literally makes you do evil things. It's the whole system of capitalism
that encourages a, you know, it leads to certain outcomes when, you know. Are you talking about
like unrestrained rampant capitalism with no caps? Yeah, like, I mean, the whole thing with
fossil fuels being, you know, like climate change, there's no incentive for them to stop
getting that cheap, easy fuel from, from under the sea and all that. They're still going to use oil
because it's good for money. And like, there's not really an incentive to heal sick people if they
aren't, you know, they don't get a lot of money back. There's way more money in like an ongoing
treatment as opposed to a cure, for example. So that could be bad incentives. Do you know about
what's going on right now in Canada with the Wutsueten? I think I might be saying it wrong,
the Wutsueten, like, tribe of native people. Okay, well, there is a, there was a little,
it is a, it is an independent territory. It has never ceded control to Canada. Canada does not
rule it, but some fucking oil company wants to put a like toxic oil pipeline directly through
their territory to make money. They do not have the right to do this legally. And yet, and yet,
like the Wutsueten people like made like truck blockades to like block the company, because
the company just wanted to try to do it anyway. The people there like fought back, they set up
blockades to like prevent them from doing it. And Canada responded, they sent the Royal Canadian
Mountain, the Royal Mounted Canadian Police or the RMCP or whatever, they sent the cops in to
like fucking use lethal force to just fucking genocide these people, just like kick their
fucking asses and be like, no, it doesn't matter that we like, we're just, we're just gonna, no,
they can just do it now. I know you're, they're not allowed to, but we want them to. So they're,
they're just, they're just gonna do it. Is there more to this story than just being,
well, there's been a, well, there's been a huge backlash against it, like on the internet.
Was this recent? Was this a recent thing? Yeah, this was like last week.
Okay. Okay. Well, look, based on the facts provided, look, I agree, I would not, I would
like oppose that with whatever levers of power I have, because that sounds bad as described.
So, I mean, I'm with you, I'm with you. I mean, this is a particularly bold and barefaced example
of like the ruling class and the government and the, the, the, you know, big corporations,
the interests of capital, just like, just like, just nakedly fucking over people.
I haven't talked about, I'm still utilitarian and I, so I don't think I'm not an anarcho capitalist
despite the memes. I don't think people just do anything. There has to be some checks, but I'm,
I'm not a scholar. I don't know the specifics. And you know what, I've got a confession to make
for these stuff, you know, all the stuff that we've been talking about, I'll tell you,
I'm strongly considering voting for Trump. And I'll tell you why. It is, it is because
exactly as you said, Ben, when it comes to more government control of things versus less,
ideologically, I just know super clearly which side I'm on and which I would want to win the day
ultimately. I'm not for no government. I'm not for like bad things. I think we would agree on 95
percent of every single thing we want to have happen. I just don't think that on these, on these,
everything seems generally good in America, the localized place where things are right now.
And I don't know, like I just haven't been presented with a case that anything that other
people would do would make the world a better place, which is my main goal. So it's fine,
it's fine for the middle class probably, it's fine for the one percent. Yeah, the, yeah, the
shrinking middle class, the shrinking middle class is doing pretty, is doing reasonably well
for now. We could use, poor people could use healthcare, I think. Also, the minimum wage
should be higher because people work in these fucking like slave, slave wages, like Uber jobs,
gig economy. I just don't think that the government incentive system presented is a better
solution to make the world a better place overall. In the absence, in the absence of any like raising,
federal raising of the minimum wage, we've got like increasing, increasing wealth inequality,
and we've got fucking the GDP rising while like these standard of living drops.
Well, I just haven't been presented with solutions that make me think they'll make the
world better. But I'm just curious, Nate, why, like what have you heard from Trump that makes
you think he would be good to vote for? I will be completely honest, I don't follow politics
subjectly at all. Oh, here it is again. Here's this shit again. Look, like you said, Ben, we all
know our core ideology. I'm for a smaller government. I know which side that is. Why do you think Trump
is for small government? I don't think so. The guy just fucking completely overreaches his
presidential power. What are my options? Vote libertarian that'll lose? Trump is basically an
authoritarian. He'll just do whatever he wants. He doesn't care about this. Well, I mean, less,
some more than others. Anyway, I don't think Bernie's an authoritarian. Bernie's pro-labor.
Bernie is considered one of the more libertarian candidates. I feel like if you have not gone
into any depth to see what the policies are, you shouldn't vote. I agree. Well, I agree. I would
not cast a vote today because I don't have enough information. If you go into, if you research what
Trump is saying on whoever the Democratic Party is and you say, well, you know what, I do still
prefer Trump, then that's fine. But the fact that you don't even follow it in any way and you just
assume that Trump is your guy. For what it's worth, there's not much reason to even think about it
yet because as much fun as we all are getting hyped in these primaries, speaking for me personally,
I've literally never watched any primary debates or anything until this election,
and it's only because I'm with May who gives a fuck. I would not, I didn't even know about the
primaries until the last election. I did not know that was a thing that they didn't just select
their guy. I also was only vaguely aware of the process of the election before 2016.
All of this is just because Twitter now is politics Valhalla, which I'm fine with because
it's hilarious. Now that I follow nothing but what I'm going to call woke, but not what you're
thinking when you think woke accounts, it's been great. I follow Moon Cult and
guys like Michael Tracy. I don't actually follow him. He tweets too much. There are certain people
on Twitter who, not that I trust them as in I think everything they say is true, but I trust
them to be politics I want to follow, essentially. Everybody's got an agenda. Nobody's perfect.
What are we supposed to do? Look, I'm not going to count your vote.
Yeah, so just vote Trump. Simple.
Life's going pretty good. Yeah, seems fine.
Horrible. Absolutely nightmare. Let me say one last thing about,
I want to say one last thing. Hey, can you guys hear me?
Yes, now we can. Okay. One last thing about Bloomberg is that, oh, fuck, was it? Oh, yeah.
He's actually a giant balloon.
Bloomberg is a great dipstick, if you know what I mean, for liberals, right? Because a lot of
people really hate Trump. A lot of people can't stand Trump, but a lot of those same people
are fine with Bloomberg, even though he's just as much of an authoritarian,
just as much of a racist, misogynist, douchebag, just as much of a piece of shit as Trump is.
Well, it's not like ability voting because they don't have to see it. With Bloomberg,
Bloomberg acts presidential. He puts up a nice front. He's polite on Twitter, right?
Comparatively. And a lot of shit libs are like, oh, thank God, a return to normalcy.
They don't care about what he's actually going to do. They don't care about any
material consequences. They're just like, Trump is ugly. Trump is offensive.
I don't like seeing him. As long as I don't have to see him,
Bloomberg, if Bloomberg, I won't have to think about it as much because I won't hear as much
about it. Thank God. And it's a very sad state of affairs that we live in. And everyone that
supports Bloomberg should be put on a blacklist. And let me be clear. Anybody in the comments is
going to be like, oh, my God, Nate's going to vote Trump. Shut the fuck up. I'm not voting for
anyone. I'll tell you, if I had to vote today, I would blindly vote for the libertarian candidate.
That's what I would do today. Oh, you should vote for vermin supreme.
Well, who's that guy? I forget. He's the guy who wears the boot. He's the presidential guy.
Who wears the boot on his head. Let's get him up to 1% for the giant rat party.
I followed vermin supreme on Twitter the other day, but then I had to immediately
unfollow him because he tweets too much. He was retweeting something every five minutes.
Nothing worse than somebody you follow because they're cool, but then they just tweet too much
bullshit and they water it down. Yeah, it's the worst. All right, well, let's go to voicemails.
Let's fucking do it. I got them all right here. I test this beforehand. So hopefully they work
as they sometimes do and you ladies and gentlemen can leave your voicemail at the speak pipe link
down below. All right, what do we got first? Oh, I'm very excited for this one. This is my favorite
voicemail. How many? How many we got today? There's like five. There's like only five. Okay. So first
one is simply titled, fuck you, munchy. Is this better be about dads? Munchy, you're a real son
of a bitch. You know that? You know that you piece of fucking garbage used to be one of my favorite
members. But this last episode, every episode that you've been on recently has just been garbage.
Somebody says that you do that. You do that. You do what I just did. You're a son of a
bitch. You're a snake in the grass rat bastard. You'll never fucking hear this because you're
not going to be on the podcast. I'm all about the self improvement. We're like, I'm so fucking intelligent.
Damn. I wish Munchy were here to defend himself. If only he was here. But I guess this is, we'll
have to take his word for it. He's too busy stealing dads. It was like an actually scathing
criticism kind of, but it was embedded in such a funny sounding voicemail. I just, I just enjoyed it.
I hope he hears that and gets offended enough to come on next episode and respond. Me too. Me too.
We can only pray. All right, what do we got? Next one, we've got a professional podcast
procrastinator. Okay, take it away. I think this one was kind of quiet. So turn up your volume. All
right, go. So I'm about 10 episodes beyond the procrastiners podcast. Just finished watching
Pokemon Sucks. Now, if I were to watch the rest of the PCP episodes right now, how much of that
spicy YouTube bread money would be going to our ripple overlords instead of you guys?
Mmm, all of it. That's it. Yeah, right now, all of it. So for people in this guy's position,
as of the recording of, of, yeah, it's still in the hands of Brad Garlinghouse. We don't
have it back yet. Hopefully this will, this statement this week, hopefully this statement
will be incorrect. And when you hear it, we can only hope if this episode or whatever, if you're
listening to a new episode past like 195 on the PCP, then you're good. If not, I mean, it's fine.
That person will get the ad revenue on their channel, I guess, which is also fine. Okay,
that's it. So there you go. Don't watch other stuff on a channel until it's back. Fuck them.
All right. Next one, we've got, oh, I think this is a longer title, but I just called it proof.
It's proof of something, but I can't remember what. Let's find out. Go.
Hello, PCP. I hope you know I have your grapefruit held hostage. And if you ever want to see it again,
unharmed and unsweetened, then you will deliver 1000 pounds of bread and 1000 pounds of garlic
to the Washington Monument three hours after listening to this. Your beloved grapefruit won't
be unsweetened for long. Click the link. There's a link I posted in the gross disgusting audio
links to a DeviantArt image that this man uploaded. It's cute. Quandary poser, I guess. Oh, at least
he's using zero calorie sweetener. Oh, thank God. Thank God. That's good to say. So he's got a spoon
up to a grape, or he's going to eat it with a spoon with sweetener. Oh, God. I noticed that his first
thing says 1000 loaves of bread, which is different from pounds. That's probably less. We should
probably play it safe and go for pounds, because I'm pretty sure a loaf of bread is less than a
pound. Also, the plural is loaves with V. That's true. That's true. How is he expecting to feed
that grapefruit the sweetener when he taped his mouth shut? I think he's going to have to cut it
open. He's going to have to surgery. Is he going to joker the grapefruit? He's going to be bifurcated,
yeah. Well, we'll see what happens. Good luck to us. Poor disenfranchised grapefruit.
He never had a chance. I really like his face. Let me see. Yeah, there's actually pretty good
art on there. This is not bad. All right. We've got a completely unfunny voicemail from a concerned
citizen. Let's see what he has to say. What else is new? Hey, PCP, it's me. One of your brainless
fucking fans. I just wanted to call and ask you about the Radcon 4 fan meetup thing that you guys
were talking about two weeks ago. You're going to set a date for that, because if I'm going to buy
a plane ticket to go halfway across the continent to go fucking look at you and then murder you.
If I'm going to do that, I kind of need to buy a plane ticket in advance, and it gets
more expensive, the closer to the date you are. Could I know when that happens? That's a great
point. That's a great question. First of all, the Radcon, we will be at the place
doing Radcon stuff from the 6th to the 16th. It's in that window. So if you buy a plane ticket
to be, where were we thinking we are? Somewhere on Virginia Beach? We're in that town. We should
probably do it on a Saturday somewhere in that stretch. We had a thing on a calendar that we
were thinking of a possible meet update near the end. Where did I put that? Yeah. Okay, because
let me see. March 6th to 16th. Okay, 16th is a Monday. Okay, so like Saturday and Sunday. So
Munch is leaving Sunday night. So maybe Saturday or Sunday at the end of the con. So at the end?
So like we have all our stuff done and we can just kind of, I don't know, hang out.
14th. Yeah, that makes more sense. Maybe should we commit to the 14th Saturday
sometime during that day? We could do it Sunday too. We could do it the next day. I think Saturday
is a better idea. And I think, yeah, I do think we could do it on this. There's two Saturdays,
the 7th and the 14th. What do you think? I just don't know. Yeah, I think we should do it on the
14th. Okay, yeah. Okay, there's four of us here. Digi is muted for some reason, but I'll assume he
agrees. Right, so the 14th, Saturday, March 14th. All right, we're committing. That'll be the day
when we have a meet up and we are gonna do one. We should make an announcement outside of this
episode so that it comes out. I will make an update on the Kickstarter confirming that and I'll let,
I don't know, Tom and Munchy know that we're gonna do that. I guess it's not as critical that we
pick a place as long as we know that it's gonna be in Virginia Beach, but we should. Okay, yeah,
we can commit to that Saturday, March 14th in the area of Virginia Beach somewhere on that day.
If you want to come and do your stuff that's on you, that's not for us. It's not our problem.
We'll keep you posted here and on Twitter. Yes, we will. It's at tpcrastinators.
About where exactly and when and what the times are. There you go. That'll be the day.
Okay, well, let's update the Kickstarter with that information too. So that's in stone somewhere,
but okay, we got one more voicemail and this one is from Boyan. Let's hear Boyan finale,
as I'm sure it's called. Go. Guys, for the special occasion of episode 200,
could you please consider returning written questions? Some of us really appreciate that.
And maybe, maybe, maybe question mark live questions.
Live question, like doing the PCP live.
Well, the PC, well, episode 200 is going to be the streamed live at Radcon, right?
Yeah, I don't think we 100% settled on that because we'd have to do the 200 and one and like
202 episodes first. Yeah, we said we were just going to skip 200. Okay, if you want, all right,
that's fine. Okay, that sounds funny. It sounds amusing to me. Okay, we will probably do, I think,
okay, let's do like live questions via super chat, which are... Yeah, yeah. That's what we did last
time, right? We're going to have streams going... I think he was thinking that we wouldn't do it
all the time anyway, so. Yeah, that's, it'll be basically like a live stream, but we'll love
probably Victor's camera set up like we did last time and do it. That was so strange. I remember
watching, then, the way he zooms in right on our faces, like, oh god, it's too close. It's too close.
He was very close. You could give him notes, if you like, to be less close. Good memes, though,
good memes from that. So, okay, since we're doing things like out of order that way and we'll do
200 at Radcon, yes, you will in fact get a chance to say things to us. Although, I guess on the
larger point, I mean, as for bringing back written questions on like Twitter and stuff,
I don't know, bro. I'm not really feeling it. It seems like a lot of work and I don't care.
Well, it's not a lot of work. It's just, I don't care.
Yeah, I'd have to go somewhere else. Twitter questions are sweet about it.
In fact, it's because it's less work that the quality of the questions is usually so much worse.
Yes, that's why I was going to say the skill floor for asking a speak pipe question is higher,
and I think it self-selects for quality to a certain extent.
And I'm just reading minds here, but I don't know if this guy's maybe thinking that because he's
got a thick accent or it makes it harder to like, I mean, I'm sure whoever you are, you could make
a good voicemail with whatever good question. If you really, really needed to, you could do
like a text-to-speech robot voice to say the thing. Maybe he just doesn't want to put in the work,
which I guess. Look, guys, this guy can clearly speak English. I don't think that's the issue.
He was wondering. I don't know what he meant there. I mean, if there are any other people who
have struggling with English or like have a thick accent and they feel like they wouldn't get
understood, they can use a robot. Some people I think legitimately have that concern, I think,
when I call in. I don't know. But we're doing what we're doing. Use text-to-speech. I mean,
you can figure it out. Just be creative here. That's it. That's our last voicemail for the day.
So again, if you want to leave one, that is the speak pipe link down below. Click on that,
and leave us a voicemail. There you go. Let me see. We got a bonus episode coming up soon.
It'll be the bonus episode before Radcon, just like a couple of days before, and that'll be
on the 1st of March, and you can get that by pledging $5 to the Kickstarter at
what is it? Patreon.com slash TheProCrastinators, $5 bonus episodes, $1. You're in the bonus lounge,
or the normal talky discord lounge with all of us hanging out good times, and pledge as much as
you want. Do $1,000. Why not? I beseech you. Oh, and you know what? It'll be
funny to see. There will be a PCB episode that comes out at 2pm normally, and we get into our
Airbnb at Radcon 4 at 4pm, so that episode will probably just be rapping as we get to the house,
and we'll probably set up a live stream real fast. So on that day, on March 6th, you'll see
a bunch of stuff coming that evening, I'm sure. And also, follow us again for more info and updates
at TPCrastinators on Twitter. Updates about more stuff about the live meetup probably. Maybe we'll
iron that out fully on the Kickstarter. If not, TPCrastinators, follow us there for more info,
and yeah, I guess that's about it. Anything else? And we'll let you know on there when we get the
channel back as well. Go check out The Lord of Ghosts, Chapter 3 out on you. Yes, I have not read
it yet. I'm very excited to check it, to scope it, to peep it, to scopio-peepio it. Yeah. Go read
Chapters 1 through 4 of The Road to Radcon 4, Chapter 5 coming soon. That's right, Chapter 5
will be out very soon. Pledge to my Patreon to get early access to the pre-finale Slime and
Punishment updates coming out now. Patreon.com slash Ben Saints. Don't wear it out. And my channel
will have videos again soon. If we don't get this channel, if we don't get the PCP back,
I assume we'll stream the Radcon countdown to the end of the Kickstarter on your channel.
Maybe. We could do it on Twitch or something. I don't really want to do it on my main channel.
I guess we could. I don't know. Because it's closer to the Radcon
like viewer base, I guess. That's true. People would know the PCP would know your channel more
than they would know your Twitch, I think. Yeah. I mean, definitely true. Plus, there'd be way
more viewers just being on that platform. I would be in favor of that if you'd be okay with it.
Okay. We'll tell you what. I'm not super opposed. We'll iron that out and we will let people know
where it's going to be. Yeah. Okay. We'll decide that stuff. Well, it will have already happened.
Oh, yeah. Right. Oh, yeah. That's totally inside baseball right now.
Lol. You will have seen it. And oh, won't that be exciting for you?
All right. Anyway, we're out of here. Thanks for funding Kickstarters.
Road to Radcon 4. Radcon 4 Paradise, everybody. We're going to make all that good shit.
It's going to be good. You're going to enjoy it. I promise you.
Thank you, everybody, for supporting. $20,349 right now. My God. It just keeps going.
It just keeps happening. Well, thanks, everybody. And hopefully we hit that 2-2-2 goal.
Radcon 4 is going to be sick as fuck. Yes, the 2-2-2 goal. Will we have hit it by now?
I am optimistic, but we'll see. As am I. All right. We'll see you next week, everybody. Bye.
Losers.