Hello everyone, and welcome back to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's me, BGE. And what's
going on today? We've got Ben Saint around here.
Mmmhmm. That's right. It's Monday. I sure hate him.
It's Sunday, but you'll hear this on Friday. But that's okay. We've got Digibro.
This is a real low-T intro right now.
Yeah, you're right. I'm on Hormone Blockers. What can I do?
I'm making a transition in my life, if you know what I'm saying. And we've got Munchy
and Hippocrit as one horrible hydra.
Poke. You poked me.
Oh, check out this visual joke. Isn't this funny what I'm doing with my hands right now?
Oh, dude. Oh, dude, check out this sign language I'm doing right now. Read this out loud.
It says I'm a big fan.
Oh, no. They want to be able to bear for it. That's not the case. The only Hippocrit
would see me because he's in my house. And by my house, I'm in his house. All the houses
are my domain once I get my claws into them.
I hope the adoption papers go through soon. And also the disowning of Digibb happens soon
in his family. And then you are in England.
What you're hearing right now is actually a lie, by the way, because when you're hearing
this, this will no longer be the case. So this is a snapshot of a bygone era that you're
hearing right now, where I'm sitting inside of Hippo's house right now.
What's like looking at the sun? You only see the sun from seven, eight minutes ago because
of the speed of light. It's when you look at the cosmos, you see the universe, not as
it is, but as it was many light years ago.
Are you fine right now? You're slurring your words. You didn't know what discord was. You
didn't know how audio connections worked. You didn't know how voices or speech worked.
And you're trying to learn how they are on the fly right now recording a podcast. It's
like you handed like an extra treasure, like, hey, make some audio content, make some like
40 hour audio book right now, and you're handing it to a fucking alien who doesn't even know
what a voice box is. This is what listening to Ben speak and think is like.
You know what I'm excited for? I'm very excited to hand oblivion the Gibb Munchie audio track
and have him untangle them and separate them manually into two separate audio tracks so
that he can sync up the flashing independently. Oh, I forgot about the flashing put them in
one avatar together. That'll be fine. No, it'll be fine. Oh, you just one slightly larger
square. Yeah, right square like Steven Universe Fusion. Yeah, exactly. Exactly. Oh, cut diagonal
like Gibb Munchie Gump Gump. The rest of this podcast, they are, we shall not think of them
as separate people, but as one entity. Exactly. We are the same. We have the same opinions.
One. I really love that race that I'm thinking of right now that you can also understand the
one I'm referring to because you have my same brain. Yes, the white. What's in it? Oh, no.
I propose Muncho Crit. Muncho Crit. Yeah, that's good. That's good. We've just been the whole
podcast talking about things that have happened to us. So you guys are just like peripherals.
Oh, I gotta tell you, I'm most interested. I would love to hear what you guys have been
up to. I think you had like a meetup going on. I haven't followed it closely because
I'm too important, but I would love to hear it. Before we jump straight into them, we
should do at least one little topic. So here's what I thought of right before the podcast.
How do you shit? I want to know how everybody shits. You know, fascinatingly, there was
a voicemail asking this very question that did not make the cut, but I guess he's getting
his wish nonetheless. Because I don't know about you guys, but the way I shit has evolved
a lot over the years. Let's do our quick poop craps, Donators, you know, intro. Welcome
everybody to the Poop Craps, Donators podcast. Pleasure to be here as always. I have shit
the same way since I was born, but I'm recently trying to curb my unhealthy shitting habits.
You said that you shit too long. Do you take too long of a shit? So here's the thing. When
I was younger, I too took way too long on the toilet, like 30 minutes usually. I knew
people who took 40 plus. Apparently, I'm taking 30 seconds tops. So what I've read is, you
know, that whole gut bacteria autism thing I was bringing up before. I had already heard
about the connection between gut bacteria and autism because apparently people with Asperger's
take too long to shit. And it's a general problem. And I think that, I don't know, maybe I developed
the proper gut bacteria later because it no longer takes me very long to shit. In fact,
I go in there, I shit all the shit out, and I just sit there for a while because I'm still
reading the manga chapter that I'm trying to read before I get out the toilet. Or people with
their phones. But I think a lot of it is like, I think when I was younger, I just was never sure
I was done. It's like you are done, but you just sit there for like 20 extra minutes because you
feel like they're supposed to be more. You know, the worst one is when you've done like the main
shit that you came in there to do, but there's a potential like another one down in the pipeline.
And you're not sure whether you should strain yourself to get it out while you're here or
wait until it needs to come out later. I'm going to tell you right now, my piece of advice to
anybody who has this problem, just get off the toilet. You can come back. That's true. That's
the right way to handle that situation for sure. It's very, very rare that that extra one is actually
going to be able to come out anytime soon. More likely once you get up and you walk around a little
bit, it'll shift around and you'll realize you don't have the shit actually. You don't need it.
You don't got to wait. This is another one of the many arguments that I constantly mock you behind
your back for. And it's the extended sequence of Digibro realizes and presents as new information
that which everyone has known for decades. And this is an ongoing series that I'm constantly
fascinated by. And I enjoy every interview. You can know it. It's not like you put words to it in
your mind. I mean, I suppose so. I'm literally like certain if this podcast had come out like
three years ago, it would have been like, whoa, dude, shred, like speedrun shred. Maybe.
You have to understand, Nate, that what's so appealing about the internet is that people who
have been completely left behind by society can gather and take notes about what's actually going
on in the world together. That's fair. I see the appeal there. That's like, I've never talked to
anybody about how they shit before. I was just taking too long on the toilet. And then one day
I read an article or something that's like, Hey, don't take too long in the toilet, you'll get
dysentery. And I'm like, Oh shit, I better start quickening up my poops. And then I start reading
studies that are like, Oh, Asperger's tied to taking too long to shit. And I'm like,
well, maybe this has something to do with it. You know,
you know, this is just an area that I'm very sensitive to because I feel that a lot of my
videos, I'm extremely concerned that I'm just saying things. Everyone's heard a million times
and are super boring. But I'm saying it anyway, which we all are. There's no new info. Nobody
is ever on YouTube who is going to be grudge having to hear something they've heard before.
It's like all YouTube is. I mean, you're right. You're absolutely right about that.
But maybe that's just my resentment to the, I mean, we all agree on this. Like,
I think about this a lot that the information that you come across on YouTube,
like these are not the experts. These are not, these are not people ahead of their field. These
are basic bitch observations about the world. And I suppose I feel a sensitivity and a bit of
shame at that fact. I think about that so often because I've gotten so far down like history
holes where like the popcorn historians that get like thousands upon millions of views on YouTube
are just like nothing to me to the point where I can't believe it was even made. Like someone like
had the idea to like not, not even just recite history, which isn't even history. It isn't even
interesting. And what's the word inherently, but they just had the goal to just, you know,
recite it word for word, but also to do the thing where, you know, I have to cut it down to 10
minutes. So it's just like skipping over lots of information, like stuff like that where it's,
it's so boiled down from an actual interesting thought. Like it actually, you know, you have,
you have like the deep level shit, you have like audio books and real,
horse storyography shit. And then you go up to the YouTube where it's just like so
polished down to like absolutely nothing that it is wasting your time.
You know, I feel like there's a, maybe it's some sort of inverse of the Dunning-Kruger effect,
but there's got to be a graph that charts like, like general interest in a subject matter that
peaks super early on with like the basic facts and like the further you go into like becoming
an expert, like people's interest or willingness to commit to learning more goes like exponentially
down as you get further and further out. I think that's just, I think that's just the Dunning-Kruger
effect. Well, I mean, that's a different effect, but I see your point. I have to ask, did you get
into history through videos like that? Yes, I did. I won't lie. Yeah, there you go.
See, there is use for that. I think that's the main purpose. Like I view YouTube as a
gateway drug to more interesting stuff. I completely agree. I don't want to
besmirch. I, you know, I don't want to like make it seem like I'm really angry at them,
even though I am constantly, I click on them and I think, oh, maybe this one will be good.
Ah, God damn it. It's always weird from the perspective of like being either, either a creator
or a fan because like the, there's always new people and it makes it confusing because like
for me, I always used to view like, okay, my like main channel is like the basic bitch stuff that's
like just meant to introduce you to the concepts and then you get sucked into like the deep lore
stuff that I do otherwise. But like there's always new people to be hit with the basic
bitch stuff. And so it's like, I have to keep repeating myself because those people are not
going back four years and watching, you know, my video explaining the concepts I'm talking about
now. So I still get questions. That's just what, that's just what most people cap, like guys like
Jeff, not to even, this isn't even an insult, but he clearly is appealing to that demographic
as his primary focus and you know, wise, wise. I get stuff like that even like on this show
where I forget the specifics and if it comes back to me while I'm talking, I'll mention it,
but there was a PCB episode where I was discussing like a topic that I had been
brewing and stewing on for a while. Oh, it was, you can't waste too much time chasing perfection
in art and it's very to have released something than not to have released something and just
put it out, just put it out, just put it out. And I said something like the tale, I said that
sort of like condensed aversion of the idea, the sort of like, you know, good art, you know,
technically impressive art isn't valued by said that on a PCP recently. And someone came in here
saying that like, um, like there are of course reasons to have technical art and like
a technically impressive art and like, yeah, duh, like I didn't think that I had to express it
because the, because this point had been discussed on RFCK and even on previous PCP episodes and
just two people in the circle. So I didn't even think that it was necessary to say it to people
in PCP, you know, the audience, but I guess it makes sense. Like maybe this is someone's first
episode, maybe these tuned in on episode 300 and fucking thousand and they want to get
on the lowdown. Or even they just forgot because they're dumb. Yeah, that's true.
That's true. Like I have people in my audience all the time who like,
who I'll be like, didn't you watch this video? And they're like, yeah, but I forgot.
And again, like, again, it's like, I don't really want to shit on them. It's just like,
like, what am I supposed to do? Like say the entire point from the beginning? I mean,
which makes sense in like a neutral context, but we can't just like stop the podcast right now to
explain the nuance of every single thing that we're saying. I think, I think there's a level of
which, like if, if it goes without saying for you, and it's not like completely ridiculous,
like if most people get it, then it's fine to just to, to say the thing, assuming that most people
get it, you know what it is, the initial context, but and just ignore the people who don't because
they'll eventually get it. Yeah, we're, we're talking about the difference between being a teacher
and being a scientist right now. Like a teacher is somebody who takes information that science has
discovered and repeats it over and over again every year to a new group of kids. A scientist is
always trying to find new information. They are expected to already know every piece of information
that currently exists as they pursue others, which is why those people, you know, are sequestered
into academia, where like you have to pet, like, well, you know, in an idealized way,
what academia is supposed to be is you pass all these trials to prove that you know everything
going on, and therefore you can think about what comes next. But you, if you, you know, stop off
to be a teacher, it's just repetition. And I think on YouTube, a lot of us are trying to do both at
the same time, like we're on a journey of self discovery, like the stuff we're talking about,
it's not necessarily that like we know everything, you know, we might do research projects and
stuff like that. But it's more about exploration of the self and the science of understanding the
environment around you. And then again, you have to go and teach that to your audience. But
it's like you're more excited about doing the science role, but you have to stop and do the
teaching role if you want to keep those people, if you want people to be able to keep up with you
basically. Yeah, okay, Mr. Philosopher, let's get back to shitting because I didn't get to say
what I wanted to say about shitting, like large shits out your a**hole.
I just wanted to say about the teaching thing. It's funny how like on YouTube,
like the biggest educational channels, the literal teachers, are usually only making videos about
stuff that is like spiritually, not spiritually, but like enlightening to them like new information,
people like Veritasium and Smutter every day and Vsauce, I guess. They're teaching people new
things that they have found and they make the videos in such a way that you don't really need to
understand all the science, but they do give you books if you want to read more and like get the
basic concepts out of the way so that you're on the same page and you know, they do it.
That's good. Yeah, that serves as a pretty good shitting. It's become so much more,
so much more than just the active shitting to me. It's become like an active part of my leisure
experience where I will put off shitting if I'm in the middle of writing so I can have the release
of taking a sh**. Like the shitting is my break time. It is literally how I experience like
a job well done. It is my reward. I do not go to the bathroom when I have to go to the bathroom.
I do it when it's convenient to trick my brain into like performing tasks that I want it to do
and like punishing it by holding in piss or sh** into the point where I'm able to take a break.
Who's f**king cat is that? Get the f**k out of here. Obliterate. No. Exodia. Obliterate. Send that
tanderlott pony back to the moon where she came from. I will spend like seriously like 30 yeah
like did you say like 30 minutes on the bathroom on the sh** as they call it and just yeah like
did you say just on my phone reading or writing or just doing anything just because that is the
time under which I am free to do as I please and I have not locked my like you know I haven't
turned off my computer manually from a frozen turkey and now I literally cannot turn back
on my computer again. I've taken a sh** from the respite of literally not being able to use my
computer at all. Munchy I'm proud that you're trying to address this problem now because my
cogey who used to share a room with me he just he did not care about how long his sh** took.
He felt like it was he was just really taking long sh**s and he would take his laptop in with him
and watch yeah no movies full films and he would do it in my bathroom because I had my own
bathroom and he was a roommate I do that too and I would be like you mother like every single day
I'd have to go downstairs and use someone else's bathroom because this mother f**ker is sitting
in my bathroom for two goddamn hours out of every f**king day watching whole films and he would do
it at work too and I think eventually I will do one better. I remember many a summer nights
while I was in middle school where I would in order to like dodge like my mom like a question
to me or whatever I would go into my bathroom and instead of like having like the lights on
in my main room so she would be able to see me I just went into my bathroom and I literally
stayed in the bathroom on the toilet for all night six hours plus I've done that most of my
god damn just avoid I mean that just shows a dysfunction I would say there's something wrong
where that is happening well I remember very specifically one time I watched the entirety of
marble hornets well in the bathroom and that was a great experience the ideal scenario to watch
marble hornets. Bathrooms are a comforting place and I used to be I used to feel very strongly
about the bathroom like because I spent so much time in there I always felt like it was a a place
I had a strong connection to I filmed a lot of music videos in the bathroom back in the old
Modal Soul Productions days but these days I just don't have the same effect I view it as
more utilitary it's just like hey that's why that's the place where you shit you don't want to spend
too much time in there you know. Yo I think one of the subjects we're talking around is kind of the
sanctity we feel in the bathroom in today's modern interconnected society where can you have true
privacy the bathroom. Well not if you bring your phone with you. Well okay I mean I mean you have
as much privacy as you want in the bathroom if you just leave it off or what I mean maybe they're
listening to you via apples or I don't know. They are. They are totally with you. They are.
What about the recent kerfuffle about bathrooms where did you hear about this one of my very
favorite streamers Dr Disrespect filming in several bathrooms at E3 and getting it which
is a crime in the state you live in and got banned from Twitch temporarily. Dr Disrespect
isn't actually blockbuster video game champion 1993 or 1994. You know actually Ben I think as a
matter of fact he actually is those two things I think those are one of the two things that are
actually true about his legacy. Okay well I think that's correct. I don't think that well okay I saw
a video. Maybe I'm wrong. Who was it? Was it a gaming historian? I don't know. I watched some video
that talked about because there were two blockbuster championships and we know who won them. Yeah I'm
pretty sure unless he like unless like he pulls off the sunglasses it was me all like one of the
guys who actually won one of these championships like beefed with him like on Twitter. That's funny.
Yeah he's like dude I I'm the blockbuster 1994 video game champion and this asshole is claiming
to be it. What the fuck man. You know we know his name and like you could look it up so that
that could very well be true that could definitely be true but but let's focus on his violation of
the sanctity of bathrooms and you know I I like the guy a lot I think he's real funny it was obviously
a joke but he committed a grave sin by by filming in bathrooms that is a place where I have my
pp on full display to all comers and I'm glad you're saying this honestly this liberates me a
little bit because yeah for for over a decade this is not a controversial position I don't think
dog I think everybody's on I think so too but like I okay so like 10 years ago I came up with
a bathroom rating system and every bathroom I go to I gave it a score out of 10 and I've always
wanted to do bathroom reviews but I'm like I can't really like how can I communicate this
bathroom to somebody without showing it visually and I just I was like I don't know if it's legal
slash I don't have the balls even if the room is empty to get out a camera and record in the
middle it's not illegal in every state you can't do it in California you might be able to in other
states you could just like make sure no one's in there I mean if so who would object as long as
it's legal yeah it just is it feels like to pull out a camera in a bathroom sure sure and who who
even wants these bathroom reviews honestly who gives um well tell you uh Kazi has a friend and I
want to disclose uh the Instagram in which it exists but she has a friend who owns a like
bathroom toilet review Instagram where she literally rates them on a scale from one to ten
and like what you're discussing in your brain is already real and people are doing it right now
it's an untapped market I guess my idea has was not that unique and other people probably came
to the same conclusion is this a popular account I'm just curious is this popular does she actually
write like a like text post or is it just like a picture and a score no no no no yeah yeah yeah no
there's there's well it's not a long-winded like like a video like essay transcript but it doesn't
have to be there's only so many properties that a bathroom can have indeed indeed uh but you never
know okay I want to go back I want to go back to Nate saying that like everyone's already thought of
like the the bathroom scenario and you know how to do strats I want to say that literally you
Nate on the pcp like 20 episodes is the reason I'm trying to cut down on shitting because you
because I said something about the fact that like I like I am on the bathroom for three minutes
and then you get ulcers or whatever you said something effective or hemorrhoids hemorrhoids
yeah yeah yeah you said that and I was like oh shit is that true it is true it is true and I was
my doctor told me you know what you know where I got that information is from an xkcd comic
that I mean it was just a joke but it was a a graph that was showing like cases of dysentery
over the years and it goes from like the 1800s where it's way high up and then it goes down down
down down down and then it suddenly starts going way back up and it says invention of the laptop
yeah yeah I was like oh can you get dysentery from and let's get real let's get real precise
about what's going on you're getting shit in your body the poop is rising in a in a fine mist
or getting smeared around because you're wiping improperly it's getting on your shit and then
entering your body through one of your orifices again and making you sick do you like eating poop
if not don't sit on the toilet too long after shitting get the hell out of there it's gross
don't do it I do it too but I fight it so hard I know I know I can't pry myself off sometimes
this is why I hate I hate smokers so much because when I was in like working in retail
because they always have this get out of jail free card of I gotta go have a smoke and I always hated
my employees who smoke because they could use this anytime I can only say I gotta go take a shit so
many times per day but these motherfuckers get double the breaks with their fucking smoke breaks
why do they get to kill themselves and get rewarded for it motherfuckers get out your candy
cigarettes my head gotta go gotta take a smoke break boy I will go ironically smoke my candy
cigarettes while while leering at everyone with my with my dreamworks face you know every 20 minutes
at work that'll go great as a bonus just a just a little tidbit just a little piece of information
for you that if you think taking a shit feels good that is gay yeah oh well I don't but I don't
think that's possible because I don't believe in the prostate okay well I don't I think anyone that
says they like lies lying yeah what's really you know I don't usually think it feels good I don't
usually think it feels good to shit just for this one day only I felt gay for some reason like
there's just oh my god it felt like I felt extremely gay just for something would you say
that you were gay for a day I think that might be accurate I think that might be wait yeah yeah
I think that's right on the money right there obviously we don't know all the details but
ladies this very day I wake up and I see a fucking a scheduled video I've never clicked reminder so
fucking fast on a on a fucking thing because I bet you guys years ago at radicon 3 I bet this
would never happen I said to you too I said this will not happen to our faith it's too ambitious
you will never do it and I don't know what it's gonna be but Jesus Christ what is that what's
what's about to happen I want to say to correct you real quick Nate because it's not a scheduled
video it's a live stream this is a live concert that you will be able to watch it we're gay for
one day only today exactly oh I didn't know I oh my god that's even better so this is this is the
one you know England concert exclusive you know maybe we should maybe we should literally make it
unlisted after it's gay for one day that's not a bad idea for one dude this is literally like that
one time only Beatles on top of that rooftop event that like only the literally Illuminati was invited
to do or whatever anyone who's listening to this podcast will have missed it so lol yeah ha ha
I there is there is a secret playlist on the pcb of unlisted videos maybe it's there you will
never know you will never tell we'll we'll never I mean it won't be unlisted they're just saying
you would have missed it live well I mean they were saying it might be unlisted which would be epic
meme you know you hear gay for a day and you think ha ha silly as we when we walked in we
walked into the Abbey Road recording studios right and then and then as we walked out we looked at
each other and just started saying gold solid gold gold solid gold over and over increasing the volume
over and over and over again because it was true it's so much more than any of us could have predicted
or imagined and it's actually real and go to the video somewhere if you're able to do so
three hours from right now in my life and that's fascinating yeah uh as as I was just
like an actual explanation gay for a day is a music project uh that me and munchie cooked up at
radcon three well not not me me and hippo didn't make this art the band sleep tight made oh yes
our band sleep tight consisting of us it's it's low buys for the modern age
sleep tight okay sleep tight um we came up with this idea at radcon three we came up
with lyrics gay for a day what would happen if you were gay for a day one day just for one day the
album um the other day like yesterday or two days ahead was finished shot to be gay would you take
it exactly literally yes we have recorded um an album and then we're going to do a live stream and
have that be like the live version of the album yeah and then maybe do like a remastered version
later where like it's actually like good no listen it's good i mean it's good it's good but it's very
like like sleet oh yeah i'm a little i'm almost a little shocked i mean we've been we've been supposed
to keep this under wraps since uh since radcon two we haven't been supposed to talk about one word to
anyone yeah yeah this has been a tightly kept secret a sleeply tightly kept secret yes a trade
secret a tightly slept secret um well it i wouldn't be so ready to talk about it if not for the fact
that like it is done and in the past and not only since that when you're hearing this it will be in
the past but also in the sense that we have already recorded a version so literally if i like die right
now if like both of us die right now the album will still exist so it is literally out
was this at all part of the plan when you went to england and whatnot uh i i'm not not really it was
just sort of like what better time than yeah exactly right now to yeah yeah absolutely fascinating
especially when we are able to enlist the talents of of your brothers who are musical genius genius
yeah the the musical genius and hgb guy who you may know yes the chas uh the chas made that one
road toad's video game that played in rfck one time yep of course of course and and uh a run
away from snakes yes famous uh bail jade video game and a hgb guy is like hgb guy is the best
savage comment responder in the entire world yes he is a hero he's a god damn hero he's communist
a frame he is uh he is neo gay lord nelson in rfck and he is a beloved creature and everyone loves him
i i love that's true like cryptid of the modern age oh and he has a really strange youtube channel
which uh if you like like weird shit that like is no it's like give and take sort of tear like uh
this would not like make it anywhere on youtube content but like much stranger and much cooler
seeing your brother what's what's the youtube is it called hgb guy uh i think so probably there's
kind of corona on there too if you're if you're from way back but right right seeing your brothers
together was incredible because you really are like the manifestation of both of them hippo you
were like like henry or hgb guy is like if you just were fucking hit with some sort of bizarre
like wizard spell and now you're completely off the rails in every way and and and the chas
is like if you were like restraining you got like a like a five to nine well-paying job and you
became a construction worker like normal person and the intersection of those two are you yeah
literally yeah they're they're very cool they are very cool and i like them so anyway sleep tight
gay for a day full album high quality in the past get fucked kill yourself damn oh i can't believe
i live to see the day you know you know going back to the shit you know the the shit conversation
really good but i just feel like the the shit needs something like if i had like an extra like
letter in there somewhere if you know like shit if there was some sort of like shirt conversation
we could be having right i totally forgot i like these i like these glances you're giving me
yeah i don't know what i'm supposed to add to that i wasn't sure if we were gonna use the gay for a
day to transition into you guys talking about you're more than one day of gay together but we
can do shirts for us yeah i know you want to talk about shirts and ben was was winging uh
justly that teespring earlier before we recorded so all right shirts are big news they're big news
in shirtland let me tell you right now there is seven hundred and fifty dollars sitting in my
PayPal right now mm-hmm on the basis of selling about fifteen shirts was there zero before or was
there seven hundred forty nine okay just check you say there's seven hundred dollars because you
sold fifteen shirts somewhere around there well this seems like that's like a thousand dollars
a shirt what are you talking about uh no i'm selling shirts for thirty dollars each okay okay
don't ask me to math that shit out i have however much well some of them were 40 because of
international shipping look okay the cost of producing one shirt like the full cost of just
the production of the shirt before shipping is about five dollars mm-hmm shipping in the us costs
five dollars how much was the device the device is a hundred and forty okay one time that's not bad
at all no that's that's let that's a lot less than i thought and however the result can just use an
iron but uh yeah the results are great they're uh perfect i mean i need to pre wash my shirts because
the first round i did i didn't and some of the graphics got a little scuzzy after being washed
but um yeah so i bought these transfer papers there i you can get a pack of like 16 transfer
papers they're like a dollar a piece basically um but if you buy in bulk you know the price goes down
marginally um one the the most expensive part of the process really is the ink i mean it's
pretty much like a dollar or two per shirt when you consider because printing these things will
shoot through your ink depending on the design i mean my design is really complicated it has
lots of colors in it and it's it's huge but like all told again the total cost of production
of one shirt is like five bucks i can sell them for thirty dollars um you know take away the five
dollars of shipping that's twenty dollars of profit per shirt as opposed to the two to five
that you will get on teespring and people are way more likely to buy them because i'm selling them
like i'm hand making them i'm writing my name on them in uh in paint so like a shirt paint
uh huh so i'm just saying uh this is the way to do shirts like well quick question quick question
fuck spread shirt this is the way to do shirts i hear you but what is the time investment per
shirt uh 20 seconds okay once you got your operation running okay i mean because you you
do have to print i mean if printing one paper can take a few minutes i mean you don't have to do
anything you just hit print yeah and you wait but if you print like a hundred that's just slightly
more work like like an extra click and then it takes a couple minutes for the heat press to heat up
but obviously you would just do them in bulk but you literally to to print this is how printing a
shirt works you take a piece of transfer paper print an image onto it you put that shirt on a
just on the base of the heat press put the design on top of it close the heat press for 20 seconds
open it and you're done like that is it i mean it's literally just an iron it's just a big flat
iron that's easier to use than like trying to you know smoothly because like if you use an iron
it's hard to get it even you know but i mean you can look up a tutorial it's not that difficult
people do it all the time with just an iron but like it's only 140 bucks for a shirt press that will
always give you the same result um yeah i don't know it's pretty fucking easy like the most time
consuming part is just going to the post office uh i mean i was inspired just because i lived with
tom and who of course was doing this for iam games and like seeing how easy it was for him to do and
i had always just assumed that shirt presses were expensive but i overheard him telling ben
that they were like 200 dollars or something like that which i didn't even pay that much to pay like
150 mines perfectly fine um yep yeah as soon as i heard that i was like oh fuck it's only a hundred
you've already recouped that why am i yeah i recouped it with several well i recouped that on
my fucking test run because i initially printed like eight um i just had like i had some papers and
i had just whatever ink was left in my cartridge and i did a bunch of test runs my printer was
fucking up so i had all these misprints but they all looked really aesthetic and cool so i sold
all the misprints to my patrons and uh they were gone instantly it was like i posted a picture of
like eight designs and within like 20 minutes i'd sold them all that already recouped the cost of
the t-shirt press so um yeah all right like the the only unfortunate part is like i can't really do
colors other than white although there are like there's different types of papers you can use to
do different colors i think um but i mean if you're doing something like endless war like t-shirts i
cannot imagine a better way and also part of my inspiration to even do this type of stuff was ben
when he did the vapors comic because when i saw that he shipped them in those cool black envelopes
with like the white writing on them i was like oh that's the coolest thing ever that like i i wish
i had bought that so i could have that presentation you know yeah a little yeah a little trade secret
there um be cool and look stylish all the time no i know personality goes a long way yeah uh
vapors two kickstarter coming soon question mark
hey you know i did have one strong thought about this um uh this isn't to shit on may specifically
it's to shit on you digi but that the very beginning of your t-shirt video that little joke
quote unquote joke that you do of the like focus on may's chest where she's like where are you looking
that was the most reddit tier normie god awful like are you saying entry-level anime quote unquote
joke are you ever seen in my life and i wanted to die are you saying that digi posted cringe and
will lose subscribers yeah namely me namely me i uh so i condemn you for your terrible joke did
i did that just because i had the camera pointed at her tits and then i went wait i'm sure you did
i'm pointing the camera at your tits you should say something about it that would be funny
no you don't acknowledge it you leave it for the audience to have their own thoughts on
yes that's correct that's correct what what what thoughts do you think would be uh would be namely
there look you you guys know that was an awful joke i wanted to die i wanted to i've never seen
you know everyone says digi's not funny blah blah blah i don't even totally agree with that
this was the least funny thing i've ever seen in my entire life i wished i was dead instead of
and that's not even against me it's against you digi you're the man in charge of this joke
and i blamed you 100 i did tell her what to say exactly exactly any treats women like objects
telling them what to do yeah i'm a feminist what did you think about the part at the end where i was
counting down the uh the shirt press that i'm going with thousand what with thousand two was that funny
um well i'm afraid that when i saw this video was 15 minutes long i thought there's no chance
i'm watching all the way into the end of this video i don't even think it's 10 well no no you're
right it is over it's 15 minutes never mind uh okay but i mean you know that's that's fine that's
fine i got my my my bugbear off my back thank god i i don't know what youtube is anymore especially
now that i'm here in the nether world in the in uh just farming meh nether rack and nether
works day and day over in england yet i don't think they have that i know they have nether
portals right now right now i'm jumping in and out of other portals to speak to you like a real
life name right now jumping in and out of everywhere you have to jump out of the nether portals like
in binary code to to you know convey your internet presence yeah that's good that's good uh but uh
you know what we're good at it uh i love right dear jokes so please don't up my plan
max
real um but bin what what do you think i mean i mean apparently shirt prices are uh
cost nothing are nothing and are just more romantic and better okay um well wait at well i
i think depending on i thought it was a big problem it doesn't sound like it reduces the overhead
from teespring by that much wait what what do you mean teespring is the only overhead is only
like 10 bucks per shirt and that includes and that includes shipping wait how much do you make per
shirt uh depend uh about 10 bucks okay because i'm making 20 by selling them for 30 dollars
well we sell ours for 20 so there you go well i mean it's all about how many you're able to sell
and whatnot yeah i mean you know because the thing about teespring is that they have the better
turnover but they also have the shittiest shirts and like they i like i look maybe i'm crazy i love
my classic v-necks that i got from teespring though i think you're crazy my shirts suck my
shirts fucking suck from teespring well you you didn't get the classic v-neck did you i didn't
get the classic v-neck i can't imagine it would always go for the classic v-neck i legitimately
love my classic v-neck you're gonna have a classic fucking no-neck once i whack your fucking head off
i i i i guess i can't argue i guess i can't argue with that i don't know i couldn't care less
about t-shirt quality i've wore terrible shirts for years and years just because i like the anime
logo on them so i don't know that's that's all i need i used to wear i'm really in a need for cool
shirts i really like i have a lot of t-shirts right fine my slime corp shirt i don't know where
it is it's been missing for like a month let me in one fell swoop completely sell you on the
shirt press though because the best part is not the money i make off of it it's not printing
shirts for fans it's not making my own designs and signing them it's that i can just make my own
shirts for myself of anything i want yeah i can just print any random bullshit out of shirt
immediately when i jump to immediately yeah uh because i fucking printed i made myself a
did you guys see my fourth of july shirt no i did i don't think so my god let me send it to you
please here we go it's my miracle show notes show notes um no i should post it in the gross
disgusting audio okay i see it i see you're gonna want to look at this in full size to to be able
to read the text and all the extra stuff but this i for the fourth of july i was like i need a special
shirt so i printed this unfortunately i printed it backwards however thanks to the magic of the
internet you're all seeing it the way it should oh good is that baracko trump hole it's yeah it's
trump trump bomb i literally just googled trump mama and got exactly what i wanted
oh you got the the comic my favorite comic of all time where george washington and ben franklin
smoke weed together and he says get money fuck bitches smoke trees um it's got you know a rainbow
murica with with uh with fucking right i'm gay i dubs on it uh the pansu party quote which i actually
misquoted i wrote the american flag the american flag is an autistic concept it was actually the
original quote is america is an autistic concept and the flag is to help normie's understand it
hmm more nuanced yeah way to way to contribute to the continual degradation of the discourse
yeah uh well forgive you and there's a beer and a well i'm basically sold for my own self so good
job digi yeah this is so i mean that was i can't imagine being able to just like print my own design
which is what i literally just want to do that's what i've always wanted to do yeah like i want to
have a whole wardrobe of like i want to have a shirt that just says i disagree on it every every
time every time i think of a shirt that i want to make that i'm like ah but i'd have to pay it
cost me like 10 bucks it cost me like 10 bucks to make it and order it for myself on teespring or
whatever i guess i could shrink that well i would always make that money right the profit would go
to myself so what i what i would just what i shrink that cost i could shrink that amount if i owned
a tea that honestly that actually would and the best part is that i just had all these materials
because like i'm already preparing to sell a bunch of shirts to fans and then i'm just like hey let me
just dip into my fucking supply here grab one of these larges grab one of these papers print one
for myself fucking wear it on america trump obama that's good uh you know i'm just a controversial
opinion but uh you look damn good in this picture did you look at that thick head of hair look at
that short i gotta tell you let me see look at the vibrant colors of his lips i gotta say very
appealing yeah yeah you do you do hold on i was gonna say why do you look like victor in this picture
why do you just look like you turned into you you're like half victor you guys you you just
went down it looks like someone trump bombed you with victor yeah i need to send you the full
story so this is going to have to go with the show notes as well so before that picture existed
mere seconds before i had you know i i want i had this shirt i wanted to tweet about it
so i took a selfie of myself in the shirt trying to emphasize the graphic so you would
you'd be able to read it so here's the picture that i tweeted initially
yeah okay which is this is like are you familiar with the hideo and kojima memes of uh
it's like that it's like that i don't see it where is it it's in gross disgusting audio links
that's the yeah um so this that was the first picture i posted then may look at his instagram
right here angles angles and filters yeah may was just like oh that looks like shit let me
take another picture where you look good so she just yeah just changed the angle slightly and because
i'm not holding the camera i had all of my body to pose and uh yeah that was just that's the difference
that a camera angle makes fascinating i don't even know okay but the first one shows the shirt
there's no filter at all so it's just uh it's just the camera angle and being a forward facing
camera versus a uh outer camera as you look you look you look you look almost as stylish as
nathan masry founder of garfield eats okay look at tiny mouth true look at just the change of position
makes digi looks so much slimmer like his jawline looks so much more defined his skin is like glowing
and looks like tanned and vibrant which indicates health like his lips are brighter like everything
about that this is this is a fascinating contrast is he single specifically look at the difference
in your beard it looks so much smoother and fuller in the second one it's a different way i'm
blown away by this the first one was taken from a low angle and the second one was yeah from a high
angle which i you know i always make sure in all of my videos that i'm looking up at the camera
because the only way i look good i don't have a very well-defined jaw so like you have to see me
from above to get that definition but um the fact that i look also like 30 pounds lighter is particularly
hilarious it's incredible uh life is a crime and this is a lie uh everything is fake nothing is real
all observation is just uh what's the word non-objective based on our position in the
universe relativistic whatever and this is just uh the person the putting subjective that's the
word i was looking for buffalo new york lifelong pokemon fan neil ferraro threw away the chance to
teach his level 63 venomoth quiver dance in pokemon ultra sun after deciding it was total
garbage as a result of dealing no damage according to those familiar raises the users a special
attack special defense and speed by one stage power zero what the fuck who would want to raise an
attack when you can just do an attack for our reportedly said before choosing to keep twister
due to its tornado animation what's uh what's that ben what's the story there
oh i'm just reading the hard times dot net uh i saw an article absolutely useless pokemon attack
doesn't even do damage and i thought this is an outrage all right hey hey ben speaking and looking
30 pounds uh lighter what's what's going with you and q are you still are you still quarreling
or the lovers have they reunited oh i'm back no i went back on keto and i lost like 10 pounds
instantly and yeah i'm down to like 157 so pretty good pretty good uh not as interesting what was
the origin of your stint there like why why were you questioning it it wasn't quit i just i just
fucking stopped doing it for a minute and then i got fat and i was like well fuck this yeah this is
uh this is not as interesting there's no narrative here but i have been counting my calories 100%
accurately well 99% probably for the last several days and uh have not lost the 25 pounds i hope to
yet but one step at a time and uh i'm i'm doing it last the time has come i'm cooking my own food
i'm dieting as well as i i broke 180 and uh a lot of my pants are not fitting right
they're enough yeah you sure you shrinkin you shrinkin no i need to i think he's going the
opposite direction he's saying oh i'm about to attempt shrinking because my pants are
fucking oh i see i see um well hey if you guys need any hot tips i'm all i'm always available i
i think there's no there's no better weight loss motivation than just keep your wardrobe fitting
like i used to always wear just like xls and double xls and shit and so like it never made a
difference but if you buy all large and like stuff that just fits and then you start getting fat you
immediately are like wow i can't wear any clothes now so i have i have a bunch of underwear and a
couple of pairs of shorts that are like ah i can't wear these anymore i'm too skinny but then i have
a couple that are so huge that i'm like these could i could never possibly have worn the i have a pair
of shirts that's like waistband size 42 and i'm like this was this was never this was never me
what was what was going on here i'm just finding a bunch of like oversized shit in my drawer and
i don't know why it's there i could never have worn it our parents just gave us some shit back in the
day i don't know if it fits under that category i don't know maybe yeah maybe boy it would have
had been kicking around for a long ass time if that's the case i i've been orbiting uh fitness
in one particular way and i've been thinking recently because there's going to be a gym
inside my dorm like just literally inside of there you go no excuses yeah yeah i've been
thinking myself oh yeah there's one thing i want to get fit in there's exactly one way and that's
i've always been destined from the day i was born and i've known this fact that i was always meant to
be a barra munchie barra was what was in the universe's plans when i was spawned
and for me to not be a barra specifically a strong fat barra like i want to be fat munchie but also
just to be a barra big man that is what i was meant to be and i i've been thinking it might be time
to achieve it uh yeah specifically but i'm fucking referring to you dumb piece of shit all right
munchie this should be you this is a this is a famous guy from uh let me see this is going
to gross disgusting yeah there it is this is a famous guy from uh fate zero it's alexander the
great in fate style he is he's number one daddy in uh in the fate universe and this should be you
in a few short years this could easily be you sir uh it might be it might be maybe yeah he could be
the next we'll see personality wise you would love him as well i mean he is a great guy all around
and he loves anime and he loves history uh so that's cool i mean he is history he is well okay
why is why is it why is it what does that what does that mean by the way why is he alexander the
great well i mean in fate in fate stay night they summon heroes from the past like fight in modern
day and they just they summon alexander the great and that's him that's you know okay that's him
cool he he trains this little bitch boy uh waver and to be a man coming of a not baby bitch and now
waver has his own spinoff show that just started this season did you know that oh really yeah there's
no is it is it at all good i never actually liked waver that much the first episode's pretty good
i mean it's him like all grown up he's like long haired he's all like i have to be better to like
live up to fucking alexander's teachings and that you know that's pretty cool alexander was so popular
i can imagine a lot of people would be like yeah continue it's almost like like simone kind of
carrying on like comment is like it's just it's presented exactly as that like yeah monchi i can
get into that uh speaking of that um kazzie was here on the fourth of july for our fourth of july
party which was not much of a party but whatever and uh she wants because we have we have a weight
rack in her brain she was telling me about how you guys are gonna have like access to a gym next
year and and uh she wanted to use she wanted to use the weight rack in our basement because
she doesn't have access to one right now so uh yeah we're we're lifting buddies now
can i be on that yeah absolutely oh yeah oh this is perfect yeah it'll be uh it'll be just like
when me and digi used to fucking squat together uh in the garage guys just just when you picture
someone squatting and spotting someone squatting i just i doubt too many people out there have the
visual imagine a man like just bent over knees been ass stuck out as far as it can and imagine a
man literally sandwiched dick to ass right behind him caressing him and making the most you know
ecstasy filled face as you go down and up it's worth that and i never actually like
properly spotted each other on squatting it was not like we just watched the other person do it and
we were just there in case they dropped it and we needed to call
911 there was one time i got stuck down and ben kind of sort of helped me mostly i just kind of
fell to the side and dropped the bar it's what i don't do that whole spotting shit um it's not
it's not my style i know i've talked about this before no you gotta no you gotta stand behind
you gotta stand behind on the bench you gotta hold your hands under the bar like oh it's all you
bro it's all you bro two just for sweet nothing three more three more it's all you i'm not touched
in the bar i'm not touching the bar this is all you this is all you bro one more come on come on
lock those not those elbows out i'm not touching it's all you bro that's what i'm in it for unironically
those things can be helpful uh yeah sure i yeah kind of having a lifting buddy is a good thing
which i've never ever in my entire life had although one time i have uh i was just like
all that's i was the man you would not have wanted ben as a lifting buddy because ben was in the middle
of texting uh his girlfriend in between every single set i mean sure and it's one of those things
where it's like a set only takes about you know 20 seconds but texting takes about a minute and a
half when you're ben yes i like to work out alone uh and i i'm i'm thrilled that that i've had the
ability to do so primarily but uh there have been some times where like i'm benching and i'm i'm doing
a little bit too much and that bar gets down to my chest and i'm like oh no i can't i'm this is it
it is 100 over for me i was a good run uh i will be dead momentarily uh but have you ever had to do
this ben you probably have like sometimes sometimes people will be on it and they'll come and help
you and it's a little embarrassing but i appreciate the gesture but more often than that you do the
little wiggle where you slowly work it down your torso like crushing every muscle as it goes and
you kind of you're able to sit up it's resting on like your little i don't know the the joint between
your your waist whatever and you yeah get out under it the dick yes the dick as it's colloquially
known and uh it's it's a very painful shameful experience but yeah i've done that it sucks it's
not it's not fun it's not fun but just so on the squad anything i was just gonna say that i once
squatted uh i'm probably the strongest man i've ever seen in my gym was a guy i went to high school
with and we were at our we are at the ymca that i worked at in my hometown and where he would work
he was squatting around 500 pounds or more uh he was he's a gigantic man and like he he was like
hey dude i'm about squat would you spot me i'm like a baby in high school what am i supposed to do
if you're squatting 500 pounds i got right up in there i mean because like he can do most of it
obviously it's just that if he needs it he wants a little bit of help which i can kind of provide
so i'm right up on him like dick to ass i'm feeling the strength of a man it's fueling me the musk
is filling my nostrils and i'm feeling true euphoria at this moment as he goes down and up
down it up us grinding against each other oh my god that's when i knew that the greek lifestyle
was the only lifestyle for me um and uh it was it was euphoric simmer down so i can say i have
squatted 500 pounds uh come at me gays i'm stronger than you yep so that's it that's it that was fun
one day i'll make uh i'll make uh one day my son will be there to spot me in the same way and
we'll be bonded as you know blood you you you won't hear any updates on on the munchie bar front
for for many of an episode of the pcp week because i'm gonna be fucking way too doing anything to
even attempt to even know how to begin but i i i will you know what munchie barra munchie barra
is the new storyline i'm gonna commit right here and you know what that storyline may it may
burn up and die and it may become a failure and that's the point of it do you know how unbelievably
powerful munchie barra would be like munchie's already like a force to be reckoned with like
a human wrecking ball on wheels yeah if he has muscles as well like he could probably punch
a building in half like i can't even imagine anything you wouldn't be able to do did did you
i remember i won the first like digi bros like after like you met me the second time at broding
con there was a digi bros reflecting upon the broding con and you're describing as like as like
an unbelievable tank slash a wrestler like some sort of like a bizarre yeah i've always thought you
needed to be a pro wrestler like if you were muscular you would easily be a pro wrestling
personality so you know there's another guy i think it might become real there's another guy
i just remembered about that you should also aspire to be munchie this is this is even more
famous than alexander and it's just it's the uh the husband from full metal alchemist who has a
big belly i was thinking of the same exact yeah that guy yeah that guy is your barra whenever i
think barra i think i think the blacksmith guy from full metal alchemist yeah yeah this is the
ideal this is the ideal right here can you imagine can you literally imagine you can't you can't you
you know i feel such envy i am limited by my genetics you know i've uh i'm of average height
basically i will never be the towering adonis to like a um what's his face uh fucking uh
armstrong no not armstrong uh who's the real life arm's horse nigger that's what i'm thinking of
just the biggest widest man in the planet but you munchie you have you have all the potential
in the world to be literally the biggest man on the planet and you could be you could be
one of the small weak guys from baki the grappler you could be one of like the tiny pathetic ones
on that show you know i was just looking at it like i was going uh i don't know whatever i was
looking at fitness stuff and i just saw like there's like a some fitness youtube guy who was
like a marine or something and there was just a video of him competing against like i think
literally like the winner of like world strongman competition just like this is a guy if you saw the
marine on the street you'd think holy shit that guy's huge compared to the other guy it was like
looking at a child versus an adult that man was so unbelievably jiggy we're talking like like
six nine or something and like probably 400 pounds just a monster and uh that could be you
that could be you and i hope to see it look out very soon munchie shasky's in town that that second
puberty is coming hard and when it hits it's funny it's funny when you watch you watch a basketball
and everyone playing seems normal because their only reference point is each other yeah and they're
all enormous and then you see them like next to regular people next to like the coach or whatever
and you see and they're like like regular people like come up to like their nipples and it's like
okay all right i see what we're dealing with here i accept my role to be genetically removed
from the gene pool you it's true you guys deserve to reproduce and i do not i get it you're king of
the menlets aren't you aren't you you're king of the man no i mean does the future does the future
really have a place for tall people like uh you know we we don't need to be physically strong to
survive anymore and the overpopulation is putting us into denser and denser human clusters do we not
need overpopulation is a myth overpopulation is a fucking i need a little bit of myth god damn it
god damn it i'm well listen when the bombs drop and it's us against us as nature always intended
we'll see who ends up on top and it won't be the guy when the bombs drop anybody who's tall enough
to see over a wall will be evaporated but like there'll be much like in barefoot again us small
people will just hide behind a chest high wall and we'll be fine in a minecraft hunger game scenario
what the with the pcp as the only players who would come out first in a in a minecraft hunger
game specifically well the the the different areas like you already know because we have the arena
so we know who survives that no that doesn't they're guns that no it's a man man e-man just
complete it has to be dominance physically well the the the thing you gotta account for in minecraft
you gotta account for for trickery and and stratagem and alliances which could absolutely form
let's say if like munchie might have a big advantage against like gibb for example but if
like everyone was team gibb and we said we will feast on munchie's corpse then obviously we have
you know the the edge there and we can uh so you know things like that i don't even know if we do
have the edge there i feel like i can imagine just swatting us away like flies like donkey kong
yeah it's like throwing us 20 feet i think munchie could see tomorrow night when we're all shipped
off to the fucking minecraft world to get out when battle royale happens pcp battle royale that
will be our next uh you know thing dude oh okay i'm sure today that's before but there's nothing
i love more than like physically beating someone up like i'm not joking right now we're like trying
to like make a joke that's why you need to be a pro wrestler god damn fighting people it like it
actually makes me feel so good like munchie unironically someone as hard as i can unironically
you me everyone else on the planet should do some type of contact sport like uh like people
really like brazilian jujitsu it's not as dangerous i mean it's really not that dangerous at like the
level that most people do it and the feeling of like there's something so lost in our modern society
of not physically engaging with each other which frankly i think is mad gay it's way less gay to
be all up on your bros and be comfortable like there's a thing of like ooh i don't want to touch
anybody ooh that's uh that's weird and gross i don't ever do it you should people should be more
comfortable with that in my humble opinion i think we're all singing all dancing crap of the world
exactly got a form fight club when i was a kid when i was in like like middle school and elementary
school i used to wrestle with my friends all the fucking time and i want to get way up on top of
them and i would be shirtless and i'd be so fucking fat that i would just like jump up and down on
their chest make them hyperventilate and i would be like oh i win the game and then i would just
like keep on being them even though they aren't even responding to me anymore it was so good the
adrenaline was pumping i was so fucking sweaty and i felt so good because all my friends were just
white twink and i was obliterating them i was reading the world of the of the right ways one
evil seed at a time it was already i was already splattered in blood but my fists just kept hammering
and hammering away uh good time hey uh let me capture it total left turn but uh you feel any
of those earthquakes out there in california munch that i've been oh wait you're not in california
right yeah yeah i'm not yeah yeah shit no i know i know you're referring to be because not only did
my mom text me saying this there's an earthquake but then hippo's mom like a minute later said did
you know there was an earthquake in california uh yeah so i've heard about them uh we get we get
like earthquakes literally like every day it's not a big deal i know when i was in when i was in
california when i was a tutor at astro camp one day i like you know i slept in and then i went to
like fucking like a councilor mess hall or whatever and i'm eating my i don't know my bullshit like
salisbury steak or whatever and everyone's like oh did you guys hear did you guys feel those
earthquakes this morning and i'm like what because i'd always wanted to feel what an earthquake
felt like because i've never felt one but i literally slept through one and uh now i'll never
get the chance when i never experienced an earthquake before no they don't happen they don't
happen on the east coast dude on the east on the east coast never there ain't no fault lines on the
east coast okay wait has anyone felt them besides when i when i went to tokyo i won't i won't say every
night but like to like japan is formed due to volcanic activity due to fault lines is directly
over them that's why it exists i felt them for the first time and frequently at night and i felt
so small and so powerless before the might of the planet moving underneath me it was a very uh
humbling experience but yeah i obviously that they're they're different you know ranges of how
powerful earthquakes are yeah but even like the small ones like it literally feels like just shake
your body up and down like your your like head that's what it like looks like to have an earthquake
happen yeah like the entire room and ground around you shakes and things like fall off your
shelves and like things can break you know there was another time like if if it's like a particularly
powerful one like in like like look up like i mean teleporting is famous for earthquakes like look
up like the san francisco and like la uh earthquakes those like obliterated entire fucking like cities
like countless city blocks obliterated you know when i was quick so just wipe things off them out
at my last apartment uh in sincenady um there was uh there was a big flood that i've talked about
that i got into the local news for yeah i know i've talked about that before it was pretty pretty
funny but like and the the car at the bottom of the hill got straight up completely covered in
water there might have been a little of the roof poking out but that car was destroyed and uh it
was fucked up and it just that was such a the the water the amount of water just going by on the
street luckily my car was parked at the top of the hill and it was totally fine but i thought to myself
my car will not survive if i attempt to escape this area therefore all i can do is stay okay now
that that's established the water is slowly rising more and more towards my apartment i will not be
able to escape and it's coming towards me more and more i live on the first floor of this building
the basement is filled with water right now there is no escape and i just thought well
i could die today um and there's nothing i can do but i will just sit here and hope it doesn't
happen and that's exactly what i did and it was fine it wasn't that big a deal but it was that and
like the earthquakes in japan were the two most in awe of the planet and in awe of nature experiences
i i have felt personally and it was sure was fucked up bro i want to live i don't want to die
i wanted to fight but there was literally nothing i could do like fighting the ocean or you know
whatever she was crazy she was crazy uh huh yep yep i don't know yep uh oh you know what i was
gonna say though the earthquake was a missed opportunity i wish i wish i'd felt it but i slept
through it uh you'll get a chance there'll be more chances um uh but but you know what i was gonna
say come out to the san yago conben just come on out dude sounds so hard here he was my theory
though here was my theory on the earthquakes my thought was that this was god's judgment against
anime expo taking place this was my theory because it is uh there's too many humans and it's too
shitty yeah i mean i think you might have ended by now but it's are you sad you missed it i'm
fainting right now oh i didn't i thought you i figured you knew no i i should i should know it's
it's always at the same time every year yeah oh man you know what you missed uh i'm i'm i'm i'm a
hippocon right now and you know what that's that's true you you missed the um the premiere of uh new
gern logan kill kill production promare that just aired in the in the thing i was i was there last
year and i got into like the first screening of like they were talking about it and they were and
i got to see the first screen of grid man uh right right it was great last time instantly
they're gonna play promari at otacon too so i get to see it there yeah oh that's that's i you know
somebody somebody tweeted me like net you getting tickets and i was like oh there's tickets so i went
and bought tickets september like 19th or something i will be going seeing not the dub that is available
because fuck that but the subtitled version uh can't wait can't wait though you know so okay where
where's otacon where's otacon baltimore dc this uh oh now okay uh wait when uh the 20 the like last
weekend of this month uh yeah it's pretty man fuck you guys not everyone i wish i had known like it
took them extra long to get the uh because i was like basically i'm not going if i don't get a press
badge and it took them a really long time to get the press badges out but i i did get one so
hey so i guess you're not blacklisted yeah no how nice uh yeah it's july 26 through 28th um
i still haven't got a hotel situated yet though so i need to do that gotta gotta work i i i i i
i'm craving the con experience and thankfully even though i missed an expo i won't be able to go
to otacon like how i would have liked to do either one of those uh all of us besides did you
will be a brony con yep at the at the at the beginning of next month yo my crazy we uh i've
got tickets uh to brony con we have to get plane tickets and uh and a place we're gonna stay but
we were looking at probably do that today or something but we were looking at arabian bees
in the area and first of all let me tell you guys arabian bees are the way of the future hotels
can literally die and go away forever i don't care about them anymore they're shit they're a meme
they're a fad and they are obsolete you can just you can get like some dude's house he's just out
of town you get a whole fucking house which is full of cool things to touch and look at and
experience and a new family to pretend is your family which i very much look forward to doing
and uh it's it's literally cheaper than like most hotels and it's just better in every way too
it's incredible it's incredible now i hope we'll be able to find one that's like relatively close
and still relatively cheap but hotels are a fucking scam don't don't do them don't do them
abolish them that's what i'm for wait wait give them back to the people i wasn't paying attention
what did you say to do instead of i'm saying arabian bees are great hotels are shit because
we were looking into doing an arabian bee and i was like i don't know because i don't know if i
trust like that in in washington dc but if you're if you're giving them the strength of why in
washington uh i don't know it's just for otacon scary dc is a pretty rough place from what i hear
yeah oh i i had no conception of such a thing i think it's one of the crime capitals of the
country like not like the very center where like the the fucking you know all the rich
white politicians are is very nice but like outside that it's apparently pretty rough victor when he
went to otacon last time gave me the impression that it was uh that it was not so that it was
kind of a janky and scary place in places i mean the con is like literally right behind
the white house it's like fucking a block away yo go say hi to drump for me dude let him know uh
you know let him know he's got my official endorsement that the pcp officially endorses
drump 2020 baby all of us are on board for this right right uh wait who are we telling who are
we're voting for drump fan thanks for signing off don't go away did you know every year every year
poor republicans vote for republican candidates we need to liberate them from their vote so they
don't make this mistake hey uh say is seeing as like every single topic that has been brought up
i have had absolutely nothing to say on anything sure and i feel stupid uh let's talk about like uh
munchie being at my house yes please what's going on sure uh i feel okay so so that there was one
big thing that happened while we were here was it the anifred redemption because i've heard a lot
of stories about this all right it was the anifred redemption i oh is that who that kid was in your
video yes okay so he was in fact like a 10 year old as i thought he is 13 okay um he is younger than
the teen cp god damn it might be more appropriate to say on the rfck about the bean up but i don't
care because we're just gonna talk about it now you know what the pcp needs more good topics or
i didn't talk about it an rfck thing and this is fitting this is fitting that we're talking about
here because this is there's pcb stuff here too it's the redemption of pcp fans in my mind
yeah it is the complete redemption of them as a concept because i was so racist towards them
and you know i still will be because i don't fully trust them i don't fully like trust people
who are just like into the pcp and not into rfck that's just like sort of like weird my brain
doesn't fully comprehend that's even possible of course of course but it made me really understand
that there can be good ones like there are like there's there's some of them yeah it was in the
in in in the mostly rotten patch of pcp fans there are a few good ones yeah it was it was a really
good con um literally everyone there was great and no one was annoying yeah there was not there was
not a single person who was like you know annoying but we couldn't bring ourselves to tell him you
know that sort of person who sometimes appears none of none of them were there with that guy and it
was just a delight the entire time to get some backstory because i feel like it's important
to understand like like the narrative arc of the con because it was you know of course a
rowdy fuckers cop clears con you know it was steep and lore and and lore things in rfck narrative
arc things happen within said con it was like an arg but in real life uh but but you know i
i guess so so wait so so you're saying it was just an arg yeah it was an arg it was a real game yeah
and and and so uh i i nest on the pcb is i mean oh maybe like one or two people will want to come
to this from the pcb and they'll be able to be you know indoctrinated into rfck i thought that
was the plan is that it would be like you know because there are a lot of our european rfck
players you know they're shouting yeah there's magic there's a lot of people i thought would be
coming uh none of them came besides magics and it was like ten hardcore pcb heads you're not gonna
believe this but there was at least one person who was just a knight head oh my god what was he
doing there the most oppressed minority we have to liberate them it's not fair wait when you say he
was just a knight head do you mean that he like didn't even watch the pcb well no he he described
himself as a knight yeah he introduced himself as a knight and he did expect the abuse okay
do you know his name i'm just curious who this person is his is cake okay okay this is internet
handle uh so so so we i post the link on the on the pcb channel people start with loading in with
was it they call him cake my favorite uh my favorite uh huge huge tits uh nsf w twitter artists
that's a god i don't know why you even just said that that's terrible anyway i don't know i just
wanted to plug my boy people started flooding in to the meetup channel and they all these anime
avatars they were saying memes and it was just oh god i can feel my life draining from my body
knowing that i was gonna have to interact with pcb fans and it was going to ruin my entire day
having to deal with like the meme or the antagonistic memers and the anime avatar of wielding mother
fuckers who uh watching pcb it's gonna be a nightmare i was dreading it and of course of
course any freddy it's called out for being the epitome of a pcb fan on this very show a couple
a couple episodes ago and you know i was dreading the entire experience but we get here we unload
and immediately you know there are people who are like oh yeah i'm a pcb head but you know i
had to very least i i checked out a little bit the wiki i checked out a little bit of you know i
joined the server and i read a little bit of orientation and i don't ask for much that display
of at least willingness that curiosity that that that that a gumption inside that entrepreneurial
spirit yeah literally yes they are able to recognize that you know you should at least try
to understand anything rfck that loosened me up a little bit and throughout the day as we
shared our pain our growing pains together all the joys and the ups and the downs that we experienced
throughout the day i became closer to these people and i consider i consider these misfits
these these uh these sicko fans these insane pcb heads who were sucking my dick the entire time i
consider them family you know what they were great they were great that's great beautiful beautiful
by the way i'm looking at this image gift posted of him in uh oh sorry the lord of ghosts and you
know i just know no this is very specific this is the cool lord of ghosts yeah sunglasses now
i just i want to mention ben wedges describing the picture let me finish describing the picture
yeah yeah on on the right is the cool lord of ghosts after the lord of ghosts got a fucked up
i'm in retreat the sewers we in the cool over ghosts he's just vacationing right yeah okay and
and next to next to him on the left is communist a frame who no no relation really yeah uh who has
who who went around all day wearing that and holding a boombox from the 80s that was playing
like radio static and then occasionally you can't inquire me by the way i just want to illustrate
that it was it was so hot that day and the and his hat was so tight that he had to leave the con
early and he threw up on the train back so that's dedication like a true communist way to go
fucking cool is that is that fucking ham palace yeah i was going to ask what's that yeah that's
in front of buckingham a proposal of everyone with with all with the the edited one where where
everyone's oh yeah i have i have been there i have seen that statue my own my own eyes yeah isn't that
isn't that cool to think that like you know in the same spot like if you trace like ben's like
path of life you would be able to intersect that with like yeah you know where these guys are
what do you call it my my uh donnie darko time worm extends through this zone oh that's pretty
sick i like that pretty cool you mean you're thin from the felt uh worm yeah okay i understand
yeah yeah yeah home a home stuck invented time travel um i don't know if you want to go through
beat by beat but there are some like like like notable events that have happened it was posting
right now in the show notes an ed version with everyone there this is great fantastic this yeah
we started at trafalgar square um we had a lot of adventures and just so happened to come back
to trafalgar square at night why we went to we ate at pubs we're munchie oh oh munchie all right
here's the thing munchies since he is uh 18 that is legal to drink in the uk oh so he had his first
pint of alcohol oh my god and i shugged it i i shugged it i didn't say that i shugged it oh my
god yeah oh my god i i was i was there i was there you know like i said um on the fourth of july
um kazzie was over and she told me about that and i was happy to know that you're in the doghouse
i'm happy to report you are now in the dog dude and much you're wearing the
i bought you as a birthday present that's yes i am oh ney ney i cherish the shirt so much i wear
all the fucking oh i'm so glad oh i'm so glad by the way shout out to chip wiseman who's looking
like a golden god of aesthetics first of all those glasses that hair quaffed ever so gracefully
loving it and that rad con three shirts impeccable fashion why why are there why are there girls here
that's a good question there were two whole girls it was incredible no it was like i was blown away
don't fucking don't hippo don't fucking sit there condescents don't fucking try and treat me like
i'm stupid okay no that's great that's great i don't recognize their names so i assume they're
lurkers uh but that's that's cool yes uh i didn't recognize a few of them uh because i didn't
recognize like any of them there's a bunch of names there's a bunch of names there's a bunch of
names i don't recognize you but that's i knew uh joe swoe from from chat things and chip and
i i i knew my good friend and and like and like refugee exile like you like from way back in the
day trackmaster four uh my literal god and son who has left uh the internet to do his own things
but left the internet i mean i just haven't seen him in a while so that was great and of course
of course uh my right hand man and brimstone programmer magix rambage there works in the game
magix by the way excruciatingly german by the way it's you can only see his face because he's
hidden by gibbon takes a nametag but he is like literally like craft work like if you
would condense craft work into like a human being that is him magix it was insane i couldn't believe
by the way magix got me magix uh messaged me about sly moids we talked about sly moids
because he i remember right from the very beginning magix was magix was all on
the sly moid update and sly and like maximizing his sly moid stats so he messaged me about it
yesterday and to talk about like updates and he got me into the new the devs or the new
i didn't realize i didn't realize that development had just like shifted to a new server i thought i
thought i was dead i told the steal a while ago but i can understand that it wouldn't have clicked
maybe i have well you well you told me that the new server was for like testing and i was like
well i don't yeah so i okay but whatever so i'm in there now let me give a quick verbal lashing
to farafrog bro what are you doing being like the kirito of the group get in there and get some skin
on skin contact my dude you should agree but on the other hand he looks like he looks like a little
baby yeah exactly no he wasn't he wasn't actually there this is a component i'll crop this in later
he voted you photoshopped him in yeah okay you know what now i see it now i see it who is who is that
kake made this and he photoshopped the people in who is left at this point the nade head making the
best content to come out of it that's what i like to see my who is who is that ghost who is that ghost
in the pillar that's got to be any friend of course yeah okay and at the bottom of course you
can see that antifred has been unblocked by the administrator oh so so to give more context on
antifred it in his journey so of course he gets called out mercilessly beaten and shackling crucified
on the pc and p in absolute like the passion on display there unrivaled and and so he sets out to
not become the of why i referred him as the epitome of our pc p fans okay the worst thing
that's so sad and and so i joined the surfer i don't trust him so i ban him i banish him immediately
yeah okay and and he says munchie how do i become a ratty how what can i do and i said you have to
prove to me that you're not a pcp head you have to recite to me one event from rfck history at
rfckcon just one that's all i asked for and and and then i'll know that you're not a pcp head
for you know what did he say the can the cancer is it isn't fully hit you and so and so he said okay
i'll do such we meet up in the beginning antifred comes over he says i have i have a speech prepared
and when i do it i need you to hold me up so everyone will hear and i said of course i wouldn't i
wouldn't plan anything other yeah so so it gets later in the day you know we're saving with the
perfect moment and and and we are outside the the british museum in front of like a crowd of people
there like like behind us this is like big public square and then i hold up antifred and you are
able to see the photos and videos of such antifred's redemption where he just reads aloud a a wiki
article that he had memorized about the food shortages the first line the first line of which
is after bin sain raises food prices to ludicrous levels a strike conducted socialism at work ladies
and gents speak speaking of which munchie i've had this idea this past week i i want to like wouldn't
it be great i know i want to make it communism i want to make communism in uh rfck like like i i don't
i was thinking about how i could do it but no no no no shut up i mean i was thinking about ways
that i could do it on on the killers only but i was like well would it be unbalanced i was just
thinking about like what if we like what if we had like uh i don't know some sort of like we just
changed how like killer slime calculation works so that like it was like the average of all killers
or something or like some fraction of the team of like the team slime would like became the functional
number or something or maybe some form of universal basic income where like every killer
about every every newly enlisted killer gets like gets like a stipend gets like a lot of his utopia
inside of surely i think it would be really funny okay and also i literally think it would work and
make the team better and be proof of coming to communism works this is this is a fascinating
point ben because i i just i think i have to say that like if you instituted a policy such as that
i think that you would find an organization that is obviously cut through capitalist immoral
agency such as slime corp just as we theorize what happened in real life if you were to institute
that this corporation would leave slime city if you're going to attempt to co-opt their their profits
and uh i these are these are my profits we're i can do what i want with my slime in the anarcho
capitalist nightmare that is new los angeles we're talking about things that aren't terrible
right now we can come back to terrible things later yeah okay agreed agreed well well i want
but i wanted to do that but then i was like that would be too good literally communism would be too
powerful and it would make the killers so powerful that they could not be defeated you know i would
be completely unbalanced i mean you're the leader of the killers do whatever you want uh that would
be interesting to see i guess what happens you know uh as an experiment if nothing else um
shit i shouldn't have said anything i should have just done it you can cut it out you can cut
this part out tell oblivion well now munchie knows oh yeah uh not now i'll be able to institute
communists and communism dammit you came in this this idea this idea that no one's ever tried
communism is so good i shouldn't have said anything because it's guaranteed to work when we
yeah dammit ben ben saint inventor of communism it's to protect his intellectual property
hey hey ben i i sent you i sent you like audio uh a content after the last episode recorded
did you ever get around to reading listen to that wait you did yeah and you said oh yeah i'll for
sure listen to this uh wait okay sounds like he didn't is the obvious answer let's make a whole
rfck thing wait what was it what was it it was it's like like like history through oh yeah yeah
no i did i listened to all you did yeah yeah did you like it did you like it yeah i did um the most
yeah i actually listened to a bunch of the ones like in between like i listened to the whole
series wait what what is this what did he what did he do so last last episode he was telling me about
this podcast called revolutions yeah he was like i think you'd have some uh interesting bits about
the the russian revolution here yeah i want to i really want to hear more of it i was disappointed
that like the series isn't done yet because i want to listen to the whole thing the most
interesting thing about it was the um the paris communes oh oh do you know do you know about
the story about that well like the story behind it kind i mean i i basically only know what they
said about it in this series and i feel like there's a lot more to it that they know i i i beg you
please let me talk to you about it later this is outside the scope of this episode right now okay
but it's very interesting and it would be and it'd be yeah anyway uh that was that was the most
interesting part and that was what got me i want to know more about this uh yeah i listen to listen
to everything i will tell you yeah yeah uh we'll talk about more later anyway uh and i hold up any
friend he recites his speech and immediately upon him doing so i lay him down i throw him down on the
fucking ground i punt him and then i i unban him from the rice and so now annie fred he is roaming
around the streets of new lestadule city a proud rowdy eager for knowledge and curious about the
history and lore that has come behind him this is how you do it guys this is how you become
this is how you get on munchies good side this is how you become best friends with your god idol
munchie shatski is you just show any curiosity whatsoever and you're fucking all bones of your
body is you even just try to be a good person i will shower you and enjoy and lollipops by the way
even more interesting than that is a fairfrog is annie fred's friend who was whisked to this con
by annie fred and fairfrog has just become a foil to annie fred just because he's his friend
and so now a fairfrog is a huge killer with like like mega slimes only trying to destroy
annie fred's good time well good glad to hear how did that happen that was so on brand
so on brand uh there was the twins as well oh yeah okay the two twins one is a rowdy one is a killer
yeah it's just like all this all this duality going on too much as you can see i'm pretty sure it's
callum and happy callum k64 unhappy yeah they are twins and i don't know if it's communicated in this
photo that you're able to see right now in in the show notes oh yeah but they like look exactly the
same i see in person they looked exactly the same and they sounded the same and they just were the
same person and and yet one's a killer and one's a rowdy just just touch you know just like like
one one leaf blew in a different direction for one of them in their crib and their life was irreparably
changed forever like just like this is butterfly effect in action people completely different
results from the same upbringing and same genetic code it's all it's all about that nurture when it
comes making a rowdy or a killer well it looks like this is a this is an outstanding success of an
event despite it being so many pcp heads yeah yeah but did you make any money oh did you make any of
that sticky icky cashish munchie no we didn't make any money because because we're friends now because
we're friends what was the point i asked you what was out of here oh oh by the way i also want to
reiterate that that this was uh you know on the fourth of july and we were walking around london
and and there was absolutely no reference to it as i assumed there would be you know i didn't
think there would be except for one alone cinema in the london china town and there was a cinema
there that first of all played the room monthly which was cool monthly we used the room so we
should see it sometimes you should anyone but also they were playing team america or i'm sorry
yeah yeah and we stopped in and watch it on the fourth of july in london oh that's great
what i would have done i would have taken you know those little um they're like little rock
poppers that you can throw on the ground and they spark and they do a little like explosions i would
have been walking around london with a bag full of those throwing at the feet of every fucking
lyme i come across going bang america bang america big bang fucking red coats you know then they
say like is that a gun i don't know what a gun looks like is that a gun all throughout all
throughout uh july fourth i was telling michelle like today munchie's doing us proud today he's
taking the fight back to england it's a reverse colonization he's running he's running around
in a powdered wig with a bayonet just stabbing people i mean not even untrue not even untrue
listen this entire trip i've been i've been trying to restrain myself not even a very good job at
because it's just so grass but a graphine to say like oh things are different here yeah uh it's so
much fun and i love it and it's great my favorite parts of the con when they'd be like oh you're
certainly such an american right now i'm like oh i'm different than people in certain ways of my
speech and it's cool it feels it feels good man it's it's interesting to see that's one of my
favorite things about when i went to japan it's just such a fucking i mean it's pretty similar
it's very business capitalistic i don't know fucking go buy two shops do cool things but
it's the culture man we're most of the attendees uh from england are they yes almost exclusively
yeah okay i only magics was from anywhere else in europe i'm pretty sure and where was he from
again we're germany you said right oh no lemontarp lemontarp's from i was gonna say i was gonna say
i thought i thought lemontart was there lemontarp's from from spain okay that's cool that's cool i mean
for them that's like a what like a 10-minute bike ride to get to england as i understand it yeah it's
um that's pretty cool yeah it's just a hop skip and a jump so fucking e you shrinking the dimensions
of the world i oppose that policy but fucking e you making it easier to go on vacation mother
fucking globalist fucking parentheses parentheses parentheses globalist you said it
fucking up the discourse it was it was a great time i mean there's just a thousand and more things
that we could say i mean it was an actual packed event filled day yeah no not even just that day
like the the the other days that we've been spending just doing like time has frozen we've
been doing so fucking much lately it's it's it's felt incredible it's felt really good oh one thing
i want to mention um is that we were doing just before we started recording uh recording something
that i've wanted to do all the time and you brought up which is what we just we were working on our
laptops doing writing things in the same room but not talking to one another and and i was introduced
to this concept many years ago as a child watching autopimp videos autopimp as this person would read
homestuck comics right and voice act for the characters and there was one famous homestuck
comic about dave stealing terezi's panties and then all the homestuck guys wearing their panties
feels good for them the point is is that the first panel solex and i think someone else is like like
decoding on their computer on their laptop on a bed or on the side of the bed and then on top
of the bed is john carcat playing super smash brothers and the idea that you can be with your
friends but then also working while they're playing video games that just is like the
best thing i can fucking imagine that's that's what my entire life right now is me doing something
else while my friends are in the room doing a thing together and me i've never done that before
not it's so it's my favorite thing it's my favorite thing in the entire world it's so good
it's like perfect how was like humans were not meant for such a height man was not meant for such
a height yeah men will tower at the site this is what my whole entire teen years looked like
basically uh digi thank you for it anyway we were doing it and it was great i was able to
just like work on work on in this work coding and hippo was able to i don't know do what the
fucking yeah you know just i'm just writing thinking of of characters and and arcs and acts
and beginnings middles and ends i i speaking of that is like a brief aside um i've i've learned
that like the whole like a story has to have a beginning a middle and an end is like in it like
you hear that and you're like duh but what does it mean and i've realized what it means uh just in
like i put it in words that actually makes sense uh story has a pay a setup uh a suspense and a payoff
if you get rid of any one of those things uh it's not satisfying like if you get rid of the payoff
this the setup means nothing and the suspense is just sort of like well what happens um if you get
rid of the setup uh you're not invested in the characters or something or yeah people are just
doing stuff and you're just watching them do stuff and then they end doing the stuff uh if you get
rid of the middle there's no suspense there's no uh will they won't they um so like if it starts off
like a guy says i have to avenge my father and then he finds the guy who killed his father
like one second later and kills him that would be like if you got rid of the middle uh so uh writing
cool hell yeah i i i realized that if if if a piece of media is missing like something fundamental
is usually one of those three things or is like lacking in one of those departments it's like
yeah that's what beginning middle end means uh is to have the setup be paid off but also have
suspense as to whether they will do it what uh what brought up this this thinking on this particular
subject if anything uh cuz cuz i've been writing like crazy like writing like 18 different stories
like different comics uh you know i'm just i'm just feeling very typey feeling very textual
great sounds like you're shaking off your your doldrums a little bit well there's there's that
i mean i i feel like i'm getting good at good at writing but the the thing that i've come into
like this is like getting me a little bit is i'm not you i'm not really the right man for the job
to write to to draw these comics because i can't draw that well and i would need to take time away
from what i'm doing to get good and i it annoys me that that's the case like i'm writing all
these stories and i'm coming up with these specific types of characters and then i try to draw them
and they look like cartoon stupid stickman it's like ah i suppose i know the feel uh so i'm i'm
looking for artists you know i've been thinking about this is the thought i had recently that like
there's probably so many good ideas for stories that like let me put it this way more people
need to like sell each other ideas and like just or like team up because like there's so many people
who probably think like oh i have this amazing idea for a novel i'm gonna try to write it but
it's like your writing voice doesn't really match the story and it's like oh if you just pass this
to somebody who whose voice would match the story it would be good but because you feel like you
have to write it because it was your idea then you know it's gonna come out like shit and like
in different worlds this is commonplace like you know in the world of music ghost writing is
commonplace you know people um there was just an album that came out of prince songs where
it was a whole album of songs he had written for other people but it was like his original
performances of them um like that he had sent to those people so they could do it and it's like
you know all these major stars who he just wrote songs that didn't really fit his style like they
wouldn't have sounded right on a prince album so he just gave them to people who it would sound
right coming from and it's like they're all majorly successful because they match that person's
style it's like you know i i've had a lot of ideas for stories myself that like i can't write
because just my writing style is it just doesn't match the tone of the story but like it's it's
got some kind of core idea that i want to be communicated that i wish it existed it doesn't
have to be from me but at the same time i don't like trust anybody to be able to deliver on it if
i don't like you know work with someone closely know that they're professional know that they
can do it well and that takes time to investigate which can be a real uh wall in uh in do even if
you're interested in doing that and even just finding people who want to write somebody else's
thing who are actually competent writers you know like yes i've i've had people online like when i
talked about an idea for a story who are like ooh can i try to write that and i say sure and
then they do it and i'm like okay well you know i could have done better than this so like you
know i'd want it to be somebody who was actually good but most people who are good want to write
their own stories you know that's true you know i think a part of this comes from excessive pride
of people feeling that there's no way that someone else could ever do the job that they want to do
100 on their own and i heard a great quote that i'm sure is based on like real actual like i don't
know ancient chinese wisdom or something from avatar i was saying this yesterday but like i was
watching avatar clips of uncle iro the wisest mother fucker whoever lived uh great show 10 out of 10
literally perfect and uh he said an amazing line that like i said i'm sure this has been passed
around for generations and but i heard it from iro in avatar and it was azuko was going on about how
like uh iro was saying like oh you're full of uh you're full of shame zuko you got to get over
this well so that you can like you know shoot lightning or whatever and so it was like i don't
feel any shame i'm as proud as ever and then iro said a genius fucking line that was pride is not
the opposite of shame but is its source only by embracing true humility are you able to let go
of your feelings of shame and this for me was a very profound thing to think about and i don't know
i feel like when it comes to like my content creation as a whole i do think that i'm too proud
on a lot of things and that uh i don't know i that that had a lot of value to me and i think is
relevant to this overall question of like working with other people and allowing others to have any
impact on your work if your goal is it depends on your on your goal is your goal is to be vain
and just make your perfect project and take as long as it takes to be the one who did everything
that's cool if instead your goal is to like produce as much great content in your lifetime as possible
you should definitely incorporate the talents of other people and find ways to do it
uh and not let your pride get the best of you so thanks uncle iro i obviously maybe this is
obvious but i think i've in a way i've done more collaboration than most of us in this group because
i've always had editors you know like i had davoo edit a lot of my videos and like davoo had offered
to edit for other people sometimes and like i know you jesse hippo like all of you like the
editing tossed around the idea well so for you guys the editing is so integral to the process of
even creating in the first place like you have an image of what the finished thing you're supposed
to look like in your mind already for my videos a lot of it is just i just write a thing and then
i look at it i go okay what would i set to this and then a lot of it i have no fucking idea i'm
like oh shit i did not think about how this would look on screen so if i pass it to somebody who's
good at taking a paragraph and figuring out what to show then you know it's perfect so that's that
is what ultimately i plan to do with we agua because i do not make those with a vision in mind
i want to eventually have a editor i currently have uh you know may edits all the manga monday's
videos for exactly that reason it's just like i i just sit in front of a camera and talk about it
she listens to the video anything in like i've also gotten into a style of showing myself on
camera so that i don't have to have images for every single second of the video you know yeah
because it's unnecessary people don't need that much to pay attention they just want enough to
to you know to shake it up so there's some pacing to be able to see the thing you're talking about
people are perfectly happy to watch a video of someone's face talking to them because it's exciting
especially no editing required if it's somebody who is you know interesting to watch or has a
charismatic speaking voice or you have a good set good background you know but like i want the the
images in there just so you have a sense of what i'm talking about so you can picture it you can
know what it is um you know see some exciting stuff and of course again the pacing it helps
with that like if there's an image every say 30 seconds or so then you never feel like you're
just watching a guy talk but like when you try to pack a video with images every single second
it's like some of those sentences just don't have an interesting visual for them you know yeah um
so like then you get those retarded like super literal like and that's what opened the door
image of door slowly zoom in on the yeah yeah i think those are funny sometimes but sometimes yeah
i mean if you're like a jack is boy who like makes fun of that kind of stuff intentionally
i can get way into it but that that's a lampooning that's uh you know so like the way that i've been
doing the the manga monday's videos is like i will record my review you know and then just edit
edit it down give it to her she then listens to it takes notes on like anything i say that
should be visualized then she reads the manga behind because like you know obviously i have to
read it before i do the video she doesn't read it till after watching the video so that she can
just while reading put post-its in the book and uh and then just shoot you know all those parts so
it's like that collaboration it literally cuts the time because if i were to do that like i don't
know what i'm gonna say before i read the book so i can't make those kind of notes i can't sit
there and put post-its in i guess if i was like saying ooh i'll probably mention this but like
i really don't know what i'm gonna say so it's a lot easier for somebody to go in behind me and
that way i don't have to reread the whole fucking manga you know if we both get the experience of
hey we got to read a cool manga i get to work on a different project and not edit this one it's just
all around yeah keep the pipeline going yeah makes sense that's why i like uh working with editors
i mean that was always the appeal of working with divu was that like i you know i could just move
on to the next project while he goes and edits that one i crave that i crave that uh reality yeah
yeah though the way i've been doing uh today's anime is that i just screen record while i'm
watching the shows so that i have all the footage ready and then i just you know sprinkle a little
bit in in the edit but uh those are not like yeah i should do that oh you know what you know what
wait on specifically that uh you know michelle had a little bit of feedback for you on that
specifically and she said that she thought that putting the date was she has watched all of those
i think but she said that it was a little bit off putting to have the dates and for some reason it
feels like it cheapens the experience and she suggested leaving it as just the like the subject
matter and leaving those offers specifically marketing purposes to make the video feel more
whatever so there's your feedback i don't know take it or leave it timeless yeah timeless that's a
good that's a good word for it i i mean i agree that it would make it feel more timeless i think
that the reason i'm doing it is so that i i have this weird tendency that i am overly honest with
my video titles no matter how quickly i try to make them like i want to communicate to you that
hey this is just me reacting to the shows that happen to come out today you know yeah i know what
you mean um and like it also kind of helps with you logically understanding why i'm talking about
these shows in particular you know um yeah there's a there's a that question of like how
quote-unquote honest do i want to be like ideally we should probably make every video we produce
sound like the greatest video ever in the title as some people do and you know the problem is a
lot of people do that and as far as i can tell they really it's not even that they don't feel
shame it's that to them like this is obviously the right thing to do and like why would they
even question that no it is because like i historically i feel like this this strange
sense of like i want to stratify the content so that people know at a glance like if they're about
to click on something that's you know high level or low level effort but most people can't actually
tell the difference and the works against us right the reactions people like if you don't tell them
this is low level content and you let them come to their own conclusions like first of all there
are some people who are going to think something i did spend a lot of time on is low level content
like there's there's going to be people who you know are going to rag on the thing even if i thought
it was good but yeah and then vice versa there's people who just they don't come in with the
presupposition that this is an under underdone video and so they end up enjoying it more so
yeah i definitely agree that putting the dates on there probably does cheap in it i
it would feel weird to me to not do it just because it puts them in order it's basically
like saying like numbering the episodes but um yeah i don't know if they probably are unnecessary
so i mean i definitely debated removing like i put we agua at the end of we agua episodes
and i don't know my whole thought process is is really all about stratifying that content as you
said is like this is we agua it's not that good like don't get excited it's just a we agua episode
there's going to be people who like don't care about gurund laghan and don't care about the best
anime ever video and then you make a we agua about like say mob psycho and like that's their
favorite anime and it doesn't matter that it wasn't as detailed a video that's their favorite video
because it's about mob psycho or yeah because it made a point that they hadn't thought about
and the other video didn't you know yep yep so it's a it's a real it's a complicated dance
so i do think i would say it is in everyone's best interest to just title every video as though it
were as though it were you know completely meant to stand on its own it's not being compared to
anything else yeah yeah maybe this is that pride i don't know it's it's it's definitely that pride
because i that's exactly how i feel like i feel this yeah but again and it has nothing to do with
how i expect the audience to react it's entirely based on my feelings towards the product i will
hamstring my own marketing just because i'm not proud of the video and it's uh it's foolish yeah
yeah anyway fascinating voicemails i guess everybody else is asleep yeah yeah i'm ready
i'm ready uh let's uh what i put that okay here we go how many how many voicemails we got i've got
i've got nine voicemails oh i must say wait hold on wait one second sure i just want to say that on
the subject of manga monday's anime reviews shimibakas akira coming out soon oh yeah oh my god
hey did you guys hear they're making an akira anime that's gonna be more true to the manga yeah i saw
i was fascinating yeah it we i had no idea that it took place in 2019 oh my it does ah
what if akira what if akira was an anime imagine that what if i mean it's gonna be it's gonna be
way quote unquote worse like moment to moment but it probably will have you know more information so
so that's cool i don't say as somebody who has read the manga like yeah the movie is amazing as a
technical showcase the manga is a much more interesting story so i believe i think if they
uh i believe that completely only have watched the movie that movie so good though the movie only
adapts the first two out of the six volumes of the manga what what yeah yeah i gotta read the first
two volumes and then it just kind of skips to the like it incorporates the ending in a different way
into the ending of volume two but the manga goes complete basically after the city gets destroyed
is a whole post apocalyptic storyline that is like the bulk of the actual narrative
damn yeah i gotta i gotta get in on that i'm a mango man i think you only takes a day to read
plow through it yeah it's one of my favorites so so on the subject of the voicemails though
let me just say that things i was feeling a bit of despair last episode you know all voicemails
are shit hashtag uh voicemail lives don't matter but the good news is oh i distinctly better batch
this week yeah yeah i i i forget if it was cake i don't want to misattribute to him and and to uh
out him as an anti a trader and a head but someone at ars k con i believe it was cake the
native head tree yeah yeah says something the effect of it's better when you pick the voicemails
munchies oh that as a badge of honor some native it wasn't cake i'm using your words to to drive a
knife run into your father's heart and you know what that's fine i'll i'll cry later uh let me
just say and you know there was a message from nate's number one fan that okay it was it was
interesting and it was good but the thing is like it's gonna sound weird but like it sounded great
and interesting there was clearly a lot of work into it but the actual audio quality was simply
unintelligible and i couldn't like the microphone he was recording on was way too bad i could hear
like music and like things happening in the background nate's number one fan try again
and fix your audio because it sounded cool so like whatever that was i want to hear it as it was
supposed to sound um and also requiem for a meme called back but i'm not going to play his because
it was way too rambling and a bunch of personal details that like are fine uh he was like people
do this where they'll like call in and try to like follow up when we respond to them they're always
boring you're always boring when you do these like follow-ups on the details i'm sure they're
really important to your personal narrative of whatever but don't even bother because it's
boring and and a lot of people have been asking what makes a good fucking voicemail this is the
answer entertainment value in whatever that may be so just be entertaining and you're
miscellaneous you're about to play a voicemail that was the answer um maybe maybe okay but you
know what let me just play the first one which is uh oh you know you're absolutely right about that
and our first voicemail is from uh burnt cookies this is this teen cp application form oh and on
the subject i'm playing this because it's actually good and entertaining there are so many fucking
voicemails about the teen cp this is not the fucking teen cp go away i'm not playing your
fucking voicemails unless they're actually funny like this one so there you go all right burnt
cookies let's see what you got go sliding out of bed half dead socialism in my head so red not
even thinking comprehending that ubi so i can keep my sign got online catching bitches with the
slime can't deal with the finance staying away from the ants keeping one hand in my pants i don't
want none of this dance keeping one eye in the ranch because i would rather be a juby than a boomer
cavio is cuz it's in kosher big show show you kill a coach uh skirting on a skateboard with a bad
site and hosing the slime off a door looking fly bang sound number one nine man's playing all night
want to see you crap fuck slime bitch let me make her die no strings attached motherfucker you should
end up later sucka like me should have seen the writing on the wall now you back in the green
sea and i'm chilling in kill town ignoring the call to cap because i gotta work on this one
person to dance with the tap and you only give you the ones keeping purple on the mat because
i gotta get myself on the team cp save jen z from the sick rowdies me and get the kids in the
tank and we gonna sneak in and kill my chi and me and my wife happens to run up to fight
doing these niggas like i'm cooking rice boiling the ramen get down with the spice bring me a
soda no coke with my ice ice doesn't die stay with proper my fans speaking at deep ground slang
we just need to fuck with a bang and difference my yang gang back unto the main thing it's like
qualify it's like 18 it's like i got the cred and let me tell you why first of all i got these
base stars come to loony to the stars hope the white race car it's you love stars because i
dab on god and i dab on the rowdies i dab on nine eleven and i dab on the saudis
that was burnt cookies burnt cookies and that was his his acceptance not his his attempt to get
into the teen cp the lone cool killer the lone yeah did you hear that he's gonna sneak in and
kill you munchie in real life can you catch that yeah i'd like to see him try when i when i break
out my bar of muscles when he snaps katana and hat but you know we'll see um incredible boy great
fucking yeah he killed it was so good so good cookies don't worry um boys will be communist soon
yeah yeah but voice now that voice grail i think there was a voice grail voice grail do we want to
be that loose with our voice grail applicants that was good that was very good that isn't loose
that was the best like rap i've ever seen on a voicemail you know what easily okay fair fair
enough all right burnt cookies you're in the grail you're in the grail burnt cookies let me write
it down i'll add you later is there like a okay anyway next up place where that is like is the
voice grail of an entity you can view it is a google drive word document where we have added
you know several names visible to the public in any way i think it was included in the show
notes at least once does anybody have any idea who is or isn't in the voice grail or is it just
you know what we can do we say we say we say when we add okay oblivion oblivion do me a solid
i just hope that they are happy about let's put in the link in the description to the speak pipe
right underneath that let's just put a link to the voice grail or the voice jail what if we
have a like we we should have a png of like a grail with like the names in it like on little
slips of paper and like a grail i mean okay that's true but that requires effort a word
doc we pay a guy to do that kind of effort um i guess uh you know what i will paste a png of a
grail into the word document and a picture of a jail that'll be increasing its production
value by ten thousand percent that's correct all right we'll do that for now um okay next one is
okay okay this one's long we're not going to play the whole thing but it's uh this is an
actually good topic nate is the name of the voice spell okay so go so this is an argument i've been
having with my friends for uh the last few days and i felt like ben because i was explaining my
point and they didn't get it and i would just get angrier and angrier uh my relative like ben
i think it's fucking illogical to believe or to think that because somebody dresses up a certain
way or looks sharp they will immediately and objectively do a better job than anybody else
in the same position just because of how they look like i was telling my friends you know it's
it's completely baseless like there is a societal expectation that certain jobs
demand certain appearances and my point was never that there aren't any benefits to doing that
or that it's detrimental in any way i think just think it's it's illogical and i don't i don't
and your friends sound retarded so easy okay i'm gonna he goes on in that way for a while
that's enough i kind of wanted to hear what he was trying to say is that his friends seem to think
that if you are better dressed you will just do your job better than someone who is not better
dressed and he was trying to really doesn't clarify any more beyond that yeah he was trying to argue
with them that that is not necessarily the case that that's that there there may be advantages to
dressing up but it doesn't mean that you will automatically be better than someone who is not
dressed there are i mean in a job that involves like dealing with people there is probably a
reasonable expectation that you should right but it's not there's no guarantee like there's no
reason to think that somebody who isn't dressed up can't by way of some other methodology that they
have some other technique they know be better at it you know that it might be i mean i would
i would make if you're a guy if you're a guy like trying to sell stuff and like um you're
you're you're you're you know really sharply dressed but you're not charismatic the charismatic
guy is going to win i mean even if even if even if he has a wrinkly shirt and he's like but he's
if he's like the life of the street he's just like yelling and it's really selling you on these things
saying ding ding if you're saying ding ding real loud i mean out outside the context of the job
it doesn't matter how they dress if if i'm like hiring someone for a job i want to see them and i
want to see them present themselves like in a way that is like yeah this is what i expect i have
never seen a better salesman or marketing genius than the shirtless guy standing outside of otacon
and brony con that guy is not dressed up at all in fact he is wearing less clothes than most people
dude no he's dressed for the job he wants yeah i would have to agree he's dressed for he's dressed
for success in his field have you ever heard there's a legendary moment in are you guys familiar
with internet historians videos um there's a moment i believe it's um dash con uh the the tumblr
meetup where uh there's there's a guy filming and there's just a moment where he goes up to a man
dressed as the devil and he goes up and he says to him famously sir so what made you want a cosplay
as the prime minister of israel and the the devil replies back well i always heard growing up that
you got to dress for the job you want and that was one of the most legend like this was at dash
con i was expecting a pure cringe i got legitimate comedy gold so shout out to that guy that guy
that guy really nailed it also uh israel's not a legitimate state uh your death israel long live
palestine uh you know you know how it is but anyway um next voicemail uh yes next voicemail
next one is from dj jesse jess oh wait wait sorry i was just gonna say uh on the on the actual
subject of that last one i was just gonna say that the the thing that they're your friends are
kind of right about and i would say is there's a general feeling of when when someone like looks
good socially like i don't know like a girl does their makeup they're like in good shape they're
wearing nice clothes i think it's a signifier of general life i think he knows that i mean he was
kind of saying like i was not disagreeing that it has advantages i'm just saying it shows general
life competence but anybody who thinks in those kinds of absolutes is a moron like that is a
normie way of thinking that is why regular people are so dumb is that they can only see things in
that black and white terms if look you have to make assumptions sometime if you go and you see
a bunch of people and you don't know anything about them but one is dressed nice one is dressed
not nice that is a limited selection of information you have and it's reasonable to make a constantly
changing initial assumption yeah Nate hard agree okay but that's not what did he was saying no i mean
okay it's not everything i agree it it was it was not about like the dressing correctly it's the
fact that if somebody argues a point um and then people assume that that means you're like against
the opposite of that point when you're not actually oh you know okay i guess i misheard or
something like if if you're saying sometimes it's like this and and then the other people like wait
you think it's always like that right right that's what is stupid oh okay i totally missed that i'm
an idiot like like if like if nate says that israel is not a legitimate state that doesn't
necessarily imply anything palestine is a legitimate state yeah yeah none of them we doesn't mean we
shouldn't wipe both of them off the map fair fair um all right dj jesse jess with a voicemail uh
PCP i need your help i recently developed a sexual fetish in which i can only get off when i'm
having sex with someone who espouses political views opposite to mine i've been to so many
trump rallies picking up people my apartment bedroom floor is littered with camouflage
shirts and accessories so much so that when i wake up i think i'm in a literal form when i roll over
half the days i wake up to find a man wearing nothing but a locker up t-shirt
seeing in this block on my cable box which i actually have because i need fox news for the
post-coldest cuddle the reason it's taken a dark return i now can't get off unless i'm in a threesome
with a lefty and a far right winger who are both arguing at each other trying to win the sexual
battle for my political soul i need your help to stop this or reverse this i don't know what to do
by the way been an eight you should hit me up sometime i think we can have a good time
yeah that's fair that sounds good um um i mean that's it yeah you said it all agree hard agree
hard agree yeah yeah text me i don't see the problem i'm playing a kibush on this right
fucking now you guys are not using hard agree hard agree is a fucking teen cp zoomer thing
fuck all you can't say hard agree it's our word okay whatever what next hard agree stop no agree on
that one munchie next voicemail uh good man suck dick uh go you guys talked about sucking dick is a
straight going let me tell you sexuality is entirely irrelevant a good honest man a true pillar of
his community sucks dick and he likes it not because he's gay though he may be but for the
sheer satisfaction it brings him to make the life of his fellow man more pleasurable goodbye
uh can i just get a hard agree
i saw like a post somewhere of like a it's like a model wearing a t-shirt and like
if you know what i'm saying the back the back of the t-shirt it had like a big picture of an ak-47
it was like it was like in protest of uh you know Colin Kaepernick kneeling for the
national anthem or whatever and it's like the only time this patriot kneels is when he's
sucking a hero comes
damn that's multifaceted i didn't know which way that was going i i i'm like i'm not in i'm not
entirely sure if it's ironic it's hard to tell i mean they could just be like a gay you know
trump or whatever i think probably i think probably but i can't i'm not a hundred percent sure
it's hard to know i don't know not a hundred percent sure like that feels like something
like Milo would wear like he'd wear it relatively unironically but like for everybody else
i just don't know okay all right let's check back in i love the police about like hard
agree being co-opted uh i i feel like hard disagree on that i i feel like that's like
your parents discovering facebook and now you can't use facebook anymore so you'll have to think
of something you hard agree forever this is not a new thing i know i i know it's not a new thing
but like it's just it's it's been popularized by the teen cp the teen cp owes us their entire
existence i will take whatever they produce it's mine it's my literal property success all right
next voicemail fucking boomers thinking thinking everything even related to the podcast feels
under there it's literally my property that's correct uh but let's uh okay next voicemail
so okay just a reminder for everybody we're gonna check in with who wants to be a pcp millionaire
and uh it's just just to just so you know what we're going in for this is johnny bravo on a uh uh uh
uh content on a trivia quiz show so that's just clarifying that yeah know that going in okay and
here we go ready set go welcome back to who wants to be a pcp millionaire hosted by yours truly where
my ass bad man yeah are you ready to continue i'm ready to continue as much as i'm ready for a woman
the final of man who is holding back the max revival of tbap uh also known as two best birds
but you're about apologies is it right best guy ever don't need another answer there
you know my ass bad man i'm gonna go with a best guy ever b correct question three what does the
pcp one from the voicemails is it a hold on right there sweet cakes no one knows answer to this one
i'm gonna have to pull the pcp on this one okay johnny you do uh 30 seconds to talk to the pcp
directly your time starts now hello pcp my question for you this is johnny bravo asking you
what do you want from the voicemails do what do you want from the past pcp do you like this long
form content like this you like songs do you like relationship uh violence piano solos what do you
mama would you just let me finish my answer put in my question i'm sorry baby go on what you're
me and rings sorry johnny that's time's up oh but i didn't get the answer get my question answered
maybe you'll see it you'll hear it next time on the pcp like and so you know to the next time on the
pcp like to the next time that's the final what happens with johnny's answers like same time same
pcp channel what do you like in your voicemails do you like relationships do you like songs do you
like relationship violence yeah relationship violence um a little bit of all okay a little mix
a pcp i just beat my way okay okay real nice mad man i have a message directly towards you
can you please perform a musical cover of one two oatmeal for me i feel like you would go well
with your oh yeah i don't know that i don't know that one uh i don't know it's gonna be enough
well okay i guess and i think we're supposed to answer his question i we said i said this boy this
is what i was thinking up i think uh what do we want entertainment entertainment really as long
as the entertainment we want to we want to be inter gaged yeah that's we want to be inter gaged
we want for creativity but also but also stupid stupid relationship questions are fine i'll be
i'll be absolutely clear if it gets a laugh out of me i'm almost guaranteed to play it uh whatever
it may be that's that's my number one priority beyond that i don't know i say creativity like
you can't just like someone playing the piano is funny it's it's not funny anymore it's not funny
anymore yeah yeah yeah so watch is like the next voicemail has someone playing the piano
oh wait i just uh hey yeah anything else i gotta delete one real quick just just follow your heart
just follow your heart uh potential uh i would say don't be dispirited if we don't play any individual
one even if you thought it was good i just keep trying and like if it's good it will get played
because there's not that many i play all the good ones basically and it just happens to be between
like five and ten most times i've probably called into biggest problem in the universe slash the
dick show like 11 or up to 15 times over the course of like three years before i finally got played
on the show after i had already been a guest on the show several times it still took me another year
to get a voicemail that was funny enough to get played on the show and then i nailed the formula
and got played twice so nice nice just gotta do one and done as i understand was uh in and out
what a legend all right next one it's a it's an ironic gang weed guy an ironic gang weed guy
let's see what he has to say okay go attention fellow gamers and gang weed members i've heard
past voicemails about one itis quality woman and guy with generic problem number 137 examined
life of gaming gentlemen have we learned nothing from best anime ever tangentopagar and longing
fuck women and honestly just work on yourselves and let an actually good person come into your life
screw the yokos and wait for your nias gamers i have essentially had to give up on veronica
she has been with chat for over a year why even bother with her just because she has huge shits
she probably has a shit personality and has been brainwashed by the government media and corporations
yeah all that matters is being able to say the n word
veronica sounds like a total neoliberal shit so not a fan i would agree i would agree with you on that
yeah man just fucking just fucking wait just wait just hang out just chill out just let don't
don't worry about it let life bring provide you opportunities as you are doing shit to
make your life better and don't ignore them just seize the opportunities when they come to you
that's what most people did throughout history it's not a bad strat and if you feel more desperate
then that's fine devote some of your day to go meeting people you know start well you know the
one thing you can do to make yourself the best you can be is go to go to church start going to
synagogue oh yeah and you're bound to meet the ladies um in temple uh that's what works for me
question reminds me of the number one most pro bully person i know the most pro veronica person
in my life which is michelle uh where as she is absolutely pro bully uh saying various things
like uh those nerds probably deserved it and uh their biggest problem was that they were boring
and uninteresting as opposed to veronica and chad who had more going for them so no wonder those
losers were jealous and you know wanted to be with them because they just don't have as much going
on in their life and you know what hard agree yeah um i want to meet this chad i bet he's not
always cracked up to be oh no he's more than you could ever possibly imagine okay all right whatever
next next call let's go to uh adaptations are always bad okay go so i was recently talking about
different adaptations with my friend like the idea of taking like sequential art such as like
comic and mongas and making into like films and tv series and just from like talking to him
and this is something that i know that i felt in the past he really stressed like this inherent
value of having like a movie or a tv show based on the thing you like and it being good
and it seems to like almost undervalue the actual work itself or the original manga
or comic and i just think that's a really common attitude in like normie culture currently very
much and i was just kind of curious if you guys have noticed this too dude it's yeah if there are
actually any good adaptations of something or superior adaptations that you've experienced
let me say first of all it really can't think about damn this motherfucker just okay he's done
there are definitely good adaptations that the reason people feel like that is that just more
people watch movies the re comics so like more more people have watched like this i don't know the
fucking avengers movies than ever read the comic i have to talk about the so to most people the
comics just don't matter it's a weird and i'm gonna have been abusing this word today but
stratification that people have in their mind of like how much value they put on each different
type of media because like this is why all these fucking disney live actions have been getting made
because normal people just straight up think that like something being live action just is better
than if it was animated like regardless of how well do they enjoy the animated version or not
like normie people like when they hear oh this animated thing is gonna become live action they're
like oh it's gonna be a real movie now like that's how they think of it it's like oh wow
they're gonna make Aladdin a real movie and so they watch it and like really really really why
those adaptations exist is so that disney can keep its stranglehold on the copyright well sure
but it's this is why the people get excited for it like it's why they do so well because they do
i oh this is what dude i'm so excited for black ariel dude i can't wait to pay disney more money
to show me black area that is a that is a hard thing for me to swallow ariel being a ginger is
like the most classic ginger ale such a classic architect that's fucking that's fucking stupid
why but anyway why is that stupid because who because who fucking cares i mean her whole family
is gonna change race now because i mean you know her dad so what guess what the movie's gonna suck
and if you see it you're an idiot regardless of how her fucking hair color is the story from
what isn't it from like grease or something i don't know it's french oh my god my historical
accuracy and my fucking fantasy mermaid it doesn't matter don't look at me like like it's weird of
me to feel like well that's a weird reinterpretation of the character it is weird it is weird so it
what if what if you're the weird would i be weird if repunzel was black like that's such a such a
core feature of the character her long blonde hair why is it so crazy for me to be like ariel
being like a redheaded white dude that's what i do expect that story just would not work if the
hair were black i'm sorry it just it just wouldn't make any sense like i just it would just strain my
suspension of disbelief too much are you being sarcastic are you being serious of course i'm
fucking being sarcastic what the fuck is wrong with you look jesus i mean what is your objection to
my feeling that this is weird is it not weird it is not weird no i don't well i just i i think it
if anyway beside the fucking point uh the the movies are garbage and they only exist because
people think that live action is just inherently better than animation in the same way that people
think that animation is inherently better than non-moving comics people just straight up don't
have a respect for those other mediums because they just see no value in it like they see it as like
oh yeah sure a manga can be good but an anime is automatically better unless it's like obviously
bad you know unless there's something really wrong with it people will always be more excited
but like in my experience most of the time if the i mean there's times where the original
is not good and the adaptation fixes it like in the case of kaon the manga is just not good
the anime is great because they took it and they reinterpret it as like what would be good in
animation um the there's plenty of cases where like the original story was already like as good
as its medium could get and then you translate it to something else but it's not as good as
that medium could get so you end up with something where it's like okay it's theoretically adding
all these extra facets to it should make it have more opportunities to be great but it also adds
more opportunities to fail so if you know for instance um an anime that just came out the
season fire force i love the manga because the artwork is fantastic it's paced perfectly the
images flow into each other well the choreography is perfect and like the anime has certain bells
and whistles that are nice you know you got music voice acting color you have uh like certain action
scenes that are really beautifully animated but the backgrounds look like shit and that's just a
problem the manga never had and now we have that and it's like no matter how good all the other
stuff is the manga was perfect the way it was and the anime is flawed as an anime so if you value
all those extra things just inherently more if you think like oh i don't care if the manga was
perfect it doesn't have color and i just value color above all else then sure you'll think the
anime is better and i think most people think that way as with so many things it depends on what
you value obviously and what about what about akira didn't you say before that akira the movie is
like a better uh it doesn't even adapt the whole story though so i don't i don't i mean i wouldn't
say the akira i wouldn't say the movie is better necessarily in any way it's just a it's just a
really amazing technical showcase of a film but like um the main problem with the movie is just
that it doesn't have the complete story um okay i mean in the case of the akira movie as well
literally the guy who drew the comic directed the film so like it's as close to being the same thing
as it could be basically there are i'm sure i'm sure we could think if we try it of an example
of like a work that was like not like you know an original work that was left that was you know
not as successful and then it was adapted into a movie and the movie was a masterpiece and it's
i mean i think kaon is like oh well how about the godfather there's a godfather book that was
really good uh but they made it a movie and it's like you know some of the most beloved films ever
made that's probably a good example yeah okay um so i mean i would say that like like people really
like the book i've never read it but i have seen the movie and it is like some of the best movies
ever made but does that make it better than the book i'm on record it's just different i'm on record
i think that originality is worth a lot and i think that to us in a certain way the original
will always be superior to an adaptation in just in that aspect um yeah i think it's it's possible
to improve you it's possible to make a superior adaptation uh but it's rare and probably people
should not try well you know the godfather is an interesting example because in the godfather
you can feel because i've watched it so many times i'm well aware that like a lot of information
from the book like didn't quite translate you know a good example is i was always a little bit
confused at the exact relationship of the godfather with um luke brazi who's like the biggest enforcer
or whatever and luke brazi actually has like a a large storied history with uh vito corleone the
godfather and like they barely get into that at all in the movie just enough so you know like what
he is and what his role in the story is in the first movie but i think in the book and i know
in like the video game and other things they go way more into the backstory of that guy and like
so basically information is lost in translation when you're making the godfather movie part one
versus the book but in contrast uh kaon it seems the difference with kaon is that that was a four
panel four coma manga originally mostly comedy not a ton of story what they did instead was they
it seems to me they expanded the shit out of it exactly they added so much more to it and barely
lost anything so it's like in a sense of that like you might be able to make as good a case
as you ever could that like nothing was lost and only things were added and you know there's going
to be people who value the original which is you know because the original was minimal um yeah like
there's like a lot of it is functionally original right material i mean which is yep it'll always
come down to again what you value i mean some people are gonna say they like game of thrones
more as a book some people say they like it more as a series because it is you know what each one
has over the other is so different that you know you could easily make the case either way and both
are good anyway that's enough of this fucking god damn i just i just want to like briefly touch on
like the whole black aerial thing because i've been pondering it in the background okay let's
get into it well i feel like you know i like nate's problem i guess is like
black let's not use the word problem okay it's not a problem it's just like you you say it feels
weird but like yes mermaids and like uh magical long hair doesn't exist like these are fantasy films
so like you can make them the right hair color for like for like marketing you could make her be
black and have red hair in in little mermaid i mean well okay i mean i would say that her being
her having red hair is not like an essential aspect of the character nor is being blonde it's not
but what but what but point taken yeah i mean uh and it's you know i mean i they may do it for
marketing i haven't seen anything of this i mean can i just raise let me cut to the okay you finish
you finish the thing is like the race i feel does not really mean anything in these fantasy
tales because mermaids do not exist doesn't matter what i agree i agree if and the reason it feels
weird is because you know her to be a white person from the time when you watch the original movie
and i'm like the only time a race does matter is in a story about racial differences okay guys
live action remake of the black panther but they're white
oh i mean yeah that's pretty strange pretty strange yeah uh i mean some people were joking
well that would be that would be like i mean that okay i haven't seen black panthers take
this with a grain of salt but i just feel like that would change the tone of the story a lot that
would change the context of it yeah it would probably i mean there there is like there is like
actual like racial i mean you could you could have a theoretical country like that is Wakanda
that's you know it doesn't happen to be black happens to be all white people like but in
africa the story is the same in scotland i mean i suppose maybe you could have the exact same story
but the context the movie exists in would be that's true that would change well let me just
clarify my point here it's just that this has been on my mind a lot like these reimagining
and whatnot because i'm i'm making a weag with it we'll be out by now that's literally about tifa
and how i just don't like how they're making minor tweaks to her bus size and her outfit and this
annoys me as a fan like it's not that they're making like disney presents a new mermaid story
what they're they're literally making little mermaid butt live action now my brain thinks oh i
know what little mermaid looks like oh a black chick well that's not what the originally was there
that feels a little you know that's a change so it like oh here's a question why wasn't bell
funny at all because like yeah the the thing is a little mermaid it's just you know it's a john christian
anderson what's his name is that hans hans christian history so it's been adapted a thousand billion
times aerials looked different in every different adaptation it's only in any way noteworthy that
they made her black because of the fact that they are literally translating the exact movie assumably
because that's what they've done for all the other that's my entire grievance which i mean the thing
is that they all have had this issue as well like how the lion king translated to live action has
the same problem that like using these realistic care animal characters that is some unique issues
but yeah it breaks the movie because you can't characterize them the same way like if you're
doing the exact same movie but now they're they're realistic it's like well okay it was kind of
integral to the original story like banjo kazooie nuts and bolts let me let me ask you this let me
just ask you this okay they made a live action beauty and the beast already we've seen it here's
my question why isn't bel blonde in the beauty and the beast movie why isn't she blonde because the
original had her with brown hair here's my other question why didn't but why does bel wear a yellow
dress in the famous dance with the bc why does she wear yellow dress because she did in the original
so am i crazy to be like let's let's fill in the blank of why is an ariel you know it's just the
same logic it's the same shit would you be would you think it was weird if bel was blonde i wouldn't
i'd be like i would think oh bel used to be brunette that's a change i wonder why they did that it
would be just as easy to make her well the thing is with this is like you don't need to wonder
because it's it's you know good marketing like that's a cool thing to do now to be progressive and
inclusive and represent uh you know minorities in in movies it's obviously a marketing thing
i i just resist i resist this thought that like nates the weird guy for being like well that's
not how that originally was am i taking crazy listen no it's not weird for you to make the
observation that a change was made but it's weird for you to think that it's not good or that it's
like bad do you think it's bad it is bad because it wasn't what what did your film originally
was and why would you think would you think it was bad if bel was blonde yes for the exact same
reason okay i wouldn't i think i just i think that if you took the original little mermaid
movie you could make the exact same movie dude they were if they were black the movie would be
exactly the same nothing would change it's not an essential part of the story so making that
change i agree basically no i mean that's how i feel about making it live action at all
yeah that also yeah there's that you you have to listen when my wiago comes i'm making all these
exact same arguments about the tiny tweaks to tifa's design that everyone says nat you shouldn't care
about these things nat you're you're a dumb in-cell for giving a shit about a female character design
blah blah blah it but but i do care i i liked it as it was why are we and not frankly i'm i'm fairly
attached to aria i fucking love part of your world i've watched a million times i was never
gonna like or watch this but it just i mean you know that's it she could still sing part of your
world she's black nae what what is nothing changes about that song you're filling that in but what
it there's a disconnect in my brain that i don't like and there was no reason to do it so why did
they do it the thing that's a little weird okay well hippo hippo was right i i want to say more
about this you can get i just want to say hippo was right before when he said it like it is for
marketing and it's and it is cynical in a way look maybe it's not even for marketing maybe she
was literally the best one who showed up to the audition i mean but uh you know this is this is
disney it's for marketing everything's from right look the point is right you could uh you can be
like i don't like that she's black you know you can be wrong like that you can be like i do like
that she's black this is great and you can be slightly less wrong but the point is that it
having an appeal the fact that you differentiate between those two shows your true cards ban
you should feel exactly the same about both those observations no you're wrong um but the
like having any opinion on it at all is the point of the decision the fact that people will
feel one of two ways is why they did it like you know disney does it disney makes every move that
they make in order to make money this has stirred controversy i hate that it has stirred controversy
but it has and because of that it will make more money this is getting people talking this is the
plan they knew this would happen they did it on purpose and it's not good or bad that aerial is
black but it is bad that disney is a fucking monopoly a capitalist nightmare that is controlling
your brain and stealing your money movie who cares you care more than i care right here's here i care
about i care about our capitalist oligarchs ruling our ruling our society that i do really how by
making movies what's even the big deal they i mean they've they've shaped the discourse now right or
no they're they're they're capitalizing on it right like i mean they'll continue to they'll continue
to profit off of our off of the fact that we feel so strongly about this by making decisions of this
sort and here's an interesting thought about that and it's just and it just i feel infinitely less
strong about this issue than i do about minor tweaks to tifa's design which i utterly despise
so that's where i'm at okay okay i think um i would argue about that as well the i'm sure you
would not the time if she her original model was like seven polygons they had to change the
design oh my god then listen to my video okay fine i will cover these arguments in extensive
detail okay all right all right i i i here's here's my my thought that perhaps you know this is no
real basis but it's like interesting to think the the doing the marketing gets the money you know the
appeasing crowds that you know like this sort of stuff and it's good to be representing people
because it is unusual and it is like it is a progressive thing in a world where now it's
just normal like to remake something with any race character and it's no longer a you know
a marketing gimmick that disney can do would they stop doing it because it's not as profitable
anymore yes i would yeah probably they would they would they would stop anything if it wasn't
profitable i mean like let's not significantly more profitable the the obvious choice if you're
remaking the little mermaid is you get someone who generally looks like ariel that would be probably
your first instinct you can you can do something else but then you know you've got whiny old
fanboys like me who are just like well why the change this is my question why the change
and you know marketing like you said that's clearly the answer yeah yeah but that would be the answer
no matter what that would be the answer no matter what race ariel was the answer would the answer
why would be marketing um it would be because it would be because it makes the most money that's
that's just the thing that really annoys me about like the representation when it's used for marketing
for money for profit as a no no but everything is used for that it's not i know i know that yeah
but like in a world where people don't actually care and if the situation changes they'll just
stop doing it and then it's it's back to how it was yes you know that's what i don't like
you are on to something here right okay whether like whatever they decided to make area look like
it would be equally cynical like the fact that she they made her black is not more cynical than if
they decided to make either one would just be profit motivated and nothing else the problem
is that disney is able to make decisions like that and like like the fact that they have
like the fact that they can make ariel black and we can all look at that and go oh this is great
thank you disney thank you for representing minorities like you've like you're really helping
right like the fact that they have that power is fucked up if you really think about like the
fact that it means that much to people that ariel is black i don't even think it's bad i think it
but i think it's bad that it matters so much i think that just means that disney just has our
society by the balls and it's a nightmare with a neoliberalist capitalist nightmare uh and then
we live in hell dude hard agree dude hard agree you have a much more pessimistic view of life than i
do thank you okay let's get the hell out of here not to our next voicemail uh by cooking bad cooking
bad okay go i've called in before with a simple message hello fresh bad cooking good everyone
can do it it's literally easy yay but after seeing munchie make ramen i have to renounce
my previous stance boom some people just shouldn't be allowed to cook at all no it's a sad world we
live in and there's really no reason to make it any worse he saw your disgusting peanut but a ramen
and is rejecting it at a visceral physical level wasn't that a uh wasn't that a uh a uh a cluster
punk kitchen recipe yeah i don't i don't know well i guess you found it offensive it was hell no fresh
yeah it was hell no fresh who was in the voice grail for his contributions to the show he was i
think the very first person the voice grail uh well once we i mean you know fucking the real
mass batman was was you know on the on the trail before that but my my audio kind of at the end
did he give a reason why i was bad he did not clarify why he i think he expected to be obvious
which i assume was that peanut butter ramen looks gross is my guess okay it's just it just sort of
looks like a white sauce almost have you it was nice there there is food there is food that can be
tasty and delicious but look like absolute shit right yeah i don't i don't i don't know if you have
this conception dude i don't know if you if you've ever heard of food that looks weird but tastes good
i don't know sometimes you can have food that is just like a brown slop but it's like a robust
umami sense sensory overload uh curry looks in there curry looks disgusting and yeah it's very
i mean it just looks like some brown sauce you know yeah it doesn't look like i mean it looks pretty
gross i'm just saying i'm just saying well fair i'm just saying ugly food can taste good well
well that's that's what i'm saying too and i think that it's on brand for cluster punk kitchen
i think you should strive to make your food as ugly as a kitchen i'm very i'm very
that's where the that's where the ramen recipe right didn't cluster punk kitchen call in with
the recipe for peanut butter ramen no yeah i think so that was no it was hell no thresh you did that
wait it was it okay well maybe he had a show called cluster punk kitchen i can't i forget i forget
take a bite change your life that's right am i crazy am i fucking crazy here i think that's right
i have no idea who you're talking about no no no you i know who i was talking about yeah it's like
the guy who speaks really slow and is like take a bite change your life like that guy you've been
on an episode i feel like i feel like i'm me and bitter for like from alternate realities you know
we we've got we've got bear stain and we're in each other we got we got mandela effect we got
mandela effect yeah and we now neither one of us know what's happening okay well glad we sorted
that out let's get to our last voicemail all right brace yourselves because we've got another
call from wacky wavy inflatable tube man hashtag no voicemails matter okay let's bring it home go
we try nice baby
All right, you've had your say, and I'll have mine.
Fuck you.
Well, they've had fair warning now.
Yep.
Everyone gets one, and you know what?
I like inflatable wavy man a lot, and I like the cut of his gym, and you know what?
I'm sorry that I'm encouraging shit voicemails, but you know what?
I like that guy.
So good job.
I'll tell you this, though.
The audibility is a factor, Mr. Wavy Man, so you're on Thin Ice in the future.
I can't guarantee.
It's just barely comprehensible enough.
Yeah.
It's just riding that cut.
Well, half of it isn't, but you are able to clue in what he's saying based on the other
half, you know?
Yeah.
That's true.
It informs the other pieces, because language and shit.
Yeah, okay.
There you go, everybody.
That's the voicemails.
Watch out.
If you see on the street, you're driving by a car dealership, and you see one of those
wacky wavy inflatable tube man listening to this podcast.
Watch the fuck out.
Duck into an alley.
Don't let him make eye contact.
Or try to crash into him with your car.
Take him out and save your fellow listeners.
Do whatever it takes.
Highly recommended.
I guess that's it.
Hell yeah.
All right, we're done.
We're done.
That's it for today.
Hey, lads.
You know what you should do?
You should go to patreon.com slash the procrastinators.
Give us $1 and be in the Discord.
Give us $5 and get the bonus episodes, of which there's 27, including the most recent summer
cast.
Oh, it's summertime and the water is hot, and I am loving it.
If there's any PCP member who you are not subscribed to every channel they have, you're
not a true fan.
You got to watch all the content from everybody, or else you're gay.
Indeed.
Yes.
Watch.
Check out that feed.
Someone was...
I think they were talking shit about me.
Apparently, there's more than one place where there's a PCP content feed where all our shit
gets pumped into besides just the patron discord, but the patron discord's the place to be anyway.
And you get to give us money.
What a privilege.
Follow me on Topastic and Lion Webtoon if you'd be so kind.
Use every link that's in the description.
Post it on all my shit there.
Yeah.
Oh, by the way, update from the summer cast.
I did go to a water park since then, developed a wonderful tan, and look like a bronze god.
Oh, god.
Yeah.
Nate, okay.
My water park story is so vast and great and just so filled with terror and peril that
like it will have to be an entire segment next episode.
I'm so, I'm so remiss that I didn't talk about this time.
Okay.
We'll talk about it next time.
Oh, god.
Oh, you guys gave PTSD in such a terrible, visceral way.
I'm so...
I will talk glowingly about my experience.
I can't wait.
Yes.
For those who aren't aware, the most recent bonus episode was about summer, and that
is what he's referring to.
Yes.
So many subjects in great water parks.
To the patrons so you can listen to it.
And Nate, both went to water parks since the previous recording of the PCP, or did
we?
You'll have to find out.
You'll have to find out next episode.
Oh, my god.
Okay.
I'm hyped.
I'm excited.
Follow us at tpcrastinators on Twitter, updates, releases, et cetera, et cetera, good place
to be.
And that's it.
Thanks for listening, everybody.
See you next week.
Oh, so by the way, this episode went on so long so we can push back gay for a day premiere.
And haha, that's really funny.
Oh, yeah.
Bye.
Click on that shit to watch it.
Okay.
See you later, everybody.
Bye.
What the hell is wrong with me?