PCP? PCP?
PCP? PCP.
PCP. PCP. PCP. PCP. PCP. PCP. PCP. PCP.
Hello everybody, and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
We are the reason people are dying and you can now be the reason people are dying along
with us with the new I Am The Reason People Are Dying T-Shirt on the t-spring of The Pro
Crastinators Podcast.
Yay.
Leave the description.
Holy fucking shit, a t-shirt.
Yay.
We're gonna make more t-shirts.
Gotta make more like I honestly think we should we should we should all be obligated to make like one new t-shirt per month
We could churn out fucking shirts, okay?
I'm hypocrite that was Ben St. and Nate Bestman the best bangers
I'm voting for a t-shirt that says holy shit a t-shirt you should make it make it and put it on the PCV thing
easy to make um
Um, they're so easy well kind of if you know how teespring works, which I had to learn through a long and arduous arduous process
It was a give as well also dealt with some shit there. I mean he's my he's my I'm tutoring him
I'm tutoring hippo in the teespring arts. It's the uh, I'm an apprentice to that to that skill
Because teespring is is like a bucking bronco. It's really yeah, I went to college. I I majored in teespring
You know engineering and teespring uh usage. I'm pretty good. It's pretty lucrative career
Yes, it is hippo by the shirts you had to buy the by the shirts
Uh, they should be uh, I went and connected the youtube so you might by this point when you're listening to this
You might be able to see shirts down under the video. Oh hell. No hell. Yeah
Uh, you had a great idea hippo with a we talked about this before the show
And I'm gonna bring it back up the the where hashtag wears the podcast shirt
And I said that I said, yeah
I said I would love that but what I would really love to really solidify that meme is if
Whoever runs that podcast that pizza party podcast
I've heard so much about but haven't been able to locate
If one of them would acknowledge it if they would like be like why is everyone always saying hashtag?
Where's the podcast in the comments? What's going on? That would solidify it. That's that's my goal
They should they should make sure and they should all wear them
I just want them to acknowledge that no one can find this podcast. Yeah, the problem with that is that um
In order to leave a comment on the podcast
They need to find the podcast and we just can't find the podcast to leave the comments
I I can't find the podcast
But if anyone finds it, please leave a comment that says where's the podcast
Please leave a comment asking where the podcast is on my behalf and then and then
Let me know what they say because I'm I'm really looking
We need them to establish some sort of shirt on their end that says here's the podcast
And then we can wage epic large-scale warfare between the legions of where's the podcast
Everyone's got to choose a side in the battle of good versus evil. Are you team?
Where's the podcast or team? Here's the podcast
It's truly the red and blue shown in a single a single a single w separates heaven from hell. Let's rock
Uh
I speaking of
Speaking of winning welcome to episode 150 of the procrastinators podcast people because there's a hundred and fifty
Oh
To pcp members are destiny. Oh, that's good. Yeah, but you'll never be just give up that home
Pidgeot, just as ash ketchup niterino gold duck. Oh my night. Slow. Slow. Mewtwo tentacle aero dactyl
Oh my night. Slow. Hey guys
Mewtwo tentacle aero dactyl. Oh my night. Slow. Shut up. Shut up enough
Fuckin go back and in in in every podcast you will you'll find if you look hard enough a secret, uh, meme
A secret code that links to the specific pokemon that the episode is the number of
I've I've been leaving them all in every episode from the very beginning. I thought this far ahead
I knew there would be 150 episodes. I knew it wouldn't have been a waste of time
We'll get I'll give you a hint. I'll give you a hint of one episode episode one best game ever
What's the most gamer pokemon? You know, you know the answer to that
It's definitely I was thinking rotom rotom looks like a hardcore game, but he's not number one. Fuck rotom
It might be it might be bulbous or though. Um, it's up to you to figure out one of those two. It's definitely one of those two
Um, depends what decks depends what regional decks you're using some regions. It's rotom. Yeah, that's fair
In in gamer in uh in gang weed, uh region, you know the gamer verse, uh, I think rotom is pokemon 001
Isn't game reverse a real thing
Um, I hope so make something called the game reverse
Oh god, he would from game grumps ross. He would make something wait. It might be the game. That sounds like a nostalgia critic
It might it might be the game over the game, but whatever it is. I think it's a bell, but I don't know what it is
Uh, it doesn't sound impressive. Let's talk about how much I hate ross
No, okay before we talk about how much we hate ross, let's talk about the thing that we totally
Intentionally, you guys did not talk about on the last pcb episode because this is the pokemon episode 150
Let's talk about pokemon sword and shield and how it was just announced
And how it looks like a real video game. It was completely unmentioned last episode
Well, you did do a whole other like a stream, but it was on nate's channel. I think well, yeah, that's true
That's strong
And while you all should go to definitely twitch.tv slash definitely best guy ever and subscribe, um, nonetheless
Some people did not and so they need to up
We I mean, yeah, it's fair to say just go watch the video. It's on my live stream channel and stuff, but yeah
I mean, I
Think I said everything I had to say about it on this on that stream
Well, I wasn't on the stream and I tweeted about it like all day after the announcement
Like all that day I was making tweets about sword and shield
I made a few tweets as well
Yeah, it was all it was all shit pokemon comes out social media is blast and you can see sobel
You can see groovy. You can see bunny
And you can see them everywhere
Uh, cool. Let's let's get into it. Let's get into it new starters all stupid all the all the same round head
All the same shape. Yeah
Underwhelming underwhelming. I don't know. I don't care overly homogenous designs. I don't care about the round heads
I don't care that much, but I do think it's a pretty weak badge
Look, everyone knows they're fine. Levolution is the one that really matters. Yes. That's true. That's true
No, and in the case of torchic that is not true
Uh, well, yes, some people really like blaziken. I'm not one of those people. Yeah the digimon fans of the pokemon
I don't hate him. You like blaziken. I don't hate blaziken. He's fine
I mean, he was the first of his kind right the first of the digimon in pokemon
Was he before was he before druddigon?
Yes, probably I forget who that is, but yes
Uh, he looks like a digimon. He's that blue. He's a blue dragon with a red head
Oh, yeah, it was before that. I uh, I remember you guys talking about like, oh, is it england or is it not?
And I guess at this point it's been confirmed. You were you were like it's england. Um and stuff
No, it's great britain not just england. Well, yeah
Oh, fair. Oh, very good. I didn't see an island anywhere. The lecture gave about that some more. Why don't you mage?
You fucking foreigner. Cool
That's called that's literally cultural appropriation
Knowing things about the United Kingdom. You came over here, you're an imogrant
You get out so you get to the brush the broom and sweep you out the door. Wait. No, you get out
Uh
Hippo hippo care is from africa hippo is from africa. So he's an imogrant
Oh new character in the hippo court universe the imogrant. Uh, yeah, he should I don't know
Well, it's it's a side story
It's like it's like after after hippo wasn't allowed to make videos anymore. He like he had to like walk the earth
He's a stranger in every land. It's like it's alt universe. That that is canon hippo hippo is walking the earth right now
Yeah, in search of the purpose
Yeah, frankly. I'm not optimistic about his chances. He's a very small boy. So, you know, it's a very very small animal
Speaking of small boys small animals pokemon, right?
Uh bunny. Yeah, I like him. Uh the little lizard guy. He's he's funny. I saw I like that
He's crying all the time. That's funny. Yeah, he's just so like
That's his cry. That's his cry because he's crying
Uh groovy is just a guy with a thing. He has a he's a farfetched
You know, I've heard a lot of people saying that groovy is gonna evolve into like a
Metal drummer or like some kind of like like drummer. Oh, which sounds pretty cool
And I would be into that if true. Oh, yeah, that that was the thing I was thinking like pokemon based off of things in
The great britland the u.k.
Mum Keith mum Keith threatened me. He told me I better not pick the monkey and I told him he can have that gremlin
But if he turns into a cool rock drummer, I might regret my words. I might eat. I might eat my words
Yeah, if he turns into a drummer, I'm definitely gonna name him bonzo because that's the perfect name
Why is that the perfect name to everyone who knows the reference?
I don't know the I'm not I'm not in on the reference
Because you don't know you don't know enough about english rock legends. That's why I know neil pert
He's english. I think
Wait, is russian american
No, russia's american
russian russian limbaugh
Yeah, he's american the famous drum, uh, but like, uh
Bunny right that I saw there was a soccer field a football field
So i'm thinking maybe that's a football playing bunnies running real fast. He's got like the color of things
You know the whiteness
White people play football only white people are allowed. There's a lot of racism in the football community
So like that fits that works. Hell. Yeah
Yeah, and the little
Crying guy, that's me. So like it all is like very accurate to england
And I and I really want to see if there's like a t-based pokemon or like a
Oh, yeah, you know like a black pudding pokemon. I want a garden. No, I want a garden. No pokemon
Yeah, I think you're already doing pretty well with like the knights and shields and swords
Garden pokemon sounds pretty funny actually
It's like ground fairy type
And like it doesn't actually look like a gnome, but it's got like the hat
Shape that's like definitely what I would love. What I would love is like um a pokemon
That's like a suit of armor and if it comes into contact with an age slash or whatever the sword guy is
Um, then he then they evolve into like, you know how like um
Sheldre clamps onto a slow poke and they turn into the other guy
It'll be like that sort of thing
Wait, he just gets a weapon and he wields it. He wields his friend and then he's super powered
That would be really cool. Who's kind of the best pokemon, uh, who reminds me of that? You know, you know gollerc
Gollerc rock flying or no, he's rock ghost. I think he's he's ground ghost
Ground ghost and he can just fly because he's a hero. He can kind of the best goller can fly
Uh, is he the evolved form or is he the first form? He's the evolved
Okay, the the whole point of that ghost rock golem looking pokemon is that when he evolves where he learns fly
Because his whole thing is that he's a giant golem who can just fly
That's weird. How sick is that that's the coolest thing sick of all time
Yeah, it's kind of funny like the idea of like a rock that has departed
From the mortal realm and it's ground. He's made of clay
So like he can he can like, you know
If you smash a rock it becomes a rock ghost and then it hits you because it can still it's still a rock
I gotta I gotta put this in the show notes. Um, you gotta behold the image of gollerc in the okay
It's going in the links thing. There it is. Uh, like this is him
He's just like a mech who just flies and it's sick as shit. Uh, is this in gross disgusting audio? Whoa
Oh, he that's that's
Oh, that's cool. I don't know. I've seen that guy before I think that was like an edit
I think the bottom one's like the the the real one if that's it. Okay
Is that a shiny color because if so, it's really cool, but I doubt it. I think so because shiny
I'm gonna look up shiny. I don't know. I haven't I haven't checked the top one looks like a bend 10 guy
He does. Yeah, he does. He does. You know, I kind of want to go back. It's kind of rfck
I love tyranitar, but I kind of want to put gollerc is my favorite rock type pokemon
I'm telling you he's ground
Damn it. How many times do I have to say it?
Yeah, okay. Good point. Doesn't he just look like a rock guy though? I guess he's mud though, which is
Yeah, all right. I think he's supposed to be made of clay. I mean, he's a golem and golems are made out of clay
I that's true. That's true. Oh, no, that is. Uh, yeah, that's that's his shiny color
He's got like a green kind of crack in him and he's kind of grayish and bluish dark. Yeah, awesome
There you go. I like the the the aesthetic of him being like, uh
Cracked open but then with a little metal plaster
Yeah, just go yeah, you're super cool
Every single that's just part of the process of making a golerc is like you you fuse him in the in the kiln
And they all crack across the middle and then you put the band-aid on him and then bam you got yourself a golerc
By the way, I might be wrong about him learning fly by evolving because I'm not seeing it in his
Thing, but whatever. I'm just assuming that's true. He learns flea because he's a fucking coward
Anyway, he's a badass. Uh, he's killer it but it can it can learn fly
Yeah, it can learn fly. So that's confirmed. That's confirmed. Oh, I just remembered. Um, is the bunny called score bunny?
Like scoring a goal like goal
So I think he's gonna he's gonna evolve to have a football or something
He's gonna have some dumb
Don't you hate those kind of powers like yamcha where he like makes an energy ball and then he like volleyball
Is it it's like just shoot him with the laser gun
No, just my my boy my boy's my boy's spork spork town hero drew something on twitter that just
Is the weirdest thing girl I didn't
uh, nothing
I didn't um, I didn't uh
Understand, but it was it was score bunny evolving to
Into like a wheelchair
Yeah, yeah, because um, because um, what they probably like broke his leg or something and and like couldn't pursue its career
Like in these like evolves into like a amputee
I thought the joke was that like the first guy has a piece of tape on his nose
And then as he evolves he like has more more wounds and more injuries until he's like in a wheelchair at the end
And he's mad about it
You know what he should be in true soccer player fashion
He should be he should evolve into finally like flop bunny
Or like his main move is that he pretends to be injured to elicit
And and yellow cards on the other opponents that he's fighting
Uh, or he injures himself perhaps to do this
You know, I've just realized what if they have like pokemon football like a sports team where you choose who plays in what?
like uh thing
And the stats
Determine how cool. Yeah
Like uh, oh, yeah, I'll put like goal lurk in in goal and he's so big
I'll put like whale lord in goal. Nobody would get pasta. Yeah
That that would be like a really good mini game that they could imagine like mega man soccer, but with pokemon
Imagine like ape escape to soccer, but with pokemon
Yeah
Ape escape to soccer is the best thing
Wait, is that a real thing?
Yeah, and there's a mini game. It's not ape escape soccer. It's ape escape to soccer
Yeah, because in ape escape to
Oh, it's a mini game
Yeah, one of the mini games you can unlock out of three
So the you know, there's only there's not so that many of them
But there's like every ape you can collect in the game
You can they have certain stats the the more powerful monkeys
Have like higher stats and higher later in the game
You can find like really powerful monkeys and special monkeys like the santa claws monkey monkey claws
Uh, they have like really good stats and you you just play football against ai and or a friend
and it's just like the the silliest and best football game ever made because
You the the main thing is that you run around with the left stick and with the right stick you choose which direction to kick
Oh, that's good
So instead of it being like a whole like oh press the x button to shoot if you're in the right position
You you pass with the with the the you know the shape buttons triangle circle
To to the to you know
A bunch of monkeys who have that over their heads, you know instantly who that is that's that's normal
But then to shoot you just push the direction and if you kick it really hard with a monkey that has really high attack stat
You can just kick the ball
Smash it into the monkey's face that's in front of you and knock him out
And you can just keep doing that and and if the ball goes out of bounds
You know there's a chance that the ball thrown back in could be like a spike ball
Instead of the regular ball and if you kick that that like knocks them out and then that you know half time comes around
They have no energy left. They can't play anymore. You have to swap them out for someone else. It's epic
That reminds me of kind of blitz ball from final messy 10 only
Better everybody loves everybody loves blitz ball
What's the fuck I'm here too. It's me. Hey, what's up?
Is it is it daylight savings time? Is that why I'm late? Is it not my fault? Good. I'm glad I did at everybody
But you know, you know fair it is in fact daylight savings time
Hi jess you recording. Hi. Yes. I am. Okay. We are talking about pokemon mostly and and let's get down to brass tax people
Because here's the deal. Oh, by the way, jesse. This is episode 150. So, you know pokemon. We did it
Ommonite slow poke mule tool tentacle aero dactyl
Ben stop, please. I can't. I'm just stuck in a loop. Dude, ben. We should we should put that on a shirt
The same board's over and over again. Just ommonite slow. I did it. I did it. I made a meme
I pushed it so hard gross that everyone loved it
No, just just just that part of the ninja rap but repeated over and over again
You put like the symbols for like each of them you put like an ommonite shell
Like a pigeon feather or something and you just repeat the what what is the say the say the line one time ben?
Well, now I don't want to say it anymore. You made me feel
I forget what it is got ommonite slow poke mule tool ten mule two tentacle aero dactyl
Okay, there you go. So that five that's the meme put those in a row and make it incredible
Make it short that just does a mule tool and it's like a mule tube
But like he's got like wrenches in his hands and shit. No, but he wait wait hold. He's mute. That's my cool
But he's like a god kid and he's wearing like a tool shirt because he really likes the band
Yeah, yeah, like uh, he's like tim ellen
Much better new tim allen new tim allen new tim allen that's that's all good, but here's hey
Here's a thing. Uh, so new pokemon sword and shield. That's all cool
New boy and new girl most importantly. So there's a new pokemon girl. I like her a lot. I can't she looks exactly like the last one
Who gives a no, she's different
No, they do they they look exactly the eyes and the mouth and the face and the hair shape is exactly
Definitely have the same dead eyes
They I don't know what the pokemon company is like the most successful game franchise in history
And all their games look like shit. What's there?
That doesn't look like shit. It's just like they don't need to make it any more than that
Because the kids just they just care about they don't care about I was I was indulging a parent
Character that they are I was indulging want to look at the pokemon in one of my many vices
um watching arlo videos
uh, and I uh
Yeah, I was listening to his thoughts about uh the new pokemon and he's like, yeah, you know, it looks fine
But it doesn't look you know, it doesn't look like a game that makes like
Billions of fucking dollars like no, it doesn't it doesn't it is a disturbing vice. Yeah
You like you can not even go into like a closet in the dark to watch arlo videos
Oh, oh and let people know about that shit. I put on I pull out my puppet and he's the one who watches arlo videos
Not me. I'm not watching
All right guys, uh on the topic of arlo
I've I've had a problem with arlo in the past because I always thought like, you know, the muppet thing
He doesn't really go very far with it
Indeed indeed. How could he go any further with it?
Well, you know by by no what I mean is like he's not he doesn't use it for comedy necessarily
Or like he's just not very funny with it
But recently I found I found a muppet who is a stand-up comedian and he is he's unbelievably funny
No, uh
Both because both because you know the jokes are pretty good and he seems to have a you know a real grasp of reality
And he's not like a dumb idiot
But also his his his muppet movements are so correct
Like like like
I'm trying to find what it it's called randy his randy the he looks like a grape
Um, I'm looking him up. I'm I'm googling him. I saw he has he has a he has a special
And that I found on youtube called randy writes a novel
And it's a it's a that sounds really good just from the title
Yeah
Oh, he's really creepy looking. Oh, no, but he's great and he swears as well because it is like he's he's like uh
Randy writes a novel he does look like he's spooky
He yeah, but he's like an he's an australian, uh, you know vegan crazy man who is a really good muppet
puppeteer
And he's now sounds like it's really funny
unironically now this is epic
Yeah
Everybody should go look at that
I'm looking i'm gonna watch more of this later
um, okay, hey to make us a fun happy time
uncomfortably
Uncomfortable for everyone. Please I want the reason I brought up shield chan
Is because so new pokemon came out new pokemon girl
Everyone starts making porn of her right? That's just what happens every single time. Oh my god
Amazing. I I I'm sorry. I'm so I'm I'm really hung up that everyone's like oh the new girl's cute
She looks exactly like the old girl
She's got a new hat. What do you want? Yeah, new new fucking hat
Her hair only curls in on one side of her face. You can fucking change your hair curled on both sides
You know, you can go to the fucking barber. She's the same girl. I hate it
Every every human-shaped thing is going to be the same if you can customize the appearance
You can just make that's not like whatever. She's the exact same face the exact same body customizable hair
I feel like a lot of a lot of the time
Is exactly the same thing where all the girls are exactly the same person except the hair is different and everyone thinks
Look, I watch anime. That's always been the case. That's always been the case
That's just not surprising real life. Also. Most people are just interchangeable sacks of shit with different hair
Look, I get your point Ben and I actually agree. It's just that I don't know. I'm I'm over it. I guess I've just accepted that this is
I don't if you can customize the appearance then
I don't know. You just make them look however you want exactly. She's not a new girl. She's nobody
Okay, but she has a default design. Look, she's Scottish. This is her biggest personality trait that she people whatever
They never have personality. We infer we we put a personality onto her. She's a rough and tumble Scottish lass
That's what's been projected by the audience. That's a distinct personality
It's exactly the same whatever the girl from black and white looked like like she had a design
Like yeah, this the new girl doesn't have a design all she has is a sweater and a hat
That's literally all you can do the thing the thing that is just the case
Is that the thing is announced and everybody gets hyped when it's announced and they you know, they see her and they're like
Oh, I can't wait to play pokemon. Oh, and she's a girl. That means I want to have sex with her
So I'm gonna do a porn of her. I'm gonna give her a character and she's like that hat. That's a Scottish hat
She's a Scottish lass and there's that means she's angry and she punches people great
I love this person. The boy is all in their heads and it's it's it's all in our collective heads in the video game
Nothing not even slightly gonna be like that
But we like it we get we get hyped by ourselves
Well, it's the same as toho like toho the characters barely of any personality
They have a little bit and it's the fandom that runs with it at least they say that's just how it is
At least the characters in toho. Yeah, do have dialogue. They do have
Well, like I don't know like the the main character persona. I've been led to believe
It's a it's a player avatar. It has no defined personality. It's how you play it that gives it a personality
So, you know, that's not true in toho. That's not true in toho. That's yeah, you're right. That's not true in toho
I mean, I can't remember when they stopped doing this
But isn't it like the character you choose the opposite gender character that you could have been is your rival and they do have a character because they have lines
I think so. Yeah. Yeah, but like uh in the last one was in sun and moon
Yeah, like that they're changing it now. So that's true. That's true. There is no character whatsoever
Wait, it's it's been through some sapphire and ruby and sapphire and ruby that definitely was how it works
Oh, yeah, that's that's the one I remember because that's my favorite. Sometimes it's like that not always
Yeah, that's true. Well, hey, okay. Here's my point. Here's the thing. I want to talk about it's just that
New pokemon comes out. There's a girl whatever
Well, I think in a game with I think in a game with customizable characters. They won't do that
I think they just never gonna get to say I just want to say they it won't be like it's so provocative
It's so big brain
They won't I'm just saying they won't do that because the characters have no set design
And there's no point making them a rival because they are no one
I guess that makes sense. I get well, I don't know. There was no character
In emerald or sapphire ruby. There there was kind of like there may is a character
Yeah, may and that's only because the show the show gave me her character. She's she's nobody. Well, I've never seen the show
And I know what maze like she has big boobs. That's her character. That's not even accurate. Okay, whatever
Um, uh speaking of big boobs. This is my point. All right. Here it is. This is my point people are complaining
About people making porn about the pokemon girl. This is the point. I want to get you. She literally is her hat
Uh, she's she's she's indiana jones. That's my point though, ben. That's my point. Look, I get it
People come out of the woodwork and they're like, oh my god guys. What are you doing sexualizing like a canonically 12 year old girl?
But this is not a real person and this person is so undefined a personality or an existence
And the porn of her doesn't even necessarily draw her at that age generally doesn't right? I mean, how would you even know?
How would you even I just it brings to my mind? How can anyone
Care about this issue is what comes to my brain?
I don't understand like if people are looking for things to get mad about and find reasons to be it's a it's a it's a combination
Of virtue signaling and also extreme mental retardation
Where they actually believe that lines on a piece of paper is a person. Yes
If you don't believe that then you can't care about this issue
You have to be mentally fucking retard the fact of the matter is like you look at pokemon and like characters that are like 12
18 20 30 they all pretty much look the same
Like you can't really even tell until they start to get into like middle age
It's like they expect are like our our vision when we look at an anime character
We should be able to see past
Like the the physical appearance of the character and be able to deduce like the stat sheet and see uh-oh age
Uh, you know below 18 if that means sexuality switched off
We cannot you know, but that's not it just makes me so mad that I see people and look
I know it's probably like a fringe group, but surprisingly large
Surprising large number of people I'm gonna I'm gonna play the devil's advocate on this one. Okay. Um, I feel like it's not
Play the devil's advocate and advocate against pedophilia
Yeah
indeed
Like I feel like
With anything of this nature where you you know as a person says like oh my god. Oh my god a porn
Yeah, it's just because they're young with a bokeh no hero academia characters. They're like. Oh my god. They're like canonically 14
Stop guys. It's not even that it's unreal age. It's it's that they're just like they they are
um
Young themselves and they're like they maybe not like they've seen some porn and like oh, I don't know whether I like this yet
And pokemon is for young people lots of sure ages are gonna be looking at pokemon related things and then uh-oh
You know they stumble across something that is sexualized and they're like oh god damn it again
I you know for them the only other time this has happened is the last time that they noticed
Uh, which is like, I don't know
Some game that came maybe undertale or something or delta room
Like that was the first time it happened for them and they're like what the fuck the second time it's pokemon
And then they're complaining even more when you talk about the first time they became sexually aware while playing undertale
Is that no no, I mean like I mean like the first time that they've seen rule 34 stuff
Of things like they've just become a teenager
In that would understand that that's fucked up maybe
And that they would have a problem dealing with it
And it's like I
I can't you know
I can't get too mad about the people getting mad about it because I don't know how old they are and I can assume that you know
They're just kicking up a stink because they're a kid
The way I don't know it seems to me like there's some older people, but here's a question
Let's just say there's like you've got whatever misty, right?
She's she is canonically like 10 or 12 or whatever 12
I draw a sexualized picture of misty and say next to it misty age 25
And now she's got the big the zongas and the big booty like okay, then we're like, oh, this is fine
I guess what if I just erase age 25 next door and it's like, oh my god
You've sexualized this 10 year old as like a big sexy baby
Stick if you if you draw a stick figure and just say oh, that's a five year old then that's
Like I'm I'm over this topic. I don't I don't believe I don't believe that anyone actually cares as much as you're saying they care
I also agree with that. I don't believe anyone really cares about anything
I think that everyone in the world is just constantly virtue signaling about everything
I don't believe that anyone actually has any stake in any of these bullshit fucking issues
I hope so like they'd say like oh
This is fucked up right and then like in brackets the inner thoughts
I kind of like it though, but I don't want anybody to know. I don't want my friends to know
And then in smaller brackets inside those brackets
They think but if I see someone else doing this then maybe I can get somebody else publicly shamed and yeah
That's when someone's life. He I'm getting a lot of this from threads on 4chan
Where people like it is the place where you just attempt to like fuck other people up and insult them and make them feel bad about stuff
So maybe not the best sources though. I know there are some real people who feel this way. I know it is a fact, but
Uh, maybe they are a small minority who deserve to be shoveled into a fucking hole in the ground and shot with a rifle
Yeah
Okay, well that was the thing I wanted to say about shield chan and you know what?
I'm gonna fucking jack off to shield chan after this podcast
I don't give a fuck if people can suck my dick when you've jack off to shield hero
Yeah, maybe I will when you say shield chan. I think you're talking about someone from shield hero
Reftalia because I don't know anything about shield hero. I'll go jack off to her too
And you know what as the loli as a fucking loli slave because I don't give a shit. That's how I feel people
This is a protest fap. That's what I'm going to do and you can't stop me
All right
Hell yeah
Hell yeah, um
I've got a
I've got a gross story
If if if you're all if you're all okay with a bit of gross stories. I'm ready
We've been talking a lot about poop lately. So I feel prepared. Yeah. Well, this involves poop. I'm hopeful. Oh, no
So, all right, so I've been the last few days
Uh, got a cold. Whoops. It's the it's the cold that goes around and everyone's getting it
The family got it. I got it. I was like, okay. Well, I've had a thousand calls at this point
I know how to deal with the cold you drink a lot of water
You don't be stupid and that then it goes away and that's fine
um
This cold caused a different problem which has made me
Bedridden almost almost bedridden and it's really fucked me up
And here's what happens
So when you have a cold you get dehydrated really quickly you need to drink water because your body is like drying up
I don't know exactly why
But you feel dry all the time your lips get chapped and you're like, oh
If need a drink so you have a drink
And then you go to bed
I go to bed and then through the night I become crusty and withered and dusty and
Everything's fucked. Yeah, I wake up and I'm like, oh
No, yeah, yeah, and and in my intestine like a beast whale
Yeah, in my in my in my gut things that have been digesting
Have solidified into like a a brick
And this is you know, this is like, ah shit sucks, you know, similar to
You know Nate's problem a while ago, but I knew I shouldn't eat a lot of carrots. That's what I shouldn't do
Yeah
Um, so I was like, okay. Well, I know how to deal with this as well. I've had this happen a lot
Uh, you just you drink a lot of water and you do the the things you eat the right food
I I had some lens sips, uh, because of the cold
Oh, uh, uh, night will probably be the equivalent
Okay, uh medical drink
I had some of those and I was like, that's good hot water
That's good for clearing stuff out and then I was like, I'll have some tea as well
And you know what I'll have some milk in my tea because
Uh milk makes me burp and that that means that it's good for indigestion for digesting things, right? That's good
Yeah, it's incorrect completely incorrect. I had way too much milky teas and caffeine
Because I was trying to work through the sickness and I ended up doing quite a lot of work on the first day
but then I went to bed again
And uh, this was the worst night of my life
At least in 2019. Are you sure?
uh
So basically every five minutes I would have to get up to take an hour's long shit
And I was I was sitting there in the toilet with my legs up on on the seat
Straining nothing was happening. Oh my god. Yeah. Uh, it was like, okay
This is you know, it's one thing to be constipated. It's another thing to also have a headache and be dehydrated
from a cold that
Your throat is sore and you're sneezing really loudly so so loudly so consistently
That my rib cage started aching because of how much my lungs were expanding and contracting sneezing so loudly
Yeah
So I was like
And so
You know
It sucks and then the milk started to to react with all the stuff that was going on. I was the milk anything
Yeah, I milk I I was you know going back to bed after like not shitting anything out and like
Moving around trying to jostle at it. You know, you know the stuff sure
But then the milk started bubbling and creating a pockets of gas
And I started burping and I started burping a lot and I started farting a lot and I started burping and farting a lot
And it was really it was really satisfying when I got one of those farts out because like my butthole was like there was a brick in the way
Yeah, I know sure. Yeah, I would have killed for a fart during when I was constipated. Yeah, it was like it's like
It's
Like one of those so I was like, oh well god damn thanks for that, but there's not enough and I keep burping
Um, it's like 2 a.m. I'm still going to the toilet every five minutes. It's agony
I'm really need sleep and I can't have it
And then I start burping some more and the burps start to taste acidic and I'm like
Well, here it comes here it comes
Well, well well
Look who dropped in and I I I go turn around and I I up chuck fuck spew
All of my last dinner just happened to be fish and chips, which uh, I like it's very delicious
I know which is probably why it was so bad. Uh, I vomited it all out. It was very very loud and fish oil
It was it was very loud. I was screaming like
Oh
It came out my nose and everything and it was oh my god for real. Holy shit. Yeah, it was one of those big ones
But like Jesus Christ after I know that after
Vomiting you feel a little better, right? Because it's the problem's gone that stuff is out
Not the case because I still had the cold and I was still I was still bunged up down downstairs
And now what a phrase now what I had
Right is I had acid
Going up my throat that was already sore from sneezing and coughing
So now I had double acid burn ouch on my throat
And in my nose because I had so much mucus it caught a lot of the vomit
And for like the last the the next like 30 minutes
I was blowing my nose and bits of fish and chip were like coming out in clumps
It was terrible
Well, and um and then uh, I still couldn't shit. I I woke up the dog
I think by by vomiting so how I'm really like I'm happy that the dog was cared about me
And he heard me vomiting and he started barking like oh no. Oh no. What's going on?
And that woke up my mom and she came and gave me some water and it was like, okay
Uh, shit
Terrible
And so I it was like 5 a.m. By the time I actually managed to fall asleep
After that it was you know not no more burping
So it was just sort of like pain constantly and I managed to not fall asleep really and then
Today I have been basically doing nothing and staring at my screen and thinking
Maybe maybe I could at least you know play a video game
If I can't work on anything maybe I could play a video game. I can't even play a video game
My head's hurt so much. I can't even watch a youtube video. I was watching a red letter media thing
I was like
Shut up
Shut up. I turned it off and then I was sitting around and I was just like god damn it
Fuck
And that's my story
Oh, and then I started being on the podcast
Hooray
I'm glad you're still alive though
I want to quickly say though like now to prevent all of that that for people who are ill
Don't eat dairy products like the only dairy product you could you could you could eat
It's probably like a yogurt, but not like those flavored whatever fake yogurts. It's like a plain Greek yogurt or something
Yeah, yeah, naturally yogurt. Those are good for you
It's not like not only was I having like milky tea, but like I do some weed
I mean that might have worked
But like I I accidentally why didn't accidentally I stupidly had a slice of new this new lovely cheesecake that was in the fridge
It's like ah lovely big slice
It was delicious and I didn't even realize and then I was looking up later like what not to do when you're ill and
Constipated and sneezing and it was like don't don't milk. No, and I was like, oh
Do not let the milk you don't
Cows of the world rest your milk at the old milk mill
It's it's because it's difficult to digest dairy products and like when you're ill and have a fever your
Um stomach just sort of shuts down
Yeah, you know the pH changes in your stomach and you can't digest
This segues perfectly into what I wanted to talk about which is ice cream snacks
All right
Listen, okay, so everyone knows that I'm post food and I hate food
Um, but I make an exception. I'm interested for his tasty ice cream snacks. They're so good. No, no, listen
I make an exception. Uh, I'm I'm intellectually curious about like
No, shut up. I'm serious
Stop laughing
I'm I'm intellectually curious about like
Weird snack foods that other countries have that I've never heard of and I heard about one
From australia. It is okay. Well, first of all, I found out that in australia. They call popsicles icy poles
Which I thought was really funny wrong
Well, that's wrong. Just gotta update that this is not a popsicle
It's it's one of those ice cream on a stick type deals. Uh, and it is called the golden gay time
Oh, I've heard of it. Yeah, and their slogan is
It's hard to have a gay time on your own
True, so contrary. It looks really good
It's like it looks like butterscotch. I mean, I'm guessing it's like butterscotch and vanilla or caramel and vanilla ice cream
It looks like it's ice cream products from other countries and have it survive the trip
Maybe and and it looks like and it looks like it's coated in like crushed heath or butterscotch or something
I don't know, but they got other flavors, right? Let me read you a couple of these other flavors. They got
Um
They got unicorn flavor. Nice. That's gay. They got real gay. They got if you like pina colada flavor
And they got choc mint mc mint face
And uh, last one again, australia
Is it I okay now like did body mc vote phase get named after it or did it got named after
Body mc vote phase or is it just a coincidence?
I don't know what that is. I think people have always just been putting something mix something face on things
It's like a weird stupid human thing
This compulsion does something mix something face everything they see
It's just really weird that you would be like we got to make a new flavor of our of our highly coveted ice cream bar
And we're gonna call it and we're gonna make a chocolate mint flavor. We're gonna call it choc mint mc mint face
Is this like some millennial shit infiltrating the company mc donald's face stupid names? I don't know. I don't know
The new mc donald's burger burger mc burger face. It's just like it's got like five patties this time
And then and then they start a twitter account that is burger mc burger face and the burger is tweeting at other burgers
I refuse to let my generation take the fall for stupid names as if we invented them. Okay
I mean, you know older generations caught a bunch of shrimp and called them sea monkeys
That's that's wrong. That's not correct at all. That's incorrect. Yeah, that's fair. They're not they're not monkeys
They're not even part of the great eight family
Check the genus and file on you dunces. Jesus christ
Yeah, they did it. They did it for the marketing thing so for the lulls
I think I heard I think I saw a video about the sea monkeys guy and I think he was like a nazi or something
I think he was like a real big eugenicist or something really cool
He was a scammer through and through
Yeah
That stuff. I think he was hoping to use those. No, I think he was a kkk. I think he was like a keynote kkk
A key a keto kkk. Is that what kkk is very sensible? No, he was not one of us. Keto kido kido kido kido kido kids club
Yeah, that's what it is
Fuck yeah
You gotta start a brand new shirt the keto kids club
It just says kkk. You know, yeah
I have a strong urge a lot of the time to tweet things about being in the cool kid like in a video
I say that I say I say the cool kids club all the time and I want to as a joke write kkk on screen
But then I know like oh Jesus here we go with this guy wanting to kill all minorities and you know
Well, that's yeah, you know classic Nate bestman
You know what I'm annoyed about is that I can't I can't make I mean obviously you can't make racy jokes anymore, but like
It's this
You can but like people will not assume that you were joking. They will assume that you're one of those people who actually think it
And you have an argument with them. It was like I'm just I was just being you know
Exaggerated for effect, you know for a comedy thing and then they like reply with oh, I was just pretending to be retarded
Well, shut up. Oh, right. They're saying that you are in fact like obfuscating your true intentions now after the fact
You've been criticized or you're like you're normalizing like you're you're normalizing this this hateful language or
Yeah, I mean, I don't mean really that's what they do on 4chan or whatever like it's all memes, but it's not actually
Yeah, I guess like I don't even mind the normalizing thing. It's just like I would like to not have people
Assume things of me based on
Jokes I make so I guess I'll just stop making those jokes
I mean you go you go you go to you go to poll you go on poll and it's all you know everyone's like ha ha
So funny to joke about how the jews control everything, but you know, but they kind of actually do though like yeah, but you know
They kind of we kind of actually believe this fine. That's fine. Well, I mean I mean they do but it is a joke
sure
But like like to me it's
It's funny that the world is so fucked that like secret societies control everything and that we're all complete slaves
And we're all fucking doomed and society is going to collapse and the and the super wealthy
Will stamp their feet on our necks for all time. I mean like you just got to laugh at it
Did you guys see by any chance reminds me about the world going to hell?
Anyone see the the jewellery I mean I'm talking about people being racist like scary racist like
This the real yeah, I know what you mean like I know what you mean though like
Sure, like I don't know means like ha ha aren't aren't black people stupid
But then like also like but it is cool that the cops shoot him a lot
I mean, yeah, I feel I feel like the cultural battle
Look, I'm sure people would disagree and I don't have a ton of life experience in these areas
But like I feel that the whole racism issue
Is is at a point where it's less of a problem for the world than like
I don't know the suppression of global communities and like the control of the population by technocrats
That's what I've done with racism as an issue completely like I'm over it. It's solved as far as I'm concerned
I'm done pretending that racism is a problem. I'm done pretending that it's bad like it's it's funny
Fuck off racism. It's funny. Everybody suck my fucking dick. It's funny
I mean
I get it. I'm not a minority
People get shot out there in the real world
People definitely get shot and it's fucked up and you know what maybe even there's like some racist stuff going on
That makes people more likely to shoot like a black dude who's just walking down the street than a white dude
Totally fair. Totally fair. Um, I don't know don't mistake internet for real life. Just please
Because in real life in real life, I'm pretty sure racism is a lot, you know
scarier and and more threatening than someone
I just I just hate I just hate this idea that people have this completely insane
ludicrous notion
Literally a ludicrous notion like the rapper who is a black man
This notion that like if you say something racist, then you're racist. That's not how it works
Like if you oh, yeah, you've made some pretty good points on that in the past
If you believe something racist you're racist if you do something racist you're racist if you say something racist
You're just being cool. Well, it's fucking funny. Okay. I mean, I get you I get you
But like say you're you're an outside observer and you hear someone say something racist
Like it's like hippo was saying you're not it's not crazy in this day and age to think that this person making this joke
Actually believes the thing that he's making because people do it all the time
Well, that's how the problem there is just this Trump got elected
Well, yeah, but the problem there is just this epidemic of mass retardation where nobody can decipher context anymore
Or nobody can understand when somebody is clearly obviously not
The context has been deliberately obfuscated
Ben, please clarify what you just meant about that's how Trump got elected because I I don't understand what your point
What I think Trump got okay. I will clarify what I mean by that is that
Fucking everyone thought it was real funny and a real funny meme to be a white nationalist and
That's what happened because it was a real fun. Trump is not a white nationalist
No, but like the people who voted for him. Yeah, I'm confused about
Like I get what you're laying down. We're I we're kind of talking about two different things here, but I get you
Well, I mean, I'm just saying from an outs
Pete people
You know, there's people that make jokes to be funny and there's people that make jokes
So that they can say what they actually believe without having to answer for the consequences of it
I guess so I I mean, I suppose that's totally fair. I'm sure there's people like that. You can't you can't know you can't know
Who's who okay, but but I think the solution there is
I would get what people would disagree with this
But like I think it's very important to give people the benefit of the doubt
Without a substantial case to make your like if you want to insinuate. Okay, let's say, you know
Louis CK has said hard rn words on occasion. Okay. Let's make the case that Louis CK is racist
Um, he said the word. Well, you're saying that you can infer things from what you know about. No, you fool
I'm saying that you can't know. I'm saying that you might suspect. I'm saying that you might have reason to believe
I'm sure you can't. Yeah
You never know you never know that's what I'm saying
I I get your point and I mean, yeah, I get it
Like if all you know about if you know nothing about someone except that, you know, they they called a black guy hard rn word once
Okay, you know starting to make a pretty decent case there. Um, but uh, I don't know like maybe it was in fact a joke
And that was like his best friend like that's you know possible
So you got to you know dig into it more and I just don't like the jumping to conclusions
We see a lot of the time. Why are you fucking take and I'm not this point is no longer rebutting your point
I am now extrapolating my mouth. Okay, fine. Yeah. Yeah. All right
Remember how the time Count Dankulous life was absolutely ruined because he made a joke about a pug
See that's what I'm talking about. I actually don't know who Count Dankulous
How is that true?
What do you mean? How is that true? He's a Scottish guy who made a youtube video about his uh,
his friends and he is his girlfriend's pug and you know as like a little bit of cheeky revenge
She taught it how to do a nazi salute. Well, no, it's just like racist paw
Like instead of like well, yeah. Yeah, instead of using the word really cute. Yeah, and and like like
He obviously like in the video said
um, I'm not a racist lol
Uh, but this is like the worst thing I can think of to to make this pug say so it's like
Do but people just took it as like you just wanted to make a pug a nazi
And the thing is like a nazi
He only had like four or so subscribers only his friends and it was just for his girlfriend and his friends
But it became it started circulating it became way more popular than it ever was meant to be
And yeah, he was convicted of a crime. He was yeah convicted and like and like the the the um
When he went to court they decided in the end just like let's
Not look at the context in which he said the thing and just focus on the fact that he said the thing
And he he got he was guilty and then like this but that's britain. Thank god
You know your hellhole of a home country. So thank god for that. I mean, it's not just britain
I mean not you know
It that the the whole idea is that that kind of retardation could spread and it clears you well, of course, of course
I mean, that's my issue is just that nobody
Is even capable of looking at context anymore people are so fucked in the head
You know, I probably because of social media and the you know words like polarization and whatever the fuck you want
To blame it on but people are just fucking stupid or now. That's the you know, I do agree with that
I think that's definitely like
My annoyance is that with racism is just there seems to be like no
acceptance or no room for the archie bunkers of the world anymore like
That's true. What do you mean?
And all what's an archie bunker the old 70s sitcom all in the family
It was like a show about this old conservative dad and his family was his
His daughter and his stepson were more progressive and they clashed and his whole thing was that you know, he was low key racist
And he said, you know mean things but he was like a good man. He had a good heart
He was friends with george jefferson who was black, you know, he like grew over the course of the series
He's like, ah george one of the good ones, you know, he was
He's a good guy like the whole point is that like you can be sort of low-key backwards and racist and still be a good person
It's not the end. I'll be all of what makes you
Think a lot of people your words are the human being these days. Yeah, but a lot of people are stupid because like yeah, like
Like like I grew up in like a really small like backwoods fucking hodunk
You know white people town and I grew up
You know poor and I grew up around a lot of like low-key racism, you know
Like people would talk. Ah, you know blacks and mexicans. Ah, you know, you know
My grandma would talk about blacks. My you know, my grandma we grew up. I always thought
I I truly believed for most of my life that brazilian nuts were called nigger toes
That's what they that's what they were called when I was a kid. Everyone called them that
So, you know, you you grow up and you go somewhere and you and you go sit down at a bar and you go
Oh, I want some of them nigger toes in my mouth people look at you like you're crazy and you're like
It's what my grandma called them. I don't know
You know like my grandma used to my grandma used to say that's not even particularly insulting though, obviously
It's you know, there's baggage in like words, of course. It's funny like my grandma used to say stuff like
God made the niggers. He made them in the night. He made them so fast. He forgot to make them white
And like I don't even know what to think about that
Like it's funny laughing at the racism people that's what I'm laughing at just to clarify
Like because it's fucking funny. It's just ridiculous to me that you can't even say funny. Shit like that. That doesn't that doesn't hurt anybody
It's fucking funny. Yeah, you know people. It's pretty funny. Oh, it's normalizing views that like God made them wrong
Like no, it's just fucking silly and stupid. It's funny because it's ridiculous
I mean it gets into this thing of like like if you make a joke like that like, okay
percentage-wise, maybe it's like 99 funny joke, but then there's like that one percent. It's like, hey, yeah
Yeah, it do be like it is
You're you're you're normalizing racism like no, I mean, yeah, that's the
But like how can it be normalizing racism when like people are less racist than they were 200 years ago?
Yeah, maybe maybe they're they're a minority. I mean, I think they're a minority
I'm scared of everything
Um, but like, you know the the people the people that like really hate minorities or whatever like the way that they
The way that like they do want to normalize it and the way that they do is through like seemingly innocuous jokes
Like that and like kind of a conspiracy theory though. Yeah, I mean tell obviously
It's obviously that does happen. Yeah, there's people. I mean, it's mostly like teenagers
I think unfortunate yet who like
Are drawn to the memes and then start believing the memes and like start internalizing that. Yes. I agree. That's fine
That's I get all that it's just that in any specific case
Isn't it true that you need to dig deeper to find out which one it is? Is it just a joke or are they you know
So, I don't I don't know. I guess that's all I have to say on it. Okay. I just I just I just
You can say the worst things in the world
Okay, whatever you got my point
I grew up with a lot of like, you know low-key racism, but I never saw anyone actually do
Anything racist or hurt anyone or actually like follow through on some racist belief
It was all racism was always just like a funny fucking joke like and that's what it should be
That's how you that's how you kill racism. You make it a funny fucking joke. You make it a stupid fucking thing that everybody laughs at
I mean, I agree with that for the most part
But you have now you could have a guy be like a philanthropist like a
Great man who does great things you could have him like give the charity his whole life
But then like he slips up and one day he gets caught talking about coons, you know, he's he's just says something funny
And there was that there was that guy on the weather
Remember that guy on the weather channel who accidentally said he said like martin luther coon jr
Like he just made a mistake and like they tried to fire him. He had to like, you know, do a bunch of bullshit
And it's like well, remember remember pewdiepie. He he said the word while being angry and then he apologized immediately
And then like yeah, everyone just got on his case
Yeah, and all this time on the internet right in like in a whole decade of like uploading almost daily
He messed up once
Yeah, like all it does is is is saying the wrong thing and suddenly all the good you've ever done in your life is washed away
You're just a racist. That's all you are. You're a piece of shit. Go to hell
I don't know like a bad and I get your point, but I feel
No, this whole thing. No, we need to like sense. We need to get fucking
No, shut up. You can't fucking argue with my point because my only point is that x happens
And unless you're gonna fucking stand there and tell me no, that doesn't happen. You're not arguing with me
Yeah, yeah, that's true. That's true
I just don't think that way I guess
Well, like the the biggest problem is that I don't want to see bad things
I want to see good things so I choose to focus on that which maybe is bad and maybe is wrong
um
When you decide collectively as a society that
Saying a racist thing is what makes you a racist or like saying the words the magic fucking words
If you say the words you're a racist when when we start deciding that and we start going after people, you know for words
You know people who are actually bad people are smart. They know how to hide
So the people who are not saying the words are going to end up being the ones who are racist because the ones who really have these
Beliefs are going to know how to hide and not say the magic fucking words
And the people who aren't racist are the ones who because they're not racist
They don't think they have to be careful or I don't know and they just fucking slip, you know people fucking
So what's going to happen is that the real bad people are going to slip through the cracks and not get called out
While all the regular people are going to get called out for saying funny things and saying the wrong fucking words
I mean, I guess to be fair and eventually there'll be nothing left
But bad people I mean that I suppose like even if we adopted that belief
It's like, okay, then we could just have people running around just like throwing racial slurs willy nilly and like
Okay, then people would just do it out in the open and like that I think we should I think I think everybody should be out
Throwing around racial slurs willy nilly and making a fucking joke about it
Everyone should be fucking, you know like like an old when you see like old comedy movies from the 70s like airplane
You know there's like racist humor all over there's you know and everyone's getting along and everyone's fucking laughing
Everyone laughs at those movies, you know
When when when when an airplane when they have the joke about the old lady speaking in ebonics and and it's like it's really exaggerated
Super racist ebonics. It's hilarious and everybody understands or like blazing saddles where they say nigger like fucking
11,000 times in that movie and the whole movie is about racism
But like it's funny and because it's funny it brings people together and everyone laughs at it and goes ha ha
Racism sure is ridiculous and stupid. That's what we need
We need more racism out in the open so that we can laugh at it
Instead of having to shove it in the fucking corner and hide it like it's something to be ashamed of and hidden
Or else we get shunned from fucking society if we say the wrong fucking magic word
There's my rant for the day word. I'll let I'm not I'm not above laughing at a racist joke. I'm just putting that out there
I know I know one racist joke back from my childhood, but I'm not yeah
Let it fly I can I can I can type it out and you guys can read it out, but I don't want to see
Sure go for it. Go for it. That's fine. It's like
I guess it's sort of racist, but at the same time it's like
It's making fun of both sides. I think so. Okay. What's the targeted demographic here of the
I I couldn't say like let me just type it out. I'm sorry for the typing noises. Uh hippo
That's fine. Maybe maybe he'll edit it out. He's a good boy. He knows how to do this thing. Yeah, okay
Uh, I guess uh, uh, you know a really good way to to to not be racist
I don't I don't because it because it haunts it's because it's
I know you're looking for this. I know you're walking a tight
You're always you're constantly walking a tightrope
And if you ever slip you ever slip you'll fall into the abyss of racism and you can never get out of it
It's just like being gay with chris chan
Yeah, like if you like it's just it's a constant struggle to avoid being gay
You got it. You got it. You got to you got to really work it
You got to really strain that straightness muscle here's a thought
I do think literally every person in the world is racist
Um, because when everyone has like, I don't know you think about a factor
I don't know. How about being italian that brings to mind some things that you mean are italian humans definitely have like
Tribalistic instincts. Thank god. I had an italian like me in the media in the form of mario
Thank god. I had mario to relate to someone who looked like me. You know ben
I'm offended by mario because not all italians are mustache wearing, you know plumber low blue collar workers
My father or my mother was an educated woman and she was italian. God. How dare they
God rest your soul. Yeah
I don't know. It's all we've talked about this a million welcome to the pokemon episode. Yeah, we talk about race relations and racism
mule tool tenacral aerodactyl
mule tool
It's a mule tool put a mule and a tool this episode is going to be called
Episode episode 150 pokemon and then in parentheses the n word is used 11 times in this episode
Just like in most pokemon games. We should put a trigger warning on
It's like now that i'm translating it from luffianian to english. This is a very stupid joke
Most of them are I think I remember the best kind you told the joke you told like no, it was like it was a gay joke
It was oh boy. Oh wait. I'm thinking I think i'm thinking of like you told a lithuanian fairy tale and it like didn't make any sense
Oh with the with the sausage
Yes, yeah
Someone just like became a sausage. No. No. No. Someone was already a sausage. It was a was a sentient sausage. Yes
Yeah, sure
um
I respect your culture. What can you do? What can you do? A little we just got to oppress the gays?
Um, that's all there is to it really fact true fact a little while ago
I heard in my headphones a little beep that signaled that uh ten paces in draw is rendered
It is done. I think I will put it up after this episode
Uh, if anyone would want to like peruse it and see if there anything sucks about it
Okay, I think of the audio mixing or something. I tried really hard to keep the audio mixed as well as I could
Think I did an okay job
It's hype uh the ending the ending of ten paces in draw is fucking hype. It's a yeah, it's a blast
It is a blast and how long is it? It's about an hour long. It's like just under an hour
It's like a motion picture. God damn it is it has a it's a you know
I mean, I hate it because I've been looking at it for months and months and I'm fucking sick of working on it
uh, but uh
It's got you know, I used um oblivion falls
redo of the of jesse's uh pcp theme song and it's
Really fun and cool
Uh, so yeah, watch if watch that I would recommend viewers. It's yeah, this is from this is footage from radcon two
Uh
It was a thing it was like a little side project
We came me and munchie came up with it on the fly and then we all we all just did it
Wait, you mean radcon three, right? Did I say two? I meant three. Yeah. Yeah, it's from radcon three
Yeah, that's dope. So that's finally and it's a pilot. I mean
You're will be looking for feedback to see potentially if more could be made or some fact
The idea was that it was a pilot episode that we could do more of I mean, this is a thing that's out like a thing
That's coming out. It's it's it's just I just finished it. So it'll be out soon
um the
Yeah, the idea for it was a pilot. Um, I mean
Obviously because that was done at a radcon and like
I mean
If we did more of them, they would look they would look a little different and they might be formatted a little differently
But yeah, we could definitely like
I mean, I would definitely make some changes to the premise. I would
Fuck I would give more time for each round and we would have more to work with and fucking ballpoint pens. I think
But yeah, yeah, the the concept is definitely something that could be
Expanded upon and made more of
Uh, yeah, well, that's so that's neat in terms of radcon three content
Content three. We've got what what's left. Okay. I'm good. I'm gonna read this
I'm gonna read this joke out loud without reading it beforehand. So if it's if I say something horrible
It's not my fault. I have no idea what I'm about to say. Okay
Let's see here
A white guy and a black guy. I read a bar the white guy turns to the black guy and says
Do you know why your feet are white? The black guy says nothing just takes a drink of his beer
The white guy continues because you stood on your feet when I painted you he laughed
And then asked again
Know why your palms are white the black guy says nothing the white guy continues
Because you stood on your hands when I painted you he laughed
The black guy finishes his drink and stands up speaking. Well, you know why your asshole is dark
The white guy looks at him the black guy continues because the paint wasn't dry when I fucked you
He then pays for his drink
Uh, I think I'm getting the gist here. They're painters
And there was like, okay
No, I think the idea is that like they're just skin will like wipe off on other
Did you guys not get it? Are you what's happening? I don't get it. I don't get it
I don't get what the white guy's talking about in the first. I don't know. The white guy is just
It's just two guys in a bar, you know, you know, busting each other's balls
I assume as you do. Yeah, the white guy is you know saying some low-key race to the black guy like hey
Hey, you're black. You know what black people are fucking your feet and hands are white and painted you
And then the black guy turns it around on them and it's like, oh, yeah
Well, your asshole's dark because I fucked in it and the paint wasn't dry. I made it dark. Oh, wait, wait, wait
Oh
Like the souls like talking about like the souls of his oh, yeah, I get it. I get it
I was gonna be like his but his feet aren't white. What do you talk? Okay?
All right, you know what? This is my favorite kind of race joke because frankly, none of this is actually like offensive
It simply is pointing out like facts that person
And even in the context of the joke, it's just like a white guy and a black guy who are obviously hanging out together
And they're clearly friends. So
There you go. And then there's banter and he gets me hoists his own petard at the end there
Yeah, good
But when did he paint him?
Don't ask me like this hardly analyzing
The black guy not know he was being painted by the white guy. This is not this is not an origin of creation story
We didn't literally it's just the guys busting each other's balls and making shit up
Hey, hey everypony and welcome back to another episode of thoroughly analyzing mage's racist joke. We got another one here today
This joke's like a strong
Eight
No, that's too high. That's too high. I don't know. It's like too dicky. It's like a 1488. I'd say
Got him
um
It was told to me by a drunk guy in a family meeting gathering. I think I don't remember who it was my uncle
Maybe my dad. I don't know someone. It's always a drunk uncle. It's always
I mean, that's my whole point. We have to have some sympathy in this country for the drunk uncles who make up
You know a sizable portion of the population and they're getting
Marginalized we are marginalizing the drunk uncles by making like I had a friend. I hope this racism considered bad
This is similar to that, but it's just that I once had uh, uh, well
I have a friend and his little brother one time they were at the grocery store
And uh, like it was it was his little brother who was like three and his mom
And they were at the grocery store and you know, they're white or whatever and they just walked by a black guy
And the little kid said mommy. Why is that man blue?
And that because he didn't he just fucked up his color. She just doesn't know what and that was hilarious
One of those was it mill smith as from uh from the rabbi's cat when they find the shared ancestors of all blacks and jews
And they're like 20 foot and they're like 20 foot tall giant like blue
Jews that like yeah, yeah
There's the true uh, they're like so dark that they're blue and they and they all and they have they have uh, they have um
Oh, fuck. What's the what's the word when a jewish boy becomes a man?
Ramadan no
Ramadan yeah close enough
Uh, mage. Okay. What's your other joke? Uh, let me type it
Okay, go on go on
Were we
Nate were you were you doing like a round up like a like a radcom three content round up? Did you do that?
Oh, right. I was gonna say yeah, uh, what do you remember? I was like, okay in terms of stuff that's left
I know that gibb has one piece of content left. Uh, ben's finishing 10 bases and draw
I think there's something else that was like, uh, like a reward or something. I can't quite remember
I think there's something else too something. I don't I don't it was a reward tier. Yeah, I can't remember
I'll have to go check. I'll have to go check. But I think there's one other as well
So that's maybe something something something nine thousands
And you know, it's almost uh, by the time this comes out
It'll be pretty close to the like the one-year anniversary of like the end of radcon three might even be past it
Can we march sometime? Can we get it all released within a year of the event?
Do you think it could happen? Well, I know for a fact that gibbs thing will not come out, uh, before like the end of the thing
But you know, uh, frankly, that's his business and I don't care. I'm not involved in that. Oh, wait. Yes. I am
I'm literally in it now that I think about it. Um, well, whatever
He should release it. Is this is a secret what it is
I just want to say just in case he doesn't want to if you can clarify it if he wants, um
Uh, but yeah, so we're we're getting close to the end
And I know I said last time but my god was radcon three such a derailing of like how great things were going for me
In terms of getting my work done on my channel and it's all it's all my fault. I blame no one else
Yeah, but you know same. I can't blame radcon three. It's own. It's no one's fault, but mine
I just I just I signed up for too much shit and it was great. Uh, we made all the stuff almost it'll all be done soon
But uh, I think
I mean, I think I'm done. I think with 10 paces and draw. I'm like done with everything
Technically, I mean you may or may not have a little bit of more work to do on the thing
I'm still working on but you know, I think it's very minimal if anything, so
Fuck yeah, that's that's it. Well, I'm very excited to have that monkey off my back
I cannot wait. Uh, I've got big plans for things to do with my spare time once that is all gone
It's really loomed over me. It's like it's really been a black cloud. Um, yeah, it's it's a nightmare
Just a burden. So not doing this just a disaster. So radcon four
I'm gonna waltz in do a lecture waltz the fuck out and that's all I'll do people can make their vlogs people can
You know other people want to make more complicated content. I want to do
I want to do two lectures at radcon four. Excellent idea. Whenever that happens
I might do like one long one and two short ones
Welcome like mini lectures. Hey Gib. We were just talking about things that remain for radcon three
Uh, I didn't say yours in case you wanted to keep it on the down low
Oh, I mean, I've I've mentioned that it's a thing, but I I don't know whether I'll ever release it
It's the g rpj kingdom hearts two
Which I have the footage for can can I read this one? Can I read mage's next racist joke?
Yeah, please. Uh, remember, uh, the attitudes expressed in this joke are not mine. They are mages not mine
They're just jokes. I remember
Uh, a white person and a black person are talking the black person is ranting
Tell me this so when you're cold your skin turns blue when you're embarrassed your skin turns pink
When you're angry your skin turns red when your nauseous your skin turns green
And when you're tan your skin turns orange and you say, I'm the person of color with you
Destroyed
You know that's so that's so weirdly wholesome. Yeah, it is. It is extremely wholesome. That is like
Yeah, that's like something mother goose would tell me
Something mother goose would say to the black people in the neighborhood. That's like a witty the poo-wism
Yes
Oh god mother goose
I don't know whether I've mentioned this before but I have nightmares of mother goose. What for what reason explain
Because when I was a baby, I had the mother goose thing and the the the packaging that it came in one thing
What thing is like some some brother's grim stuff that's like been repackaged for the waste or something now
I have no idea what it is. I just know that there's a goose and she wears a little a
Bloop on it. Yeah, and it's supposed to be for kids and there was this I guess plastic um
You know robot thing mother goose that would sing to you. I think mother goose is public domain character. Okay. Yeah, I'm tempted to say
So so there was this thing. I don't remember what the product was but I remember the packaging
Um, which was this big cardboard box with a mother goose on it and I always used to see
Mother goose staring at me on that packaging from the other end of the room
It was the only thing that had eyes in my room like when you were sleeping from your bed or something
Yeah, when I was sleeping I was like and then later we moved that up into the loft
Um, and it would be put right at the back and when I was like young and like the loft at the moment is like renovated
Since been renovated into an upstairs
Bedroom like it used to be uh, uh, uh, you know a horrible
A dark scary cold uninsulated
mess of a broken childish
Broken children's toys and like old photographs and demons and spiders
And so occasionally I would go up there and like there would be mother goose staring at me in the exact same way
On on that box all the way in the end in the darkest darkest bit
And she would eat me and I would be scared that she would fucking bite her goose
Fangs on me. Geese are very aggressive. They are. She's that's true. She's open domain
So welcome new mainstay pcp character mother goose haunting gib in his dreams and nightmares
Welcome to the family mother goose
Glad to have you you're equally important to the dude. We gotta make a mother. We gotta make a mother goose shirt
Immediately, please make a mother goose harassing gib shirt everybody. You will see mother goose below this video
When you watch it, I want to see you know what I want. You know that um that american gothic
I want one of mother goose is like the masculine like farmer and like the terrified woman to his left
Is gib just being intimidated. Is she terrified? Is that how you read american gothic? No, but i'm reinterpreting it for this particular
I'm like the weirdly hyper realistic goose face, uh of the american gothic. I think would really work
I think would really work
So please draw that for free ladies and gentlemen, uh and send it to me put some hyper realistic blood on it like my creepypastas
Hyper realistic blood
Yeah, you know, you're playing you're playing a haunted video game. You're playing a haunted pokemon cartridge
You're playing a haunted painting. Yeah, and then you get you get stabbed and and your pokemon die
But there's hyper realistic you get that blood dot png just right on the screen there
It's just from google.com with watermark. There's nothing more realistic
It would be so it would be so much more scary if it was pixel art animated blood because then it would be like wait
Did they program this in there or is it real? Oh my god?
Do they believe the actual pixel mons to get this pixel blood that's fucked up? It's not it's not scary unless it's a ghost
It's not scary unless it's a ghost with that on this shirt. It's not scary unless it's a ghost
God i'm just i'm just full of brilliant ideas. God. I'm this could all be shirts
Uh, okay. Speaking of gold mine. Yeah. Yeah, do I marry emily abigale or lia? Jesus christ
I'm gonna say lia. I'm
I'm gonna say
Emily because I like that name the most is from stardew valley by the way people no go for lia lia is obviously the
The diamond in the rough waifu that you're supposed to go. Emily. Emily was my first pick
Yeah, I mean immediately. I was I honed it on emily, but then I'm like a little bit
I don't know and now i'm like wavering back and forth between abigale. Well, it's uh, do you want to?
What's what's the word when women marry up? Uh poly no, it's uh, you know what i'm talking about hypergamy
Hypergamy, yeah
Like because if you marry lia, you're getting nothing you're not getting a single sheep for your dowry. You're getting
What am I getting from abigale?
Uh, abigale has like a she lives with her family, right? So they can supply a dowry of of pierre pierre doesn't have the kind of
Money to throw around he's he's always struggling. He's got some gems. I don't know. Let me her throw up
She's she's uh, she's spike. She's a dragon
Um guys, uh, could that be please a a my little pony risk in of stardew valley where I could choose to marry fluttershy
That'll be good. Thanks. I don't know. That would definitely. I don't know why there isn't one already
In fact, I wouldn't be surprised. Well, you can already ride a horse. You could just roleplay as that horse
Um
Dude, I put a hat on my horse. It was fucking sick. You get hats for your horse
You can put any hat on your horse. I had no idea
Yeah, welcome to hats for your horse
Slimefield slime felt has never looked better horses for your hats like a little horse that goes like runs on the inside of the
Brim. Yeah. Oh, they'll be sick. They'll be sick
Um, you feed him tiny tiny carrots. I only know two things in this world. That's hats and horses
You're voting you're voting leonate. Yeah, mostly because emily's mine. So stay away from her. Are you fucking? I?
I've been leaning more towards leon abigale. I don't know. There you go. There you go. Abigale's trash to pick her
I think
Ah god, so difficult. I think
I think leah is probably the most like she's the obvious choice. I think she's she's the one who
Okay, I like leah because it seems like she probably
Isn't like an idiot like abigale seems like kind of an idiot and like it's kind of cute
Wait a minute. I just found
A sexy picture of abigale. Now. She's the top contender. She looks way less fat than she does in her portrait here
But I kind of hate
Leah's taste in food. She's got basic bitch taste in food. She's because she's poor as shit
She can't afford the gourmet stuff. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. She likes wine. She likes truffles
She likes goat cheese. She is totally human core and it's disgusting
Oh
Abagail is nothing but heel and monster zero
Abigale is practical leah is practical and abigale is kind of like like what the fuck is she thinking?
What is she doing with her life? She's all so random, but she's not no emily's random. Yeah, I guess you're right
She's the pinky pie of but abigale is post food. Well, no, she likes to eat but at least she's less human
Oh, yeah, she sure does. Oh, I'd love to eat. Oh, I'm gonna be stuffed more food in my face
I found a I found a secret note from her that says like here's some things
Here's some of my favorite foods. I love to eat and I'm like
Fat confirmed fat confirmed
But even more damningly human core confirmed and that's
That's the worst of all leah is the most human core and it's damning. It's the one thing against her
All right, uh, should we move on to the voicemails? I think it's about how long we've been going an hour and 22 minutes
Pretty good. I guess I guess wait, um, no
Nate play play me off play me off for the uh for the
Shit on the pizza party podcast don't have it prepared
Uh, uh, wait, I got you
Uh
Listen, I called up. I called up my local
I called up my local italian eatery. Yeah, I asked them if they delivered and they said, yeah
They said it's not deliver is to giorno
And I said, would you please bring me?
Would you please bring me the pizza party podcast? I've been looking for it everywhere and you're my only hope
And they hung up on me
And they swatted me
The swat team killed my dog
Had a dog human core anyway, the pizza party podcast for this
Damn you pizza party podcast
Hashtag where's the podcast?
He just wanted to know where it is. If only it'd been easier to find this wouldn't have happened
Goodbye slime fields. You were a good hound. I uh, I know there is a voicemail that's about the pizza party
I forget it's the first or the second one. So we'll just have to dive in and we'll we'll get to it
Either first or second here. Um
But hey speak pipe people link below send us voicemails. You know the drill
Let's see if this first one's about pizza party or not. Uh in any case
This first one is from dining kroger
Dining kroger, uh go
I met an interesting guy in a brew pub the other day and I actually engaged in a long conversation with him
First we talked about anime and I thought he must be an anime reviewer of some sort
Then we talked about video games and I was certain he was a game designer
Lastly we talked about memes and I was sure he was a four-changer just like myself
Well, the hour grew late and the next day I inquired about this man the waitress
I'm describing his unkempt appearance and she stops me and says don't you know that was the pcp
Had no idea
Wait, what that I guess this entity was the pcp
I thought this was like a joke. I I thought this is I thought this is gonna be to laugh
Like you know, I thought this was like a uh, a um, you know a four-channer a game designer and an anime reviewer walk into a bar
And it's the pcp and that's and yeah
That's the end no one laughs. Um, I'd like to apologize for selecting this just like the real podcast
Oh, no, everyone started everyone started laughing until they all bowed their heads in shame and walked down
Um, although his name was dining kruger, which I'm wondering is a pun on dunning kruger
You know, maybe it it sounds like could there be a joke here. Could there be a joke?
Um, we'll never know. I think it's probably just his handle
Okay, anyway, let's go to the next one. Maybe this is the pizza party one. Oh, it is. Okay. This voice smells from where is it?
It's from where is it? I think I'm detecting or is my own heart. Yeah, let's let's see what we've got go
Huh pizza party podcast. I'm like shits a party podcast more like pizza particularly bad podcast
More like pizza part terrible podcast. Yeah, it's a party clod cast. It's pretty snot cast
It's a party. Is this all you got cast?
It's a party podcast do shit. It's a party podcastration as a reasonable punishment for crimes against entertainment
more like more like more like where the freak is the podcast you guys
Oh, there it is
A savage series of blows guys a respectable string of insults
I'm getting like I'm getting answer to answer. We got we need first hand. We need first hand accounts
Ben's going into remission. He's going it would not remission. He's going into we got we got to get on social media
We got to get on social media. We got it. We got to start atten
We got to start atten these fools on the pizza party podcast
They have to answer for their crime. They do of hiding the pot. Ben's dog is dead slime oid or whatever his name was
He's dead field
Crushed under a military
Steel toad boot
Of the non-existent podcast
Smashed open smat rent a sunday with the butt of a rifle
Oh, it's sad sad day. Well, I'm so it's you know something in the face of such tragedy. All you can do is laugh
It's true. It's true. Um, okay. Let's move on. Maybe that'll be resolved one day
Next voicemail is no, but no, but seriously at the pizza party podcast guys and asking where's the podcast no choice at this point
zoomer joe at fortnight.com
goes in with a message
Let's go to the phones
Hey guys zoomer joe here calling in again to celebrate my fifth birthday
and also
My fourth the anniversary of like the fourth or the third year of me watching the procrastinators
Guys, I'm a big fan and I'm a big zoomer
zoom
Hey, I'm just zooming around on my birthday while I'm playing fortnight
Uh, and just general multitasking like you do
Like I'm actually listening to the pcp right now as I record this voicemail
Just because you know, I'm a fucking zoomer who multitasks on everything. That's just what we do
Anyway, great show guys. Keep the show up. I'm just gonna I'm just gonna zoom away right now
I bet that guy's got so many fucking tabs open right now
Yeah, I think you're right, uh, you know, I'm too intimidated by these kids. I can't handle it. They're pretty high level the five-year-olds
You know, yeah, it's good that we got young blood. You know, it's good that we're educating the next generation
I agree. I agree. It is it is pretty funny making a better world
Zoomers of the world don't forget to take your adhd medications stop zooming your mother needs to calm down in the evening
And medicating yourself with two glasses of wine a night just ain't healthy just tone down the zooming
Um, okay next one. We've got a call from grandma loves you. Finally my grandma will be alive go
Hello
PCP
This is grandma calling. Just wanted to let you know how proud I am of my little angels for helping less less fortunate latino men
Oh, yeah, I just wanted to let you know that I I'm very proud and also if if you could put the the podcast on
on facebook and and
Share it to me. No
I'm not particularly a fan of uh
The susan with jisky
Polish lady. She's she's very unnice
You you know grandma's big fan of that zuck
so
mistake you again for for being so such such a
Smaking grandma such a proud old bitch
And please you call sometime
Okay, well grandma. I'm fucking busy. Stop calling me. I don't have time to come visit you
Shut up grandma. I love you. We we do not share the the the the reverence for the zuck
No, no, no not one bit grandma. I left you in a grave. I expect you to stay there and stop bothering me
All right
Love you grandma appreciate that. We all agreed it was best not to spend your savings on a nursing home
Yeah, what's the fucking point? We instead spent that money on renting a gun and buying a bullet
That's what we did. That was your retirement savings amounted to grandma. So enjoy that
She's got a way with words grandma. Um, okay next call from arcade nova. He sounds like a real gamer
Let's let's see if you can back it up
Hello, I am deus x commina and I am your god. I am a machine created. Okay, so now that's out of the way
Here's the tier list pretty based dayzube and saint hippo great absolutely fucking based
Digital conrad brother and nate best guy ever
Wait a minute. Is it true? Are you the conrad that I have been searching for? Are you digital brother?
Model 8.88 it is iDigie. The prophecy has been foreskid error error three nine eight four
K-e-k-o. No, it seems that I cannot handle your content creation power systems in check restoring energy
Scanning scanning. What's this? You're a filthy fucking fraud. You have only reviewed point zero zero five four three four seven eight
percentage of the gamecube library
Bro, where's the gamecube forever unsubscribed?
Got him. We um, I think uh, I think we better alert digi
Yeah, I think I think uh, I think he wants to know I think he wants to know that this
This ai is is gunning for I think may or may not be his digital sibling
Possibly wasn't quite clear on that. Yeah
Viewers listen again. Let us know in the comments. Who is this creature?
I uh, I think gamecube chats could come back. I think that's that's a cool name for a thing
It's not bad. It is
You could review more gamecube games like hey guys were those specifically like reviews or were they like let's play
No, there was just let's play with his friends. Yeah, like that's a cool name for a thing
Just like chatting about gamecube games. Hey
Yeah, we're playing wait. Was that not a thing on im games? No. No, it's way before that
Hmm was there another game
This was pretty didgy brony. Yeah, I don't know. I don't know
Arcade novice pissed that there's only zero point whatever percentage of all gamecube games reviewed though
So he better get to it. You don't want to uh, didn't do didn't devoo like I don't know how far he went
No, no, no, that was like any s quest or something. Yeah, that's what I was gonna say. He was playing every game on the nes
Which was a cool idea. I like that idea. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, keep it up devoo. All right next call. We've got
Let me see gigadonk mcfronk calling back. I think let's uh, cool. Let's let's let's go
Hey guys, sorry if my voice sounds a little gay. I've been listening to the procrastinator's podcast recently
I just wanted to follow up on my previous voicemail where everyone took it at face value that I was actually asking you for
romantic advice at age 21
Uh, I'm not really a fucking turbo virgin who lives in his basement and thinks that he needs to date someone who
Likes video games to be cool. Okay. Uh, I know I know it sounds like uh, I was just pretending to be retarded kind of scenario
But no legit. I was no cool. I didn't mean it. Uh, the girl broke up with me anyway
So uh, while I'm here if you guys don't mind, I'd like to seek out
A sexual fulfillment by giving each of you a kiss full on the lips one by one then saint
You're up first. Come here
Oh
Yeah
I have aids
Sorry bro. Well
That's it. You could have told him you had time
Why didn't he kiss the rest of you and get you all and get you all some of that distracted by his recent diagnosis of aids
So, you know, I suppose he'll come back to us. That's no reason. That's no reason
We all know that aids is like a sudden shock that runs through your body. You know instantly that you have it
I've always been a bug chaser. This is my one chance to get those sweet aids, but maybe next time
Maybe next time. Well, you just got a kiss bent on the lips
Um, I mean we are married now. Oh, yeah, you know, that's true. Uh, but I've sworn a vow of celibacy
But anyway, we'll get you've done all the gay sex
But you you're gonna get around to the kissing on the lips part in the holding hands that comes last
Yeah, I guess one of these days. Okay next call. Here it is from zack
go
So last time you guys mentioned that nobody on the pcp actually does much procrastinating
Which brought to my attention that you gormless peons don't even grasp the true genius behind your own name
See when the unifying theme of the pcp is that every member has another creative outlet aside from the podcast
The act of recording the podcast itself is inherent procrastination from said creative outlets
But since the pcp is monetized, you are literally professionally procrastinating. You are pro
Crastinators
Yeah
Oh, I wish it had kept going. Yeah, but uh, that guy is on the money. Yeah. No, that's good
That guy that guy gets us better than we get ourselves update the wiki ladies and gentlemen. That's canon. That's confirmed
He's I already knew that like the professional part of procrastinators was that it was a thing we were getting paid for
Like the idea that that we are procrastinating on our own stuff
By doing the money thing. That's that's good. I am smart at this very moment
I am filled with anger and piss and bile and shit and come at the fact that I can't be working
On my weaguar right now and as soon as this is done. I'm getting back to it. So it's fair. The fabled we are going to be working
Right now. There you go. Instead. I'm recording this fucking podcast. Nobody likes it
It's really bad. It's really bad now
All right, we've learned we've learned a lot today. That was good. We've covered a lot of grounds. I appreciate that Zach
Thanks. Uh, okay next one's from f-frame. F-frame's got some frame. Mm-hmm. Oh
So I'm big into rfck. I hang out there a lot
And there are so many people there that I can safely call my friend at this point
In that got me thinking about the whole pcp friendship simulator meme
And I thought
Is pcp a friendship simulator at this point? Is it really just a simulator?
Because with me new moving to new areas for college
Um, I don't have many real life friends and I go to rfck and that's my social circle
And sure i'm not friends with digi or nate
But pcp the pcp has probably got had the biggest role in creating
my new social circle
And I just think that's funny. Um, little food for that. Well, that's nice. You know, I
Thanks for the call of frame. I know that guy. He was at the first. He was the first
He was at rf roddy fuckers con killers one. Um, so he did it. He turned it into real friends. Yeah, I guess so
He's not he's not all talk
Living the gimmick. I was I was thinking about this. I've been thinking about this recently how like
the
I mean I
How am I gonna say it like to to a certain extent? Yeah, like
You might you might think that like the point
Of a community, right? Like around the pcp community. Yeah that the point of it is the pc is the pcp
But maybe it's not or it doesn't have to be like the community itself and the people in it
Can be the the point. I don't know. Maybe that's obvious
Maybe that's really obvious, but I was just thinking about I was like, huh, you know
I mean people don't just people like people don't necessarily just I don't know
Pop into rfck for the game or for me or munchie or whatever. Yeah, they don't come to the pcp discord just to like, you know
See us or whatever or you know and so on with like anyone's community. That's true. They're they're they're they're
You know, it's the other people that are there that they're congregating. I mean really it's it's you know
A like-minded people like everybody likes this thing. So there's a lot to talk about that they know that they can talk about
Yeah, I guess the discord community and just you know, the communities that have spawned is a
Is more of a benefit than you might think at first. It seems like it's pointless and meaningless, but no, it's actually kind of good to have
Um, well, it's not I mean, it's not just discord, but yeah, for example for example
Discords and and you know, I guess we can as the members ourselves, uh, especially for me
I can be very like member oriented and not thinking about other people and so when I've said friendship simulator
It's it's like in goodwill hunting
Like the teacher guy whatever shawn says to will hunting like hey
Uh, who who like who's your buddy who inspires you and the guy's like, you know, uh, nichy lock and he looks Shakespeare, etc
And he's like, yeah, but they can't give back to you. They aren't your soulmates, you know
You can't have dialogue with them and I feel that applies to like the pcp members in the audience specifically
but
Beyond that though as as you know a frame and ben are saying the uh, yeah
The community absolutely you can't touch and frankly guys like ben and munchie get pretty deeply involved with their communities as well
Anyway, and meet a ton of them. So it's not even that much of a distance some sometimes don't say that because I've really been well
Yeah, I've really I've really been neglecting rfck this last like
But I'll be back
With the people active in my discord. Oh, I recently launched gonna. We're gonna do anime nights on
Fridays and Saturdays and I'm gonna watch a happy funny comedy anime
You know that makes me want to plug. Do you want to plug your discord or something? Is it a patron discord or is it?
Okay
Maze elitist lethal aurora hates the common people
No, I mean you can
Get get through a patron just because I'm lazy to edit it out and I feel like you know, it's fine
but uh
It was open to the public at some point and a lot of people got in and they're still around and
There are ways to get in but like I don't want to open it publicly
I don't want too many people, you know mage that just reminds me of uh
I can be a real one-man show with a lot of stuff
I'm doing and I kind of hate involving other people in the work
I'm doing depending on what the project is
But like it reminds me of when I was in college and I was in an anime club that was full of giant spurg lords
But they weren't bad people and frankly just having people around who I could finally talk to about anime for like the first time in my life
Uh was real special and they introduced me to a lot of anime
I probably wouldn't have found like gurl a login and shit if it wasn't for that club
And oh, just it's just making me nostalgic. It was it was a pretty good time. It's a pretty good time
I used to be in an anime club too, but I don't remember much about it. How old were you when you were in it?
Uh, I was I was definitely a teenager in the older years, but uh, I like they were nice people
They weren't like spurgs or whatever you call them. Uh, I just but I use the term endearingly
Yeah, they were they were cool people
There were just a lot of them and I had a very hard time sort of talking speaking out
My mom was happy that was finally like going out and involving yourself with people, but just like
There wasn't like a tight connection with them. They were nice to me though. Like they they were really people
So nothing bad is just you know, sometimes people just don't connect
I did meet all my best friends at my anime club or my all my college best friends and uh, uh,
They only came for like one day though, and I'm the only one who stayed long term
But thank god they came for that one day because that's what I remember
I remember we watched this this one anime movie and I I don't remember the title
But it was I remember it was weirdly trippy and I can't describe it. It was like a dream, but it wasn't a dream
so don't worry, uh
It was it was it was it was so weird and I I wish I could find it again
Just so I could rewatch it with like fresh new eyes of like yeah. Yeah
I don't watch tokyo godfathers
Oh, I still want to watch that as well. Yeah, it's dope. It's totally dope
Oh, and I downloaded perfect blue gotta watch that sometime. Okay. Anyway, we got two more voicemails
Let's let's get to those next voicemail is from center point old fan favorite go
Hey guys at the pcp, uh, this is center point. Uh, just wanted to say that I'm at cancun right now after being a poor boy for
Up until I came to cancun
Since I'm not actually going to be able to hear this until uh Friday
I wanted to know, uh, what is the best thing I can do on the last day of a cool vacation?
Appreciate it
Okay, first of all whores
Find the whores find all the prostitutes and do them all spend all your money
If you're single if you're single on a tropical vacation
God damn my cursed interrelationship status if I was single and on a tropical vacation
You've got to fuck up like a tropical honey. You've got to do it. How can you not?
No, no, no, no get it get a good nice rest for a very taxing trip tomorrow
Well, that's so boring
Exactly
Whores I'm going with whores. Yeah
Just imagine just imagine walking on the beach
Hawaiian or here's what you do. Yeah. Here's what you do. You go. No. Here's what you do
This is this is cool. This is cool. You're in a foreign place. Yeah, you don't you don't have to worry about anything
You do not have to
Commit crimes my dude. No, I'm saying I'm saying you can go out. You can go to the local watering hole
You can uh, you can uh
You can get wasted if you want you can you can um
You can make advance you can make advances on all the ladies
And you don't have to be embarrassed because you will never see them ever again. That's right
That's a lot of empowerment for the pickup. You should go you should go out and fucking you should go out and fucking
Get a little loosey-goosey. You should go you should go
Women on vacation want to fuck end of conversation. This is your golden opportunity. You've probably already done it like every day of the week
That's what i'm guessing and maybe you haven't and you feel bad. That's okay. Give it a shot, dude
Grind your skills
He took he took a day off
Fucking the locals to make this voicemail and it was worth it. Yeah, good
Don't don't wait until you're old and married and not allowed to go all over the world fucking every whore in the world
Because then every day of your life will be torture. I gotta tell you guys
I there probably will anyway, but you can enjoy you can enjoy now
I have come down maybe I have come down with some serious island fever now that I visited hawaii a couple of times
Every moment that i'm not there is just like
Why is life just so much worse? Why do I gotta be
In this place and I could be in that place. It's it's pain. It's pain
I know that I haven't been there. So maybe I can't
Say I just
I don't get it
I do maybe maybe I'd get it if I went there, but I don't think I would I think I like my rainy
I think I like my rainy urban fucking
Uh
Well, you know, you know, I mean don't they say they say that like you know seasonal depression is the thing, right?
Because like it's like it's cold outside. It's winter and stuff. You can't go outside
You gotta bundle up life's just kind of a hassle when you live in a cold and rainy place
In like a in a sunny tropical island. First of all, you can just go outside in nothing and feel perfect and feel great
Second of all the beach is like literally right there
And I've always loved the ocean and I miss it so desperately living in the middle of fucking nowhere out here
And uh, you know, I want to live there so bad
I want to live in either like LA near the beach or like destiny islands fucking texas by the beach destiny islands. Yeah
Yeah, why not? That's basically hawaii right there. Oh, I love the fucking ocean. I'm literally saura and I miss it
I I love the ocean too. That's great, but uh
Yeah, it's all right. I do like to take the ocean. I do like urban grime. Sure
But it's Stockholm syndrome. Hell yeah, it's Stockholm syndrome though because you know, the only
Yeah, the only brief windows in my life that I've ever even been anywhere close to approaching
Remotely in the vicinity of happiness. I've been on a beach somewhere and you know
Beach is a great
Same thing with that dreaded interrelationship status, you know, I like it, but it's Stockholm syndrome, you know
When I was really happy it was completely alone in the world
You know, I feel like the whole like beach thing like most people don't live on beaches
Yeah, except people in hawaii
um, but like
There's I think most of hawaii isn't on the beach, you know, it's it's it's just that it's no
But what what I'm getting at is like the beach isn't inherently way better than you know any other place
Um, but when you're on holiday, it's uh one
It's uh an escape from whatever bullshit you have to deal with back home and all the people that you have to deal with back home
I hear you all the people who give you shit were on the same beach. It wouldn't be very good anymore
You know, that's a great point. That's a great point. I don't I mean, I think if I lived on in hawaii or something
Or if I lived in it, I mean, I wouldn't swim in the ocean
All of the see I would just because I just because I lived I would if I lived like let's say a five minute walk from
Damn it. I'd probably be like a five or ten minute walk from the beach at least or maybe a drive
I feel like
I feel like I'd be there every day
I feel like I'd make time to go there every day if it was if it was a drive
I would go
Couple times a year if it was a walk. I would go maybe once a month
You know, because I've got to accept the fact that my lifestyle right now is very much inside on my computer
You know, I go get up and go to the gym when appropriate, but I'm not like thinking about like yay go do fun things
I'm a worker man. That's how I've
Configured my body and my brain
Uh, so like even if I lived straight up in like the best beach in the world
Would I take advantage of it or would it just go?
You know unused as I'm stressed out with work and stuff in the day-to-day grind
It's definitely possible. Definitely possible. It's yeah, it's possible. But like
I said that but like I do like the idea. I think it's just
you have to
To understand that going somewhere forever is a lot different than going somewhere pretty often
That's very living in hawaii is a lot more different from going to hawaii every year for a whole the good news is
That michelle did live in hawaii. And so I got her stories now to be fair
She lived with her parents and didn't have a ton of responsibilities
So, you know, that's different from like my life where I have to do lots of work all the time and stuff
um get a job michelle, but uh
um
You know
That's it. Like I just frankly I watched point break. Okay. I watched point break again recently
It's a movie about surfing. I want to be a surfer so fucking bad. I want to be on the beach
I want to hit the waves. I want to those guys are so tanned and beautiful and fit
I could be that if I was just by a beach right now with the board
Get me there remember that that episode of pokemon where they have to ride the big wave to hit the the rock with the flag
I think I do remember that actually is that like season one. Is that squirtle like surfing or something?
No, it's just there was this old man who was just like
Uh, I I used to be able to ride the wave to put the flag at the top
And now I I I failed and I can't do it rings a very vague bell
I feel the same and then the episode straight after was in the same location
But it was a ghostly house on the cliff. Don't you love when they do that? They do stuff like like they're in the
Building an environment is a really satisfying thing and having like even a like a pokemon show where like they're journeying around
To have a couple of episodes like in the same town doing like different things within the town
Pretty good feel pretty good feel mr. Mime, pidgey, Bulbasaur, Nidoran
Jinx, Sonic's
God, I am a night slope everybody. Here's your homework. You have to go watch point break
The first one not the remake the remake is good, but the original is way better
God I long for the beach. I long for the sand
I wait, what's what's the moana song? I'm a girl who loves her island. Okay, that's
That's all I got how
And can I be?
Okay, we got one more voicemail last one last one last one rounding it out this one is from let me see
PCP israily shills
2019 so uh, they caught us sounds pretty good sounds pretty good. All right go go
Best guy ever
More like best goi ever got him crap endless jess
More like endless jihad
Oh
More like munchy wears tiny hijabs
That's a half of those things half of those things aren't even israeli. No, they're not. Yeah, no really not maybe
In fact a goi they were all they were all explicitly not. Yeah, all those things are wait a minute. Okay
Maybe this person is the pcp israeli shill 2019 of fame of the and he's mad at us for not being israeli
We're not we're we're not supporting the israeli state. Yeah
He's shilling for israel in this voicemail and try and he's like he works for like the uh the tourism department of israel
And he's trying to you know bait us
Into coming to israel. Well, damn. I mean, I guess we better do contact our jewish overlords and make sure we're pleasing them properly
Could this be my beach vacation of my dreams?
It could be they do have uh, easton client from h3h3. Yeah
Isn't it, you know
Not to get too serious or anything, but isn't it just what an what an absolute beach of a man
That's true. They just straight up pay you if you're jewish to come to israel or they'll like pay for the trip
That's a fucking deal. What a deal the human sandbar
That's fair. That's accurate
Is he still shit is the consensus that he's still shit and gay?
You know online or is he been ready yet? I I thought they were both always shit. So I don't know why everyone
I saw a left-wing commie
Yeah hero
Respond to ethan
And I don't know what the controversy is but apparently there was a controversy being responded to
And this guy was like this guy was basically
imploring ethan like ethan
You know your fans are mad because you said the wrong thing and you have failed as what they perceived
You were as their quote-unquote thought leader. You need to not
Do you need you need to stop pandering to these people that hate you now?
Because they do not you know, they're in it for what the some weird political stance. They thought you represented
You need to get back to your lefty roots
You need to you need to be you need to be true to yourself
You'll lose some of your fans, but those are the fans. You don't want to have and da-da-da-da, and I was like god
I hate capitalism. Yeah
Yeah
You know, you know what that's the story
I forget if I talked about this go on jesse go on go on
It seems like from what I've seen of like the backlash or people turning from h3h3
It all stems from like
When they started doing their podcast and filming it and people saw that like they have absolutely no charisma in real life
but like
Wasn't that always
Obvious from their videos like why are people surprised?
I thought I thought the whole gimmick of ethan was that he was a weird gumpy guy with no charisma
I think I think the format social skills being edited. I think is a much better
Like he's able to be funnier and you know do takes over and do stuff. I think that works better for him
They associate the the funny meme edit with his
Ability to make the joke even though that's what you get for following anyone who uses jump cuts ever. Yeah
Yeah, stay tuned for this week's we Agua everybody jump cut central. Here we come, baby
um
Shit I was gonna say something. No, whatever. I don't know
happy pokemon day
of
thing
Business. Yeah off of just looking at videos and going what I mean
Yeah, and then and that that's it when he's in on a podcast
He's just he's got a lot less to say which is why it's all guests
That I mean, that's fair. You know, you got to spice it up. It's yeah
I mean his whole lawyer has been reacting to like other people's shit. Indeed. That's how he got
I don't hate him which I have no respect for in the first place. Yeah fair enough. Um, hey
Yeah, yeah go on
Nothing, just fuck them. I don't like them. Okay. I I don't hate him. I don't know. I haven't tuned in to where's the podcast
Ethan I don't hate him, but I don't like him
No, no, we can't dilute that. Okay, you're right. That is a pizza party podcast meme
That's the only podcast that I can't find all right. I I found all the other podcasts
That's the last one that I haven't added to my collection
But but the the h3 podcast. I don't know when it's when it is so like when's the podcast
That's that's the meme for them good
Hey, uh, Ben, I just wanted to respond to your thing about hating capitalism. Okay, serious point, but I'm not going to get that into it
It's just that I had a thought. Oh, let's fucking get I may have said this before
But I think I deduced what the issue is and and here it is. Okay. It's that I think
Capitalism has a very specific usage and that's like wealth generation and it seems pretty good at that
Like communism and like other stuff like that socialism, etc
Seems really good at like taking wealth that has been generated and trying to like, you know
Make society fair make everybody even and all that stuff and like those both make sense in different situations
It's just a matter of like what your priority is
Which which of those things you like better and I'm you know to me helping people helping people
That's some pussy shit. That's some pussy shit helping people
Fuck it. I mean make money
You know the way you said that is just sort of seems like the perfect solution is to
Just do both
Do both in like a in a in a rotation like you do kind of yeah to make gains and wealth
I mean, I followed up some of some communism to spread it out and then do a little bit a little bit
I mean, I mean capitalism is is a crime giving a shit about anyone is just an anchor
Human beings are just capitalism is ideal for generating personal wealth. That's well, okay
But I mean, it's totally true that the world has been improved by like the west's
Development of technology and you know, they talk about like the iphone has helped the world
I would say and you know all the technology that's gone in. Well, I mean, yeah, those things did those things did happen under
Capitalism, but I don't think it's fair to deduce that they would not have they could not have happened without it
But but I I mean I 100% think that's fair to say because what what's how would they
They were generated by the profit motive of the people who were working for those companies trying to you know make better
It's not impossible, but like the the reason that works is because
uh each individual comes forward with their own idea and
In the communist society or like where there's less incentive for the people with the good ideas to come forward
Yeah, um
They would need to be recruited and that just takes a lot of time and a lot of manpower to like find the people who can make
Really good technology. Yeah, I I agree
So like it's just it's just faster to do it capitalist because like people are motivated by the their own
You know the things they can get for themselves
So they will do it and then everybody turns around like oh that guy's doing something cool. Yeah, I agree
Yeah, and I just don't get like but then everyone's poor except the guy who did but that's their problem
I don't get the argument that people give of like well, you know people can criticize capitalism
But it's the best we have and nothing else would work and without capitalism
You know any other system would just devolve into complete and total anarchy and violence and I'm like yeah and your point is
Like is that supposed to be is that supposed to scare me? Is that supposed to be bad?
Jesse I was I was just about to agree with you. I was so close
Uh, like what what what is what is everyone's like what what what is wrong with complete and total anarchy and violence
We haven't tried it in a long time. Maybe it's time to give it a try again
Okay, it's been like thousands and thousands of years since we've had a state of complete and total anarchy
Maybe it's time to give it another go
Maybe it'll work
We we have had a lot of practice with a post-apocalyptic media to get used to the idea of a fucked up world
Where you just have to fight and kill and bite people
So many things that are issues and problems would not be problems in life
If just one change one simple change make violence legal. That's it
That's all you have to do if violence in all forms was legalized. There would be no problems in life
Life would be a happy stroll through a field
You gotta move to new los angeles city my friends. Yeah, he's right. He's right. They're your people. They're waiting for you there
I mean, this is what I am come come join us in the slide. I warm more and more every day to anarcho capitalism
It just seems like it's a real good plan. Uh, I see I think if you ben if you mother fucker
Violate the non-aggression principle on me my privately contracted nuclear device will be headed to your domicile
At you know at the fastest speed that my slave soldiers can make it go, uh, you know indentured servants
I pay them is the appeal is Nate is the appeal tell me honestly
Is the appeal of capitalism that under capitalism under like under anarcho capitalism?
That you get to daydream that you could one day be
At the top. Is that the appeal? I feel like that's the appeal for a lot of people
I think that that there is definitely a strong appeal. Well, it's like protecting the quote unquote american dream
Which is to like make it yourself, uh, you don't have to like rely on other people to help you
And then also that you've acquired, you know a decent amount of wealth
I don't think most even I think it's possible. I could get rich
I think it's pretty unlikely for me
But I do think I could carve out a pretty decent middle-class survival for myself in my life. I don't need to be at the top
I'll be happy with that. I just want to be Han Solo shooting a guy under the table. That's all I want
I want all of us to be free to kill each other
I mean, I didn't
Because you know, it's fair to say if you if you really are into capitalism, you're definitely
De-prioritizing like like fairness because I straight up don't believe in free will and people are born different
And that's not fair. It's not fair that people just are born different
So it makes sense to just even the playing field so everyone has an equally good experience of life
But that is fair. But we but we don't have an equal experience of life because capitalism rewards those with capital
And people are born with differing amounts of capital based on the families. They're born
I couldn't agree more. But what's the solution?
The only way that anything is ever going to be fair. Don't let people inherit wealth
Obviously, don't let people be billionaires. Why would we why would we punish people who raise?
Who like work really hard and acquire money to pass on to their children so they will have an advantage
No, my my children are not inheriting my wealth. No matter what I will be buried with it
I I don't want I want my children to grow up poor
So they have a sense of values instilled in them or a sense of complete mental insanity and fucking mental illness instilled in them
One of the others said for that
Nate, how is it a how is it a punishment? How is it a punishment to mr. Smith?
That smith that mr. Smith jr. Doesn't get to well, I'll tell you how Ben
I think a lot of people uh, the reason why they are trying to amass wealth is so that specifically
They can kind of pass on their wealth to maybe it's about protecting their legacy and it's wrong and it's wrong
And it's literally the the the argument for you know
Passing on wealth depends on what you mean by wrong
If if my father was wealthy then it's my birthright to inherit that wealth
But then isn't it all of our birthright to be born free with the freedom of killing each other and beating each other up
And doing whatever we want
Nate, I don't understand how you can sit stand there and be like oh under cap capitalism is the best system because
Everyone has the saint everyone has a fair shot at making it at making it big
Yeah, and then turn around and be like yeah, but people should be able to inherit wealth from their parents
They didn't earn I'll tell you I'll tell you exactly how bad because one of the one of the big components here is just freedom
And if we're gonna say that it's people aren't allowed to do with their money what they want
Which includes giving it to their kids or helping them or whatever then I mean
That's a huge invasion of like their personal freedoms
And maybe you think it's best to just do away with it, but you know
I just think these two ideas are completely at all. I agree. There are conflicts for sure. Listen. Listen. Listen. Okay
Human beings need motivation to do a good job
My grandma told me like back in her day back in the world wars and back when communism was the thing in the thin air
A lot of people you know had to do a job because they were told to do a job
But like a lot of the jobs were done poorly and a lot of like let's say construction work and bricklaying stuff like that
Was sloppy and the nation suffered because no one wanted to do the job
And they would still got paid the same amount whether or not they did a good job or they just did the job
So I'm gonna jump with them in the end no motivation. No need to do a good job
So and everyone suffered for it for it. Yeah, that's you know, that reminds me of mine
I don't see how that's different when when when there's like life currently like that's how
Like how many how many people like do office workers now do like nobody fucking cares about their job. No one's motivated
People will hate their jobs. I mean most people will hate their jobs
But the thing is like there is still a sliver of a chance that like they'll get a raise
They'll be promoted. They'll do something better. They might they might get a different job at some point
Like maybe maybe it's a stepping stone in their career. There are options. There are possibilities
But when when when you're stuck in one job and no matter what you do
You're still gonna have the job in the end of the day because someone has to do the job
You're not motivated to do shit. So long as you're there and you're punching the hours
Is
There was the the bad guy that's life for most people listen the bad guy in the movie the musical
1776 who is the bad guy said this and he's a he's a conservative
You know like right wing guy and he is the bad guy
Nonetheless, I think his point gets to the heart of the matter here and he just says
Uh something like most people would rather die like whatever. He's he's lecturing john adams and why john adams is wrong
and what he says is um
Like most people would rather die
Uh fighting against like being
God damn it. I forget what the point is he said like people poor people don't want to they want to protect the possibility
Of becoming rich rather than face the reality of being poor or something like that and that like that's why they support like whatever
Property rights and stuff like that. Okay
Um, so so like what it talks about is people want hope and people want to feel
Autonomous and when you do something like you institute a top-down
System where you've like slotted everyone into a thing
I think goes to mages point of like it just makes people unhopeful and unmotivated and that's why it slows down
Productivity and that makes the whole world worse. It definitely does less to exacerbate
Disparities but at the cost of dragging the entire like gdp if you want to think of it that way down
And you know, it's just a question if you think that's better or worse
Uh, and what problem you're trying to solve at that time? I think I just think that you
I don't know about any of that
You shouldn't you shouldn't extol the virtues of freedom at all if your idea of freedom comes with any caveats whatsoever
Well, that's silly because no, it's all or nothing every
Either you're allowed to do everything or else you believe not real
You don't really believe in freedom if you believe that i'm not allowed to kill you and take all your money
I mean, you're correct. I don't believe that that should be allowed. So I don't believe in absolute freedom
Um, ah, you're all coddled by modern society. Yeah, we're gonna see it for the facade that it truly is
I'm the only fucking forward thinking
Like who will be motivated to do anything if you if you know that you're just gonna die around are you kidding?
Anarchy is nothing but motivation. You're motivated to survive by any means necessary
Someone has something that you need to live you kill that person and you can't fear though
Exactly. I'm gonna I do I live in constant fear anyways
Everybody is living in constant fear anyways fear of having their shit taken away by by people above them
You know, everybody is afraid of getting like uh, you know, like kicked out of their houses or losing their jobs
That's the same fear
Just why not take that fear that you have for the people above you and just make it fair so that you're afraid of everyone around you at all
times
We still have like, you know the trust in the system that like maybe if someone screws us over that there's still
A way of making it right but like there's not though
Do you know how expensive lawyers are to fight for what's right if somebody that's with you in the current system
If somebody breaks a law and like hurts you in some way and you try to seek legal help
You're fucked it costs thousands and thousands of dollars if you're poor
You have no rights as it is if you're poor you already live in anarchy
But with all the rules of fascism it's the worst of both worlds
So you might as well just make everything fair for everybody and destroy all law and destroy all order and have violence be legalized
Once and for all and fix the fucking world once and for all
I'm like 90 there with you. Jesse. I'm I'm pretty I'm almost there with you. There's okay. Well, let listen
I did not grow up poor, uh, but the the larger factor is I have had very very few
Interactions with the law period you can't go to the fucking cops if you're poor and someone commits a crime against you
If somebody fucks you over and you go to the cops you get fucking singled out and like profiled as a criminal somehow
I just don't know if that's true. You can't trust the law. It's absolutely true
That sounds it's all bad. It's all the whole system is poison. It needs to be fucking destroyed. That's the difference
I have not lost all faith in the system
And furthermore, I feel strongly that whatever challenges are placed before me by the world
I have the tools and resources to overcome them. I feel that that's how I feel day to day
So that's why I feel resources to overcome them because you were born into those tools and resources
I mean, I mean I've I've been stolen from I've had my house broken into and robbed and I've
And I've gone to the police before to help and the police didn't do fucking jack shit for me
The police have never done shit to help me anytime that I've been the victim of a crime
A lawyer has never done anything to help me anytime that I've been the victim of a crime without just
Siphoning my money and doing nothing doing jack shit in return
No one has ever helped me legally when I've been the victim of something
So why shouldn't I then also be allowed to go rob someone and get back what was taken for me myself?
Why shouldn't there just be no laws?
Since the laws only apply since justice only applies to people who can afford it or people in higher social strata
Why shouldn't it just did all be destroyed? I mean, what do you want the system ain't perfect? I agree
But I mean, it's been real shit for you. It's been pretty great for me. So who's right? Uh, I don't know
Jesus christ, uh, well, how about this? How about this?
Uh, no more billionaires
Ben, this is the number one fucking thing. I hate about all you fucking make make nobody poor
No more billionaires and nobody has to be poor. What's his name that's skull with the glasses on his face, you know, uh,
Sean, yeah, Sean. I bet you retweeted this you fat motherfucker
Uh, it says it says, uh, he he's imagine being a billionaire and never once thinking about using your money to help poor people
Oh my god, you're right. How could elon musk have like never thought about that?
I don't know. Maybe he's thinking about like first of all, that's not hard liquid assets
That's investment in the companies that are currently generating wealth and helping the world
So I I think if you're a billionaire and you're not doing something charitable or philanthropic, you're obviously
How about making the world better by converting gasoline cars into electric cars that's going to help the planet
So there you go. I'm not against elon musk as a person. We're not we're not talking about your corporate assets
We're talking about your personal wealth people have personally owned billions of dollars. Well, that's fucked up
What are they doing with whatever the fuck they want to do with it? That's what they're doing with it. Yeah, they earned it
Yeah, they did fucking earn it ben donald donald donald trump earned that all I hear
All I hear when I hear people doing this is I hear a bunch of fucking losers
Who can't make a buck and then they're crying about people who are better at using the system to generate wealth
That's what I hear and it's embarrassing and pathetic
But what what if you're in a system where the thing that you're good at is no longer viable?
Maybe the thing I'm good at is killing people and robbing them. Am I supposed to be singled out like that's not viable
That's my talent. Maybe I don't know. I haven't tried it yet. I'd like to see
Well, for many reasons we don't want to do that. I can't believe I cannot I can't believe
You think it's fair that people can have that. Okay, but please understand
I cannot believe that you guys think it's not fair. So we're at an impulse. I don't think it's not fair
I think it's I think it's totally fair that people should be able to have all the wealth in the world
I just also think I should be allowed to throw a mile to have in their corporate windows
Kill a bunch of people cut their heads off go up to the top floor kill them take their money
Take their gold plated toilet seat take their fucking wife and their fucking jewelry and just
Think about this and a big burlap sack with a dollar sign on it and a fucking hamburger mask and a and a striped
Chail suit and run off and fucking go into a cave in my hideout camp
Like the fucking red dead cowboys and start my own society, baby. Hell. Yeah
Okay, please respond to this however you want to what do you think it?
What do you think is the proportion of people who are currently fabulously rich?
What do you think the proportion of them is that we're born into wealth versus came from nothing?
What do you think I don't know. That's probably quite a few
I don't know probably the majority I would say you think it's probably pretty skewed
You think you think maybe there's a lot more people who are rich now who are born that way
But ben while your focus is on the injustice that some people were just born into these systems
My thought is no one's entitled to anything these children were not entitled to the wealth that they now have and the people who don't have it
They you know, they're not being there's nothing being taken from them that they should have
It's just that the the rich parents here
Choose what to do with their money in this case support their kids or give them their billions of trillions of whatever dollars
And that's their right. Yeah, which leads to a society that is inherently unfair
But well look tons of societies across the world are terribly unfair. America's pretty great. America's pretty good
What can I do about Saudi Arabia? I can't do anything about Saudi Arabia
What I can do is try to make the world around me a little bit better. I'm I'm I'm here
I'm pointing out a thing like this is unfair and you're like, yeah
What and and what do you want? What do you want? I I would like it to be less
I would like it to be less unfair. I agree. So how about they adopt the american model because it's pretty great
I'm put I'm taught. I'm pointing at america, Nate. I'm pointing at america that we live in
Your focus is the best country in the world. That's your biggest problem not like the terrible totalitarian nations
The best country in the world. That's correct. The best country in the world. No, no fucking no fucking subsidized health care
No universal health care best country in the world earn earn money pay for health care. It shouldn't be free
All this like how much does college cost in america too much? Don't go get a trade
Best country that's great. Shut up. Yeah, you're an idiot. You're going off on a
harshly defending america being the best country in the world when you don't actually
Like you're just it's not really about that
You're just angry at this. You know what? I really think I'm explaining my point. Am I?
I'm a little I'm a little angry. I mean, I think you're very wrong. I mean, I I have uh, I'm not I think you're very wrong
There you go. I'm not I'm not like the rest of you weak masses adopting other people's philosophies. I've created my own philosophy
That I call uh anarcho fascism
Where that doesn't make sense
Basically the the way I see it is that the only way that anything will ever be fair for all of us
The only way that human society will ever advance and prosper is if we decide once and for all as a species
Whether we want complete anarchy or complete fascism
One or the other because both of those systems are fair in their own way and everything in between is just a middle man
Is just a compromise a worthless half measure that isn't fair and is never I mean to be fair
You could just say that you know like
Every system of government that we've ever tried has been some worthless
You know half measure between fascism and anarchy and we just need to decide once and for all
Which one of those fair systems we want to adopt and when we do everything will be fine
Because when when you have anarchy you have perfect freedom and when you have fascism in theory if it's like you don't have
Perfect fascism and anarchism it like if you're talking about gun to your head
Well, Nate you want you want parents to be able to give their kids their wealth like that's you know
We don't want to regulate that so we should unregulate everything
Anarchy because it would be it would be unfair to it would be unfair to tell people what they can do with their money
That's correct. That's correct. Jess. You should you should focus on bringing about like um
Zombie apocalypse, then you'll have anarchy
Well, like I mean, yeah, I mean because like for example in in the judge dread universe one of judge dreads famous catch phrases
Uh is the the price of justice is freedom
Meaning that you know, we sacrifice a little freedom for a little bit of justice and that's how judge dread
Justifies the fascist state that he operates in which I think is a you know a logical justification
if not a totally perfectly sound one
but
The the basic just you know with anarchy you get freedom and with fascism in theory you get justice and comfort
So we have to decide once and for all whether we want all the comfort and all the justice or all the freedom
We just have to decide one or the other because both I mean, I just would be better than anything we have now
I think that forever people will just debate the nuances of trying to balance those two things and that's where I mean
This is all hypothetical
Obviously because no one is ever going to adopt my policies because the world is stupid and no one understands how correct I am
But you know, I'm just saying if people were smart then we would decide one way or the other
But we never will so it's all fucking it's all hypothetical and pointless. It's all worthless. Nothing matters
Fair enough
Fair enough, you know when in in Minecraft when I get my house griefed on a server and it feels unfair
They steal my stuff. They steal my diamond pick. That's true anarchy
And so I don't like that. Like, uh, I like to have a locked chest. I like to have a chest I can lock in a
But then it again, you know, sometimes it's fun to go into someone's house and steal their shit. So, you know, I guess I'm I'm
Uh, I'm I'm politically fluid
I I I I swish to and fro between all all of the things
I don't even necessarily think that you can just arrive on one political philosophy that will just work forever
Like I was saying before I think that like capitalism is good at wealth generation and things like like being more socialist is about
You know, like fairness if like you have to probably cycle between the two
I don't think there's even like a perfect thing you can do
It's just we give up more and more freedoms for the sake of supposed justice because we want to believe that if someone
Wrongs us or commits a crime against us that the system will sort them out and they will face justice
But so many times so often that completely fails us, especially people in lower social strata
That that sense of justice fails you completely and doesn't actually work
So if it doesn't actually work, we need to either make sure that it completely works by taking away all freedom
Or we need to just get rid of it all together by taking away all law
And and having people sort it for themselves letting people kill each other
It can work. It can work to an extent though, right? Like it can work some of the time. I think if it works
I think I think working to an extent isn't good enough. I think it has to either completely work or not be there at all
Yeah, I I feel like that's work for everyone or for people should be free
It's it's it's a ridiculous statement, but it is kind of true that we need like it would be the most fair
The only thing is at the moment why there's like always conflict about it is because
The anarchy is good for the people who have nothing the poor people. Oh, yeah
And the justice the justice is good for the people who have the money. Yeah, that's true
Anarchy is not anarchy is not good in anarchy. You'll just develop like the very least you'll develop stratified societies
In it like because people will just you know ally and then they'll be able to win
So they'll just do that anyway the way they do now
You'll you'll just you'll just have I mean you'll just have exactly what we have now
Which is you know people hoarding all the wealth and becoming like, you know forming
Protective societies around themselves and probing themselves up only worse because it'll be unregulated
I uh, I said something a while ago in another. I think it may have been a bonus episode, but I like um
the idea that
humans
As a species have just not evolved to the point where we can deal with the amount of connectivity
We have with one another like we're still pretty tribal and we stay we like to stay in a small amount of you know
Small amount of people we know and we would be happier and easy and better able to deal with life
If we are all in villages still
but because we're all connected
It's it's you know, we're always fighting because we're always exposed to every other type of person the internet must be destroyed
I definitely believe
That's 10 at one of my philosophy room for a glorious new age
Step one destroy the internet
They say for example and I agree with this that communism works really well for like five people
Because you know them and like you don't mind like helping them out like the people who like need help
It's like I don't give a fuck about just some dude across the world. Sorry. I don't know you dude
I don't want to give you my money if I knew that guy. I probably wouldn't mind
Um, that's just I I blame my human genetics for that. Um that I you know
We we either need to evolve to be like a strange
Insect hive mind where we're all okay with the amount of people
And we we all like work together inherently or we all need to turn into you know to
Post apocalyptic go in small tribes and small villages again and eat saber tooth uh slime tigers
I just want to set my position right now, which is just that I'm I am not a rich man, but I'm doing fine
I'm surviving and doing okay, but if I
Succeed at my quest in life and become more and more wealthy to the point of you know, like I'm doing very well
Um, and then the people come out and are like, oh now we want to take your money and give it to the people who really need it
I'm gonna be like listen. I earned this. I did this all on my own
I had many advantages growing up that other people didn't have absolutely true, but why should I
Give up what I've earned. Why because I didn't deserve it. I think it would that's fair
What what what what what about that part? What about that part about how you had advantages that other people didn't have?
Well, see there's what about you okay? Here's the thing free will doesn't exist
So it's a matter of what do we do to make the world the best place it can be
But we have to factor in that people need a motivation to do stuff
My motivation is I want to make myself financially real secure
So you so you deserve what you got because you had a head start over other people because
You wouldn't have done it
You wouldn't have done the word deserve is you should not use the word deserve
Deserve is the wrong word because I'm not talking about what anyone deserves. I'm talking about motivation
I'm talking about motivation to do things because if you just if you tell me now that Nate, uh, listen
We're gonna implement hardcore socialism in 10 years all the money you earned by that point
We're just gonna take it then I'll be like, oh great now. I know not to do that now
I know to just relax and play video games. Thank you for letting me know that I shouldn't do this
But if I get cheated well, I don't think you should make well, I don't think you should get nothing
I don't think you shouldn't make money from your hard work. I'm just looking at these
I mean you look at someone who's got 170 billion dollars and like that's wrong
Like yeah, you should you should you should be rewarded for your hard work and for your good ideas and ingenuity
And all and your skills and all this good shit, but like nobody should be rewarded that much. That's an accident
That's the system failing
um
I mean Jeff Bezos hit gold and he developed a system that was disproportionately better than what everybody else was doing
and
Yeah, and now he commands enough wealth to house like
Half the fucking pop homeless population of america. Ben. It's not like he's not stolen this wealth from anyone
He just generated it through sales. Yeah, he is not taking anything from anyone. These are willing transactions people are making
He what do you mean? He's not taking it from anyone. It's a zero-sum gain. He has it
That's not how wealth generation works ben
It is it is how wealth generation works as a matter of fact. Okay, so so what so ben you're telling there's only so
Why did the people choose to buy the products available on amazon?
Because they would just want to give their money to jeff bezos or maybe because he was providing value through the service
Maybe that was part of it
You think jeff bezos is like do you do you think he's there like in amazon headquarters?
Like making all these sales and no he built like a system that he deserves to profit off of
No, he doesn't deserve to profit that much. Nobody. Well, I I'm with both of you
I think you're both right and I don't think that you're really that your ideas really contradict each other as much as you think
Because I think
Like you can have a system of capitalism that
Creates itself naturally without being backed up by stupid laws and regulations and bullshit. Like that's my main problem
Like here's my reason number
1517 million why the system has failed and must be destroyed every year
I have to sit down and do my stupid taxes and I have to you know, give the government money
Taxes and amongst people do your taxes. Don't forget. Yeah, and like but like it's complicated and it's annoying
It's a fucking process that I have to go through like fucking homework that the government gives me and if I do it wrong
If I make a mistake they can audit me and destroy my entire life. Why is that fair?
I think like I'm totally fine with the government saying we have the guns. We're going to steal your money every year
That's fine. I understand that I respect that but the fact that I have to do fucking homework and do this complicated
Bullshit and pay a service like turbo tax, you know, like like if I had the money
I wouldn't have to think about it because I could pay someone to do my taxes for me completely
And that's like another reason why like if you just have money then the system works for you
And if you don't have money then you have to do all the annoying fucking grunt work bullshit and homework that they give you
I would be fine with capitalism if it was natural and made sense if if you have the will to make a billion dollars
Whether by hook or by crook
Even if you have if you just hire a bunch of guys with guns and take over a small village and take everybody's money
I respect that that's fine. You could be a warlord for all I care
That's fine. You can come and take my money
But if you want to take my taxes every year then have it be like fucking disney's robin hood
Where the fucking cop comes knocks on my door and takes my coins in a coin purse and that's fine with me
Don't make me sit here at my computer and do this stupid fucking homework every year because it's fucking annoying
I I want to say I just want to say I have a consolation but go ahead. I'll say what if what if jeff bezos
We're only allowed to keep we're only allowed to have a hundred million dollars from his amazon mp
From his you know from his his master mining behind the servers that lots of people use and benefit benefit from
What if he were only allowed to have more money than any person could ever possibly need?
What a tragedy that would be. Well, listen
So you you have to acknowledge that you are taking the money that he otherwise would have gotten and so what do you call that?
Is that just distribution? I would call it theft
Uh, but you know, I'm totally fine with capitalism
It's just all the bullshit that comes with it the regulations and laws that I think need to be destroyed
It's just decided that I hate and people that I hate
It's it's theft if it's illegal. So you just make it legal. I hear you and you know what ben
I will give you my grand conciliation on this point
Just as I think it's fair and I think people
Must admit that the the people have inherent
Generally selfish motivations because we're built that way you have to bake that into your system
Which is why I think something like communism like mage was talking about
I just don't think it's gonna work for like
Compelling people like do stuff. You're just just as but as a person who is not rich
Well, I don't understand how you can have empathy or go to bat for people that have
A hundred or a thousand or a million times as much wealth as you do. Why are you?
Why do you want to defend because ben? I have principles. That's why like
Oh, that's right. If you're I don't I don't I don't if your stance is if your stance is capital
Slimes don't bother me be the richer for what it has nothing to do with me. I don't know
I mean, if you can prove that Jeff Bezos is using his money to like ruin the world or you know influence elections
It doesn't matter how he's using it. He doesn't deserve to have that
The word deserve is so loaded with like
Assumptions about you know the way the world shouldn't shouldn't be and I mean, I just don't agree here on wealth
Then we wouldn't have Batman. I mean, he's obviously using his money for good. That's fair
You know what? Let me let me just say this on this point. Okay on this point
Just as I have to I have to accept I think other people should that human beings
Need the proper motivation generally selfish to work and create and do things
I must also even though I don't want to I must accept that
tiny
P-brained
Baby unprincipled individuals like ben will just get mad and rise up
When they see people with too much wealth, that is a fact
You can't have things too out of balance or people will just get mad
Unfairly they will get mad
That's the natural order people who have the will collect all the wealth and hoard it until the people at the bottom get fed up
With it and rise up that seems to be the case. Yeah, but the but the problem with the current system
Is that the regulations and the technology and all the fucking surveillance and shit that we have
Is making it harder and harder for the lower class to rise up so that's destroying the natural order
Which is anarchy and violence when necessary
Capitalism only works in anarchy
Nape capitalism, baby. We fucking we outlaw monopolies. We bust trusts. We don't allow like corporate collusion
We like we we don't allow
Power to accumulate in that way. How is any of that any good?
Are you are you saying we shouldn't outlaw monopolies because I don't see a difference in principle between saying between saying
What wait no no no between what's what's the difference in principle between saying one company can't own an entire industry
Versus saying one person can't own like lots of money absurd. Well, I'll tell you Ben. That's very simple
Because you yourself I mean we all acknowledge the roles that monopolies have on the market
It makes a real difference, but you yourself said it doesn't matter how jeff bezos uses his money
Therefore influences the market you said all that matters is that he has
It doesn't matter and it doesn't matter in the sense that him having it is immoral no matter what he does with it
Well, I mean well fine then i'll just finish the point. It's that it matters how like if he does something bad with his acquired wealth
That's bad and we should stop that if he does nothing bad
Then there is no problem. So detect a problem. Well, you're wrong. I think I think it is a problem that he is allowed to have that much
There's nothing you've made no I just think it's self-evident. It's that that's your problem right there. That's your problem
I've been making a case this entire time. You have made no case that just having money is a problem
You've just asserted that you you've made well
I could just as easily say you've made no case that people being allowed to have all the money
They can they can they can my position does not impose on anyone there for I have no burden of proof
You have to show why is your your position imposes on society as a whole
You allow this incredible wealth disparity. You have to fucking prove it. Fuck you. I think you're wrong. I have to prove
I have to prove and you're saying something is a problem. I make no assumptions
I just say it's fine as it is. Don't worry about it
That doesn't that doesn't mean anything the fact you're you're saying something's good and I'm saying
No, I'm not. I'm saying it's neutral. I'm saying don't interfere with it. That's my point. That's
That's not what I'm saying. That's not a defense. I have to personally think that it's working well
That doesn't the fact that you're defending the status quo doesn't exempt you for making a case for it
I mean
What is exactly?
Where'd everyone go? Am I alone there? No. No. No. Okay. I feel like everyone cut out for a second sounded like it
Like what is exactly the status quo because capitalists?
I guess that's your stance Nate as a capitalist. I mean capitalists
like
Will rat will rally against the idea of socialism
But isn't that already? Well, are we already socialist if we're paying taxes? Yes, that's correct. Yeah, and so you're obviously right
Is the point the point it's about the balance and I you know we can all get carried away here
And as I was saying before I've tried to make it clear that I don't even think that socialist type programs are all bad
Or all need to go away and we need to swing like either 100 socialist capitalists
We should be 100 capitalist that doesn't make sense because there's going to be problems and it's going to cause issues
So I guess I just you know when I see someone saying that we need to be you know way on the other side
Maybe a hundred percent or maybe less. I think well hang on. I don't think that will work
I think I see issues with the way that'll be and I can point out my specific problems
Like you know I have with Ben here
So, you know, I guess that's my point. I just don't want to have to do any more fucking homework
That's my point. I guess well, I don't think I don't think we should uh, I don't think we should just
Level the playing field and say everyone everyone
No, no no ownership no private ownership
Everyone gets a fucking
Everyone gets their their canteen of victory gin and victory cigarettes rations and that's and that's and that's what you own
I mean, uh, but I think we should definitely be more socialist than we currently are. How about you?
How about universal health care? How about some fucking?
better fucking
subsidized
public education
Sounds pretty sounds pretty cool. My opinion. It's to me
It looks like the fact that the government is involved with both of those industries
It's what's drive what's driven prices up so high that they've become unsustainable and sort like that's right
That's ridiculous. Why the college school school doesn't cost what it costs in america in europe
Exactly the problem with the school price in america
The reason that it's gone up so much is because of the dedicated confirmed federal student loans that every student can get
So every college knows there was a huge cash of money guaranteed by the government
They can then afford to raise excuse me raise their prices and the government will subsidize it
That's what allowed the prices to spike so much since like the 70s
That's been the source of the problem the government intervention. Uh, I mean, that's what I've deducted anyway
I think that's correct. I don't know about how and they don't have that in europe, which is why it's not a problem
But we we do get loans. Well, so like
I mean, it's about the degree I would I would argue
I don't really know about it in europe
But like so so you could say that the problem we could just quote and quote solve it by just paying for these loans
But the prices have already gone up when the real solution is to step backward and say
Whoa, it's these loans that inflated the prices so much that have caused the problem
And caused so much like administrative bloat in colleges across the us
I think the real solution is to step backward and say this doesn't make sense from the start
We should, you know, find a better solution that doesn't cause these kind of effects on the market. Well, well, well, here's a solution
Don't give loans. Just pay people to go to college
Well, we've got to deal with the fact that prices currently have been massively spiked
I don't I don't know what to do about that. Somebody smarter than me needs to weigh in and like how to fix it short-term
My favorite pokemon is bulbasaur. Have we talked about that yet? Have we talked about
We did mention bulbasaur
My first my first mon my first love charmander. I picked charmander
You know the squirtle guy now the war toils my favorite pokemon or he's one of them
You know, I started out as a kid when I was in third grade when pokemon first became a thing
You know back back in the day my my guy was charmander. I was a big charmander boy
But as I grew as I matured
I uh, I slowly came around to being a bulbasaur boy
Yeah, and I think what what what ultimately changed me
Is even though I was a charmander boy at that time
They had the the jelly jars that had pokemon on them a little jelly and I had as a kid
A bulbasaur jelly jar and you know once the jelly is out you wash them they become glasses
So all my life did it what flavor what flavor jelly probably strawberry or fucking purple or whatever the fuck
Okay, I was hoping for something green. All right like mint jelly. Whoa. Whoa mint jelly. That's green
Uh, that sounds icky. That sounds like toothpaste basically. But anyways, I had the fucking it does sound gross doesn't you know
I had this I had this little glass that I would drink out of this little bulbasaur glass my whole life
Oh, you know and you know, I guess over time
Me drinking out of that bulbasaur glass every day in my life
It must have gotten into my brain and gotten it wormed its way down my spinal column into my fluids and into my heart
And uh, you know
That eventually I just said ah, fuck it. I guess I like bulbous or the best because I like my glass
If something happened to that glass
And with all the glass that breaks in my life all the glasses that tip over and shatter
If anything ever happened to that bulbasaur glass that would be it for me. I would be done. You'd never see me again
I'd kill myself. Mm-hmm
I like I like how I left for like a split second because the discord was fucking up and we went from whatever
We were talking about about bulbous or glass. I'm really happy. That makes me happy. Yeah
That's good. It's it's good to be back. And you know ben ben. I felt to be back
I did I did a cheap tactic there, which I shouldn't have done which is just
It was a little I said the thing when I said that I have principles what I should the the real answer there is
We have different ideological priorities. I think is the real
Issue there and I totally get and frankly we're different people. We definitely do. We definitely do and uh
I don't think uh
I don't think you're completely wrong about everything. You're wrong about everything. So there's
I think it's yeah, all right. Our priorities. I think I think we'd agree
Look if somebody laid out like true god-given facts on the matter
I think even just given who we are we'd probably just like maybe get different stuff out of them
Because that's what people seem to do
Um, I mean at some point it becomes hard to argue about these things because I mean, I don't know
I don't have like, you know, big fucking national brain
budget
I mean, there's a lot of there's there's a lot of data you could potentially consult
Yes, to uh to make these decisions and I you know, neither of us have it all in front of us. Maybe I've been straight out like
Oh, yeah, go on. Like oh, look, here's how here's here's what here's what happened to college prices
You know, here's here's what the here's what's what's going on with that
That's just what I've heard from seemingly reliable sources, but I have no data. So, you know
Yeah, I don't I don't know. I don't know why they're
We I mean, it's yeah. Anyway, I mean, I guess that's it. So see people we can we can end this on congenial terms
Obviously, I mean, I guess if we were like politicians and like needed to like make hard decisions on like how to operate the world
I like I guess what I would do is I would like commission studies and try to get like real data that would actually tell me
What would work best because I just want to know that. Yeah, you know
You know, it seems it seems like a fool's errand though to like like so much
There's so many people so many bits of data to collect
you would never really know
That much about anything ever. I mean people are collecting data
Uh, you know, I mean a lot of a lot of a lot of the people a lot of the people collecting data are doing it with an agenda
Um, and you got to watch out for that
For sure on both sides on every side
Um, and it's really hard to fucking navigate the maze of uh information and misinformation
That is our modern
And it's so easy to have confirmation bias
Uh, when you just go looking for stuff like, you know, I log into the pcp
I see ben watching all these lefty tuber guys and I want to throw up a little bit
I want to puke but I was I was on a real lefty kick
Uh, for a while a couple maybe like a maybe a month and a half ago or two
I was on it. Yeah fair enough. I just like, you know got real and just got real and got real into shawn for a bit
I tried to I I tried to play
I don't know if it worked. He's okay
Uh, what I was logged into the procrastiners account for like two weeks and all I did was click on like zit popping videos
In the hopes in the hopes that one of you would log on and have to see it too and you'd be like, eww
I'm always seeing
I'm always seeing Nate's weird asmr. There's just for that animal. Yeah
I log into pcp and I see Nate's weird asmr. You got charar
Lobster boy mob boss asmr. That's my dude. Yep
And I and then I log off. He's been on a real meat kick lately. He did like level one crook into level 100 boss asmr
Um, what the fuck?
It's a meme. It's the thing that was happening and like I mean year this was a year ago. I guess I I guess I know the meme
I guess I I I'm I mean you might be
But what the fuck does that sound but what the fuck does that sound like I mean
Question which I guess I could be answered if I went and I watched the video
But I don't know if I want to do more fame
He did pickle rick asmr where he dressed up as pickle rick and was featured on a beauty pies show
Um, because like what the fuck? Um, you know, so you know, he's getting around
That is epic. That is that he's been doing lots of memes. We can all we can all agree on that
Whenever I log on to the procrastinators channel, I try my best to never click on a video
So as to not because I don't want anyone to know. I you know, I feel yeah
I feel yeah, even though it's nothing even though it's like the things I watch aren't even that weird
Oh god. Oh god. I hope I didn't wasn't logged into the pcp when I was watching all those arlo videos
Everyone's gonna see all my arlo videos. This is the history. We'll be out of the closet
Wait, what's the was the name of that purple guy? Oh, uh, randy randy writes a novel
I want to check out randy writes a novel. Yeah, that'll be good. It sounds really great from the title
Check the show notes people. There's all kinds of fun stuff there
All right. Well, that's the end of our voicemails. I guess
God, we're we're at almost yeah, that last discussion went a long time that last voicemail was the real doozy
That last yeah, thanks for the call pcp israeli shillers 2019
Appreciate that. Yeah, right. Thanks for the edifying conversation
All right, that's it
Thanks for listening to this week's procrastinators podcast patreon.com
Slash the procrastinators five dollars people. There's 23 bonus episodes
Uh, you know that you want to listen to them. That's a lot of content. It's a lot of fucking content
So go listen to it. Oh man, we'll be at the two-year anniversary of the bonus content
Uh bonus episodes next time. We should do uh, you know something
Anyway
Oh