The term was originally coined by James Bartholomew for the spectator to decry people who say,
I don't like this thing very much in order to feel good about themselves and then just
vote labour every few years or whatever and take no stake in actually making things better.
This is a fairly straightforwardly good call to action. The term actually decried a real
existing problem. Of course, then the idiots got their hands on it.
Hello everyone and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast,
a podcast on the internet by people also on the internet. We make stuff and now we're talking
about other stuff. I'm the best guy ever and today we're joined by such charismatic individuals as
Tom Oliver. Hello, I am here, signaling my presence.
Excellent. Virtuous it is indeed. I try. Hippocrit is here. I'm great.
The end. Lethal Aurora Mage. And I'm not like the other girls.
I'm purple. Yeah. Excellent. And the often forgotten Fertive Benz.
The Fertive Benz. So easily forgotten. Crouched in darkness.
Origin of all despair in the world. Excellent. Excellent. I try. Thanks for being here everybody
and thank you audience for being here as well. It's time to talk about some dumb shit. So our
topic today is indeed virtue signaling. Virtue signaling. Virtue signaling. Wow, Nate.
Is that impressive? Yeah. Virtue signaling when they get a big, big old light bulb and then they
shite it in the sky and then Virtue Man comes. Is that what they do? Exactly. Basically. You know,
I'm unclear. I'm unclear on what Virtue signaling is, but I think I know where we can find out, Nate.
We got to go to a place where there's both the intellectual content we desire
and the street smart delivery that makes it go down oh so smooth.
Guys, before we go and read the official definition of virtue signaling, I just wanted to
define a possible meaning for virtue signaling. Do you guys have you seen the anime state young
men? Yes. So when Buddha is being virtuous, he starts to glow and so he's signaling to everyone
that he's being virtuous. That should be the thumbnail for this episode. That would be good.
It's kind of like how, this is actually a very apt metaphor, like how lightning bugs are signal
like that they are prepared to mate the fuck out of the ladies out there or maybe the female signal
or something, but it's like a mating dance they do when they light up. So what? Yeah, it's that
kind of shit. That's just like the beta males on Twitter. Exactly. Virtue signals retract at
pus. I see what you're talking about. I got you. Exactly, right? That's a very apt metaphor.
Just glowing. Glowing with virtuousness is their Christ consciousness sores and their
myrkabah spins and the dimensional energies just go higher and higher as their chromosomes multiply
and they rapidly become over 50 feet tall. Just like the ancient Egyptians. Of course.
Okay, so here we go. Here's our top definition on urban dictionary for virtue signaling.
Saying you love or hate something to show off what a virtuous person you are instead of actually
trying to fix the problem. Jane. Wow, I hate Fox News. They're so evil and they hate women.
John, why don't you actually do something instead of just virtue signaling about it?
Jane. OMG, that would be way too much work. Goes back to shit posting on Twitter. Yeah, why don't
you make your own fucking news network, Jane? All right. So I have consistently heard and
reheard this definition of virtue signaling. I always forget it. So I'm just going to give you
one and see if this is true. Okay. I hate starving African children. Is that virtue
signaling? Because I hate how starving they are. In a way, it sounds like you hate them as
opposed to you hate the poor conditions that they live in. They make me feel bad with their
insistence on not eating anything. That is a miscalculation. They're over it. They're
guilting me every day. It makes me hard to enjoy all the luxuries in my life. It makes me hard if
you know what I'm mean. Oh, yeah. No. Yeah. I guess this is good. How quickly you had me
again some decent. That was fast. So, okay. So the whole point of virtue signaling is not to
feel good yourself. Well, I mean, it sort of is. But it is to make people think that you're cool or
good for whatever reason like you would want to do that. And this is run rampant in our society
these days. And it's like absolutely everywhere. Everybody's including me. I'm sure we've
all done it. I'm doing it right now by being on the PCP and letting everyone know what a cool guy
I am. Indeed. Indeed. It is part of it like you aren't actually doing anything good. Yes,
it is. Yes, it is. That's a key component here. Sometimes you don't even have to believe what
you're saying is just you doing it so that others people would just... I would almost say that's
a requirement. That's the difference between virtue signaling and actually being virtuous.
Well, no, you can virtue signal by like trying to amplify what you already believe. But there's
tons of people who just be like, I want to gain social favor in some way. Usually online. A lot
of the time is on Twitter. So I'm going to either echo or project a sentiment that is popular in
order to align myself with this popular perception to make myself look better by by osmosis.
I got my start virtue signaling very early in life. When my parents, my dad, I think, got me
a Backstreet Boys CD and I was jamming out. I never want to hear you say I want it that way.
Yeah, it was a smooth. It was a smooth and silky jam. But I came to realize that the kids at my
school were over the Backstreet Boys and that was not cool. That was something that girls liked
and cool kids didn't like that. So one day I told my dad and he was like, hey, you want to put on
Backstreet Boys? I was like, no, dad, I don't like the Backstreet Boys. They're gay. My dad
called me. He was like, you like them. They're just not very popular. And I was like, it cut me
to the core because it was absolutely true. But I couldn't admit it. Now that is definitely in a
sense similar to virtue signaling. But specifically, this would relate to trying to make you look
morally superior. The virtue of being cool and not liking things that society has deemed are for
girls and gay. In that case, you're absolutely right. By the way, I also had an in-sync CD that
we bought simultaneously to the Backstreet Boys. We each had one. We were jamming. We were jamming to
the. So where does giving to charity so that you can say I give to charity? Does that fall into
the same thing? Absolutely. I mean, you are giving to charity. So that is like a real action you're
doing. But like it depends. A lot of it depends on your motivation. The giving to charity isn't so
much virtue signaling. It's making sure everyone knows that you did it. That's the virtue signaling
part. But let me give you a great example from recent days of exactly what a virtue
signaling is. Like when I think virtue signaling, I think male feminist almost immediately. That's
where my mind goes. And like Harvey Weinstein, big leftist, turns out he's basically a rapist or
something. That is a classic virtue signaling right there. It's these guys with these duplicitous
motives. Like again, male feminists who go on and on about how much they love women and they want to
fight for women's rights. But their end game is to fuck women. That's their goal. But they're going
about it in such a way so as to like do it through virtue. They're doing the popular thing to get
closer to what they want. What really bothers me when people virtue signal is like they pretend
like they're seeing something like non-mainstream, something edgy and risky and like, oh, they're
going to get in trouble for seeing that. But like they say the most popular mundane acceptable
shit. An unpopular opinion. But I don't think people should be ostracized for their sexual
preferences. Society. Just slow it down. Okay. Yeah. That's such an unpopular. You know, I'm in the minority here.
We don't know what's funny about this whole thing. Unpopular opinions. I guess we're all
virtue signals. I have a gay friend. Hope I don't get stoned in the town square.
Oh, but I'm going to get stoned in the town square if you know what I mean.
Legalized, bro. Unpopular opinion. But legalized weed, bro.
You know, it's funny because a lot of these issues now I don't want to be insensitive to
people's lived experiences. But a lot of these sorts of unpopular opinions, I mean, I'm sure you
guys will generally agree with this, are things that people like are no longer problems. Like,
for example, like a gay marriage was legalized what like like seven years ago. So that's like not
that's not a long time. But the not everywhere. Well, it federally has been the problem is
I'm going to interject right here. Oh, right. The problem is it's not even that these things
aren't a problem anymore. It's that you have a bunch of people who ardently believe in these
things. Sure. Like they believe in gay and like, you know, gay marriage and LGBT rights and all
that stuff, right? And that's all those are all good things to fight. Right, we would all support
those in general. Here's the problem with virtue signaling is that when you go on Twitter, and
you tell everybody about it, everybody who's on Twitter already agrees with you. So it's a circle
jerk on Twitter to get all the people you want to like you to like you because you share their
opinions. Whereas you actually want to do something about that, you'd have to like go somewhere
besides Twitter where people don't believe these things and state your case and try and change
OK, here's here's a great thing. I've been watching I've watched for a long time now Sam Harris's
podcast, the waking up podcast. And one of his episodes was he brought on this guy. I can't
remember his name. But like the whole point of the episode was like doing the most good with your
life. How do we do practical good? Could there be a more Nate podcast? Sam Harris is like exactly
me. He's like literally me. So like the whole point of this is to like mathematically determine
what is the best way to do the most good with your money, which is the exact opposite of virtue
signaling. It is the mathematical other extreme. You can't see me smirking and shaking my head
right now. Good. That's what I want. That's what I want the people to do when they hear me speak.
So like and what was determined throughout this was that for like for your buck, the best you
can do to like to help people is to buy mosquito nets for like Sub-Saharan Africa, I think, or
maybe it was like South America, somewhere where like malaria, I think was like a big deal and
mosquito nets would prevent that. Like that was mathematically the best thing you can do to save
the most human life on the planet. And that could change for sure. Like let's say the mosquitoes
die, then you would find something else that's like the best way to help people. Once the mosquito
problem has been curbed, the supply and demand curve will shift and you got to keep up with it.
That's right. If you want to do the most good, that's right. That's right. And like that's the
real shit. And so for just for example, like Sam Harris was like, you know what? Okay, this is good.
I'm going to immediately start giving like X amount of money to this charity because like he's a
pure like rational, scientifically minded guy, of course. So he's just giving his money there.
And if I was so inclined to give my money to anyone, I would probably feel like that would
be the right thing to do, you know, give to those people. Or of course, you know, just engage in
capitalism in general, which is not really the same. It's just like how you build a functioning
economy. But yeah, that's like that is the good stuff. That's what I want to see. And I got no
time for people and their personal little issues. Like, like, like for example, feminists in America
complaining about how women are, there's a problem with AC is being too cold. Like I actually
sympathize with that immensely. I hate when it's too cold in office buildings that like men of
internal higher body temperature, like I get it. And I'm with you on that. But let's not forget
that literally every woman in Saudi Arabia is a slave for the for the most part, like all of them.
All of them. It's fun how we don't talk about that at all. Well, because I mean,
I think the AC thing is like it's not it's not like like the fact that there are worse problems.
I support their struggle. I was sexist. Like, okay, it's a problem. Okay, like, hey, it's too cold.
I would prefer it to be warmer. Okay, sure, that's an issue. We can fix that. But don't call out of
your way and claim it only sexist. I mean, I guess I mean, I guess it is a gendered problem in that
like, statistically, probably management of most places is male. And they're probably the ones
making the decision. So like, it is a gendered issue. I would argue it's a gender issue, but not
sexist issue. Not necessarily. It depends on how you frame the frame it. Like if you say that only
men's, you know, quote, like lived experience is used to determine the correct temperature
for inside the office building. And we just like don't care about the women because they're the
minority. If they just went to like someone who works the AC and be like, Hey, could you raise
it a little bit? I'm sure they would have raised it a little bit. But the goddamn patriarch, you
won't allow it. I mean, I mean, yeah, like, like what it comes down to is that like, obviously,
every employee's input should count the same. Yeah, everyone's comfort should be valued equally.
So like, yeah. And if they're not being, then that is sexist. But like, yeah, yeah, I doubt
that they're saying, fuck the women's opinion, we don't care. Yeah. But there is a certain temperature
that will be the middle range of the comfort level. And people just need to attune themselves to
whatever that is. Realistically speaking, you know, you got to do an example of virtue signaling
would be somebody who runs like an office of like three people and goes on Twitter, he's like,
I changed my AC today because I care about my female employees. Give me hundreds of thousands
of retweets, please. Yeah, you're not wrong signaling right there. Especially because like,
again, mathematically speaking, what if two of your employees are male? Like it actually makes
sense to do the most good for the world to make it like a temperature that, you know, is the most
comfortable for the most number of people. Like just as an example, I'm not saying you should
always, you know, cater to men, I'm just saying, mathematically speaking, it makes the most sense.
That's the way we should operate. Do you think a way to determine virtue signaling is like
the percentage of people who respond to what you said with, yeah, all right, whatever, fine.
Like if you say that, the more people who say that to what you say,
that makes it more virtue signaling than less. Difference is the answer.
It's hard to say because it depends on who you're projecting to. There's a lot of people who laugh
that shit up. Like if you would, you cast that net into the right audience, everyone's gonna be like,
oh, you're so great. You're so good. Like every time, you know, a, a, a, like this whole like
me too thing, like it's a huge problem. But every time another celebrity comes out, like something
happened to me at some point by somebody, this is bad. Everyone's like, oh, you're so brave. Well,
you know, the real problem. It's like, well, why don't you drop the name? It's less and less brave.
Let's solve the problem. The more you do it, the more it happens, the less brave you are.
And you're not brave for not dropping names. If you know exactly who fucking did it and you're
going to keep letting them go on and continue to harass other people, you're not brave. You're
looking for social credit. Fuck you. I have no respect for you.
Entirely true. And the thing I hate about, I don't, I don't hate the movement, but the thing
that is a problem about it is that so many people, like just under this heading of me too,
like everyone's thing gets lumped in together as like equally bad. Like you could have been
legal, literally raped by Harvey Weinstein, or you could have had like your butt touched by Al
Franken, or you could have had like a co-worker make a sexually charged joke to someone else,
not directed at you. And these would all be lumped under me too. My life is hell. You know,
I have experienced deep sexual, like the problem is not that these things, that,
that that you're complaining about these things. Each of them is fine. It should be treated with
a level of, of, of respect. But the issue here is proportionality. That is my favorite word in
the world, proportionality. Just like I was saying before about how the women AC thing,
like that, that, you could take that as a problem. I understand. I'm willing to talk about that.
But also Saudi Arabia, full of litter, all the women are slaves, all of them, basically. And
like, like proportionality-wise speaking, we should talk about that a lot more. That's like
the big deal that, that really matters. Right. Yeah, but like Saudi Arabia is really far away.
But like the AC knob is right here. It's right here in my, in my house. And I can't twist it.
You have to claim patriarchy for someone else to twist it.
Well, well, let's, I mean, Alexa is a woman and she's the one really in charge of all our
computers and environmental controls these days. So Alexa, be the patriarchy. Maybe it's
internalized patriarchy or internalized misogyny on Alexa's part. You know what other sort of
virtue-sugging I really dislike? Like someone, let's say, you know, they're sharing an experience
maybe a negative one, something bad that happened to them. You know, that's fine.
Sometimes you need to vent. Sometimes you just want to share a story and that's perfectly fine.
But then someone else takes your story and then runs with it, puts it on blast, and like, look
at me. What a good person I am for like making this public and we should all stop this horrible
thing from happening to people and then they make it their own problem. Are you saying they're like
just lying and like taking other people's stories to gain the social credit?
No, not lying rather than like, like, look at me. How good I am. I'm helping this person.
Are you saying virtue signaling they're virtue hijacking? They're like hijacking your point
and making it about them. They're like, like turning someone else into like a symbol of like
they're using your struggle as a prop for their virtue. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah. That's a classic thing. The whole idea of like, of like retweeting and sharing and
liking and stuff like that is just it. What's the word? It accommodates virtue, virtue signaling
to happen because it's like it's very easy to just put someone else's statement on your thing
and say look at what I believe. What look at what I agree with. Like it's fine to sometimes just
share certain stories that you want to make people aware, but like don't make it your battle.
It's really just an obnoxiousness slider. Like you can be a good person and say,
hey, you should help this charity or this thing and this guy's got a kickstarter to get medical
funds or whatever. And you know, you re-share it or whatever because you care and you want people
to know about it. But there's just like the more you're putting yourself in the picture frame of
hey look, it's me who's doing all this. It's me who's showing you this.
And that's what it's all about. That's what this is all about.
Let's not mince words about this. These days, virtue signaling is big fucking business, right?
Oh, of course. Like you can be financially successful. You can make like a living. No,
no. You can make a living if you invent the right hashtag and are active enough in a hashtag. You
can be like hashtag famous because you made the right hashtag that embodies some social issue
that enough people want to jump on the bandwagon for and fucking be up on in a Twitter arms race
about. Oh, for sure. Absolutely. And it's like just showing that you support an issue enough
can make you famous, can make people want to support you based on that. So you can make a
living virtue signaling if you're smart about it and if you can get like a following based on it.
When discussion gets wide enough about it, you can monetize it so you can get
monetized thickness. Right? I mean, that's what, I mean, this is, I'm kind of going,
I'm going broad with this, but that's kind of what like, that's kind of what like fucking
YouTubers that like that's that's what like someone like Sargon of Akkad does is they just
virtue signal their what they what they perceive as virtues and like people just like pick up on
those like, yes, this is a very virtuous person. I want to ally myself with that. I mean, this is
like this is what all pundits do. This is what like every YouTube or like blog pundit or something
does. They're out there just putting their opinions out there showing that they support the right
issues and then the other people that support those issues want to be like, yeah, me too. This
person is powerful. This person is influential and I want to show and I want to show myself
to be in alliance with them and I'll do that whenever I can. I'll retweet their shit. I'll
back them. I'll guess I want to show that I am also on this bandwagon and that's what it's all
about. I really because like thinking about that, like everybody is basically a virtue
signaler in some fashion. Does that mean virtue signaling is not really that bad and it's just
sometimes people take it to an obnoxious degree? I think it is one of these things that is
almost a fundamental human desire or tendency, but that doesn't make it good. It would be good
if we could stop doing it and just be objective about things. I do think there's a difference
between fighting for a cause or like trying to spread. I'm not even awareness, but like just
discuss things. There's a difference between having a debate or a discussion and trying to
just talk about a certain thing and virtue signaling, right? Because like if somebody,
like to go back to a pundit, if a pundit talks about an issue and like hammers away at it all
the time because they truly believe this is a big problem and it needs to be addressed more,
that's different than that same pundit going on and making a big deal about whatever's popular
at the time in order to bolster their own self-image. Well, you know, it's a creeping thing
really because like the real issue with virtue signaling generally is it is catering to an audience
and like every every worse because there's money because people will pay you to cater to talk about
the thing that bothers them. Yeah, it's just it's just kind of by nature of the business of
having someone with a pain. It ties to victim culture, right? That's true because in order to
be like it's because we have this weird kind of social dynamic now where being a victim is
virtuous. Yeah, so they tie together a lot nowadays. Like I've been wronged. Look how bad this thing
is. We need to solve this problem because I've been wronged. Now please give me money to make
up for the fact that society shortchanged me in the next way. Yeah, sure. But because we've got
like, you know, social media in the way that we do now, it's so easy for people to like keep catering
to their audience and it just like things spiral out of control and they just keep going down a
rabbit hole where you got guys like, I don't know, like there was some guy on like Joe Rogan's
podcast recently who like it was a self avowed like big SJW guy and then he was there saying like,
yeah, that like and he had supposedly like stopped doing that or whatever and I'm taking
him by his word. I don't really know who he is or anything and he was just and Joe was like with
him on it. So he was like, yeah, man, like I just kept like retweeting the same people. Like just
kept doing it and doing it because like everyone around me was like, yeah, this is it. This is
right. We got to keep doing this shit. There's no alternative facts to be considered or other
viewpoints or whatever. So like, I almost want to give people credit or not not give them credit,
but like not lambast them too harshly for this because just by the nature of the way that our
interactions work these days, it is almost inevitable that we fall into these. I was going to make
a point at some point that this is a huge this is I'm not going to say this is a product of social
media, but it's absolutely spiraled out of control. The way it has because of the way social media
works. Like social media first enables us to happen at scale. Virtue, virtue signal in person
very effectively. Yeah, you have like five or 10 people. Virtue signaling on social media is highly
incentivized socially as well as financially. Well, even the algorithm does because as you
continue to virtue signal and like you show support for that content, all these algorithms
just show you more of that stuff. So you're just seeing more of it. It's just kind of and then
you're you'll be have this little like social bubble because you're only going to interact and
you're only going to see people who talk about these topics and you know what I'm like a bigger
problem to you. Let me let me give you a big example that's happening right now. Okay, and it's
net neutrality. And I think that we might actually disagree on this to some degree because I'm
actually not 100% in favor of net neutrality all the way. Whoa. But let's let's let's let's discuss
this. So so right right now, a lot of people just assume that net neutrality is obviously the best
thing. Obviously. And I feel it sort of fits under this discussion about this recently too. And
it was aware of new facts that I was not aware of. Okay, so maybe we'll both learn something.
Yeah, well, I'm not going to learn anything. It's super. It's I think you're I was going to bring
up net neutrality at some point as well. And I think it's a great example of what we're talking
about right now. Yeah, is because net neutrality, the issue there's huge issues with revoking title
to status. But I think so the conversation has become that title to has become synonymous with
net neutrality when net neutrality is just a subset of what title to means for internet regulation.
Right, right. Because we have so many people who are defenders of net neutrality, myself included,
we nobody talks about the other effects of having a title to classified internet,
there's a lot more regulation on building out infrastructure and stuff. And smaller startup
companies are have more difficulty. Let me let me throw this at you regarding
regarding net neutrality, everybody. So like, this is this is just an example about you fair
viewer, you probably have heard almost nothing, except that net neutrality is great by people
online and that it all it is is super important that we keep it with its title to status and
all that bullshit. You've probably heard nothing about that. But let me raise this,
this point to it. Right now, net neutrality enforces that all internet traffic go along
the same exact channels that there can be no delineation between, you know, different types
of pipelines. It all has to go through the same series of tubes. Therefore, things that take
up a lot of data, for example, the gigantic advent of online HD streaming these days has
completely changed the game for how much data is demanded per capita at any one time. And like,
it is like, I don't think it's the majority, but it's really getting up there to be like a huge
percentage of like all internet data traffic. It counts for like 40% of internet bandwidth.
Exactly, exactly. And so considering that, everybody, let's say you fair viewer are just
trying to watch, you're just trying to go online, trying to go to fucking your own website to do
something, you know, bigdicks.com, your favorite website, you're just trying to get there.
If I'm going to bigdicks.com, I definitely want some 4k HDR.
Well, let's use an example we can all agree on.
These are artistic photographs. Let's use an example we can all agree on. Maybe you're headed
over to your favorite hub for all your favorite content on the internet, patreon.com slash Ben
Sane. Just check out what's been going on.
Yeah, right.
I thought you were just going to say St. Comix because that would make more sense.
Your life is an absolute shambles. It's in shambles. It's the only place you can take
solace in this cruel world is on patreon.com slash Ben Sane. That's where you need to be.
You know, you'll find a friend there.
For a price, of course. He hasn't come cheap.
Okay, so you're just going to some bullshit website that's not an HD video streaming website.
That's the point I'm trying to get to. Okay, so you go there and the page is loading really slow
and you think, why might this be? And then you realize, like, it's the season finale.
It's the series finale of Game of Thrones or something. It just came out and everyone in the
world is using Netflix right now to try to get that fucking, you know, watch that fucking video
that just came out. And so the internet is just down like around you because everyone is demanding
so much data right now that it's a fucking nightmare. Now, does that model necessarily make more sense
than one where there are indeed separated lines where something like Netflix has a dedicated line
and then something like, you know, your static web page loading service that has its own dedicated
line? No, I'm not saying they necessarily should be charging different rates or any of that bullshit.
I'm just saying that that neutrality enforces that everything uses the exact same pipeline
and that does not necessarily demand or create the best environment for all use. It does not
necessarily optimize happiness for everyone. I think not necessarily. There's absolutely a
discussion to be had about how to best optimize, you know, bandwidth and stuff like this because
you have these heavy ban. The problem is by revoking, and this is the argument for net neutrality,
is that by revoking Title II, we can optimize like that, but we can also do all this other
heinous shit which Comcast and Verizon have. Did you expect them to make money to not milk it as much
as they can? Like, do you know there's like, I think there's no net neutrality. They've already
started doing it. There's already examples of them doing it. I mean, if you, a couple years ago,
Comcast and Verizon throttled Netflix, they throttled Netflix until Netflix started paying
them extra money to cover their bandwidth costs. And then there's like graphs of like this,
the speed slowing down significantly, then the date Netflix started paying, it all went back up,
and both these companies colluded to basically kneecap the company and extort them for money.
Well, okay, I mean, business is business. And I get them wanting to be able to do
those sorts of things, or how businesses find an equilibrium of power. But like, again, you need
competitors to drive down Verizon. And that's the problem right now. Isn't that collusion
and monopoly monopolizing and, you know, trust, aren't trusts illegal? Isn't that why we busted
all those trusts back in the days of Teddy Roosevelt or whatever? To some degree, yes. To
some degree, you're absolutely right. And I totally agree with all of these things,
you know, in practice. I'm sort of being an idealist about like what I would like to see.
I would love to have a free market of competition in the space of ISPs and stuff.
The problem is right now, we don't have the infrastructure to do it.
Okay, but it's just that the problem is the origin of this problem was government regulation,
because there used to be a lot of little ISP providers until things got consolidated. And like
AT&T was like the big one that just took over everything. So as to like supposedly to streamline
the process and to make things more efficient in the development of like phone line infrastructure
at the time and now, you know, a lot of, right? No, no. The problem right now is that government
regulations and like letting these companies lobby and basically dictate policy has totally
fucked up any new players stepping in. It's like, I want the libertarian solution. But like
this particular thing of like enforcing the neutrality is indeed like an extra like restriction.
But like, that doesn't get it closer to egalitarianism. I just want it to like all stop. And it's all
to be free to exchange commerce in a free open way. But that's not like what this one issue
solves. Let's say we pull it all back and we revoked title two and put it back on title one and
anybody can do anything. My concern with that is that, okay, this solution, because like this is
what people are talking about, let's get rid of all the legislation. And yeah, if Comcast and Verizon
and all these fucks decide to like make the internet terrible, we're just gonna have more
companies come in and take their place. And my two concerns with that is one, what do we do in the
meantime, while all these new companies magically sprout out out of the ether, the internet still
fucked, we're still kneecapped for the time being. And two, like if the market responds to supply and
demand, like if we wait long enough, and this is just how the internet is, like none of these
companies are legally binded to be good people, like you can just have another company come in
and like not restricted by regulation, but be like, yeah, Verizon and Comcast is doing it,
I'm gonna do it too, but I'll charge five bucks less. And so there's no guarantee that the problem
that we're talking about that's going to go away would go away. Whereas with net neutrality,
it does go away. So it's a guarantee versus a hope that people are going to do the right thing.
And I don't trust people because people are assholes. That's understandable. That's understandable.
But I think there's way more nuance to this discussion that's being completely thrown out,
because we're not talking about title two, we're just talking about net neutrality,
which is only a small part of the impact of title two regulations. Indeed. And this is what I
want to bring up. Like what we're doing right now is not virtue signaling. This is an actual
discussion about the pros and cons of these issues. What I'm gonna do after this is that I am going
to post this, the time code of you talking about net neutrality on my Twitter saying, I was there.
I know about net neutrality. This is me and my buddies talking about it, even though I didn't
say shit because I don't get it. You'll be so smart. You'll be so smart. That'll be new virtue
signaling. That's my plan. Yeah, intellectual virtue signaling. Yeah, that's cool. I like it.
Make sure you put your Patreon in there so people can give you money to help fight the good fight
for net neutrality. Oh, yeah. Oh, that's the thing right there. Like guys, I'm working so hard to
support. Oh, you know what it reminds me of? Remember Ben, like Mad Munchkins, like her,
her like, what was it, another Patreon, but her like things like support artists in the local
community or something? Yeah, yeah, her kickstarted with the incredibly vague like goal of like,
yeah, support like local business. Okay, she's just giving me money so I can buy things.
Live in my town and purchase things from my local, from my local vendors. You know what a great
example of virtue signaling that kind of hit close to home because it's in our backyard
is all these people being like, I got demonetized again on YouTube. Please give me money on Patreon.
It's the only way I can survive. That's the virtue signaling right there. Tom, didn't you say that
exact same thing? I don't know. I did. I did. I keep bitching about it, but I'm not like I never
post my Patreon link ever. I think I did once as a joke. Okay, but but but I don't say it's funny.
There's this one guy is a joke though. Yeah, I will agree that one time I'm being hypocritical,
but it's funny. I mean, I don't blame every time I bitch about like being demonetized. I'm not
I did it just now. I don't like my fucking because like minutes ago, like like if none of these videos
I post are going to make any money anyways, they're going to make like a dollar like I don't even
fucking I if I should just turn off monetization on my channel entirely because I make nothing.
It's more the principle the matter that pisses me off. Absolutely. Absolutely. But it's funny
because this one guy keeps replying to all of my posts with my Patreon link. I'm like, dude,
I'm not posting it because I'm not trying to I'm not trying to virtue signal. I'm trying to say,
look how dumb this is. But um, but there are people that who do that who would just make a big
deal about it and like I get it. I get that it's a huge problem and but to there's there's a point
where like I think there are some people who like have like hundreds of thousands of subscribers
and just lost 50% of their income and that's all the money they were making and they're like shit
guys. I'm opening a Patreon. Could you help me? I don't know what I'm going to do if I don't have
this and then there's the people who jump on that bandwagon or like this is a good way to get on
this narrative and get some extra Patreon. Because it is legit for some people because it is legit
for some people. It's also a convenient excuse. And I mean, I said, but now Patreon's kind of a
bit fucked as well. So it's getting there. Okay, as much as I depend upon it, Patreon is a terrible
company and I wish there were an alternative. So these changes, these changes that are happening
in Patreon that definitely are to some degree going to make people not want to use it as much.
There are people who have already lost hundreds of dollars for this.
Yeah, I've lost a couple bucks so far and it's going to hit on the 18th. I believe it's one of the
fees like the bill comes for the for the patrons so we will see them leave. It's a thing that's like
it's not it doesn't yeah like like more of the fee is the fees putting like part of the fees being
put onto the the patrons rather than taken out of the of the creator's cut and like it's a pretty
small percentage but it's also got like a small tax on it's like 2.9% plus 35 so for a $1 pledge that
it bumps it up from like $1 to like $1.40 which is right and that's a 40% increase yeah the thing
that sucks is that like let's say because the argument that everyone's making I think is totally
valid let's say there's a guy who pledges a dollar to the PCP and a dollar to all of us that's $11
a month he has to pay that 40 cent fee on each one so now that's right he's paying $15 $16 it's
really it's really it's really it's really much more harshly punishing like low level patrons I
don't want to point out that like this fee this cost has always been there and so yeah we were just
taking it out of our income which I was fine with yeah I was pretty fine with it like I understood
that going in I don't I mean I would rather I would rather lose I would rather lose a cut I would
rather lose a cut of a patron's pledge than dissuade them from pledging at all because they're
uncomfortable I hear what you're saying I just wish things had been like this from the start and
people knew what they were signing up for that would make here's my thing yeah here's my question
because like if you know because I looked at the numbers and I'm dumb I don't know man you're smart
um because the numbers that patreon threw out is that we made what like 80 to 88 percent of each
dollar and that was what they were talking like that was the number before and now it's 95
yeah that's about right because I don't understand where if it's the same percent that seems low
well the thing is is like if we were making 80 percent at the low end before but now one dollar
patrons have to pay 40 percent more it's it's because patron making more money no no no no that's
coming from patreon is taking the same amount they're they pay they need the more money because
they're changing the infrastructure so that they it's uh the the thing is more like a subscription
service where the person who pledges um gets paid on the same time every month that they pledged
well to do that they need more they need to do more transactions which means higher transaction
fees I I wasn't aware that that was changing so there is there is more money being taken total
now right I do not think that's being taken more money is being taken in total but the money
that that's right that is being taken is used to pay for the extra transactions which I mean
would make patreon more smooth and and less confusing but it does you're being slightly
inaccurate that that's not quite right what's actually changing is patreon is specifically
trying to change how transparent they are about how much patron pledges like actually are giving the
money to the people you are patroning to so when you pledge one dollar what you're pledging is to
make to do whatever is necessary to get that one dollar to the pledge I was just explaining that
the reason the money is going up is not to get patreon more money they they made an update
to to alleviate concerns and I read that and I was like okay I like the the the main goal was to
make patreon itself work more smoothly and less confusingly um and they gave a few reasons for
like the way the system is now people like yeah I don't know it's it's I just want to look it up and
you'll read it I'll lay this case out real simple for you before patreon used to like if you pledged
a dollar what uh we you would send in a dollar and patreon and the money you know and like the
people you are patroning to they figure out what fees they need to pay to get whatever's left of
that pledge to the person that you're patroning to now what they're doing is they're making sure
that uh okay so 95 of that one dollar goes to the patreon person and then five percent of your
pledge goes to patreon as their earnings and then off of your back you do whatever's necessary to
pay those fees that like 40 cents or whatever to get that money to where it needs to go that's
that's also true but like that yeah the reason that that is like the thing is they wanted to
to like dress it up nice because that their main thing was they were for the artist they're for
the artist yeah they're for the artist they wanted to be like oh we're gonna give the creators more
money make sure there's we're taking less of off of your paycheck that was what they led with but
the reason they're doing it at all is to change the infrastructure of the site which just leads them
with more transaction fees that they have to give to either the creators or the the the pledges and
they decided to give it to the pledges and now everyone's upset I don't like the okay patron
has done but that is the reason they've to bring this back to virtue signaling because I we're
getting a little we're getting a little caught off-path now oh yeah don't you think that this problem
has become exponentially bigger than it otherwise would have been because all these artists are
virtue signaling online about how bad it is and now everyone's aware that's true yeah that's true
yeah I you know I've I've been a lot of people are deep pledging because they've been made aware of
this where they have just saw it in their bank account they would have been like that's dumb or
they would have like investigated and read what patreon said to be like that's okay but because
all these people like this is evil now everyone's like I don't want to support this evil company
I've been that's not true guys it's just business I've been seeing a lot of comic people on Twitter
who are like railing against it and like on the one hand like I'm not happy about it because I am
I do think that it has us a pretty good chance to de-incentivize people from pledging and put
people off and and could hurt me but on the other hand like to go to go out and be like guys patron
is evil like well I mean I don't want to my goal is not to dissuade people from from doing it I mean
I don't want them to jump into it and then get hit with a bunch of extra fees they weren't expecting
but like you know I just as long as it's transparent and they know what they're pledging for like
of course I want people to do it you know that's my people are so people are so retarded when it
comes to like fees and business and whatever I have I feel like I have a fundamentally different
view from like a lot of my fellow millennials out there like guys business is business sometimes
businesses rearrange the way that their cost structures are working sometimes they just
have to make changes and and they they are telling you what the changes so you can say you know what
this is not not what I want to do I'm going to stop doing this it is not evil to change your
business model they are simply adjusting things and if you don't like it fucking leave well from
that's not evil perspective because I agree with you you know like they have to do what they have
to do to make the business work and like there are there are questions of ethics that we can ask
I don't think sure but uh but like again like that's it's not a question of ethics why they're
doing it I think the the problem with patreon doing this is that they've tried to spin it
to make them look like good guys and not just like this is a business decision because I think
they just like work that's what I hate about we have to adjust for the market and this is how
we're going to do it would have been much better than like hey guys we really want to make sure
you get as much money as possible because we love you so much patreon is going to give you some more
money right all right that's that's the part that really pissed me off like like I don't know like
like jack conti really kind of just creeps me out jack conti biggest virtual biggest virtual
signal in the world and about hater of all pornography patreon like pornography patreon has
in an infamous I mean at least among the pcp an infamous email writer who sends us yeah
um every single time it's like some sort of announcement yeah and she's like talking to
us like we're four year olds like oh we're patreon we love creators like you it's like oh
sad okay it makes me mad it makes me mad and it feels disingenuous because because patreon
like yet like to me and like to us like they're this is like they're not a community like we
don't interact with the patreon community they're just a service dude they want you to be in that
community so bad so that you'll keep recirculating you'll pledge to your friends and then all the
money will continuously recycle and then patreon just draws more money off the top of all of it
don't know what community they're talking about I don't know I don't know they they really just
they feel they feel like I don't know they like xylophones to them to like it's like from their
perspective or at least how they wish it was it's like all the people that have patrons are like
their family and they're all their children and they're all working and we're all working together
for the common goal of making patreon and they need to dictate what's good and what's bad art
and they need to make sure and I really do not like the attitude they cop that like I'm supposed
to buy into this narrative let's just let's just same side no you're a service that I use you should
be literally paypal paypal is all these things people have been asking me like what to do if you
don't want to use patreon anymore because you find this evil because you're a retarded person
uh the the answer is use paypal yeah like you can set up you can set up recurring payments on
paypal if you want I have links to my paypal in my fucking my channel bar so I have I have links to
do that on my on my about page on stcomics.com I mean I've had yeah it's it's not one guy but it
works just as well I mean I was using paypal for recurring purchases before patreon even existed
so like it's not like this is a new service they have but it but it needs to come to me
didn't you were like how do we make money and one of the things we were like oh we can make
recurring payments on paypal I guess we can try that but it doesn't have that friendly face painted
it's not a creator's maybe maybe that's a necessary evil then maybe some of these people
need their hug box in order to get them on board which I find really odd but it just makes me mad
it just makes me mad to hear from Taryn all the time because she's talking about what a great
hug box community and I'm like I have yet to receive a single hug from you patreon
hahaha
some hug box yeah what the fuck I want to talk about um the the the dick show patreon because
okay I I don't know whether who would agree on like where would this would stand in virtue
signaling because the reason his patreon is gigantic yeah is because he's writing off of
the the backlash from Maddox like that if Maddox wasn't um doing things against dick and giving
him reasons to you know to to feel like the victim people would not be pledging to dick
it's interesting that you bring this up just because I I I just finished the biggest problem
like listening to it like three days ago uh because did you told me to like get off my
ass and and listen to it so I finally did so I was I've actually been interested because like
it just ends the podcast just kind of ends I'm like what the fuck so I I've been starting to dig
in like what the fuck happened like what and then I saw dick's patreon I'm like holy fuck the man's
loaded yeah so yeah the basic idea is like Maddox didn't say anything and dick did so everyone
went over to dick's show and dick you know said all the gossip and stuff and then recently Maddox
is like filed a lawsuit against uh dick for like um you know damages and stuff and it's a big lawsuit
and dick is like dick's patreon has blown up considerably since then because because he's
because he's you know I saw he was at like 20k before is it like he's at almost 23k right now
holy shit and yeah it is like every every time Maddox every time Maddox lashes out against him
and he's done and he's done so in some really stupid and baffling ways before so I get it like
I get how I get why dick looks like the good guy in this I mean I don't even disagree with that
Maddox was a big asshole uh but but yeah like every time Maddox takes any action against dick
it's like we gotta it's it's a fucking rush to to support dick because now Maddox and any and he's
hugely benefited off of it to be fair I'm sure the biggest dick sucker in the world a digi bro
would say that like a dick has like capitalized on the opportunity and turned that gossip into a
comedy show yeah like that's his real source of you know stuff yeah I don't know tomato tomato
tomato hmm but I think we can agree the foundation here is is a sort of virtue signaling I think
I have no idea what you guys are talking about I think it is yeah I think dick I just yeah dick
did a really good job dick did a really good job of painting himself as the good guy in that conflict
and he did it paid off I don't uh yeah you know uh virtue signaling pays guys once again good good
good good for him good for him I suppose like he really did monetize being a victim and in
sometimes that's appropriate like if you yeah a bit you know yeah you know you know like if you
sue someone in the US that's reasonable oh yeah go on go on no no no that's fine that's moving on
if that's what we had to say about that I I feel like we've pretty much run of gamut here I think
we've done a lot of good stuff on on this topic and I I'm pretty pretty spent I just I just want to
say that I think this discussion has really proved that all of us are just really just we have a
really good nuance and understanding of this topic we're just we've elevated the discussion much
higher than anybody else has so if you really want to if you want to enable more amazing
discussions like this please go to our patreon and give us money yeah because we're going to have
con slash the procrastinators every night and we believe in whatever social issues you do
believe whatever you want please I'm with I'm with you if there's a steady if there's a steady pay
check in it I'll believe whatever you say that's from Ghostbusters that's Winston is that the new
Ghostbusters the old no no that's the old one yeah yeah when he answers the ad he answers the ad
and the receptionist is like do you believe in the paranormal experiences after like life after
death the Loch Ness monster and UFOs and he's like if there's a steady paycheck in it I'll believe
whatever you say because he's a because he's an opportunist but he's also got a heart of gold
Nate that was Winston not women Jesus hello okay let's I mean I got I got some questions here
if we're all set I can pull up some of these questions I'm okay to do that okay here's a
here's a point of order question at the one true Henry asks okay why does your logo say TPC
but the podcast is PCP wouldn't it be TPCP if you are the procrastinators then it should be the
procrastinators podcast justify yourself okay okay I'm gonna I'll go on record I think the logo
probably should read PCP rather than TPC but the reason it says TPC is because it stands for
the procrastinators which is the name of our organization whereas procrastinators podcast is
the name of the show indeed I like I like TPC just because it means that if we if we if we want to
end the podcast and make a different show we can that yeah that's true that's true there are there
are many shows under the subset of this other the heading of TPC of I mean let's let's be honest
just just to be like we we've talked a few times about munchy rebranding all this because this was
all cobbled together without any sort of like logical thought at all we just kind of like
squeezed our cheeks together and shit this out and that's that's the graphic design of
the procrastinators in general wait if you squeeze your cheeks together and then shit it out well
you're gonna get shit all over your cheeks just yeah and that's why that's why we're such a
fucking mess that's why we're a fucking mess and that explains where the the aesthetic is
shit everywhere all over the place in places except except get out from my case Jesus yeah
it was even more apt than you know than you know it's it's shit everywhere except on
procrastinators red bubble merch shop where you can get all the cool not shit designs right now
indeed uh so that's that that's that under the under the sweat under the rug what else we got
hey uh here's one I don't know if this might be a quick one but at stumble reel asks any of you
watch or listen to Harman Town do you any of you guys watch that show I listen to like one episode
I kind of always meant to listen to it but I haven't so no also stumble reel is the guy who
discovered the origin of the pcp guy that's right that's now dead pcp guy rest in peace
long last it's forever in our hearts uh and here's one more question from from the pity from the
pity section here on on twitter uh at zacktm underscore asks wait oh sorry that was the wrong
person get fucked zack uh it was actually at center point 360 uh asks what's your favorite
thing to do while sick that's an important question because you're always looking for something to do
while sick any tips here would be very much appreciated do you sleep yeah sleep yeah sleep and
just do my own thing I always roll around in my vomit and my shit and just my favorite thing to do
is is to have like a like a thing of like just plain crackers and a glass of water and sit and
watch a show a marathon a show on a big old tv marathoning anime is what I do I don't I don't
know if this counts when I say everything to do while sick is to skip work any excuse I have to
oh yeah work is a 10 out of 10 in my book I depending on how sick I am like um if I'm super
sick and I can't do much like in super high here whatever didn't sleep because that's the only thing
I can do and it makes time pass and hopefully that means when I wake up I'll feel better uh but if
it's like the kind of sick that I can still get out of bed and do stuff then um usually just like
maybe play games on phone or watch videos or listen to something something mild
I mean I mean everything I do is just fucking sitting around on youtube or just drawn or whatever
so I just I I do all the same nothing changes nothing changes when I'm incapacitated nothing
changes between Ben being alive and dead it's basically the same
same difference um okay should we have some patreon questions absolutely I've got one right here
there's two questions related to me so I want to okay go for it are we gonna see mage at ratcon
three the rat cunning uh where is it gonna happen do you guys know in america somewhere that's a
no no no mage there you go maybe maybe if we maybe if we kick started the shit out of it
we could we could fly you out I mean at at one point at one point we were we were considering
like me and mage flying together so it wouldn't be like scary but it's we don't know anything about
ratcon three yet so it's gonna happen barely even exists so yeah it's gonna happen during the summer
so long if it's gonna happen during the summer then it's gonna be a strict no for me because
I have obligations during the summer but really noted yeah it's gonna happen at any other time
then we'll see we'll have to discuss it I'd really like it I'd really like it if we don't we don't
have digi house anymore so that that that's really been the big issue I think if digi still had his
house we all would have hung out again by now probably possibly yeah I'm glad to get out of that
house no I want to expand just come to like UK and have an adventure in London but that's so much
more expensive for everyone you know combined I know but like one day one day we'll do the
maybe you have a little bit of female privilege but don't don't push your luck all right I don't
know maybe maybe maybe if we get me you know maybe if the pcp keeps growing and we make you know we
start we have more money to throw around maybe we could make radcon four in fucking London patreon.com
slash the procrastinators uh hey here's a here's a question one more question for me just quickly
uh can you deduct me everyone is my children so there you go okay go ahead there you go okay uh
Ben here's one for you uh Delta Cullis asks favorite vape juice what's the good shit Ben
well um I've been I've been on a kick for menthol flavors uh I think watermelon I okay I buy on
dirtcheapjuice.com most the time even though they're not true is that real of course you would
is that actually what it's called dirt cheap juice or dirt cheap they're not actually a good deal
like but I but they keep sending me every time I buy from them they send me a little coupon for
one dollar off my next order and even though that doesn't make it cheaper than the competition
I have to spend that free that dirt cheap dollar or else it's a waste so I'm fucking trapped I've
got stock homes man uh I got watermelon ice uh blue ice uh I like I like fruit flavors with a
menthol kick I like vanilla ice play a lot of do a lot of that shit uh okay okay now my nickname
in the patreon lounge is mom so that was the right nickname I thought no it was nom for the halloween
okay so I just know it's official I see um okay here we go um here's here's another question from
one spar and this is relevant because this is like basically our christmas episode
because this will be actually this will be there will be one this will be out and then next week
there will be another one and then christmas will be like out a couple days after that one
but we're we're in the season anyway so um one spar asks what do you guys want most for christmas
this year what do you hoping that Santa will bring you want to feel happy you can't Santa only
gives gifts to good little boys hippo so uh you're out of the running for that one tell me tell me
who to kill and like I'll kill the other side I'll kill somebody I gotta kill somebody kill
I know what I want for christmas what's that undertale to yes made by Hideo Kojima aka death
stranding I can't wait uh do you I think this might have been edited is as real I don't I don't
know that this was real or not but I did see a screencap of Hideo Kojima tweeting I am making
undertale to probably a lie probably a lie but god I want to believe I can't wait to see gell
mill del Toro reprise his role as sand yeah it's gonna be fucking great that little troll of a man
yeah oh fantastic uh tom what do you want for christmas um oh my god I don't I don't do it I
don't have a meme answer so I just want to fucking switch I want to I want to I want to buy mario
honestly god damn it can't blame you dude I cannot blame you it's fucking good dude they just
announced bayonetta 3 I'm done I know for the switch the hits keep coming god damn like fuck
yeah that that that and 10 billion subscribers so I can stop working yeah job that that's that'd be
nice we all want that uh mage what do you want for christmas uh I don't have a meme answer either
like I have a bit of a dilemma I do want the switch as well but like there aren't any currently
games that I want on it but there will be like I know that there's a shin megami tense a game
coming out yeah that's coming that's coming there's definitely going to be a pokemon game on it so
no doubt me getting a switch at some point in my life is probably going to be inevitable isn't
ultra sun and ultra moon coming out on the switch yeah that's already available yeah that's out that's
yeah I have a 3ds so I could get it if I wanted to but I'm I'm not particularly inclined to get it
because I'm saving up some money um and the other thing I want is I want to play persona 5
really really bad but the problem is I don't have a ps4 nor a tv to put it onto that's on vita
2 isn't it um no no it's not sadly no okay just pull your just dust off your old vita I yeah I have
a vita like I've got it for really wait you do yeah I have a ps vita I got it for really cheap for my
sister's but uh well currently husband it's really cheap and I got a digimon game on it
that was fun hey apparently it is available for the vita but it's got stutters and it doesn't run
great wait no no I love it up are you sure maybe I'm wrong I don't know I am not you know what okay
this is my mission life I'm gonna find out right now hang on okay because there's definitely a persona
for golden on ps vita which I'm gonna get for Christmas from my parents oh wait it's available
on ps3 that's that's something I don't own it though that that has stutters I've heard though
okay that's that's probably what it is okay well that's fucked uh yeah so like if if I want persona
5 I'd have to get like a ps4 and a tv or so I'm not gonna get any of them but in a perfect world
I would get everything dreams are made to not be fulfilled that's what I that's what I believe
men going and keep them unsatisfied indeed my dream is to never have my dream fulfilled
that's that's a pretty good dream I think because if you do then you'll just languish
wait that's not true life should be about achieving goals then setting new goals so never mind uh
yeah ignore that uh anything else gib is there anything else you want um I was trying to think
and it's really just I want to get all of my affairs like my currently outstanding affairs in order
by the time the new year party and all that like right clean slate let's do this let's do like it'll
help my mind be clear yeah so that I so that I don't have to think I gotta do that that's a great
I totally feel you because I just finished that animation and now if I can get that strike off of
that uh second part of the y3d anime fails all the projects I started this year will be done
and yeah rates so I have like a two-week window to make that work I'm hoping I'm hoping like even
even though it doesn't really make any difference because it's just the next day but it is new year
it's a very mental like block when totally old year stuff is still being done it's become a cultural
thing and so you're affected by it naturally um and I guess what I want for Christmas I want a
microwave I would like a microwave for Christmas I don't want a microwave I do not have a microwave
yep yep I don't know I feel like they wouldn't having a microwave make it easier to to start eating
things that aren't fucking cans of kidney beans oh you just want to heat up those kidney beans is
that is that what this is all about frankly the real reason is I just want to be able to cook oats
much more easily than I do right now that's that's the real thing I want dude you know what I have
when I have like oatmeal and stuff we have a water dispenser and it dispenses hot water so it's
like instant like literally like you pour the hot water in with the oats and it's instantly done
it's the most magical thing of all time that's pretty good though I'm not sure that actually
works with like the steel cut oats that I've got because like you have to like they're pretty tough
and I think the microwave process like softens them or something maybe I don't know maybe I'm
wrong I don't know but in any case I need some solution well I'm gonna work on that that's my
goal to have better oats really what I want for Christmas is oats I want those sweet sweet oats
like what a weird utilitarian answer I gotta get my fucking gains dude okay here we go
now another question uh snow zillofenikin that's mazillofenikin what's up dude
any plans on the pcp having more guest appearances or guest interviews with content creators you
enjoy I've been thinking about this a little bit haven't actually haven't haven't had any ideas for
that lately that's true I I want to get Andrew Hussie on the Undertale uh what oh my god it'll
be our Undertale 2 podcast our best game ever number two when I get Undertale 2 for Christmas
and then release it on steam and make a hundred million dollars um I actually there is a guy who
I've been I've this has been like a pet project of mine for a long time uh that I haven't really
talked about that much but I I want to interview rosseter from twin perfect because he fascinates
me and I he's like the main guy with glasses and uh blonde hair with no beard you know okay
yeah yeah yeah he's like the he's the main dude I want to know what fascinates you about him
like because I've because I've watched those twin perfect silent hill videos yeah you're at your
behest good good it's it's the the the uniquely like adversarial attitude of his videos I find
very compelling and the incredible meticulous detail both in the research of the videos as well as the
editing of the videos is definitely like an has been an influence on me and uh uh I mean it's it's
it's just very interesting especially the kind of languishing that the channel has done uh that
like I'm I'm just wondering why he hasn't like dedicated himself more to producing more content
in a more expedient manner I just want to know what makes the man tick and and know what the
deals because it's one of my favorite channels on all of YouTube that releases content very
irregularly I don't know that there are real enigma to me I want to know them more you're
going to have to lick me this channel because I have no idea who you're talking about I will
twin perfect youtube search youtube search uh the real silent hill experience there's a playlist
just start watching it it is like it is like an 18 or 17 episode long gauntlet of like some gigantic
videos it kind of it kind of falls apart at the end but whatever nah yeah it does there's like a
podcast in there well okay that that yeah is it like a let's play or is it like no no no no no no
it's like a long analytical thing okay it's it's on youtube the merits of silent hill 2 it basically
it's it's a it goes through the whole series the whole series yeah it just discuss it in great
detail I was pretty interested by even despite that I've never played a silent hill before
watching those is what maybe you want to play sound hill and then I did so they're they're real good
they're real good uh in any case that so that's that's like an idea I've had and I actually
messaged rosseter once before but he just didn't reply but now that I am now that I've officially
passed twin perfect insubscribers perhaps now he'll pay attention to me and give a shit about me
we'll see will I pay attention to you when you're the senpai yeah exactly the co has become the senpai
I just realized I didn't credit the people that I asked and answered the questions too so quickly
oh okay the the person who asked if I was going to be in radclan was daxter from patreon lounge
and Ken majored out me person was squid mika from patreon lounge excellent um I okay I think that's
going to do it I'm not seeing any other questions here okay not about me okay back what was each of
your best parts of 2017 both professionally and personally oh that's a good question that is a
good question buy a one spar on uh let's go first yeah I think for mine it was following after me
and math of uh it was you know it's dark demon blood month bro and then Igmovo to a ditch that was like
that was a lot of videos and that was really stressful but it was cool that I did it some
stressful and some of those dark the just some of those dark demon blood month videos are really
good still damn right they are and the thumbnail to the first one for demon stills is still like
one of my favorite thumbnails of all time a demon an arrow to the demon oh it's excellent uh this has
been a huge year for me obviously uh me and mafa was was was uh crazy was huge was big uh but actually
like the channel doubled in size of course with the galco video beforehand where I finally broke
like it was funny like all these barriers like kind of broke all at the same time around like may
this year were like I had never I remember like I had been saying on twitter and stuff
I so I'm so close to 17 000 subscribers the old goal that that uh tbap never reached I want to
break that that's my goal and then I did and then immediately galco came out and over the next like
couple of couple of days and weeks my channel more than doubled in size like 40 000 and then um
yeah fuck and then just like me and mafa was already happening because I already planned it
before galco came out and that was that was big that made people like aware of my channel as
like a thing that was it was going to update regularly and now I'm I've just like learned
from those experiences and I made a couple videos and now I'm doing we agua and things have never
been better in terms of the online stuff yeah it's real great it's real great oh also we all
started the pcp uh patreon this year and that was definitely god that was only this year that was
only this year it was only this year it was like march or something yeah she it yep yep yep um
well I mean I finished champion chapter one finally uh which was great I finished a nuzloc
conquest which was a relief oh yeah I was so glad when that was over um yeah good stuff good stuff
yeah um I think my favorite like professional thing that I did this year was just learning 3d
like I've I've told myself I wanted to learn I was gonna make a video about this actually today
just talking about it because I just released the animation uh but I've wanted to do 3d since 2006
and I always told myself I was too dumb to do it and this year I finally nut it up and I went from
knowing nothing about it to making an animation in 11 months so way to go dude that was cool
and I really love your little uh the little gifts like rotations of like little models you make
oh tom yeah the the thing the animation went up today right uh you went up yesterday actually
okay I haven't seen it yet so I gotta I thought it was pretty impressed though I want to watch it
again because I could only quickly watch it at the time yeah it's not I mean there's room for
improvement but in terms of just like getting it out look pretty smooth I noticed that hips way I
noticed that hips way going on which which channel was it on uh it's on my main channel it's on
it's funny you say that hips way is good because I had a guy uh who I woke up to this guy who looks
like a huge essay comment saying he was quote a professional animator and did a shot by shot
breakdown of how terrible it was well that's kind of a compliment I suppose in its own way it's his
comment was a fuck you I thought you were good at art what is dude what the fuck that it's it's
it's really all right I saw that comment as well it's basically he he copied it from a discord
where he was discussing it among people yeah and he pasted it but he didn't take out like the the
colloquial things he was saying to his friends about how tom in in the third person is terrible
yeah it was it was the worst thing and then I called him on it I called him on it he's like yeah
that's exactly what happened and then he messaged me on twitter's like I'm sorry I'm like yeah fuck
you well okay that's nice but yeah some of the some of the criticisms he had was you know they
they they they they were all right like there was tons of good good ideas in there for improving
sandwich between you're a fucking retard so that was fun but that that my favorite like
professional thing was was a 3d my favorite personal thing this year was definitely uh
rad country watching mad bull with everybody oh i forgot rad country was this year guys remember
that i remember now but yeah it was fucking january jeez Louise yeah i miss those days soon for me
personally i think i mentioned that in the last podcast when i got my health in order like at the
end of um may or so that was that was like the best that's a huge deal major's out there major's
out there grinded random pokemon with her whole team either dead or at low hp so she finally visited
nurse joy and everything's in top shape once again yes i was visited the pokemon center finally
professionally i i don't know like i feel like it all fell into place this year you had like two
videos hit a million views this year yeah it's nice yeah that's insane i i am i i had to i had to
turn off comments on one of the videos because driving insane like i don't want to like um what
would they do it or they tell what were they saying smack about it's like it's like the same
comments every now like every every day i wake up to the same exact comments and i have to reply
with the same exact same thing and like we don't have to like i know i don't have to but like i was
i just i had to i've i've stopped i've stopped uh i get i get a ton of comments on the christian
video to this day and like i but i haven't replied to one in a long time i i do like that comment
that was like uh man this video is great too bad about the autists you know just like that you
have to look at and and experience yeah yeah uh those are my favorites he loves those fucking
odd he's watching a christian video he loves autistic people fuck that someone someone commented
like like a couple days ago and said like i watch this video like every like every two weeks
and i i i almost i almost commented like thanks for the clicks or like thanks for the views dude
thanks for the watch time that's nice that's nice because like i do want because because like when
people legitimately like it i want to yeah i want to like tell them you know i'm thanks i'm glad you
enjoy this but there's just so many there's so many when i see when i see comments like that like
the king of hearts video was out this year and that was also great but whenever i get a mean
comments on anything or rather when i get a really nice comment that i'd like to be like oh thanks
dude or anything like that i i generally suppress the urge because i don't want the people leaving
mean comments to know that i'm reading their comments and only replying to the nice ones i
don't want to give them that yeah no i never i would never reply to like a shitty comment or a
comment criticizing me because it's like yeah yeah we don't we don't we don't need to give them what
they want we don't need to spare those any attention no my favorite thing to do with mean
comments is to reply nicely because they don't know what to do after that that's always fun because
if they respond they're just like uh if if fuck if they do uh they are in fact the fool i usually
reply by making their attitude or make fun of them i don't know like it really depends on the comment
like sometimes i don't reply at all if it's just not worth my time sometimes maybe if i feel
feel like i have something to say i say it but if someone if someone just seriously if someone
just comments in a way that's like they don't like me then i just don't respond because like
right or whatever but if but if it's someone like if it's someone who's like criticizing or
saying something that's like wrong or like making some kind of some kind of like claim that's wrong
and like then i'll reply and be like listen yeah let me set the record straight on this because like
i don't want people reading this comment and and believing it i'm always tempted to reply to those
sorts of things but generally i find myself replying more to i mean if this is rare this is
like the rarest breed but like someone making like a substantive sincere criticism of like any
point or whatever those i will reply to uh sometimes not i want to say quickly uh it's like um if people
like post like super angry or or something like comments like that like one of my favorite things
to play with is just lol that that's all i i don't want to do that because i feel like that gives
them what they want they got your attention no i just like they never reply they never reply to
it though like i haven't had a person reply to lol to lol well fair enough if it works for you then
but godspeed uh i don't always but sometimes i do well um any more questions i think that's about
it i think we've tapped out you have something to say i think i feel like he had i was it was just
about a comment thing um but i don't know the moment feels like it's past you can say it's okay i
want to hear it give i want to hear that shit tell me about the comment oh okay who are you
the the fucking uh i had a comment recently uh on my ape escape part three uh video
saying it was the worst one i ever made and i was the worst video ever i felt terrible yeah i saw
that i wanted to kill him yeah but um has he even seen a g r p j i mean i i love g r p j i honestly
i wish you would make more g r p j yeah me too me me too um anyway uh there was two people who
asked that said that and i was like oh i'm gonna respond because i i just i just really want to
know like why why why is it the worst one and i felt better just asking him so what didn't you
like about it and then he replied with more specifics and i was like okay that actually makes me feel
better knowing it precisely what was wrong yeah because it's no longer like an ephemeral thing of
like you're terrible now it's like okay he's like specific criticisms like these can be changed or
you know i can totally relate uh one of the comments i got on the the video that i disabled
the comments on like it's not necessarily a bad comment it's not the reason i disabled comments
it's just like um and they come to someone like oh well where the fuck did that at enemy go and i'm
like what's the problem with it and they were like oh and that specific point uh uh his head
seems a bit too big and i was like yeah that's a fair point uh you could have just started with that
and they're like i'm sorry about being too direct i was like see that the problem was that you
weren't direct enough right exactly yeah it's just like the commenter atmosphere you know like we
we got to change the commenter culture guys make it work it's it's really just that people think
that they're not going to have uh to respond to a reply about it so they don't feel the need to
make it clear the first time and i just throwing it out there we all love a little bit of shit posting
down again yeah well all right i guess that's it everybody i think we're i think we're we're concluded
so uh let's see let's see what do we got here uh thanks for the questions sent on the twitter
using hashtag ask pcp we record on saturdays around noon east of standard time so watch out for that
shit uh we got recording earlier we're recording earlier now that's true in case you in case you
might be confused mm-hmm we've got uh the the the the the oh yes of course we got the the fan
patreon chat uh if you subscribe to our patreon at patreon.com slash the procrastinators get access
to that where we read generally just more questions we're more likely to see your questions from
indeed indeed that's what the good shit is everybody so uh pledge to the patreon at in any
amount i actually has to be a minimum of one dollar technically i believe and you'll get access to the
patreon uh uh the patreon discord that is and you can talk to us we hang out we all have fun times
and it's good now pledge five dollars of course and you get access to our bonus episodes there are
nine of which out right now last one was inuyasha versus charlie brown and oh wait there was a preview
of it at the beginning of this episode no last episode last episode that's right that's right
so uh that's some good shit you can hear a preview last episode and there's there's more good things
coming and uh we've also got the podcast here available on itunes and google play at least for
now even though we seem to be getting shit for downloads on those so uh i gotta i gotta everybody
asked for and then i checked the google play downloads yesterday it's like three yeah exactly
i don't i don't know what the fuck you people are talking about making me work to the bone
maybe itunes is more i don't know maybe i i was agonized over the itunes things for like a year
it was it was a lot of work and it still isn't it's it's more work than it should be getting them up
and the dumb thing is itunes doesn't track your downloads so i gotta dig in the blue hose to find
out downloads for itunes which is her moronic regrettable i found no the reason i found out is
that itunes like apple has one guy in charge of all of podcasts because they don't because they
don't make any money off of it they don't give a fuck so one guy's in charge of the entire thing
yeah i guess that makes sense okay well now we know that's why capitalism works baby if you
made money then people would care about it capitalism makes me work i gotta do extra
shit now because these motherfuckers we'll have to throw you an extra tuppence or two uh what else
are we a bit i think that did i miss anything oh uh uh red bubble dot com slash people slash
the procrastinators we got shirts and stuff people go buy them they are fun they are good
and they are uh the money supports the show so there you go and enjoy some sweet loot oh it's a
great christmas gift everybody go to red bubble dot com slash people slash the procrastinators
and buy in all your loved ones procrastinators merch you will not regret it put a sticker of
ben saint in your fucking fridge to steal all your food put a sticker of uh you know whatever you
want remember remember guys don't don't procrastinate on the holidays procrastinators the holidays
yeah if you buy the stickers especially with me and tom like with me pointing at something like
please like send me like tweet at me where you apply those stickers i want to see what you're
just pointing at please mention both of us and be sure to buy a stack of them so all the important
things in your life you can have yeah pointing it to get it done do you need to go to the gym
put this mage point to your gym membership get your ass to the gym you know what we should do
we should make another version of that sticker that has like a speech bubble over mage's head
so you can write in like a note so that she can point at the thing and it could be like
they could all have a bad idea they could all have a speech yeah not a bad idea that we could
they could be actually useful notes people write sheet of right add some weird utilitarianism to
the whiteboard exactly oh i like this oh i like this uh all right oh dude what if we had a color
coded set of nine markers each like with the color of our like avatar thing oh there's maybe a lot of
she's a purple i'm not gonna mind mage is a separate pack that's just like 20 different shades of
purple that i want mine to be black not gray i want mine to be black okay just like your uh race
right okay good all right well i guess that's it everybody go buy things well we are brothers
indeed indeed well uh uh you know uh soul brothers not blood brothers yeah that's what i'm saying
right we are in fact soul men uh all right thanks for listening everybody i guess that's
gonna do it thanks for listening to this bullshit meandering ending here and we'll see you uh next
fucking time yeah
i am