Take me to the channel for the PCP. Listen to some voicemails for the Minecraft stream. I really want to have Redcon funded by you. We can be Pro Crastinators.
Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast.
During the Ben Effort Arc, which is long over, that was sure was a time and place. We're past that now.
Remember when this show had effort and every episode started with like an actual edited segment of like a joke?
No, actually. I think Jesse and Davoo did that a couple times and that was it.
That happened pretty often in the olden times.
We set expectations too high.
It's true. We were still young naive fools who thought podcasts were stupid, not realizing that nobody cares about the presentation.
They only care that something is in their ears in another tab while they're doing literally anything.
They're only half paying attention to what's being said in the first place.
Yeah, I mean, that's me. I understand. I too am a consumer pig who just wants more slop in my trough.
Okay, today's episode, we got two guests. We got Kazi.
Hello, I'm a pony character. I'm Yiffy Snout the Pegasus and I'm here to talk about the pony movie.
That sounds like an OC that would do very well.
I'm not hungover at all. Neither has been.
No.
And we got Crack as well.
Good morning. Oh, man. Oh, man, I'm dying.
I'm trying to bring the energy.
Before the episode, you were doing a bit. You were doing a bit where it's like, oh, I'm going to be so energetic,
but you clearly have blown out all the energy you have already.
He's gotten a lot.
No, yeah. I was giving it all I had. I woke up Harganine. She's real upset about it.
Good you. Good, good, good.
I woke up Ethan to take his microphone, so we're on the same level.
I'm glad that it's ruining not only our lives, but the lives of everyone around us.
The collateral damage of the podcast, just wonderful.
We have to release this episode at 10 in the morning so everyone else can live.
The story.
We were recording in the afternoon and I just think that that's bad because then I spend the morning being like,
well, I've got to record in like six hours and then six hours later, I've done nothing.
My day is basically over and then it's time to record and then I got to do audio editing
and then it's 8 p.m. by the time I'm done.
My day is over. It's ruined fruit fly.
No, we got to get up and I got to get my day going in the morning, same time as lifting.
Same time as lifting.
Yeah, that's fair.
That's fair. When we're sitting around at five in the morning and you drop on me that we have to record in five hours
and I didn't know.
That makes me so sad.
Yeah, well, good.
So this is what we're doing now.
Oh god, we didn't.
Okay, on the count of three, let's say sync.
One, two, three, sync.
Sync.
Oh god, I guess this is just going in the episode.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
They love it.
Then it's content.
Everyone is fucked.
It is content.
It's inside baseball.
It's candy.
I got some good content right here.
You ready for this?
Oh yeah.
Lay it on me.
What?
You hear that?
The pot open.
The first morning monster.
Here we go.
Yeah.
This isn't just time to do drinking or spying, snapping.
Well, I got my seltzer here.
So we all watched a fucking movie this week.
Yeah.
We watched a film.
It finally happened.
It's finally here.
The bro analysis community is saved.
The drought of content is over.
It's okay, everypony.
Your TF2 analysis anarchy episodes will continue.
Don't worry.
We're working on them.
Yeah.
Dr. Wolf has content to make content out of.
We're meeting through the rift cafe right now.
We're hanging out.
What are you doing in my analysis channel?
How did you get here?
Wait.
I just remembered the whole fucking commission.
Was it me and Steve?
Kazzy that commissioned you to draw the entire brony analysis TF2 analysis community?
Can we show that image on screen right now?
I'm sure I still have it somewhere.
But yeah, no, give and Steve, they paid me like $80 to just redraw the analysis anarchy
poster.
Don't add anything funny to it, they said.
Just draw it again.
There was no joke except just draw it and we'll pay you to do so.
You were the joke.
Just to make the puppet dance.
You were the punch.
And then we printed it out at like a fucking staples and like on just like computer paper,
brought it to brony gone.
And then I think steel viper like took it and she went up to like all of the, you know,
all the people on the poster and had them sign it.
Someone crossed out who's the guy that did the really bad shit.
Tune Critic Y2K.
Yeah.
Someone like scribbled out.
I drew Tune Critic Y2K and just because like he was on the poster and I was supposed to
redraw it.
So I was like, I'm just going to, I guess he's, he guess he's in it and someone scribbled
it out and I'm like, that's appropriate.
It's, it would be, it would be unfair.
It would be unfair to draw a false equivalence between the rest of them and Tune Critic Y2K.
Yeah.
You know, I think I have a photo of the signed poster and I can get that for us too if you
want.
I just hit my mic really hard.
Maybe I'll edit it out, but if I forget, at least I'll edit it out.
Oh, you know what?
Oh, you know what I did this week?
Speaking of, speaking of hitting your microphone and editing shit out of your recording, I
am going to be, I'm going to be a Tails gets trolled canon.
Yes.
I am the voice, I am the voice of the Dark Lord in the audio books and the Tails gets
trolled audio books now.
And as well, as well as one of the cultists in the scene, in the scene where they, where
they drink blood and get their neutral powers.
It seems appropriate considering you're the voice of the Dark Lord in real life.
Yeah.
It's just when, when they drink the blood and get the Satan powers, the Satan, Satan's
voice basically comes from nowhere and just says like, Hey guys, here's the deal.
You got to use your powers and you got to not get emotional or else I'll kill you.
Okay.
Good luck.
Bye.
And that's my line.
Congratulations.
I can't wait.
I'm so excited.
I'm so excited for that to come out.
Ben, I got to tell you listening to the PCP, like a nightmare.
No, I actually do it sometimes, believe it or not.
No.
But like listening to it is.
When you need to pick me up, you're just like, I need to feel better about myself.
Yeah.
You know?
Well, no, that's not even true because listening to it is really just like a hearing of retelling
of my own life because I see Ben like literally every other day.
So every single like thing that Ben does, every time Ben does anything, like I also was there.
And so listening to the podcast is just me hearing about what I did that week.
Listening to the PCP is like journaling.
Yeah.
You know, this is why, this is, wait years ago, this is why I kind of like stopped listening.
This is why I stopped listening to Digi Brony After Dark to the side channel because I just
lived in Trixie's house and I was like, well, now I don't have to listen to your content
anymore because like it's just a hearing someone talk about things that I already heard you
tell me about.
Yeah.
It's just my life.
Exactly.
That's what this podcast is.
Like actually.
Yeah.
Think of how far things have gone listeners.
I know.
They used to live in the same house and now they want to kill each other.
What a strange tale.
I mean, those two things can happen at the same time.
What a twist.
That was the beginning of the end.
That's not even that uncommon of a thing to happen.
It's not.
When you stop listening to the side channel, that's the beginning of the end.
Oh, absolutely.
For any friendship.
You realize that they're not like a super content creator, God, they're actually just
a human being is boring.
Where's the horse cast, huh?
I want more of that.
The horse cast.
Where's my Blu-ray copy?
Oh, for a second, I thought you meant the pony cast.
No.
Whoa.
That takes me back.
You know, Ben knows this and Gib knows this, but Tom, you don't know this.
That means.
Sounds like most things.
Me and Munchy and Ethan and Steve and Acro.
Like three years ago, we recorded one episode of a podcast where we reviewed the horse
cast, like we recapped the horse cast and like I found that podcast recently because
it was up on YouTube.
I think it's set to private now.
It has like fucking 200 views on it and I realized that like I was listening to the
horse cast when I was like a 15 year old kid.
So what you're saying is we should just release that podcast as this week's episode.
Yes.
Yeah.
I remember watching that and how people like everyone was like so kind of unsettled by
how weird, yeah, cringe and like knew the relationship was between all of us in the
horse cast early days.
Yeah, especially me.
I paid attention to what they thought of what I was doing because I always hated that.
I was like, Oh God.
It's the most embarrassing thing ever.
I don't know how to speak to anybody.
Oh really?
Are you embarrassed by the horse cast?
Well, in like a general like I was like really shy and obviously like bad at speaking to
people.
I still am, but like less so, but like I don't like want to hide it.
It's just funny.
It's just funny how bad I was like doing all of that stuff.
And yet I was on a podcast for like five years.
I mean, like that podcast, like the first one was like your first time like talking
to Jesse.
Yeah.
Period.
Was it not?
Yeah.
And in voice call, I think it was, we were going to do the horse cast, but Digi or Trixie
was a was not able to be there.
So we were in a Skype group.
We just did it.
I had never talked to him before.
I talked to him in text, but yeah, it's so weird because it was extremely awkward.
That stupid little, like I back in the day when I was a fucking child, I like re listened
to the horse casts and like there's imagine doing some such a thing.
I think there was some joke like made in the horse cast.
I don't know who said it might have been Jesse where they were just like, oh, I love to go
re listened to the old horse cast.
And I was thinking like, yes, oh my God, I literally do.
Wonderful.
So funny.
That's terrible.
So there was a horse movie.
Yeah.
It just came out.
How'd you guys like the pony movie?
Five out of 10.
Really?
Let's move on.
Yeah.
Oh man.
No, I thought it was great.
I didn't get that.
I didn't get that much out of it.
I didn't think it was that great.
I didn't hear that much about it.
Yeah.
See, my thing, I really quite enjoyed it.
It was sort of comfort food, if you will.
I can tell it's not like the best thing ever, but it was the best pony movie I've ever
seen because the rest of them, they have they have they have a problem with like six protagonists
plus new movie specific characters and villains.
It's never enough time.
But like with this new thing, it was like, oh yeah.
It's a pony movie built from the ground up to be a movie.
It's got the three acts, it's got the hero's journey.
It's got cute moments.
It's got funny moments.
It's got great music.
I enjoyed myself thoroughly.
It was a very nice time.
I compared it favorably to the, you know, the two part, the premiere episode of Gen 4.
That one is like famously terrible.
It's not that bad.
The second one is really bad.
The second half where they go on the quest and what did I say last night?
I said, I honestly swear that you won't die if you let go.
So dumb.
So it's better than that, which is not a high bar, but it's something.
So I mean, it wasn't a nightmare.
It wasn't a complete disaster, but I'm, you know, we were watching it, Kazi, and we're
just like, oh, they're in like a spooky valley.
Do you think they're going to meet their next friend now?
And then she did.
And we were like, well, okay.
I mean, what's so weird about that?
Like the story is progressing.
I called.
Things happen.
It's like, wow.
Things happen in a fucking movie.
It just wasn't, it just wasn't, I know, but it just wasn't very engaging.
I, by the way, I called, I called the, I didn't know what the plot was, but I called it like,
oh, the unicorns don't have magic.
I bet the Pegas I can't fly either.
I was like, yeah, they can't fly.
I was like, wow, they have wings, but they can't fly because it doesn't make any sense.
It doesn't make any sense.
I'm a genius.
I don't remember what the Pegasus name is that they end up, the two Pegasus.
Zip and zip.
Zip and pip.
Zip, I guess she was just falling with style in that scene.
She's just doing flips.
Believe it or not, I watched the movie twice and I was paying attention to that the second
time.
And yeah, she's kind of just like jumping on rocks.
Okay.
But then she like comes up from the side of the cliff and it's like in a way that you
couldn't do unless you had some momentum to fly.
No, it's fine.
It was a big jump.
But also it's a child's film.
That's just some classic misdirection.
That's a Tony Hawk maneuver.
Okay.
Here's one thing that I don't understand.
When they leave Pegasus Kingdom and zip and pip both come along and I'm like, I thought
we're supposed to hate pip.
Pip is like obnoxious.
Pip is like an annoying Instagram influencer.
I kind of thought she was set up to be someone we don't like.
But then she comes along and it's like, well, she's just here now.
She's just one of our friends.
Friendship is magic, family.
We have to be friends.
Well, I'm like, oh, really?
What do you mean?
They're bringing her?
It's a, it's, it's, it's zip sister.
You know, you can't just, you can't just throw out your family.
She had a moment where she was like, I can't believe you ruined everything.
She could just stay at home.
She can't.
What do you mean?
She was on the run.
The royals are on the run.
Yeah.
Did you watch this film?
It was out of necessity at first.
And then it was like, and she was like grumbling and with what's his face.
It's like, I can't believe they fucked my life up.
And he's like, yeah, it sucks, doesn't it?
The cop, the cop.
Wait, did I just agree with the characters?
The cop pony.
And then it was like, oh, then they just sort of hung out and realized it was fine.
It's cute.
It's a really cute movie.
I like it.
I just, I don't know.
It's like, why is this person that I don't like along for the ride?
The same, I felt the same about the cop.
The Instagram lady and the cop are both, they both shit.
I hate them.
Bruins it.
The main character is a nice story.
The cop is great.
I'm like, really?
These guys, these guys are going to be in the show that you expect me to watch?
No, no, no.
The cop is great because for not even one moment, is the cop ever like a good guy?
No.
He's always petty.
He's never right.
Why is he here?
Go away.
It's great.
You know, we're teaching the kids.
Yeah.
Don't trust the cops.
My little pony, you know, they implicitly said ACAB.
Why did they play?
I think you are supposed to like him by the end.
He's one of the main characters, a cop and a man, by the way.
Why is this guy in our movie?
Get him out of here.
It was really funny.
The beginning of the movie was hilarious to me because we meet the dad, right?
And he seems like a competent, good head on his shoulder.
Nice guy.
Good father.
I'm like, oh my God.
That's shitty facial hair though.
Shitty facial hair.
Well, everybody has their flaws.
I'm like, is this like a respectable male character in My Little Pony?
This really is a new generation.
Dies between cops.
We're back to where we should be.
Oh no.
Okay, I was so sure that he was not actually dead that it was going to be revealed that
he was actually on a long trip like Arnold's parents to the jungle or something.
You just went to a farm.
You know, they never once mentioned that he was dead.
So he could appear in the show.
I just stepped out to get milk for 10 years.
No, no.
See, I think that was genius.
It was genius not because they'll bring him back, but because they're showing that Sunny
has grown up.
She's aged.
She's gotten over it.
She's learned to accept that her father is gone.
You know, you easily make her whole character.
Whatever it was.
Oh, my dad died.
They didn't do that.
She's over it.
No, but that's quite good.
She doesn't cry about it.
It's not a big deal.
It's like, oh yeah.
Sometimes your parents are gone.
You've got to work on things yourself.
Yeah.
No, that's great.
Here's the thing.
And here's the thing.
When I die, I hope that none of you ever get over it.
I hope that you do spend the rest of your life moaning about, like, I miss Ben so much.
Ben, I'll get over it so fast it'll make your head.
Otherwise I'd be really offended from beyond the grave.
It'll make you spin in your grave so fast that you'll dig a fucking tunnel to hell.
That's how you got to do it.
So I just thought that was pretty disrespectful of her to not spend the whole movie being
like, my dad's gone.
He was such a cool guy.
I mean, whatever.
I never assumed that he was like a rare poochie.
If you just don't love your dad that much, you know, it's fine.
It is what it is.
I never assumed he was going to come back because she says, she kind of talks to the
picture frame and that's like a thing you do if they're dead, right?
That's not a thing you do if they're, like, away.
That's what I was thinking.
He's right in the painting.
No, I think if he had just been away for, like, years, it would be you could also just
be like, talk to the painting.
I mean, you know, either way, he's gone, right?
And you're like, I wish you were here today.
Maybe.
They have wiggle room that if they wanted to bring him back, they could.
I definitely think they, I really thought they were going to.
He was going to show up, like, in the final act and be like, oh, hey, that's all the conflict.
You did it.
I said all the clues and then you did it.
You're like a real daughter.
You followed the breadcrumb trail that I left for you.
Oh, it turns out he had entrapped himself in the gems.
It's just like sore.
Why not?
He's just like sore.
Oh, the gem.
Should we talk about the gems?
Should we talk about the actual plot of the movie?
Well, OK.
Spoilers.
I mean, obviously spoilers for the whole fucking movie because why would you.
There is not a single person in our audience that either A hasn't already seen this movie
or B doesn't give a single song.
Why did you watch a podcast about a movie you haven't seen?
Absolutely.
You can't make hours of content about a movie without spoiling it.
You just can't.
Ben, do you remember?
Me and Ben watched this movie together.
I was a little bit tipsy watching the movie.
I just want to be clear.
If I don't remember some things, it's because I was like five or six trulys deep.
You drank an entire pack of trulys.
Almost.
You drank like nine or ten.
But we watched the movie.
The only way you could get through this.
We watched the movie just you and me because I had Netflix and you were at my house.
And we did that.
And then Munchie was like, I also want to watch it and make a party out of it.
And so, you know, we sat down in the living room.
No, no, no.
Wait.
Funny story.
You were like, I have Netflix.
I was like, oh, well, can I watch the pony movie here?
And you were like, yeah, I can watch.
And you were like, let me ask Munchie if he wants to watch with us.
And you asked him and he was like, no, I don't want to watch that movie.
And then you were like, well, I think me and Ben are going to watch it.
And he was like, oh, shit.
Well, in that case, don't watch.
No, I do want to watch it actually.
But we watched it anyway.
I changed my mind.
We watched it anyway.
Well, you watched it twice.
Yeah.
No, well, it was because you were talking about the gems.
Because we all were watching it again in the living room.
And then you showed up towards the end of the movie and I sort of got up and hung out
with you in the kitchen.
And then we heard people shouting from the living room.
And Ben was like, I know exactly what's going on.
They see the third gem in the background.
They all just noticed the third gem.
Because when we were watching it and we both were like, oh my god, there's the freaky looking
lantern with the most sparkly jewel in the entire universe.
Well, there it is.
There's the McGuffin.
And it's frustrating that it's on screen.
And I can tell, OK, there it is.
You're supposed to do that.
You're supposed to screen.
Why is it there?
At what point?
Do you mean right at the beginning?
At the end.
No, no, no.
At the spoilers.
What she's looking at.
What you said.
After she comes back from the quest and the quest has failed.
I mean, she finds it right after that, though, doesn't she?
Yeah, but there's a minute.
In a moment.
Yeah.
OK.
She she goes home and she's just like fucking around with her stuff.
And it just like is there in the like lamp.
That's for some reason.
The jewel is fine.
I'm not saying it's a problem with the movie.
I'm not cinemas in stinging it or anything.
It sounds like you are, though.
No, I mean, what's the complaint like?
Yeah.
Of course.
They want you to see it at that moment.
You're supposed to realize.
Not only does it make sense compositionally in a metatextual sense.
It makes sense that Sunny having this object since her childhood is like not looking at
it as a MacGuffin.
OK.
Just as like an object that's been part of her life.
You're not going to like make that connection, especially since up to that point, there
wasn't even an implication that there was a third gem.
That was like the revelation of that scene.
OK.
But obviously there was going to be a third gem.
Yes.
Of course, obviously, like from our perspective.
And that's why they show it, so you can bring that home.
But you didn't see, do you see the gem earlier, like in the beginning of the movie?
Yes.
Do you kind of see it?
Yeah, he's building that little thing.
I don't know if I see the gem, and I can't remember.
David, explain where he got it.
I don't think so.
Well, he's an explorer, architect, archeologist.
I want to find out why nobody likes each other.
He's an earth pony.
And they're in their earth pony town, just like the other places just had the gems because
they're birth writers.
Because they have them.
Yeah.
I mean, I was looking for an explanation on the second watch.
I didn't get one.
A distant descendant of Star Swirl of Beard.
That's why his beard was so shitty.
It's just so many generations removed.
It's just the magic was gone.
His horn nearly gone.
His beard terrible.
What I'm saying is not even a complaint.
I'm honestly complaining about like, oh shit, the movie got one over on me.
The movie got me to understand the stakes, and then it showed me on the corner of the
screen, the object of the jeopardy.
And I'm sitting in the theater.
I'm pointing.
I go, oh my god, there.
There it is.
It's like Dora.
It's like watching Dora.
Yeah.
Ben's plan.
Ben's clues.
Yes.
Yeah.
Guys, I'm going to be real with you.
I've seen this movie twice, and I still don't know what the fuck happened.
What?
There's so much going on.
What do you mean?
You don't understand.
There's so much going on at any moment.
I'm too busy.
I'm too busy paying attention to the spike.
It's so dense.
Every shot has so many moving parts.
Well, there's a pony.
And she wants to be friends with people.
No, I'm joking.
I know.
She doesn't want to be friends with people.
Why do you even say that?
She wants to be friends with magical people.
I just, towards the end, you just kind of get like mind fucked.
And then like, the red cop.
Yes, this movie mind fucks you towards the end.
Like the red cop gets in his big fucking Avangelion.
And I'm just like, I don't know what the fuck's going on anymore.
Like, I no longer know what the plot of this movie is because he got in the big robot.
Everything about Sprout sucked.
I'm saying that.
No.
I'm proud of Sprout.
It's like the stupid, funny idiot.
Sprout's angry mob song is the highlight of the movie.
Oh, it's a bear.
Absolute bear.
No, I hate it.
I hate it.
It is.
I hate Sprout so much.
I agree.
Yes.
That was pretty genuine.
Angry, angry.
Genuinely, the funniest part of the whole movie, probably the best part is the part
because it's stupid on purpose.
And I'm like, yeah, yeah, you know what movie?
You are stupid.
I agree.
But you're doing it on purpose now.
I'm with it.
He did the White Stripes Seven Nation Army music.
Yeah.
Oh man, that was so cool.
When, yeah, when that song came on and it's sort of like a rock medley, I was like, are
all the songs like, like references to other pop, because the Netflix description of the
movie is like ponies go on an adventure set to like a, like a pop soundtrack.
And I'm like, are they, are all the songs like, like adaptations of pop?
Oh.
Yeah.
Everything's like a, like a loose ripoff.
Are they really?
That's really tough to know these things.
And that song I could tell that it was like a medley.
I don't mind.
I'm just wondering, because if, if all the other songs were derived from pop hits, like,
I do think there was originally going to be like, just like licensed music and Hasbro
is like, we're not paying for that shit.
No, I don't, I don't think so.
I'm sure this was always the plan.
Probably.
I think I have an essence.
I just remember the Lady Gaga side of it.
10 out of 10.
I was surprised just because, just because, you know, the old show was, you know, it had
its, its original like, like songs.
And then, you know, to hear these like, I don't, I don't, I think I don't like it that
it's like real world pop songs are what we set the movie to.
It's like, oh, okay.
No, I think it's good because they're sort of doing this in the style of a musical, right?
Like every time they do a song, it's, it's non-diagetic.
A musical review.
Yeah.
And the ponies are always doing like the, the musical actor face where they're smiling,
they're extremely big during the song.
It's, it's very much like seeing a musical on a stage.
And in that kind of setting, this is the kind of music they would have, which would be like
sort of a, a pop amalgamation.
True, I suppose.
I liked it a lot because, I mean, it sounds better than just a generic, any given pop
song because of the, the lyrics were like, true.
I don't usually pay attention to lyrics and songs, but I really liked, I don't know,
something about the, the arrangement of the words in the music was good.
And I liked that.
I don't know how to describe it, but I don't know.
How do you just, how do you say lyrics good in a specific way like that?
You just say lyrics good.
I appreciated the, the syllables, the syllables were replaced excellently.
The phonetics had a flow to them.
Masterful lyricism, poetry, it was poetry in motion.
It was poetry in audio.
Yeah, like when they said, here's a corn, it's on the cob.
Here's a bag.
Like that kind of, like when they said that.
I felt like the rub bit was, was lame, but the corn on the cob was perfect.
I don't remember.
There were some parts in like the Izzy song where they're trying to like learn to be
unicorns where there was like some awkward rhymes.
But like, yeah.
No, no, the rap is good.
It was actually good rap.
This, this movie actually gets some points for not making a cringe rap section.
Like it actually worked.
I kind of like it a little bit.
It was like only, it was only like 50% cringe instead of 110% cringe.
Like, oh, I was moving.
No, no, you're right, Tom.
It was bang.
The last movie I watched was Space Jam, a new legacy.
And they had like a rap in that that was actually like physically destructive.
Like I'm pretty sure I aged 10 years watching.
You took psychic damage.
Yeah.
Am I, am I crazy?
Has LeBron like ever rapped?
Does he, does he do any, any music?
He didn't rap in it.
It was like Elmer Fudd who rapped it.
I don't mean in the movie.
I mean, in general, has he ever done like, like, like a, like a rap album or something
like Pull Day?
Yeah.
He's been trying to get into it for a few years.
I thought so.
So I like, like, it wouldn't surprise me too much if there was some of that in the
movie, but if it's bad, it's like, well, that's not good.
It was probably the most painful movie going experience I've ever had in my life was that
three minutes.
I don't remember what song it was.
I don't even remember what is happening, but there's one song that has like a little,
there's a little aside where just there, they're singing about the adventure that they're
on and the cop pony just like, there's like, if we fail, we'll go to jail.
And I'm like, prison.
They'll go to prison.
He doesn't even rhyme it.
He says if we fail, we're going to prison.
Ben laughed so hard with that part.
Because it's just like, you're going to, you're the one who's going to put us there.
He loves fucking jail.
The cop.
What are you talking about?
So damn much.
This entire movie.
He's so fucking into it.
No, it's good.
It's good because otherwise we don't want the kids to forget for a moment that this guy
is terrible.
He's a cop.
He loves, he loves jail.
No.
That's not even true.
Why is he in on my show?
Get out.
I didn't get the sense that he was like authoritarian with his police chief stuff.
That's the whole movie.
He's just supposed to be mildly annoying.
But like, he's really a good guy.
He's supposed to be like, oh, I'm your friend.
But like, I can't.
That's his whole shtick.
And like, the whole, like the whole rub in the beginning is that, is like, hey, Sonny,
look, I'm your friend, but like, please stop doing illegal things.
It puts me in an awkward position, but he's not like fucking immediately thrown the book
at her.
Yeah, that's the other guy.
Okay, but the whole reason he's out on the adventure is because like, well, I got to
go and put her in jail because she consorted with some foreigners and that's not cool.
Well, it ends with the kids.
Yeah, because there's like hundreds of years of indoctrination in the culture.
This is annoying to me.
Like, his whole thing is like, I got to go find, I got to go arrest her.
I guess she might also be in danger, so I guess I'm going to save her from danger.
But like, the point of what I'm doing is I got to go find her and burn her to jail.
Until they get to the campfire and then he turns around.
Yes, but then they, well, but then they, is that, I don't remember a moment where he's
like, you know what?
I changed my mind.
Actually, there was a big moment where he literally, is he brings out the letter that
that Sonny and her dad made in the beginning of the movie.
And she's like, this is why I came in the first place.
Cause I was told I had friends here.
And like in that moment, he's like, oh, you know what?
I want to do my part.
I'm going to help.
This is something, this is actually something that could bring us together and is a good
thing.
And that was a good moment.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
His police thing was only at the Pegasus area.
You know what?
Cause they were all in the other room.
Getting another truly at that moment.
He missed that.
Yeah, genuinely.
You know why I don't remember that moment?
The emotional crux of the film.
He just was powerful.
Okay.
I do remember that moment, but what I remember is that I foolishly forgot about the letter.
I like, it seems obvious.
Oh, that was obvious.
Oh my God, dude.
Come on.
Yeah, but I forgot about the letter.
So when she pulled out the letter, I'm like, oh, I remember that.
I remember they set that up in the movie.
Oh my God.
The movie got me is like, I forgot about that too.
And it's so obvious.
Cause I was like, why is he even here in the first place?
And then like, it's so, it's like so blatantly obvious.
I'm like, oh God, I'm an idiot.
Oh, no.
He did set it up.
It does make sense.
The kids movie bamboozled me.
Okay.
Yeah.
I was sitting there waiting for her to pull the letter out.
And then she did.
And Ben was like, oh my God.
And I was like, man, are you kidding me?
Like this movie, this is a masterpiece.
This is an absolute masterpiece.
The Citizen Kane.
Did Orson Welles write this movie?
Did Alfred Hitchcock set up the Jeopardy?
I'm on the edge of my seat.
Right, but the cop is bad.
Yeah, no, like towards the end, I was like, well, you know, he turns around and I'm like,
I'm supposed to enjoy this character, but he's not going to stop being a cop.
I know that's not going to happen.
So I can't enjoy him.
The movie, I think I did enjoy the movie more as it went on.
Izzy was cute.
I like Izzy, frankly.
I think she's pretty adorable.
Izzy's great.
Sure.
Yeah.
Izzy gang.
Izzy gang is great.
Izzy's good.
Sonny's good.
I like Sonny too.
Sonny had the best like fuck your shit face throughout the entire movie.
Like every time something blatantly stupid happens, she's just like Jesus fucking Christ.
I'm sad with these fucking smooth brains.
What am I going to do?
Sonny's my favorite for sure.
Sonny is just right 100% of the time, just like me.
And just trying to win everybody over, wake them up.
It's great.
It's wonderful.
Wow.
What an interesting character.
Just being right the whole time.
I'm trying to like visualize the characters, but I can't help but envision the Gary's Mod
pony models as the characters.
I can't think of what they actually look like.
I'm seeing Gary's Mod right now.
Oh no.
Oh, it's terrifying.
The designs are pretty good.
Yeah.
Okay.
I don't like.
At the end of the day.
Hair cut.
I don't really like.
The zip hair cut is.
The zip hair cut.
The eyebrows.
The eyebrows are not great.
Everything else is probably as good as they could have done.
In 3D.
I don't know.
I like the eyebrows.
What's wrong with them?
You don't like them because.
It's not that any of the.
Toneys look.
I don't like candy sometimes.
Particularly bad.
I just, I still don't like the 3D.
It just looks like any other like Dreamworks.
It is much more generic.
Production.
It just has that generic 3D look.
And like it.
Yeah.
I guess they did it well.
It looks good, but like I don't like it.
I don't know.
I don't think that's a nuanced opinion.
I think you just haven't seen a lot of 3D.
The, it's.
As someone who has seen a lot of 3D.
It's pretty true.
It just looks like a lot.
They have the same eyes.
They have the big.
Well.
The same Disney eyes.
There's.
I wouldn't go that far.
There is some subtle differentiation in the stylization of this movie.
It just doesn't go nearly as far as like the material that came before it.
You know?
Because even Sunny's action figures of the main six look much more visually distinct.
Well.
Than the characters themselves.
I liked how those looked.
I liked that they were clearly like carved wooden figures.
Yeah.
Who looked like.
I mean.
I like that Twilight's dead in this movie.
Every time.
Okay.
I was wondering are like those are.
Those are like real like historical figure.
Correct.
It's very.
The main thing.
The main thing that did in fact live.
I don't know that they are historical figures.
I think it's unclear.
Yeah.
They're in the canon of like her dad's storytelling.
Or are they fictional characters?
No.
And in the ruins of the Pegasus city, they have like Twilight's symbol.
I guess.
But like I feel like you.
Okay.
That still doesn't necessarily confirm.
Yeah.
That could go.
I guess it could.
But I felt like the implication was very much that this all happened.
I thought so too.
I guess the whole story is that like, oh, we all used to live together because of this
story of Twilight and everybody.
Yeah.
No.
It's very funny.
My understanding was back in the day.
I agree.
I think the implication.
I think the implication is that like the, that is, it's just canon that like all the
events of Gen 4 happened at some point in the past.
But like 10,000 years ago, it's like Dark Souls 2 is like there's a whole kingdom built
on top of the old kingdom and all the names are different.
And as everyone's died, you know, a hundred times over, it's been so long, completely
legendary.
Yeah.
But you see, you see, yeah, there's a bunch of things that have Twilight's cutie mark
on it.
It has like a necklace with it on it.
You see it in the stained glass window.
You also see Rarity's cutie mark, like Rarity's jewel, cutie mark shows up in the, in the
same window.
Okay.
But let's think about this.
Why would Rarity's cutie mark be in the window?
Is it more likely that?
Because she's one of the, because she's like a fucking, a mortal from like a brief moment
in time versus someone like Twilight who would have lived a long time.
And we know the window's not that old, right?
Because this is in a station where they used to all meet up, used to all come up and shit,
but like it's, you know, it's fairly recent.
It's not ancient.
Yeah.
When they talk about it, it sounds like, it sounds like, oh yeah, the pony races used
to get along like, like 20 years ago.
Yeah.
It's like within, within a hundred or 200 years, it's not thousands of years.
It's supposed to be a couple hundred years ago, right?
That's how long it's been.
I don't remember.
I don't think that.
They don't say in the movie, but I thought like bleeding up trillion years ago, it was
supposed to be only a couple hundred years ago, which really begs the question to me,
why even bother tying these two together in the first place?
It seems like it would have been much easier if this was just a hard break and a new canon.
Well, that's what I'm saying.
I don't think they're really that tied together.
It's more like these are the figures that her dad carved.
He pulls in the symbology, you know, from, from the real world, but that doesn't mean
that those characters were real.
I don't know, Tom.
I really like, I like the idea that, you know, Twilight brought friendship to the land and
then somewhere along the line, she fucked up and it all got ruined and she fucking died.
And that's kind of like clearly.
She would still be alive if she hadn't fucked up and ruined.
Yeah.
And that's why she's dead.
A minor, like a much less extreme version of like when people complained about like
Star Wars and stuff.
It's like, oh, well, by continuing it and showing how everything immediately went back
to shit, it kind of like rubs the previous series of like it's victory, I guess, you
know, and this kind of does the same thing, but to a much lesser degree and to a degree
that bothers me far less as well.
It doesn't, it doesn't, it doesn't impune the old story too much to be like, well, yeah,
that was great.
You know, eventually, you know, hundreds of thousands of years later, eventually things
did go back to shit.
I don't think it was that long.
That was the whole thing.
I seem to call an artist on Twitter drawing something about this particular conundrum,
which was very effective.
I think his name is Ben St.
What are you talking about?
What did I do?
I don't even remember.
The tweet, the Trump tweet with Twilight, with Phantom Horn going to the Trump rally.
To the rally.
Yeah.
Well, that was in response to this whole thing.
Of how we were dunking on the fact that Twilight fucked up, which was hilarious.
And then a bunch of people took it literally.
How do you not remember this?
Are you that fucking on over right now?
I remember drawing that image, but I don't, I feel like you're interpreting like a weird
intent behind it.
That was literally the point.
We were having a discussion about it on Twitter when you drew it.
What?
Where?
How long ago was this?
This is like a year ago.
No, like a year ago.
Six months ago.
Because this was, this was after the, the riot, the Capitol riot, and I was like, yeah, Phantom
would have been at that.
No, that is not what this was about at all.
This was about when we were talking about how in this, like we were talking about how
the, when the summary of the movie came out and it was like, oh, Twilight fucked up.
And you drew that fucking drawing because.
What, what drawing?
The drawing of Phantom Horn at the, at the, at the Twilight rally.
How do you not remember this?
Like you got dragged on Twitter for it later because like a bunch of people started dogpiling
before it.
It's not, it's not a, wait, it's not a Twilight route.
No, it is.
Yeah it is.
Okay.
I think you're reading it because I don't, it didn't have anything to do with the movie.
We had a discussion about it on Twitter.
It didn't have anything to do with the movie.
Oh my God.
Okay, you're wrong.
It was just a political thing happened and I was like, yeah, Phantom is, is kind of
like that or he was kind of like that.
I'm really wrong.
I'm totally wrong.
What do you mean, what do you mean, no?
I'm telling you what my ethoreal intent was.
Because you didn't even remember you drew it five minutes ago.
No, I don't think so.
No, I don't think that's what you meant.
Okay.
We had a discussion on Twitter about this, but okay, sure.
All right.
I don't, I never have a discussion on Twitter.
I know.
Oh my God.
I don't do that.
When I say discussion, I mean like two tweets back and forth because that's how long a discussion
on Twitter should last.
I like to think that Twilight was mid-flight and then she fucked something up and the power
of friendship was gone, so she lost her flight powers in the fall because she was mid-flight
and the fall was so deadly that it fucking broke her, her, her alicorn immortality and
she died anyway.
And that's why she's not here anymore.
Like her bones got, all her bones got broken and the magic was not enough.
Her immortality was not enough to save her.
Her bones are too fucking broken.
Damn.
Yeah.
The, the window, I thought for a second that the window showed Twilight, but no, I think
it's just a bunch of other purple, purple ponies, just like creating the crystals.
Yeah, I mean, I think they're keeping it vague because they probably don't even know what
they're going to do with it long-term anyways, if anything.
Why are, okay, question.
Why are there three crystals that, if taken apart from each other, make ponies not have
magic anymore?
Well, that's, I think.
Because this is a child's movie.
Okay.
Well, yeah.
That's literally it.
Our job is to go over all of the fine-tune comb.
Why did the ponies make these three things?
Why did the ponies make these three crystals that, if separated, would render them all
useless?
Because it's a child's movie, Ben.
Hmm.
That's not exactly.
Well, well, hold on.
So, bringing the crystals.
The crystals are always done.
Yeah.
The original show is just like, oh.
The elements of.
The elements of harmony give you superpowers if you have them.
Yeah.
These are like, these don't give you anything.
They just, if you separate them, your entire species loses their whole fucking thing and
you have become like a bunch of.
Well, by the end of the movie.
I don't know whether it means that.
I think what, I mean, they're obviously just MacGuffins, but the reason that you put them
together and nothing happens, but then when you show them that you're truly committed to
being friends with everyone, then they wake up and they do something.
I feel like friendship, like, is more important than the crystals.
I don't think, like, if you put the crystals, you just took them.
People wouldn't stop being friends suddenly.
I think the friendship eroded and that's why the crystals are separate, you know, lost
their magic.
Yeah.
They're vague enough with like the lore that they can flesh all that out later if they
want to.
They just don't think they need to even bother because, like, they've established their cast.
They can go off and have their little half hour adventures going forward.
That's always been the best part of the last show.
I'm sure it'll be the best part of this show is just the character interaction.
Speaking of having your little adventures going forward, what's the deal with Sonny?
What is Sonny now?
She's an alchor.
Oh, yeah.
Obviously.
Is she permanent?
Is she permanently magical?
They didn't even have the decency to wait three seasons.
Greedy bastards.
When that happens, does she permanently just have glowing wings and a horn now?
I would assume.
Yes.
That only happens when you have toys with it.
So like they have.
Okay.
That's what I was saying.
When that happened, I looked at her and I was like, I know exactly what the toys going
to look like and what plastic they're going to make the wings and horn out of like when
she appeared.
They're going to use that clear plastic with the sparkles in it.
That's what they're going to do.
Sure.
Toys.
Toys is toys.
But that's fine.
That's fine.
I'll give you a toy.
Give me a toy.
I feel like they made the design like that in the movie sort of look temporary.
Like it's glowing and it's magic and it's not really actually a physical thing.
It looks like it's going to fade away.
I was kind of hoping they would flick her back out and this would be like, oh, this is like
your fucking elements of harmony, MacGuffin mode.
Yeah.
Maybe they needed to do that to sell a toy or whatever they say.
Just don't show it disappearing.
You can't do that.
We need people to want that.
Yeah.
People need to want to buy that.
They need to have the super form of Sunny.
It seems like, yeah, this is like a thing that's like when there's a problem and you
harness the magic of friendship to defeat an enemy.
We got a call for friendship.
This is her super form that she gets to do the, it's like summoning the Megazord.
Sunny went super sane.
Yes.
When you get the crystals together and you go friendship-powered, you get the gun and
you can shoot people and kill them.
It's like, okay, unicorns get their magic back.
Pegasi can fly again.
Earth ponies, they're like, hey, I found a gun.
Blam, blam, blam.
And that's what you get.
I mean, they honestly seem to be like inventors, they can make machines.
I was hoping that one of the things they would do is like give earth ponies something to
fucking do.
They don't get anything.
They had this whole thing going throughout the entire movie of Hitch having some strange
connection to nature.
All the animals just loved him.
I also didn't notice this.
Are they trying to set up something with earth pony magic?
They also had little hints of unicorn magic coming back because Izzy kept being able to
see people's ores and shit.
I thought those were all just breadcrumbs leading up to all of them getting their own
kind of magic, but earth ponies just get nothing, as usually.
Well, we don't know that because the movie ends, but they do show a small thing where
a bunch of ponies are one of each fillies that are like, we're playing and we're running.
Don't use magic now, we're going to race.
And then the earth ponies' hoof prints leave behind some sort of weird magic something
or other that sort of makes the grass glow when I assume that's like, oh, growing power.
That looked like shit.
That effect looked so bad.
It's not the last thing that happens in the movie.
It is the last grass.
Yes.
Yeah, no, me and Ben sat there and we were like, why does it look like shit?
We were just both struck by how bad it looked visually.
Okay, Izzy, she keeps bringing up, she talks about people's sparkles.
She says, my sparkle is bright or something, and she says, oh, your sparkle is tur- that's
just a weird Izzy or a reader thing.
I thought that was leading to something, but I think it was leading to literally nothing.
No, I think it was just trying to intro that the unicorns are like kind of hippy, superstitious,
you know.
I guess.
It makes sense.
They lay it on pretty thick once they get there.
They didn't need any lead up to it.
And like, I guess my question, why is Izzy the only one who's not like emotionally destitute?
Like I get, like she's so far beyond broken that she's just, she's looped back around.
That's what she's doing.
I mean, she's like Pinkie Pie on the farm.
That's what it's like.
Yeah, yeah.
It's the same.
I guess.
And she is the Pinkie Pie clone.
But that never really made much sense to you there.
We have a clone for all the main six basically, except for Fluttershy, I think.
Good.
I mean.
Well, I guess here is Fluttershy.
There's like a parallel to each person, to each pony.
Yeah, it's not exactly the same, but I guess it's good.
The dynamics aren't identical, which I think is a very similar archetype.
Like Pip isn't really a rarity.
She is vain, but I guess it's sort of a little different.
She's modern vain instead of classically vain.
Yeah, she's on her phone.
An H phone.
She's a zoomer.
She's got a P phone.
Do you remember when it like, like it cuts back to like Maritai Bay and then when we go
back to like the Pegasus City, it just like shows an ad for perfume on the billboard.
And then that's it.
And then it just goes to something completely unrelated.
And I'm like, what was, are they just, are they just going to actually sell that perfume
in real life?
Like they just show an ad.
That's just to be like, oh, this is a real, this character is a real advertising consumerist
icon.
And this is what Pegasus City is like.
I guess it was just framed here.
It's all about those billboards.
Pegasus City says a lot about our society because the Pegasus I live, they clear, they
clearly live under late capitalism and also like, and the magic is dead.
Magic is gone in this, in this consumer society that they're relatable.
And I just think that that is like me too, you know, me as well.
We've all been there.
I mean, yeah, no, the earth ponies are too.
They have their, they have their stupid like Silicon Valley tech demo.
They do.
Yeah.
They have Steve Jobs.
What's, yeah.
What's her name is like, she's like, she's like Steve Jobs, like Elon Musk or Earth Pony.
Yes.
There's, there's something, look at, I made a, I made a stupid, I made a stupid hyperloop
that will help you like run away from unicorns faster or something.
There's something kind of related to that, that I wanted to talk about.
And I want to know if any of you guys noticed this, which is that throughout this movie,
like if there's ever, there's a lot of like character talking to crowd scenes.
And whenever that happens, the, the opinion of the crowd will just immediately shift based
on who is talking as in like one character will make their point and the entire crowd
will be swayed.
And then another character will say a thing and once again, the entire crowd will like
change their mind immediately and then just go back and forth and it happens every time
reactions though, like in most, in most all ages media, the crowds are pretty easily swayed,
just like real life.
Correct.
I just thought that that was funny and interesting.
Yeah.
It's, it's, it's, I mean, it's really awkward, the, like the, the, the beginning when, uh,
when Sunny like, I guess she's doing like a protest thing at like the, the, the, the,
the tech demo demonstration.
And it's like, they, it's like.
It was very strange to say, hey, don't do it before I have this plan this time, dad,
I'm going to be a smart, uh, pony and then she's like, walks up on stage and just like,
hey, stop her to do it, hitch, like, no, she's going to do it.
And he's like, Hey, don't do that thing that you always do.
And she's like, I won't, but then she does it.
But, uh, I think she just walks on stage and every year because he's like, that was
what he said.
He was like, Hey, every year I stopped you from doing this.
So like, just don't even bother this time.
But this is not even that disruptive.
She's not even that disruptive.
Like the, the, the demonstration just goes ahead with her in, in the, the boots or whatever.
Yeah.
And it's like, it's so, it's so, it's so, I find it weird that those wings and boots
didn't come back in any way.
Well the, the, the balloon, the, the pony, uh, that like get blown away out the window
and balloons keep showing up.
Like, yeah, that's, that's, that's a running gag, gag thing.
But like, um, you know, they got the slime ball throwing things.
That's just, I mean, that does come, yeah, that comes back in, but the, the, the, the
like anti-pegasus grab me boots don't do anything.
And the like metal wings, which I'm not even sure what they're supposed to do.
Well, I mean, they can't even fly up until the end of the movie.
So they would have been ineffective anyway, as I suppose, I guess.
Yeah.
I just felt like, I mean, I felt like those wings were like an opportunity to
like get the fuck out of there.
Oh, we got to run away.
Yeah.
But I mean, although these fucking wings, it's supposed to be the future
technology coming out of care logic.
So that stuff is not like widely available yet.
Although the, the little anti-brain read hats apparently somehow got manufactured.
Well, it took over manufacturing.
Oh, I really liked, um, the fucking in that scene where they're like, Oh God,
we got to stop the computer presses the one button repeatedly.
Yes, I like that.
They had, um, they had a, it was just like in the old, in gen four, um, daring.
What's, what's the woman who writes the daring do novels?
A.K.
Yerling.
Oh boy.
Yes.
Wow.
A.K.
Yerling.
Yeah.
She, she has the, the keyboard, but her keyboard is just like two big buttons.
They have the, they have the same, like just two big buttons as their keyboard.
I mean, what else are they going to do?
You have to click it like 14 times for K.
They do it in Morse code.
It's Morse code, basically.
It's like dashes and dots.
They're running language is just Morse code.
I mean, we, it's only scribbles, so we never see actual real writing, I guess.
But we do, so you do see real writing in, in the, in the movie, though.
We do.
So, but they didn't, they weren't typing anything.
They have smart voice dictation.
They can just be like, Hey, Siri, I just turned on all your phones.
Yeah.
Wait, why, why do they have a smartphone that looks like that?
When they have hooves that press the entire screen at once.
Yeah.
Right.
Well, I mean, their hooves do some magical things throughout the whole movie.
They're in the future.
I guess I could use their nose.
There's no longer like distinct actions that you have to press on the phone.
You just press the screen to interact.
Just press screen, interact.
Ooh, get my interactions.
Whoo.
Yeah, it's just, it's just, you could go live or you could buy
like a new fucking crystals for your, just press the screen.
A cow clicker.
I like how they like, they put enough design sense to like have like a little
like a slot on the back of all the screens, like for like hooves.
It's like a reverse pop socket kind of thing.
Yeah.
Well, what is a slot on the back of all the screens?
Yeah, there's a slight event where all the phones and tablets have a
little slot on the back that your hoof goes into so it doesn't fall off.
And I'm just like, it's funny that they do that for like that one object,
but then like the rest of the objects functionality completely falls apart.
Well, yeah, because if you rewatch the beginning, you know,
Sonny is on her roller blades, right?
Oh, right.
The roller blade just attaches to the back of the truck, that trolley car or whatever.
And she's just touching a wheel to it.
And she's somehow being pulled.
It was, it was, I think it was so drawing because that was like dead center
in the frame and it's just like, you can't miss this little like, yep.
We're not going to explain how this works.
Don't worry about it.
No, I prefer that.
I like when objects just stick to the ponies who?
Yeah, I think it's hilarious.
I was like, when, when Izzy puts on her glasses and she like flips the glasses
on the glass like the edge of the glasses, she's holding like slides up her
hoof as it goes on to her head.
And I'm just like, I don't know how that works.
But yeah, you know, it's awesome.
Friendship is magic.
I love it. Yeah.
And that's why I can hitch to this.
Yeah, yeah, you know, was it a truck or something?
The magic of friendship keeps the magic of friendship and let me hitch a ride.
Sure. Why not?
This might be a this might be a CinemaSins ding moment.
And it would be if it didn't go on for so long and bother me so much
because like just because it went on for like 15 minutes straight,
which is the scene towards the beginning of the movie where Izzy shows up
and all of the all of the earth ponies are running away, screaming
and they do the joke that's like Izzy is clearly just standing there,
going like hello and like everyone which basically like their their senses go.
They can no longer see or hear or think.
Yeah. Thoughts like it's like if you were using your eyes slash ears,
you would see what's in front of you, which is just someone going hello.
And they run away screaming.
And if they did that joke one time, I get it.
Like I get that joke is like a common trope.
Yeah, but it goes on for actually 15 minutes happening.
And so I was like that scene was like the whole start of the movie.
And yeah, it got a little it got a little obnoxious.
But like you're supposed to be you're supposed to be a little kid in the theater.
And you're supposed to see that and be like, wow,
all these ponies sure are foolish for being racist.
If it were me, I would just be normal.
I would say I would say I would say I would say I would simply accept the foreigner.
I would simply accept the harmless foreigner into my side, but whatever, you know,
do we think that the racism allegory works in this movie?
I mean, my answer is I don't know.
I guess like it's like probably probably I'm going to say I could tell
I could tell what they were going for deep into the into the G four thing,
as we all were as someone who is deeply racist myself.
I guess I did not see myself reflected in the in the politics of this movie.
It's just like a lot of the like questions
like the fan theorizing or just like speculation, like half for the lulls was
just like, like, why why are all these people equal when earth ponies are clearly
like at a disadvantage, you know, like that was kind of like the question
you'd ask watching G four, like everyone's just friends.
But like, you know, like, wouldn't there be some like tension of like, man,
you can do magic and I just dig in the dirt and like just ask as a joke, you know.
But like it was the point of the show was like they kind of transcended those kind of things.
And so like it almost feels like going back and being like, hey,
everyone's divided into it.
It feels like the more obvious take with with this kind of setting.
So like it felt almost like a step backwards, I guess.
But the reason the whole point is like we're getting back to that point already.
Like that's the whole point of this movie is to get us back to status quo.
So like I was kind of not invested in any of that because like all this world
building is like going to be irrelevant by the end of the movie anyways.
I mean, I guess the show then will be about them like learning to live together
and get along as now that they've they've been separated for.
Will they?
I'm not sure if I guess I wonder if she's going to go back to status quo.
I don't know if we know this.
I would assume so.
I mean, this this movie is like this is like the setup.
This is like the pilot for the new show.
Is the show going to look like that?
I don't think it'll look good.
Well, it's not going to be as high effort.
But is it going to be the same aesthetic?
In the same way?
I believe so.
Yeah, I don't I don't know if it's been 100 percent confirmed,
but I felt like it's a fair assumption thing with the with with the stuff
with everybody screaming was actually pretty good.
I didn't feel like anything was like bad with the I felt like it went on.
I mean, maybe I was like the screaming the screaming was happening.
But like the stuff.
I was getting a little annoyed.
I was getting the stuff was like, you know,
it's first Izzy is there and then Sonny sees Izzy.
She realizes that Izzy is not dangerous
when other people still continue to not realize that then people have to go after them.
She protects her and then she gets captured.
Izzy gets captured and then she decides to free her,
thus becoming a criminal.
All these different things happen.
Meanwhile, everyone's doing the screaming thing.
So I guess it does go on for a while.
But like the stuff that's happening, I feel like the pacing was quite good.
No, I agree. I think it was and and you know,
you imagine this is a society where all these earth ponies have spent
their entire lives being indoctrinated into the fear of these these terrible
creatures that can fry your brain with with, you know, nary a thought with.
Oh, yeah. Of course, they're scared.
You know, that's the idea.
They're supposed to be senseless.
And they sort of they tie that in again, right?
With the angry mob song where it's like, don't use your brain.
Just follow me brainlessly.
Right. If you use your brain, the unicorn can fry it.
Yeah.
Leave your brain at home so they can't get it.
It's the only way.
Yeah, I try to go a little bit.
I know that's what they were going for.
I think it was good. Yeah.
Also, I wanted to mention the reason in in Gen four
that that question of like who's actually why they friends is was funny
because of the fact that there were certain animals that they had
as livestock, but could also talk to cows.
Yeah.
But then other animals that they could talk to were not livestock.
And what do they all think about that?
What are they?
And then some livestock they can't talk to is like, OK.
OK. It's funny.
It's it was funny in the movie.
All right. I guess there was a thing where like Hitch is like has animal empathy
skills and like I just totally missed it and I didn't I didn't even notice.
No, I thought that was quite clever.
He just they kept bringing that back because he's got like the two birds
in the crab at the beginning.
Yeah, just little critters inexplicably love them.
That's all. Yeah.
And he's like kind of an enemy dog becomes the friendly dog.
It's like, yeah, the enemy, the enemy dog.
Toby Fox, Toby Fox, I thought Toby Fox, it was Toby Fox.
I'm not sure if that's like if that's supposed to be an earth pony magic thing.
But no, I thought it was weird.
I think it was just a hitch thing.
Yeah, you can't use the Fluttershy.
He's what Fluttershy was a cop.
Yeah.
The the yellow.
It's funny how like this, you know, they don't get any magic.
You know, when magic is restored, it's like Pegasus I can fly unicorn
skinny magic and it's like it's they say it a couple times at first.
Sunny is says it.
It's like, oh, wow, wouldn't it be great to have a friend who was magic
to have a friend that can fly?
Yeah, it's like it's like what earth ponies get by restoring that?
They don't get anything themselves.
But what they get is the blessing of like they know they can have friends
who have power. Sunny knew the whole time
that if she could con the earth ponies and to bring back the magic,
she would get both.
That's why she was on board from the beginning.
I mean, they they they allude to it right away.
Right. She breaks into a counter logic.
They throw the the wings and the horn on her.
Yeah. Oh, my God, they do.
Oh, my God.
She was like, yeah, foreshadowing foreshadowing.
It's not. I noticed that on my second rewatch or my first,
I guess that's the first kind of interesting, I suppose.
That's a bit that's a bit of a dramatic irony.
Dude, it's like they set things up cleverly.
Oh, my God. And oh, my God, the letter.
Oh, my God, she found the letter.
True. You know, I'm pretty good.
All right, movie, you got me.
You got you got me. It's a 10 now.
It is my story.
My score is steadily rising on my I am I.
Yeah, it was just it was just good.
I found myself just smiling, smiling just like, you know what?
This is a fucking this is a good time.
Oh, the conversation is silly.
This is dumb. This is fun.
When she sits down at the bar
and she's talking to the the unicorn bartender.
Yes, I just like my favorite design.
But I remember thinking that it was very funny.
Their dialogue was pretty. It was good.
You know, like is when the bartender is like, you know,
it's big talk for a little pony and she's like,
I think you'll find I'm average, right?
Like, that's funny. Yeah.
That got that got a laugh out of me.
I like that guy. I like that they do DDR.
It is very much like they're going to do it.
And it's going to be like, oh, she's going to get her ass kicked.
And then she's going to win the third round, maybe.
OK, OK. And she well, I it's funny that they do DDR.
But I it sucked a little bit
because like she doesn't win by any like clever scheme.
She doesn't. There's no.
She just kind of gets the hang of it.
It's like, it's like, why does why does she?
OK, she she enters into this bet
that she has like no hope of winning.
But then she just she just happens to be really good at it.
To be fair, she enters into the bag under the assumption
she's going to solve the Rubik's cube.
And she's like, I know how to solve Rubik's cubes.
Really good guys. Don't worry.
I mean, first of all, first of all, it's totally unfair for him to be like,
no, no, no, no, actually, we're going to do a different.
It is unfair. And what you challenged me for.
No, I should have an option to dip out at that point.
But yeah. And then there's like, and it's like, OK,
well, actually, we're going to do DDR.
And actually, you only have to beat me one time out of three
just because it's I don't know.
It just felt like no, I don't even have to work, but it's totally arbitrary.
I thought the guy was characterized beforehand.
It's pretty poisonous and sure of himself.
They should have set something up with with with either
her wanting to be good at dancing, but not being very good.
Yeah, I can't dance or the earth ponies just have happy feet.
That would have been cool.
That's the end scene.
I mean, I have a happy, glowy feet and that's how she won.
Well, I thought I thought.
Yeah, if she just happens, I thought Zip was going to come in and win it
because like Zip was like seeing was like being characterized in the background
as like being like competent at that.
And I thought she was going to jump in and like win.
I feel like it didn't do anything.
I feel like it came out of thinking like, what was Zip even here for?
I mean, Zip was like the info dump about the station, I guess.
I just have no, I have no impression at all of Zip as a character.
She's the rainbow dash lookalike with the like, like,
but like she's studious.
I guess she's smart.
I'm you, I'm you, but I like she's, but she's not even insane.
That's the thing.
She doesn't have like a weird, not.
Not even insane need to be slightly insane to be funny and cool.
Twilight was completely insane.
But Zip is like rainbow dash, but without the, you know, the the the radical.
She didn't have this is not real anxiety that she's she's not like she's not like
athletic, she's not like strong or anything.
She's just kind of there.
Well, she could be.
We just didn't really see any example of that in the film.
She didn't she didn't do anything.
She didn't do anything.
And Pip, all Pip does is be obnoxious and be on her phone.
I kind of be on your phone.
The worst I like Sony and I like the Instagram pony.
I don't care.
Sonny and Izzy are the only important ones.
Also, they're gay, by the way.
They're they're gay.
Sonny and Izzy are gay.
I would I would say that's probably true.
All right, print it.
I would say that that's canon.
That's it.
So who's best pony and why is it Izzy?
Because she's so cute.
I mean, it's I mean, it's got Izzy's the one who has the most
because because when she leaves the prison, she chuckles really
devilishly by replacing an orange with the tennis ball.
Yes, she thinks it's hilarious, but it's like not that good of a prank,
but she thinks it's so funny.
I she just puts it in the box and she's like,
wouldn't it be funny if I swap them because they're both spheres?
And then nothing comes of it.
She just thinks it's funny.
Just just thinks it's funny.
And yeah.
And the tennis ball is a pretty funny visual game.
Yeah, it is pretty funny.
And then in that moment, it's extra funny
because it's clear that she could have taken it off immediately at any time.
Just chooses not to.
She just did.
Izzy, like, never, you know, a lot of the jokes in this movie
did not make me laugh and didn't like land necessarily.
But like whenever Izzy made a joke, I never groaned or anything.
I was just like, I didn't laugh, but I still love you, Izzy.
Yeah, like she was never annoying.
She never annoyed me.
She was always either funny or just like, I can't wait to work three seasons in
and they just dial Izzy up to twelve like they did with Pinkie Pie
and just make it obnoxious.
Yes. Oh, I'm sure they will.
When will they flander eyes?
When will they flander eyes, Izzy?
The countdown begins.
Dude, did you see how they fucking plagiarized
Beljap at the end where they're trying to get the jewels,
but they keep falling off and they're like, oh, I've got to catch the jewel.
That's right. The end of Beljap.
Remember that? Yeah, yeah.
The jewel of Splish falls into the lava.
They have to go, oh, shit, it's falling.
Oh, they slippery. Oh, these jewels are so slippery.
Why can't I hold only we had hands?
Yeah, fuck.
Holy spike was here.
If they if they had hands, I'm so glad there isn't a spike.
Thank fuck. Me, too.
I'm also glad there's no spike.
I guess like hitch it. Hitch is the spike.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm not kidding. He is.
It's like one of Spike and Fluttershy and Big Magnetage
and a boy character was a cop.
He's the he's the one guy who sucks.
And he's he's plays the spike.
No, I liked him.
I thought he was all right. I didn't mind hitch.
I hated Sprout.
Fuck hitch. The thing I did like about
is that he's like he's like not for the reasons they want me to hate him.
ACAB means hitch, too.
Hmm. ACAB includes that.
I never liked Spike or like I couldn't find
myself to like Spike is is that he's just he's just the little nagging voice
that's always next is that he's a sidekick.
He's like a Robin to a Batman.
He's like, oh, geez.
Oh, wow.
Twilight is like a good line.
At least is his own character.
Oh, geez, Sonny, I can't wait to put you in jail when we get home.
We're all we're all going to jail after this, by the way.
At least he's an environmentally conscious.
Yeah, you know, this friendship thing is really cool and all,
but I really got to get you back and put you in jail, Sonny.
Hitch, jail is magic.
The the the the punitive justice system is magic.
Everyone, everyone brings something to the table in this ragtag band
of misfits and hitch is that you can do paperwork,
process you through the penal system and to get you and get you get you
sorted out, a special guy removed from society with a minimum of fuss.
Everybody's got a super special talent.
If he's going to be like in the show is like one of the the main group
and he's the sheriff, what what would that like?
What it's like having the mayor there as one of the main troop.
Yeah, what is going to even happen?
They can be like, Hitch, don't tell him.
He'll be like, OK, you were like you were right last time.
So what he what he brings to the group is that he can he could get you
and he can get you out of jail.
He could just be like, no, I just won't prosecute this crime that you commit.
What is going to be is going to be like doing that illusion with this position
of power as he continues to go.
Or that's true.
I was just going to be learning.
Learning that you can't quit.
Like, yeah. Oh, she's character.
You can't do that. I'm the sheriff, you know, I get.
Oh, I don't like this.
I don't like this gun.
They probably won't acknowledge it at all.
It'll probably just like be a thing that's ignored.
Yeah, he'll just be a guy.
He'll put Sprout in charge for real.
I mean, it worked out so well this this time.
It's true. I like that Sprout was just Josh Scorcher.
I also.
He's the best character now.
The same.
He acts the same to.
Yes, correct.
I want to see Josh Scorcher's review of the movie and see if he goes.
I can't wait to see the new and improved analysis.
Anarchy was using 3D models that don't animate.
They just glide around the 3D pony maker.
Like you rotate it, take a picture.
I just find it I find it funny because like up and up until the release of this
movie, I'd always been like saying like I even if I don't like this,
I can't wait for the chaos because like it's going to be like
a Star Trek original series versus Star Trek the next generation.
The fandom is going to fracture and there's going to be people on each side.
And just as someone who's been in the shit long enough to understand
the inevitable arguments, it'll be fun just to watch from the sidelines.
And then they literally called the fucking show a new generation.
And I'm just like, it's so perfect.
It's like poetry. They rhyme.
There's already people bitching about it.
And it's really funny.
There's some account that has like 200 subscribers or 200 followers on Twitter
called like Save MLP G4.
And they're running a change.org position to get this show canceled
and get the finale of G4 rescinded.
Bro, it's not that serious.
Chris Chan was all about that.
No, see, they lost their figure.
Chris Chan was trying to promote that before it went to jail for reasons
that we don't have to get into. As long as Chris is in jail.
As long as Chris is in jail, it's all over.
It's as long as as long as Chris is in jail, we're safe.
By the way, this is unrelated, but did you see the letter
that she wrote from prison?
Oh, my God.
The letter. Why? What?
The letter wherein?
The letter is insane.
The letter is the Jesus Christ.
Do you believe that's the West Sea?
Just like I am Jesus Christ reincarnated.
I am like, please, please draw a fan art of me on the cross, please.
It reads exactly like I completely identically to like a caliber and rant.
And this is the person.
This is the biggest proponent of like, bring back G4.
No, G5.
Yeah, it's so.
She's the biggest in here.
It's so fairly strange.
Yeah.
So it's so weird that Chris would say something bizarre.
It's so weird that it's bizarre.
Like, obviously it's going to be bizarre.
She thinks stupid, insane things.
But it's like the way it's written is so dramatic.
Yeah.
That it's like how I didn't know they could write like that.
Like that dramatically.
It was gripping.
I was I was totally engaged.
She writes almost as though it's like biblical as like it's like say say unto
me like like like do unto me that like thy thy duty.
Also, I need like five hundred dollars transferred to my bank account, please.
The.
Oh, OK, sorry to derail the conversation.
I was just I just forgot about that.
And I just remembered gripping stuff truly, truly a miracle.
Right. But anyway, we got to bring back G4.
We got to sign the petition.
We have to undo the finale.
Twilight can't be a long legged freak.
She's got to go back to be in a cute little pony.
It is.
Chop our legs off.
Job. Definitely chop her legs off.
We got to we got to like cotton.
We got to like cotton hill her ass.
If you know what I'm saying, this letter chop chop her shins off at the knee.
So her hooves to her knees.
What? That's what that's that's what Hank Hill.
That's what happened to Hank Hill's dad.
That's why his dad is short because they shot his shins off and they just
sewed his feet to his knees.
That's what you got to do.
OK, totally unnecessary.
So we're getting we're getting off time here.
But thank you. Yeah.
What are we talking about?
My little pony, the movie, the new generation.
10 out of 10.
Do we have anything else to say about the movie?
I liked the song at the beginning.
I like the songs in the middle.
I like the songs of the end.
I like all the songs.
Oh, the pacing of the songs is great.
I thought it was perfect.
I didn't think any of the songs really stuck with me that much.
I like the mob song because it was so stupid.
It was funny, but it was like that on purpose.
None of the other songs really did anything for me.
I'm being swayed.
I'll bump my score up to like a six.
Hell, yeah. Hell, yeah.
I have things that I liked.
I also this movie isn't for me.
It was much better than I was expecting.
I haven't seen the 2017 movie since it came out.
So I don't know if it's better.
Was that the 2D one?
Yeah, the actual like My Little Pony movie, the G4 movie.
Not a question.
Did I watch that?
The actual one.
The one that wasn't a fucking dumpster fighter.
Well, no, no, no.
I mean, OK, I remember now.
As compared to the Equestria Girls movies,
which are all living nightmares.
That's true.
I don't know if it's better than that one
because I haven't watched that one in a million years.
What, the 2017?
Yeah, I don't remember anything about it.
Oh, no, it's Dreadful.
Is it? Which which movie?
I don't remember it being the Dreadful.
Oh, the one where they go on the.
The one where they go to Aladdin
and then they go to the Sea Ponies
and then there's Pirate Parrots and it's like
there's too many things.
They don't spend enough time on anything.
None of the character,
none of the main six gets enough of screen time
to like really have anything to do.
My initial reaction was that this is better,
but I can't say for sure because I haven't seen it.
And then there was there was the fucking
there was the fucking Lion King fart guy.
The fucking Gremlin like minion,
blue minion, little rare.
I'm a fucking asshole, annoying piece of shit
from the line. Of course.
There is there.
And also, there is when Twilight gets like captured or whatever,
the like lava place that she's in looks exactly like
when you fight King Caliente for the second time in Mario Galaxy.
Look it up, you'll get it.
And that's why you've all been there.
Playing Mario Galaxy, everybody.
It's just like it's just like like metal hexagons over lava
or something.
That's what made me think of it.
I need to get a picture of that Gremlin guy
because he was so annoying.
I think I know who you're talking about.
When I say Lion King, there was like that Lion King reboot
like TV show. Oh, yeah.
From the Lion Guard.
The Lion Guard.
Tom, you made a video about Lion Guard.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I still get comments on it to this day
saying how wrong I am in the show.
No, that's how you do it.
That guy and that guy is this like spiritual
successor to Skunk Freak is in the Milo Pony 2017.
I would say that.
And he's a villain.
I would say that Western animation fans are the lowest of the low
and just the worst kind of person.
And you should never listen to them.
Well, why? Why?
OK, Phantom Horn.
You should never listen to me.
My last mistake was getting into the pony show.
And it's all just it's all been downhill from there for me.
So don't don't be like me.
The pony show is taken up like a quarter of my life, at least.
Easily. And and what a quarter it was.
I was 12 and 2010.
Oh, my God.
Is that one pony started?
Is that when Gen Four came out?
Yeah. Yeah. Cool.
So I was probably like
here under under the evil doer thing.
Here he is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that guy.
Oh, this. Oh, I forget him.
Yeah, I do love how there's a villain wiki.
It's really funny to me.
This is this is this guy.
Isn't there someone who looks exactly like the quote?
Oh, that's what you're talking about, right?
Yeah, he looks exactly like that porcupine or whatever.
Yeah, I don't even.
Yeah, I look at the quote.
Oh, I love pie.
Lots of rubbers, most famous line.
Oh, I love you go, brother.
Oh, I love pie.
What a great fill.
God, the wiki community is what a memorable character.
Whatever. Barry.
What a Barry Fizzle sparkle twist.
Was the name of what's her name at the end?
That's a little whistle, whistle, whistle, whistle,
Bibi Babis, snap, crackle, pop.
I liked I liked that pony a little bit.
I thought she was all right.
Right. Tempest, Shadow, Alias,
Fizzle, Pop, Barry, Twist, that's a very twist.
I thought that was a funny little twist at the end.
Remember when they turn that guy to stone
and he just falls over and they shatter him into pieces
and he just fucking dies right on screen?
Remember when they killed a guy?
Yeah, that was awesome.
Then kill anyone in this movie.
What the fuck? They should have.
They should have killed him.
What's his name?
They should have killed the Josh Scorcher character.
Skit, Sprout. Sprout.
You needed. Yeah.
Was I a good fucking sheriff?
Mom. They should have killed the mom.
Die. Mom just pulls out a gun.
They should have killed the Silicon Valley milf.
Absolutely.
They should have. She's a milf, though.
You can't do that.
You can't go around killing milfs.
Oh, we go. You could.
Oh, you just call me the milf hunter, I guess.
No one gets redeemed.
You're good at your body.
Die, Pony.
You got to drop off the side of a building like Gaston.
Yeah, you don't you don't kill him.
You don't kill him.
Yeah, they fall to their death, death. Yeah.
Yeah, one presumes that they perished due to nobody's.
No one's fault.
It's just now they double jump when right at the bottom.
They roll. They hit roll right before.
Yeah, they get no full damage.
They continue.
I'd like a Mufasa death where they fall and then they go down
and like hang out with the body for a while.
Like if it were me, I would simply hit roll
right before hitting the hitting the hitting the ground.
Simba like like sets up like he he he he sets up
like a scuttle bug just the right place.
He goes back in time.
Mufasa bounces off of it.
He sets up a scuttle bug to bounce off of it.
Uh, Simba, why didn't you set up the scuttle bug?
Simba, there's supposed to be a scuttle bug.
No. Watch for the rolling rocks.
Oh, he didn't.
He didn't watch for him.
And look what happened.
Watch the Lion King.
I love the Lion King a whole lot.
You know that.
Why didn't we watch that?
Lion King 2019, what a great movie.
Oh, my God, the Lion King is very important to me.
And the Lion King 2019 is my least favorite movie.
Did you see it?
Of course, I saw it.
Oh, you mean the live action one?
I mean the live action one.
Yeah, the live action one.
The live action full CGI animated again.
Oh, right.
But made exponentially worse.
I only just learned who YMS is
because Munchie was like, you should watch the Kimba video.
And I did.
It was really good.
And yeah, I never watched YMS before,
but I've seen like some of his highlight streams of him editing
his Lion King 2019 video.
And he I was like, I was just overcome
with this feeling of like, finally, there's someone who gives
as much of a shit about the Lion King as me.
Like I've never met anyone who could just fucking talk about it.
He's been making that Lion King video.
He's been working on that Lion King video for like 10 years now.
I'm terrified.
It's so excited how long he's worked on it.
There was I it's going to be like a day long video.
It's going to be like a 20 hour video.
There was there was like a stream highlight where he's discussing,
like, in depth, like, not just the fact that like the music
in the stampede scene is like synced weird, but like why the why it's bad
because there's specific musical cues that they use in the movie
in the original movie that they still leave in the remake.
Like, but they're they happen.
Like nothing is going on.
Yeah, like they they use this instrument to like to basically
like it's just represent that Zazu is flying, but that sound
just appears when Zazu is not even on like on the screen at all.
So and I was like, this is what I think about every day.
This is the only thing I think about is is the the the sinking
of the score and the stampede scene.
Finally, someone's talking about it.
I I see I understand you understand someday.
Maybe it was it was it was good.
I watched that as well where he was going over that.
It's essentially like the cuts and timing
is different, but the music is basically the exactly the same.
And so bits that are supposed to line up with animation and shots.
Like you don't notice it when you're watching,
but when you go over it and be like, oh, that that instrument is going
as they're falling down.
And it's like, oh, that's like it makes it pop more.
Yes, smart.
And then in the new one, they don't do anything smart with that.
Yeah, it'll be like they have like the the because, you know,
when you write a score for a film, you do it intentionally.
So they have a you feel like, yeah, you'll have a doodaloo
when they're falling or something or they're making a face or something.
And then, yeah, it's in the remake.
You you have the doodaloo, but like nothing
is what is happening on screen doesn't relate to nothing.
This doodaloo, doodaloo.
There's no there's no doodaloo, but they're not falling.
So like you it's not why the doodaloo.
So the purpose of the score is like the doodaloo undermined.
I see. I see.
It makes the scene feel really flat and like not.
It's it's so it's so overly in depth, but I can't wait for the big video.
Yeah, where he talks about all of that.
I know I love that shit.
I love that shit so much.
I'm very excited for this video.
The the Kimble.
He just like made the Kimble one like as like an afterthought.
Yeah, but it's like three hour long.
Yeah, yeah, it's I mean, I like that one.
It's very good, good time.
I learned a lot.
I had a lot of fun.
It was fun.
Good time.
You all had a good time was had by all.
There's so many good things in YMS is.
Catalog.
I mean, all I see of him now is yeah, it's I see stream highlights
and him reacting to Darman, which is a whole a whole genre onto itself.
I haven't gotten into watching the Darman things.
I just want the Lion King editing.
I agree.
Give me a Lion King editing, please.
Correct.
But I have seen some Darman shit.
I saw I saw a thumbnail yesterday
that was like YMS reacts to the cringiest,
the cringiest Darman video yet.
And the thumbnail was just YMS just making a face.
And he's like, wow, he's really cringing.
Was it the cringiest one?
Really?
I don't know.
I didn't watch the video.
I just saw the thumbnail and I was like, that is a big cringe.
Report back next week.
It looks like a real cringe.
OK, you got to watch it.
That's what we're all watching reveals.
No, we didn't talk about peeled Pokemon.
Oh, God, yeah.
Yeah, true.
We were looking at peeled Pokemon and we were getting.
I was getting mad.
I don't know what that is.
Some of the peeled sounds dumb.
Have you want to explain?
Have you seen like banana peel?
Have you seen that the peeled Pokemon Twitter account?
No, you know, a peeled Pokemoner.
Oh, here we go.
Cracks got it.
Yeah, it's disgusting.
Is it gross?
What is it?
No, just peeled.
The peels are peeled.
Oh, OK.
I get it.
You've probably seen like peeled dialog.
Next we think of like a potato peeler and that's
that feels like like like like a dangerous.
OK, I'm looking at this.
I don't like the idea of cutting these ears off.
You've probably seen the peeled dialog image floating around
because that one got kind of popular and a few others.
But yeah, me and Ben just scrolled through the entire account
and looked at every single Pokemon and I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
What the what the fuck is this?
What the fuck is this?
It's a potato.
This is this is just like going too far.
This is like you're not when you peel it.
You when you peel it, you take the extraneous elements off.
You take like the dude.
The very balance pretty good.
You take the doodads off.
You take the extra bits off.
You don't take its limbs off.
You don't remove its arms and legs.
That's not peeling.
That's dismemberment.
That's cruel.
It's an egg.
See that.
See that's peel.
No, that's peeled.
That's an effective peel.
That's a peeled Pokemon.
This this pig egg.
This pig egg is an abomination.
This pig egg is against the spirit of the endeavor.
Is it fair to say that the reason
that you were so mad when we were scrolling through the Twitter
is that like the rules about what you take off
when you peel a Pokemon were very inconsistent.
Yes, like like when he did or when they did,
I guess they they've them pronouns and bio.
When they did the the the Pidgey,
when they did the Pidgey line,
all they did was they took like the bits off
and they took the hair off and they took the stuff.
But it was still recognizably a bird.
It just had its elements removed.
But when they did the one from Gen 5,
I think Pit Pit of and that line.
Yeah, they removed the beak.
They took the beak off.
They took the feet off.
It just turned it into a lump.
But it's like OK.
This is not the you've gone too far.
This doesn't make any sense.
How could you peel his mouth away?
If he does this a lot, they do this a lot.
Yes, that one rule.
They will they will just remove the mouth.
And it's like that's not peeling.
Yeah, you've filled it in.
You filled it in with plaster and then like smoothed it over.
This is the opposite of peeling.
This is insanity.
As we were scrolling.
This is fucking distressing.
I feel like some of these feel like a troll.
Some of these feel like they did them deliberately bad
to make me angry as like a practical joke.
As we were scrolling, like Ben looked away for a second
and we came upon or I came upon this.
Which one is this?
This is Hapodon.
And I was like, Ben, I need you to embrace yourself
because you're going to hate this one the most.
And he did.
Oh, oh, wait.
What's the one Tyranitar?
Tyranitar, for some inexplicable reason,
they they remove some bits and they don't fill the mouth in,
but they just edit the mouth to be closed.
Like they just closed its mouth.
Oh, but the line, the outline of where
they did it, they did it, so it looks like he has a giant
Adam's apple.
Yeah, these are awesome.
I want to find it.
I mean, they're all unique.
I'll give them that.
They're all you never know what they're going to do with it.
I just I do like the account quite a bit.
It's very funny.
I'm sitting over here.
I'm going to find Tyranitar.
Mouth agape.
What?
Someone is doing this.
I just don't understand the appeal.
I know pun intended.
Any the appeal of doing this or consuming this content.
This seems like utterly.
Oh, no, we scroll through the whole thing.
I don't like this.
That's Kyogre, right?
They just go out of everything.
Those are the worst ones.
No, look at Groudon.
Get Groudon.
Look what they did to Groudon.
It's inexplicable.
What they did with Groudon doesn't make any fucking sense at all.
It's just a line.
That's not right.
This person just not right.
I like to think that this person has no object permanence.
And whenever they remove something,
they can't fathom that there would be stuff behind it.
So they just take it.
This person just can't think in 3D.
They can't think that if I take an element off,
there could be some body behind it.
This is like this one.
Groudon looks like a shrimp's hard outer thing
that you peel off before you eat the shrimp.
But this is off the peel, rather than it's been peeled
and this is what's left.
This is a picture off the peel.
I kind of like this one.
I kind of like lunatone.
I don't want to rag on this person.
I think that they're doing it on purpose,
and it's supposed to be stupid.
I think.
But it's also fun to get mad at it and be like, what is this?
You broke your rule from earlier that you don't remove the beats.
I think that they are not a good artist,
and they can't think in 3D very well,
and they are genuinely just kind of like, I said they.
No, I just said damn, that's scathing.
Yeah, well, I think they're kind of bad.
I mean, they're making it work, but I also
think there is an element of like some of them
are just bad on purpose.
Now this person rules.
Just because, like, Lamal.
This person rules.
Oh my god.
What is this?
What the fuck were they thinking?
What are they fucking doing to me with this nonsense?
I have no idea what this black dot is.
It's a ooze.
Is it like Kabuto?
Yes.
Oh, I have the number.
So give your guesses.
I actually don't know.
Is it something with like a shell,
and this is like just its face you can see under the shell,
right?
Oh, it's fucking cradley.
What?
Oh my god.
Yeah.
The object permanence.
They didn't just make it like that.
It should obviously have another eye.
It should obviously have another eye on the other side.
You don't see it from this angle.
You should be able to see just a little bit.
It shouldn't be entirely hidden.
No, I'm proud of them.
They got the object permanence.
They made it a whole sphere instead of like the bit
that you can see through the fake mouth.
Look at this.
Yes.
Like, obviously that's not what their mouth should look like.
That obviously that's not what their head would look like
when it's one, why did they close the mouth?
Two, why is their neck sticking out like that?
I'm so mad.
I'm so upset.
I can't believe they would do this.
Feel free to start your own version.
I wish on Pylos' line they removed the fur
and made it some flesh loams.
All right, I've seen survivor done by someone else before.
Like, what if survivor, like, what if you improved survivor
by getting rid of all of it's like too many like things?
It's just a funny squishy snake.
I mean, I never really liked the way they have like
something about the designs sort of uneven.
Is it the way that they're like,
they're permanently like squinched up?
Permanently like crunched? No, no, no, no.
It's about like their, if I get an actual picture.
Okay, I'm gonna show another one that makes me really mad.
This one is like, this is like,
this guy doesn't understand how to think in 3D.
Look at,
There's survivor, but yeah.
I think they did a pretty good job.
Ben, that's a good job.
I think it's just the purple,
the purple is just sort of like kind of random colors.
There's too many a little bit.
I don't know. Oh, yeah.
I always felt it was a little busy
and I could never really get into him.
True. What is this fire dog?
Entei. What is his name? Entei?
Look at Entei, like. I love him.
Why is he a Cyclops?
No, that's a completely insane criticism.
Obviously the point is that he's making it look stupid.
Yeah.
Right? Like they're making it look stupid on purpose.
Ben is thinking it too far.
I think that this artist doesn't understand 3D perspective.
No, no, no, no. I understand, I understand.
I understand that it's supposed to look silly
and it does look silly, but it's like,
well, I feel like you broke your rules here
because clearly this is not,
this is not actually what it would look like
if you feel it.
I think this account was designed for you.
It was designed to make you in particular.
Oh my God, look at this fucking.
That's what I said.
It's all, it's a joke in my.
Broken rules on totodiles.
Why didn't you fill totodiles mouth then, huh?
Why didn't you remove totodiles limbs either?
Inconsistent.
So inconsistent.
It's great, I love it.
If you're listening, I love you.
I don't know who you are.
You're great.
It's just, I look at this, I look at this intake.
Someone should make like actually properly peeled.
I look at this intake.
Consistently peeled Pokemon.
Yeah, yeah, the account is called
consistently peeled Pokemon.
It's like unlike some other accounts.
We obey our own rules.
We stay true to the spirit of the endeavor.
I love the idea that something this stupid
could have drama and a candy.
It's like the people that made the alternative
out of touch Thursdays account that is like
we're out of touch Thursdays,
but unlike the real out of touch Thursdays account,
we just don't ever retweet like Palestinian aid
or anything.
Wait, really?
Yes, yes, there's one that's like we're out,
we're out of touch Thursdays,
but we never do anything political.
Yeah, there are at least two extra
alt out of touch Thursday accounts.
Who's writing that account, Nate?
Probably some dork like him.
Yeah, some stupid motherfucker.
Got him.
Anyway, we should do that.
What I'm saying is we should do that to this guy.
Wait, okay, the Wailord rules.
The Gen 3 legendaries were like the worst ones.
Is that Wailord?
Wailord and Wailmer, yeah.
They just closed their mouths.
Why closed their mouths?
Eleazar's gonna have to edit all these in, right?
Oh my God, I mean, he better.
You gotta, every time.
He better.
You gotta.
All right, I'll stop posting them, but yeah.
Funny account.
I've seen enough, I've had enough of this nonsense.
I mean, we looked through the whole thing
and Ben was getting mad.
Ben was like screaming.
I'm still mad, I'm still mad.
Yeah, I was punching holes in the wall.
Yeah, you peed on the floor, you shit on the ceiling.
I shit myself, yeah, I shouldn't come.
You shouldn't come.
Oh, and it was, oh my God, what have they done to Harayama?
What?
Let me see, let me see, plus one more, one more.
One more.
They just, he has gloves on.
They just, they just like peeled back the gloves
and they're the same shape, but skin,
like that doesn't make any sense.
Take his gloves off.
Oh, oh wait, can I?
Yeah, other Pokemon, you take the hands off.
Why not take his hands off?
What do you think this is?
It's not who you think.
Oh, I know who this is.
It's not who you think this is, but I don't fucking know.
You don't know.
No idea.
Any guesses?
I mean, it looks like a Kuna, but it is a Kuna.
I know what it is.
This is Zapdos.
What have they done to my boy?
Yeah, it looks just like him.
You know those like fetishes that some people have
where it's like you get encased in like goo
and you basically die?
That's what the Snorlax looks like.
He looks like he's been encased.
They got him with the My Little Pony movie,
a goo stroller.
Yes, he looks peacefully dead in this image.
He's resting in peace for real.
He really is, he's resting in peace.
I don't know what's going on with his chin.
I don't know.
His chin line doesn't match up with his headline.
He's just got double chin.
This doesn't make sense.
The dark part is supposed to be the fur
and the belly is supposed to be like the unfurred part.
It should be entirely the belly color.
I got more.
If you're peeling it.
It's Magmar.
There he is, this is the boy.
It's Magmar, baby.
He's back.
Hey, get her, leave it.
It's better than ever.
What are you going to do about it?
Nothing.
I can't.
It's mutilated Pokemon.
This is terrifying.
I can't, I can't.
It's so good.
I can't have any more.
I can't have any more of this.
I'm feeling like maybe it's time to go to voicemails.
I'm thinking it's time to no more peeling.
This is cruel.
This is unusual.
OK.
I just thought that that was funny and a good way
to end the show before voicemails.
I'm so upset.
Peeled ponies.
Make your own peeled pony.
The first voicemail of the day is called A Bit of Trivia.
Also look up the TV chair.
And we'll post it right there.
There it is.
Are we ready?
Are we ready to go?
Oh, yeah.
OK, on the count of three, let's play it.
One, two, three, go.
Did you know the term information superhighway
possibly originates with the artist Namjoon Paik
with this term electronic superhighway
where he predicted the future of telecommunications
being all connected by electronic technology?
He's a good artist, too.
You should look up some of this stuff.
Specifically the TV Buddha.
That one's really cool.
Thank you.
Next.
OK.
I did not.
You've learned a lot.
I did not know that.
So that's pretty, pretty good.
I got my, that came out of my speakers for some reason.
I want everything to set default.
Yeah, I heard it.
You're going pretty bad.
You're sorry about that.
You annoyed me, Ben.
Again, like you always do.
Classic Ben.
All right.
Ben traumatizes me every day.
Oh.
The next one is going to be better.
The next one is called My Story,
which is a bit different from the normal stories.
Let me put it here in chat.
Do we wait for Gibb, who's peeing?
Should we wait for Gibb?
And just cut it out?
Why?
Why would we wait?
I don't know.
I don't know what's customary to you.
You usually wait for her.
Well, what are you going to fill the time?
Time waits for no one.
We can just post another peeled Pokemon.
No.
No more.
We can get a good one.
We have to unpeal.
OK, here's what we got to do.
I got to start an account that's called Unpeeled Pokemon.
You add things.
And it's just me redrawing the stuff that's
supposed to be there back on the peeled version.
That's honestly a great idea.
Just take their peel and then draw back
on what it's supposed to be.
But obviously, do it a little different.
Make it better.
I've got a good one to fill the time.
Just indulge in this for a moment.
Just indulge in him.
Just relax.
We listened to the second one.
No, we waited for you in post-it.
OK.
I'm glad you're back, so we don't
have to look at this anymore.
All right, the next one is called My Story, which
is a bit different from the normal stories.
Three, two, one, go.
My story is a bit different from the normal stories.
It started with me and my friends.
Our names was starting to get well known in the world we live in.
So that's when it started.
We had no idea what trolls were, so we didn't see it coming.
We was invited to a party, a troll party.
All of them up, it showed up.
And we had a pretty good time with our host.
They seemed pretty cool, but that was just to draw us in.
They asked us to come play some games with them.
At the time, it seemed cool, but that was just to get our trust.
So me and all the rest of them played their games
and had an awesome time.
But like I said, it was just to get our trust
so they could rip us down.
But none of us understood that, and they started to insult us.
But we had no idea how to react to it,
so they didn't get the negative response they was looking for.
What are they talking about?
We was just confused.
But some of the muppets found it interesting.
Muppets?
We went along with it, and that's when it started.
Is this Tales of the Trolling?
We decided to do it.
But we didn't understand what we were doing.
So we was liking it, but we didn't get a point of it.
This is a Tales of the Troll.
It was all fun and games, really.
Some of them took a liking to it.
All right, I've had enough.
Yes, Tales of the Troll is a funny comic
with funny, weird dialogue.
It's really amusing.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Thanks for wasting a minute of my life.
Next voicemail is called, I Know Nate Will Not Be Here
to Respond.
Thank God he isn't.
Three, two, one, go.
Nate, you coward.
The gamer zone is just the PCP.
Yeah.
It's just the same thing.
You're just doing the exact same thing.
Also, not even punctual.
All the topics you covered felt like they were like a month.
So if you're editing these things for like a month,
stop it.
Release them in a timely fashion.
You're talking about like JoJo Part 6 release.
That's old news.
Ancient news.
Feel with the times, buddy.
Thank you for your criticism.
It is just the PCP again, but with different people.
It's the alternative out of Touch Thursdays,
if you know what I mean.
Oh, I know what you mean.
I know what you mean.
Yeah, yeah.
Next one is called Josh Loading.
That's torture.
Josh Moon, Joshua Moon.
I don't know.
Three, two, one, what?
I know what I saw that name.
I know it's coming.
That's the that's null.
That's null.
I mean, I don't know if that's what this is about.
Whatever. Three, two, one, go.
OK.
Cool.
Get a drink of water, maybe.
Cheers.
You OK, buddy?
You good?
How you doing?
Are they like trying to wheeze with laughter at the bletter?
They're simply overcome by the world.
They are.
Next one is an image link.
I haven't seen it, but I'm going to post it here.
I don't know.
Oh.
How cute.
It's a pizza.
Pizza, pizza, pizza, he's like a Pokemon.
He's saying his name is Pizza P.
He's munchy.
Pizza P, it's munchy.
I'll show this to him when he wakes up.
He's back.
Is he still asleep?
What a bitch.
Dude, we all went to bed at 5 a.m.
Of course he's asleep.
I guess I got I got like four and a half hours of sleep.
Why would why would you be awake?
He is snoozing.
Here's another one.
Oh, I think I think this is just a dupe. Okay, they just they posted it. I think they sent the same one
It's actually really cute drawing. I like it a lot
It's cute. I mean it looks like a small child exactly. That's why I like it
I want to print it out and put it up in our office
Or in our bedroom or something do it do it dude. Okay, the next one is also an image. So here it goes
Well
What limited color palettes, I'm following the link limited it's like
Okay, it's just a bunch of like images of like album covers and animes that are like redone
With like dithering in like a limited palette. Okay. Thank you for sharing
Thank you for living your dream. Thank you for showing. Yeah, nice
Based based
Okay, cool. Next one is called cyber shell fan a 2003
Loading there it is
three two one go
Hey, the podcast is like ten times better with cyber show on and
I would estimate about like
30 times better with a laser button. So
Going forward
Can you just have them on every episode? No, you're stuck with me now. We forever. Definitely can't get laser
I I don't really need the other guys on just um
Just keep those two guys around so I was showing laser, but they're
Laser, but was on one episode and he'll never come back. Oh also
Acute girl willingly had sex with me this week
Oh
Damn willing to get like a round of applause
Boost my ego
Congratulations, not even for like self-esteem reasons. I just want to have like my my back patted basically dessert. Yeah, you got it
I like a trophy or something should have asked her to do it
Tell me I did a good job. I'm she just had my back to be like my back. I'm make me
Anyway, if cyber shell is on this f-side, I want him to be the one who graduates me no
And I fucking whoever can do
Didn't specify willingly I would have assumed otherwise. Yeah, what's your what's this person's name?
Who are you? They didn't give him congratulations. Her name is cyber shell fan 2003
Cyber shell fan 2003. Good job. I hope you foster healthy and nice and happy relationships in your life
Next voicemail is called
The tale of Tommy J
and here it is
three two one go
Tommy do you think you are funny?
Yes, I am very funny. My name is Tommy J. And this is a funny bet
Give it a really long voice man
many of them facts
Tommy do you think you are a being look I'm playing the heel. I'm being a bad guy, right?
Voice males on purpose. It's hilarious
Know what they say the more times you do the same thing
It's a great bitch. All right, I'm really annoying. That's the bit
It's just kind of shit
I was gonna ask who Tommy J is, but I think I've really gotten all the context
There was a whole saga there was a whole saga with I think I've heard vaguely about it. I don't yeah
Yeah, what it that was I mean
That was I'm enjoying. I'm enjoying the continual pink Floyd the wall
Very
All about Tommy J or just this one. I can't remember
Oh, no, no, that there was cringus bingus. There was it's just like a
Oh, yeah, PCP things. Yeah, I mean to ten ten thumbs up for that one
Well, we could we could
When that's done the PCP will have a better version of the wall
We should yeah, we should release we should release it on an album. We should release an album
We'll take everyone's fan fan voicemail songs
Steal them steal their value their surplus value
Make it into content. Why waste content? That's true. You gotta package it. Yeah, pack it. You're absolutely right, Ben
When you're right, I know you're right. I know I know it's true
Next next voicemail is called a death note spoiler warning. Oh shit three two one go
What's your opinion on the first half of death note i.e. before else death it's good
I like it. Yeah, it's good. It's like the first anime that I watched of course it was
But I've only seen like five anime so that's not saying much
The first half of death note. I mean, it's it's good and it's better than the second half
I don't remember the second half, but I know the first half they get handcuffed together and it's so
sexually tense
Yeah
It's it's it's it's the it really is a yeah we story
That nobody likes me said when I was nobody nobody wants to fuck Misa
Go away and let the boys have their fun, please
Yeah, I mean I guess the first part Misa is kind of annoying
She's not a very interesting character, but she gets a lot of screen time the whole like weird
I kind of like the weird convoluted scheme where like light makes himself lose his memory
But it's all in the he gets the note back in the end. It's like that's kind of clever
Yeah, it's it's it's like it takes a long time, but when it works out
It's like yeah, it's like the fucking Sherlock Holmes, but evil, but Japanese, but high school student. Hmm. Yeah. Oh, yeah, they're in high school
Yeah, he's like they're like 30
Yeah, he he graduates high school and starts college and I think in the sea in the second season
He's like an adult like he works like it's ten years after L's death and yeah light has become like one of the police guys
Yeah, secretly still killing. You know, I haven't seen death in a long time
But I think my and all of our opinions are probably the same
Consensus is which is like first half is great and it's cool and interesting and the second half
I don't even remember what happens. I I remember near and the other guy
I remember them and I remember being less interested in it was definitely like a very
The story was like this rivalry between L
Yeah, that was what I'm getting rid of it
Like you deflate a lot of the like intrigue of the story
I mean, I mean sort of a punch it again because like the the of the new L near
Who has white hair and he plays with puzzle games and toys instead of like
Sweet treats or whatever. Yeah
he's
He somehow manages to outsmart him
Alongside his like accomplice the yellow haired something or other from bleach. Yeah
Mellow yeah kind of kind of the point kind of the point of mellow and near is that they aren't as good as as L
Yeah, they can't they can't measure up to him, but somehow together they managed to do it
I can't I can't remember how he gets outsmarted. I
Figure out whether that was smart or whether that was just like
Yeah, it's a good show. It's kind of long. I don't know if I would watch the entire show again
But the fucking the the highs are really high the good mom the
I guess the mangas not nearly as over at the top. It's very much just like presented in a
Straightforward manner, and I'm kind of curious to see how my opinion of the story would change if like the dramatics were toned down. I
Read the first volume of like the follow-up series about like the
It's it's basically death note, but it's like a thing that can make you fall in love. I think
breast
I
Didn't stick I didn't stick with it
You guys watch the you guys watch the movie right the the live-action movie with Nat Wolfe from naked brothers band
Of course, I I think I only watch the English one and I was like, oh, it's in live-action. No, I watched it
No, I didn't I didn't watch the American death
You know, I really like the ticotomy the the virgin Nat Wolfe playing
Playing light in the not good at all live-action death
Versus the Chad Alex Wolf playing Peter in hereditary and saying mommy and crying weird, which is cool and awesome
Haven't seen hereditary you're at Terry's cool. We should watch it
You'll be scared though. You you might cry then I
Yeah, I might I'm very pretty easily scared by films. I'm pretty easily unsettled
By images on the screen. It is
It is a tough watch, but it's great movie dear
Well tough watches are even tougher for me
Nick next voicemail is an image, so I'm just gonna post it right here. I don't know what it is
Let's see what we got. I think I forgot something if you forgot then it wasn't important
Yeah, you're right
Did I say that I
Don't remember. I'm just I say something alluded to the same effect. I probably say this all the time
This does seem like me. It brings true. I don't remember. Yeah, we probably said something like this on the last episode
I don't know. I don't know
Next voicemail
Next voicemail. Wait a minute before we move on
I feel like maybe I should say a lol Chris Pratt Mario
What's his name always
Charlie is Luigi
Jack black is Bowser is awesome something. I'm literally hyped now that Jack black is Bowser
Jack black is really important. It might be kind of good. I don't know. Jack black Bowser
Yes, I don't think I like I don't think I like Chris Pratt as Mario. I don't think I appreciate that
I think it is very no, I think it'll it'll be so strange
Cuz like well first of all, I don't know what Chris Pratt sounds like. I can't envision in my head. He just has a face
He sounds normal. So like a just some guy
With like what I presume is like a Mario that is reminiscent of the actual video games
You know short stuckey's cutesy with a just a normal guy's voice coming out of his mouth
It's gonna be so weird. I mean, do you think he's gonna do like a fake Italian accent?
If he does it'll be the
It'll be I'm very I think the universe will collapse in on it itself if he does like a Mario
I can't wait for this movie to come out and it's gonna be like Chris Pratt in the real world as a normal person just like a
a dumb but like like
Nice hearted father who doesn't understand that his wife son play so many video games
Until he gets he's a kite into his son's Nintendo and then he is no
Has to go through all these. Please. It's gonna be a great. Please. No
I should have just given Charles
Mamma Mia been fucking is a kind they don't even have to have Mario talk in complete
Sentences like they could literally have Charles Marnay. Just do it like Wally worked and the characters don't talk
Just do that. Just do Wally with Mario literally goes up and says yeah, Chris Pratt
He's so cool. Mario's gonna be talking a lot in this movie. So we had to make sure the casting was right or some shit
I'm just like he's Charles Marnay. The funny it is mentioning that Mario's going to talk a lot
Like what do they mean? That sounds like it's like you normally doesn't talk
I guess is well, he doesn't normally talk, but like it feels like a strange thing to highlight
What we've got an actor and they're gonna work part of what announce all this like star-studded cast and they're like
Oh, Charles Marnay is gonna be in the movie doing cameos like imagine voicing Mario for 30 years
And then having to walk in the booth to do cameos for the Super Mario movie like I know I feel bad
It's like like hire real fucking voice actors, please
Like except Jack Black is a good voice actor like he's done other roles that are good like if you said hey
Do a voice acting role for Mario in a theatrical film like he could do it like he's a voice actor. That's his job
Yeah, he should yeah
Illumination slash
Chris Pratt, oh, yeah, okay
I was basically I I mean no my point is why is Chris Pratt Mario Charles Marnay should be Mario? Everyone thinks this
I think it's Jack Black is
You know, I gotta assume that they wanted Mario to sound more like normal and you know
Martin a gives him like that very like silly like like
Wahoo, yes
Bowser and the fucking castle's collapsing Luigi we gotta get out of here
I think I see me sounds like yeah, just imagine like Star Lord, but
Mario, I mean Star Wars already red. So if you squint you can kind of already imagine it
Just watch Guardians of Galaxy and squint the whole time interested to see what they do
But because I'm sure it's gonna be strange, but I just don't feel like Mario is a franchise that you can make a movie out of
I feel like this. Yeah solidified my opinion that like Shigeru Miyamoto is a hack now
Like he's washed up. Do you think it's gonna be like f zero?
I'm not like Mario and Star Fox was already bad enough, but this this solidified me Miyamoto's a hack there. I said it
Well, they said it was gonna be animated by Illumination Studios, which is like the the Minions movie
Yeah, I'm so excited to see what they do with Goombas. I'm sure it's gonna be great. I assume it's not
It's not gonna be like Half-Life action, but they didn't actually specify anything. They're gonna. I mean like they're gonna make all of the like
Lovable little enemy characters like insufferable like I I'm really not looking forward to watching this movie in theaters
Which I will do by the way
I'm not looking forward to but I'm definitely going to be
It's it's a nice day midnight showing
Yeah, I'm just seeing like characters that I love like little like shy guys on screen and being like I love shy guy
And then going to see Illumination making them be like horrible to listen to you
You have to buy your ticket to see this movie because it will be all that they're talking about around the water cooler on Monday
And if you're not in the conversation, then you might as well be fuck be a left
I don't care about Sonic therefore. I didn't watch the Sonic movie. I I love Mario. I'm gonna watch the Mario movie
I'm just gonna do it. I
Think you're I'm curious the idea of like being in a cinema and and and seeing
You know before you actually watch the movie for the first time it's the first time you're seeing the movie
You know that there's all these famous people playing these Mario characters
You're like what the fuck are they gonna do with this and whatever it is to be bombarded with it on a giant screen
I feel like you would make you laugh so hard. You would die exactly
That's why I want to go to the theater because I think it's gonna be so
Stupid I'm gonna laugh and I'm gonna be entertained genuinely
Perhaps
Maybe the movie will be great and will move me to tears
Anything just like just like my little pony the next generation
Let's
Go to the next voicemail, which is called. I hope you're ready for this. The next one is called fapping on Mike
Three two three two one go oh, then you're actually gonna play it
I
Was gonna do it now here's the part where you actually don't know. Okay, good. We got Rick
We did they played it
I spent $50 on fucking on fucking
No, you didn't know you didn't I'm paying you literally did that look at the rest. Yeah, you're right. Yeah
Was it was like 20 it was like 20 but it was like 20 bucks for like
Which is like 50 if you think
It was oh well, it was 50 for that plus all the other stuff we got
We need we need Kazi on that we need Kazi in these episodes more often to be the Ben fact checker
How much bullshit has been spotted that has been exaggerated. It's true. It's true. It's true. I just lie
I just lie all the time. It is true. I need someone around. I just assume I just assume you actually made the vapors
Cassie's in the back drawing everything like god damn it Ben someday you would think you would think so but no, it's not real
Next the voicemail is called. Oh, here we go. It's called a PCP episode compressed to 15 seconds
three two one go
To the channel for the PCP listen to what's up with the podcast ring
So is always always always always always always that's the end of the show. Goodbye everyone. We'll see you next time
Basically, I thought that we're gonna like edit like get the entire episode and like squish it down
And it was gonna sound like a noise like it sounded like it was just gonna get faster and faster and faster
But no, it's just actually
It's funny cuz it's true and it's true because it's funny. Yeah, it made something they made something pure
They made something they made a hell the mirror up to our reality
And that's what great art does
Next voicemail is called based timeline three two one go
Man, I just received my
Cato anthology same I was able to buy a physical release of tales gets trolled on
Amazon and soon I'll be getting a physical release of Lord of the Ghosts along with a red band comic
When did this become the most based time? Yes, you should the hate media
Consider adding consider send me a message and get a copy of road to rad con
Do yeah, if you if you might be interested if you like if you like physical releases of stuff
I finished a sketching. I finished sketching my Lord of Ghosts
Guest comic it's nine pages
Pretty long. Mm-hmm. It is long. It's gonna take me a while
It's gonna take me a while to to ink it, but I'm gonna try and do it
Quickly so I can get back to my video game. Yeah, I'm trying to wrap mine up as well
It's I'm I'm looking at though. It's fun to draw. I really I really enjoyed drawing flower head
You were right to to to give me the flower head one because I'm really I'm having him like
Stalking around and like mugging the camera and looking like a real badass and making like
Faces, it's great. It's great. I'm jealous. I want a whole flower. He's comic to
Flower heads at the end. I dream. He's there. I drew so much so much flower head just just so much
Next voicemail. Okay. Okay. This is this is good. It's an image. It is called the irritating gentleman
And I think I know
What this is? Oh? Oh
What is I need to zoom in yeah, I got it
It's been okay, so it's it's been with with four
For Doris or some other hat munchie in the back of the caravan just about is that me there's
That's mage, and that's Kaz. Oh, it's me. Yeah, it is
And there's a barrel of slime. Why do people give me 3d glasses?
Cuz you do you do yourself?
They weren't 3d glasses. They just had a colorful reflections in them
That's okay, though. I like it be creative you do you
Because Christina superstitious about the number 13, but then she just called the next one number 13
Anyway, so wish you 12 9 is the story of night star and night star is a unicorn from a question
She was born the same day as Christine and also tis just like it's okay. So this is me
I'm just talking about Chris and talking about Sonic and we don't want to do
to
Like
What's the relation I don't know
It's like a guy talking to a girl who's disinterested I know that well
That's misgendering things and I will send you to jail because that's a hate crime
I'm gonna put you in pronoun jail. Oh
Well, they just they just honestly good good job. Just oh
I see I can see the the cropping on on you
There's like you can see where they just cut out the the edge around the hair
I mean, I don't know what did possess this person to do this, but they did a good job
I like that slime. I'm getting hungry just looking at it. I want to dip my hand
It's such a strange yeah
Yeah, why why these people why this situation? Why is Munchie there cuz it's cuz I'm there
So Munchie has to be there because we're tethered and we don't do anything apart from each other true
I guess that time Ben came to London to annoy mage
And has he was there?
And Kazi was there for some reason and there was a barrel of slime and they were on a train who could forget
Okay, next one where was I I gotta find
Okay, the next one is a YouTube link
Here we go. Yeah, I don't know. I don't know what this is
Okay, it's Keyblade Spirits video the realest meme in the world. Oh, it's it's that it's Marjorie Taylor. It is
All right, I think the video doesn't matter
Well, read it. Yeah
What does it say?
Listening to the peace
Okay, because you think it's just Trixie's anime podcast where the okay, this is this is like Goofus and Gallant of like what you think about the
PCP the bottom one is good
The bottom one is good
Proud Lord of Ghosts plujaer
Okay, we're gonna we're gonna need we're gonna need
Eleazar to put this on screen. I don't think I'm gonna read all of these
No, Nate. Yes, watch. I like that
No, Nate. Yes, watch. No, Nate. Yes. No, Nate. Yes, watch
Ironically. Yes, Nate. No watch
Atomenous is my favorite indie game. That was a good one. I should replay that
What I hear Nate almost listen to the gamers
Just listen, it's just the PCP again, but with with other with other people better people
That's what the gamers that is what the gamer that is what the gamer zone is
It's just he just made the PCP again with different people. I mean as in he made a podcast, but sure. Yeah
The PCP is a very original concept
Thank you any other podcast is simply a ripoff of the PCP. I
Agree the next one is called wrong number
It's one second long three two one go. Sorry wrong number. Thanks. Thank you very much
Next one is called next one is another oh god, like hold on
Well, PCP 281 that's the dream. That's the dream line up is Ben Tom. It's it's it's the old it's the old cast
I'm gonna have it on 281
This is I think this is I think this we're recording 281 right now. That's the point. This is their drug
They gave you a free. This is what you're gonna use as the as the thing. Oh
It's a thumbnail for us. That'd be so sure me and crack in there
True. Yeah, just just turn mage into me. That's fine
Yeah, you just
Just just give her a snout. Yeah. Yeah, basically basically works
Yeah, and we'll just well, we'll just we'll just take the munchie one and we'll make it we'll give it the the red and blue glasses
No, I don't
I
Want to say it's just true
I want to ask who made the thumbnail for the last time I was on where it's like my head on one side of the screen Joe
Biden's head on the other side. I think it was Eleazar Eleazar makes the thumb
Eleazar that was hilarious. Please do that again, but with sunny
Or with me and Josh scorcher
No, no, no do it like a screenshot from the movie where it's the wanted poster, but it's sunny and Cassie. I
Want crack to be there too though crack
crack needs to be in the
Absolutely, just just peeking out just peeking out the corner. Be creative do something hilarious. I'm counting on you
Wait, no, it's the last 10 year on I'm trying to find Joe Biden was elected. That's why it was like right after the
So it would have been no member
or
So wow almost a year ago. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I see it. That was about 10 months ago. How was it feels like only yesterday?
Okay, well next voicemail is called whatev three two one go
Hey PCP at my local grocery store one of the baggers like he doesn't say hello. He just starts quoting I
believe either
spongebob or
That one Batman series that was really popular and like maybe the late 90s or early
2000s the animated one and
But he doesn't like say hello. It's just like you pull up to the register
And then he just immediately starts going into like quoting these and like I I just usually ignore him
But I don't know I feel like I'm starting to get kind of like a guilty conscious about it like
Should I say hi? Should I interact? It's like he's not interacting in a way
SpongeBob memes
Autism or something it's hard to tell I don't know you should you should memorize the both series
And so like you know like when he says a quote you should know like what the next line is and you should say it back
I think that would make his day. That's the lowest man
Just say some spongebob meme or just refer to like the episode with the gray ghost from Batman
Like you should just laugh. I'm gonna say the same thing. Just just fucking do a spongebob laugh impression at him
Really got to test the waters
I don't learn the language kind of leaning
I'm kind of leaning towards the do not interact like just just just just just avoid just avoid
I mean why you open a can of worms?
avoid
Yeah, honestly, yeah, that's my advice of no Ben's mean and wrong
I'm
Just Ben Ben Ben. Hey Ben Ben speaking for Ben. Hey, it's a central interacted with a lot and
Don't make that one person that Kona grill. He screamed at them and they cried
Screamed I was a bit annoyed. I was a bit annoyed because he double-charged me for my meal
And I think that you assumed malice though. That's unassumed malice
Well, you got to be firm you got to be firm and you responded in kind with malice. Yeah. Yes, absolutely
That's the only thing they respond to it's the only thing they understand
They talk about the working class is a lower a lower
You know those people that's kind of people. Let me go sharpen my guillotine
Hmm
Next voicemail is called Ben fuck Ben fruit fly fucker
Taint
There it is three two one go
James
Where were you when Ben saying was the fruit fly creator?
What I
Guess you're the right creator because you left the coffee
No, I got rid of the coffee I got rid of the rotting coffee for my for my closet
There's no more there have been significantly fewer fruit flies. Did you did you salvage the coffee maker is it?
It's on my it's on my kitchen counter. I cleaned it out
I think I might go and do a more thorough cleaning of it soon. It's just kind of I rinsed it out with it with hot water
I feel like it needs to like get soaked. I think I need to do some kind of
Did you get a new mattress yet?
No, then you have to throw your mattress away
Yeah, I know you need to throw it away. Yeah
Yeah, I know Ben's mattress is not yellow. It's orange at this point
But my shit, but my shitty but my shitty apartment is so shit
I'm like why why get a new good mattress just to put in my shit apartment make it a little bit better
You can't sleep on that thing anymore. You can't do it. What's what's even the point?
What's even the point of trying to improve my lot if this is where I'm at
It's never gonna get any better. I'm this is that I'm stuck here
So I might as well just embrace it. Okay, I might as well
Just embrace the filth and the end the decay and this my slow decline into into obscurity. It's gonna be okay, buddy
Don't worry about it
Okay, if you if you say
Okay
No, it's why I speed up the process
Next one is called trying door dash
God, it's a minute 30. Okay, three two one go
I took Tommy Oliver's advice and placed an order in door dash for Tommy J's body
The delivery was successful, but I don't see it
Tommy J's body
That's what I'm saying
I
I mean what more can I say that what can I what can I add
Got stepped on and that's the story that's next
Called
That's okay. That's okay next next voicemail is called guest tier list
three two one go good
So in F tier we've got Merlogic fuck that guy
In D tier we're gonna go with Jim storm dancer and Brad Garlinghouse
Nothing really wrong with Jim. It's just wasn't all that anxious like interesting for a bit
Fuck Brad in C tier. We got laser bot fit MC Nate bestman and Trixie
laser bot was awesome, but I don't know
Please watch really that to give it a guest it was just kind of an interview about
Tesga's troll, which was awesome. Yeah, but not like in every episode type thing. He's not a
Fancy was fine. I guess
Nate bestman's kind of cringe don't have him on again same with Trixie. Yeah, I agreed in B tier
We got Mallory and president Barack Obama. Yeah, I don't have much to say about them. They were cool when you had them on
A tier kaiju Koon CC Tectonic Improv Applejack and oblivion fall
CC ground me a lot. I'm gonna be an S tier right for CC in the first ones, but
CC is pretty based
And S tier come on make them members
Cybershell cheesy and gamers. Where's Kazi didn't where is Kazi?
Mmm left out again Kazi's left out everything as he and Craig
This is never been on though. That was a very limited. That was a very limited
No, I was on I was on an episode. I was a whole episode. You were when it's true. Oh
Wasn't it just the legendary laptop discussion? Yeah, it was
Right
Everyone fell asleep during the frame laptop discussion and
It was highly it was highly divisive quick what what boring technology topic can we talk about today? I
Would appreciate it very very much if you revised your list and put me on it put me wherever you feel I should go
Where's Kazi? Where's Kazi?
Like tier list PCP guess what?
What kid I'm gonna see if it actually is like a yeah Applejack applejack was it was S tier yeah Applejack Barack Obama
Legendary PC incredible that they remembered Applejack, but forgot us they
They forgot they forgot they forgot area they forgot area dimets. Oh, how could they forget legendary legendary guest
Libertarian candidate for mayor of fucking Keen new Keen County, New Hampshire area dimets. Oh, yeah, I just told you
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Yeah, the person that was in F tier. It was that the Wonder Bread person
Yes, more logic is the one right fuck fuck you Wonder Bread person
Such a bad guess that I think he circles around to being s tier is a lose a legendary, you know what you're right
Yes, I know
Next voicemail is called not Cassidy
From alias at one two three fake dot mail
three two one go
Yo
This is the tea
so I got a
If I can't find Z it is it is so when mr. T was in Kawasaki
I found
This weird book
the
Nurtama time or something like that
It's written in some bizarre language. I ain't ever heard of before Japanese apparently. It's called English, but I don't know
Let's go to the chase
In reading this book because I learned the language in reading this book. Mr. T. He fucked up big time
Y'all might say that I'm a dang foo perhaps
I'm really sorry
Revival with the necronomical yes, of course, of course fuck are you
Necrono
Just cute. Yeah, I'm not gonna comment on that
Okay, okay
I'd made my tear list. Oh shit. I found it if there's a piece. I think I did it before
Oh damn not a bit for but that's the true heat. That's awesome on its tear
Mother's basement
I love that
Did you make this is your last game that you you decided no no no
Somebody made this a while ago, and I remembered it that it was on the tear maker website and it's Google
I was gonna say did you you so you ranked your friends?
Just just rank my friends how much I like how much do I like them? How much do I like now?
No, no, how funny they are on the progress news podcast
I will but mother someone surely blows us all out of the water through no joke
Someone should make maybe maybe at some point I will make a guest list and just put all all the PCP guests on an actual
Like every single one I can't take that kind of criticism if anyone puts me in like b-tier or lower. I will I will cry I
Won't make it to you. I won't make you. No, I won't look at the results
No matter what the Mario movie I will seek out pain
Mmm. Yes, next we have one more voicemail. It is called
redrawcast snitch
There it is
three two one go
More like a bitch
I don't get it funny. What was the title? It was called re like regarding drawcast snitch
What are that and then more like and then it was sent from
It was sent from f you the channel got taken down now. It's back at snitches get stitches calm
I don't get it. I don't get it either. I mean you said a dirty man said a bad word. And so that's funny
Okay, hey Ben well, that's all that's miss one. Did you miss one? It's it's three seven one nine the file name
Three seven one nine you post it, but I don't think we played it. Oh
Yeah, okay up the yeah up there three seven one nine. It was called. What did I what do they call it?
It's called words are cool. Shit. I did miss it. Okay. Let's do it. Words are cool three two one go
Yo, I just realized the word impotent is just a negation of the word potent
That's so cool. I never thought of it like that before
I
Played it. I'm glad you're learning. Keep doing that knowledge is so good
I mean
When I think about my own impotence, I always think about how you know, like otherwise
I would be I would have such potency, but it's it's just been negated and
It's just it just makes me sad. It makes me sad
And
Well fuck
What what else? Let's keep this let's keep this podcast train going. Okay? I don't have anything to do today
We had not even a three hours. Yeah. Oh my goodness
I know my hangover is is
Non non-existent. I feel yeah, I feel I felt a little sick when I when we logged on but I feel fine now
I've been drinking seltzer water. I'm fully hydrated. I'm not I haven't had anything
String you drink water. I will I actually wasn't over
I was a little bit. I was a little bit. This can be the section of the podcast or I
Recount all of the embarrassing things that Ben tells me while he's drunk
And you do the same of me
Eleazar edit this part
Cut it cut them cut them off cut them off
No, uncut it and that's it. That's the show wait wait wait wait wait wait wait before we go before we go
Yeah, how fat bone bone is I can't I can't I can barely handle it. Look at this poor cat. Oh, look at him
He's got a little backpack
Yeah, that's so cute
I
Armour pauldron's on he's got one little world of Warcraft spiky shoulder pads
What is that piece of shit this thing look I mean look at this guy
He's just out here
You're working it you're working it you're making it happen look at his fat
Cradle that guy. Yeah, look at his big ol arms and his big ol face and his big ol eyes
Crack you done good today, buddy
This is much better than peel Pokemon. No, it's not I wouldn't it's not that good
I wouldn't peel. I wouldn't even peel this cat. I would just let him be I would just let him keep all his pieces
Oh, I love the picture of him in the fucking grocery store. Yeah, no carriage. Oh
Oh, he's coming shopping
It's just like Garfield. It's like Garfield. You got it. You got to take your cat shopping
All right, are we are we are we concluded?
Have we had have we had a successful podcasting experience today? We've never had a
Podcasting experience or we didn't complete it
I'm hearing a lot of different opinions a lot of different takes about it
But yeah, just like the takes we had on the pony movie. Oh good movie bad movie
You decide let us know in the comments. Let us know in the comments patreon.com
Pleasure to get the bonus episodes if you're a patron you get five dollars off the
The the the road to red con send me a message buy a copy of road to red con before I run out again
Speakcribe comm slash PCB voicemail if you want to annoy us with these
And I guess that's it I guess that's all I have to say any last words people
No, no, no, okay
That's it get those Lord of Ghost things done
Yes
Working on it. I'm working on it. I'm working on it. I have it open right now
My policy is to remind Ben at the end of every episode, but you mentioned it first. I brought it up
I'm proud of myself. I didn't I didn't neglect my duty this time
Okay, that's the end of the episode
You