Hello and welcome to The Pro Crastinators Podcast. I'm Ben Saint, introing for the first time and I got it's such a rush. It's such an adrenaline rush. I can't believe it. I've made it. I made it dad. I'm here and I'm queer and get used to it. And I'm here with Digibro is also here.
Oh man, I just like moved my beer and it made my mic fall over and I didn't realize it was resting on my beer.
Oh yeah, and I'm here with Nate Best Guy Ever Bestman.
Oh man, I just moved my tea and it slightly jostled my microphone arm. What a conundrum this is.
Whoa boy, and there's also The Davoo here. The Davoo from Saturn goes to Saturn.
And whoa, we got fucking Hippocrit here. He's a fucking Hippo boy. He's on the show.
It's an honor to finally be on the show.
Yeah, all right. We're here and we're talking about, hey, let's talk about how we all just went to the fucking movies together.
Like a bunch of cool, oh wait, nobody else is here. Nobody else is here.
Did you go with you? I'm here. I was there.
Yeah, it's only Digi.
I can speak for Tom because I know the entire experience he had as I drove him as he now lives with me.
Let me quickly look up the Urban Dictionary definition of going to the movies.
Yeah, sure. Urban Dictionary of going, Urban Dictionary of two, and Urban Dictionary of the.
Just add a plus between those and you got it.
And I've just returned back from the harrowing adventure of riding the fucking bus. What a shit show.
Tell us about your bus woes.
Ben, I didn't even think you lived that far out of like the center of Boston that it would take like an hour and a half, almost two hours.
And I should have probably just gone with my normal route, but I decided to look up the fastest route on my phone,
which had me jump three different buses, which would have gotten me home fast because I wouldn't have had to like wait hardly at all.
Only one of those buses ran late and missed its connection, so I ended up having to wait around.
So yeah, normally to get into the city, I just have to take the red line and then a quick bus ride to Harvard or Davis Square,
which is pretty, it's pretty convenient, but I didn't do that.
How long would that normally take though?
If I, if I time it so I leave like it exactly when I need to be like, like, like so that I'm not waiting for the bus,
like half an hour, 35, 40 minutes tops.
Public transportation, ladies and gentlemen.
What the hell are you going to do?
I love public transportation. I am so, I am so overjoyed every day of my life.
Every day of my life, I look up at the stars and I say, thank you, God, that you didn't curse me,
that you didn't curse me with the modern leprosy that is automobile ownership.
Ben, do you remember, do you remember when we were young and we missed the bus?
There's no public transportation. What we would have to do to get to school, we would have to call a taxi service to dispatch a taxi to us.
I mean, our dad did it so that we'd like learn a lesson.
Yeah, yeah.
We could have driven us, but like he wanted us to learn.
Our parents made us do it mostly out of spite.
Well, it was not spite, it was just so we'd learn, dammit, and I learned, dammit.
Tomato tomato.
Yeah, yeah.
I remember one time, one time I missed the bus.
Expensive too.
Yeah, and this was the worst, but also it was a little heartwarming at the end.
Oh, shit, spoilers.
Okay.
So yeah, I missed the bus and I think dad was like, I think I had missed the bus like not long before and dad was pissed that I had missed it like twice in a row.
So he was like, you know, get a fucking taxi.
I was like, okay.
So I call the taxi service and I get in and the thing is I, at this point in my life, I was not driving.
So I did not really know the way to the school like by car.
So I get in the taxi and the guy starts driving me and he asks me where the school is and I tell him I'm not sure,
but I try to give him directions as best I can and I fail and we take multiple wrong turns and we end up driving for like an hour.
School is like, what, 20 minutes away?
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah, so we drive for like an hour and the bill is like $40 at the end.
It's like way more than it should have been.
He could have just looked it up.
He could have just looked it up and I don't even have $40 on me.
So we get to the school and he's, he even got mad at me one point.
He's like, where's this fucking school, dude?
Cause like, I don't know why he was mad though because his plan was then to charge me for the whole ride, which he did.
We get to the school and he's like, okay, that'll be like 40 bucks.
And I'm like, well, shit, I don't have 40 bucks on me.
It wasn't supposed to be that much.
And he's like, all right, listen, I'll take what you got on you right now and then I'll come to your house when you're out of school.
I'll come to your house after school and collect the rest.
And I'm like, uh, okay.
Little baby Ben's first experience with debt.
Yeah, we'll come in and break your legs.
Probably like 16, 17, I'm going to say 17.
So, but anyway, long story short, I get home and it turns out that he did come to our house, but he met our parents and apparently our parents told him to fuck off because, uh,
Excellent.
Yeah, so I did not.
Yeah, yeah.
So I was, so in the end, I got that's the heartwarming.
Yeah.
He deserves to get told to get some money.
This was before Uber, by the way, for anyone that doesn't know what a taxi is.
I was recently in other countries known as Europe and I was, I usually loved public transportation because it's like, you know,
That from my house, I can walk to the train station.
I can go anywhere in London.
I want at all through the trains.
And that's, that's cool.
Um, but I was in like Switzerland, I think, and I had to like, I was going to this film festival on short notice.
It was, it was a secret, secret project.
Don't, don't worry about it.
Um, so I was going to your folks.
Damn.
Um, I talk about it on my Patreon podcast.
Okay, subscribe.
Yeah, I'm behind.
I'm behind on the, on the pay, on the pay podcast for the Hippocrates.
Me too.
Yeah.
So we all Hippo patrons?
Not me.
Never.
Bitch.
Anyway, um, I mean, I'm in Switzerland and I'm freaking out because I'm scared of different people to me.
And so, and I don't know the language and they don't care about me and it's really late.
And so I'm like, okay, I need to get from Switzerland to France.
Um, because the only airport that's close by is in Switzerland.
There's like, you've got to go over the border, uh, through a coach.
And I'm like, how do I, how do I do this?
I didn't have enough time to like research it beforehand.
So I was fumbling around in Switzerland looking at like the train like things and there was no people around.
I had to like smash on, on, on the like little ticket, uh, you know, dispensers.
Oh.
And it wouldn't go to the place I wanted to go.
So I couldn't get the train.
Was it in English?
There was an English option, but it just wouldn't go to the place I wanted to go to.
Dude, this is literally like watching someone go through Valley of the Drinks with two flasks.
Like, oh my God.
Yeah, it was like the most unprepared I'd ever been.
And at this, in this moment, I was like, public transport is the worst thing of all time.
It doesn't, it doesn't cater to me.
A weirdo foreigner who had not looked up where to go and how to get there beforehand.
Anyway, I, I ended up having to get a taxi, which was like a 45 minute taxi.
To France from Switzerland?
Yeah, just, just across the border.
It's like near the Alps, like little, little border thing there.
And I get the, I think...
Countries are really small over there.
Yeah.
Those are pretty decent size.
I get the, I get the taxi and he's like, yeah, yeah, just, just get in there.
It was really funny having him like fail at trying to like use his like Google voice recognition to input the town that I wanted.
It's just funny to see that French people, Swiss people, they have, they have funny problems just like us, just like real people.
Hard to believe.
It's like being British and then describing going to Europe.
But I guess ever since Brexit, we can, and Yuri Hirasawa's opinion, I guess that basically passes now.
Well, it's like, it's like being Chinese, it's like being Japanese and going to the mainland.
Yeah, I guess that's true. I guess that's true.
Yeah.
I can only relate to things through Japanese.
The scary ending of public transport and the fact that I had to get a taxi is that it was like 200 euros.
And the guy turned around to me when he got there.
That's like $10,000.
Yeah. And he, and he's like, you know, 200 or something.
And I was like, okay, here's my car.
And he said, oh, we don't, don't take car.
I'm a taxi.
And I didn't have Europe money.
I didn't expect to be using Europe money.
I was expecting to be using a train.
I was expecting to be using my funny car to, to, to beep on like, like public transport.
You, you beep your card. It works everywhere.
It was very stressful.
So how'd you get out of that predicament?
I ran. No, I, he took my card and he did some weird thing.
And then I got an email saying money has been taken.
And I was like, oh, okay.
Oh, all right.
So you still had to pay 200?
I think it was like, he doesn't like, this is a thing in Europe that I've noticed a lot of times when I didn't have cash.
They really don't like, like using cards because they can't, you know, if it's cash, then, you know, you can't, the government doesn't know that you have the money.
Oh, sneaky, sneaky is not on record.
So they can do something with it.
They can be sneaky taxes.
Because when you, when you run a credit card, there is a charge.
That's why like most small businesses will have like a three or $5 minimum and all that.
But like specifically in Europe, people are very, very cash only please all the time.
To fill your hands with coins during the smallest of exchanges.
Like that, like, like in, like in David Lynch cooking quinoa.
Yeah, David Lynch cooking quinoa.
It's not uncommon for that to happen in America, but only if it's like places run by foreigners.
That's true.
There's a burger place, it's run by fucking Americans, but it's small and it's frustrating.
It's fucking small business quirks are kind of infuriating.
Wait, wait, you're talking about Burger King small business quirks?
No, I said Burger King.
Yeah.
Hippo's memes became reality.
But Yovoo, I don't even work at Burger King.
There it is, there it is.
Yeah, memes, meme count one.
Can we get an air horn?
Can we get a fucking soundboard?
It's all fucking quaint and quirky that they have like fucking like dish towels hung up on the side.
That they have like these weird names like the farm hand, which is a hamburger with ranch on it.
It's all nice and quirky.
And that you're in a building that's from the 50s until like you're sitting down waiting for your order
and then the lady goes, oh yeah, by the way, cash only.
And it's like, goodbye.
I don't understand how they don't just put that on the fucking door of the place.
I believe they like...
I mean, I know they post it somewhere, but never prominently enough.
There should be a picture of like an old family from the 1800s saying this must be you.
And so, and like, you know, the fucking, you know, Cole brought me over there because she was so excited about it.
And she didn't even remember that part, packed.
Well, that's confirmation bias because you're only remembering the times that you failed to notice it.
So those times they failed to post it prominently.
We show up like a month later, this time with Cash Ready, and you know, we got the food just barely in time.
We got there just before closing at 5.30.
It's a fucking restaurant that closes at 6.
On which day of the week was this?
I think it was just a weekday.
I mean, if it's a lunch place, that's probably reasonable.
Maybe on a Sunday where things like close early.
I don't know.
Fucking Kevin's Doghouse.
As much as I love Kevin's Doghouse, and I promoted it so much online,
that place had the shittest hours in the universe because they were like closed on two days of the week, I think,
and they opened at like 11 a.m. and closed at 3 p.m.
But then if they didn't have enough customers, they would just close like an entire hour early just because they're like,
ah, well, nobody's showing up.
And then me and Victor would get there at like 2.30 and be like, mother fucker!
It's like a 15 minute drive, so it would be frustrating.
One of the least appealing...
Oh, sorry, you can go.
This was really funny.
It was really cathartic.
No, not cathartic.
It was hilarious.
I don't know what the fuck it was.
To be sitting there, we sat outside the store because they closed,
so it's like, okay, shit, we gotta stand outside at the benches that are outside.
Eating our hamburgers, 6 o'clock happens, the store closes,
and we watch like half a dozen vehicles pull into the drive-thru,
and the lady who's like cleaning up like gives them the no signal,
and they have to like drive away and being like, yeah,
maybe don't fucking open a restaurant and close at 6 on a weekday, you morons.
Like what?
One of the least appealing cities I've ever been to was Richmond, Virginia.
And I would only be there for a little bit, like I would stop there between buses and trains and shit,
and sometimes I would walk around.
Incidentally, the worst place I've ever lived, Richmond, Virginia.
Yeah, cool.
Home of the Confederacy, right?
Right?
One of several, probably.
It's around there.
That's one point in its favor.
So, I mean, first of all, the whole thing is a rusted, concrete nightmare,
like the downtown area.
It's hideous.
And second of all, I walked around for like an hour on a Saturday,
and I went into like, you know, stores that normally sold food,
and like all the restaurants were closed on Saturday,
like in the middle of the day on Saturday.
There's a lot of Jews around there.
I doubt it.
Frankly, I doubt it.
Okay.
But yeah, everything was closed in the middle of the day on Saturday,
like convenience stores, like they were that normally would cook food,
their grills were off, they were no longer, they were not cooking,
because like there's just nobody around, nobody, no business on Saturdays.
No business on Saturdays.
Which is the opposite of what you would think.
Yeah, like if you think one day they were going to operate, it would be then.
Is there some sort of siesta going on, like across town?
No, I asked the guy, because I was like, hey, are you cooking food?
And they're like, no, the grill's off.
And I was like, why is everything closed?
And he's like, there's just no business on Saturdays.
So I was like, well, this city must be in a bad way.
Must be in a bad way.
Must be the internet.
Everyone's ordering their burgers online now.
I guess so.
Ben, I'm gonna ask, what was the total cost of your travel
to and from the theater today?
It would have been less if I had taken the normal route.
It was maybe like $7 or $8?
Okay, so next time, I think as of you saying that just now,
I am never driving into Boston again.
Did you have to pay to park?
I always have to pay to park.
Yeah, that's where the, yeah, no.
And I never think about it.
Don't do it.
Because what happens is I look up the amount of time it will take,
and I think, oh, well, I have a car, so I can just drive in.
It'll only be half an hour, as opposed to 45 minutes to an hour.
And then I never, until I get there, do I remember, oh yeah,
I'm gonna have to pay for parking if this is anywhere exciting.
And the way they structure the hours everywhere in Boston is fucked,
because it's basically like zero, it'll be like 15 minutes is the lowest amount,
and that'll be like $10, and then it'll be like 15 to 30 minutes,
30 to an hour, an hour to an hour and a half,
an hour and a half to two, two to two and a half,
and then if it's after two and a half, it's just like some astronomical amount.
Who's gonna park for 15 minutes?
I know, I know.
Who's got the kind of business to be done?
And a parking lot that's built into a movie theater.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
So we had all said that we were gonna show up at the theater,
the movie was at $12.55, so we were like, let's all show up at $12.30.
I get there at $12.34, and it's like, if you're under two hours,
the maximum that they charge you is $14,
but as soon as you're over two and a half hours,
it's just a flat $28 for the rest of the day, or $24 or something like that.
So of course, I'm like, well, we've showed up 30 minutes early,
and it's a two hour, like, you know, two hour, 10 minute movie,
so yeah, I had to pay.
That's why the PCP is recording quite late today,
because once I had cleared that two and a half hours,
I was like, well, we're in town, I'm not gonna fucking leave
and spend $28 without getting some food with my friends here,
so yeah, that was the logic.
I guess this is like, it's a fucking,
I've never done a lot of city living myself,
but you're really just paying for the convenience of having a car
and being able to drive it around the city,
they're trying to discourage that, it almost seems like.
It's not even, yeah, and it's not worth it,
because part of why we got our house where we did
is that it is within reach of public transit.
We deliberately didn't refuse to get a place
that was too far away to make it into the city.
It's just that I've never used public transit in my life,
because this is the first time I've lived anywhere that has
even remotely reasonable public transit,
so I'm not used to it.
There's nothing better than living on the red line.
You live on the red line, you're all set.
Yeah, we live on the red line.
While we're on this public transportation,
the only experiences I'd ever had with public transportation,
because Ben and I grew up in a rural area
where there was nothing there,
and then when I moved, when I went to college in New Jersey,
there were trains and buses,
but I would only use them when absolutely necessary,
and it seemed extremely poorly optimized,
and there weren't the kind of apps that there are today
that let you track buses, locations, and times and stuff,
which are a godsend for this kind of stuff,
because there have been so many times,
I've been just fucked by buses, just not showing up
when I was in college.
But when I was in Tokyo, it was just the end of my college days.
It was just a hard left turn
to just the greatest train system in the world,
and it was unbelievably great,
and Boston is also not too shabby at all.
Boston's amazing because it stops everywhere.
Every fucking 10 feet, there's another T stop,
and the thing is that in order to get to the T from my place,
I would have to drive two minutes to the place,
and so to me, it's like,
well, if I'm going to be using my car anyways,
why don't I just drive into the city?
And then, of course, I always forget how expensive parking is
until I get there.
And now, today, I am cutting that off.
I'm excising this cancer from my life.
All right.
Yes, yes.
I'm definitely addicted to the autonomy that my car gives me,
but I've also just got no other option.
I am too, but I use the car constantly in town,
and that's fine.
Like, where I live, which nobody please say,
but where I live is very dense and interconnected,
and using the car is like using the T in Boston.
It's so easy to get around with a car here that it's like,
it's fucking mega convenient.
But yeah, if you're going into Boston,
the thing is, even if you take public transit,
yeah, that takes longer,
but the traffic is always so fucked that even if you drive,
it's going to take just as long anyways,
because it's definitely going to take longer than it says it is.
One downside is that Boston closes kind of early,
and I think on most days, the T stops running around like one.
Like, I think of the last trains are like one, one, eight.
Oh, well, I'm not going to probably do much
that would keep me in Boston.
I wish they went later, but you know what, it's all right.
I mean, that just means like everything just closes at one,
because that's when the trains stop running.
As amazing as public transit is in Japan,
I think at like midnight, they fucking stop.
Yeah, they shut down at midnight and restarted 5 a.m.,
which is okay.
But you know what, speaking of public transit,
I just wanted to say my last thought on this
is that there's been some interesting developments
in Slime City.
Looks like some kind of transit system.
Yeah, New Los Angeles City, aka Neo Milwaukee.
Yeah, some kind of transit system.
Some kind of transit system has become back online,
and I'm really all interested.
Serving all your public transportation needs,
now you can go from West Glockesbury to Assault Beach,
or Assault Flats Beach Resort,
Lickety Split.
This has been a message from the
New Los Angeles City Board of Tourism.
Join my fucking Discord, assholes.
I can't wrap my little head around it.
It's too much.
There's too many chats,
and I don't know what to do.
Well, for you there are,
because if you're a mod,
if you have mod, then you see like all like 30 different,
all like 35 different zones.
But otherwise, you just see the one you're in,
and it's a little more manageable.
Sorry about that.
Whoever's editing this, could you edit out
that I said I'm the mayor?
I'm hypocrite.
I'm not the mayor of that place.
That's just a hearsay.
It's just a little dream of mine, actually.
There you go.
Is the mayor the same thing as the Lord of Ghosts?
Well, the Lord of Ghosts was elected mayor.
In a Democratic election that overturned the status quo,
and threw New Los Angeles City into a dark age
the likes of which have never been seen before.
That's true.
He got upgraded to the Lord Mayor of Ghosts.
Yes, yes.
Oh, that was cooler than being a Lord Mayor.
Much to all of our detriment.
Except for being a fewer president king.
A fewer president king, yeah.
Which is...
Ben, have you seen Full Metal Alchemist?
Yeah, yeah.
Do you remember that the guy...
The fewer king Bradley.
Yeah, but no, fewer president king Bradley,
except that King is just his first name.
Which is very confusing.
Wait, wait, wait.
I thought his title was Fear of King the whole time.
Okay, I knew his name was King.
I didn't know that he was...
How can you be a fewer and a president?
Those things are not the same.
His name is Fear of President King Bradley.
I don't remember him being president.
His name is King Bradley.
I remember him being Fear.
I remember him calling him Fear of King Bradley.
Well, this is in the Japanese version of Brotherhood, at least.
Okay, well, I watched the English dub of Not Brotherhood
of the original animated series.
And in that one, they just say Fear of King Bradley.
And I just thought his title was Fear of King,
which made perfect sense.
Frankly, I think you're fully shit, Digi.
I think that he's just Fear of King Bradley.
Well, I fucking remember the subtitles
and I was laughing every single time
I saw Fear of President King Bradley.
Ben, remember that boot?
Okay, way back in the day, Ben and I acquired
an illicit copy, an illicit copy
before all of FMA had come out in America.
I bought a DVD of...
It was like translated to Chinese
and then translated from Chinese to English
by a non-native English speaker.
It was incredible.
No, you know what it is.
Those were always Babelfish.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Winry.
Somehow, the way that they transliterated Winry's name
had a fucking X in it.
Okay, that's true, but that wasn't even just it.
In every single episode,
Gluttony was Blatney.
That's how they translated that.
And Winry's name was different every episode.
It was a different name.
There's some mix of stuff going on here.
Okay, did it have the phrase Ohio State
in there randomly a whole bunch?
I don't remember.
When you translate the English word O, like OH,
through Babelfish back and forth,
it becomes Ohio State.
And one time I watched an illicit copy
of the Death Note Live Action movie,
and that kept popping up,
and that's how I knew it was Babelfish
that they used to translate it.
This was before I knew anything about computers and shit,
but I'm sure that it was what we're talking about.
There were online translations were done or something,
because there was all kinds of characters
stuck in there in weird places and stuff.
Did you buy this DVDs from one of these
random Chinatown stores?
This one was actually straight up from eBay.
This was from eBay, I remember buying it.
Did I guys ever tell you guys about
illegal and really weirdly fucked up DVDs
me and my family bought and watched
when we were in Africa?
Ooh, that sounds interesting,
but no, I don't think so.
Well, we drove into the city one time,
the city of Kampala in Uganda,
and fuck, the idea of really slow traffic,
really gassy air, went to a grocery store,
and when we get back to our car,
we're sort of like behind the store,
and there's a guy on a motorcycle
with a big like duffel bag type of thing
filled with those little paper sleeve DVDs.
Filled with them.
As far as I can tell, this is like 80%
of what the third world is.
It's just guys selling bootleg DVDs
behind stores.
Go on, go on.
The collection was comparable
to those Walmart $5 DVD bins,
where it's like, wow, it's a giant bin,
but the giantness of the bin is just to obfuscate
the fact that it's the same movies over and over again,
but there's more variety.
But what we started noticing, and again,
they were all in those like paper sleeves,
is that some of them had errors on the printing.
It's not like they were hand drawn.
They were actually like professionally printed.
They were just, okay, so, okay,
it had the mid-90s live action version
of Disney's 101 malations.
And it was the right font, malations.
Everything was correct.
The font was exactly as the actual poster is,
but it was just 101 malations.
Something hit on wrong.
We just assumed, okay, so every time there's a printing error,
they ship it to the third world, makes sense, right?
Yeah, okay.
How do you get that printing error?
How do you get an error where it's just the wrong letter?
I mean, one way is that you just have like foreigners,
people who don't speak English,
like hastily typing out these things
and just resell them quickly
on the black market in one day.
I imagine that these printings happen in like factories, right?
Don't they just mass produce the DVDs?
Like how the fuck are you...
That's a hell of a typo to me.
It's a shame that I didn't...
It's a hell of a thing not to spell check.
I never got on a podcast sooner
because I did, I know I've forgotten
about plenty of the typos that I saw,
but there's a lot of various things
about these disks that I remember.
So like we went home and started watching them
and I don't remember what movie it was
where we first saw this, but halfway through the movie,
like we just started seeing like black orbs
appear at the bottom of the screen,
like the movie was being eaten away.
Is this a creepypasta?
No, no, it's just it's people's heads in the theater.
Yeah, does Ben drown in this story?
There was live filmings of...
Yeah.
Were the black orbs hyper realistic?
It was just the shape of people's heads
because it was people's heads.
So that's the issue right there.
What had been done is these people had filmed theaters
with people, you know, these were secondhand filmings
and then they printed these sleeves
and put them on DVDs and sold them on mass.
Not all of them were like that.
Some of them were, some of them weren't.
It was really weird how that works.
I'm quite familiar with these because of the fact that
my dad, for whatever reason,
in spite of the fact that my dad was very
against us torrenting movies
because of it being illegal,
he nonetheless would buy
the vast majority of his movies from
a guy who would sell bootleg
movies out of the back of his car
and also bootleg suits.
This dude would just come to the dealership
my dad works at and just sell suits
and DVDs and just random stolen
and or bootleg shit.
And he would sell these for $3 a pop
and I'm like, Dad,
if you want to buy an illegal movie,
you can get it for free through torrenting
as opposed to paying $3 for it.
Is your dad just like, feels better
spending some amount of money as opposed to nothing?
Well, I just don't see it as untraceable.
So, it's interesting that
because like,
I mean, Dad's buying
illegal stuff but like
not having a problem with it because my dad
occasionally he would come
with like a hard drive
and he says he knows a guy
who I also know who he is.
He's not like a secret guy.
He's not even like a criminal.
He's just like a normal person and he's like
he'll just like have a
huge amount of like
newly released films
on a hard drive
or like a big lot of music.
You know, just give it to my dad
and you know, dad would be like, yeah,
got all these movies now.
He had a Plex account that he just has
like he had his own server and he would upload
like insane amounts of movies
and shows and shit to his
Plex server and then just give the
information to all of his friends
so we could all just access the server and watch
whatever. That's fascinating. It's pretty cool.
When I went to college, they had
like the thing in place where like we're on campus.
They shut it down so you can't torrent.
They like close that down. But what we did
have, I forget the name of it, there was
an in-house torrent or operation
running where on the local network
of the school, the College of New Jersey
FYI, it's been shut down
tragically now, but there was something
and I knew the people who were running it.
Wait, the college has or the network has?
Select students at the school
ran a network
on the school network.
There was a border set up so that you couldn't
torrent outside of
within the school, but what you could do
is someone could set up a server within that network
on the campus and then
people, if they had access to that thing
you could download from those people
and it always struck me similar to
the scan-lating crowd, it's like
who are these heroes
who just make it their hobby or their job
to make these things
accessible to the rest of us.
I was in a scan-lating group for a while.
Scan-lating is one thing.
People can't read that, you got to translate it.
But even beyond that, just these people
who want to just get movies
and just hold them on a hard drive
what's in it for them?
Being able to talk for my friend
Donsan being able to talk about the stuff.
Could I literally get pussy
by doing this? Is that what I want?
I think I could.
You easily could if that's what you're going for.
My friend Donsan was really into pussy.
He just wanted to talk about these movies
with his friends.
If you're in a community of
piraters or scan-laters or what have you
it's a thing.
It's the same reason people do the coordinate harassment online.
You accrue social capital
in whatever context
you're working in.
It gives you a fucking vain and cheap sense of purpose.
It's the same reason that people send death threats.
It's pretty comparable I'd say.
What?
I'm saying it's a pastime
like any other.
You spend your time in it with people
and you form bonds of camaraderie
and you build social capital and everyone
it's great.
It's just a way to
not just that but also for me
when I got into scan-lation
and I was just doing proof reading so like
basically
I don't know what that was about.
What he's trying to say is that
that same kind of social capital
is why people form hate groups online.
People on the internet
are bored and have no sense of purpose.
They'll do fucking anything that gives them affirmation.
You won't get any pussy at all
from just telling someone to kill themselves online.
Unless you've got a girl
sitting right next to you
and it's like a rape group
well
you know?
Do you mean a rape list
like on Dick's website?
Yeah.
Just maintain a rape list.
Yeah. That's true.
Turn my rape list guys. Here's the link.
By the way I did have more things to say about
Ugandan bootleg DVDs
but I don't know if it's that funny
but I don't know.
Go for it dude.
Just go for it.
What does that mean?
Well I guess
if you have a word document that at the top says
women to rape
is it too rape?
Is it have been raped?
What metrics
are we tracking?
I believe that the
8chan threading question literally just said
rape list and then just was pictures of women.
Well there you go.
There you go.
I don't know what a rape list exactly is
but we're going to find out
in this episode of the Procrastin's podcast.
Oh boy.
We're tackling the hard questions.
This one video game you
should not 100%
Incidentally
that guy who made the rape list eventually found
out about what it had caused and apologized to Dick.
Yeah I heard about that.
I heard about that.
Davoo tell us more about Ugandan Knuckles please.
Yeah.
Well
okay there is
for whatever reason
even though I've never actually seen all of
the Lion King from start to finish
I just never got the ground to it
more of I've seen the Lion King 2
for some reason we just decided to buy from this little
double bag the Lion King 3.
Oh okay.
Speaking of the Lion King
today we were watching Princess Mononoke
and Kaze leans over to me and she's like
this song is exactly like that song from
the Lion King and I'm like
which song from the Lion King
and she's like
you know the Lion King
song and I'm like
so I don't know what she's talking about
so I say
I'm not that familiar with Lion King
it was my least favorite Disney movie as a kid
because I don't like animals
and she just stares at me and goes
fuck you
Wait what song was she talking about?
I don't know
I was thinking about
I was thinking about all the songs and Princess Mononoke
it was some background music
there might have been some background noise
I'm not sure
remember when Mufasa's ghost
comes and gives Simba guidance and shit
and there's all that mysterious
ambiance music and he's like I am your father
yeah there might be something there
same voice actor actually
Jamesville Jones that's right
I didn't even intend that
I was just saying that
so if you ever want to know
how the third movie after Princess Mononoke
Lion King 3 Return of Simba
we're in Africa
we're super bored we'll never find a way
we'll just watch some DVDs
this movie takes place in Africa
so it was probably pretty appropriate
you'll never find a Dway
here's what happened
we put in the movie
Memes Counter 2 Airhorn
we did it first
the Lion King 3 Return of Simba
uh oh
it's The Flower of Oz
which is a 2D animated movie
about the lion
the cowardly lion and his
side story before he found the yellow brick road
funnily enough I had actually seen that
movie before but it was well I guess I'm watching it again
so after I watched it
I can confirm that the Lion King 3 is not
a movie that exists
whoa that's fascinating
they had one and a half
there's Lion King 2 Simba's Pride
and then there's Lion King 1 and a half
I was going to say where did Simba go
that he needed to come back
apparently outside of North America
it is known as the Lion King 3 Hakuna Matata
oh okay
this was not called Hakuna Matata
it was advertised with like
you know um I think it was actually just
the uh the stuff that was
the Lion King 2 where it's like scars like
sun or whatever the fuck like that
so it's just the Lion King 2 that's what it was advertising
by the way just FYI that is
canonically not Scar's son
you know the guy who looks exactly like Scar
in every way and clearly should just be his son
canonically he is just another lion
no relation
don't worry it'll be tough when I tell you what happened
when we looked at the you know at the sleeve
so we're like okay so
the logo clearly says the Lion King 3
but then I look at it for like
more than a second and I realize
I mean I would have noticed this as an adult
probably but as a kid I didn't notice it
the actual cover art
is the Lion of Oz
it has the Cowardly Lion in 2D animation
and like the girl that he meets
and I'm like oh so it's
the Lion of Oz cover art but with the Lion King 3
logo
and then I flip it back right I look at the back
of the sleeve and it's got
um it's got like the new
Lion King 2 characters with that
okay I typed Lion of Oz
into Google and I completely
appreciate why this would be
mistaken for the Lion King
it looks like Simba he looks like Simba I can see him here
I mean he looks like Simba but also
kind of looks like the art style for that one
fucking animation that inspired the E meme
yeah I mean
the white lion or whatever his name is
I mean this is like
I mean yeah the fonts and the character design
this is like the equivalent of like
you know what's that company
that does all the like
the rib off what it is
rat a toying in little panda fighter
what do you mean like
I can't remember the name of that company
they did snakes on a train
oh god
and they also made Sharknado but like it's not
the asylum
that's a great people
but dude on the back of the sleeve
it shows like the new
the new young hipster
snake on a train
and the other
the other Lion King characters right
the back of the sleeve shows Lion King art
and it has a back of the blurb
right has like a blurb on the back
for the Lion King 3 right blurb says
what
happened to the cowardly lion
before he found the yellow brick road
and I was like oh
they just somehow
like
mashed up two different movies like completely
in every possible way
we also had this
we also had like a DVD this was like a DVD
in a plastic case for Cheaper by the Dozen
if you know that movie
is that the one with Steve Martin
yeah it was funny though
is that you know how like the back of DVDs
will have lots of symbols like the rating symbol
or like the MPAA symbol
this DVD just had like all the symbols on it
which row after row
after row after row of like every possible
symbol and it even had multiple
ratings it had an R rating
a PG rating and a G rating
and it was really weird
it depends on which subtitle track you chose
man there was lots of weird things
I probably could have like just made a whole podcast
just recounting these memories but
we also thought like these
hang on, hang on
did you just post an image and I have a problem
with it
we're not an image podcast you guys
Kermit is a frog
and then Fuzzy Bear is a bear
none of the three in the middle at the bottom there
they're not mouses
show notes link I guess
please
this reminds me of
a phenomenon that I don't know
if any of you will be familiar with
but are any of you familiar with a
genre I guess called
Pooh's Adventures of
what?
a genre of Pooh's Adventures
it is called Pooh's Adventures of
or Pooh's Adventures of X
and it is a
okay I think it was popular maybe
a decade ago or a little less
like it enjoyed a brief surge
like a weird surge in popularity of lots
of people doing it and like a little community
kind of like the fucking
pony analysis community it was like
this little niche community of people all doing
the same thing and what they were doing
was taking footage
from Winnie the Pooh
movies and splicing
them into other Disney movies
or games or like
footage from Disney World Rides or just anything
or
they didn't have to just be Pooh but mostly it was Pooh
whatever they would take these other characters
or Pooh characters and splice them into
other movies and make it a movie
about Pooh experiencing
the story of the Lion King
or Snow White
or like some fucking
point and click Disney CD-ROM adventure
or something
I want to see one of these
I will
how long would one of these be
like how long would this be
like the length of the full movie
but longer because there's Winnie the Pooh footage
who is in there
it's like a
Pooh character reacting to
anything
that happens
yeah
and it's like the idea is just
making it
yeah
this
no look this is a really deep
rabbit hole actually
and like it bears more
explaining
I can't do it justice on a podcast
there's a
there's more to it
there's wikis or there were wikis
where people where there would be
there were character lists
and people would have to basically
people would jockey for the
rights to use certain sets of
character and like two groups were not
allowed to use the same character like one
character would be claimed by one group
who is enforcing
the claims here
it's just a zeitgeist I guess
I googled Pooh's Adventures of
what I'm finding is like all these movie
covers and then like it's like a
Toy Story 3 cover and then just like
it is filled with like characters
from like other cartoon properties
like Pooh and I don't know
the fucking Looney Tunes and
Gronk you know
I don't
I'm pulling up the Pooh's Adventures wiki
oh my god there's like a hundred of them
oh no there's more
there's more like
I love me some way of the Pooh
how convincingly made are they
they're not like okay
like the Pooh
segments will just have no sound and just
have like some
badly fonted some badly
typeset text over it
are there any good ones
no it's sincere like
they'll take the silent Pooh footage
and put it in and put
some text at the bottom
giving them a new line as though
Pooh is saying like wow
Maleficent sure is a scary witch or something
you cannot be understated
when Nate said that it's like
movie posters with a shitload of characters
it's like a hundred characters every poster
I'm seeing Pooh's Adventures of Freddy
got fingered with like some
like Dr. Phil, Barney, Panty and Stockings
some of them are probably tongue and cheek
like especially the later ones
but many of them are sincere
this is fascinating
my question is Ben
are there any good ones
was anything good ever made
I will
there is this little cabal
or there was this little
cabal of four dudes
they were headed by this guy
called Benny the Beast
and there were a couple other ones
whose names escaped me
it doesn't matter
but they were called Lion King Heart Fantasy Films
and they evolved the format
much like
much like all of us evolved and grew
outside of the bounds of Pony Analysis
they too
these
sort of
these guys
they were doing Pooh's Adventures
and they would do other adventures
they did like a snow whatever
eventually they started inserting their OCs
into it as well
and then eventually
they started making movies that were just
about their OCs in other movies
are those good
no but they are more
interesting because these are like
these are like specific people
and I mean
okay I dug into this a while
back
and I had
okay
the saga of Lion King Heart
Fantasy Films is kind of
okay
I want to talk more
I want to talk more about it in the future
I feel like I'm not prepared to
a lot of info about it
Ben stop doing comics
stop doing physics
stop doing anything just become a full time
internet level six bottom of the iceberg
researcher and make of
lectures please
I would be happy with that
there are plenty of people who do that already
this is gonna
this will have to be in the show notes
this image I just shared because
I can't stop staring at it
it's blowing my fucking mind
so this is
Mintchi33's
Anti-Poo's Adventures
team
and it's just an image of
like 12 characters this person likes
but what's really fascinating about it
is that it's the most girl internet
thing I've ever seen
it's like all either
really obscure old western cartoons
or
some of it's like Winx Club and shit
and then there's like a bunch of pre-care characters
and a common writer character mixed in
and like
I just
I'm trying to picture
someone who even knows
this is exactly like that scene
in Tales gets trolled where they do the group pose
and they all get like the
the title like you shadow the awesome
the emo the annoying etc etc
that's what this is
I'm just really
I read that as the brain
that some one person has this set
of characters they like because it's so
weird and diverse
I mean this is just everything
from everything they've seen
this is a kid and this is all of their shows
I haven't even seen some of this stuff like what the hell is the damn
elephant thing from
Mumfy
I'm not familiar with Mumfy
Im not familiar with Pam
so in the middle
of the video
is this
one like
Akari Sakura
is apparently from JullBett
he's a long running
running little girls show that not a whole lot of people
know
Doesn't look like it's along the lines of like pre-cure and shit like it airs in that kind of time slot
So you oh wait no, I'm looking at common. You really should look
Right or I'm really curious
The common writer would probably be like she has a brother and she's seen common writer
I mean common writer wizard is yes, it's it's an entire series
He is the main character of common writer wizard, which was the the 2012 common writer show Wow
I wonder if this person
Like actually lives in ship because like common writer airs again in the same block as pre-cure
And I think Jullepet might be there too
So it's possible that she just like watches this whole block every morning. Also. Do you like that?
Do you like the fucking Cinderella is the stealth expert?
Appropriate at all
That like transformation is that the logic? I don't understand
Well, she has tiny feet. Oh for sneak in right?
No, she has tiny feet dude
That's why she wears tiny slippers that don't fit any of the other maidens and the king make sense make sense
Still and she's got her fairy godmother that can like turn vegetables into things for her. Yeah, that's good
Um, I don't have enough information about Vivian to figure out where she's from
I don't
Guys we're going down a rabbit hole here
I mean this talking about I mean I could we could probably go on a talk
We could probably go on to discuss poofs adventures of indefinitely. There's there's no shortage. That's true
There's just they're just they just never end
They just get better and better. Well speaking of crazy funny things that are very makes me laugh a lot
I have a topic to bring forth
I have just very recently
I would have said like within ten minutes of record the starting to record this episode
We had to wait a while as there's more like 40 minutes
But I just finished watching the very last episode of Tim and Eric's awesome show. Oh hell. Yes hell
Yes, even I haven't watched every episode. That's awesome. I
Enjoy Tim and Eric. It's good. They make me laugh. Have you seen the billion dollar movie? Oh
I haven't yet. Oh, that's the billion dollar movie. They're like to
Horses
Running in the way
Always thought about keg and phantom when I heard two horses. There's still time. There's still time horses
The thing I haven't actually got yeah, we got to work that in soon soon work that into the max revive agreed
But like I was I was watching it and it's like some parts aren't that funny some parts don't really land
That's like all of it really gives me a lot of funny ideas
Like I I really want to crank it like put a staple my green screen to the wall and just do silly faces
I just I just really want to do that and I have the ability. Yeah, this is sort of like inspiration
comedy like because I've always loved like
You know the goofy the goofy stuff. I sometimes get bogged down when writing scripts
That I have to like make the jokes be smart or have something to do with something and I
I'm watching Tim and Eric. I realize I don't have to I can go back to my roots
I can go back to my YouTube poop days and see and see all of this this
It's it, you know, it's it's based on some sort of observation
So it sort of makes sense, but it is like
It's just really creative and I love it
But I feel I feel so like into making film
Right now. Yeah having having finished, you know, what I what I love about Tim and Eric is that even though I?
Didn't really watch it at all growing up because it was like too much for me
Every show they did
The stuff in it is just so fucking out there that something will just like get into your subconscious at some point like I can remember
Like I only ever saw a few episodes of Tom goes to the mayor and a few episodes of Tim and Eric
But from each of them I have like it like vivid memories of like one line
Like in the first episode of Tom goes to the mayor
I just remember good Tom Brady got his kiosk
Things were finally looking up for him and that's it
I never I never really liked Tom goes to the mayor and so I didn't check it. I didn't really get into
A awesome show when it aired but then at some point someone showed me billion dollar movie
And I really liked it and I was like, hmm. Maybe I maybe I wrote Tim and Tim and Eric style off too soon
I wonder it. Sorry. It's just it's okay. Whoever just linked to this
Davoo linked part of this comment doesn't need to be in the show nose
This is like a like we I think we've talked about this before
But it reminded me of the new storyteller and I'm wondering what a lecture could be done on the new storyteller
If there is enough that would be
The great that would be like the biggest fucking research dump ever though. So, okay, what I linked though
You'd have to watch a lot. Yeah, so
Do we have to talk about more images? I mean, that's just not the whole time you guys were talked about all this giant
Collision I was not do don't look at me scrolling through my deep my Twitter to find this this old gem
I found I'll just read you one pass. Okay. I'm gonna read one of the panels
Here is the panel. I'm gonna read it in the way. It's lined up
Sunset shimmer says any ideas Brock. Why don't we could split up and look for the green genie that way
Thomas as in the tank engine point taking Brock
Sunset shimmer do Susie and autumn ride with swindle Ellie you Amanda Mindy and Sally search the parks
We'll meet back at Pioneer Square Square Ellie says, okay
So it's a bunch of Thomas the tank engine characters some magical girl characters
I don't recognize MS paint modified some transformers Brock from Pokemon Sunset shimmer and the fucking
The fucking parrot from a lab. Oh, yeah. Yeah. The magical girls are all from ojimaja Dora me
Okay, heavily modified their mermaids right now. Oh, there's also Jackie from fucking cyber chase in there
Yeah, I wish I was like I allowed myself to
Express myself this freely, you know, this this thing. I know what you mean. This is this is Chris Chan
I look at this and I think this looks like solitude to me. It's with the same
I feel that same that same like
yearning for like just doing something on this level without worrying about myself image, but I
Yeah, the thing is I think that if any of us tried this, it would actually be amazing. Yeah
I
This is competence. I mean like we all thought that when the only rise tails gets trolled
It sounded like the greatest story ever told. Yeah
the
Yeah, no like hippo if you just fucking took all these fucking magical girls and transformers and Thomas the tank engines
Combine them into a into a gripping narrative. I mean hell
Well, remember that comic that fucking Gibb did with like twilight and you know remember that thing
Oh
Yeah, that was like one of the first deviant art things in my in my my little pony drawing of ponies career
Which lasted like a year or something a really funny interesting fascinating and also ultimately tragic
Case of one of these kinds of creators who's actually good at their medium is elvin earthworm with his creation of Super Mario Bros
It was a Z. Oh, he was back. Is he how are things going? Oh, no, this is the problem. So yeah, wow
Dude who didn't he yeah, yeah, dude who yeah made one of the it was in the height of the sprite animation on Newgrounds phase
And he was the best one
He just took Mario and Luigi super star saga sprites sonic advanced sprites and DBC sound effects and a million people were doing that
But what was unique about elvin earthworm is that he's actually like he got really good at animation
Yep, it had a really it has a great cinematic a style a lot of punch and it's just just as a quick aside
Just a quick aside. I have a rant about like
This and also various other things like Minecraft animations that I've seen in a similar in a similar way
It's my problem with the the thing the reason I never liked it was because it's sprites
But it's animated in flash and the sprites don't
conform to a grid they they move
Diagonally and it looks terrible and I hate it. Oh, yeah, it's cute. It's quaint. I
Agree, I agree. I mean that does bother me, but like
Considering the kind of like this is this is like Newgrounds like early naughty. I mean, yeah
So it's just like as a kid. I see stuff like that and I it was just you know it
Well with Minecraft animations, there's a similar thing where instead of like animating pixel
Movements they have like a jut like a mouth jutting out like in the in the Minecraft model
Like it's supposed to be his fate his head is supposed to be a square, but of course
They don't do that
They they made models so that they could have movable lips and teeth and stuff and it juts out in a way that would not work
I mean, you know does not conform to the size of the pixels in the game
And it just sort of annoys me because it's like you're breaking the rules
It's not mine when I'm watching Minecraft porn
It really pulls me out of the experience when she's got like clearly defined triangle exists and shit like that's really that's not
Come on that doesn't exist that's not a real thing. No, well, they have they have cuboid somebody
Has to be cubes I agree
Hey, Tim and I continue unless DeVue is gonna finish this. Oh, yeah
The tragedy of Alvin earthworm is that because he takes his shit seriously, right?
Which is great because it gives it gives super marabrosi and in sincerity you couldn't you couldn't imitate the problem
Is that he's worried about it's like quality consistent consistency?
So he finally came back after like a three-year hiatus his plan was to remake the show rather than just continue it
And his plan was also to have like a total of 45 episodes each out of 15 like 350
episodes yeah
Considering it was taking him a year to make each one
It's like you're not gonna finish it obviously and like even 10 years ago
I even PMed him saying like I think that's too many episodes
You should stop at 15 because 15 was gonna be end of this one arc and like sure the point is that every episode is more
Bombastic and fast in at 15 that'll be the perfect level
He really should have come back and made episode 9 and just made five more episodes after that that would have been done
He would have been finished, but he wanted to go back and remake episode one
That's a mistake. Yeah
Stuff makes me really sad like he really they have such such like talent, but they overdo it instead of instead of well
It's not even like that
You know the man spend their time making something that isn't like their own original IP
Yeah, like to to not have like I don't know. Yeah, just the fucking
Trapped in f**king giga-paws
Look dude, this is not your magnum opus. Yeah, it's not yeah
Yeah, and then like he did the remake of episode one
I believe three years ago, and he hasn't continued it since so I mean
Yeah, I just think a good really like never you don't redo stuff like don't redo anything
Why would you ever waste your time finish it and then do it better next time?
This is my whole remake things
Why would you ever waste your fucking time remaking something that already exists when you just make something new and the reason is so that you can
Sell things with like that same name, but Alvin ain't making no fucking money on this shit
So just finish your goddamn series and move on
So like you can just make the same like you can just make a different version of the same thing like
some people I
read this review of
Princess Mononoke that was in like an old magazine where this guy was accusing it of just like being the same thing as
Naska but like but with less heart or something
To me that's just like that be a meme of like heart and no heart anyone know this okay nevermind sorry
To me it was like well the thing about Naska is that it is not a functional film
Like the original manga is is amazing and I mean the movies still holds up and is really entertaining
But like as telling the story that the that the manga was trying to tell it falls entirely
Flat of doing that whereas Princess Mononoke was just like let's take all those themes and all the stuff that I care about
Me being Hayao Miyazaki and be like let's make a movie out of that
You know so like something that functions completely and coherently as a film
And then he hasn't had to tackle those themes again because he he did it you know he just
Made it something that made more sense in film form
Yeah, and it's as a film it is way better than the Naska movie
You know and I granted I would you know the Naska manga is also great
I would even say Mononoke just by being tight and
Perfectly crafted is in many ways better than the Naska manga even if it's not as broad sure but like
It's just like yeah
You could just take these concepts and do something better considered instead of literally
Recreating the same thing with better graphics because that doesn't add anything to the meaning
Graphics if you're fucking modern alphadream
It would that yeah, that's true
Significantly worse graphics
You know like the the conundrum of the author or of the of the creator of any medium
Who's just like you know you're making your thing you look back like you're an Andrew Hussie or whoever and you're like man
My early stuff man like I'm writing that I'm doing the same series for so long
Oh, I don't really like that beginning. I gotta fix that. I gotta fix that
What what a terrible ends like we just have to fight against that it's it's a and I know what that feels like too
I know what that feels like to I've always hated that which is why like I have made a point aside from like one or two
Yeah, but very clearly. Yeah, I should get rid of I always try to keep every video. I have live
So the people can see like where I came from and I trust that they have
You know the mental capacity to understand that it's an old video and if they do get upset then I don't have to worry about it
Because there's hopefully with regard. I mean about for me
I feel like maybe I don't get that as much like with my comics
I'm thinking of because like when I finish a comic I feel I look at it and I think oh my god
What a disaster it sucks sure. I hate it
I want to be done with it and never think about it again. So I actually feel very I don't I don't feel the urge to read
I think that it sucks, but I don't feel the urge to redo it. I feel the urge to to throw it away and
Never come and then get it as far away from me as possible
I feel the same way you know
It's like when you take a shit and it's like wow that smells really bad. I want to like be far away from it
Like that's me with art. Yeah
Like any time an artist like looks at their own work at things like wow my technical abilities are so much greater
I could recreate this with better technical ability. It's like dude. How much of what you like
Do you like for its technical?
Like you know quality like yeah much of what all of us like stuff that is like for me
The answer together in an hour almost yeah, just I think most people are probably I think most people are probably the same
Even if they don't know did somebody say John Tron I
I think I think
Probably more I think a lot of people probably
Think that like technical ability matters
More than it actually does them. I think they probably are affected less affected by technical ability of a work
Then they maybe think I don't know if you work if your work is not successful
It's for one of two reasons either at its core
It is not good or you didn't market it enough like I think that if something is good and it fails
It's not because the work wasn't wasn't of a high enough like technical quality
It's because just the right people didn't find out about it and you just got
That's kind of part of what I talked about in this how they market it series
It's something I've fucked up on throughout my whole career is that like I've made stuff
That I just thought like oh nobody's gonna watch it because the lighting is not good
And it's like meanwhile like paranormal activity is like one of the most successful movies of all time the production
It was made on like $2,000 and it looks like shit and most of it is still images of something in the dark
But like it was successful because they put like a well an investor who you know
So like it was it was made on the shoestring budget and sold to an investor who decided to put it in
Test theaters continually of increasing size and when it got good responses from those test theaters
He released it wide and eventually made a thousand sequels because like if you can find something profitable that takes no money to make
You were talking about looking at your old stuff and like being afraid of it trying to destroy it
What one thing I had to go and looked us up to confirm it still true one thing I respect
deeply is that the game theorist's channel still has fully listed and available at the bottom the like
Three or so dozen like clips of young matpat in like high school plays that were
That were uploaded on the channel before game theory started those are still listed
I don't have the courage to have my videos from 2008 listed the digi brony videos are unlisted
70% of everything Jesse's ever created has been deleted, but in matpat
He the king is the spirit of you
Interrupt his searching at all like
The reason I hid all my pony stuff was that like it was like I had like 10 anime videos
And then an endless sea of pony videos and I was like this is not gonna help me market myself as an anime channel
You know
Like yeah, and and also YouTube is really weird about like when you
Relist I don't think this happens necessarily with unlisted videos
But sometimes I've had videos that I originally had unlisted and then I published them and it made them publish as new videos
Oh, I'm afraid of that happening
And that's why you say those were you say those were originally have they been unlisted the whole time and then you made them public
The the the ones I've seen that happen with yes because I actually take the risk to the public service
For everybody April Fool's a public service for everybody
I do you guys watch the creators studio channel on YouTube?
Because it is the thing that we've always wanted of where YouTube directly tells us what they're doing
And I feel like they're oddly unknown among lots of YouTube people, but anyway, they actually just
Yeah, by MKBHD sometimes will mention they just talked about this very issue where yes
If you've had a video unlisted for a long time if you are making it public for the first time
It will treat it as a new video and then it'll you know do all the things yeah
I mean my pony videos were originally listed so assumably. Yeah, those that have that problem. Yeah. Yeah, but
Yeah, yeah, I would kind of want to feud with those guys TBH
I want to feud with them with creative studio
Beef now if you're a PCP fan go leave shitty comments
No, no, no, I don't encourage that at all. No, no, no one's gonna do that. I hope not
I want to start
Yeah, yeah, they're all they're all to do it. Here's my here's my
We tried to start beef with the pizza party podcast like six months ago
I didn't even we didn't we did not try nearly hard
Look, this is a real complaint with the with the with this with this channel the creator studio
I haven't mentioned this up to this point, but here's here's what it is
My complaint is this these people on the channel act as if they have earned the like something like
70,000 subscribers they currently have through like some sort of like skill or like resilience or or where with all of their
Own when these people are the first party
Publishers of YouTube news
They are the sole source of what the hell YouTube is doing it like I am contractually
Obligated as a youtuber to be subscribed to you
So the fact that these people take joy from like yeah, we're doing so well as a channel. No, fuck you. You didn't earn shit
You are you by the way these gems of information by fucking
It is they think if they think like they've accomplished exact somebody should be legally download them and then reupload them
And then that should get a
Call to harass their comment sections and like it's farce on this
I think you at some point are going to experience this paradigm shift when you hit a certain level of popularity
And a certain level of fan base because as it is your fan base is pretty well curated of only people who kind of get it
But if you intend to get like one
Like degree more popular where like what would you call an order of magnitude more successful?
You're gonna have several ghettos full of morons who support you and now you know how I can avoid that
What I have a I have a lot more patience for interacting with people now because
It used to be that all of it frustrated me
But now I realized that like
Almost everyone who like comes at anybody online. There's only two reasons. They would do it either. They're ignorant
They either they either don't actually know what you're doing or they are just like dumb and like they think what you're doing is bad
But if you explained it to them, they'll realize well, hang on Digi
That's assuming that you could never do anything wrong on your own
You didn't point out that you might legitimately be doing something wrong that is
Something wrong. That's fine. You can attack me for it. I would deserve that
But like what I'm saying is that like I used to just see people who were
Misunderstanding me or something or or talking shit and my thing was to just complain about it, but not respond
And now my policy is if someone like shits on me on Twitter
always respond because
Nine times out of ten they just misunderstood something
That's also kind of why Digi bro versus everybody exists because like right right most of the arguments are like someone comes on and like tries to argue
With me and I'm like, oh, well, that's not actually my stance. This is my stance and they go
Oh, well, then we agree and I go. Yeah, you would have known that if you knew my stance
But because you had assumed something else
You didn't know that
So like and they always end amicably like I haven't had a single argument on there that like ended in a shit fit, you know
So I just think it's a better way to resolve things
So when people have their fan base that gets out of control, it's because they don't respond to it
They don't interact with it. Yeah, like, you know, I mean, I just generally agree with that
And that's why I think that the format on your Digi bro versus everybody is is like a smart way because when you get someone in the call
To actually make their arguments about whatever it is
They really have to like present something of substance or else they look like right
But the problem is that happen like people come in and I say like what's your argument?
They're like this and then I'm like, well, why do you think that and then they're like, oh shit
I didn't realize that I don't even know like the last episode. I did someone was like talking about
Oh, your content has changed blah blah blah and I was like, what about my content has changed and the dude had like no real answer
And I was like, well, I mean if anything's changed
I mean, I've changed as a person so it might be that he was like, oh, I didn't think about it that way
I mean, the only thing about this I think is that this can't possibly like compensate for like all viewers
Like I'm not sure how much it could sway like public opinion
Did you like I was saying like like yeah, you're saying oh, I'll have to interact with the community when it's like it's big enough
That's basically what I'm saying the paradigm shift is going to be there's gonna be a moment where there's like more things
You have to watch yourself before you say I remember the last time this happened was when it was your most boring taste in anime
Vlog which wouldn't have been a problem to anyone at all
except for the fact that you name dropped a fucking anime every day and
There was this sudden reaction see what I what I should have done is after he made his video
I should have like
Called him up. I was deeply frustrated
You didn't just like address it directly and you just let the narrative sort of die there
That's the thing like I I used to get so frustrated that people were not understanding my point
And I'd be like that's their fault and now I'm just a lot more patient to just like not stop the argument until they get it
And I think it's just I'm a big believer. I'm a big believer in the idea that like
The I'm a bit I guess I'm a big death of the author guy
And I think that whatever whatever a viewer takes away from a work of art is is the meaning to them and like can the conveyance of meaning is
The author's responsibility and if something other than what was intended is is conveyed to the reader
Yeah, it's not the reader's fault. I don't think it's ever the reader's fault for misunderstanding
I kind of under I kind of agree, but I also feel like
I feel as though it's easy enough for you to just follow up
Like if the reader doesn't get it then just tell them what you meant and a lot of the times they'll go
Oh now I get it. Yeah, I see it happens to me every day
No, I'm arguing with what I've been doing lately is just like dropping these super spicy hot takes on Twitter
And then getting like shitloads of responses and then I just argue with all of them until they
Acquiesce basically like or get it. I I have been away from Twitter not because of that
But every time I come to you know, see what's going on see my notifications
See if anybody said anything and I see you with like a huge big thing and I'm like
Well, yeah, but like I just it just reminds me of things that have happened in in you know
Like the the sort of people that I have had arguments with and then I looked at my last notifications
I I redesigned survivor the Pokemon right thought he looked bad and like every reply was like fuck you
Yeah, and I was
Why would I stay here if if everyone's annoying I've been off Twitter for a couple weeks now
I just fucking I didn't know I I didn't know how terminal that cancer was until I got rid of it
Holy shit every day. I don't log into Twitter. It's like a victory
It's it's it's it's sort of
Dazzling when you when like I've awakened from a from a you know an eternal nightmare
And I just look back at like the the the fire that is like
Wow, I was in that I was there all the time guys about a magical phrase
I've found to so so part of the problem with arguing on Twitter is that like
Some the way I've always handled it is like the people who have a kind of reasonable or like they have an argument
I'll argue with them and those are the people that are easiest because you could eventually reach a point
But then there's the people who just say you're a fucking moron and like I never knew how to deal with those people
But now I figured it out. I just respond explain yourself and like it works because they they either have to now
Explain themselves or not and like so now they have to formulate an argument the only people it doesn't work on to the ones who say
You explain your point first, and I'm like I already did that was the original tweet was an explanation about what are you fucking talking about?
You know like and
Even the people who are really obstinate
They're often obstinate because they're in the heat of the moment
But those people will sometimes come back the next day and be like, yeah, I thought about it and like realize that was stupid
You know my tactic used to be for like for like
You know no argument insults
Tweets or like comments would just be to reply with no
And if they reply it again, I would just reply no
Fingers around my dick when the guy says no
You know, maybe I'm cynical, but I consider responding to most of these things a huge waste of time
No, it's really not because I convert people every day like every time I do this every time I hot take on Twitter
I change a bunch of people's fucking minds about shit, and that's what I want like that's my
Full argument it's that would the time spent okay?
I'm just talking about for my personal life with the time spent doing this
Possibly be better used on just making and I know I can't get like a full video out in the time spent
We'll make working on something that would just like
Isn't it you can reach you can reach 50,000 people kind of sure, but you can reach one person all the way
Yeah, did you explain? I mean, that's good. That's what like community outreach. Did you this is working for you?
There's definitely a place for engaging in like a one-on-one doing doing all this
Did you has worked for you because it's after
Three years of you letting stupid misunderstandings and bad communication fester. Why are you telling did why are you telling digi?
His situation that I've been there for a lot of it. I've been following it very closely for years
It's like I always knew why people were misunderstanding his shit or like not getting his content and
Oh, you always knew to do you had the answers all along is that is that it's not complicated did you's explaining it now?
It's not that hard. It's easy to get people to get it and
It's just a matter of you have to be willing to not give up on a person until they get it because if you
But what the reason that I've taken this stance is that what I realized is these people never go away
Yeah, they never disappear like but the
I mean you'll never convert them all you'll know
But if you can convert enough people that the people who who disagree are in the minority those people will eventually
Look like chumps and they will okay
Other than they won't want to be that way. Yeah, you know
I hear what you're saying, but like on my part of me is just thinking that like I think the best way to handle like
There's no way I can convert the numbers of people. I mean, I don't really have a lot of haters
But you know, that's exactly why it isn't really as relevant to you Nate
You just like make good videos you haven't like gotten that these made opinion shit fit things that it's not universal
I remember I remember in the t-bap days
Yeah, had kind of we had kind of a policy of like don't respond to comments basically. Yeah, that's right
And you know, I think I don't think that was wrong or the wrong way to do it or a bad idea
Like I think the idea was that like responding to comments like kind of puts you down in the muck like with the commoners
So this is a disagree between you and I I very much was of the opinion that like I don't want to engage with the people who are criticizing
The comments because that nothing good will come of it. Yeah was my thinking. I think I
don't know I
I
You know, I don't know. It's calm. I mean, I think okay here. Let me give the most milk toast boring answer
I think I see the validity of both sides of the argument. Okay
We're all winners here. I feel like I'm coming across like a big anti respond to people think it's like if people want to do that
That's fine. I like my my thought is like I could take the time to respond to everybody
But I think that I'm better use of my time is to like work and like lots of people will email me or send me a message
With like I don't know I get a lot of sincere comments on things or like personal messages that people don't want other people to say
I respond like people on my on my on my patron on my discord, you know in Twitter
Like I respond to everything that is clearly sincere that I've ever gotten and if those numbers inflate it
I might not be able to so you know, I miss you in the future take it easy
That's how I want to respond to comments. You have to decide first
We have to decide what is the goal and did you describe his goal pretty clearly? Yeah, basically shift
Where the consensus is to be in my favor, right?
That's been the goal of my all my content basically is like right convince people that
The whatever the consensus idea is if it does not jive with what I think then let me move people over to my side
It's not taking every hill. It's about winning the war net balance, but yeah, but that's that's how I think to and this is my approach
I'm trying to crowdsource the conversion. I'm not trying to do it all myself
I'm trying to get that ourselves here
That's I'm kind of
Kind of that's part of my goal, too
It's just that like and I think with your content you have such a very clear stance that it's easier
To have people who totally get you on your side like I think so for you you you have like
several key points that I think are broadly understood by your whole audience and I have a few of those like
Objectivity doesn't exist like that's something that I don't have to make that argument because literally if someone
Attacks me by saying like your reviews aren't very objective a swarm of my guys will just like jump on that dude
Right, and that's the kind of thing that would probably happen with you if someone was attacking like the core principles of what you do
But yours are just so well-defined and mine are so chaotic
And then also it's very contextual talking about okay does responding to comments put you down in the muck in the
Mire because like there's a pretty clear I think this is I just think it's inefficient. That's all I think there's a pretty
Yeah, unwritten unspoken set of rules and paradigms as to like what is proper conduct, right?
We always have this there's a pretty well your unchallenged consensus that's implicit in a lot of people's ideologies about
Punching up versus punching down
Hence why people suddenly found it controversial that did you would call out other content creators only once his sub count rose
Significantly before that he could call out anyone and no one gave a shit
But once did you was perceived as popular suddenly?
Oh, yeah wrong before that sure not fucking all and and also so it depends on how you respond to individual comments
And what kind of comments you respond to oh so for okay? Okay? No
Sorry, I'm sorry. No, no continue. I have a thing. I really want to say good
But this is my thing. I'm gonna say and then yes
So I had been witnessing a certain a certain like cultural mindset around to me that I wasn't into
This whole idea and I believe it was yeah
I I saw it starting a couple of years ago or a year ago or so this idea that oh
Davoo, you know, he doesn't make his own videos. He edits someone else's videos and this is a problem
He could get held back. He's not doing he's not like trudging out analysis videos like everyone else
He's not writing. This is a problem. He could end up cold and alone any day now
And so step one is to not just dismiss the argument dismiss the idea as just stupid
it comes from a place of logic and I get it and
I saw there was a person who confronted me on it like on a comment section and
Being a huge
Huge condescending prick about it saying shit like oh, this is going to stunt your growth. It's like okay, dude
Fuck off. I get that the internet has made people like he's making a lot of assumptions about your goals in life
Yes, I think people have gotten really used to things the internet the idea of people who make
Things all by themselves, but sure even on the internet. It's actually not that common for things that are actually really popular
Yeah, so but I knew that there's not that many people who are saying this yet, right?
It's not like I'm being inundated with it
And so I can't just make I can't just mount a giant like rebuttal to this
I have to wait for the right time
I mean all that really matters here is like like if he's saying this like all this is an entire argument hinges on
What are your goals if your goals are to become an independent video game analysis channel?
You are fucking up massively, but that's not I mean, I don't think that's a plan
So so on this
This is basically this was basically my tactical decisions. I made right?
Yeah, I was sensing hey some people are murmuring about this
And so I bet there's a lot of people who aren't saying it but they're on the fence about it, right?
People who would love to hear what I have to say my response to it, right?
And so I just have to be tactical there if I immediately jump out like being really defensive about it or really being
Argumentative about it. It'd make people think oh why you've been so defensive about it
There's only like a couple of people who've said this so far
So I just laid and wait and I remember specifically thinking if anyone else comments this to me
I'll I'll fucking I'll do that shit like that's when I'll like that's when I'll strike
So what happened was this one super ultra turbo shit posty troll guy who like is the worst troll of all?
Like commented the perfect model of this ideology, right?
He posted a comment on me, and he was a huge dick about it, and I'm like perfect
I will read this comment in a vlog and then very very
cordially and politely respond to it and
Like provide my case right and I'll look amazing and this whole ideology will look fucking
Retarded because this guy was being hugely like dickish about it, right?
And now I have the video the video is called
Response to everyone who thinks that working with another youtuber is bad something like that and now I just have that vlog in which
I perfectly make my case and I can just link that forever, and that's how I've pitch-shifted the fucking narrative
The subject of like responding personally to things okay, so so
There's this idea, and I think it's pretty obviously true that like you know
You if you've got a fan base if you're if you're popular on the internet or in anything
You know you've got your your body of fans
You know you have people that know you and follow you and maybe like what you're doing
But then there's the subgroup that is like your real fan like the people that will like the people that will actually
Support you in what you do like the people that that care enough to like you know, you know buy your book or or
You know yeah, patreon you or whatever it is
The people that would probably support you no matter what you were doing like that's like a small that's like the bottom
That's like the top ten percent of the top one percent of like the people and like a lot of those
Like those people a lot of them like sometimes you just reach someone on a real deep level with your stuff
But other times that kind of thing comes from like you know you had like you connected with someone on a personal level and you like
You know have like a real human connection due to whether it's just a fucking reply to a Twitter a tweet or I don't know
Maybe the conversation and on discord or anything that could happen. Yeah, and like so
That's
You know like you might grow you might grow your audience you might grow your audience numbers by like putting out like broad
Stuff and like big projects that get seen by a lot of eyes
But like getting that like you know getting like real support
I think to a certain extent it requires or or it's aided and abetted and bolstered by like making a personal connection and doing what I
Guess you might cut through as community outreach or you know just engaging with your fans
You feel that way and I also feel that for everyone. It's a matter of different strata of what you need because I
Ultimately like all of us has a world view and we're hoping to get as many people as much on our side as possible
And so like if you're but there's three different concerns really
There's like how many people can I reach how deeply can I reach those people and also?
Can I live my life while doing this?
You know not just monetarily, but like do the things I want to do in a case like Nate's I think it's healthy for Nate to not be
Like you know answering comments all the time and shit because Nate's got a regular-ass fucking job
He has to do on top of making videos and I think that freed up of that extra seven hours every day
Maybe you would have more time to talk to individuals and stuff because probably I
Don't know. I think you would probably get bored if all you were doing all day was nothing but working on videos
So but like in your situation
It's like there are other things and for me for a long time. It was a combination of I
first of all
If you're not feeling as though your basic need of like being
Understood by people and like fitting into society and like having a concrete purpose is met
It's a lot harder to then go and like
Communicate with others and and for me
I always felt like the outsider even when I was getting big because of the fact that like the anime YouTube
community never really accepted me and the fact that like
You know, even though I had all these subs
I was always like a weird odd man out like I was always the the last guy
Invited or informed kind of thing but like in the time once I you know got a relationship
And I feel like may
Understands me completely. There's nothing. There's no disconnect. You know, even with like some of my closest fans
There's always a disconnect because they know me as the guy who I am portraying myself as on the internet
And even with you guys, there's some level of like macho posturing that has to go on with a bunch of dudes in a group
You know, you know, but like if I have somebody
By having somebody who gets me all the way it's like that need for acceptance
I've I've got that and I don't need to fight for that now
So it's not it's not about like oh, I have to make ever make sure everybody understand on the internet gets me and accepts me
Now it's more like all right. Well, that's fine. I've been accepted now. I'm worried about it for their sake
It's no longer about like I want everyone to understand me because that will make me feel good
Now it's like I want everybody to understand me so that they get my message clearly and because my message is ultimately trying to help people to
You know to do the things that that have worked for me, you know, like it's it's I guess it's just less ego driven
It's less of like I've been right all along and you all should listen to me now
It's more of like hey guys if you listen to me, this would actually help you with your life and you'd be less depressed
Yeah, you know, so like let me help you with that
That's how I feel to about my content but on the subject of people understanding you I take it a couple steps further
Then then what you're saying because I believe that literally no one will ever fully understand me
Who is outside me and also I myself will never fully understand me either
And I can't predict what my response is going to be and so I've just accepted the the darkness of my existence
And I've made some degree of peace with it and it feels pretty okay as long as you're at peace with it
That's all that really matters. I agree. It reminds me of my brother Victor when
You know, he had long-standing depression and thoughts of suicide
But he he tried therapy he tried medication and none of it worked
And he just kind of came to terms with the idea that he just was depressed and that's who he is and once he accepted
It was no longer scary, I guess and I mean eventually he got into a loving relationship and now he's like happy
He's no longer like considering suicide, but like it was just like once he was
What if that crumbles for whatever reason, you know, you need a foundation. Yeah, well, I mean he found the foundation
Yeah, so far as realizing that like
This was just not something to be like the only thing that makes it scary
You know sure I think that I think the takeaway here is that he made he made peace with it like before he finding this
Yeah, yeah, okay. That's less. Yeah, like it was that he decided that he needed the relationship to save him from the depression
Yeah, it's that he realized that like this is not something curable
So if I'm gonna have to live with it anyways, then let's not get hung up on it
Like let's not spend all our time wallowing in the fact that I'm depressed and suicidal
Like I have to just live my life and just like let that be a part of my life
Yeah, I was able over the course of like five seven years just turn all of my mental disorders into my job
Very conveniently how that worked out. I don't I mean I've never been diagnosed with with clinical depression or anything
but I mean I thought
Yeah
I've had the same like you know leave the world really sucks and and even even if you're healthy and even if you don't have
Mental illnesses per se like you know the world's a dark place and things are gonna suck some time and you just you know
You got it. You gotta no matter who you are. You got to make peace with that and once you do it's not as bad
That's the one way to make it better is you got you got to make peace with that it sucks
That's something I kind of I touched on this a little bit in my land of the luster's video that like I think
One of the biggest problems with with people is that we all try to run away from trauma or like view it as something to be
Healed and it's like trauma is going to happen to you because like if you love anyone
You're gonna watch someone you love die. That's gonna happen to you and like so you unless you're lucky enough to die soon
That's yeah, I almost said that in the video, but I cut that line out cuz I thought I would scare too many people
But like yeah if if you if you know if you live you will experience trauma and like there is nothing that makes
The past not happen. There's nothing or even if something happens now
You have some yes
But the way I see it you can either run from it or learn from it. Hey cause a I like Lion King
I like Lion King. It's fine. Don't don't hate me
Yeah, that's Rafiki ah good old nigga Rafiki
Damn it. That was my best Rafiki impression
Is that the first nigga word that has been said
No, since we since we we implemented the nigga jar
That's two from hippo
If I referenced the job, but then you could get away with like hey just look at that nigga jar over there
He's gonna steal my wallet. I better walk on the other side of the street. You know, that's that's no good
That's no good. I can read between
Yeah, exactly none of you are pure I had I had a thing as to say about the comments
Comments that make me confront harsh truths about myself and make me sad and it sucks such as
That wasn't very funny. That's the comment that really gets me
When I know something wasn't good and I put it up anyway, and I was like no
They found out. They know they see it. It's when you kind of believe it
Yeah, it's when someone points out something that you believe to one degree or another
Believe it and like my reaction is always to try to explain it away
And at that point it becomes kind of a battle of wills of like that's true
Because a lot of the times I'll like someone will criticize me for something and then I'll like
Justify it and they'll go. Oh, well, I guess it's fine
But then like because I am smart enough to then run the rest of the scenario of like how the argument would have gone if they had
Been strong enough to fight me then I'll then get depressed
Realizing that they were right. They were just
What I have like
You know gone beyond that whole like
Reactionary like well, no, no, it's not it's not true
Like when I see a comment that is like tells me the truth and I'm like, yeah, man
I want to like I don't want to respond because I just don't care to involve myself with
Things like that but the way they phrase them like it's just a normal thing like these comments
Whether then like putting me down easy or not
There's this sense of like
They expect me to if I read it to respond in a defensive manner and to have an argument against them
And they're sort of preparing for that in the original sort of statement
And if I don't respond it like in reality, I'm humble and I'm like, yeah
I agree, but I don't care to say that but I feel like I have to say that
So that I can appear humble because that's the truth and they they they they like if it's just left
Responded to that makes me look publicly like I
disagree
Let me give an example
Let me give you I just had a great example of this the other day confirms everything you're saying and it was um
This is on the on the pod D cast there was a commenter who just respond like I there's been a little controversy lately about a little bit
Of convenience happening in one piece. We won't get into it, but someone just said simply something along the lines of
Nate like you're fucking wrong. You noodled armed fat faggot and I thought
You know, I just thought to myself, yeah, I guess I could hit the gym a little more
Better if I just admit to it and cop to it like if it's something I agree with and I
Because for me it it helps to put like it's like if I don't respond
It's because I'm afraid of having to change to confront it
But that's absolutely what it is. You know what? I want them to be respond though
Sometimes if I like actually say like you're right, I will then go change it because like
100% 100% of the internet is people being afraid to say man that makes me sad. You're right
Yeah, that's true. That's true. What happened. Okay, so recently I ended up
We're turning the comments on my roller coaster Tekken one versus three video back on again thinking, you know a year after that
Stupid undertale video I made happened
I like close the comments on that and then un reopen the comments a year later and fucking no one commented
So clearly that's a safe bet reopens comments and RCT video the comments just continue as they always had
Today what I fucking cursed myself with the algorithmic eternity
I don't are they as shit as ever are they yeah, they're they're just as bad as ever
They're it's literally like 2015 and we'll never stop fucking happening. I god damn
Interesting I still get I mean this makes sense because it's not out
But my I'm happy to say that my final five seven. Why does it why does it bother you so much that you keep getting comments?
Maybe they're just never stop
Why does it bother you that they don't so much that's bothering so much that it baffles me that they're still
Consistently coming out at the same speed. It's really funny to me
But here's what I've done decided to do differently with my approach because I mm-hmm like like looking at the video now
With a lot more experience. I mean, I haven't even rewatched it. I'm just like remembering it now with better critical thought
It's pretty obvious why people walk away with that video with the exact misunderstandings that they do
So I took one comment that says by mr. Star it's a comment that says
I have never seen a video more deserving of dislikes than this one
I took that comment pinned to that comment and then replied to it with about three or four paragraphs of me
criticizing the video on
My terms and that is how I think I'm fine
I just I just feel like you've already lost by taking the effort to do that like this is already a lost battle
I mean, it's
Because you're fighting the tide you are fighting the tide my friend and there's no
Winning when you're fighting
It's it's not necessarily like a waste of time if you're not changing someone's mind because you might be changing
His mind somebody's gonna be right behind him by being okay
Billion you can't change billion. I mean, I obviously
There's only 300 million in America. Okay. All right. I can work through 300 million. I
Well, I mean frankly, I don't want to so I guess that's where I'm approaching
Hey, I think I want to I have done a thing. We hang on. Well. What was gives it?
I am I have done a thing where I have gone through like all of my hypocrite videos because uh, you know, I have like troubles
knowing where to take
New videos and I just like I just have troubles. I just have troubles. I well, I you know, then don't we all
But uh, I've I went through them and I made a little
Spreadsheet and I put the name of the episode or the video and I did a little like
Review of it. Like what I thought when I was rewatching it
What problems I found and what things I actually really liked and then I gave it a little like
like
Word school like good bad great a little iffy like stuff like that and
Then I put that on my on my discord for people to look at and I feel like that's basically the same as like criticizing
Like what DeVoo did with criticizing. It's not about like changing other people's minds. It's just like a helpful introspective
Way to like think about what you have done and how you can grow from it here using that using people's like
This taste as like a catalyst. There's a difference between what I think you think I want
Emotionally psychologically and what I actually do want which is okay not an admittance of wrongs from anyone
I mean that'd be nice
Sometimes when someone gets real heated and like keeps responding like five times over the course of two days
I'm thinking it's time for you fucking admittance
But even then if two days go by they don't say anything
That's what I want the feeling that I made a good case that satisfies me
Automatically regardless of how they actually respond, right? Okay, so like around like when the video was new my my approach was just
Asked them to elaborate like what the fuck do you mean by bias? What do you mean by nitpicking?
You know, which was satisfying enough, but now I just say I have a copy pasted
Please go look at the verse
I have a pinned comment a reply to a pinned comment where I analyze what I think is wrong with this video
Go check that out if you're curious what was wrong with this video
Uh, I even got one person explicitly saying no, uh, it wasn't because of the writing structure
It was because you're biased
It's because you're biased and so then I just went back to the old technique explain what bias is hasn't responded and
That to me is satisfying because I that's the thing about what people don't get about angry mobs on the internet
They're often right, but in the wrong way
Yeah, they're or they're wrong for the right reasons. They don't know
Econ is always saying yeah when I talked to him about this stuff is that like
That you know, even the dumbest shittiest commenter like they have a point. They're just bad
They're just like they don't understand language well enough to explain it
So if you are good at language, then you can kind of work on sussing out what they actually think, right?
But unfortunately with people like that at the same time
They're too easily swayed like if they're bad at language and you're charismatic and good at language
It's easy enough for you to kind of trick them into not
Unders like you know into like just agreeing with you without actually addressing
What was their original point?
Not that that's necessarily bad because it just means that now they have moved past this whatever they were ignorant about it
Just doesn't like you didn't have to like
Let me respond to that too because here's my here's my hardcore anime analysis response to that
The reason why I think my approach is better is because what I'm doing is I am showing and not telling the audience that I am correct by
Not responding directly with the long word exercise
But just by living a great life and achieving things and working hard
I'm showing them that I'm right in just in a general sense of in life as opposed to in the whatever particular argument
Is that going on? I think that like mounting a a strategic rebuttal to anything is only something you should do like
Empirically, it's not something that everyone should do clearly your whole like your whole brand works on it like works itself
It doesn't need to be self-justified. It like it just works, right?
Meanwhile, there's definitely a too much. There's definitely you can definitely
Respond to absolutely
I would say someone who really should have done something to respond was the irate gamer who
In 2012 made this like whole like big
Confessional vlog about how like oh the AVG was actually ripping him off not vice versa or something
And I remember reading like blog posts like like rebutting irate gamer saying that like no he's still wrong
I read gamers like full of shit. I don't know if irate gamer was full of shit
But it was basically him talking about his perspective of this huge fucking YouTube career
He had of being this in like infamous pariah
That like people didn't under like like like that that was just en masse
Disregarded and shamed for being a blatant APG and ripoff with lots of those okay, whatever never mind go on
There were there were a lot of people trying to be AVG in from the beginning
It's just that irate gamer was a really shitty one
sure he would like steal individual jokes and what really incited the the criticism was that this was back when YouTube had to
specifically authorially ordain
Monetization upon people and would also personally get involved in who gets promoted
AVG in was totally snubbed despite being one of the top 20 channels and irate gamer was like black like
Air blasted up his ass for no particular reason why no one knows your situation
All right good the algorithms or at least you know or at least chaotic evil rather than
Orderly evil so
The problem with irate gamer trying to tell his story is that he told it in 2012 when his YouTube career began in
2006 your six fucking years too late if there's a real problem out there
There's a real misunderstanding and their misunderstanding has some intellectual merit
Even if it's being made by morons and troll faggots. Mm-hmm. Do we need a faggots jar?
You you are not above that stupidity
I think there is an extent to which people are overly egotistical to think that they are so above it all that a valid
Or at least seemingly valid criticism is beneath them
I'm on the record is very much pro comments, and I retain that now
I'm all for reading comments in a way that just doesn't waste your time
That's what you need to remember is also there is you might think oh
Like you're never gonna change the opinions of the of the angry mob battering down your doors not by responding to individual comments
Yes, that's my position even if that's the case what we don't ever give credit to is the 90% population
They actually legitimately silent majority don't write comments who don't need to be responding to and read the comments well
But they yeah, yeah, yeah, they they want to they want to support you they want to be on I mean we're right
You're not just respond. I mean if it's in a public place like Twitter
You're not just responding to this one person when these okay to to a sentiment that is shared by a silent group
And this one person is just
This idea
People who are most inclined to share their opinion are outliers the people who are most inclined to speak out are people
Who think that their stance is not normal or that it's not held by the majority
But but how often are they gonna be the only one not only will they be the only one but to look at those people as
Like a huge group. It's like more likely. They are the smallest group, and that's why they feel so in-sense to say
That you will sway the majority by responding, but you will doubt you're definitely influencing more than just
I'm talking about the majority that does like you
I'm talking about the people who are like are your subscribers
But not the people whose names you know right and these are people who want to be on your side who by default are on your side
but
They might be concerned by the criticisms and they might want you to respond for their sake
You know what you know, that's true. I mean I want to hear you out
They do want to agree with you, but they can't agree with you if you do not make a case for them to agree
I'm all for I am all for addressing concerns of
Like any serious issues that are brought up if it's like you got a fact wrong is like sorry, whatever
I mean, you know that there's a like if someone's like your content's going to shit
These are my arguments why and also I hate you then like there is things of value in there to be to be addressed in some way
Now is the right way to directly respond with comment? I could see that is the right way to I don't know write a blog post
maybe or
Possibly is the right way to just take that advisement on board and try to adjust your content to address that
I don't know that I know you were just like like grab bagging for like an extreme example
Yeah, I would say that's an example that is so extreme that it doesn't really need to be said because it's just like if someone thinks this content is all shit
Oh, well
It can be far more specific. It can be a way better example
Yeah, I think you need to have like stratification of your level of responses where like right again because of the fact that we're
measuring these these different factors like
Like your your own time, you know like if if you that's a big one for me if I read a comment that is in any way
Reasonable then I'm fairly confident I can reach this person without too much effort if I read a comment
That's totally unreasonable. I might it depends on how dumb the person
Seems because if they seem really dumb but like in a kind of innocent way
Then I'll be like I bet I can convert this person because they're just dumb and they'll just listen to me because I sound smart if it's somebody who's like
Malicious and like act like the only people who I block on Twitter are the ones who just come at me like fuck you
You're a pedophile and I'm like I I could argue with these people about like Lolly or whatever
But like they're they obviously don't care they obviously do not care about arguing
They are just determined towards hatred and like those are the only people where I look at them
And I'm like this will not like there's no way I'm gonna be able to do this via social media
Maybe if I met this person face-to-face and talk to them. There's a chance
but like
Like if this person is just someone who views the internet as a place to spew bile at people with no consequence
Then it's better to just excise them because eventually
Everyone will excise them like people who are like that people who are just like who are just toxic like
The thing is everyone's on the commute on the internet for a sense of community people come to the internet because they feel that they are
They don't fit in enough with the people around them immediately in their personal life
So they need to find a group they need to find a tribe and they come on the internet to do that
But the thing is most people your tribe is either
It probably has to directly interact with other tribes on the internet and that's where all this conflict comes from
But I'm glad for that. I'm glad that all these people are being challenged and constantly being asked to to reassess their opinions
But if you approach it like sociopathically if you're somebody who comes in and you are not interested in conversation
You're not interested in like, you know
In in forming an argument if you're just trying to spew bile eventually you will piss off
Everyone like one by one people who are on your side will eventually be like fuck man
Like you really like you're really gonna go that you really gonna go there
You know and eventually you'll get you'll slowly be cut from everybody. I agree
And so yeah, so I think it I think there is a power in just like blocking people and just being like fucks you
Go go in the corner and think about what you've done and eventually at like when enough people block that person
They have to finally at some point ask. Hey, am I a piece of shit?
I'm a piece of shit, you know, you know, you don't there's no responsibility
There's no responsibility to engage with everyone and some people are definitely not worth engaging with you
There's no shame in deciding this person's not worth my time. There's nothing. I don't think there's anything like
Yeah, I don't think you should feel bad about blocking it
It's interesting like if if you don't want to engage with someone you don't have the kind of thing you're talking about
It was slightly different what I was gonna say, which is like just non malicious people
But just people whose opinion of you is that your shit, right?
And no matter what like lead in or rationales I have for why your shit whoever you are
The thing is if they just think outright your videos are bad and you think your videos aren't bad
Then it may not necessarily be worth talking to them or trying to change their mind because like there's a clearly
Fundamental difference in opinion here, right?
So I mean it kind of depends on if there's somebody who wants to like your stuff or not because like yeah
Suggests that like like most people who just don't like something aren't gonna go out of their way to say so
So like if they're going out of their way to make their stance apparent either they're a huge douchebag or
There's more to it than that like that dude mr.
Cynical who came on did you brothers is everybody and like both times his argument was basically like you're not doing the type of content
I want you to do right dude's been watching me for like five fucking years. So that's clearly not entirely true
It's just that like is that are you I mean couldn't he have just liked your early stuff and just obviously he's still
No, he like he comments on like every video I make
Possible that he there is a sense of dissatisfaction despite still being heavily there's definitely a sense of dissatisfaction
it's just that like
the to to boil it down to like we just are looking for something different out of videos like I
Don't know if it's that simple so much as it's that we are both
Understanding what the videos are or like what the goal of them is differently and that could potentially be reconciled like yeah
I haven't I have not given up on this guy changing his stance or me changing my stance and like for what it's worth like
his
His idea that like my videos were too personal like my response was like well in my opinion all
Criticism is inherently extremely personal like because you can't you're not writing it from someone else's perspective
You're writing it from your perspective, and that's always going to be affecting it
So like whatever is unique about you is the thing that you should fixate on but at the same time I
Have found ways that I can write about shows that are extremely personal, but aren't like flag-waving about it
Yeah, you know and like I think that's really what he means is like not so much that he wants me to divorce myself from
the analysis but that like
To remove the ego from the analysis
You know something like like my gurren login review is just like like that is a late in
100% like with my personality the why like I've interpreted things this way
But then like I get away with that and nobody accuses me of ego because I just slip in the like me relevant thing at the very end
Like that's just one little it's just a little and yeah
I mean and that you know I can get away with that but like on the subject of of like how we
Like personal like what I wanted to say about that was I think we have a fun a slightly different just world view as to like how to
Change people or if people can change I think I do think that I will be less successful
I have a little bit less faith in the earnestness of commenters and like their willingness to change and also
I think it is harder for people to change with with some of this stuff, but like I just view it that I
I'm not necessarily concerned with their willingness to change. I will force them to change
Okay, okay, but I think that is a world around people they have to change to fit into that world
That's true, but like I mean and I so we're kind of on the same pager
But like I see it that just like I will just I will just front load myself with like the kind of like
Positive vibe that I want them to have with me initially and maybe that makes me more like milk toast or less provocative or whatever
but like
You know that like like Ben was saying before like I don't want people to walk away from my content
And I don't really think about this a lot
It kind of just just happens
But I don't want them to walk away with even really much of a chance of like a bad impression
That I then have to correct later. So like, you know to at least some degree
I think about like how what I say will be interpreted and so like like I think like my first impression is the is the best chance
To like hit these people and make them, you know, not think that I'm totally retarded. So, you know, I guess that's just where my
Though that's why I say before I do think that your content is just a lot clearer than mine about like what your intentions are
Who you are what you want the audience to take away like that's all very
Evident and with me there's always been an unsureness even within myself about what my content is why it exists or what I want
People to take away from it. So like that's why I haven't been able to like communicate as clearly as you have
But I hope to fix that. You know, sure. I mean, I'm not trying to suck my own dick or anything
I'm just you know, just just pointing out. I think that the the difference of worldview that I think you agree with
At least to a degree
Well, we're two hours into this should we get into I think it's time. I think it's time to switch gears a little bit
Yeah, I'm ready. Let's uh, okay guys. We got a couple more PCP themes on deck for our listening pleasure
Next week will be the last time we actually let me bring stuff
So so I'm looking at the dates. We said that the 31st is like the last day that people can submit
We've got today's recording the 29th recording and then there's two days
I think technically speaking what we should do is say that the fifth is the last day
We listen to anything but it's only going to be submissions that were in on the 31st or earlier sound good sound fair reasonable
Yeah, okay, so there'll be two more segments after this one though. They'll probably be shorter and shorter, okay?
So here we go first one. So if you're listening to this, this is probably your last chance
Yeah, yeah, you've got like two days if you're listening to this to get it in or something
Let me double. Yeah. No, you got one two three
You've got four days you got four days to get it in if you're listening to this
Buddy, I'm sorry. So anyway, yeah, here's our first PCP theme of the day
This is from oblivion fall who comments. Uh, this is the first out of two PCB themes
I'm submitting to the procrastinators his second more serious entry, which is going to be called PCP dream theme
It's currently in production and will feature real musicians ETA one week
He's I have I have real musicians unlike all these fucking acts that have been submitting
Means live musicians probably in fall makes me think of what your name is trying to be you should just take it all the way and just call it
More oblivious fall room
Probably he has a dragon after also is at his at Oblivion. I mean he probably only likes those two games that he's referenced
Like two and four that's like the most weirdly specific elder scrolls opinion I've ever heard. All right, but let's get to it. This song is
It is called this is the PCP meme theme is the meme theme meme theme
Call aka horse tranquilizer
Here we go one two three
Bam
Oh god, that is sharp
Yes, I think this is
Make Starfleet
I think of my first time
Oh
I thought that was actually fucking awesome. There's more. There's more. Oh
I think I was just you crying at the end Ben weird that creep me out a little bit aside
Oh, I felt like if you took out the quotes and the random sharp spikes of it was a meme theme
It was a meme theme by the way. Yeah, but it was like it was
Yeah, no, I mean, I think it's awesome. It was like a it was like a
Demon version of like dragon
So that should be no, yeah, I think that just needs to be a video
Someone just needs to make a video
Video is this video right now. I guess we animated somebody animate the whole thing
I'm a little disappointed with my quotes
I guess I gotta work on I like I don't remember the the line where you said I'm pretty sure I didn't come my first time with that
Yeah, yeah, I'm sure it's from the virginity because that's a strange line to pick
Funny I appreciate the going back through the episodes. Yeah, he clearly worked hard on this one
That's to be saluted for sure
Now remember this guys. This is one of two and this was his meme of version
What is his real submission going to be like dude?
Maybe maybe if there's any topping this I don't know if there's any topping I mean
I really like I don't even like hate that as like a real pick possibly that was really good
Really want the first like 10 seconds. Yeah, for sure
But like imagine if someone animated like a procrastiners opening like with this
I think it's a little too intense. Oh sure. It's the opening because like if someone clicks on this podcast
Who's never heard of it. It's just gonna open with
Yeah, blast beats, you know, that's fair. That's fair. I mean man. That was a great fucking we should use that for something
We should we got to use all these for something we should literally put together an album at the end of like we should creme
Yeah, oh dude, we should put together an album and then we can get the guy who did the gorillas animation
We will sell the album and reap all the profits and pay nothing to the well
They did
Pay them an exposure. Yeah, that's what we do. That's what we do you Vee explain
Well, that was fucking great our oblivion fall. You're killing it, dude. I'm super excited to see the next one get that in
Just to be clear. I love that. That was also. I'm eating beef
I'm eating slow slim chips. Well, there you are ladies and gentlemen. Next up is oh, what's what's his Twitter thing?
This is from
How damn it Ken at fit what the fuck at Ken Crayley Ken Crayley this is Crayley. This dude's an actual musician
Oh shit really. I'm like all these other have been submitting
Sent me an album. He made one. So wait a minute. Okay. All right. Let me read this thing here
He says here's a short rock instrumental called explosion
5,000 that my band Casino's made a while back that we never end up expanding into a full song
I thought it might be theme worthy
Maybe you'll dig it. Well, I mean, let's just let's find out. This is a
Explosion 5,000 by the casinos here we go
Oh
It sounds like an 80s anime theme. Yeah
I'm just waiting to hear a Japanese man singing about Gundams pretty much
Oh
That was really good sounding. I mean I like I like that. It's you know, it's short and punch. Yeah, it's very triumphant
I feel like it's uh, it's it's almost too hopeful for this this
Yeah, I'm with I suppose that I am approaching the the theme concept from the same way
I did with the me and math of the theme which is use a short segment for like opening of the things
But I do want there to be like a big epic version that can be played during our anime final battle
You know, that's that's how I'm thinking about
More to that song that maybe he just said no
He said that this is just like they made just this little instrumental that they never expanded into a full song
So I guess that's this is what there is. I mean anyway, it was well was really good. Yeah, I mean
It's not as it I mean, I can't
Actually made for the show
It doesn't feel like it was written for the PCP because it was which is indeed indeed
All right next one. It's a good it like if I ever made a show that I felt I needed an intro with that tone for it
It would be fine for that. Yeah, like if I was doing like a Conan barbarian review show like I'd use something like that
All right, send that to Razor fist let that be his new oh, yeah, he'd be down for that
That's kind of like it. All right. Here's at zero alias 394 submits
It's called love stuff and each other PCP theme attempt number one. Okay. Here we go
Go
Shit
Yeah, all right
I like this it's got a it's got a yeah, it does really like melody
Oh
You know what would make this great, but also just an oniguchi song what if they did the oniguchi like Blast beat drums in there
I I love I really like that one. Yeah
Yeah, I really like the beginning when it just sounded like a fucking acid trip. That was I it was yeah
I like the beginning. It was interesting, but then when the the actual like tune came in. Yeah, it was great
I was way into that melody. Yeah, and I think it's not a bad fit tonally that that would be like
I'm imagining like quotes being laid over the top of that or like somebody speaking over the top of that
That would be like a good. I don't like the idea of using quotes from the show so much
But like well someone speaking over it to like explain the basic, you know
I want someone I want to not one of us person being like I don't know in the midst of time
There was a podcast where a bunch of gay homo boys got together
Sleepy cast and so I I would like to point out that there is I have seen some sentiment
I have seen some sentiment floating around that my musical intro to Steven Steven universe episode 2 was the best
PCP intro
And I agree it was yeah, that was that was very good. This is like an original. I haven't seen this. Yeah
Well, I sang over I sang over a piece from the ruby the ruby writer song, but I changed the lyrics
Yeah, I just made like two lines
It's like I mean it had a lot of charm and I really liked it
It was really good
I just was humming that song in my head and I thought about the PCP and then much like Christian
Weston Chandler thinking about Sonic and
Pokemon and wanting to make an album cover with
Combine the two together
Perfect melody to represent the PCP. What's that? All right, it's gonna go like
Yeah, we've got one more over here from actually two more all right, this one's from a Sasuke zero pro
And it's called a PCP theme boy. Wait hang on the fucking go over here and
Go
I'm listening to the PCP
I don't even care if we keep the guitar part. Yeah, ten out of ten. Oh my god
Guys click on the Robo Nazi techno state chat and look at the album art cover for this
Um, I mean obviously they just did a little thing here
But I I love the aesthetic of like husband comes home
But oh actually wait no the wife is apparently the breadwinner here and this is say at home dad
And she came home
The British she did not pick up the groceries because she was distracted listening to the PCP
Oh, man, this one is by far my favorite. I want it on record. This is the best one. I said so
Well, you got the just vote. I don't know if I get a vote, but this one is my favorite
This one is I think for once. Oh my god
Oh great way has been lifted and suddenly for the first time for the first time in my young life
I feel like I finally could actually see this at the beginning of a fucking PCP episode
The first one and I mean it uses the existence
To sound like an intro. Yeah, this is the first one that I unambiguously feel like
This would just and who else would bring it to us, but Sasuke Uchiha himself
The competition is over. Okay. Goodbye
Later, dude. Well, I mean that was fucking awesome, but we got to give I guess we'll give the next guy his affair shake
This is
Eric C base at Eric C base with a crazy X. This is apparently his third submission. Oh, I recognize this guy
Okay. Yeah, let's let's play this and there it goes
I
Like this hard-thriving beat. It's good
Bass
Good walking down the street with the pace a pay at my back back back back back
Yeah, I mean and then we were like fade out now I
Want to hear like a new wave
This is third version of this
I still like yeah, he got the
Yeah, that's pretty good. That was the best version of that for sure. We had we had yeah
Yeah, this is I'm sorry that this is we had a version to this one. Well, yes, we did like two versions
Yeah, I I mean I don't remember them well enough to be able to say which version I like the best
But you know, I still like yeah, I like that song with some like like
Interpol style vocals, you know like some I went to the store and I was procrastinating like that kind of
I mean that'd be cool. I
Mean I liked it. I did I mean we're starting to get a bunch of like good things in here
That's a good. That's a good. That's a good tune and it would and it's a good and we got oh
I just remembered digi you said you were gonna enter. Yeah, I sure did say that
Well, you got to 31st buddy
All right. Well, that that's all the
Because I actually am satisfied enough with an entry at this point
Yeah, there you go even even a couple of options, but I mean, you know just think about that aesthetic
You got us the stay-at-home dad is just he's like oh when's honey get so sad and lonely
She came home like shit faced out of her mind did not get the groceries did not pick up the kids from from daycare
Because she was listening to the goddamn PCP. It blasts her mind. It blitzed her chakras
She didn't have time to think about other shit. I I love this aesthetic. I'm way into it. I'm way into that
Hell yeah
There's there's no argument Lord of this one Lord of this one. Yeah. Oh, it's that's good shit. It's strong
You know, it's it is really strong contender oblivion buddy
You got your real submission you got you got a serious contender here to fight with but I'm sure we're forgetting like currently some like the old
You know dope ones that we said we're like this is the best one. I got to go through all of them and yeah
Yeah, all those suck now
I'm gonna I'm gonna put together like a playlist like the best ones and listen to for a while to figure out
Which is actually the best
Yeah, I mean, I definitely want to read you haven't done. Yeah, good. Good. I definitely want to re-listen before I cast
So, I mean, okay, so we're done with that shit. All we got left is our is our little question thing
We've got to throw a bone to the old page
I got one right now. All right
Cicero asks and I'd be shocked if we've never answered this before but I don't remember if we did
How do you all deal with writer's block or other blocks when trying to be creative for me?
Switch mediums like I I've you know, it's which genders. That's what I do
Like if I can't think of any YouTube videos
I will then go and work on like a song or write something or just do something else creative because like, you know
There's no sense beating your head against the wall
Like if you don't have an idea you don't have an idea
So like it's time to do something else and I granted you could just as easily go, you know do something in your
Like something that's just totally unrelated to creativity, but for me. It's just like, you know, I'm I'm
Proficient in multiple fields. So I just go and do a different thing my answer is that there is no simple answer
And I think it's something I've said on this on this podcast before, you know
There's lots of competent artists out there
And then there's lots of competent artists out there whose job it is to do that art
And I think that my stance is that the real dividing line between a professional artist and just someone who does art
Sometimes because it's fun the amateur is
Their ability to stay motivated and inspired because like you can be like a pro artist in any medium and be really successful
But a lot of people in the peanut gallery could think a lot of people could do that a lot of people with the same level of skill
Basically what I'm saying is that anyone with a with a minor amount of skill can make something really great
sometimes when the inspiration happens to strike and
I think that is what artists who get paid really get paid for is to learn it's like 50% of the job is learning how to
Control your own inspiration, right?
So I don't think there's anything simple that will work in all purposes
And I think that as the years go on I get more and more attuned to how to
Modulate inspiration like oh and you just reminded me what what the most common advice that writers give is read
like yeah, I mean for me if I go if I consume almost anything and I'm thinking about
It at all. I'm probably gonna get some kind of idea, you know, especially if it's something good
And I mean for an adult just mean that in terms of like oh if I watch enough anime
I'll find something to analyze like if I watch enough anime
I might see an idea that sparks something within me
You know or if I if I go read a book that is from a favorite author and I try to like imitate a technique of theirs
You know like yeah
There's just just constantly have your eyes open
I would say if you go out of your way to hone the skill of inspiration and motivation
Modulation it can get pretty easy to control basically before this podcast started
I was looking at my empty Photoshop document thinking okay. I need to draw a level right now
Not feeling it and I knew I knew that if I go wash dishes
While specifically listening to mr. B tongues video about the great infinity engine do over
I know for a fact that I will walk back to this screen
Totally motivated to do it and I was right
I would say that um a lot of the time I
The way I get through
You know a problem like the reason I don't work is because I'm not sure what to do next
It's not usually because I have no ideas. It's like I have my idea of I'm like how do I do that?
Usually with drawing or with like a video edit like how do I convey that how do I write this next part of the script and
The best way to get through that is to ask like the very basic of questions get to the very base root of
What you're trying to do and the reasons why it's not working, but it's hard to do that normally
So I like to take a long shower and just like okay. What am I trying to do right now?
Why am I not doing it? Is it because I just want to watch more Tim and Eric probably
Okay, stop doing that. We didn't talk about Tim and Eric. God damn it. All right next time
We didn't next we talked about Tim and Eric every day
Like yeah long showers and like just asking yourself asking yourself simple like questions
Methodically going through until you're like, okay
I think I know the solution to my problem and it's to go
You know either research something or look into something or just you you get inspiration
Maybe because you weren't your mind was muddled with other things and if you if you ask the questions
You'll you'll get to something you'll you'll have a direction
Logically your way through it like oh what texture do I put on these walls?
Well, hold on. What was the last wall?
Well, the last wall was polka dots and the wall before that was stripes
So I guess zig-zag
I think it's just a lack of a loss of focus and when you really focus back
I'm glad sometimes it takes like you can go to like the very
Like like logic your way into like a really very specific very core thing like why do I want a texture on the wall?
You know like what is the purpose? What is the purpose of drawing it like this?
What's the purpose of this paragraph? Do I even need it?
And if I do need it then I have a better understanding of what I'm doing. Yeah, I'm glad we're talking about writer's block because I'm currently
I know that in one sense it's not real kind of but at the same time
It's very real in another sense and in that fake sense. I am dealing with it right now with regards to into a very specific thing
I got asked to write
This is kind of interesting. So I'll say I got asked to write um a comic for the official zone tan like
comedy
comedy strip thing and
It's hard. Do they like give you specific parameters or like what Mary Mary?
This is this was Mary weather who invited me to do this and he showed me some of the he showed me like the first strip and
Which is not which has a totally different format than the one I was asked to write
So it's not much help and then he showed me the script for the second strip, which also has a totally different format
Like it's supposed to be a comedy, but it's supposed to be a comedy, but I don't know I I don't
I don't I don't get it. I feel like maybe needed more and kind of hash it out the project
Maybe I do sounds like yeah, I'm I'm it's okay to ask questions if if if the if the only like
Way to understand it is to ask them what the deal is then I would say it would be
Unreasonable of them to ask you to do something and then
For you like and then not allow you to ask for further clarification
I don't think there's any more information to be gained like I don't think there's more that they could show me
If if the first two are so fundamentally different does it not stand a reason you could just do what you want?
But what do I want what do I want to zone tan getting
Or something all got him joke and then write a comic about that joke
Oh, I never thought about
That's something I've been like
Developing around okay in the last several months. Well ever since reading Homestuck, okay
People have this idea this this writing principle called the rule of cool
Which is in a lot of dumb action movies
Is it like does it always work logically? No, but if it's cool, then yes
It does work logically because the rules of this universe is what is cool and from reading Homestuck
I learned the rule of fool, which is that if you can make a joke out of it. It works
Any problem you have if you can that's just the rule of funny. Yeah, there's already a word
Is that well, I hear by recall it the rule as a former as a former hardcore troper as a former hardcore troper
I'll tell you that yes
This troper would like to add that there are actually many variations of the term the rule of funny
There's there's no way I just remembered another way I deal with writer's block
This one doesn't make as much sense to most people but it somehow always works for me
Which is I'll go on twitter and just ask something like what should I make a video about?
And then I'll get like a hundred responses. None of them will be good at all
But like the frustration I feel towards that fact will inspire me to come up with something
It reminds me why you're the one with the youtube job
Yeah, it's I do it probably like once every month or two and it always works
Hey, here's a here's a quick tip just on the on the thing
What would gib said about breaking down the the problem?
We've got writer's block and busting through it by breaking down the components and figure out exactly what you're trying to do
That helps for me. I get stuck more at the like I know what I got to do
I just like oh god, I have to do it now
And the way I fix that is I I I do what gib said break it down to the smallest bits
I do step one whatever it is. I'm just like I'll just do step one once. I'm doing step one way easier to like
Only guess that is by far the most important step. I was yep. Yep. I will say definitely
Opening the program is never step one. Do not trick yourself into thinking that is step one because you will just have the program open all day
And then you will not do it. I don't think the program tends to work for me
Although I tend to just not close my programs
I mean sometimes it works, but like I I have fallen into the trap of thinking that opening the program is enough
How many times how many times you guys open the program? You've got it open and you're looking at you haven't touched it
And you're like, well, I've been doing this for hours and nothing's changed. What the hell
I
Once I put pin to paper that is step one and then I'm good
for me when I when I like uh
When I lay in the first clip usually I'm shocked by
How much like it take like how much I've already done
Yeah, let's say you have a five minute video and
Like you lay in the first clip and it's 10 seconds and you're like, oh
That's already like that's like 10 of the video or whatever it is. You know, yeah, exactly
And you see it in one sixth of one fifth. So that's one thirtieth of the video
Which is not so bad because that means like if it only took me like five seconds to lay this clip in
That just means, you know, what's 30 times five? No one knows we speculate to this day
I also edit like preposterously fast. So for me, it's like as soon as I have
Done like sometimes I'll say something like okay
I just need to do like the first two minutes within this hour and then I'll do those first two minutes in like 20 minutes
That's the way to do it. Well now I can edit the rest of this
I totally edit by percentages like my encouragement level my heart meter is definitely
Keeps up with like I go by like I do the zoom out and I say, okay
I've edited this much of the total audio that's laid out. That's 20% done. I got 5% done just now
I'm on track. There's another 10%
That's uh, it really helps me like see that I'm making progress as I'm doing right now
Doing youtube and you know while also balancing another job at the same time
I pushed my bed my bed, which doesn't have a frame. So it stands up about two feet
into my desk
fell asleep
And now the technique is that beginning to work on the next video is literally the first thing I do when I wake up
That's what wait. Wait. Did you interesting that that that works so well for me?
That that is so great and such a great feeling when you do it when you follow through with it
But I know I don't have it. That's healthy. You should only do that when you're like, no, no, no
And it doesn't matter
And I got to talk about it because uh while maize mom was staying at our house for a while
Which she was uh like to help her like acclimate back to being human
Uh and being in society, right? Uh she kept talking about this speech
To make your bed speech. Have you guys heard of this? I know. Oh, is that a jordan peterson thing? No, that that's no
It's it's it's all that's clean the room. Sorry. My mistake
It's a super super famous speech that was given at a college by I think like a military guy or something
But yeah, the the premise of it is that if you make your bed first thing in the morning
Then you will already have this sense of having done something. Yes. Yes. Yes
And not only that but like if you were to go out and have like a bad day
You'll come home and you'll see your made bed and be like, yeah, I did that and like it's you know
So I think that as someone who who doesn't give a fuck about making your bed
Probably at the very least you're you're doing the same principle
You're getting the ball rolling so early that like throughout the entire day. You'll always know I already did something
That's exactly why I need to get myself into a place of life
Yeah, I always make a point to do something satisfying as soon as possible. I was just saying specifically rolling
The monitor is like an unhealthy practice because it's literally
Your screen I'm sure this applies to everyone but artists specifically always say like, you know, you got to do like a war
You had to do warm-up sketches
You spend like a couple minutes you do warm-up sketches and then and then you start drawing the real shit
What that's how you do it you do a warm-up sketches and then like I've done something today and I'm ready to go
That's fine and all but what may and I have to do is in like we've been waking up and just
Immediately going to the gym like that's exactly what I was gonna say. That's do not collect
Straight to the gym and the reason is like not only do you have that sense of accomplishment?
But like when you hit the gym so early that you forget about it like your whole day is a blessed day
It is a blessed day when you've done it crazy. You've already got your blood moving. You're already like circulated
It's easier to eat healthy
You know because you get home and you want to just smack down some protein
It's like you like if you go to the gym
I've discovered this the hard way if you go to the gym first thing in the morning
And then the first thing you consume is mountain dew. It will feel like poison
Like it hurts to have consumed because your body is so desperate for nutrients after that workout that it's like
You have to put something good in there or else it's gonna hurt. So like it's trained me to
Be in a mindset of just like living healthier and doing more every day. I've been seriously considering
I've always loved um like doing an early morning walk
Even before pokemon go if you can believe that
People walk before pokemon go
Yeah, but like uh, I would get up and I would go and I would go
With the purpose of like seeing the sun in a way in like
Custing shadows in a way that I don't usually see it's like that's that's cool
And then I come home and I'm like hungry the whole time
I'm like I'm really hungry and then that motivates me to cook my own breakfast because no one else is up
And I I need a big something or other. So like it's it's two things
It's like I get some exercise in and I also make my own breakfast and it feels great
Yeah, uh, do we do we want to do uh, how how much longer do we want to go?
My eyes are starting to really hurt fair enough
I've got I've got one question the pity question over on the on the twitter here that won't take long
Um, this is from uh lex paradox
I just gotta say it's such a shame because we actually have like a decent handful of good questions this time
But it's like the show that ran so long
That's true. I don't even want to bother with them, but maybe we'll get to some of these next week or something
I mean that they're all still there if you had a good question restate it next time. Yeah, that's a good idea
um, uh, uh, so at lex paradox asks um
Um, was there a defining moment nat when you turned into the chat you are today and for the rest
Would you say when would you say you turn into the beta virgins you are now?
Wow
I'm sensing a fight. I'll tell you this there was no moment. I was born this way perfect walking
I fucked the bitch on my way out the vagina and i'm fucking one going back
Aka the vagina of the earth, which is my grave. Uh, that's
Yes, that's what I fucking I got lost. Yeah, all right. Yeah. All right. Thank you. Thank you. Um
How am I supposed to answer this question? I any answer you give is a question
Uh, uh, uh, when did you become the beta virgin you are now?
Please comment. Oh, I was it was 40 years ago today. I remember it like I signed that illicit contract with the devil
Damn it. I got this lustrous mane of hair, but dammit a perma virgin for life
I I I signed I signed the the the the beta thing and then and then vhs one in the end
Oh, yeah, same tbh
I mean I've got I didn't even look at any other questions. So should we just wrap it up here?
Hey, I I see a question blue blue nimbus asks can we get another speedrun race and the answer is
Yeah, we we have had one that we were gonna do for a while, but we all fell off the wagon and
Uh, I'm still interested in doing which one so I'm uh, I'm not gonna say it, but we'll talk about
It is I mean, I think it's in I just put in the main chat. I just oh you mean we're gonna play
Hey
Actually that would make sense
Undertale would make sense. Yeah, I mean it's not that long to be real. It would be well
There are things in that game that it would make sense to try to race to do first
Snail race. I mean, yeah, you're right. You're right
Um, who can seduce story?
Or or is it? Well, yeah, the point is we do want to do more. Uh, I yeah, yeah
This was like a couple months ago. It got brought up the next one got brought up and we all agreed that year ago
I feel yeah, I suggested no suggested this game
I mean, when was the curvy race? Yeah, when you first suggested it
But like it was yeah shortly after a little after the curvy race maybe a month after the curvy race
We were like guys what race we're gonna do and then this one came up and we all agreed on it
And then nobody we'd not I distinctly said I was too busy. So I was just put myself out of the curvy race
Was literally a year ago. There you go. There you go
I mean, I'm counting there. They are difficult to organize because
Rules and such it takes work. Yeah, Nate and it's like do you
Run the game a million times and then submit your best time or do we do it the first time?
That's not even a question
I know but like how long should there be like and how it's it's not as simple because people have different approaches
I mean, I would prefer it to be everyone on the level playing field i.e.
Just do it like a like snap your fingers and there you go
Someone should just say and I'll I'll say right now. Here's what it should be this game
Someone should design some
Reasonable point that is like the the the end goal like what you have to do and just say what you want the rules to be
and like like, you know
You want it to be such that
You are allowed to do it like five times only and you can like get better and then that's it
Who can beat the dancer first? Oh, man, that'd be
That wouldn't take that long. I don't want to get dark souls three. I'm done. I'm done with souls
embarrassing
All right, whatever the point is that we want to do more we'll talk about I just wanted to
Ask that question to reignite to reignite that extinguished spark of speedrun races because I really like them
And I want us to do that one. Yeah, the only reason I like haven't been gung-ho is because of
The autistic amount of time. I mean I've worked really hard on the dark souls and I just know that I suck at this particular game
That it will be hard as shit. I suck at this game too. This is not my kind of game
But I think it'd be fun though, right? I can probably I think I think it would be fun and I think with
Effort like think about it this way whatever game it is. I've been thinking about it this way
like my computer now can handle it's like that's a plus and like uh, uh
To to do a speedrun of any game and to like figure out like what the things you need to do
Like you will when you play a game for the first time you like everything you're doing is blind
And you have no fucking idea what you're doing to play a speedrun is you like you learn the mechanics inside and out
You have to know. Yeah, you know everything. You know everything. Yeah, so, uh, I mean, I mean
Yeah, the the the reason I don't like necessarily to do that's not bad
I would just see to do a race when I don't know the game and I have to play it over and over and learn everything
It's like
I I'm not as invested and therefore I am at a disadvantage against you and then so I don't even want to try
Or I mean this this game has a certain member who is a particularly bit of an expert on the subject
So, uh, I gotta say that does have a somewhat diminishing spark in me for like well
I mean I couldn't try really hard. Yeah, but that person will also put less effort into practice
No, no, no, no possibly true. I
It's not like it doesn't matter if you're good at this game because the speedrunning is like a totally different. I guess you're right
I don't I don't I don't see that as being like an issue. Well, whatever. Let's talk more about it
I want to kind of get into specifics just for fun, but uh, you know, whatever. Yeah, all right. I think all right
I think that's that. Yeah. All right, everybody. Thanks for listening to this
Hang on we gotta do patreon.com
Slash the procrastinators one dollar you're in the chat five dollars bonus episodes. Uh, that's what's up and you are fucked
Thanks for listening to the episode. We'll see you at tbcrasners on twitter. We'll see you next time
Working right now, but I'm not working
I'm doing nothing
My dick. I'm jerking
Myself. I'm sucking
I am an asshole. I am a stupid
I've got a deadline
Don't want to do it
What the hell