Hello, everybody, and welcome to another episode of The Pro Crastinators Podcast. It's me, Best.
We've also got Worst, aka Ben. Hey, buddy, how's it going?
Shut the fuck up. That's wrong.
Well, you're actually everybody's favorite.
You're spreading wrong information. That's illegal.
They call me the father of lies for just this reason. We've got Endless Jess over here.
Yeah, we've got the best guy, we've got the worst guy, and we've got the medium guy.
Everyone's most electrifying character. We've got Tom Oliver.
Hello, I'm here. The medium rare guy.
Oh, no. There you go.
And we've got Digibro.
Everybody, we've got such a big show for you this week. There's so much news in the world of capitalism and communism.
There's so many political things happening. There's politicals coming out of my eyeballs.
Before we get to all that juicy capitalism communism stuff that everybody loves, let's take it back.
Let's go old school and be mad about a comment.
Okay, sure.
I just saw this come up in my notifications as I was getting ready to do this from last week's show.
Now, most of the comments last week were shitting on Ben, which is fine, but this comment is shitting on me, which is not fine at all.
A lot of angry centrists last week.
Oh, I hate them. I hate them. Pick a side, cowards.
This villain decided that he didn't like me.
So there was one point when we were talking about Nate's dog.
Oh, this one? Yeah.
I said something like...
You were cruelly and viciously roasting my perfectly proportioned, corgi dog.
He's half corgi, it makes sense.
Yes, I remember that.
And I said something ridiculous like...
On his birthday, dare I say.
Okay, I'm sorry.
It was his birthday!
Never let us forget.
You know, I just threw out there like, it doesn't matter.
You know, everyone knows that a dog being fat has no negative impact on its health whatsoever.
Of course.
Obvious sarcasm that everybody understood in the entire world, except for this one commenter who's like,
stupidest comment of the podcast definitely goes to Jesse.
Why does it matter if a dog is fat?
It doesn't affect it in any way?
In parentheses, paraphrased.
So, thanks.
So, I responded to him and I just said, I know, right?
That's almost as stupid as not being able to detect sarcasm.
That was a good one.
And then, just now, 18 minutes ago, he responded to my response.
And he turned so vicious.
He's like a mad dog, you might say.
Yeah, a mad, fat dog.
He goes impotent.
Don't try to save face, dude.
You may be funny, but you're not intelligent.
Your theory finger quotes of anarcho-communism is actually nonsensical.
And not even a political theory you ignoramus.
Learn some philosophy and come back with a systematic approach to politics that isn't just an assertion of facts,
but based on actual proof.
We've gone astray a couple of times.
He's either confused you for me, or he's misquoted anarcho-communism.
All the fucking time is, I know our voices on the PCP are somewhat similar,
but for fuck's sake, if you're gonna have opinions about us, figure out who we are.
You guys implemented visuals.
You can literally watch the clip where you heard us talk.
Look at whose fucking icon is flashing.
Figure out who that guy is.
I'm so sick of people telling me about my opinions on things that are Nate's opinions on things.
God damn it!
We work our fingers to the bone, whipping Oblivionfall to make him give the visual indicators.
Working day and night to whip up these opinions for you.
Just to have you mix them all up in a food processor.
Just as you make whipped cream by taking cream and whipping it really fast,
you take normal decent political discourse and you whip it really fast,
and you turn it into a delicious topping of comedy that you can put on top of anything,
but it's just pearls before swine, I guess.
I don't think that he's mixing us up.
I think he's just a fool.
I think he has just misspoken and was talking about the anarcho-fascism thing.
Yeah.
If you took that exact quote and just replaced it with anarcho-fascism or whatever,
then I would understand, so I think it is simply,
Occam's razor, I think he simply made a mistake.
He's simply trying to break down the capitalistic allegory of the overloaded dog.
Everybody knows about that theory.
It's so common.
Yes, people.
Anarcho-fascism is obviously absurd.
It's called anarcho-fascism.
It's funny because the other definition is equally absurd.
Yeah.
The definition that I found was like some weird racist shit.
Well, yeah.
It's fascism.
I looked up the definition of fascism just to be sure,
and whoever said it, Mussolini or something, didn't bring up racism,
so I'm assuming that Mussolini is a pretty smart guy about most things.
I would also defer to Mussolini on most issues.
I don't know.
He's probably one of the experts.
Maybe it needs a different name, like anarcho-tyranny or something.
I don't know.
But the whole point of it is to be absurd and to argue with people
and convince myself of it, which is even more funny,
because when I start arguing and articulating,
I can almost believe it and I go,
cool, this is stupid.
Did we mention on the PCP that time?
It's not anarcho-communism.
Did we mention on the show the time that Jim Carrey was shitting on Mussolini on Twitter
and then Mussolini's granddaughter came and was telling him a piece of shit?
That was crazy.
That was fucking hilarious.
I was reminding everybody that happened.
What he did, what he did, and this is kind of understandable,
what Jim Carrey actually did was, you know Jim Carrey's gotten into art and painting and stuff?
What he did was, he painted a picture of Mussolini,
and I think it was his wife or his current lady or whatever it was,
and he drew, he painted them being hung from their feet after being assassinated or whatever,
and Mussolini's granddaughter was like, this is pretty fucked up.
And of course you understand both sides,
not a big fan of Mussolini, most people.
Also his literal granddaughter is probably going to have some feelings.
I mean, that was what made it so great.
I don't know if I was Mussolini's granddaughter,
I don't know if I'd really want to be out there on social media
sticking my neck out, dying on the hill of, let's defend my grandfather's honor.
It takes balls to defend your family when your family is Mussolini.
It does.
I would want to be in the camp of, hey, I'm not like my grandfather, I'm a cool Mussolini.
I'm taking it back.
Yeah, exactly.
So I don't know if I agree with her tactic on this one.
Well fuck her, she didn't make Ace Ventura.
Gotta make Mussolini great again.
Hey, you know what I did recently?
I watched the Boba Duke, and I've gotta say, it was a cinematic masterpiece,
and I was in fact Boba Duke spooked consistently the whole time.
It's such a Boba Duke spooky movie.
One more can you ask for it?
You know, there was really an amazing arc in that movie.
I guess slight spoilers for people, but it was just Nate Movie Guy
weighing in once again on the new movie he saw.
It starts off with this mother and child who are, like this weird hyperactive,
possibly kind of a genius, but he creates all kinds of problems.
He makes all these weird tactics and stratagems to fuck up his mom's life
and make her miserable because he's too hyperactive and their dad died or something.
He starts the movie as the clear villain, but by the end,
he becomes the Macaulay Culkin fucking trap genius
fighting against a literal demon attempting to murder his mom and himself.
And I was team kid, I did not expect to be,
but kid proved to be such a fucking badass in that movie, and it was great.
And then they make peace with the demon in the basement,
and he just lives there now, and they feed him worms to placate his rage.
I guess it's like a metaphor.
It's the best interpretation of that movie I've ever heard.
I mean, like most people try to go nerdwriter about it and be like,
the Babadook is a metaphor for depression, and we see at the end,
she's learned to lock her depression up.
She can never truly get rid of it, but she's learned to,
and you're just over there like, ah, that didn't become friends with the Babadook,
and he lives in the basement.
It's fucking dope, right?
I know writers who've used subtext, they're all cowards.
Sometimes the service level is the only level.
That's my motto.
In fact, that's mostly the case.
Anyway, it was great, and I very much enjoyed it.
I recommend it to everyone.
The Babadooks are great.
And also check out, what was it, Jesse's Dark Souls 2?
Oh, that's where you're the Babadook.
Yeah, check out the Babadook and the sequel.
Oh yeah, the continuing adventures of the Babadook in the Babadook.
There's so many chapters of that saga now.
It's gone from Dark Souls 2 to Dark Souls 1 to Dark Souls 3,
back to Dark Souls 1 Remastered.
The Babadooks pooxpen everywhere.
What channel is that on again?
I forget which of your channels.
I upload them all on the Blue Glow.
They're all unlisted, because most of them are Patreon exclusives.
Oh, I see.
What I'm doing with the Blue Glow is that I'm just stockpiling unlisted videos
until I have enough to release a video every week for the rest of time.
Nice.
It's a good method of doing that, actually.
I've had many times where I tried to be like,
alright, I'm going to fucking schedule a video to come out every week forever,
but I have to make like 52 videos initially to cover the whole year.
And so I will set about trying to do that and make like 10,
and then I'll have 10 weeks of videos and it's great,
but releasing them to just patrons is a better way of going about it,
because then you're still making money off of it.
Yeah, someday I will come out and be like,
hey, everybody, guess what? The Blue Glow is every fucking week now,
and everyone will love me,
and everyone will finally get to see the entire saga of Babadook Spook.
But until then, Patreon.com slash endless jests and fuck shit.
I have already kept up with the saga of Babadook Spook.
You just have to keep playing Dark Souls forever,
because that way no one will ever realize that they've all been made 10 years ago.
It's like, why is he playing 10-year-old games?
Because Dark Souls, duh.
You can mod yourself, you can mod the Babadook into perhaps,
well, Bloodborne, I'm sure there's some Babadook Spook stuff you could do.
In Sekiro, you could definitely mod in some Babadook.
You see the mod the guy made for Bloodborne,
where you can control the enemies and play as all the enemy characters?
No, that sounds sick.
Yeah, it keeps popping up on Twitter, it looks fucking rad.
Apparently, like the way the debug mode in Bloodborne was designed
is that all the enemies work like playable characters,
so he just like brought that to the forefront,
so you can just play as enemies in the game now.
Does that include bosses by any chance?
I don't know, but I would assume so.
I'm gonna play as the one reborn and lumber around and like puke on enemies and shit.
That would be insane.
You're fucking sick.
Yeah.
People are gonna be like, hey, why are Jess and Digi playing Tomb Raider fucking
and talking about Ratton 2?
Tomb Raider 2.
We're just reminiscing, that's all, wink, wink.
Jesse, we lost like all that Luigi footage, right?
I have the files, but I like cannot get them converted on any program.
They're like just a weird file type that I can't get to work anywhere.
It's fucking mega unfortunate.
We have like 20 hours of us playing fucking New Super Luigi bros that like,
for some reason cannot work.
Someday, the world will see them.
I'm dedicated to it.
It's like how you have to put a person who has like terminal cancer to cryostasis
until the technology has to save them in a thousand years.
Man, speaking of computers, messing up my entire life by not working properly
and file types being weird.
I spent like all of this month because I finally got my computer like set up
in my nice cozy little office.
And so I was working on a big like a vlog project video.
It was like, it was gonna be like a classic endless Jess style video where it starts
as just a weird bit and a vlog and then it spirals out of control
into some complex three hour nightmare that nobody should ever want to watch.
And I was making that I was filming it all month for my for my friendly patrons.
And I was just, I just, I can't do it now because like something about the file,
I filmed it on the webcam of my laptop, all of it.
And something about the file when it's in Sony Vegas,
Sony Vegas immediately crashes every time I open it.
And like, it'll let me work on it for like five minutes and then it'll crash.
And it's just like, okay, video is not that good.
I give up.
Fuck it.
I'm sorry.
I'm just gonna throw this out here.
Because I recently, after years and years of Unison Vegas,
I discovered, if maybe this is something similar,
that if I simply put too many MOV files in one Sony Vegas project,
the whole thing simply stops working and will eventually, I think it crashes.
So maybe if too many MOV files, I don't know.
That's possible.
Who knows.
Hey, give it a try.
Maybe it's, maybe.
Handbrake, handbrake, all to MP4.
Oh, no.
I try to handbrake.
Like I turned them all into MP4s to get them to play.
But even then, they're like bad MP4s.
They just kill it.
I've had issues like this.
Vegas is fucking terrible.
I know everybody just uses Vegas because I recommended it way back
because that was what I used.
But everybody's always like, why do you use Vegas?
It's fucking terrible.
Go learn Premiere.
And I'm like, but it looks hard.
It does look hard.
It is hard.
I used it just the other day.
It's not that hard.
Okay.
Specifically with Premiere.
I thought you were a Premiere user.
I didn't know you were using Vegas.
No.
I have used it here and there.
In fact, just the other day.
I've seen you do things that I didn't think you could do in Vegas.
Well, that is true.
But like I've just kind of gotten a lease.
I've always meant to transition to Premiere like long term.
I just never summoned the testicular fortitude to, you know, put in the effort to make the
transition.
I used it for a good long time back in the day.
I don't know.
I think TBAP stuff.
But like, I was just the other day.
All right.
I was doing a little fucking around at Premiere trying to do something.
And I was just trying to like copy a section.
And it was like, like, okay, I have, I drop in a track.
I cut it at a certain point.
That's reasonably easy to do.
But to try to copy one section of footage proved impossible.
I could not figure out how to do it other than to like, I cut off the section I wanted.
I moved it aside in the track.
Then I like re-dragged out the piece that I had cut off from the original piece, cut
it again, and then like dragged it over so I could work with like the second piece.
Control C, control V.
I tried control C.
I'm pretty sure I tried that.
I don't know.
Maybe I fucked up.
It sucks.
I'm pretty sure that works.
I was giving you the most, the scoffest scoff I have ever heard.
Okay.
I'll give you another thing.
I'm just very confused.
I know that this doesn't work in Premiere though.
I haven't used the new version of Premiere, so maybe they changed it.
I mean, that's an Adobe thing to do to just, they changed all their hotkeys in like last
year and everyone was pissed.
Here's something though.
Here's something that Vegas can do and is unironically superior to what Premiere does.
And it's that if you've got two video files in Vegas on the same video track and you drag
to overlap them, Premiere just doesn't let you.
And it's like kind of annoying and it sucks.
What Vegas will do is instantly overlap them and fade between them automatically.
Now that is convenient.
Premiere just doesn't do that and it sucks.
It's insane that it doesn't do that.
Man, I don't.
You have to like manually create a fade on both tracks and put one on a separate.
Alright, we gotta stop talking about this.
I don't understand any program.
Alright, it's gonna hurt the fuck we're talking about.
It's fine, fine.
You know, it's the same, it's the same horrid fear that I have every time that I'm like,
I'm looking at my desktop and I think, I'm gonna try to make a dope rap beat on Fruity
Loops and I open it up and I look at it and I go, no.
This isn't a real, this is not a real program.
No one actually uses this.
I don't believe it.
This is bullshit.
It's like looking at a system of like steam work pipes and like organs like controlled
by instruments and shit.
Like Fruity Loops is one of the least like intuitive to look at out of the box programs
I've ever seen.
And like the only reason I figured out how to use it is that I watched my brother's
shade do it.
But I'm also retarded with programs like the fucking May has been using Vegas for a while
and she's planning to start using Premiere on her new laptop.
But like, but like she found things that you could do that I have been using this program
for seven fucking years that didn't know like basic things that she figured out it could
do.
So I'm just like, okay, well, because I don't think about, and I know Tom, you're a tech
guy and you said something that kind of blew my mind one time when you were like, yeah,
like if there's a problem that I run into in tech, I assume that there's a solution
and try to find the solution, like, you know, and then like give up if I can't find it.
Like my methodology has always been, I just, I just work with what I know to work.
You know, like I don't go and say, oh, I want to do this.
Let me figure out how I go.
What can I do that I know how to do?
And then I do that, you know, it's interesting how these thought process, if you look at
our videos, they're informed by these thought processes and our approach, very, very simplistic
stuff.
I mean, I will throw like, if I can't figure out how to do something, if I do have on
the rare occasion, I have like an idea.
If I can't figure out how to do it in like 10 minutes, I throw it away.
I'm just like, yeah, fuck it, you know, it's also like, it's, it's, it's lazier, but it's
also funnier to do it bad at this point that's like, I worked for so many years to like learn
how to do things right and how to edit well.
And then like now I look at it and like, yeah, but it's funnier if I edit poorly.
So I just like throw it literally prefer poorly edited.
Like goofy things cause they seem self aware and cute and charming as opposed to like visual
effects, art history, but there is like, which looks phony on Kenny Valley shit.
There is like no beat making programs that I will ever understand the, the only good
one, the, the classic program that I used to make all my great music and rap beats on
was a program called magic's music maker 16.
And that's where I made the butt chugger beat and the reapers beat and all those classic
tunes that everyone loves.
I, you know, and it was like, it's like considered by people a bad program because it's not like,
I don't know, I guess you can't do all the fancy like actual producers shit, but all
it was, it's just like a shitload of genres and samples from like every conceivable genre
of music.
And you just click and drag the samples and build them on top of each other and build
what you want.
It's like musical lego.
That's exactly what the, on max, they have something called garage band that like often
just comes at new max and it's exactly like that.
It was so intuitive and so fucking easy to use.
And I made beats on it that people remember and love.
Everybody loves the butt chugger beat.
Everybody loves reapers.
And so like, I, I've always wanted to like recapture that magic, but like the program
is so old that it doesn't work on like new computers.
I've even, I've gone back on Amazon and like, I've bought the program again on a disc and
tried to get it to install on my new computer and like, it just doesn't work right.
It always is fucked up now.
So I have to use fruity loops, which doesn't work.
So I give up.
That's a talent that I no longer have, I guess, because they took away my Legos.
I got to these roblox.
It's just not the same.
Yeah.
Have you seen this video?
Maybe.
You know, Diplo blocks, something, uh, those, those big ones, this one, Diplo musician.
I don't.
Duplo.
Yeah.
That's the one.
Or Lego Technics or Mega Blocks.
Mega.
Or Playmobile.
That's more like it.
Hey, speaking of Mega Blocks.
Bionicle.
Oh, do you?
Speaking of Bionicle, you know what we should do?
Buy Greenland.
This is a proposal that we should a hundred percent as a nation do.
Don't we already own Greenland?
No.
Denmark owns it.
We already own the entire world.
The rest of the world doesn't realize it yet.
I thought we were going to sell Greenland to Denmark.
The quite the contrary.
I don't think it's going to happen.
I'm just saying we should definitely do it because it sounds sick.
Yeah.
And Greenland is really big.
So I saw Trump tweeted that the Denmark lady didn't want to, didn't want to do it.
Very true.
But we got to put the squeeze on her somehow.
Didn't the Denmark lady said she doesn't even have the authority to do that?
I don't know.
I did not look into this.
It's, it's real estate.
I was too busy responding to some idiot on Twitter to pay attention to this.
It's real estate.
If we invade with the military, it'll basically be free real estate.
We can make it free.
Is there a reason we actually would want Greenland?
Maybe.
Okay.
Like literally all I know about Greenland is that everyone kills themselves there.
One, it's sick.
Okay.
Two, there's some bullshit about like the ISIS thawing and it might improve shipping
routes.
I don't care about that shit.
I just want to buy fucking Greenland.
It would be sick.
I could go there.
I think that we're, we're, we want it because like the, like global warming has made it
a better place.
Like, is that real?
Well, not now, but the, the theory is that in time that will do so.
Isn't the North Pole, Greenland is like kind of the North Pole because the actual North
Pole, you can't stand there because it's water and ice.
Something like that.
Yeah.
But Greenland, the northern most point of Greenland is like where Santa probably hangs
out.
Oh, if we, if we control Christmas, we control the world.
That's what he's doing.
Exactly.
It's tactically beneficial.
The thought that like Santa would reside in the country with like the highest suicide
rate in the world is really sad.
Why do you think he does Christmas is to keep him from offing himself?
He has to give himself purpose.
He's probably like one of those like evil horror movie Santas like rare exports or the
Bill Goldberg one Santa's sleigh and sleigh is spelled S L A Y.
Yes.
Nate, I saw this video the other day.
Have you seen this?
It's a video about Tifa and it's by some like, it's a, it's like a real lefty boy
who clearly has never played a video game in his fucking life.
The video is called the outrage is about control, not breasts.
And it's a 20 minute video of him like calling everybody in cells and not understanding shit
about fuck.
Of course.
And he like rambles about like institutionalized racism for like 10 minutes, which has nothing
to fucking do with anything.
Is that like cause a barrette or something?
Is that?
No, he just has no idea what he's taught.
He's just like spewing the talking points that he knows in relation to every single
topic, even when it has nothing to do with them.
You and I just aren't the target audience because we actually play a big game.
But the reason I bring it up is because right in the beginning of the video, he uses your
tweet as an example of like stupid in cells on the internet.
You know, quite a few people used my initial tweet about like, I think, I would, I would
I was pretty, pretty extreme, but I was like extremely disappointed about them nerfing
TV, blah, blah, blah.
He has like, he has like your tweet next to a bunch of like clips, like a bunch of images
from 4chan people saying like, we should mass murder Square Enix and that's right in the
middle of those.
I've been good company boys.
I'm the, what I'm the crypto fascist to their, you know, full on fascist.
Oh God, that I'm glad that we're bringing that up.
Somebody told me in my, in my discord that like, that their friends were like, we're
like, oh Digi bro, that guy is a crypto fascist.
And I was like, what in the name of fuck is that?
And where do I sign up to be one?
Cause it sounds awesome.
It sounds sick.
It sounds like the coolest thing to be.
It's not as, it's, it's not as cool as you think.
No, apparently it just means it's actually worse than a rate.
It's actually lame or than a regular fascist.
I guess, I guess like sends subliminal messages out to people.
I just, I just, every time I hear a fascist who won't admit it.
Okay.
I just, it just to me, it sounds like a fascist who's really into Bitcoin is like waiting
for the market to swing up again.
You would hope.
So I think it's, they could be as well.
I think they just like to put crypto on things now.
Like crypto is one of those, he's just like, he's a hardcore fascist for bitcoins.
Like fuck Ethereum.
That shit is gay.
None of that lefty eats in my presence, Bitcoin cash only.
Here's the thing.
It's that punk as a suffix is no longer interesting.
Like nobody cares about being punk anymore.
Everybody wants to be crypto.
What if you're a crypto punk?
You want to go into the internet.
So you have to be, oh my God.
I don't think you want to be crypto.
My mind is fucking blown.
Crypto punk.
Crypto punk dude.
Crypto punk would be like a, I don't know, like a business guy who wears like a
suit and stuff, but then like, he's like secretly, he's like a revolutionary or something.
He's like secretly in a rock band.
He's wearing like a suit, a suit coat, but underneath it, it's like a t-shirt with an
alien giving the peace sign and like smoking a fat dub.
And he's got like a, he's got like a bandana around his head.
He like wears a suit all day, but like he has like sleeves all the way down like his
arms.
He just hides them with his suit.
He's like, yeah.
Yeah.
Crypto punk happening.
Real trademarked.
Kind of neat.
To that, to that guy in that video, I mean, you know, I totally understand on a surface
level why people complaining about a minor character detail being changed seems superfluous
and unnecessary.
I get it.
I expected fully people like on the video I made about it to like not care and think
I'm an incel and a dumbass.
That's fine.
But I don't know.
I just, it's just that they don't care.
And I do.
He's taking a very specific outrage and he's applying it to his idea of the world.
And like he's clearly not a guy who fucking like loved this game and doesn't, he doesn't
understand it.
Like people just don't want shit change.
People don't like remakes.
That's like, what's.
This is my.
What's the more believable answer that everyone, whether they know it or not, is secretly hates
women and doesn't want like the power to balance in the direction of women or that people just
don't like remakes and don't want shit changed.
Right.
I mean, you'd think people wouldn't be.
Well, okay.
I mean, people wouldn't like Tifa because she is literally a strong independent woman,
but she does spend a lot of the game fawning on cloud to be fair.
Yeah.
But I hate the notion that that is not a strong female character.
I mean, that that's very like a strong female character nowadays is basically a strong male
character.
Like they can't do anything traditionally female at all.
They can't.
It does raise the question of what, what is a feminine way to be as opposed to a masculine
way to be.
And I'm not sure what.
I mean, like it just feels like an overcorrection in general, you know, when it's like women
are different and certain feminine traits can also be strong and cool.
They're not like abnormal, but they these when people want like strong female characters
to not have any flaws, it's like they're overcorrecting to such a degree that they're
making the character weird and unrelatable because they're not acting like a fucking
woman.
I mean, true.
Now none of this necessarily applies to Tifa because we haven't played the game, but you
know, these are these are the general concerns of people.
Hey, what can you do?
She has to get pregnant and have a baby and and like have a, it's been the whole game
with like one of those like front backpacks that hold your baby in it every battle.
Yeah.
And she has to be a single mother protecting her baby.
She has to and she has to give birth to it without screaming or crying at all.
Just totally stoic.
I don't know.
That's too traditionally feminine.
She also has to be a techno billionaire.
I don't think she'll have to like found a startup corporation.
I don't think like much of modern feminism angle usually paints like like even the character
as a mother.
I think like motherhood is seen as like two.
Oh, she has to be a mom.
It's very stereotypical.
Yeah.
Agreed.
The whole mom thing.
Well, on the opposite side of the being a mom is cliche now in modern cultures on the
office.
You know, there's, I don't know if I said this before, but there's one extremely hilarious
lefty tweet I saw that I actually thought was incredible from, I don't know, some girl.
I don't remember her name, but she was just like, like, mother gives birth to female child
father.
You know, I just feel like it's kind of pandering to have these like female children.
It's just like playing into the, it's an overcorrection at this point.
You know what I'm saying?
Why did it have to be a female?
Why did you have to make this political?
Yeah.
Well, on the, on the opposite side of this baby is SJW propaganda.
On the other side of the insane people who take everything too seriously coin, I also
found like the opposite of that video.
And it was like, uh, it was a, like a real, it was like a real right wing guy, I guess.
Yeah.
He was, the channel was called blackpilled.
So that should tell you, he was talking about the, he was talking about the movie, the stepford
wives and how like, you know, it was made by Jews and it's secretly propaganda to make
women not want to be housewives and manufacture that, manufacture unhappiness and the American
female and all that stuff.
And he's like, and he's just like every single thing that happens in the movie, he's like,
he's going through how it like is propaganda to make women unhappy and think they have to
rise up against men or hate men or something.
But like, it was equally hilarious because like, even if like, I don't know, like one
in every five points is coherent, but like, he's so, he was so angry about it.
He was so disgusted by this, by this old horror movie.
That's just, you know, I, for one, am glad that the Jews are manufacturing discontent
among women since it's our main cultural export.
It's never been more profitable.
It's our bread and butter.
I mean, like, I don't know, even if it was true and I agreed with every word of it, uh,
I mean, if, if making propaganda to make women unhappy results in like cool old horror movies
then go right the fuck ahead.
Uh, yeah, pretty much, pretty much.
If making women unhappy is wrong, I don't want to be right.
If sowing discord between the sexes and destabilizing society is wrong.
That guy's argument, just going by what you presented just now is like, uh, like obviously
the movie is born out of the fact that like, there are some women who feel like pressured
to be this way and they want to present that like the horror of that, like to, to suggest
that it's like a weird Jewish propaganda.
It's like, no, it's just relatable.
Like, yeah, I mean, like, I do believe that everything is propaganda to destroy society.
I'm just smart enough not to say the word Jew because that's what you get in trouble.
We all know what I mean, but I just don't say it.
Uh, you gotta be like John Tron and say global elites.
Yeah, that's the way we all know that all kinds of a parentheses, parentheses, parentheses,
people make movies, you know?
Yeah, I mean, like I'm probably, I'm probably, uh, it, uh, in the case of a total crypto
fascist, those crypto fascist black pillars that would be crypto fascism.
Right.
Like the, the, I mean, like, he didn't, just the crypto anarcho fascist.
I'm just everything.
Just keep tacking on words.
Keep tacking on labels until I have encompassed all labels.
And that's how I'll finally destroy labels.
Crystal, Eiko, Anarka, uh, when, when everyone is every label, nobody is any label.
Black pills, blue pills, more pills than your body.
I'm just the fucking pill bottle over here.
I hold them all.
I, yeah, the guy didn't come off like totally retarded or stupid or anything, but like
just the fact that he was so into this and so mad about it was the funny.
You know, it's, uh, uh, this just reminds me it's pretty much whenever we, we, we look
at any media we consume through our own particular lens.
And it's just natural that we get out of it.
The things that we want to, uh, I don't know, like, like, it's interesting to
know, like the way that I watched Garin log and compared to those guys I talked
about last time, they got a totally different message and everyone's going
to be like that with everything.
I see the Babadook and I see, yes, I do hate children.
And then it turns around and it says, wait, children can be good.
And I'm like, well, now I'm just confused.
I don't know what I'm supposed to believe anymore.
Uh, I speak, speaking of the shonen Ronan, I like how he bombed into our
comment section on the last episode to say, to say that Ben was right about
everything and we were all retarded.
And I'm assuming Ben logged into the, the TPC account and
favorited the comment because it has a heart on it.
I just happened to be logged in the only comment with a heart on it.
He said, he said, he said, he said someone called the why, one of the, I forget
which of the two like lefty current videos, but he said someone called it Ben
St. Corp and it was the highest compliment that they could receive.
And he was correct.
I, uh, you know, what's up, shonen Ronan.
That's what I, you know, actually, I, I, I don't think this is like a
secret or anything, but I know, remember that guy at the Hunter Hunter,
2011 Dick writing association guy?
Yeah.
That guy is like the biggest lefty meme dude in the world.
That person is, is I think one of the people working on the shonen run.
It's like a team of people or something.
So there, so there's a little bit of info for you.
And by the way, I commented on their video.
Like the, the second one sounded particularly aggressive and mean towards
me and I just, in a cordial way, just posted like, Hey guys, just so you
know, I'm not, I'm not actually like an anarcho capitalist.
I don't believe in these things, but you know, it's okay.
We have different interpretations and I wish you well.
Good luck everybody.
And, uh, we just proceeded to have a very cordial discussion about, uh, this.
So we're on good terms.
Me and the shonen Ronan, uh, as a collective shout out to Hunter Hunter Dick
writing association and sort out online dick writing is Dick writing
association, both very long time commenters who have been.
One, a pure capitalist, one, a pure communist.
So there could be no peace between the two.
Well, now what?
I'm, I'm going to be fucking like Onyx Pilled.
I need, I need to invent a new pill for me, for my people.
Fucking pill, you know what?
Cause you know, people call themselves black pilled, but they're not really black
pilled. They care too much.
They're too mad about stuff.
If you were truly.
Oh, you have to be, uh, you have to take the iron pill.
You ever read those iron pill comics?
I feel like I've seen the images, but I don't, I don't have them all memorized.
That's a pretty funny, uh, comic series called take the iron pill about a guy who
is like transcended above all the other pill guys.
That sounds cool.
I want, I want a little bit of that weightlifter.
I want a little bit of the iron pill.
It sounds like it's not, you know, those comics about like all the different
countries, like talking to each other, Poland ball.
That is exactly what it's like.
It is exactly like that.
Poland ball is one of them.
Yeah.
But with pills, I want to go to the pharmacist and I just want to be like,
Hey man, give me like a, give me two iron pills, one black pill, half a red pill.
And, uh, and also some Onyx pills, which haven't been invented yet, but get on it.
Uh, and then I'll have the perfect brain.
I want to, I want to go to a pharmacy and request moods or feelings specifically
and just say like, Hey, I'm looking for like, you know, two thirds happiness,
uh, one, one contentedness, three fourths, you know, rage, it's like,
it's like, it's like a replicator from Star Trek, except you stick your head in
it and it zaps you with radiation to make you feel what you need.
That sounds great.
This, this should, I mean, this should be possible, right?
Like with current technology, like, I mean, we have uppers and downers at the
very, at the very, you know, outset.
Yeah, we've got 60s drugs and 70s drugs and 80s drugs and they all do
different shit.
This is how, you know, when we've reached crypto punk is when we can do this,
like easily over the counter.
That's definitely a crypto punk kind of thing.
I want to be a big drugs head.
Yeah, uh, same, same.
You know, I don't know if it's, if it's just me being, uh, when I was young,
I was legitimately scared of alcohol because it made my dad at goofy and weird.
And I didn't understand what was going on and so I was like spooked by it.
Um, and then later on when I became an adult, I got more, more at peace with it.
And I did my drinking for a while and now, now I'm back in a place where I'm
like drinking is fine on occasion.
It could be a loosening experience, but I just don't really need it like day to
day, but like, I kind of like, I just don't like the idea of like taking
chemicals to change me.
But then I think, well, am I, am I so perfect right now?
Maybe drugs would improve this whole scheme I've got going on in here.
I mean, why is my natural state necessarily the ideal or best one?
I think about that a lot.
And I always feel like, uh, anything that I accomplished with the use of substances
is cheating, but that's saying that anyone who's like depressed or
takes antidepressants is cheating.
Your whole brain is just made of chemicals.
I unironically believe that using antidepressants is cheating.
Well, you know what?
You know what?
And it's not the right way to think.
It just is how I think.
I know what you mean.
I don't understand.
Aren't you fucking like all about transhumanism?
Like how can you reconcile these two things?
Because transhumanism is, uh, uh, modifying your body with like machines and stuff.
And it's like a conscious thing.
Like you're choosing to do that.
Whereas with, with drugs and stuff, it's altering your mind state.
And you can't like, you're not thinking, like, I didn't expect you
to make this distinction, Tom.
This is interesting because like in, in Ghost in the Shell and whatnot,
people just like install shit that makes them, first of all, they can
like connect to the internet with their own brain and absorb info.
I think the thing about like subsistence and stuff specifically that I find weird
is that like you're, you're changing your mind state, right?
And you're, you're no longer like the thought processes of like the things
that you're thinking and doing, they're not entirely 100% rooted in yourself.
No, your mental state at any given time is your mental state at any
given time is just an output of like your chemical makeup.
Well, not change the way you think at all.
Like it's not like that.
I, I mean, it's just, it's just, it's just, it's just changing your
perception of the way you think.
It's just changing like, sure.
Okay.
For instance, when I dropped acid, basically it was, it was not
difficult to understand what was happening, which is simply that on average,
you intake a ridiculous amount of sensory data, like you're constantly
intaking gallons and gallons of it and your brain is sorting it all out and
ignoring the vast majority of it.
The only difference when you're on acid is that it does not
sort those things the same way.
Like you don't make the same distinctions between like what is valuable
data and what isn't.
So like if you're staring at a picture or something, your brain is so
overwhelmed by the amount of data it's taking in that the picture starts
moving because it can't quite fixate on it.
You know, it's just getting too much information, you know?
So it's not that your brain is thinking different necessarily, it's just
that, you know, it's not fixating on the same thing it would, it would
always fix on, you know?
I don't think that you interpret what's happening that differently.
Like, you know, I don't think that like the way I act or the things I say or
think about when I'm high are any different from the stuff I would say
or think about when I'm not, it's just that I'm more concentrated on it.
You know, it's just like, I want to be thinking because it's fun.
Cause I'm, you know, really in my head and I'm thinking faster or like it's
like time dilates a little bit, you know, like the flow of time doesn't feel the
same.
So you might be sitting there for 10 minutes and have thoughts that feel
like they've lasted an hour, you know, because you're just thinking faster than
you normally would be.
But like, again, it's not different thoughts.
It's not like you're a different person.
So to me, it just feels like, I mean, basically just modification.
Like I made a video called metahumanism began way back when I first got really
into weed where I was talking about how like, you know, different strains of weed
literally have different effects and you can figure out what they are.
And like, if you want to calm yourself down, like you can consistently take
indica and just, you know what mind state is going to put you in.
So it's not like it's just taking agency away from you.
I think people feel robbed of agency when they do drugs or drink alcohol because
they don't understand what's happening.
Like they don't know why it's changing them.
They don't understand the mechanism of it.
They don't know exactly what the changes are.
Once you know the changes, they're consistent.
It's always the same thing.
I can drink and I always know how I'm going to act.
I always know exactly what's going to happen because I've just observed the way
I act when I get like different stages of drunk.
You know, if I if I smoke an indica, I'm going to lay on the couch.
I'm going to do nothing but watch anime and eat everything in the house.
If I take a sativa, I'm going to have, I'm going to start dropping black pills
like bombs on Yokohama.
I'm going to fucking have a billion thoughts in my head and I'm going to
want to write something, you know, and it's like, that's consistent.
I can track it.
That's why I think drugs are cool.
Well, okay, you know, that's all perfectly reasonable.
And I fully admit, I don't have a vast experience with drugs.
I did a bunch of drinking and I did some weed in college fairly regularly.
And like my only experiences have been across the board are simply that,
like I've just lost the rest of the day.
It might be really fun, but I can't do any work.
And so, like for me, most of my day or whenever I'm like, should I just
like get drunk this afternoon, which occasionally crossed my mind.
It's like, well, no, because I've got things to do.
So that would just interrupt that process.
Where do I get that new drug?
What's it called?
Happiness.
Who's working on that one?
I don't know.
Yeah, hasn't been released yet.
The trailers look sick.
I've been, I've been searching for it in every comment section on YouTube,
but I haven't found it yet.
You might not be that into weed or alcohol, but have you ever considered
just like taking Adderall or something?
Considered, sure.
Because it is, it's like the few times I've done that.
Adderall is unironically the only good drug.
Adderall is, I mean, again, it has all these drugs have different
effects on different people.
So, you know, consult your pharmacist before use.
I'll be your pharmacist.
No, don't actually ask me about drugs.
Just listen to my podcasts about them.
Um, Adderall makes, for me anyway, it, it makes me feel like really charged up.
My skin starts tingling and I'm like, I have to sweat.
Like I have to do something to sweat or else I'm going to catch on fire.
So I'm going to clean the entire house.
Like every time I've done Adderall, it's just like, bam, house gets cleaned.
Everything gets organized.
Everything gets put away, ready for work.
Like super focused.
Did you, I'm with you.
This is perfectly reasonable.
And I'm sure it could definitely have these effects, but when, when
these types of things come up, I feel similarly to what Tom was saying before.
And it's that, okay, let's say that like I'm able to be very productive
with Adderall or whatever.
And maybe I can even afford it, but like there could come a time
where I don't have that Adderall.
And what I worry about is that this artificial boost to my productivity
or whatever falls away.
And then I'm now at a reduced state of my natural.
Think of it like you're playing Mario Kart and you got to get those mushrooms.
So you can go a little faster, you know.
The mushroom is a one time use item.
You just, you hit the mushroom and you go a little faster.
But did you, but did you, when I play RPGs, I'm the kind of guy, when I play
a JRPG, you have those single item use, like stat boosting items that you know
are really good, but you save them for the entire game.
Because you never know when you're going to actually quote unquote need them.
And you end up being the final boss without ever using them once in the game.
I did that too.
And like in a lot of games, there's trade offs where like, you know, in Pokemon,
if you use a rare candy, doesn't give you the same stat boost, right?
Like it, right?
Like I've used an EV stone kit.
So it's like, you know, that's, that's like, there are some, you know,
performance enhancing drugs that have drawbacks.
You're not really building the muscles in the natural way or whatever.
It's not, you know, not building everything up correctly.
But like I said, I think of it less as like, it's not a permanent upgrade, you know,
it's like hitting, again, it's like hitting a mushroom.
And I don't know why I keep saying hitting a mushroom because you would normally
use a mushroom in a, you know what I mean?
Oh, wait, in Mario Kart.
Oh, no, in the in the minecart ride in Super Mario RPG, Legend of the Seven Stars,
you do in fact hit the mushroom and gives you a speed boost as opposed to, you know,
you know, it's weird.
I've never like been dependent on any substance.
I've never like become addicted to something.
Like I, I get really drunk three times a year and I'm good.
And like, I get, I like, I'll take like an Adderall when I can find one,
which is almost never because nothing is available.
That's probably the trick.
I just know that I've been vaping THC all the time to help help the pain of being a broken boy.
And I have drunk before a bunch of times.
And every time that happens, my mind just escapes me.
And I hate the feeling intensely because I'll start having thoughts that I can't control.
They come like 10 million miles a minute and it's really annoying.
I hate it and it's a terrible feeling.
You got to, you got to manage it.
It's like everything happens in, in a gradation, you know, like if you want to get high,
if you just take like one hit, then you can measure the results of that,
take another hit, measure the results of that, you know, and like chart, like, okay, here's this,
this is how high I get off of three hits and like how, what is the effect of that?
You know, like with beers, we talked about this extensively way back in the day
that the Dick Masterson three beers rule that like if you drink exactly three beers,
it gets you just in the right mood to be like upbeat and talkative and having a good time
and like feeling the vibe of the room.
But as soon as you hit the fourth beer, that's when it's like you start acting like a fucking idiot.
You know, so it's like, you just got to stay at that, that three beers level.
I don't have that. I don't have that because I've, I've tried the three beer rule before
a few times and usually you're a lightweight than three beers is probably too much.
I mean, even like one, one beer, I can do one beer, okay.
But like as soon as I hit two, like when I don't, I don't have that midpoint.
I literally just shut down whenever I'm inebriated in any sort of way and I'll just
stare at the floor and my brain will be freaking out and that's just what happens and I hate it.
Oh wait, modern haiku, everything happens in a gradation across this gay nation.
Right? There we go.
I don't know if that's a haiku, but it's close enough.
It's a western haiku.
In a gradation across this great nation.
I said gay nation, god damn it.
This gay nation, dude.
Can't give America too much credit.
You can add some more syllables. I don't know, whatever.
Is it jumping off point, clearly?
Yeah, I think another reason why I feel I am okay with transhumanism and not with drugs
so much with the mental state thing, just because I was raised on shonen anime where
it's all about pure willpower.
I feel that, I feel that in a big way.
Though, you know, if you think about it, okay, it's true that yeah,
everyone wants to like do it through their force of effort, like fucking Vegeta and just
man up and like be powerful, but the reality of the world is some people are like literally
born with more juice of focus or whatever than other people.
That's literally unfair.
I mean, that's the entire point of Dragon Ball Z.
Yeah, I mean Saiyans are just better than humans who are better than...
Vegeta is just constantly cucked by Goku's talent.
That's true. And you know, there's that whole monologue, that legendary monologue at the end
of the Buu Saga where Vegeta questions why it is that Kakarot has
consistently done better than him.
And his conclusion is that I think it's that he has mercy like while fighting.
Like it's for him, it's not about power, it's about the love of the battle or something.
I don't know.
Makes sense in a way, because if you want to be able to defeat your opponent without
killing them, you have to be overwhelmingly stronger than them,
as opposed to just a little bit stronger than them.
Maybe that's what he meant.
He did kill Vegeta, didn't he?
I mean, Frieza.
Or did he just leave Frieza?
He does kill his enemies.
Goku didn't want to kill Frieza.
He let him live like three times.
Is that only in the English version?
Because I know he's very different in Japanese.
Yeah, in the Japanese version, he's just an idiot.
In the English version, like for example, with the first Vegeta fight,
he let Vegeta go and he said, oh, Krillin, I believe he can be good one day.
But in the Japanese version, it's totally different.
He said he lets Vegeta go specifically so that Vegeta can get stronger and fight him again.
Like it's very selfish.
Right, Goku is like a real sociopath.
Yeah, Goku is the same.
And in the sub.
Not a cool character at all.
What a fucking badass.
But that's it.
Maybe it's his like, even Vegeta becomes more of a moral fag than Goku.
Yeah, Vegeta is like the way better guy by the end of the fucking series.
Yeah, especially by the end of the series.
Dude, the fucking sickest part of the whole dub is like in the boo arc,
when he's like fucking broken and battered on the ground.
Hell yeah.
Boo kicked his ass and Goku's up there fighting him.
And he's like, you're the better one, Kakarot.
You're the better one.
He finally just accepts it that there's just this gap that can't be closed.
It's such a cathartic moment.
And by the time everything this man was about has just been closed in a negative way.
But he's found his family his other way to give himself meaning,
despite this long standing goal never being able to be.
Oh, it's so fucking good.
It's good shit.
And in Super, he's like a total family man.
He's like cranking out babies.
He's like, yeah, he's just like a good boy.
And he's like, and Goku's like, we gotta go train.
He's like, I can't.
My wife's pregnant.
You retard.
He actually tells his wife how long he'll be out training,
as opposed to Goku, who just instant transmissions the fuck out of there.
You know, it's funny that you brought up that you like grew up with Shonen stuff
that was all about concentrated power of will.
I grew up with nothing but drug music.
So maybe that's why.
I sure these things in form are.
Yeah, like I'm thinking about like the most like foundational stuff to my
personality is like listening to the Mars Volta where like in their interviews,
they're like, yeah, we've done every drug there ever has been, you know,
like just like listening to all the drugs they did on that.
I grew up with wrestling.
And that's why nothing that's real matters to me.
And I just want everything to be as insane and colorful and ridiculous as possible at all times.
You know, that's why I'm that's why I'm a crypto punk anarcho fascist fucking gay boy.
What else is going on team?
I'm tapped.
I learned I learned all about Twitter yesterday.
I learned I've been using Twitter completely wrong.
Yeah, how so?
Because I made I made a tweet yesterday because yesterday it was D23.
Wait, let me guess.
You you complained about the Twitter in some way and somebody immediately was there with
the tweet deck link, right?
No, no, this is this is like so what the story is is that yesterday was D23,
which is like Disney's big like, oh, we're announcing that we own half the world again
sort of thing.
Right.
And I don't know if you've seen Disney's new logo.
Have you seen Disney's new logo?
Oh, I saw your tweet.
The Disney plus logo where it's just Disney plus Pixar plus Marvel plus Star Wars plus
National Geographic.
They're like whipping their dick around.
They're like, yeah, we own half the world.
So I just I just screen capped it and like official logo from the end of the trading the
tramp trailer.
Everyone else find this low key dystopian.
That's a lot of plus just like haha.
Yeah, Disney's getting pretty weird.
And so someone quote tweets me some random person.
I don't know.
And they're like, ah, the quintessential.
I don't consume any media outside of a few major entertainment companies.
And now I'm scared because Disney, the company that I worshipped, now bought them and I'm
somehow surprised.
That's a lot to infer.
Yeah.
And so I just like yeah.
So I responded to them and I was just like, if you think I'm like a Disney show, you got
the totally wrong idea.
Just like casually dismissing it and then they they responded to me again.
They're like Twitter pro tip.
If someone quote tweets you, they're not referring to what you're saying.
And I'm like, what?
What are you fucking talking about?
And so was there OK?
Sorry.
Go on.
And I'm just like, what?
And like everyone just started dog piling on this guy because it was the most retarded
thing of all time.
OK, well, that's good.
Go on.
I hope he died.
Yeah.
He's like Twitter pro tip.
When someone quote tweets you instead of commenting, it's probably not about you.
And then I respond and said, then why are you quoting if you're not referring to the
quoted tweet?
Yeah.
What is the point?
Just steal the image.
If you just yeah.
And then they just got really fucking mad.
They're like, oh, you're getting so fucking bent out of shape about it.
I'll delete it.
But I'm just like, I just think it's funny.
And I'm just like, oh, I guess quote tweets aren't for quoting a tweet.
I've learned something new today.
So you did not actually learn anything.
This was an ironic.
It was an ironic message.
I learned learning.
Yeah, it was some crypto learning.
We're all on the same page as, you know, as Jesse discovered at the start of this podcast,
not everyone in our audience knows what the fuck we're talking about when we are sarcastic.
But true, true.
Yeah, we need we need some sarcasm tags.
Oh, yeah, we do.
Bro, we just need to put a slash s at the end of every title of every episode.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
Thank you.
That save us.
Is that a thing slash s for sarcasm?
Yeah, I've never seen that before.
How how thank God, you know, speaking of things.
I say that are probably sarcastic, but I've not got to think about it.
Uh, you know, I don't care if Disney takes over the world.
But if I see one more live action trailer for an old fucking Disney movie, I'm just
Lady in the Tramp.
Oh, yeah, I saw it.
I saw it.
Oh, lady.
And the only thing people remember about Lady in the Tramp is the spaghetti sauce scene.
That's the only thing that I remember.
I remember that at the end they have babies and all the boy babies look like the dad and
all the girl babies look like the mom.
Reinforcing gender stereotypes.
It's beautiful.
I just know how it should be.
I just know the part where like Lady gets all like butt flustered and mad at the tramp
because he's got too many other ladies.
And it's like, bitch, you can't fucking hold this dude down.
Damn.
That sounds like a MGTOW anthem, dude.
I got to get in on this.
My fucking Lady in the Tramp, the original MGTOW movie, the original red pill.
The fucking theater reel in my brain just unspun for a second because you guys were talking
about this and I'm picturing 101 Dalmatians because that's also getting a live action.
Emma Stone.
Oh, Cinderella, yep.
That one already had a live action remake.
Wait, they're making it again?
Yeah, they're doing it again.
What the fuck?
Wait a minute.
Holy shit.
I totally forgot about that.
They're literally remaking the live action remake.
Okay, but this one's going to be like Tim Burton Direct, you know?
It's going to be like Edward Scissor, like what's that one about the Barbershop,
Sweeney Todd style.
Is that true?
Is Tim Burton directing it?
I don't think so.
It just has that kind of attitude.
All these live action movies feel like a Tim Burton nightmare because they're just all so uncanny.
Hot take.
Tim Burton is a shitty director.
No, it's not true.
I like some of his work.
I like Batman Returns.
I unharmonically love Sweeney Todd.
I think Sweeney Todd's a fucking modern masterpiece.
And Big Fish.
Shut up, did you?
Get out of here.
He's cool.
I like Sweeney Todd, but I don't think that anything good about it is attributable to Tim Burton.
Okay, I will say that the character design of Todd himself is the most over-the-top,
ridiculous style of character.
That's honestly my biggest criticism.
That Sweeney Todd himself, he looks like such a caricature of this character
that there was no way other than him becoming a murderer from the moment he adopted this hairstyle.
It had to be done.
So that's a little on the nose.
Other than that.
That just seems like his style, Tim Burton.
Yeah, why couldn't he barber himself better if he was such a great fucking dare?
That was his pathos.
He could cut anyone else's hair except his own.
That should have been the main story of the thing.
Oh, just trapped.
Trapped on that prison island, Australia or whatever,
as before he could get back with his shaving tools.
But alas, he just can't quaff his own quaff.
They have to make the Avengers so that Sweeney Todd and Edward Scissorhands can finally barber each other.
Yeah, exactly.
And solve all their problems.
Speaking of movies and world and things,
okay, can anyone break down for me what the deal is with this whole Spider-Man leaving the MCU thing?
Because I don't understand what's going on in if I should care.
Well, back before...
You shouldn't. I can help you with that.
Before Marvel was successful in the late 90s when they were kind of struggling a bit,
they sold off a bunch of their properties to other movie studios for cheap,
like Blade and the X-Men and Spider-Man went to Sony.
So now they're successful, but those other companies still own the shit.
And so Sony is...
So Spider-Man was leased out to Marvel for the MCU scene.
Yeah, Sony bought the film rights to use Spider-Man.
Right now, Sony has all the cards and they're like,
fuck you, Disney, fuck you, Marvel.
You gotta pay us trillions of fucking dollars if you want Spider-Man back.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
I heard that like Disney...
I don't know.
There's no bad guy, good guy.
And these kind of like corporate decisions or anything.
But I heard that like Disney was like asking for unreasonable terms.
They wanted 50% of everything from the Spider-Man movies.
And Sony's the one footing the bills for everything.
That seems like a lot.
Yeah.
So I would be in favor of Marvel itself owning all of Marvel's shit.
That just goes without saying.
But because Marvel is also Disney, it becomes gray.
And gray and gay.
Yeah, exactly.
Okay, fair enough.
So I guess it's just done.
Well, that's the whole thing is like they're saying that there's still two more Tom Holland
movies that they're going to make, but they're not going to be referring to the MCU anymore
because they legally can't at this point.
Which kind of fucks up the end of Homecoming since it was all...
The last movie was tied into the MCU like entirely.
So like, what are they going to do?
How odd.
It's very strange.
Yeah.
And people are like, they're just going to reboot Spider-Man again.
They did.
They're going to bring Sam Raimi back.
What the fuck were they doing?
They were like, Sony offered to let Tom Holland play the character at least one more time in like a Sony movie.
And the last Zoomer Spider-Man movie did end sort of setting things up where like it could be
like a self-contained next Spider-Man movie without any MCU stuff if they wanted.
They could certainly write it.
Because it ends with Spider-Man getting framed and everybody turning on him and the whole world
hates Spider-Man.
So it's kind of going back to the typical status quo of what Spider-Man has always been
as opposed to this weird Zoomer Tony Stark Jr. Spider-Man that they've been agreeing with.
The stage is set for them to do something cool.
And I hope they do because I'm not a huge fan of many Iron Man being Spider-Man.
Spider-Man's supposed to be this guy who's just like the world endlessly shits on him
and he just goes out at night and spandex and tries to clear his head.
He's just like a working class dude who's got a deal with shit.
All right, yeah.
Not some bourgeois corporate elite Iron Man suit wearing, you know, motherfucker.
Yeah, the Zoomer Spider-Man is a class traitor is what he is.
It's so true.
I remember those, I mean I was never, I never read any comics growing up like pretty much
at all but I fucking love those Spider-Man shows back in the day.
Remember that one where he went to like weird negaverse and he had like a watch
that was filled with like bugs that would automatically build his head.
That was fucking insane.
That was Fox's answer to Batman Beyond and it was.
It was so sick and there was like a sexy girl bat or something that he made out
with that one time and he got sexy pictures of Spider-Man kissing
that girl villain or something or maybe-
Interesting that you remember that scene specifically.
That's, it came to my first baby boner and I'll never forget.
Good times.
We need more of that shit.
I know I said this before but like I just happened upon watching like one episode
of like the classic 90s X-Men and it just-
Hell yeah.
Soul.
Soul out the ass.
There was so much soul in every fucking cream.
That show holds up like a motherfucker.
It's so good.
It does.
I just recommend.
Morph, this one's for you, Morph.
Yeah.
Yeah, fuck yeah.
Man, I remember, I remember seeing the like first two episodes.
I think maybe we had them on VHS or something.
Yeah, I think we did.
The first two episodes of the old X-Men cartoon.
Remember Jubilee fucking up that handsome arcade owner's property because she's an asshole?
And then I never saw any more of it and I was like, what happens?
So much of that show.
There's like a whole universe here and I don't know any of it.
Did these X-Men ever become the Y-Men let alone the Z-Men they were destined to be?
The characters are so pitch perfect in that show.
Like just in the very first episode when you first see Gambit
and he's in a store and he's buying a pack of playing cards
and the lady behind the counter is like, oh, you like to play cards?
And he just goes, I like Solitaire, okay?
Unless I got someone to play with.
And it's just like, that's Gambit.
That's all of Gambit right there in that one line of dialogue.
I gave him so much.
Was that?
Oh my god.
Remember that?
It's much easier.
Hearing Lunchie say that made me instantly sad that I know that Joke is older than he is.
Listen, I used to load up YouTube.
I used to open up fucking Bud Light commercial or whatever the hell it was.
Song of the Hedgehog and Doom and Duke Nukem and all those sorts of people.
And they would all say, was that?
I would feel like nothing much, bro.
Dude, I am in fucking bliss right now.
I've lived from piss to bliss right now.
And I woke up earlier today and the piece of fuel is going to happen in like five minutes.
I was like, oh man, well, yeah, I would like to record the piece of fuel, but I got a shower.
I'm in a good fucking routine.
I'm on top of the world right now, guys.
And so I took a shower and now I'm here to record the PCP.
I don't care if I'm going to get a big penalty.
I don't care about anything.
I don't care about money.
Don't pay me anything.
I just want to record with the piece.
Yeah, was that?
Was that?
Fuck yeah.
Munchie, what's your current life status?
Are you in school yet?
Are you?
Where are you right now?
What's going on?
Blitzed to hell and back.
Baked, if you will, like banana bread.
Nice.
I am one week away from going to school.
This is my last piece of PMA record as a free man, as a free mate.
Incredible.
This is it.
This is my last appearance for, I don't know, a little bit.
Not as in I'm leaving, but as in like, oh, I can't scream really loud and wake up my roommates.
Fun fact right now, I'm in a room alone, by the way, right now.
For the past couple of months, I've been with Kazzy and she's been in the room,
but they're all off doing bullshit and I'm not here because of UPS.
I'll tell my UPS story in a little bit, but to answer your question,
I, my school, not there yet, but will be soon.
So this, this, this is my last gasps.
When's your, when's your move in?
When's your move in?
Uh, literally next Saturday.
So.
Incredible.
Yeah.
Literally, literally last one.
It, it, we're on, we're on the brink, fellas.
We're on the brink.
Oh my god.
So when people hear this, it'll be tomorrow.
Then people hear this.
Oh yeah, it will.
He moves in.
Oh my god.
Oh yeah, um, send me your ones.
Can we, can we get a one in chat for the future?
Which is, I guess, the present for you now viewer.
What were we talking about?
What's this been, what's this PCP been about?
What like, like level of interest are we at right now?
We're talking about X-Men, the animated series.
We were just talking about, we were talking about classic 90s cartoons.
We talked about, uh, buying Greenland and how it makes all the sense in the world, uh, various things of this nature.
Yeah.
It's all over the place.
Greenland would be a fucking sick buy, honestly.
Once global warming kicks in and that shits all fucking green.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Literally.
I like, I like the forethought of our president.
I'm not just like, man, the climate kind of ruined the planet.
We could stop it or, or, we could capitalize on it.
You know, we could just do, we could just do what Ben Shapiro says and once global warming kicks in and all our houses flood,
all our houses flood, we just sell them and move.
Damn, he's so right.
You know, uh, Andrew Yang's policy on climate change interested me because he said, he was like, you know,
we could try to do something about it, but America only makes up for like 15% of the problem.
And you're not going to get all the other countries on board.
Yeah.
How are we going to get China and India, which are most of the problems to do it?
So his advice was, we need to move to higher ground.
Greenland baby, Greenland just moved to higher ground.
It doesn't get higher than Greenland, baby.
Talking, talking latitude and all right now.
Yeah.
Good thing.
I don't own a house.
Yep.
Owned.
Or rather the opposite.
Dude, this is great.
This is great.
All the landlords are going to get fucked.
That's yeah.
Yeah.
Only some of them.
Some of them.
I mean, a lot of them.
Only some.
Well, only some of them and some of them are going to profit immensely.
Yeah.
So the landlords are going to be the ones who have the money to re-locate.
Break out the champagne.
Have that concentration of wealth.
How's that for redistributing?
Yeah, yeah.
Moving money from some landlords to other landlords.
All right, never mind.
I just hope that when the title waves come and everyone's rushing to get to higher ground,
it is there's helicopters blasting higher ground by the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
The whole time that it's happening.
I'm so ready for global warming and all the seas just to rise
because then we'll be able to do away with Democrats, Republicans, blah, blah, blah.
Nothing.
This will only be about the Obi-Wan's and the Anakin's anymore.
The high landers.
The low landers and the high landers.
Yeah.
The only two political factions that exist.
Oh my God.
People are going to meme.
I mean, that scene's already been mememed to hell.
But the high landers are going to meme the low landers so hard every day of their life.
They're going to be the new, you know, the new untouchables of society, basically.
What was that?
Was that cartoon with Will Ferrell as the dad where it's like there's like the hill people
and the valley people and the valley people and the valley people are all like mutated
from like from like radioactive waste.
That's exactly what it's going to be.
That's where we're going.
That'd be so cool.
Oh, I'm like, dude, I've never been more high for global warming than I am right now.
You guys have really sold it on me.
That is already what it is like.
Like the idea of the oblogs is that it is meant to be reality.
Well, I mean, there's no, I assume you mean like in terms of economic strategy.
Well, like because in LA in particular, the rich people live in the hills.
Like they all live up on the mountains and everybody down in LA is a fucking cesspool.
Well, it's like it's like that song.
It's like that that one tin soldier song is like the valley people versus the mountain people.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, literally throughout all time, kings have been at the highest point.
Like they always they're at the high ground.
Like this is just how they have structure.
They have the high ground.
It is just the reality.
I want to be in the Obi-Wan this whole time.
Yeah, okay.
Complain about white people all you want.
But I remember when fucking Liam or whatever his name is, Obi-Wan came over and fucking beat
the shit out of me and no one cared.
No one called that racial profiling.
It's not right.
Wait, what?
When a racial profiling is piled by Obi-Wan Kenobi, no one bad their fucking eye.
This is the real system.
Munchy, you got to look out.
You and McGregor confirmed to come back as Obi-Wan for a Star Wars show.
No.
He's coming back around to beat your ass in the ground again.
I'm going to go to Star Wars 500, like the Indy 500, but Star Wars character running around
in cosplay over in a track over and over again.
I'm going to sit in my seat.
I'm going to settle down and think, oh, I sure hope I am beating up today.
And then Ian McGregor is going to come out with his fucking bath robes on and his BDSM gear.
What about the ball gag and just fly it, sling it to me.
And I have to put it on and dance around like, fuck you Obi-Wan.
The Sith really are the most persecuted minority.
That's so true.
You give them the old sheave spin, my dude.
I mean, they are the smallest minority.
It's said in Star Wars there's only ever two of them.
A master in apprentice is only two.
They're the smallest marginalized group.
There's not only two.
That can't be accurate.
Not only two at any given time.
They have enclaves.
That's what the prequels said.
That's why they're fucking weird.
Wait, really?
There's two, a master.
Yeah, they said there was two.
There's two at a time.
Well, it makes sense.
It started out, there was like a whole Sith community.
You see, you like go to their little town in Knights of the Old Republic.
But by that point, it's already destroyed.
Back in the old days, but now in the modern Republic times,
aka prequel times, there's only two.
Okay.
I know that the new movies have like uncannonized all the old books,
but is Knights of the Old Republic still canon?
I don't believe so.
It's the only good Star Wars thing ever made.
I mean, that was like way back in the distant past, right?
It could have been.
It was like a thousand, a couple thousand years before.
Yeah, everyone, yeah.
A couple thousand years.
By the way, guys, that game is like great and worth playing, right?
That's what I always hear.
It's a fantastic game.
It says it's really good.
It's like Mass Effect.
Yeah, it's like Mass Effect 1.
It's on par with that.
Okay, okay.
You're all saying that, but you mean story-wise.
Because I tried to play that game after I played the Mass Effect games,
and I thought it was completely incomprehensible,
and I had no fucking idea what was going on.
Well, the game is incomprehensible, did you?
You don't have to do anything.
It's just like it plays like an MMO.
You just walk up to shit.
Oh, okay.
Well, that sounds...
It's exactly like Final Fantasy XII.
I like Final Fantasy XII.
I actually like Mass Effect, probably less than Final Fantasy XII.
I thought the Mass Effect combat was pretty shit, like consistently.
Mass Effect 1 combat sucked.
2 and 3 was fucking good.
Okay, I only played one so far.
I gotta get back to those fucking games.
What am I doing with my life?
All right, whatever.
Speaking of the Sith, I remember one of the most memorable nights of my entire life
was I got back from watching Rogue One,
and I thought, I like Star Wars now, I think.
I said my right and left brain out of sync.
Doing a hearty run.
I mean, shake with each other.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And so I got home, and I was like,
okay, I'm gonna do two things right now.
I'm gonna binge watch a bunch of Star Wars lore,
and also try to cook a steak for the first time.
And so I basically, what ended up happening was,
I didn't know how to cook steak, and I didn't bother looking it up.
So I just like basically, I would describe it as I tried to deep fry steak,
aka I just like loaded like a bottle's worth of olive oil into a pan,
set it on high heat, and then after I was like dropped in a frozen steak into it.
Meanwhile, I'm watching the Emperor Try to Star-esque videos of like,
the entire history of the Sith Wars every year,
and it starts in like fucking like 315 BBY before the Battle of Yevon,
and it's just one big circle and dots, and there's just like one,
like a set of like red dots are over taking blue dots over and over again,
for like an hour.
Meanwhile, I scalded my fucking hand,
I'm just dropping a steak into olive oil,
and I'll never forget that night.
Fuck you, Star Wars.
You scalded your hand just like Anakin Skywalker scalded his entire body.
Is that what Obi-Wan got you, dude?
Yeah, it was a recap of that scene,
where instead of there, they're on the lava planet,
it's just Obi-Wan and Anakin like being really bitchy in their kitchen,
and then Obi-Wan drops a frozen steak into a pot of olive oil,
and Anakin just scalded, and he's just,
and then he also turns into Darth Vader.
Munchy yells at his steak,
You were the chosen one!
You were supposed to bring balance to my hunger and stomach!
This wouldn't have happened in 45 BBY!
Fuck you, stupid shit!
And then the steak yells back, I hate you!
Dude, okay, okay, when you were cutting that steak later,
it was probably like that scene where Obi-Wan cuts Darth Maul in half,
and he goes like,
Oh fuck, you're cutting me, bro, don't...
Actual dialogue.
Okay, so you know how we have the voice jail, right?
You know how we have like a set,
like a cell of villains that we have,
that we like absolute with like sticks and stones?
I propose we have a new jail for people who aren't in the voice jail,
but just are like general villains of the PCP.
I don't mean internet careers,
I mean like institutions.
A rogues gallery, perhaps?
Because Ben came up with the idea of hating systems, not people.
He invented it, as we all know on PCP.
Read my book.
I want to complain.
I want to have a formal complaint and submit to the real jail,
the entirety of UPS.
Not like the CEO or the higher ups,
like every single like service worker there,
everyone involved with the opera,
like the graphic designer made logo, they're going inside.
It's going to be a crap, it's going to be a fucking,
it's going to be like September massacres.
They all have to fit into one cell in the jail.
Yeah, so all right, I'm going to paint a picture for you,
because I've just been like toiling,
I've achieved a broken brilliance,
because I'm in a great move now,
but for the past like week,
I've just been in utter despair of the chain of events that have happened,
due to the male situation.
And so, like a week ago,
Caroline's brother is going to Montreal for college.
He's doing that and he's leaving this weekend.
The original plan is her father is going to take him to Montreal.
Why does this matter?
Well, because five days ago, he says,
or I'm sorry, four days ago, he's like,
Hey, do you want to come with us?
And I'm like, yes, I would love to go to Montreal.
How many times do you go to Montreal in your life?
Never, what a great opportunity.
It would have been amazing, incredible.
But I didn't bring my passport,
because I'm just going to,
originally I didn't pack a whole lot,
because like, you know,
I'm just going to go to Montreal,
I didn't pack a whole lot,
because like, you know,
I'm just going to Boston before I go to a fucking college.
I don't need a passport right now, do I?
Turns out I did.
So I'm like, okay, mom, here, here's like,
here's like $25.
Can you please ship this overnight?
So make sure it gets here.
She said yes, she does that.
And also, she sends my computer,
because I need that for an endless war thing,
for an endless war update ARG,
that I've been like really like trying,
like just grinding working out.
I have like tons of fucking like images and writing that I've created,
been also made of a line of flavor text,
and it was cool.
So this contributed 0.1% to this effort,
so I'm technically in it.
Yeah, and it was going to be great,
and I'm so looking forward to it.
And so there's a dilemma in my side of my mind, right?
Ooh, I want to release this on a weekend,
because that'll be the most players are active,
but you know, I really want to go to Montreal.
Okay, I want to go to Montreal.
Friday, two days ago, you know,
my passport isn't here.
So I unfortunately am forced to not go to Montreal,
because the fucking pieces of shit at UBS
just did not like listen to overnight.
They were late by two days,
and couldn't fucking deliver my passport for some reason.
And so now I'm forced to live in this fucking broken,
shambled shanty house with no one in it.
Well, well, my girlfriend and all of her family
and all of the fucking seven elves from hell go up to Montreal,
and have a gay ass fucking time without me.
But I think, okay, okay, silver lining,
there's silver lining to every story, right?
You know, okay, so I'm able to like work on an endless war,
I'm able to finish it and release it on a weekend.
Oh, but wait, but wait,
a critical part of the ARG is there's a file
that's only accessible on my desktop,
which also isn't here,
even though I called a total of six fucking times
to ensure that it was shipped to, you know,
the right address at the right time.
I called the day of it was supposed to be delivered.
And you know what happened?
You know what happened?
I called them, they said,
hey, hey, we got the right address,
you know, you've been calling us,
we're asking us that we fucked up the address,
and you know, we fixed it, we fixed it for you.
Please stop making fun of us.
And I say, okay, I will.
And then guess what?
I'm on my laptop, I'm on my laptop,
it opened up the tracking,
and you know, I'm watching it rigorously.
I'm just waiting, I'm listening for like a bat,
waiting for the sonic waves of the doorbell
to ring inside my ear or for the door to knock.
I guess instead of any of that,
I get a ding in my laptop, oh, failed delivery,
you didn't answer us.
And then like, I look outside,
there is no truck outside,
they just fucking straight up lied.
I like just, they didn't do what they said.
And so now I can't even do that.
I can't even fucking release in this work
that I've been working on.
So I have nothing.
So I'm just inside this fucking frozen tundra
of a cozy bedroom in Boston that I have,
and I'm just fucking wallowing away.
And I think, okay, how can I drown in my sorrows?
How can I drown in the pain?
Play Minecraft.
So I go to download Minecraft,
and Mojang wants to have my credit card.
So I can't even play Minecraft.
I can't even do that.
Where does the world come to?
That's rough, buddy.
It's a nightmare.
It's a literal nightmare.
And so like last night,
I was just pacing around like UPS, ARG, Minecraft,
just pacing back and forth,
running across my room over and over,
just seething up in fucking pain.
And I just like, something about my brain
just like broke that day.
Something about my brain,
just like a little bit of it chipped off.
And now I've just been in like a great mood
and I recorded like a weird like pseudo podcast last night,
but I'm not gonna record,
I'm not gonna post because I only record it,
so it wouldn't appear weird to my brain
that I was talking out loud.
It was great.
It's, I'm great now.
Everything's good.
You know, my life's ruined.
I'm not able to release any of the things I wanted to.
I'm also not able to have fun in Montreal.
So like everything's gone wrong
and I want to kill myself.
And that's, and that's where I am right now.
I hate the UPS.
They've done this to me.
They didn't allow me to go to Montreal.
They didn't allow me to release this ARG.
So I don't have to release in a weekend.
No one's gonna play it.
No one's gonna like it.
No, I've done nothing.
Nothing I've ever done will amount to anything.
This is the end, guys.
This is the insta-times for Munchie.
I think, I think it's time to go into war.
This week, and by next week,
interest is just gonna be gone.
It will.
If the moment will have passed.
No, no, literally, because now all the people,
the people who play in this war are all like children.
So they're gonna be in school on these days.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Well, we'll still have the weekend.
You just, you just gotta, you gotta,
you have the opportunity here.
No, no, no.
Don't you remember, Ben?
This is my last weekend.
Next weekend, I'm moving in.
Oh.
Well, ooh, uh, uh, uh, yeah, um.
This was it, Ben!
You should have had a bigger brain and a bigger dick,
so it's that this situation never arose
in the first place, Munchie.
I just call it.
You know what, this isn't Munchie's fault.
This is not Munchie's fault.
Shame him.
The UPS does this all the time.
They are under, I don't know if it's because
they're under a ton of pressure
or they're just fucking retards,
but constantly, they will not ring the doorbell.
They will not knock on the door.
They will just drive by your house sometimes,
like they weren't there, LeMau,
and they say it's a failed delivery.
This happens constantly.
Was it UPS?
I forget if it was UPS.
I don't know.
I don't remember if it was UPS or FedEx or whatever,
but one of the people that like,
I ordered the pins, right?
This was like a long time ago.
This was like way before I was even getting close
to getting it, which I am close to getting it done,
but for the Vapors 2 Kickstarter,
when I ordered the pins,
the new pins for the second Kickstarter,
and I ordered them,
and this was right as our parents moved house, right?
But obviously, if they moved,
they left instructions for like,
this is our new address,
but whoever was delivering them just didn't listen,
and they just said undeliverable,
and they just didn't deliver,
and they just disappeared,
and they just disappeared in the mail,
and I paid for the order,
they were shipped to them,
but they just threw them away
because they didn't go to the right address.
I just want to say that, again,
this is like a malicious thing on UPS's behalf, by the way.
I don't think this is like an accident.
I think this is a premeditated attack
on yours truly, Munchy Shatsky.
They're probably a bunch of killers, dude.
They're probably a bunch of killers.
Yeah, literally.
You know, yeah.
So, again, I just want to reiterate
that I called them incessantly,
just over and over and over again
to make sure that Patrick would be delivered time,
and then after I got the infuriating remark
that they tried to deliver it,
but were unable to,
motherfucker, you weren't even here.
I called them again, it was very stern,
and like, hey, what the fuck is your problem?
Like, what can I do?
I didn't say what the fuck is your problem.
I was like, I'm really upset right now.
Can you please explain why?
But I said it in a really stern tone.
And then, by the way, none of them were speaking English.
A single person was a native English speaker,
and I couldn't understand half their accents.
And then they had the gall to say,
oh, well, if you want to pick it up yourself,
you can on Monday.
That would be $35 to pick it up in person.
They charged me to do it in person
when they just couldn't fucking deliver it to me in person.
By the way,
by the way, I just want to say that that computer,
I didn't just, like, it wasn't just like, you know,
like, oh, I picked up in a bag and I took it to the UPS.
No, no, no, no.
So it was $200 to ship it to me,
because it's my computer,
and I had to get extra fragile shipping,
and there were like three boxes for all the stuff
that was accumulated with the monitor
and the desktop and everything else.
So a $200 to ship it to me,
probably is lost in transit and broken by now,
because it's just been loaded on and off a truck
so many times,
because they can't fucking speak anything.
They are just dumb.
They're stupid.
I hate them.
Yeah, yeah.
Time, time, murder.
So UPS, I have these problems all the time.
They, I have a doorbell.
They don't seem to ring it.
It sucks.
They're terrible.
But, but even worse, I don't know if you guys,
do you ever get like Amazon delivery from,
like, there's like an Amazon independent delivery system
that works like they've got, you know,
like independent people.
It's not UPS or FedEx.
It's Amazon.
They have their own shipping fleet now.
Yeah.
So, okay, obviously,
there are a million times worse than anyone else.
And like multiple times now,
at least twice.
There's been instances where like, I just,
and I've called them to ask their customer support.
They have told me this,
that they are delivering something.
They get here.
I'm checking.
They're like, oh, we couldn't deliver today.
I'm like, that's odd.
I checked the thing.
It says it was delivered.
I say, that's weird.
I call customer support and say, excuse me,
it says it was delivered.
It's not in my place.
What's going on?
They tell me, this has happened twice.
I'm pretty sure now, like, oh yeah,
sometimes our delivery guys
are just trying to meet a quota.
So they just put it down as delivered.
But it's not actually delivered.
Like, just hang on a couple more days.
And like, maybe it'll be there.
I understand, sir.
What?
Of course, sir.
Did Jeff, I would put Jeff Bezos on the phone.
I need to talk to the man in charge.
He needs to know what's going on.
This, this has happened to me multiple times.
I can't believe this is acceptable.
Five of the people who do this.
Have you ever had the bowling ball service before?
No, I don't think so.
This is something unique,
I guess maybe to my house,
because we have a driveway on a downward slant.
But sometimes they'll just park at the edge of the driveway
and just roll the package down our driveway and take off.
Wait.
And like, I got a laptop?
I got a laptop and I was waiting for it to come
and they just rolled the laptop box down my driveway.
And I ran, I'm like, what the fuck is wrong with you?
But they're already driving away.
And yeah, yeah.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
So they did this with a laptop?
Yeah.
It was just a box.
Uricle laptop?
How does it even roll down the...
They just take a box and they just pitch it
and it just starts rolling down the fucking...
Yeah, yeah.
This is the quality you get with the Amazon delivery system.
This is how they do it.
It's disgusting beyond words.
Deb, have you ever seen an Amazon graveyard?
Do you have any of those?
Like, because like, there's an old, there's a like a plaza
near my house that used to have like a stop
a chop at a bunch of other places.
There's still a couple small businesses there,
but it was bought by Amazon.
So the parking lot that used to support tons of businesses
is now just full, completely full of Amazon vans.
It's just like, and like, it's a big parking lot.
So like you drive, it takes like three minutes
to get across it and it's just a fucking ghost town
except for hundreds of Amazon branded vans.
And it's the most dystopian feeling of all time
going through there.
Are these the, is this the fleet doing the deliveries and like...
This is like where they keep all the vans
for all their contractors to do all their deliveries
because there's, they bought, there was an old
like caterpillar billing that they bought
and now it's an Amazon delivery service.
So like, they just bought the entire parking lot
to use as their parking lot for their vans.
And it's just literally hundreds.
And you're just like, oh, I remember when like,
people would come here and go grocery shopping
and now it's just a ghost town.
I know that other people disagree with me on this.
Like in a possible world, perhaps this is naive,
perhaps this is unrealistic, but in a world
where all power is constant, like we'll like,
where wealth and power are concentrated
in a very small number of people
and those people like do everything.
If those people don't do immoral things,
I don't have a problem with it.
Maybe that's naive, maybe it's inevitably gonna happen.
Okay, that's fine, we can discuss that.
But nonetheless, the fact that it's all being concentrated
in such a shitty system, in such a terrible,
awful fucking system where such things are just tolerated,
I guess it's tolerated the way that like,
YouTube recently like constantly tolerated people
abusing their copyright claim system
because there's just too many fucking people
with them making videos and with Amazon
just asking for bullshit that nobody cares about,
including me every day by an Amazon shit.
Oh my God, Nate, you're getting it.
You're starting to see through the veil.
My class consciousness is spiking right now.
My power levels are surging.
The problem is that like, in order to get far in the world,
you have to like inherently be a bad person.
Like that's just...
I don't agree with that.
You kind of do.
You...
Now I totally agree with that.
Well, it depends.
In order to get to that upper, upper echelon,
like to really get to the tippity top,
like to get to the 1%, like to be like a student.
Okay, I've got a question.
I've got a question for you.
Okay, we all know that like,
if you're like a CEO of a gigantic company or something,
like basically any decision you make
is going to like benefit one group
and like penalize another group,
such that almost any decision you make
like has winners and losers
and those could be fairly serious.
Like people could like lose their jobs,
lose their livelihoods, you know,
could fuck them up.
But like you have to make decisions.
Like are you defining that as evil?
Because like a good person might just be paralyzed.
I would say that to get to the tippity top,
you have to be evil because you must,
like you must exploit,
you must exploit the work of employees
in order to like generate capital.
I don't even know, I mean that's true.
I don't know if I'd go that far
in what I'm talking about.
I just mean that in order to be the best,
you have to be overly aggressive to a point
that most people would find it morally uncomfortable.
Like you have to be,
you can't be afraid to step on other people
and like use a pile of like corporate corpses
to climb your way to the top.
That's just the way the system works
and most people don't have the stomach for it.
So inevitably the people who are at the top
are the people with very little more consideration.
If you're not 100%, if you're 99% ruthless,
that guy who's 100% ruthless is going to edge you out.
That's quite possible, that's quite possible.
If you're only 99% ruthless, you're in the 99%,
it's just how it is.
Yeah.
Ruthless is a world.
Is there such a thing as being ruthless?
Can I be a ruthless person?
Yeah, Ruth Grader Ginsburg.
Let's ask the Urban Dictionary show.
Welcome to the PCP, the topic is being ruthless.
Guys, how have you been ruthless lately?
Okay, top definition for Ruth.
Ruth is a very pretty girl
with the shiniest and prettiest brown eyes.
She has a warm heart and is very caring.
She could light up the whole room
with her presence around, especially with her humor.
One click by, one click by, one click by.
She can be the kindest person you have ever met.
She's very loving and the best person
to go to for a shoulder to cry on.
She will put her loved ones first and her friends second.
She is honest and loyal and has the prettiest smile.
Okay, all those, all those things.
Is that the girl, every girl?
Is that the girl everyone's been talking about?
Guy, sure is.
That's Ruth.
So I hope that's cleared it up for you.
That all defines Ruth.
Top definition of ruthless on,
so lack of this person is simply without Ruth,
lack of Ruth, no Ruth.
That's the full definition of ruthless.
Thank you for helping us be thanks guys.
So if you're Ruthless, then you're an incel
and you don't have a pretty girl with shiny,
pretty brown eyes.
Correct, and that's what turns you evil.
What else sets the stage for a corporate takeover
of society than not having a Ruth in your life?
Damn.
That all makes sense.
I'm just gonna say right now, the radicals are Ruthful.
The radicals are a Ruthful race.
A routful, rooty, race, revunctious rats.
Killers are Ruthless.
Killers are absolutely Ruthless.
They're the Ruthless.
That's the difference.
That's the difference in world view.
We're just imbued with so much Ruth,
that it's just, I really don't have a picture of Ruth.
I think this is why, I think this is why
more Slime Corp employees gravitate towards the,
towards the killer side.
Because one of the first psychological checks you do
when you're entering Slime Corp evaluation is,
do you have empathy?
If so, get out right now.
You just leave, leave the premises.
You'll get edged out in the free market.
If you have, if you have Ruth.
You just slide a picture of Ruth
over to the potential employee.
What's the first thing that comes to your mind?
Depending on their answer.
When they slide that picture of Ruth over,
you need that like Russian propaganda picture of that guy
holding up his hand going,
HIT!
Saying, you know.
Well, I just want to put like a little bow tie
on the UPS store.
I just want to say that it wouldn't bother me so much
if it weren't for like just the deception.
If it was just incompetency,
like if it was just like they like fucked up,
or even if it's like a scummy worker
that just is like trying to fill up a quota.
Even that is like, you know, fun.
It's the fact that like every single,
like I feel like there's nothing I can do
because I am constantly getting positive affirmation
that what's happening is going to be okay.
Like I'm getting constant like we have your address.
They're gaslighting you.
They're gaslighting you in a bigger way.
Like like in the exact same day,
I will, I will call them and like say,
this is my address.
Make sure you're delivering it right.
Because it doesn't look like you're delivering it
to the right address on your website.
And they'll be like, okay, you know, we've updated it.
Okay, so it's going to this address.
Okay, good.
Don't worry.
We're going to this address.
Like the same day, like,
oh, your address was wrong, by the way.
We didn't get your company name.
We need your company name for some reason.
We just assume.
Rowdy fuckers, cop killers.
We kill crime HQ.
Yeah, come on.
This is, this is why I like dealing with USPS
because like they're incompetent,
but it's they're always on the nose about it.
Like, you know what you're getting into
when you deal with a post office, you know?
Yeah.
There's a bunch of slums who just don't give a shit.
And they don't pretend to.
Yeah.
I mean, I've had issues with the post office,
but it's never been a rigmarole.
It's just like, yeah, we fucked up.
Sorry.
Mike, go fuck yourself.
Just in case anyone was wondering,
yes, it seems that Ruth, spelled with an E before the U,
was a middle, was a middle English word,
meaning pity or compassion,
has fallen out of use.
So that's where that comes from.
Hell yeah.
So I was just taking a big old shit and.
You did type an emergency.
That's what was urgent.
And that was an emergency.
I said BRB, urgent shit.
Oh, I didn't think you meant like it was literally a shit that
was urgent.
I had to take it back.
All right.
So I went to took an urgent shit and I was reading the manga
Planetes, the previous copyright over here.
From the guy who wrote Vinland Saga.
Have you read it yet, Nate?
It's by the guy who made Vinland Saga.
Yeah, I didn't even fucking realize that either.
Are you?
I had no fucking idea.
I only got like.
You'll be like, oh, OK, I got like two.
I mean, that was from way back in the day, right?
Oh, that that blows my mind.
I mean, obviously I just made a wee Agwa about fucking
Vinland Saga.
I'm a big fan.
Yeah, blew my mind, too.
OK.
Well, I was just reading it.
Well, I guess if you've already read the first couple
chapters, then I don't know.
You probably don't remember them, but like.
I just spent a while.
Chapter two seemed like it would interest you a lot.
It was about the main character.
So for those who don't know, Planetes is about people who
are junk collectors in space.
They collect space debris.
They're literally just trash men.
It's mostly about like the economic disparity of how we
treat people who do like blue collar jobs, essentially
even in space.
And in chapter two, the main character is like having
his doubts about whether space is cool.
He's like, space is kind of shit.
You know, everybody out here just kind of gets cancer
and loses their mind.
So it's not that great.
It's a tale of learning to love space.
Well, he was just like, man, what the fuck is the point?
Because like back on Earth, it takes place in a period
where like the sea levels have already risen.
We've used up most of the natural resources.
Did we buy Greenland, though?
I don't know.
I mean, I don't even know what country he's from necessarily
because it's in space.
But they're on the moon.
They have like a moon base.
It's basically like we've colonized the moon to some extent.
And we've got spaceships and stuff.
We've explored the outer belt, I guess, or inner belts
or whatever belt.
Anyways, he's like, I don't know, man.
Maybe fucking we weren't supposed to come to space.
And then the other lady's like, man, fuck you, dude.
We got to be in space.
It's the only way forward for humanity.
Like we just got to do it.
And then he meets this girl who was born on the moon.
And she's like, I can't even go to Earth
because like my body can't handle their atmosphere.
But like I'm letting them study me for science.
And I want them to fucking figure out how to progress
and fix a lot of these problems that we have with space.
And he's like, you know what?
Maybe space isn't so bad.
It's got space in the place.
Hashtag to my 2003.
I thought you'd appreciate it, Nate, because it's just like he's
having his doubts about human progress
and whether it's all worth it.
And then this girl from space is like, nah, dude.
That was a good chapter.
This guy's, fuck.
These guys are living and doing real shit,
facing real issues.
But like ultimately, I mean, what are you going to do?
Good chapter also though, long.
Not, I was, you know, I'm just trying to read a chapter
while I take a shit and get back to the PCP.
And I'm like, oh God, like what the fuck does this end?
I have to go back.
I'm going to get a penalty if I fucking miss too much.
People have been telling me for a long time
that I should, you know, read, watch whatever
Planet is because I would love it.
I never, I didn't get that far into it,
but I read a bunch.
It's funny, Nate, that you haven't like read it completely
because you gave it to me as a gift, like the first one.
I know, I know.
And you were talking up like, yeah, this is great.
You'll love it.
And I was like, oh, this must be a favorite of Nate's.
And you're just like, yeah, I never read it.
Well, people told me that and I read some of it
and thought it was great.
So I'll get, I'll finish it one of these days.
Speaking of, it's not even that long.
Yeah, I think you're right.
I think you're right.
Speaking of reading, what a common thing, right?
I don't want to get too deep into all the punk ass
bitches in the comments last episode railing against me,
but one common refrain was that, oh, Ben, oh, Ben, just what?
Ben's just parroting a bunch of YouTube people.
Ben, just watch, he uses the talking mouthpiece
for all these YouTube, he's never even read a book.
Well, I read a book.
I finished Peter Kropotkin's Conquest of Bread yesterday.
And here's my, here's my review of it.
It's, it's, it's informative, but it's very outdated.
He talks a lot.
Okay.
He talks, he talks a lot about why we should communism,
which cool, a lot of that comes off as kind of
sermonizing, but I don't mind that.
It's pretty good.
I like it.
And a lot of it is him talking about like, okay,
but how will we do the revolution?
How will we survive?
How will we feed ourselves?
And there's a lot of nitty gritty, like with
intensive farming methods.
Here's how many bushels per acre,
you know, the typical Parisian farmer could produce.
And, and, and it's very outdated.
And he's like, did you know that in America,
they actually, certain cities actually pump hot water
into homes in addition to cold water?
We could do that too, guys.
The future is going to be fucking sick.
Okay.
So it's, it's pretty short though.
How, do you know when he wrote it and where he's from?
I just, so I,
Well, he's, he's from Russia.
Okay.
Russian.
Ben.
I don't know the exact year.
Okay.
Ben, if you're going to be reading political books,
I have one I recommend, which is fucking Yang's book.
I read it.
Oh, the war on normal.
Yeah, I read it and it was great.
And I agree with everything he has to say.
Yang is my man.
Yang is pretty cool.
I won't say agree with everything he has to say,
but most of it, like the vast majority of the
just his perspective on,
I think the most important thing about Yang to me
is not just his ideas of like what to do,
but just the fact that he seems to actually know
what's happening.
Like the thing that I've been saying about like
all the politicians and stuff is like,
they're talking about plans of action for a world
that to me doesn't exist.
You know, that I'm like,
that's not the way things are though.
Like if you're not taking into account the internet,
you don't understand how like
the businesses are run there,
then you don't know what the fuck the world even is
right now.
You know, and we know.
I mean, Yang's like 40 something.
Yeah.
Yang's like 40 something.
All the other like of so many of the other
Democratic candidates are like 80 plus.
He's like 40 something.
And he's his whole entire background is working
it for startups.
You know, like all he's done.
He's also a gamer.
He is.
He played a lot of Starcraft.
Starcraft player.
Yeah.
He mentioned, he thought there's a whole chapter
about gaming in the book about like basically
how video games have.
How they need to rise up.
Well, mostly he's talking about how he's like,
you know, I understand video games and how
addicting they are and like why they're so good,
but they are ruining our men like.
Yeah.
He's he's it's a case.
I know is like the type of men he describes are
literally guys.
I know like guys who have completely been
subsumed into putting the focus on the wrong
people.
Women need to compete with video games with
enhanced surgically enhanced sexiness.
It's the only way to keep the arms race going.
We have to do it.
Yang is pretty cool.
I like him.
I know I've been hyping him up.
I've been hyping him up on Twitter lately,
selling Yang shirts.
It's all pretty great.
I'm not voting for him.
My motto is vote.
Well, he won't win anyway, so.
Vote Bernie where Yang.
Yeah, I'm voting Bernie.
I love if the polls changed and like Yang surged
ahead, I would vote for him.
Okay.
But like he's not going to win.
I'm going to vote for Bernie because he can
actually and also I like Bernie.
Let's say you had the vote.
Your only vote mattered.
You are.
No, throw.
Okay.
Did you throw your vote away on Yang so
Biden will win.
Great.
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
Okay.
You're talking about like what if you just don't
care.
He's right.
I don't know.
Yeah, I'm talking about what makes you think
that like I would not vote for Bernie.
Like I wouldn't do that.
Why would you not vote for?
Oh my god.
Why would you not vote for Bernie?
I wouldn't vote for anybody but Yang.
I would not vote for anybody but Yang.
Peer.
Oh my god.
Digi, you don't understand.
You don't understand.
What do I not understand?
What's the stake?
Fucking Biden's going to win.
Biden.
Okay, Biden's not going to win.
Like you, Biden's going to win.
All right.
First of all, none of them are going to be
Trump.
No, he's way worse than Obama.
He sucks.
Okay.
Also, he's literally demented.
Like he's clearly has like brain.
He does not seem particularly on the ball.
He is not on the, he's not on the fucking ball.
I agree.
And Bernie fucking rules, okay?
I don't know if you know anything about
Bernie but Bernie rules.
If the Democrats pick Joe Biden, they will
be just signing their death warrant.
There's no profit.
Exactly.
Yeah, that seems true.
It seems true.
Yes.
That's one, that's one of the things I'm
saying to you.
From what I've heard,
Bernie is currently third behind Warren and Biden.
Here's the thing.
Here's the thing about Yang.
I like Yang.
He's not going to win.
But he's young, right?
Like he can run again.
Well, that's why you have to vote for him
because you need to build up the
cachet of his reputation.
But he's, I want like you.
Okay.
Look, Democratic Party.
I see what you're saying, but I don't agree.
Nobody, none of the Democratic candidates
have a fucking chance against Trump.
Maybe Yang would, but he's not big enough.
No, Bernie could win.
I start, Bernie could absolutely win.
I don't know.
I don't know about that.
He could, he could have won in 2016.
He could win in 2012.
A lot of people do not like Trump.
Bernie is the only one who I think would
even have a chance, but like.
Exactly.
I also think that.
Exactly, exactly, did she?
I don't think he would.
Oh my God.
Well, okay.
I don't agree.
Whatever.
Man, what happened to hating boomers?
Let's bring back the hatred of old people.
That's the bad I know and love.
There's a, there's a small undercurrent.
Okay.
There's a small undercurrent.
Bernie's the good kind of boomer.
Bernie like threw trash at like,
separatists during the civil rights movement and stuff.
Bernie's a champion.
This conversation is the war on normal people.
Wait, hold on a minute.
Wait, I want to.
Speaking of books, speaking of books,
there's another, there is a book that I do really want to read
that's called Bullshit Jobs.
Uh-huh.
You ever heard of that one?
I don't think so.
It is just, it's just about how like.
Every job, every job.
It's just about how like most job,
or like tons of jobs.
I mean, in, in like the modern world.
Hey, hey, you know how.
Literally do not contribute anything.
You know how micro does that show dirty jobs?
They exist purely to be middlemen who like just,
just like do not contribute to the actual chain of supply.
Micro does that job dirty jobs.
I want to do my show bullshit jobs.
Just too pointless.
Don't add value to the world or anyone.
That's, that's going to be my show.
You're already doing the bullshit job right now.
We're all fucking on YouTube.
Yeah.
You're right.
By Dave, David, Bullshit Jobs by David Graber.
This is a book I've been hearing about a lot
that I want to read.
I have two books.
One for Ben and one for the audience.
For Ben, I recommend God and the State
by Mikal Bakunin.
Mikal Bakunin.
God and the State.
Oh Bakunin.
Bakunin is the guy who thinks inheritance is immoral.
He's my boy.
Yeah.
Basculean.
Bananas.
Yes.
I understand now.
Bananas.
Okay.
That's right.
So I've been, it warrants my heart that you actually
paid attention to a reference or like a reference
that I gave you.
Yeah.
The, that, that, the revolution.
I listened to the, I want to go back and listen to more
because there's probably more.
Oh yeah.
Oh, there's way more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh God.
It's so cool that bird, bird.
Dude.
Okay.
I, I was good.
We're talking about theories.
What's the other book though?
Well, hold on.
Wait.
Actually before that, because this is way more important.
I was pacing back and forth last night again,
as I mentioned, just running back and forth in my room,
just seething in anger about UPS.
And I got thinking about how like it's,
it's sort of a weird melodramatic statement.
But I don't mean it any such thing,
but I almost feel like I don't relate to anyone anymore.
Not that I have surpassed them in any level of intellect,
not even remotely that, but just as in like,
I feel as though my interests are so different
from the people I surround myself with,
that like we just have different interests.
And it's not a bad or good thing.
It just is a difference in taste.
And hashtag parents will never get it.
Got it.
No, no.
That's, specifically, no.
What you are describing is how I ended up in the internet
and in this group.
Like this is exactly, it was just like a gradual process
of like the more I got into being a YouTuber
and doing things that not, that most people don't do,
the more it's like my friends just literally can't relate.
It's just like, it wasn't like we had a falling out
or we stopped being friends or anything.
It's like they were into playing video games.
I was into making YouTube videos.
And like they didn't really want to make YouTube videos.
And I didn't really want to play video games.
And like the only people I could find
who I could really relate to are other people
who were doing not just YouTube videos,
but like a similar type.
Like that's kind of how this group got formed.
It's like, oh, these are all people who are not just even
like doing my little pony analysis videos,
but like doing it with a certain attitude of like being capable
of like a more in-depth analysis,
but not taking it seriously, having this attitude of like,
yeah, we could just have fun and be kind of edgy.
And you know, just like analyze this show
because it's entertaining to do
and intellectually stimulating exercise.
But like, you know, it's like, yeah,
these are the only people doing this,
something close enough to what I'm doing
that I can even have a conversation
about the things that I'm, that like matter to me.
Cause like even, you can't even like talk to fans
or like other kinds of creators
if you're just trying to talk about like the reception
of your work or like what it's like to do this job.
No one fucking gets it at all, you know?
And you can like, you can make it vague enough
that other people kind of get it.
You know, you can kind of say, you know,
use metaphor to some extent to make people understand
like what you're dealing with,
but like just the specifics of it,
it's like, it's, it's a new job.
No one's done it and nobody gets it.
It is definitely the most alienating hell imaginable
and you will lose everyone you love and care about.
That is definitely true.
Those are maybe a negative.
I'm feeling that didgy, but not so much for what I'm doing.
More so like, it's funny that you use that metaphor
as in like what got you into this group,
whereas suppose I feel it's almost shifting away,
not in a, in a, in a, and again,
it's like so easy to take the words I'm saying
and assign like a malice or a sort of like, I don't know,
even a victim hood, that's not all I mean.
I'll even expand on what I said and say,
like I feel the same way about this group too,
that I don't talk to these guys as much
because we're not as much all doing the exact same thing.
And like all of us kind of have other stuff going on that like,
we're definitely in late stage PCP.
Yeah.
This is going down soon.
It's like, it's harder for me to communicate
with like Munchie or Ben because,
or anybody who's in the fucking endless war
because I don't participate in it
and like a huge amount of the conversation.
Like for anybody wondering, like when we get together now,
if you get Ben and Munchie in the same room,
it is an endless war of endless war.
It's just endless war all the time.
And it's like, I literally don't know
what they're talking about.
So like.
I understand Digi in this war's rock.
I click the link in the description.
I feel whenever I get on the PCP,
I have shows where it's like,
the core appeal is my personality
and I'm selling my ideas for, you know,
I'm to the people, to the masses,
the PCP and RFCK, the show.
And it's weird because I get on these
and I'm like, okay, I'm ready to talk
and I have ideas in my mind
that I'm really passionate about
and I think about it.
I meditate on day in and day out.
And I get on like, oh wait, like I would be really boring
if I were to just like monologue for like an hour
and then like say a thing
and then like no one has anything to input on
because none of them are thinking
or care about the same things I do.
And a chief among them, I mean, there's more than this,
but chief among them is like the thing
that I always bring up and feel super embarrassed about
which is history, where there's no way you can say
that you like history
without being a fucking pretentious snob.
And just, and people like,
even when they hear the words history, they're like,
oh God, look at the, who does this guy think he fucking is?
Whereas I've always maintained that just is anime,
just is media, history just is like a cartoon show
that you watch.
And it's interesting the exact same,
literally exact same ways that any other show would be.
So that's where most of my ideas come from
and most of what I'm thinking about.
The book that I was going to recommend
is a 32 hour Napoleon biography,
Napoleon A Life by Andrew Roberts.
Fantastic, great book.
And I just had so many ideas
and I was thinking so much about it
about all the quotes from Napoleon,
all the ups and turns of that.
I just wanted to talk to someone about it so badly
and just suggest it, but like there's no one
I can do that with that I know.
Like there's absolutely no one, like no one would care.
Like it's-
I care.
I care about Napoleon.
I remember the time that he went to the water park,
that was really cool.
Oh!
Yeah.
Trash.
I, it's boring for both people, right?
Where it's like, it's boring for someone who doesn't care
to be like, oh yeah, he's like just saying things to me now.
Like he's just repeating a thing
that has happened before, yawn.
It's also boring for me
because it's like I'm just saying a thing to someone
and then they're like, cool.
You know, there's no conversation.
There's no actual discussion of things.
It's fucking, it's boring.
I feel like stifled, but not in like,
again, it's not like an outward,
like people have done it to me.
It's just like, I don't know.
I don't know how to fix it.
I don't know how I got on this.
I don't know, I started talking about this.
Munchy, did you read God in the State?
Yeah, I haven't finished it, but I read like,
I think I read like a third of it.
Munchy, here's what I reckon about, unironically.
Podcast.
I'm glad you reminded me about Bacuna.
Podcast about all these things
because what I found in,
this is what I originally loved about Twitter
and it's also true of just anywhere.
If you just like talk about something in a big enough sphere
where enough people see it,
guaranteed one of them cares.
So like, if you make a podcast about Napoleon,
like 99% chance somebody in your comments
knows even more about Napoleon than you do
and would love to have a conversation
about Napoleon with you, you know?
So like, you just got to kind of like farm around.
You know, you just got to like make public,
cause like, I think I described Twitter once
as a place where you could just announce your desire
to have a conversation with somebody
to as many people as possible
and maybe one of them wants to have that conversation,
you know, which is something that, you know,
you can't do at home.
It's just there's not enough people around you
with the same interests.
It's fun you bring up that specific thing
because last night, again, I was, oh, you PS Minecraft,
did you bro?
Because I was thinking a lot about the whirling dervish
about how I really, really have enjoyed it so far
and I listened to all of it.
Yeah, and I've gotten really like,
because more and more I felt like, yeah,
conversations are good
and like I love listening to podcasts
when both the co-house are on the same page, right?
But like, there's something so direct
about the whirling dervish
because just is like you just saying what you believe
and it's not like, it's not like you are saying it
and then the other person just has to constantly give like,
yeah, or it's like they butt in about like,
I don't know, just whatever, you know,
you could just have like a full complete point
and it feels so much more dense than another thing.
Even if it had the exact same content,
just the idea that there's another person there
who like isn't speaking can like clutter the perception
of it just being like a one-sided conversation
that feels somewhat awkward.
So I love that, I was thinking about that.
And last night, I don't know, I think I said this earlier,
but I opened up a voice recorder
and I just wanted to speak aloud.
I was going to write down all my thoughts,
but writing is really agonizing for me
and I hate it even when it's extremely conscious.
Like it just, there's just something wrong with my brain.
And so I wanted to talk aloud and just speak to myself.
I thought it'd be awkward.
So I just recorded a podcast that I wasn't going to release.
I might release it now,
but it was literally what you were describing
just like about the point about what I was thinking about.
And also just like all about what I have just described today.
I had practiced around for this very podcast last night.
Yeah, I mean, I've done that plenty of times as well.
Just like recorded a podcast about something
and then just been like, yeah, well,
I understand that I wanted to get that off my chest,
but that was not interesting.
So I just throw it away, you know.
Did you guys know that dinosaurs are a conspiracy?
They're not real.
They never existed.
I just know that endless jess is a conspiracy.
I think I've probably believed you.
He's actually an ARG that I created.
What's the basis of this?
I've been getting really into this no dinosaurs conspiracy.
All right, I want to know.
Cause I mean, like, I'm sad about it.
I'm already engaged.
I mean, like I'm really, I'm really actually upset about it
because like my baseline is that I believe
every conspiracy is true until proven otherwise.
So if I just hear something that sounds like outrageous enough,
I'm like, oh no, that must be true.
Oh no, the world's even worse than I thought it was.
And so I found out there's no dinosaurs
that it was all made up.
There's a guy who like, I guess like they, you know,
paleontologists are only allowed to dig in certain areas
and they came in and they put the bones there
and the bones are made up
and they were made out of salt or something,
some shit, I don't know.
It made no sense, but I believe it.
God put them there to trick us into thinking
that evolution was there.
Well, yeah, that's the thing.
It's like a subset of the evolution as a myth conspiracy.
You know guys, I believe the Creeges Museum in Kentucky
right across the river from here
and they have confirmed, they have confirmed for me
that man, dinosaurs were on the ark with Noah.
They just died of unrelated causes afterward.
Well, I hope so because that's better than the alternative.
The dinosaurs were totally fake and never existed
because the idea that they existed as we believe,
I don't believe that anymore.
I already saw the conspiracy
so I have to believe it.
Sounds right.
You know, yeah, because I guess,
I think the gist of it was that like the powers that be
don't want us to believe the truth,
which is that God created Adam and Eve
and they wrote on dinosaurs or something.
Okay.
No, they want us to believe that there were dinosaurs
and then people were monkeys and then came into,
I don't know, the point is some guy said it,
so I believe it, fuck it, and I'm sad now.
I want there to be dinosaurs.
You know what?
Conspiracies are bullshit.
I'm not a conspiracy guy anymore.
I'm totally, in fact, I'm anti-conspiracy.
I don't believe anything anyone tells me unless it's cool.
You know what?
That's my new philosophy.
Forget all my previous philosophies.
My new philosophy is only believe what's cool.
And if you hear something that sounds cool, it's true.
And if you hear something, no, no.
And if it sounds bad, then it's not true.
That's, it doesn't know, fake and real are constructs.
Honestly, that's like a healthy way to live.
That's like a real way to live.
What if I think like basically everything sounds cool
no matter how bad it is?
Like, am I the only one who,
when something like really awful happens,
I feel kind of like, like, yeah.
No.
I get what you're saying.
Like, what do you define really bad, did you?
Like a school shooting?
Like 9-11 happened, you were like, yeah.
No, no.
Yeah.
You're quietly to yourself.
I guess more like complex things
that seem like they would happen on TV, you know?
You go like, oh, shit, that's right.
Like, people really are fucking complicated
and weird and crazy.
It's like art really does imitate art.
No, I mean, yeah, there's a whole George Carlin
bit about that where he's like,
I kind of like it when a lot of people die.
And it's like, yeah, yeah, I'm with you, man.
I'm with you 100%.
It's fucking cool and funny when a lot of people die.
Maybe it'll help me articulate this better
because I literally just spring into my mind.
I don't know how to articulate this at all.
And he made that bit and he recorded it for an album
and like the next day, September 11th happened.
Oh my God.
So like it had, that album wasn't released,
but it's hilarious.
I just want to say, by the way,
before we lose sight of the real point of this conversation,
which is dinosaurs being great.
Digi, Digi Dino has been sitting in a cell for years.
Now he's turned into a fossil.
When will you revive him?
Please, please, please, please.
What do you want me to do with Digi Dino?
Please, please.
Have him post meme review or something.
I don't know.
I don't even think I have the files anymore.
That's on like an old computer.
Dude, don't worry, bro.
He's got you covered.
No, I got you, bro.
We're going to get like 50 animations.
I'm always hesitant to use.
I have like some, you know, certain pieces of old munchie
art on my computer.
I'm going to, in fact, post one in the chat
so we can have it in the show notes.
One that I've used it one time for a shitty attempt
at a freestyle that I posted on SoundCloud.
I don't even remember this.
That's the only thing I've ever used it for.
It's this one, the Special Forces Anime Guru Hobo Digi.
Oh, yeah, no, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I remember this.
I'm always hesitant to use any old munchie art for anything
because munchie will scream at me about how it's shit art
that he made when he was a baby and he needs to redo it
and replace it every time.
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, Digi, hold on.
I just want to clear my name, by the way,
because I understand why you would think that.
But I just want to like remind you that like things change
and it's been like four years since that this last happened.
That's not true.
I don't know if it's been four years, but maybe two years.
Well, okay, it's been literally four seconds
since Muncie questioned every piece of art
he's ever put pen to paper on and created.
I think old munchie art looks really like grody
for about like a better word.
Like it looks like weird.
If you look at my old like pony art,
it's like a fucking like, it's like a wax museum.
It's like a strange uncanny experience.
But I have no problem with anyone posting it in any context
and I would love it if you were to use
any art of mine ever, Digi.
So I'm just going to use this hobo as my avatar
everywhere from now on forever.
This is the best art of me that exists probably.
But just make sure you realize that you are Asgore
and you were destroying the undertale.
Instead of mercy, it's a good taste just there.
Oh, am I supposed to be Asgore?
What the fuck?
Yeah, yeah.
It's got a trident and a cape, I guess.
Yeah.
I had no hype.
Ever.
Remember Asgore, guys?
Yeah, he's pretty cool.
Best anime ever.
He was daddy.
He was a daddy in a big way.
Yeah, but yeah, see, look at this fucking dinosaur hoax
page I just linked.
I mean, look at how many words are on this page.
It must be true.
And they've written so many words on this map.
Why did they label it themselves as a conspiracy?
No, they labeled it as a conspiracy.
We've got to move to Dinosauria.
When everyone's like, oh, the sea levels are right now, fuck.
I'm fine in Dinosauria.
Guys, the PCP has assigned a single release contract
with Dinosauria.
It's going to be the one-stop shop for the PCP from now on.
Jesse, I think you're going to have to rethink your logic
here, because there's actually not that many words.
If you only go 40% of the other way down the page,
it becomes the comments.
So half of this page is comments,
and also the formatting of the page
is such that there is just one tiny column.
So you're right.
It's mostly comments.
It would be like five paragraphs, and that's it.
You see, that's right, because I form most of my opinions
on 40% of anything.
Makes sense.
That's as much as I care to read.
I just saw this on the page, and I appreciate it immensely.
Make your own.
Full proof instructions for budding paleontologists.
You know that I really wanted to be a paleontologist
when I was a kid?
So did I.
That's a real kid goal.
I wanted to be an astronomer.
Obviously, because of Jurassic Park.
But I had a book called The Big Book of Dinosaurs.
It was like fucking 12,000 pages,
this gigantic phone book of every page
which just had a different dinosaur and a shitload
of facts about them, which had blown my mind,
because there's only 12 dinosaurs anybody talks about,
but this book had like fucking hundreds of dinosaurs in it.
That's pretty sick.
That was more of a space kid.
Honestly, like the planets.
If someone can actually convince me
that dinosaurs never existed, you
will make me depressed for the rest of my life.
Well, I mean, this guy, apparently the guy who
makes this blog, Eric Dubey, I clicked on the link
to see what he is.
I mean, this is in very tiny resolution,
but there's this picture of him in a meditative pose.
He looks so smart.
Oh, crap.
He definitely wasn't in that bed.
He definitely took a picture of himself in a meditative
and then Google search like cool eclectic meditation bedroom
and then Photoshopped himself on top of it.
Yeah, it's a high level, high IQ move.
His blogs, Natural First, Eric's Esoterics, The Atlantean
Conspiracy, the Happy Health Homepage, and Bangkok Wing Chun.
He's a yoga and Wing Chun part time teacher
while exposing the New World Order.
This is his claim about him.
Oh, Hulcogan, Scott Hall, and Kevin Nash.
They're at it again.
The New World Order is always messing shit up for everyone.
I want to give a shout to my, when I was a kid,
I was like, it's weird to think how when I was a kid,
I just believed conspiracy theories
and wasn't even scared about it.
Wasn't even like, placed a lot of emphasis on it.
I was just like, oh, spirit science?
That's probably true.
Oh, just whatever conspiracy, that's just probably true.
That makes sense.
Unironically, love all conspiracy theories.
And I believe a few of them.
OK, wait, I've got a recommendation for Jesse.
Storm Cloud's Gathering.
Storm Cloud's Gathering has some classic Obama conspiracy
videos, just classic.
A lot of World War III predictions
that he says is going to start in 2014.
So I'm excited to see how he's justified it.
It's a very cold war going on, very cold war.
I want to make a channel, just for a separate YouTube channel,
just for talking about conspiracies
and how cool they all are, even the scary ones,
especially the scary ones.
I would be damned for that 100%.
And have it not even attached to me in any way
that anyone can trace back to me.
Because the sad thing is that you can't even
appreciate conspiracy theories, because if you
talk about them at all, people label you something,
or this or that, or think you're an evil idiot asshole.
But it's like, I don't care if it's true or not.
They're just fucking cool.
They're all awesome.
Have you guys ever watched any of that?
Fall down a rabbit hole and finding the evidence,
and finding the connections, and hearing people,
like the experts on them, like the crypto experts and shit.
It's so fun.
It's so cool.
Have you ever watched, before Alex Jones did his radio show,
he made huge documentary movies.
And I've watched all of them, and they're fascinating.
Oh, OK.
If you never had no idea.
You got to watch The Obama Deception.
That's a fucking masterpiece.
What's the gist of that one?
That Obama's a puppet of the New World Order.
And there's a whole thing.
That's definitely true.
Easy.
His first videos where he storms Bohemian Grove
and tries to break into this place where all these rich people
hang out.
That's how you get them.
You start them with stuff that's totally obviously true.
Like, yeah, Obama's a puppet of the New World Order.
So that's how you get into conspiracy.
And then from there, you can slowly get more and more
until you're where dinosaurs weren't real.
Oh, shit.
What?
You know, this first comment by Alex Jones.
It's all about the clockwork elves and the psychic pedophiles.
Oh, you know, the biggest thing he thinks
is, I've seen some of this, the biggest thing he thinks
is that the elites of our world are attempting
to create an interdimensional psychic separation where
they're going to, I think, clone themselves.
It's like literally the plot of Evangelion,
where they're trying to separate themselves
into a higher plane of existence.
I believe that.
In some interdimensional connection thing,
it like leaves the rest of humanity behind or something.
There are very few things Alex Jones has said that I didn't
think.
Yeah, that sounds plausible.
I mean, I have definitely changed the wording a little bit.
It definitely seems reasonable to me
that there are extradimensional beings that have manipulated
and convinced the elite of our society
that by sacrificing children and having blood rituals,
they can ascend to a higher plane of being
by selling humanity's souls, by convincing everybody
that we don't have souls.
What else do you have to do at that point?
You've conquered all of new society at that point.
I've been getting really into the paranormal board
on 4chan, which is like pole times 1,000.
It's like, it's where the really wild stuff happens.
If everyone wants to really pull back the lid,
I recommend the paranormal board on 4chan.
That's the cool shit.
Because all the information is 4chan.
So it's all conveniently put into these little PNG images
and these old graphs.
And you can look at one image and go, oh, shit.
I understand the whole world now.
Everything's fucked and there's no dinosaur as shit.
I didn't realize how conspiratorially driven X was.
But I guess I should start going on there.
I mean, it used to be, years and years ago,
when I first started looking at it and stuff,
it used to be just creepy postures and scary shit
and spooky ghosts and stuff.
And then from there, it turned into a lot of Tulpa shit.
And then from there, somehow that morphed into more New World
order.
I guess because the whole world just got way too political
at a certain point.
Probably around 2016.
So all the scary spooky shit kind of dissipated from X.
And it sort of got more and more into like, hey,
you know these fucking New World order guys
are sacrificing children to alien beings.
Oh, you know what the best part of the 2016 presidential
election was?
Was learning about Hillary Clinton's spirit cooking?
That was legitimately my favorite fucking part,
was learning about spirit cooking,
about all the crazy shit that Hillary Clinton does
and her fucking dance pad orgies with spirit cooking.
What is spirit cooking and why do I keep hearing about it?
Well, it's because it's my favorite thing in the entire world
and I constantly bring it up.
So it's a thing where you take like a mutilated corpse
and then just start eating it and boiling it
and just sort of just fucking around with it in the kitchen.
It makes it a delicious meal, man.
So it's just cannibalistic?
OK, listen to this.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It doesn't say cannibalistic, too.
That's another big aspect of the police.
Urban Dictionary's goddess covered with this.
OK, spirit cooking, a verb, an action
in which ranking members of the Democratic Party
ejaculate into an open wound on the breast milk soaked
left hand in a quote, art form, similar to that
of watercolor finger paints.
That doesn't explain anything.
No, I don't understand.
That's the only definition on here, by the way.
It doesn't even have anything to do with eating.
I don't know.
I know, first of it is that it's spooky cannibalism,
not normal cannibalism, but just like specifically
is cannibalism meant to scare you?
You know, actually, the time I heard spirit cooking recently.
That's totally OK.
Out of interest, I wanted to hear Alex Jones take
on the whole Epstein thing, who, by the way, was like,
the thing about Alex Jones that's fucked up
is that he seems to spout these wildly ridiculous claims.
And then like 20 years later, he's proved like mostly
correct about some of them.
Like everything that we know as being true in history
was at some point labeled a conspiracy theory.
That's true.
And I'm not saying that Alex Jones is right over time.
I remember reading about Epstein and his island
in like 2009.
Alex Jones was one of the big guys saying
Epstein was up to fuck shit like before anyone else.
Everyone now is taking it as a given.
Like it's like, oh, yeah, that totally happened.
Well, like when people were saying
it was happening eight years ago,
everyone was saying, no, you're a conspiracy buff.
Yeah.
Well, I heard Alex Jones say that specifically
they were doing satanic spirit cooking on Epstein's island.
It always has to be fascinating.
I talk about it in some of my videos for the last year.
So this idea I have of the Otaku hero
and how it's split between a character
that I call the mad scientist and the living computer.
And the mad scientist is somebody
who can make all these connections
and figure out all these things that are happening in the world.
And he understands that they must be true,
but cannot prove it or cannot find a way to convince people.
And the living computer is the extremely logic driven person
who is able to just like take in all this data.
But like they will only believe something
when they have the data in front of them.
And like-
I think there's a third version here,
which is the fuck machine,
which started with Tenchi Muyo back in the day,
which is the original breeder.
Anyway.
But go on.
So like, I think that a mad scientist
will always figure things out before everybody else does,
but nobody's gonna believe it
until the computer has proven it, you know,
until we have the data.
And that's the drama of the series.
It's just funny because like,
wait, the what?
The trauma-
That's the drama, like the drama of the series
is that he knows something,
he's trying to prove it to the rest of the world.
That's just the life story of Johnny Old School.
Yeah, well, I mean, it's the life story of anybody,
like anybody who is capable of recognizing things,
they can't explain, it's just like,
you can talk about it all day,
but nobody's gonna believe it until they see the data.
And like, you know, I think all of us have a few things
that we like, we are fairly confident are true.
And we're like, we're like, I know that
I've seen all the connections, but I don't know how to,
I don't know how to verbalize them,
or like, I don't know where I can pull the evidence from,
or like, I don't have the science to back it,
but it is observably the case, you know?
Most people feel that way, I'm sure.
Yeah, and like, other people will just say,
oh, you say it's observably the case,
but I mean, you know, it could be this other thing.
And it's like, okay, yeah, I guess, it could be that,
but also, this is obviously true, you know?
So it's something like the Epstein thing, it's like,
yeah, unless there was evidence,
no matter how obvious it might've been that it was true,
it's just not going to be believed.
And I mean, when you hear something
that at first sounds completely impossibly insane
and outrageous, like all the millionaires and billionaires
are secretly fucking kids, you know?
But then that turns out to be true?
Well, then why wouldn't you also believe,
oh yeah, also by the way,
the world is run by like satanic cannibals that also,
like, yeah, I believe it, I mean, fuck,
no one believed the kids thing,
but that turned out to be true, fuck it.
I mean, we're just talking about like,
the path of conspiracy, conspiratorial thinking.
I mean, this first comment here by anonymous really,
really spells out how we all feel.
I think he goes,
dude, my brain can't handle another lid
being blown off the lie machine.
First I find they messed with the shape of the earth,
set up a military industrial complex like space agency,
and now all the dinosaur bones shoved in my face
since I was a child as a hoax too, my heart is broken.
I have been lied to on so many levels my whole life.
Why?
The only thing that makes the most sense
is their fear of God and his power to make or break creation.
If anything, it proves more and more
we have been warned in the Bible
that the enemy is the father of lies.
What's next?
Radical Islam is the pure religion
and the sheep will run to it.
So sad.
I'm so sad.
I'm with you anonymous.
What's this about late jazz?
Yeah, written by my alter ego, anonymous.
What does he mean they fucked with the shape of the earth?
He's talking about flat earth shit, clearly.
He's clearly, you know.
They unflattened the earth.
Like the earth was flat, but these fucking globalists.
That's why they're called the globalists.
Yeah, the parentheses, parentheses, parentheses,
globalists took that flat earth and wrapped it into a ball
just to fuck with all of us.
So they could hold it in their hands
as they power over everything.
The deepest conspiracy of all,
to turn the world into a globe.
They did it.
They did it, those monsters.
Who's got any more spell side?
We can't top this.
Peace of the HQ ice wall.
We should do it at the ice wall.
Radcon five, atop the ice wall.
We threw the earth this flat at Radcon five.
That's the big vlog.
That's the big vlog, on air.
Let's go to voicemail's people.
Link below, speak pipe, leave us voicemails.
You know the drill people.
We will play the good ones.
We got like six, I think.
Okay, first one.
This is from, I think it's a misspelled rusty shackle
for it, but I think that's the idea was going for.
And he's apparently got a big problem.
So let's see what he's got for us.
Go.
All right, PCP, I got a big fucking problem for you.
I just recently moved into college.
And you know, my dorm mates, they're pretty cool guys.
You know, no problems there.
The big problem is I can't fucking have time
to jack off here.
There's no fucking privacy.
There's always somebody in the dorm
that would hear me do it.
And I just, I just need to do it.
I need to jack off.
Please, please tell me how I can find time to jack off.
I got it.
I know the answer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's definitely you problem.
You got it.
Get a girlfriend, bro.
Get a girlfriend.
And here's why.
People will leave you alone with your girlfriend
thinking you're going to have sex there,
but then you can jack off.
That's not a bad strategy, but I also think, look,
I've shared rooms with people many times.
I've gotten away with jacking off nightly
with other people in the room.
All you got to do is build on the edge of your bed,
just put like a fuckload of blankets and pillows.
Just like build a fort, essentially,
like a wall of like, I used to have,
I shared my room with two other guys.
I had a big, just like one half of my bed.
I just had like all of my pillows and blankets
just stacked on that side of the bed.
So you could not see.
I mean, I don't know if there's a reason
that you're jacking off is loud,
but I mean, all you need is to not be seen, right?
Digi, I don't know if you're on the bottom bunk
of a bunk bed, that's probably pretty difficult.
I mean, put up a sheet, just put a cover around your bed,
like just staple a sheet around the bed.
I think it's generally considered socially uncouth
to do it with other guys in the room.
I'm not going to pretend like.
I don't care about the socially uncouth.
You have to jack off.
You can't just not jack off.
I'm not going to pretend.
I haven't in emergency situations
jacked off with other guys in the room.
I certainly have, as I think most God fearing Americans
have expressed to do.
I mean, if you have to share a room with other guys,
it's like you're either sacrificing jacking off forever
or you're jacking off in a room with other guys.
You could just go do it in the bathroom.
Yeah, that's the obvious choice.
Like I don't understand why it's even a question of like,
you have to do it in the room.
Some of us don't like to hide our,
we don't like to build a wall of shame between us.
Some people like to sit in an office chair like a man,
pull down our pants and go to town
on a big wide computer screen with some sound at maximum
so everyone can hear what I'm doing.
Yeah, what does this mean?
That jacking off can be quiet.
I don't believe you.
You can improve your hygiene as well.
You can just go take a shower
whenever you want to jack off.
That's a lot of noise.
Kill two birds with one stone.
What produces noise?
I personally, I like to jack off when I go to bed.
Like it helps me get to sleep.
As I think Jesse once said,
it's the only activity that can wake you up
in the morning and put you to bed at night.
Sure.
I don't remember saying that, but it's funny.
So I'll take credit for it.
I think you said that.
But yeah, it's, you know, I can't,
I have like a pevlavian response.
Like the second I lay down in bed, I get an erection.
So I have to do something about it.
Shit.
Look, I know exactly how this guy is.
I hate it.
I can't stand it.
It's unfortunate.
And the second I see a woman, it's gone.
I remember this exact problem.
When I was in college, I shared rooms and stuff.
I remember like, I should have been like, sure.
I remember I had my PSP,
because this was like before we had, I had a smartphone.
I'd bring my PSP with the like four porn tracks
that I had loaded onto there.
I would trundle my fat ass down to the bathroom
and jerk off a few into the turlet.
And it was horrible.
And it was shameful.
And it was terrible.
Like, you know, like to watch porn.
Checking up in a bathroom is not that comfortable.
Like, if you-
No, it's not.
I agree.
Try it.
I mean, even in the shower, like you-
I would feel so, I mean, it would feel uncomfortable
doing it with like, you're in the bed.
There's another guy in like the bed
across the room or whatever.
And you'd be like, I don't know,
doesn't it take you out to be like,
oh, what if he hears me?
Oh, what if he sees the vibrations or whatever?
It's just fucking good enough system that they can't.
Like, again, if you're on the bottom bunk of a bunk bed,
just put literally staple a fucking blanket
or something around your bed and just have a sheet.
Notice how we're offering no real solutions to his problem.
What do you mean?
We're telling him like, this is,
that's not a solution, did you?
That's not a solution.
How is that not a, wait.
He asked, how do I get away with jacking off
with other people in the room?
I'm talking about a permanent-
Okay.
Put a sheet around your bed forever.
Don't just do it when you jack off.
Just put it around for privacy purposes.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Because then you could have a fucking fort you live in.
Like it's, first of all,
I would do this even if it wasn't for jacking off.
Just pretend.
Just pretend that you're retarded.
And then you can do it in front of people.
Hold hands with your bro while you're sleeping.
And, you know, like, good God-fearing Americans.
Yeah, I mean, if you're gonna have to do it secretly
with other guys in the room,
you might as well just do it openly
with other guys in the room.
You might as well all jack off together.
You might as well just all be gay.
You might as well just be boyfriends with your boys.
This method is tested and proven by me.
It works.
Build a fort of blankets.
Jack off quietly.
Whatever happened to hiding a bunch of playboys
in a tree stump in the woods?
Whatever happened to that?
I mean, that works too.
Back when I grew up in the 1970s, that's what we did.
Beep, beep.
Solid play?
Just, yeah, jacking off in the woods
is also a good option.
In the woods, in the woods.
Good, good, also.
Yeah, in the 100 acre wood.
That's where Christopher went.
The only problem with jacking off in the woods
is A, in the winter, cold.
B, bugs, grunts.
Winter's coming, winter's coming.
I think that's what the Starks were talking about.
You know, we saw the Christopher Robin movie
where he's old and he's reconnecting with Poo.
I wanna see the middle school era, Winnie the Pooh movie,
where Christopher Robin, all of his friends
wanna hang out with him in the 100 acre woods,
but he's like, I just came in here to jack off, Poo.
Leave me alone, god damn.
Oh my god.
This reminds me of, this was probably the most,
it was that exact scenario you just described,
but it was of Andy in Toy Story.
It was a robot chicken skit.
And it was that he became a teenager
and was like, oh god, this makes me actually wanna cry.
It was Buzz Lightyear.
And he's like, oh shit, we don't have a bong.
This'll do.
And they grab him, they like stick a straw into his brain
and then they're like, use him as a bong.
And then they put him back and Buzz like,
oh, what happened guys, are we going to play today?
And he's like, it's okay, Buzz, it's okay, you're gonna make.
I wanna actually cry thinking about
how he fucked up Buzz Lightyear
and made him literally retarded.
It's not, how could you do that robot chicken?
You went too far.
Let's do another voicemail before I burst into tears.
Hey P, he probably filmed himself coming all over
with Bo Peep a few times and posted it on 4chan.
Most people do.
That's just part of growing up.
Okay, next voicemail is unhuman core.
And if I remember correctly,
I think this guy was kind of hard to understand.
So, so pay attention.
So you picked it.
Great.
Okay, yes, it's good.
So let's just go with the term
trying to come up with the definition of human core,
you guys.
It was like,
I came to a conclusion about the most unhuman core thing
I ever did.
And I think it might help you guys
because the second opposite of human core,
monster core, demon core.
Okay.
I think I ever did.
So, I went to the movies with this show,
my grandma bought to me,
it was a floral pattern.
Got me looking pretty gay.
So when I got inside the movie theater with my boys,
I decided to bring up the scene from the Simpsons.
I don't know if you ever saw that episode,
the best fucking episode.
And when they meet John Waters,
they meet a gay man,
and they get paranoid that Bach might be gay.
And Bach comes like walking,
like a little faggot with fucking flowers.
So I got up on my seat to imitate that scene.
I accidentally kicked my fucking popcorn on the floor.
And my friends started laughing at me.
I fucking ate the fucking popcorn
right out of the fucking floor,
looking straight into the fucking night.
So they don't fucking know me.
I am a slave to society.
I don't live in a society.
I am the guy from Seven,
I am the Joker, and I am a demon.
So that's his demon's core story.
That's the most demon core.
Demon core is eating your movie popcorn off
while staring at your friends in the eyes.
After you kick it off your lap,
because you're laughing so hard
at the scene where Bart's cross-dressing
in the John Waters episode of The Simpsons.
Yes.
That is a very demon core.
Yeah, I understand.
But he, some, he just,
I understand none of it.
He's watching The Simpsons on his phone
in the movie theater.
He made me misunderstand,
he didn't, I think his friends maliciously
to make fun of him,
and that's why he's defiantly eating the popcorn
on the ground.
Oh, you think so?
That's why he said that you don't own me.
That's why he's saying,
he's looking in the,
I mean, it's fucking honestly,
like we're all trying to interpret,
because I could,
it was all of my mental ability
to understand that guy.
What's fucking accent?
That was like a fast Andre the Giant.
Hulk, Hulk, Hulk, Hulk, Hulk, Hulk, Hulk, Hulk, Hulk, Hulk.
All right, well, that mystery behind us.
Something South American?
I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know.
Just tell me where you're from on human core.
Okay, next up,
Stalin's ghost is calling in.
All right, let's do it, go.
Hello, this is Stalin's ghost.
Yes, God, this is he,
Stalin, recording from hell,
where all the fucking people call me scum,
go when they die.
Okay, sure.
I have message for Mr. Nate Biestum,
just a little something that's been on my mind
for quite a while.
And I just needed to cool about it
to set the record straight.
And by straight, I mean, fuck you, Nate.
Multiple fucking times on the podcast.
Nate's best guy ever,
has referred to highly civilized
and ancient practice of programming
as motherfucking coding.
And I'm just wanting to say, Nate,
my dude gave some fucking self-respect.
I don't blame Tom or Manchi.
They're just little busy babies
that haven't gone to school to learn this sheet.
Be advised, Nate Biestum,
you are on notice and we are watching
you for further infractions.
Slava Rodinia.
Is coding like a disrespectful way
to refer to programming or something?
They're just different.
Well, they're not the same thing, are they, aren't they?
Coding means creating codes from one language to another.
Programming means to program a machine
to perform a certain set of instructions.
But you write code to program, right?
I have no idea.
I have no clue.
It sounds like some semantic bull.
It does.
It definitely is.
Is that guy's fake accent sound like Manmode's real accent?
A little bit.
Is he Russian?
Is he Ukrainian, right?
He sounded a little bit Wisconsin.
A little bit of Wisconsin in there.
That might have been bleeding through.
Oh, don't you know.
Maybe Stalin escaped Russia
and is living in Wisconsin this very day.
That's my, well, he is actually Stalin's ghost
and he did say was calling him from hell.
So, okay, I guess nevermind on that one.
Okay, moving on.
Quarren, Quarren, I guess is calling in.
Okay, great.
Go.
All right, listen up you Judsters.
Watching Radcon 3 content
was some of the best fucking shit I've ever seen on YouTube.
Nice.
Now, I won't say that I'll be able to provide
every single cent that is needed to fund Radcon 4,
where I will remind you,
Muggie is now fully legal and fully fuckable.
So, Muggie is totally possible.
Not gonna lie.
But,
But, if you were to have an upward limit
of like imagination of how much
Radcon would require financially,
what would that be?
And,
how much gay sex would be provided?
Thanks, bye.
Is this guy like a billionaire investor or something?
He's our angel investor.
He's a hundred-air investor
and has a few hundred dollars to flip around.
Hey, Radcon 4 plans have been started.
They've been discussed.
To be floated around.
We're probably gonna try to do it.
Probably, we'll probably just request this
like around the same amount of money
because that seems like reasonably what we can get.
But like, you know, we'll promote it more.
We'll probably keep our costs a little lower
because we literally run over budget
on all of these so far.
So like, we're gonna try to make sure
everybody actually gets paid this time.
So, if you're asking what the absolute most
that we would ask for is,
it would be infinite.
Like, we want as much money as possible
to do the thing, obviously.
I can't see us going above our last.
We did $9,001.
That's gotta be, like, I can't possibly see us asking
for even that much.
Is it literally $9,001?
I mean, that was the joke for T-Bat Resurrection.
Right, but how much do we actually make?
Like, should we even?
Like, $9,185.
It was in the 9,000.
I remember the meme number, I think it was 9,185,
I believe.
I think we're probably,
we did a pretty good job with three
of like not over-promising too much.
Like, keeping it reasonably to stuff we knew we could do
and then having a lot of time to do other shit.
So like, we'll probably use a similar tactic next time
of like, you know, there'll be a few core things
that'll be, but like, you know,
there are ways that we can make it
so it might be more worthwhile to pay more
or that just, you know,
yeah, again though, I think the focus this time
is gonna be on like, keeping the cost lower
and making sure everybody gets paid.
And I think like, yeah,
getting paid is part of the equation,
but like, one of the things was like,
for example, with T-Bat Resurrection,
like with all the, the shipping and everything
ate up so much more money than we thought it was going to,
that like, I think Ben and I, I think we made like,
I made $0, I definitely lost money.
I think we made like $1 for doing all the T-Bat Resurrection.
Because of the fact that I got a hotel
so that May could come with me to Boston,
it was like a huge deficit for me.
Yeah, it's understandable.
I mean, oh, it's almost like we provided a place
to stay for you and you chose not to use it,
but yeah, fair enough.
You know, you provided a place for me to stay
and I don't travel alone.
That's true, that's true.
All right, well, whatever.
There you go, people, there's some information.
We'll get back to you, we'll let you know what's going on.
Radcon 4, for me, it's gonna be all,
it's gonna be all lectures.
It's just gonna, that's my goal for Radcon 4
is crank out like at least two, at least two new lectures,
maybe more.
Can you tell us, like, let's get people hype right away
and what kind of lectures you got in mind,
if there's any.
If you want to.
Well, I know for sure I will do a Sonichu 102.
Excellent, finally a 102 course.
I will definitely do a follow up to the Christian lecture.
I had another idea to do one about the Digi Clips.
Right, yeah, John, I really want that one.
Is that the cult of the real digital believers?
It sounds great.
Like, I have scrubbed the old sources
and like all the archives of the forums have been deleted
so it would be, it would, it would probably be short.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you.
There's just not that much out there.
If I had a chance, our listeners have any info on that
that would be of use, please let us know in the comments.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That would actually be, you know, very helpful.
Anyone's got resources about like, yeah,
the Digi Clips and the real digital believer
or the real Digimon believers.
Ben was in there deep.
It's just that all the forums like got cleared
or something right.
When it was being raided by something awful,
I was in there like watching the chaos
and now like the archives don't exist.
That's fucked up.
Jesse.
Have you tried like the way back machine or anything?
I have, yes, I had no, very little luck with that.
Jesse, if you were to come to Radcon 4,
I want, I really want an insane clown posse lecture.
Yeah.
That's the one that I probably would do
that I've been thinking about.
I don't know why I haven't done a lecture yet.
Cause, well, I know why.
It's cause I detest planning for anything
and I like to show up on the, at the last minute,
two days into it and be like,
I don't know what the fuck I'm here
and just go with whatever happens.
And I mean, like the idea of like planning
and getting a whiteboard and drawing stuff on.
I was like, ah.
Oh, it's fucking easy.
We just bullshitted them as we went along.
I don't know about you guys.
I spent like two whole days before my like,
like planning it out and making notes
and like arranging things on like a whiteboard
and like, like putting thumbtacks and things
and putting red stuff.
What do I look like to use a guy who's not lazy?
For the Kingdom Hearts one,
I literally did zero preparation.
I'll be honest, like I've,
I had wanted to do a co-heating Cambria one
and I still might,
but like there is a lot of research
I would have to do in terms of just like reading
all the comics and like tie-in novels
and all that bullshit, which is a little gay.
And also it occurred to me that like,
it'll be a weird lecture to give to a bunch of people
who don't really know the music.
Cause like a big part of the intrigue as a fan is like,
oh wow, that song is about this.
That's crazy.
But the story is not the last one to talk about.
I don't know if I said this on a podcast before,
but the, the, the law, okay.
After the time skip
and after like Chris's transition and everything,
there comes a point in Sonichu
where the lore becomes completely insane.
And it is, it goes,
like the comic basically just completely breaks down
and there's so much shit that is like canonically occurring
that it just has to happen in like text dump and montage,
but it's in there.
It's canon.
Fascinating.
And it, it's, it's, and it just all comes in at once.
And it just completely muddies the waters
of what's, what the deal is.
And it, it needs, it needs a lecture.
Well, fantastic.
That's great.
Is he still like, oh, never mind, never mind.
I could do like an ICP one.
Is he still making comics?
Yes.
Slowly.
I could do an Incinclon Posse one.
And I could also,
I could definitely feasibly do like a wrestling one.
I just don't know like the angle I would approach that from
to really encompass like-
That's a huge topic.
Yeah.
Like what's his face?
Max Landis with just his, uh, what's that?
Well, who's the one?
Yeah, it's all, yeah.
It's all just about triple H.
That's not wrestling.
You know what?
It would be the most entertaining to me.
Jesse would just be like,
like the whole history in as brief as possible.
Of wrestling?
Like of the company?
No, of just all, like anything currently relevant,
you know, like any, anything that has affected the way things
are now, like getting you caught up to speed kind of like-
Like the current wrestling landscape?
Like if you wanted to get into wrestling and just tune in
to- How to get into wrestling?
That actually would be pretty useful.
Yeah, that would work.
Yeah.
Cause I'd kind of like something like that.
So I could be up on shit.
Or I could just do an entire lecture all about the repo man.
That sounds great.
The greatest wrestler of all time.
He was a guy with like a hamburger mask and a rope
and he would go around and he would repossess people's shit.
He'd repossess your car.
And the only way to stop him from repossessing your stuff
is to beat him in a wrestling match.
You-
He's a real guy.
Just with these one, this one mention,
I think you've created a demand, a searing massive demand.
And at very least at me, if no one else,
I want to know the full tale of the repo man now.
I mean, that's pretty much it.
That's the full tale of a red bear.
Oh, that was a great lecture.
Thanks.
Hey, you know what?
Also, here's an idea.
A lot of us know a lot of things that we've talked about
and we don't remember what those things are.
So if anybody else remembers something
that you think we should do a lecture on
because you think we could, let me know.
That's fair.
Yeah, why not?
Yeah, what do you want?
What do you want me to do a lecture on?
I'm open to suggestions.
I've said it before, I'll say it again.
I do plan on doing anamorphs for the next lecture.
Yes, indeed.
Oh, that's a great idea.
Dude, that's great.
I'm the target audience for that.
I'm ready.
It's going to be good.
I'm going to throw out a number though.
Just to answer the question at the beginning,
like how much, here's my guess.
I bet if we are able to raise $5,000
as some kind of minimum, I'm sure
that's like a good target for us to start with.
But okay, whatever.
That's totally made up.
We'll see if that pans out.
I bet we could get more.
Like I bet we could.
Oh, I bet we could.
That was the final number that was bigger than us.
I'm just saying.
Like the goal of the Kickstarter
should ultimately be higher than the last one was
because the last one had stretch goals
that went all the way to 9,000.
But the initial goal should be higher
and then should have stretch goals
that go higher than that.
But I would like us to make more money for the next one,
not because I think we should raise the cost of it,
but just because again, we have gone over budget every time.
I still have all the fucking uncreated blue rays
sitting in a box in my closet
that I can't afford to do it.
I don't really, yeah.
Wait, Redcomb blue rays?
Redcomb two blue rays,
the Pleven the Weave blue rays that me and Jesse signed.
We signed like a hundred cases
and I have a hundred cases
and a hundred fucking discs blank sitting in my closet.
Okay, the Pleven the Weave,
that wasn't a Radcon Kickstarter.
I mean, Pleven the Weave wasn't at all.
It was.
I mean, it created,
Redcomb two was paid for
by the Pleven the Weave Kickstarter,
but it was me and it was really my Kickstarter
that I had broke Jesse into.
Yeah.
Was it really paid for?
Did we get really immersed in anything?
Well, everybody's flight was paid for by it.
Yeah, but there was a stretch goal for that.
Every stretch goal of the Kickstarter was somebody's flight.
Oh, because of the guests' appearances.
That's right, that's right.
The idea of it was supposed to be that,
because when we did the first Radcon,
we were all like, oh, we could do this every year
like we were going to Bronycon,
or because we could all afford to meet up once a year.
We were like, let's meet up more often.
Let's try to do a Kickstarter-backed one
so that we can meet up sooner.
And so it was just a few months later
and just the Kickstarter was a huge success.
So we were like, oh yeah, let's fucking do it.
And then once there was a Kickstarter involved,
there were backer rewards and ways to go over budget
and suddenly it was a different kind of animal, you know?
You gotta get those Blu-rays out, dude.
I can't afford it, he's still waiting for his.
I cannot afford to, but first of all.
What do you need to afford it?
Like what's stopping you?
Is it the shipping costs?
Shipping costs, and I, okay.
I have to get art made, I have to actually print.
I do not have a Blu-ray burner, so.
That's not probably not too expensive anymore.
Probably.
I mean, at this point, you might as well wait
because you originally,
your original thing on the Kickstarter
was to do two more seasons of it.
Two seasons, right.
And we still have it made the second season.
We did season two.
I think that's not really gonna happen though.
I mean, let's be real here.
It could, I mean, me and Jesse made four episodes
of a season two.
I think that they are being cost.
Okay, we made season two and it took forever,
but I was really happy with how it turned out.
And I thought like, at the time I thought like,
should there be more?
I don't know, this seems like a good way to end it and stuff.
But Digi came over to my house in like the summer of 2017.
And we recorded four episodes in the furnace room.
Which I don't know, they just,
without Vic being there to film it,
I thought it looked shitty.
It looked really bad.
It didn't look, yeah, on par with like what we had.
I didn't wanna go back in terms of quality.
So I don't think the show can really be done without Vic.
If we do a season three,
I mean, I've sort of like been taking notes
and like writing down episode ideas every once in a while.
So I've got about like,
10 or so ideas for episodes of it.
So we could do-
Well, you know we should have just another season.
And instead of like,
like I don't know what to do about those four that we filmed.
And maybe I could just release those four episodes
as season three.
And season three can be crappy and short,
like my little pony season three.
And then we can do season four the next time or whatever.
We should have a Radcon four stretch goal.
Digi actually releases the DVD.
If we wanted to do that, I could.
But like, yeah, I mean,
this is what happens with a lot of Kickstarter's
is that they are like, as soon as you start,
the number one thing-
Not Radcon three, baby.
We did it.
Yeah, well, you win, ladies and gentlemen.
I mean, we did go over budget for Radcon three.
Like the number one-
I mean, we lost money,
but that means we got the moral victory.
And I'm okay with that.
Yeah, well, that's right.
That's right.
The biggest thing that goes wrong with Kickstarter's
is that every time you add in a new thing,
it increases the cost of everything else in kind.
So it's like, I stretch goals, fly a person out.
Okay.
Well, that's like another trip to the airport.
Another person who has to be,
basically taken care of for the time they're there,
like drive around, make sure they get their food.
Like they have to now spend money
more than they would living at home
because they're eating out all the time
with their friends and like all this shit.
Like all that cost doesn't get factored in
when we make the Kickstarter goals.
Crowdfunding is bad.
I don't believe it.
No, you just got to know,
you just got to plan it out.
Well, Radcon three really helped us.
My Vapors Kickstarter was a huge success
and didn't go over budget.
And all my stretch goals were delivered upon
and Vapors two will be the same thing.
For the record.
It will be a triumph.
Absolutely nothing is my fault
in terms of the DVDs and the plebe and the weave.
I literally woke up one day
and saw my name on a Kickstarter
that I had no idea about
that already had like $8,000 attached to it.
And I'm just like, well, I guess I'm doing this now.
It pretty much went like I said,
hey, Jesse, we should do a Kickstarter
for plebe and the weave season two.
And he was like, sure.
And then I posted it immediately.
Like I just did that.
And then, yeah.
But no, I mean, the circumstances around it were crazy.
Like it's not, I don't feel bad at all.
Like I don't give a shit if anybody thinks
that that was like a failure because it was.
I don't consider it a failure just because
I think the episodes turned out really good.
Yes, people enjoyed it.
It came out good.
I am still holding on to all these fucking Blu-rays.
So it's not as though it is,
it's not as though I give it up on.
We're gonna have green-rays by the time you're done with these.
I don't really give a shit.
I mean, like, you know, whatever.
Time is completely relative.
You know, one time I own,
I've told this story before,
but one time my friend bought me $60 worth of art books
and I told him I'll pay you back when I get a job.
It took me 60 years to get a job.
But I paid him back on my first paycheck.
I will get the fucking Blu-rays out, you know?
Okay, there you go, fair enough.
You know, the thing about it is
we just need to set the amount that we make
just a lot higher than the cost
of what it sounds like it should cost, you know?
And of course, we feel a desire to not do that.
So it's easier to meet the goal,
but that's a negative if we end up just missing money.
I would say, you know,
set the goal higher than the amount we need
and make sure people are actually getting paid to do it.
That's another thing with Radcon 3.
Like, we covered the cost of it,
but that doesn't include actually paying anybody,
which really becomes a problem when the editing starts
and all of us have to get,
you know, we have to rush back to our own patreons
to make more money, you know, like nobody has time
to edit the shit that we did at Radcon.
So like, there needs to be editing fees,
actual payment for doing it.
And then like, yeah,
just factoring in additional costs to just have around,
like maybe like a bubble.
I feel like a hundred dollar bubble
that just goes to whatever it's needed for.
And then once everything's complete,
that money would just be dispersed
to everybody equally or something.
But like-
I totally agree.
And I just think that, yeah,
questions are super important.
There's things we don't predict.
But just like after Radcon,
like not even just the way that we assessed costs
with Radcon 3, which was too little
and we'll like know somewhat better next time,
but like even beyond that-
And we weren't even that off.
It was only like, what?
How much did we go?
Well, I mean, dude,
the biggest thing we were off about was shipping costs.
Shipping costs were so much more.
But that right there,
but the thing is we have the numbers
of exactly what it costs for Tom to ship those out.
Not that it would necessarily be him again,
but like we,
that is a super valuable piece of data.
So we know exactly,
like we can way more accurately determine that.
Even better now,
did you just find a way to get ship cheaper from his-
Yes.
Stamps.com is a great way to ship things cheap.
We will definitely be-
Wait, what?
Stamps.com.
Oh yeah, right, right.
Okay, well, yeah, that's great.
So, you know, I think that we actually said
5,800 was the minimum.
So it's probably gonna be more than that, people,
for the next one.
So, oh, oh, I was just gonna say.
I think we can do it.
I mean, people loved Radcon 3.
We got that funded after, you know, post-Radcon 2.
Radcon 3 still got funded.
Radcon 3 went well.
People love the results.
I don't know if somebody,
I don't know if there's gonna be people saying,
hey, you know, I wanna pay for Radcon 3,
but they're stealing your dad's still as an out.
So, you know, I don't know-
Was that a promise though?
No, it wasn't a promise, but...
I mean, it was promised by me to people
that we had done it and it would come out, you know.
That's fair.
You know, I will say the last thing on this
is just that, like, I don't like doing things
where I don't make a profit doing them.
I just don't like doing them.
So I really want to make sure that future Radcons
are not just a financial black hole,
because I'm trying to, you know,
trying to earn while doing things like this,
not just lose, just because they're fun.
You know, I mean, I wanna do it,
because, you know, I do think, like that guy said,
a lot of the best content we've done comes out of it,
just because it's such a unique experience
that, like, you know, when else would you get anything like it?
You know?
Yeah.
What I like about living in Boston is that now I'm with,
like, Ben and we, like, hang out, like, you know, for fun.
Like, we're friends or something.
I don't like that. I don't like that.
It's weird, right?
It's really cool, because what I really-
It's quirky.
What I like about Radcon is a lot of, like,
just, like, being around people who are also creative
and I also respect and I think are, like, interesting
and I like to talk to, and just outside of even just
the pure, like, carnal, mortal pleasure
being with your friends, which is great.
Also, just, like, being with other creatives
and, like, coming up with ideas and projects together
is, like, really interesting and valuable,
and I love doing that.
What's cool about Radcon is that we're all there to make-
Yes. Agreed.
Yes. Very true.
We're all on the same page about what we're doing there.
It's basically just, like, lightning ideas all the time.
It's just, like, everybody sitting around going, like,
okay, well, we did that thing, what do we do now?
You know, like, it could be literally, like,
oh, Nate and Hippo are doing a podcast in that room,
so fuck them, what can we do that is, like,
that not only we can do without them,
but also that is funny specifically because
they are in that room doing that while we do this, you know?
When I think about just the idea of Radcon,
my instinct is, like, oh, a bunch of people
get together and make shit, sounds gay as shit,
except that every time we do it,
it's just produces such actually good things
that, like, I'm constantly kind of astounded,
like, wow, that's actually really funny and good.
I still have yet to post the soon-to-be,
someday-to-be award-winning sitcom, The Man and the Boy.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
The Man and the Boy.
How's The Man and the Boy not alive yet?
Is that, like, the only Munchy Jesse content, like?
I think it is.
Probably. Yeah.
Me and Munchy at Radcon 3, we...
Very impromptu.
We conceived, filmed, improvised, and created
an entire sitcom called The Man and the Boy,
and there's multiple episodes,
and it's probably a nightmare, but it's great.
Jesse plays the titular man, and I play the titular boy,
and then the adventures we get up to
are unparalleled in scope and execution.
We have to get that out
because it's never gonna happen again.
If you do another season,
it's just gonna be The Man and the Man.
Oh, my God.
And if Munchy doesn't release the Stealing Your Dads episodes,
then it won't be easy anymore.
It'll be hard to steal Dads.
It will always be easy.
I don't know. It seems pretty difficult right now.
Yeah, it seems like it's been a...
It seems like a big labor.
It's hard for me to steal a Dad
if I can't watch the episode.
Okay, all right.
Enough of this, people.
Let's move on. We've got two quick last ones.
Okay, first of all, we've got Mozilla Fennekin, human core.
And this was the guy.
This Mozilla was the one who asked us,
yes, last time, what is human core?
So let's hear.
So now we're drilling this closure.
I just want to say that just something about human core,
just it rubbed me the wrong way.
And like, just phonetically,
just like there's just something
I don't like about this community.
I thought you were the one who like invented it.
I thought you were the human core.
I invented it.
Yeah, we had this discussion last time.
I remember me inventing it too,
though I guess I will defer to Ben
Okay, so if anyone remembers the invention of human core.
Let us know.
Who invented human core?
I think it was like either one of us invented it,
the other person ran with it, just either or.
I think it was definitely like developed over time.
Okay, well, let's hear.
However, I want you all to know,
I want you all to know that you can buy
human core shirts at teespring.com
slash stores slash Ben Dash thing.
Oh my God, that's all right.
I'm selling them.
I'm selling, you're buying them.
And instead of giving Ben $5 on Teespring,
just buy a shirt from me directly
where I'll get all the proceeds.
I get $10 per shirt, thank you very much.
9.50.
I've been told that the shirts from Teespring
smell bad and don't fit well.
I've got some.
Not my experience.
They don't fit well.
I think they're fine.
Oh, my, okay, I don't, all right.
If you guys say so, I get the classic V-neck
and they all fit great.
And like my Teespring shirts are like my favorite shirts
that I own.
Well, if you'd like there to say, buy Ben's shirts.
Okay, all right.
Let's go, patron saint of human core,
a paragon of wisdom in the human core sphere.
Mozilla Fennekin, educate us, go.
Last time I asked you what the most human core thing ever is.
It's something that all humans do
and nothing else does it.
It's only a human thing.
Shitting.
Your responses were very thoughtful and very interesting.
I appreciate that you participated in this.
And so you're wrong.
The most human core thing ever is having a bathroom.
Okay, hear me out, hear me out.
Get out of here.
I already said shitting, I was right.
Every animal or whatever, it's like,
they just kind of shit wherever.
This is so bad.
That's not even true.
We have our own designated shit space.
Like we have to have our own room.
What is a fucking litter box?
I mean, you might think, true,
you know, cats have a bottle or whatever,
but we decide that for them.
No, they would do that anyway.
Not for that, they just kind of shit wherever.
Same thing with dogs, like we just kind of say,
don't shit in the house, they'll just shit wherever.
We're like the only people that just don't decide
to just shit on the floor or throw it around or wherever.
God, humans are so fucking weird.
What happened?
Okay, okay, I'm pretty sure.
I know that's a stupid answer.
Yeah.
Get out of here.
He's missing too.
All right, full as we am.
I'm pretty sure, I'm pretty sure there are animals
who have designated,
like monkeys must have like a place they go to shit, right?
They don't just like, well, unless they live in the trees,
I don't know, but the ones that live on the ground
must have like a place.
They've got to, right?
I don't think he did any research.
Or they shit in the river or something.
There has to be another animal that has a shit place.
I'm sure there is.
I'm gonna Google it right now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Animals shit in a, in a shit place.
Do they shit in a society?
Oh, okay, right here, right here, earth.
Animals invented public toilets long before we did.
Article on the BBC from 2015.
I'm afraid you're done.
You're all done cheating.
Animal latrine, places where the wildlife animals
habitually defecate or urinate.
There's a whole list of them
and the whole list of people that do it.
No, no, no, only humans have toilets.
Only a human shit in the same spot.
Mozilla, Fennec, we're just gonna land back.
You're going in the voice jail.
You're so fucking stupid.
Voice jail.
Yeah, voice jail.
You're probably falling with something
that just is factually wrong,
but then you have the gall to admit that it's stupid.
You weren't even sticking to your fucking guns.
I fucking hate you, Mozilla Fennec.
Kill yourself, kill yourself.
All right, let's go into jail.
He's going to jail.
Mozilla Fennec, I'm sorry.
You were a good man for a long time.
You gave us good stuff, but it's fucking over, dude.
All right, well, incidentally.
Game over.
We have one more voice message from one Mozilla Fennec'n.
Actually, it's called Special Announcement.
It's a special announcement from a man in jail.
Let's hear what he has to say.
OK, all right, go.
Hey, PCPs, sorry I haven't submitted a voicemail
in a long time.
I've been so busy doing this fucking compilation
of all of the best and worst voicemails in the PCPs history.
And you're in the worst.
You heard that, Mike.
Best and worst of compilation of PCP voicemails,
because that's the only thing people care about with this
podcast now.
This is an ongoing project, and to prove
that I'm not completely full of shit,
I have already made a compilation for the 2018 episodes.
You can find it at my side shit channel, Luxvanlavixi.
That's L-U-X-V-A-N-L-U-V-I-X-I.
I'm going to post a 2019 compilation at the end of the
year, but I'd like some feedback from some other people.
Suggestions as to which voicemails to include would be nice.
But mainly, I want to know if I should include 2018's voicemails
in the 2019 compilation, since voicemails weren't really
introduced until around August last year.
It also has some continuing sagas, like the Great Discord
War that happened.
So let me know.
Comment on the video.
You can find me on Twitter at Mozilla Fennigan.
I'm in the Patreon Discord as well.
I'm really easy to find.
OK.
He's in the voice chat.
I just want to let you know that's what I'm doing.
See you in like five months, unless I kill myself or something.
Go away.
I can't wait to see the 2019 where it's just you.
It's just all of your voicemails compiled into this section.
Poor bastard.
Well, I'm glad someone's doing it.
Yeah, no, this is a good thing.
This is a good service he's doing.
I appreciate it.
I don't know if he's doing it.
I don't know if it's a good thing.
That's like saying Hitler had some good ideas.
I mean, we all know that's true.
At least he's staying productive in jail, getting something done.
Should we let him out of jail?
No.
include channels oh my god really that that that's that's how unfortunately
that's the only way you can find grimp is you search a grim but you search for
a channel you set the filter to channel I guess I'm spelling it wrong okay
whatever I wanted to actually go check this out maybe if I find it maybe it'll
be the show notes I don't know we'll see okay anyway that's it people better
voicemails then next time please you said something that was factually
inaccurate on the PCP because we all know that this is just a pillar of
objectivity on the show speak pipe link down below give us voice messages and
patreon.com slash the procrastinators five dollars you get the bonus episodes by
the time you hear this we'll a new one be out real quick proposition Nate I
think we should do this for the voicemails and I don't know if you've
listened to dick Masterson does this on his show who are these podcasts started
doing it as well where they they have like the ending of the show and then
they do voicemails like they'll play an outro they they they say all their you
know all the plugs and everything then they do voicemails just because so many
people hate voicemails that like people love the voicemails they're like
everyone's favorite part I mean it really depends on the person I mean I
don't know how people feel on this show initially seemed like there were a lot
of people who had bigger problems at the voice get a straw poll and show notes
let's find out just I just want to know like cuz like these shows are long as
shit and I know when people see like three hours it's just like oh my god how
long is this gonna be you know but like if we had an outro after the before the
voicemail so just make people who didn't want to sit for three hours just feel
like oh I can go now you know I hear you and I'm sympathetic to that and I want
to do things if that's we can clean people are more likely to listen through
that that's good but you know we'll a half an hour make that much difference
usually an hour bro yeah it's like it's pretty long okay you might be right you
might be right let us know what do you think of this idea okay yeah let us know
I'm open to although I made it far enough to hear me say that clearly
listens to the full episode oh shit I you're right that's that's a just that's
a that's a bad skew of the people listening okay anyway so by the time you
hear this people new bonus that was that won't be out but it'll be out two days
from when you hear this and it's a good one we we did fun things that's the 29th
bonus episode you get all of them if you are a patron of five dollars or more
is that the most recent one yeah the most we should say what it is so people
want to go fucking do it watch it okay all right fine you guys I don't know if
teasing or telling them is better but what it is is me Tom Ben and Gib all
played quake three like Radcom three guys we played it it was like it was just
like that thing we had a great time we did the thing we base the thing really
really fucking fun and please it was a lot of fun to find out you have to pay
$5 and watch the fucking episode so go do that will I redeem myself after my
embarrassingly poor performance at Radcom three you can find out for the
low low price of five dollars on patron.com slash the procrastinators one
dollar you get into the the patron chat it's a good time on discord do it up do
it up and that's it give us more money last time you're gonna hear munchies
voice for a while so see you later yeah we'll see he'll come crawling back he'll
be back feel all right as soon as I can as soon as I can
sounds good all right see you next time everybody
I am an asshole I am a stupid I've got more than one