Okay, okay, I'm, I'm, I'm, okay, I'm my audio.
Finally. I'm an audio guy.
Finally, God.
Jesus Christ.
Damn.
You're so dead. You're fucking dead.
Oh no. Oh no.
Fuck.
I'm fucked.
Dude.
I can't believe. I can't believe.
What, what a treat.
What a, what a treat to discover that you have not played frog fractions.
What, what a fucking joke.
What a joke of a person you are.
Oh man. I can't wait for the right fucking cockroaches to evolve into a civil war.
Where I just, it's not even gonna be a war.
I'm just gonna go to sleep and I'm gonna pour gasoline inside of your fucking room.
And just wait until you suffocate on gasoline.
Just, yeah, like, like everyone in RFCK will have to, will have to choose their side.
It will be, will be split right down the middle. Yes, Suri.
A group of rowdy fuckers and a group of cop killers cannot be divided.
It was, it was rowdy fucker against cop killer.
Oh, who would it be who? Oh, it's too difficult.
There's no way, there's no way.
I think I'm the cop killer.
Oh, you do, huh? You fucking, you fucking establishment piece of shit.
You think you're the cop killer? I've been killing cops since I was a penis, bitch.
My mother was a cop and she died in childbirth.
Oh, fuck. All right.
And when my mom died in childbirth, my dad gave me a little baby high five.
All right, preview stream.
Fuck. Okay, okay, okay, here's the million dollar question.
Because I have to like record like a sub region in OBS, right?
So it's like, it's like small. Should I keep it at its original size?
You can like inflate it.
Wait, you can record your whole screen. Isn't there a monitor setting?
Well, sure. But wouldn't I just want to record the bit that is actually relevant?
I guess. I don't know. I've never, I've never done that.
You can just, you can just record the window.
Yeah, yeah, I'll do that.
But you think you're so smart.
I'm pretty clever.
Yeah, you know, you're right. You've convinced me.
Thanks.
Okay, thanks for taking me at my word.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay. Okay, so do we go?
Hang on. Let me, um,
No, I don't want to see. All right. So I'm looking at your screen.
If I'm reading this, I'm gay. Yep. That's me.
Yep.
You're paid off.
I just fell for the trap. Okay.
Yep. I guess we can go if you want to, if you want to head over to, if you want to head over to, I'm going to be, I'm going to be,
I'm going to start the video recording.
I'm going to, I'm going to help. Okay. I'm going to be a very helpful boy.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
When you're recording on your frog on your quest to learn fractions with a frog.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm recording. I'm recording the screen capture and I'm singing up the audio now when I, on the count of three, I'm going to open a new tab.
So one, two, three, new tab. All right. One, two, three, new tab. All right. Sick.
I don't see anything.
No, that's fine. It's because it's not, it's not on the fucking.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. We got this.
We got to sync audio too.
Oh yeah. Okay. Well, I, hold on. This like, this like screen you're seeing isn't my screen. It's like its own thing and like the cloud.
Okay. Okay. On the count of three, we'll say peg. All right. One, two, three, peg.
All right. Great job.
Yep.
One, two, three, peg. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That's set in the mood. It's a tone piece.
RFCK is a tone piece now.
That was completely not right on my screen, but if it's good on your screen, then I guess we'll do it.
I don't see anything on your screen.
No. Well, I meant, I meant as in, we didn't sync up audio wise.
Also, I'm not, okay, whatever. I'm not recording anything.
You aren't?
I'm recording audio. I'm not recording video.
No. Yeah. Obviously. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
As long as we've synced up audio wise, then we're good.
But are you, are you sure you're recording your video though? You're sure?
Well, yeah. Okay. Yeah. Why would, yeah, why would it yeah?
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't even doubt myself. You fucking nihilist.
I don't believe in videos and therefore they never exist.
Hold on. Before we go to FrogFactions, I'm gonna have like a joke.
should introduce when... Hold on. Okay. Hold on. What the fuck is this? Pictures of a big
baby. Okay, okay, okay, okay. Introduce the podcast. Okay. Yeah, why not? Hey, welcome
back to the long-awaited Return Resurrection Reimagining Reboot of
Rowdyfuckers Cop Killers Episode 4. Rowdyfuckers Cop Killers. I think we've had way
more. I think we've had like at least like more than one. At least one.
There's at least one, and this is at least one and a half. Starring me. Starring me,
your hero, Ben St. and my bumbling sidekick, Munchy, with tiny heads. That's so funny.
It's so funny that you guys walked in just a moment while I was looking at
pictures of Ben to put in my collection. What are you? The pictures of Ben on the
screen right now. It's fucking crazy. Those babies are like 17 different
ethnicities, and I am only one, so... Oh, oh, oh. Checkmate. Checkmate. When I say that
you are you're a melting pot of cultures. I do believe, yeah, I'm all about
representation, dude. Even in my gene pool. Even in my very DNA. I know when I
think about Ben St. I think about Big Baby, Villains Wiki from Toy Story 3. It's
what I think about. Villains Wiki. That fucking baby was just misunderstood. God
damn it. Didn't he watch the movie? He just wanted to kill all Pokemon. He just
was mad because he was a mechanical spider now. Right. Tell the bitches. Oh my
god. So the other day I asked Munchy, surely you've played Frog Fractions,
and the greatest moment of my entire life was when he said,
Duh, Duh, no. What's that? Duh. Okay. Well, okay. First of all, I did say... We're
fixing that on Rowdyfuckers cop killers. We're recording. Boot up discord. I did say,
I did say it as if I had three, three, like an IQ in the single digits. However, I said
that I played like the first like three seconds, and then I was like eh. Yeah. That's why I
basically haven't seen any of it. Yeah, okay. Frog Fractions twin beard. What do you know
about Frog? What do you know about Frog Fractions Munchy? Okay. I know that Nate was like,
Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh, Duh. Yeah. That is, that is so something he'd say.
And then I was like, okay, and then then then we were in a call to record the PCP and it was like,
I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure that Nate's a pretty I'm sure I'm sure that Nate thinks he loves frog fractions
But I'm sure but I'm sure that his appreciation is like is like is like a fucking kiddie pool
Compared to the vast ocean of wisdom that is my engagement with frog fractions
If you fucking like frog so much why don't you rub one?
Anyway, oh shit, he did I didn't expect that let's let's just fuck this duck shall we oh
That's what I've always what the fuck is this shit. Oh here. Ow my brain. That's pretty that's pretty loud
That's pretty that is pretty loud. It's pretty fucking loud. I'm gonna. Oh god. Wait turn I
Turn I turn volume down. I I guess I'll I'll turn mine down too
I'll cut this cut this part out of the podcast. Oh shit. Should I be recording the sound too? I should yeah, yeah, you should
Okay frog fractions
Are you recording the sound? Yeah, okay. Yeah, okay sweet
Excellent, okay
All right frog fractions. We're gonna play all right month the kids
Know how we are. I know that you are in like fourth grade or something
So you I know you probably you probably don't even know simple you probably don't even know simple fucking
You probably don't even know the fucking chain rule for integration let alone fractions
But you're about to and when this frog is done with you you're gonna know
Everything about parts of things please please save me save me for this trap that I've laid for myself
Munchie and in the third grade the teacher came with me and said all right
We're gonna be learning about division and I and I sneezed and I feel like a huge fucking booger came out of my nose
And like it was all over my desk and all the kids laughed at me
I
Faggot it was hot. Yeah
Play frog fractions. Okay, so okay, so I like I want to get so now the learning
But you want to eat the bugs?
Frogs eat bugs and you want to protect the fruits you want to protect the fruit. Oh, why?
Frogs where are the fruits ever do for fucking me? I forget I forget what they do
But what see see you one fell on you. I think you want to
You might want to eat the fruits when they when they fall. I don't know
I mean the ones that are like on top of you just fall right on top this website. We're using to do this fucking sucks
I have huge input delay. That's not even fair
Really, that's fine. Yeah, no, you're gonna be fine. Um, okay
Yeah, so you got to get upgrades you got to upgrade so you can really learn about fractions like in a really efficient alright
Uh
Don't give us don't get the cybernetic brain get the what's the top left one there?
No left
Yeah, yeah, you want lock-on targeting?
Okay, so so so this game is like made for like for like shitty idiot babies, right?
Yeah, yeah, if you're a little kid and you don't know about fractions then this is the game for you
Anyway, it seems like it's not teaching me. It's just showing fractions on screen. Yeah
Well, I mean you gotta you gotta start by dipping your toe in just with the introduction
Just you know, they just get introduced the concept that fractions are a thing that exists
And you can you can see at the top there. It's tracking. Oh, fuck. I got two. It's tracking your fruit
It's tracking your indignity and it's tracking your Zork
Zork mids are gonna Zork mids are gonna be important later right now. Okay, just worry about fruit and indignity
No, I'm pretty I'm pretty honorable. I think I think this is fuck
I think you I think you gain indignity when the bugs like hit you or something like it like
You know like they make you mad and that's how you lose
Fuck I want I want a turtle fuck. Yeah. Oh, dude. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you can was so now you can catch
You know you can catch the apples you can catch the fruits when they fall on you
All right, so that's like I can go. That's like sick. That's like sick, bro
Oh, yeah, this is totally sick. Okay, so I can go right like I can go up
Yeah, you go up and yeah, hit your buttons stupid. I'm going. I'm going. I'm hidden down
It won't it won't fucking do it. What wait go left and right. Oh
It won't do that also either, but it just did I just saw you move. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I'm doing it right now
Ben, I'm doing it right now. What that's weird. That's I just saw you move. I
Start working now for some reason
What okay, okay, finish this round finish this round. Okay. Oh, you fucking you yeah, I see you fucking click click the screen click the screen
Okay, now move I can't are you fucking are you fucking serious?
Seriously so mad. Oh that makes me so goddamn angry, dude. I'm angry at you. I'm angry at you
Okay, okay, this is fine. Okay. Yeah dirt. Yeah, you get the durians are the king of fruits
Wait is was working
No, this is fucked. This is fucked. We can't fucking continue. We honestly cannot continue without without was functionality
Dude, you don't eat the your fucking window doesn't have
focus
Are you okay try the arrow keys to the arrow keys work?
No, the arrow keys are the ones that are making me go up and down like like my like page
Maybe we should have tried this before
This shit, this is fucking gay dude. This is fucking gay. All right, hold on hold on hold on
How it just worked yeah, it really did just work for like like a fucking second, but I don't know why it's
I
Nothing I can fucking do
It like like it was working up until I like try to do up or down and then just wouldn't I'm
I'm like tempted to say like fucking like restart the the really restart reload the page
Yeah, I'm done with that. Okay. Yeah
All right, welcome to the second attempt. Yeah
Fucking fucking twin beard fucking twin beard can't program for shit apparently
Whatever, you know, it's fine. You've you've learned the ropes. You're learning the ropes. You'll figure it out
You see you already got 16 Zork mids. You're off. Yeah, I got a ton of fucking Zork mids
When the ladies come to me say yo, how many Zork mids you guys say I'm fucking I can't talk to you your different race
You say I say 16. That's the age of consent in many states and they say damn
Damn
Into those fourth graders. Let's see. Oh, you can't get the turtle. Yeah. Yeah fuck shit. No, thanks, bitch
Yeah, say yeah, save up for that turtle save up for that turtle
I get that turtle. We got to get that turtle again and hope that it doesn't crash the fucking game again
So, uh, oh
Man before it was doing a thing before fuck it was doing a thing before I'll point it out
I'll point it out when it happens again. I'm sure it'll happen again, but the fractions. Oh, dude
You're indignant. You're indignant. He's going crazy, dude. Oh shit. I'm so shitty
Oh
You got too much indignity you got too much indignity. Oh, oh shit. Oh fuck. I'm shit at this game. Yeah. Yeah, you really are
I can't I can't believe it. I can't believe you would let the bugs do this
This would be fine if it was a toad, but since it's a frog it's a little bit
I can't I can't believe you would give the fucking these these bugs the satisfaction of owning your ass so thoroughly
Hey
Oh my fucking god, I literally fucking hate this program and I I I was just talking about before the show how much
How cool it is. It's literally the fucking worst thing I've ever seen before
Yeah, you had nothing but praise for this piece of shit for this piece of shit server
This piece of shit
By the way, the way we're doing this viewer is that munchies playing it in in the rabbit something called rabbit and like
So is it working?
No Jesus fuck
I have no idea how to remedy this it
It fucking worked before it worked. I don't know what to do, Ben
Like the game you can't you can't fucking continue the all right all right
Is there some other fucking screen sharing app I I I don't we could do skype I guess
I don't even have skype on my computer. Wait, can you and even why can you not do it through um
Can you not do it through discord?
I don't think so
Let's see
I mean, well, obviously we're not gonna fucking use this shit because it sucks. Yeah, this really this really sucks
Uh, I can't believe it. I can't believe this
I don't I don't understand. I don't understand the single fucking thing. Let's go to my notifications on twitter
Oh, hey a couple more people liked my post that actually feel good about myself
Then yeah, why are women so easily manipulated? Well
It's because it's because they don't you know, they lack they lack several of the things that we men enjoy
um
moral fiber
And uh and rationality
um, it's the two the the two the two cornerstones of civilization really and
you know
Tragic tragically don't have a prostate male. How are you gonna fucking peg someone without if they don't have a pet prostate?
Yeah, how are you gonna pleasure someone if they don't have a problem? Nothing is more nothing is more pointless than the female anus
Yeah, nothing has ever been more feudal
More feudal feudal japan
There have never been more samurai's than female butts. That's true
Except for this this episode sucks
All right, all right accessibility
All right
Wait, no don't don't turn golly-blin mode on
I don't get what we're oh shit. Should I do classic? Uh, no you go with next gen
Okay. Yeah, you gotta stay up to date. Yeah
um
All right, just play
Yeah
Yeah, I guess so and then hey when you when you get to the when you get to the like upgrade menu
try like
I don't know. I think you can select with the arrow keys. I think
Okay, all right. So here we are a third attempt third attempt to play the the little the little guy game the the game for little guys
A little tiny frog guys little tiny frog boys by the way despite featuring a frog
Um frog fractions does not endorse
Donald trump
Oh my fucking god. I knew they were racist. Yeah. No, this is I can't I can't select with my with my
Key arrow. Okay. You know what? Maybe I was wrong. Maybe I was wrong. Um
Yes
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh shit. Oh you found it. You found the secret. What the fuck is this shit?
Look at your fruit. Oh my god. I have so many fruits. You got like a billion like a billion
You can now you can afford all the fucking you can afford all the fucking upgrades. Oh my fucking god fruits have been accumulating
They've been accumulating under the sea
Dude, you see you see what I mean the fucking the um, oh my fucking god the turtle functionality
That's fucking insane turtle functionality was is key to the
I knew my my my fucking my fellow animorph my fellow my my fellow jester
animorph
My fellow fucking
Pig in red clothing. Uh, here we go. Pig in red clothing. Yeah. Yeah
Um, oh my fucking god. I'm so powerful. Are you sold? Are you sold on frog fractions yet?
Oh my god. I'm so what's this mother fucker doing in the background. What's he what's his story?
Wait, can you still move?
Uh, yeah, oh few few if I don't see you move for a while. I assume everything's gone to seed
Um, no, I I I just don't I just don't feel the need to that little totem answer
Yeah. Yeah, the little little little fucking little little gestapo
I don't know man. It's just part of the deep lore of frog fractions. I guess
Uh, he frog fractions doesn't even fucking do my taxes for me. No, man. It's gonna it pays dividends
It pays, you know, it's hard. It's hard work now, but in the future you'll be glad you look bad back on this
And say I'm so glad that ben beat me up and made me learn math
Because that's what I do. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. The chicks don't dig on cyborg
Probably shouldn't be that. Oh, yeah. Yeah, you can get a cybernetic brain
Or you can get yeah, yeah get the get the static cling tongue. You want that you want that? All right. All right
It's gonna fuck. It's gonna fuck these bugs right up
Oh my fucking god. Yeah. Oh these bugs you see that you see that you see how many bugs you can eat in a single blow
Oh, my fucking god, dude bugs can't even fucking do their own taxes. They have to get it fucking white people do it for
Those fucks
Oh, dude, dude, dude, what is that? What is fuck is it? Okay? Okay? Oh my god
I'm crazy. You're so far into a dragon friend. Hell. Yeah, dude. Oh my fuck. Uh, dude, you know, we gotta do fucking
Oh my god
Oh my god, I can go all
Fucking over dude. I can do all the chinese myths. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Just do it all just do it all
I can do all the fucking chinese. Oh, dude. They're shooting bullets. They're shooting bullets at you now. Oh my god
Watch out though. You're gonna get some hella indignity if you're not careful
Oh my god. Yeah. Oh my god. Yeah. Oh my god. This is you're in this is literally more math than fucking leonard avenge
You're you're you're in you're in bullet hell now, son
Um
Yeah, my fucking god. Yeah, good. You got that cyber brain
Yeah, I think that fucking oh my god. They're fucking now. You're in fucking that's literally a single fucking
That's literally a single science right there now. You're in. Oh my god. Now. You're an exponential now
You're an exponential functions now. You're advanced you've gone on to advanced maths as the brit as the britons would say as the ang
Anglos the anglos. Yeah
You fucked it up, dude. You didn't tow hoe that shit nearly hard enough
Listen ben not everyone has the capability to be a dictator like you
I know I know oh man. Oh man. That just reminds me of how I fucking
Oh my god, you ate all those bugs that just reminds me of how I fucking crushed it in uh in downwell on digi bros
And how that piece of shit digi has not released that video even though it's been like two fucking months
Play that fucking game. I
murdered I fucking murdered down well, dude. I'm a champion. It's all warp drive
Oh, dude, it's all warp drive and you're flying dragon. Now. He'll really take you places. Oh my god. Oh my god
This isn't really happening. This is really. Oh my god. This is really glad you could follow me
We're dealing with a serious infestation here
um
Oh my god, so uh, so yeah, so you're about to learn some really hardcore fractions. I think
Oh my fucking
Be careful those asteroids. Don't let them push you around. Yeah, watch out. Okay. Okay. Watch out. You're still recording, right?
You're screen recording everything's good. Okay. I'm really paranoid. I'm really paranoid. We're gonna lose this choice footage
This this this this discovery only happens once
Yeah
Um, oh my god. Yeah, your dragon friends are going. Oh, oh dude. That was so much fun
Fucking indignity. You just suffer
He just is way after way of it hot hot fucking christ hot fucking god. This this reminds me of my fucking bar mitzvah
You let the asteroids push you around we said not to do that. Yes. Yes, sir. Oh my fucking god
Oh, dude, watch watch that indignity
Actually, it doesn't even look like you're accumulating any
Uh, it looks like it looks like you're riding too high on your dragon friend with your warp drive
What's his name? It's terry cruise terry cruise the dragon the dragon bruise
Do a barrel roll. Wow. Oh good. Oh good had to have that
Dude, dude, you see mars in the background. That's fucking mars, dude
That's that's actually mars. Is that the real life? Is that the actual mars? That's the real life mars
It's got the fucking dry ice polar caps at the bottom
Dude, you're almost there, dude. You've almost I've got something for you to dry. It's my laundry. Please do it. It's my humps
Bitch, it's oh my god. Oh my god. It's more than I can take. Yeah
My my little heart my little beading heart
Oh
Good flying with you lieutenant hop. See you on the other side
Yeah, oh fuck. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, where are we now? We're going to mars, dude
Oh
Oh fuck
Oh fuck. Okay. It's time. It's time to get serious. Oh
All right, I wonder if the big guy has any tips about dealing with fractions
Ah
Oh, fuck. Okay. Oh god
Oh, he's unfortunate
No, no, no, no, no
Holy shit
Okay, so now you're in now you're in the court of bug mars
You're accused of breaking and entering your native habitat bug mars with intent to perloin our delicious space. Oh, fuck. I'm surrounded by bugs
A minimum sentence of 20 years hard labor, but there's a special offer this week
How'd you like to become a naturalized citizen of bug mars?
um, um, um
Oh
Oh, I you know, I'm
I I I have an affinity for bugs as we all seen in hashtag bug wars
I I I actually killed a bug and I and I and I'm more I'm more and it's lost heavily
He's now he's a fully realized pcp character the bug that died
He's real bug that died
Excellent. All you need to do is pass a test on the history and culture of this fine planet
Shall we we begin our bug plan flag as far as bug stripes?
I wonder I wonder why there's why there's uh the american the united states flag in bug mars, but it's fine. Yeah, that's
Shit, you're right. That's a that's a contradiction or is it just room for deeper lore?
Oh, it's obviously just fucking bugs a little bit on the nose, isn't it?
You can blame bug betsy ross for that one next question on the series bug
What is bug snooker's favorite player of ice cream?
Huh, when are we gonna get where are we gonna get to to troll jeegus?
When are we gonna get to that part of the history lesson here?
Uh, so wrong and it's all right four score and 20 bugs go bug in chief bug thomas chefferson
I literally I literally made the joke bug thomas chefferson like two days ago. Did I literally did you now?
I I I called him thomas bugerson thomas bugger. Well, you fucked it up because his name was bug thomas jefferson
As you can see so you so you fail you don't get to be a naturalized citizen
The only right you'll ever need. Oh fuck. I wasn't paying attention. Uh
You're you're you're you're crushing it munchie. You're I think I think they're I think the bugs are gonna accept you as one of their own
I think I think I think you've got this on lock frankly quite frankly. I mean, obviously
I mean, let me just drink my fucking
Sunrise I you know, you know, really I think bug mars is is is pretty a bunch of a bunch of crackpot in the spears day theorists
I think they I think they're all like 9 11 truthers. I don't think they really know what the fuck's going on
That's an entire people you that's an entire people you're throwing under the bus there
They're fucking bugs who cares last question mr. Hobb. How do you feel about fractions?
Oh, man, this is this is the only question that is
Shit
Oh, you know, I gotta say
Ever since that day that I spit my nose
Juice outside of my body and the entire class saw me with my with my pants down legally and figuratively
Yeah, I've I've always known that I is my favorite my favorite ninja turtles Raphael. Yeah, I love them
Dick Masterson aka Raphael
I know right fractions. I'm impressed. Here's the first perfect score in our fake naturalization program
We were going to fire you into the sun, but instead we decided to give you a work visa
Yolo
But
Yeah
Oh here
Yeah, yeah, yeah, um, yeah, please do this right do this right and never never regret it. Oh my god
All right. All right. All right. How are you guys? This is gonna. This is gonna define your life on bug mars from here on out
I'm a bug. You did it, dude. Mars fractions are the best. Yep, well, oh my, oh fuck,
oh fuck, back right into the frame. Back to the old grind. This is, this is, this is
where you belong. This is, this is what you're most comfortable. This is what you were trained
for. Oh, the indignity, dude. The fucking indignity. Oh my god, bugs. Hey, what was that
thing that just fell? Bugs, why? I, I, I, oh my god, oh my god. What, what kind of
doubloons will they have on fucking bug Mars? Um, there's, there's plenty. Uh, PR. PR department.
Oh, I need, I need some, I need some branding. I need branding. Uh, it's too expensive. You
can get durians. Yeah, I want durians. I want, I want to go down into, uh, oh. Oh. Well,
this is just like my second bar mitzvah I had because I was disowned at my first one.
You know, you know what they say, um, a bar mitzvah in the hand is worth two in the bush.
I, you know, it almost feels like a disservice to talk over this part because you're meant,
because you're meant to just, you're meant to just sail around and listen to a calm voice explain
to you the history of boxing. But, let me turn my volume all the way up. But fuck it.
All right, I guess there's no more voice. I guess not. It'll, he'll be back. He'll be back
eventually. I guess in the meantime, just check out that sweet puffer fish. Well, he's gone now.
Fish ain't even shitty. I haven't even killed my dad yet.
Hey, look, it's a dory. It's a finding dory.
It's me. Can you prove it? I love what happened because I can't remember it.
Uh, excuse me. Excuse me. While I vape, seems like the time for it.
Vape, vape, vape all day long. Vape, vape, vape. It's basically my whole personality.
Vape, vape, vape. He wears a thong. Vape, vape, vape. He's always wrong. His name is...
As, as Christian Weston Chandler once so creatively put it,
rap, rap, rap. That's a rap.
His words. His words, not mine. His words, not mine in the word, words of Christ.
Life is like a movie. And this movie doesn't have a surprise ending. The good guys win, quote from
J.C.W. Connors. I hate it when movies surprise me.
Oh, that one didn't even look like a fucking sea guy. That was a... Oh, it's a...
Coal! It's a coothaloo. It's a, it's a, it's a cuddle. It's a cuddlefish for cuddling.
Cuddlefish. Yeah, yeah. It's a horitair. It's a, it's a flathooloo.
It's a, it's a, it's a, yeah, horitair. That's right. It's a, it's a, it's a, hey,
don't click that. Don't click that. Don't click that. Okay. So, so sorry, Meister.
You know, you know, Ben, if there was one character that I could relate to you in all of
media fiction itself, it would be the heat miser from, from that one, like Claymation Santa Claus one.
The heat meister? The heat meister. Yeah. The heat meister. You mean the burger meister?
No, not the, well, the burger meister also as well. However, not.
The heat meister is a completely different original character.
You're talking about one of those Claymation Christmas specials?
Yeah. Yeah. Must not be one I've seen, because I don't know, I don't know any,
but I don't know anybody by the name of heat meister, sir.
I'm Mr. Heat Meister. I'm basically fucking sick.
Um, you know what they say, um, heat meister, heat meister, at the door,
run away quick, or you'll run no more. Yep. Magic the Gathering.
Dude, one time I was over, I was over at my cousin's house and we were playing,
we were playing fucking, uh, Magic Gathering. And all of a sudden, and, and, and it was on his
Xbox, he didn't actually have the cards on the Xbox version. So, so, so, so, so we were playing
and all of a sudden he just, he just starts jacking it and I leave the room.
Why'd you leave, faggot?
Because I didn't want to air up.
You clearly, clearly you don't know how to read the room, Munchy. Clearly you don't know how to
read the mood. Uh, that, well, you know, hey, it's a symptom of autism, I guess.
Yeah. We're all on the spectrum.
You know, I think it would be a leased artist, honestly.
Yeah, I think I would consider myself a leased game. Oh, God. Jesus Christ. Oh,
possibly my favorite thing you've ever said.
Oh, my God, it's Futurama. It's a, it's a crashed Futurama.
All right, now it's time for the true game to begin. Oh, my God. Hey, question,
are you capturing, is your, is OBS going to capture that mouse?
Yeah. There's no way to stop that. Oh, well, well, there is, but whatever.
Uh, that's fine. I just, we'll just throw this video out in the trash, where it belongs.
And by the trash, I mean the procrastinators channel. Okay. Now here, now this is for real.
Now this is the real shit, the raw shit.
Um, I feel an intense sound of pressure. You calm down and start taking your surroundings
for the first time since the seemingly dormant vessel sprang the life. The walls of the circular
room curve to meet at a point that must correspond to the curved nose of the outer hull lining the
walls. You see a porthole, a glowing display and a control deck. A ladder leads aft. Um, okay.
What? Oh, dude. What? Oh, no.
Did you, wait, wait, I see a tab. I see it. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Please tell me that the game's
still open. Yeah, it, it won't let me go to it for some reason. What?
Is this, it's, is this like part of the game? No, no. This is part of the gameplay experience.
Well, maybe you should close all those other new tabs.
I can't interact with it at all. What? No. It's, it's locked me out.
Well, what do I do? Why, why? Oh, wait, wait, wait.
It seems to be responding. Wait, well, well, like, like, like, can you like minimize it and then open
it again or something? Yeah, here. I'll go over a different tab real quick. I'll go, I'll go to Twitter.
Yeah. Something, something needs, something must be done. This, this won't stand.
Fucking rabbit. I hate it. I don't like it anymore. I, I can't fucking doing anything.
No, I'll, I'll, I'll change, I'll change like, like the broadcast
shit. Maybe. Oh, fuck. What? What? Oh, it just, it just looked crazy for a second. I missed it.
Nope. Still, still can't do anything.
The game's like safe over here. Yeah.
The question is just how do we get to it?
What happens when you right click? Nothing? Nothing. Because it's not doing anything?
Yeah, yeah. Like, I can move, I can move my mouse around, but it's not like, I can't interact with
anything. Yeah. Oh, wait, is that mouse in like the, the rabbit window? Yeah. Yeah. Oh, I see, I see, I see, I see.
I don't know, man. Might have to restart. Oh, my fucking god. Why? Why? Why were we cursed?
Try like, opening a new window and like, see if rabbit works in a new window or something?
Like, like, okay. Yeah. Yeah.
All right. All right. All right. All right. Should I close the original one?
It's pretty risky. I don't know. I mean, I'll still have it open. If you close it, will this like,
whole thing end? Here, no, I'll give you the power. Okay. Wait, can you just like,
fucking transfer it to me? I think so, yeah. Oh, shit. Yeah. Yeah, do that. All right,
you know that little thing next to the volume that says remote control? Click on that.
Oh, my god, I've got the fucking power. All right, all right. No, no, no, no, no, no, I'm closing
that and then you'll be in charge and then I'll go back. Okay, but mine's, it's not letting me
do anything either. I, yeah, wait, why did, wait, are you Joseph? Oh, oh, hey, oh, oh, yeah, yeah,
I'm Joseph. I'm Joseph. How did, okay, is it saved? Is it fucking saved? I, I, I, I, I think so. Oh,
my god. It's a miracle. Yes. How, how, how did it work? Okay, whatever. That's great. Thank god.
Okay, now I see, now I see that there actually isn't any way, retrieve arms. Well done.
Now I, now I see that there actually isn't any way to get rid of that cursor because
that's just how rabbit works. That's fine. Yeah. Um, okay. Um, well, you can go to the
porthole, the display or the control deck. I think there's doors too. Okay, hold on.
Okay, okay, okay, okay. You're in, you're in a space spaceship hull command mod. You're in the,
you're in the command, the command module. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, no, you're in, you're in the command module. Oh, shit. Okay. Fuck.
Yeah, here we go. All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
All right, let's check, let's see what my, what my, what my, what my, uh, my, my fetch modus is.
No, you got nothing. You got no, you got no modus, no modus operandi.
Shit. I'm talking like away from the modus operandi.
Getting money fastest by modus operandi. I've been ice cold since the night I saw my man die.
Yeah, yeah, my modus operandi is a malgum, a freelancer in the way of the samurai.
How do I live without you?
If I don't live without you.
We're seeing the two different ones, even though they're both the right, they can be real.
Um, look at the-
I wanna know how I ever, ever survive.
Wow, wow, wow.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, wait, just, just like look, just like look everywhere.
Okay. Yeah, let's go like look display or porthole.
I don't want, I don't want to have to fucking-
Here we go. A glowing green display shows a map of the galaxy with a destination you don't recognize.
An ETA of about 3,000 years, looking closer you see two on-screen buttons labeled root details
and new destination.
I'm gonna turn this bitch around.
The nav computer dumps you into an interface so obstruc that before you even consciously
process what's happening you've hit the back button and are at the main map again.
Excellent.
You two, you got your little frog brain, can't handle it.
Even though you fucking got the cyber brain that let you understand the wizardry of exponential
functions or exponential scientific notation, whatever.
Even though I'm frog Carl Karl Marx and I've invented communism I still can't wrap my brain
around simple reader functions.
Do root details.
Fuck.
The screen spills forth a slew of steps such as spiral spinward at Spathi system,
far faster than you can fathom.
Oh shit, it wouldn't let me do it all.
Uh, hmm, well, looks like you can't do anything with this, maybe?
Okay, what do you got?
You got the porthole and something else.
There was some other thing.
Ben, when am I gonna go back to doing bath in the third grade?
Soon, soon.
You just have to fucking, you just have to fucking escape from the cold abyss of space.
Jell-o, man.
Let me, let me drink some more of my germax.
Mortuizing original hand sanitizer kills almost all the germs.
Yeah, yeah, Rowdy fuckers cop killers.
Sponsored by germax, 99.999% of germs will die and so will you.
Kills germs in 15 seconds, hope it kills me even faster.
Kills, kills germs, kills 99.999% of germs or you get your germs back as a free refund.
Shit.
Oh god.
We can't do the, we can't do the licensing deal.
Oh boy, it's all falling through.
It's all falling through.
Um, all right, all right, shit.
Okay, okay, all right, who's, who's we got?
Okay, Puffy Cheetos, sponsored by Cheetos.
Sponsored by Monster Energy Ultra Sunrise, my favorite beverage.
Sponsored by Combo's Seven Layer Tortilla Dip Flavor.
Sponsored by, sponsored by this cup of tea that I made in my kitchen a couple hours ago
and then I reheated it in the microwave.
It's pretty good, it's pretty good for dipping Jaffas in.
Jaffa cakes, sponsored by Jaffa cakes.
Sponsored by, you know, you know that old, that old jingle, that old jingle.
Jaffa, jaffa, jaffa, jaffa in the morning, orange in the middle.
Suck your dad's dick, friend.
It won't let me see the big babies.
Man.
I want to see big baby.
This game has taken-
It won't give me big baby.
This game's taken a dark turn into dark comedy.
Google image search big baby boys.
No, no, no, no, you seem to-
I want to see the big babies.
You seem to be having parser and or guess the verb trouble, Munchie.
Remember, you can always type help for assistance.
Help! I need big baby boys!
Give me the big baby boy!
I want to see him.
I want to see him grow up.
No, no, the pathos.
No, I want to see my big baby.
I'm a cool, I'm a cold, unfeeling, phony, two-faced, amoral protagonist, down on my luck.
And I've been in jail.
I haven't seen my big baby boy grow up.
He's been without his big old daddy.
He's even- a big baby boy has an even bigger daddy.
Rule number one of thorough dynamics.
Big baby boy has an even bigger daddy.
Oh, fuck.
I want to see him.
I want to see my- I want to give my baby boy a big, a big dad.
He deserves one.
No, Jesus. Jesus Christ, Munchie.
Oh, what the fuck?
Why don't we- I blacked out.
What are we doing?
Why don't we sleep?
I don't- you go and say look- just say look port hole.
Just say look port hole.
God, through the portal you can see a background of starshifting as the ship gently spins the
constellations.
Okay, um, fuck, just do look, because there's one other thing, and I guess you got to do the last
thing.
All right, uh, control-
Fuck.
Control deck.
Oh wait, oh no, you can go to- yeah, it's- okay, I don't know, it's either the control deck or the ladder.
Okay, say look control deck.
All right.
The control deck consists of an array of switches and a pair of joysticks.
Let's hope you never need to override the ship's autopilot, because these are definitely not
frog joysticks.
You should definitely fuck with them.
I don't understand what you want to fuck.
With them.
With them is what I want to fuck.
Fuck.
Um, say like, say like, say like, uh, uh-
Wait, wait, oh, wait, I fucking got it, I fucking got it.
Yeah.
No!
Fuck!
Okay, okay, okay, okay, enough pussy footage.
We need to go all in on learning fractions.
No more, no more pathos, no more big babies, no more big baby boys.
We need to fucking get- we need to do it.
Yeah, um, uh, push- wait, wait, push, push switch, push switch, push switches.
Oh, whatever.
Um, all right, go to the ladder.
This game is made by fucking little, little, little, little bit of a- you know what they call them.
Yeah, yeah, go to- go to ladder, go to ladder.
Or go aft.
Later, go to later, fucking nerd.
This is- looks like before you go and learn fractions, you better go learn to spell.
Ben, you are going to be vaporized into a fucking pooper-dipe-wearing baby fuck.
I'm gonna vape myself into a pooper-dipe-wearing baby fuck, you know what I'm saying?
This looks like an all-purpose living area.
A sleeping pod sits next to a nightstand.
A ladder leads to the four.
Okay, that's where you just were.
An oriental rug lies in the center.
You can't say that anymore.
Dude, check the rug.
All right, you know- okay.
The decorative oriental rug sits in the center of the room looking at it more closely.
It doesn't quite lay flat on the floor.
There's a significant dip around the middle.
Okay, maybe you gotta move it.
All right.
Moving the rug, you discover a recessed hatch.
Your score has gone up by two-fifths of a point.
Fuck- Oh, shit.
Fuck yes.
That's how you know it's progress.
They should remake this game, but the entire time,
overlaid on top of the entire game are two tracks.
Number one, the John Tron theme song at full blast of, like, maximum game.
In other words, not even recognizable anymore.
And then second, to balance it out,
put the angry video game nerd as well at full game, maximum blast over it.
Oh, Zoli, Quinn!
The joke is gamer culture.
Because gamers are a joke and gamers are over.
Gamers are dead.
Long with gamers.
Gamer justice!
Gamers, um, video games.
Okay.
open it you have to work you have to give the wheels a few spins the hatchpops
open okay
enter hatch go go to hatch yeah enter what what else was there there was a
you slipped through the hatch nearly every service in this room is covered
with a sticky pink goop which seems to be thicker near a gray machine a gray
machine sitting in the corner a hole in the wall exposes a nest of wires there's
a hatch leading back okay yeah that's that's what you just were okay um make
shit can town I only used it as far as can okay okay there's sticky goop there's
a gray machine and there's a hole in the wall these are these are the things these
with which we can fuck all right all right
shucks shit fuck this machine this machine won't be moved by your human by
your human desires by your human but my human etiquette no that that I really I
really want to get all up in that pink goop in yeah that's all I want I just
want to get mad fucking into that I just want to get super embroiled in that
fucking pink goop you real you are pink goop munchie you're that's what you're
made of anyone's ever said to me it's the nicest thing anyone's ever said to me
like you're like you're like Winnie the Pooh like he when he was but with
sludge and goop yeah instead of fluff yes oh I thought you mean like he was
eating honey and that and that was gonna be oh the oh yeah actually that works
too that works too yeah you just got pots you just got pots and pots you just
got cans and cans of it look at look at examine the machine that's not you didn't
verb it you didn't verb it right the machine consists of a spigot aimed at a
flat platform a hand sheet of paper has been hastily taped over the base of the
platform definitely look at that paper this is the out-of-order note included
in your game package okay sure sounds good look at the hole in the wall a
spigot aimed at a flat platform that's Minecraft just go to just say just do
look at hole all right yeah cool yeah look hole go just head over to the look
hole peering into the exposed machine there you see what looks like an empty
coffee can that you're guessing doesn't belong there see it knew what you were
trying to do it damn it knew what you were trying to do there but it won't
it's not having it why why is it so fucking bigoted because it was made
because it was made by Mars bugs and Mars bugs lack empathy because they all
have all my god bugs they haven't even they haven't even fucking they haven't
even released and vanquished that the the synopete of their soul you do you
know do you know how do you know how you know that bugs are are bad and lack
moral fiber it's because they don't even they don't even have muskles they
can't even lift they don't even have muskles all their limbs are controlled
by by fucking liquid hydraulics they don't lift munchy they can't lift you
know how you know that bows are amoral why because they're white now we're
into the stars to start a race war comes a kid with a knack for propaganda
this is the theme song of Adolf Hitler get that can oh my god I can actually
make can town now you twist the can and eventually comes loose but you've ripped
the insulation off of an adjacent wire in the process and it begins sparking as
it comes in contact with an adjacent strut you glance down at what you've
taken huh it really is a coffee can alright so you've got the can you've
got the machine you've got the hole in the wall and I think that's it for this
room was there something else in this room what was the term of it it was
it was machine it was goop oh goop yeah yeah yeah it was pink pink goop is what
they called it fuck fuck shit can you like put put put goop in can you need
to be hold okay okay get get get goop get ye to the goop sir yes yes is all I
fucking goop is stuck to the surface could you not just scrape some off I
scrape off goop from my body all the time I guess it's really I guess it's
really sticky like hella sticky so I scoop off sticky substance for my body
all the time I don't think you understand just how sticky this goop is this
goop because it could it possibly be more sticky this is this all of my blood
clots this goop is this goop is made of a thousand neutron stars this goop is my
god this goop is a neutron star that has been that has been ejaculated all over
into the stars to drink the pink goop starts a race war
well really gets around well I don't mind being plagiarized in various
different ways by me wait who who is that who is being plagiarized Jimmy
neutron oh the boy Jesus himself I I know I know exactly what to do but I don't
want to tell you because I feel like I'd be cheating fucking okay I remember yeah
this took this took me this puzzle took me a long fucking time I think I actually
I think I had to look up like one step of it I I didn't sign up to be fucking
Sherlock Holmes all right dude this is what it takes this is what it takes to
be a frog a frog in bug marks you have to be you have to be clever as well as
dexterous okay okay okay okay okay okay okay so you got the can there's a
machine and they don't remember if there's any there's a hole in the wall
there's the goop yeah there's the goop there's the hole in the wall there's the
machine you can't scoop the goop you can't scoop the goop munchy because it's
too sticky let's see what's on the machine again the machine consists of a
spigot aimed at a flat platform a handwritten sheet of paper has been
hastily taped over the base of the platform spigot and you see if I can
look at the platform yeah the machine oh same that really boils there's a
spigot there's the paper it's been taped on the platform and I guess that's it I
guess that's it for the machine it's just those two things you rip the note
off leaving a fluttering piece of electrical tape behind and revealing
hey all right I knew to facing public property will get me somewhere oh fuck
I'm retarded you are but that's just odd that's just autism for you yeah I mean
you know what is the questions of the day what of the control panel is rendered
unusual by the sticky pink goop you see a row of what look like radio preset
buttons all but two of which are stuck there's also a big red lever none of
these are legibly labeled okay so you got two buttons and a lever the machine
the machine where is dispensing mom's specialty the voice says pink goop
streams out of the faucets splashing against the flat platform and getting
everywhere a couple drops land in your mouth and you recognize the flavor bacon
milkshake oh my god atmospheric anomaly detected a different voice says a
wearing sound ensues and the bulk of the goop is sucked into invisible vents
leaving just enough goop floating around to be gross and annoying atmosphere
purified the voice says triumphantly okay okay so that good that goop is
floating meaning it's not stuck to the surfaces meaning oh I want that goop I
want that goop I want that you can't oh you can't get a meaningful amount just
by collecting loose goop fuck shit I fuck I thought that was it I thought we
okay well you know what okay well I think okay you know you you gotta get you
gotta get it to shoot into the can you just gotta squirt it right into the can
all right wait it came out of the faucet does that mean the spigot
you platform platform so hasty you place the can below the spigot okay yeah okay
here we go here we go it mostly gets everywhere but the coffee can does end
up filled you grab the can atmospheric anomaly detected the vents do their
ineffectual thing atmosphere purified so that's all I want I'm at mystery to
be purified so you reminds me of that one time I was hanging with my bro Mike
Pence and he and he got fucking all the blood everywhere yeah was it was it the
stuff of neutron stars no it was actually acid and they destroyed all my
furniture and I haven't had him back since he was he was totally wasted this
always always forgiven thank God he thank God he went on to bigger and
better things those drops earlier were enough bacon milkshake for one lifetime
thanks well all right man you've got a cat you've got a can of bacon milkshake
hey you know what there okay there was one there was one I think you're done
here except there is one step that like took me forever and I had to look up so
I'm just gonna tell you you got to grab the tape the tape the tape that the tape
that the thing was was let was taped there with is important okay now you got
to go you got to use the tape and the and I put the tape on the sparking wire
in the hole in the wall you read yep there we go all right yeah that that
that was the one that was the killer that I never figured out okay wasting that
guy killed Michael Jordan yeah I bet his ear right off bet his ear right off in
the box where were you when the United States invaded my personal privacy by
downloading my internet history all of which consumed were consumed by Google
embassy churches of my rightful son that was taken away from me for a crime I
didn't commit big baby I want pictures of big baby I want to see him grow a big
baby spider-man talking to spider-man I need pictures of the big baby the big
boy I have to see him grow he's growing somewhere out there I'm missing it I'm
fucking missing it I was stuck in a turkey's prison for all my life and I
broken out just to see my big baby boy he's getting bigger and bigger this baby
this baby's getting bigger by the minute you know I'm saying oh my god are you
son of a fucking nightmare scenario what's that I don't know where the baby
boy is bigger than the big learn the bigger dad
the baby big baby boy gets so fucking big that the bigger dad just just can't
fucking compete can't keep up in what happens can't keep up with his with the
baby then how will I currency survive how is this how is the system of
government gonna fucking hold up it's a bigger baby get some bigger did a big
old daddy yeah dads dads grow linearly dads grow linearly babies grow
exponentially in the fullness of time a baby's eclipse there eclipse their dads
and bigness this is the issue with all the Roman Empire now it's gonna fall to
the it's gonna lead to the fall of the big baby empire babies as emtotically
approach infinite bigness you got to leave the hatch you got to leave the
hatch right you're done here I think go go to hatch okay cabin's quarters a
sleeping pod sits next to it okay I guess examine the sleeping pod no you
fucked it you fucked it you exame I think I think you did everything in the
other room well there was nothing else to do with like the control panel because
it just wouldn't let you do anything the sleeping pod looks like a bed with a
lid but you've got to assume it's got some sort of suspended animation
functionality I mean right there's a hole on the top next to a gauge reading
empty that seems important okay all right use goop on hole you bring the can
close to the hole and the hole sucks the pink group right in the gate the nearby
gauge fills up your score has gone up by nine halves of a point so is it done I
is it ready I don't know is it ready try I don't know for any of us are ready for
for a parenthood true I don't know if we can all if we can't even be prepared for
the for the biggest boy the world's ever gonna see the biggest the biggest
responsibility the biggest adventure of all the biggest adventure of all child
rearing child child husbandry as it's known I wait try getting in the pod
Gert Gert in Bud you can't safely sleep until you're confident you return to
bug Mars by the end of the trip I think what what what does this blast game want
me to do and what does that to do with reuniting with my fucking son was was
there more to the pod or did you do everything with that I I think you did
me okay maybe you got to go fuck around maybe you got to go aft yeah yeah yeah
the sleeping pod looks like a bed with a lid yeah yeah yeah there's a hole in the
top next to a gauge reading full okay all right I guess I guess that's all there
is I think you should go to the ladder and go back to the control panel a command
the walls of the circular to meet at a point that must correspond to the curve
knows the hole a porthole a glowing display okay check the display because
you tried the control deck and it didn't do anything
no this no this is this is this is a this is a go to new destination then
have computer no no okay that's no good try root details again I feel like
something must have changed you did all the screen splits forth yeah alright go
to the control deck what look look control deck no no no no no no frog
fractions listen Ben not everyone could have studied how to make the perfect big
baby I was gonna mess up along the way but that's that that's just part of the
parenting process you know learning learning as you go learning as you go
you and the baby can learn together the control just imagine a big baby would
just fucking break all my bones immediately up on looking at it these are
definitely not frog joysticks there's got to be something you can do with these
you you fix the you fix the you got the goop you filled you filled yeah you'll
have to be more specific as to what you want to do with the controls okay okay
move them what do you got you have an an array of switches and a pair of joysticks
I don't know what do you do with what do you do with joysticks
what the fuck great great great I'm stumped I'm stumped wait look at the
porthole again I mean it didn't it didn't show anything before through the
porthole you can see the background of stars yeah the constellations are all
unfamiliar okay so that's no help
hmm I'm getting the sinking suspicion that everything we've done up to this
point has been a major waste of time yes like in Homestuck for example like in
Homestuck just like the classic panel the classic panel retcon later in a
month in one of it I don't know in one of the moves that was maybe not the worst
in one of the retcons that was maybe not the worst in Homestuck
the battle the bat the bit wait you want to just look up what to do yeah I
have no idea what the fucks going on okay okay here I'll do it
all right here we go here we go here we go here we go
oh oh dude oh dude no you got to go back to the machine you didn't do
everything with the machine oh yeah okay okay okay actually wait there's
yeah yeah yeah yeah there's yeah there's something there's something else to do
in the machine room and there's something else to do in the captain's
quarters too alright alright alright okay I won't I won't be more specific than
that for now no no no a sleeping pod there's the nightstand there's a sleeping
pod in the nightstand single drawer which is closed well open the drawer
revealing a thick manual fuck yes get thick manual don't I knew I saw I looked
ahead in my fucking spirit guy it's I I rattled my Native American bones I said
when will the next earthquake come and it said oh when Ben fucking does that
shit I knew I would fucking when it happens it happens when when German the
wishcash uses earthquake I know I don't know you're talking about cuz no one
watches that show your I don't even know what you're saying gotta hate Pokemon
gotta hate Pokemon you'll have to be more specific you know do you're gonna
use it what are you gonna use it to whack are you gonna use it to whack the
hideous bumps on your I'm going to use it to see how to raise my son properly
well too bad because there's no way there's no answer because it's a learning
experience monkey it's a journey it's about the oh my god did you do you even
notice what you just did no you call me fucking monkey in earnest did I know
yeah I thought I'd be the only one that wouldn't do it no you know why you
well you know why let me explain it's just because thinking about oh oh you've
got a lot of explaining thinking thinking a lot because thinking about the
nuzlocke's just made me remember how much I hate and resent monkey Jones for
inspiring me to do this fucking stupid misguided retarded quest that I hate and
I hate myself for and I hate everything to do with and I wish I was dead it's a
manual for the navigation computer in the computer man module after leaping
through you feel confident you understand how to use the interface well and if
you set up a route back you bug my eyes yeah okay okay um go no no yeah okay you
can do that too that's fine yeah actually I should do something in the
fucking there there is one that you can do that you can do this now you can do
this here now there's you can fuck with the controls because the last thing yeah
you got it you got to change the you got to change the the route you got to change
the route and you then you got it there's something else you got to do in
the the machine room and then last thing you got to do is get in the sleeping pod
once your new destination here we go you definitely plot a course back to bug
Mars the engines were on you feel g4's shift the ETA reads 57 and 350 years huh
you run a diagnostic and determine that the vast majority of the time is going
to be spent going through bug customs luckily you can sleep through most of it
your score has gone up by three and a third points okay sweet yes well all
right yeah you can you can you can sleep you can go to sleep now okay okay okay
thank you lie down in the sleeping pod close the lid drift off secure in the
57 and something years you return to bug Mars when you wake up you're clearly not
in your sleep pod you literally glance at your bearings and you appear to have
been sleeping with a heart in on a heart-shaped bed covered with roses a
voice comes from the next room awake already a wispy human figure in the
bathroom and crown walks in she bends over and kisses you on the nose and
suddenly you feel your body shifting yay she laughs and claps and you realize
that you've been transmogrified into a human form gross this is going to be
soon this isn't what I signed up for ah it's it's it's it's beautiful it's it's
fucking world-renowned scientist Andrew W. K. Andrew W. K. it's Andrew it's
Andrew W. Bill Nye the science guy no no the indignity the indignity
muncher indignity you awake with a start what a horrible dream you call your
friend drag draggy the flying dragon just to talk to someone yellow draggy says I
just had the worst Terry's cruise I just had the worst nightmare you explain the
situation uh I'm not I'm not sure the support group for human bug eaters is
really going to be that much of a following draggy responders maybe if
we drummed a little publicity first I know just the PR agency oh my god I
love I love branding five minutes later draggy shows up at your door dressed to
the nines he tells us a frog tuxedo at you put this on babe we're running for
president you know what I think perfect yeah okay good good oh Canada what say
you to allegations you're not a natural born citizen that you're under 235 and
that you're a frog
oh yeah bro you're gonna dance your way into the bug White House
oh yeah you're doing it if all else fails try button mashing
oh this is magical this is magical I I used to be I used to be pretty great
shakes the DDR back in my back in my shit eating days as it happens back when
I was a little fuck I have to do this I have to do this I have to do this for my
son I have to see my little baby boy I have to see him dude yeah that mashing
oh no oh you fucked oh no you had such a good run there but then you fucked it
all up you'll be you'll bitch of a dad your son your son is gone and he's
better off for it you'll never see him again and it's for the best I literally
I literally can't do this by the way I literally I'm in fucking capable of doing
this you bitch you bitch you're just a zero the constant constituency loves an
underdog you're a shoe in for president
yes oh my god Betsy blue bonnet sir Clarence Clarence Gashropot
I've seen an undertale and Ferdinand Ferdinand Kroger which is not the name on
your fucking ID but that's fine and Flaps McQueen Flaps McQueen in the greatest
story ever told and and rag he jelly he a lee and introducing draggy ceiling
eater as himself wait featuring the guesswork of big baby boy
see I think I think I may have I think I may have fucked up because I think
there may have been something else in the shit I think there might have been
something else in the ship to get shit tons of Zork mids and I think you may be
fucked without Zork mids but I guess we'll see that's fine I can't read this
by the way like like the the version that I'm seeing is like artifact II and
glitchy as fuck I can barely read I can read just fine okay weather report sunny
bug assets 2 million Zork mids oh cost to produce bug porn 10,000 Zork mids
megabytes how many megabytes of bug porn you wish to make all that's not a
number mr. president draggy just shows draggy just shows up at your bed tosses
you a suit and says we're running for president
then you fucking did how many how many wait I can't fucking read how many pop
ups 15 how many pop up banner ads 15,000 Zork mids each do you want to
purchase so you made 20 that's that's a weird weird notation there you made
200,000 megabytes of bug porn and you I don't know a million a billion no a ten
ten thousand ten ten hundred ten ten thousand fifteen thousand yeah no no no
that would require okay okay so make like a hundred fuck that's bullshit I
mean I want tons of pop up ads I need them all what price do you wish to
charge for a megabyte of bug porn this is this is what the president does all
day just decide just sets porn prices on his fucking CRT computer alright I don't
think you need full proof I'm I'm
bug porn yes yeah did you super performances have today made today's
bug porn too hot the warehouse burned down you made zero of bug porn oh god I
think you made no I think you oh dear you lost most of your money how many oh
well oh how many Zork mids you can just print more money though I guess I guess
we'll let your successor worry about the inflation problem six oh yeah yeah now
we're now we're cooking with gas the system of satellites to help you meet
determine the weather forecasts yeah that sounds crucial bug drugs will
pacify delinquent bugs keeping them off the streets and staying home and
watching bug porn yeah that's all I fucking want baby you know maybe I've
been too hard on sex yeah yeah you know when you're when you're the one when
you're the one in charge of the sex it's not so bad when you all when you own
all the sex in the boat in bug money on the means of the sex it doesn't it
becomes pretty good that we we're we're we're president of the union of the bug
so vets the bug so union oh god I'm choking on my monster energy ultra
sunrise available on your eyes available at a wah wah near you sponsored by
monster you know I'm really upset cuz when I first heard did you say wah wah I
just thought he was being a retarded fucking idiot baby I wanted to be stupid
and I thought I was an actual like thing unfortunately no yeah I was I was
disgusted to realize there's a chain called wah wah like have some self
respect entrepreneurs if you don't have self-respect if you don't have self
respect you can't get love for your friends 10 10 a black to hell have a
little help from my friends I get by with a little help from my friends gonna
start a little race war with my personaries need some help starting
tensions familiar friends waiting just around the band everywhere you look
everywhere I'm just I'm no no no give me give me give me give me control give me
control the board I want to be I want to be bug fine I want to be bug present now
I'm taking fine oh my fine oh god take it okay I've got all the I've got all the
money I'm gonna make oh no it's not working been oh my god okay here take it
back take it back please okay steal it all right make make 10,000 thousand come
on let's be let's be that's not that's too many megabytes that's too many
megabytes make fifty five hundred thousand fifty fifty dozen fifty dozen
megabyte five two hundred and ten megabytes 40 413 excellent it's too hot
you're gonna burn the warehouse down but not really it's fine it's good be sure
to charge more for your product than it costs to produce thanks thank you
hamburger yeah you want to know what what what's the other date six six what
is that one what is that one it's it's it's the kids that's that's the that's
the extra ones yes the in-house bug porn musician decided to make bug IDM
today nobody's quite sure what to make of it that's a very thunder storm hit bug
March they all your bug oh shit fuck man the bug porn industry just can't catch
a break yeah man Jesus oh well they'll just have to know and and another day
another billion set of illegitimate bank notes we're making it's fine guess we'll
let your success to worry about the another another day another dollar they
say but in your case it's more like nine hundred thousand nine hundred ninety nine
million dollars yes all right um this is coming the worst thing I've ever you
just got you just got a blast through it okay okay he's got a he's got a shimmy
and shake no you're doing it wrong well no you got it I'm eating I'm eating
Easter smarties by the way Easter doesn't fucking exist on bug Mars you
fucking traitor right I don't know yeah you're right you're right Mars hasn't
had its Jesus yet but he's coming I'm there Jesus coming yeah I can't do it by
the way can't do what I can't press space you serious yeah okay give me give me
do it it's not it's not working okay you do you have the remote control I don't
think you have the remote control yeah I do all right it's working hold on
okay maybe you just overload here here take take take it I got it I got it I don't
see I don't see your answer your cursor I don't see the cursor moving buddy I don't
either but the icon is white it says I have right now now now oh now no it's
not working do you see that by the way yeah I see that okay oh great been good
what the fuck looks like capitalism destroyed this fucking society man give
me that give me that give me that
I'm what a fucking time what a fucking time for to freeze this you want to just
want I want to just like watch like a let's play or something yeah yeah it
sucks yeah what it we already became president that's all we wanted to do
we watched our son grow up I think yeah we our son grew up and we gave in once
he came of age we gave him nine megabytes of bug porn and that that should
do it that's how you know you succeeded my son I'm gonna give him a gigabyte of
gun of gun of gun porn whoa now you're gonna have to wait for the technological
singularity for that shit boy oh technological singularity won't ever
happen it'll be the bug singularity and we'll all be praying mantises been holy
shit oh my god what then clean the fucking wax out of your ears for this
one yeah boy open up your fucking socks and get ready to have them be off of
your fucking feet in just a second I'm ready I'm ready all right I'm picking a
note right this dad write this down in your fucking Bible Josh okay yeah okay
Josh yeah all right all right did you know that most praying mantis are
actually agnostic uh no way no fucking you better believe it that can't be true
gotta get that germics that can't that can't be true because germics I gotta
get out how can germics how can it be how can they be an egg in the face I need
more germics because they don't they know about God they've seen him active
ingredient I saw him I saw I saw praying man wait a minute how praying mantis
of pray they pray to God because they love Jesus Jesus
I know homo sapien homo only use hands Jesus is a guy for real
advice um context with eyes flushed through thoroughly with water what
content my banana has appeal oh I'm so embarrassed I'm so fucking ashamed of
myself his skin oh god irritation develop I shame myself in front of Jesus
Lord and save you out of reach of children and germics keep out of reach
of the baby boys I don't germics keep keep keep away from baby boys germics
I gotta stop the baby boy blood of Christ I gotta puke up the blood of
Christ because I'm unfit to swallow it I'm unfit for salvation boy growth I gotta
choose baby boy gotta follow the path of atheism and spit in the face of God who
I know to exist don't don't don't don't just and choose to fight
germics self-patriotized they stop the suffering being big cell patriotic
big boys big boys and make them normal boys
big big big big big boys what a damn shame that it had to be this way they make they may make they make they make them normal boys they never gonna come to big old fatherly
the normal babies baby boys big boys this is me make the money I just I just
watched the end I just watched the end of frog fractions all it is is you like you
do a couple rounds of making bug porn and then there's a little bit of you like
on you're the frog and you're on like the turtle and you swim around like a
presidential pool for a second and then like that's the end and then credits
roll so I we've pretty we've we've seen all we've seen all what matters of
frog fractions we've explained oh god and then there's some bug oh god and
there's some bug porn oh Jesus oh gross oh it's okay it's pixelated it's
pixelated and it's censored for my so you can see you can show this for bug
porn to your grandma and your son you know when your son is a growing boy he
needs that he needs that censored pixelated porn like to wean himself he
needs to be weaned on to bug porn with the pixelated kind only when he passes
the ripe old age of 14 does he get the hardcore stuff you know when when up when
a bit when a big baby boy he decides you know what I want to go all out I want to
become a burg deviant I want to I want to be I want to take the bugs take them
take the bugs then then you know you just got to let him be yeah he's got to
make his own mistakes gotta be proud he's gotta make his own mistakes yeah you
know he's gonna learn just how easy women are manipulated he's not gonna need
porn you know he's gotta learn those lessons for himself but if you love
him then be proud of him cuz after all he's just a man and you got to stand by
your man even when your man is a is a big baby boy
if you learn anything from frog
fractions him too long to cling to just can't live out your big baby boy
sure sure maybe you're a two-faced phony unemotional unfeeling unempathetic
unsympathetic ghost shell of a man and an atomic complete robot with no
natural feelings but at least and you may be down on your luck and in a
Turkish prison but once you break out you know you know the first thing on your
fucking list it's gonna be finding your baby boy and making sure he knows that
he's a father that loves him you gotta find the big baby boy and make that big
baby boy have a big old heart and have a big old fiesta with him
you gotta buy him a fiesta cake so he knows so he knows for real you gotta
touch your little baby boy and you gotta make him know that he's the only
little baby big old big old baby boy in your little fucking life and that one
day one day the throne of bigness will be passed on from from you to him just
that it had been done with your father to you whoever eclipses the other to his
his father and in bigness that's when he should he become a man and then and
whenever whenever the father becomes smaller than his big baby boy son his
his bones evaporate he turns into cloth at the bay the baby boy can use to wear
as a toga yeah yeah it's cannon yeah it's baby cannon that's baby cannon right
there it's cannon to existence itself well I just watched I just watched the
ending credits of frog fractions role I gotta say it was a really emotional
experience for me what do you think of frog fractions munch um I thought it's
pretty good I like I like the beginning part when you were like doing shit yeah
when you were learning about fractions yeah when you were learning about
fractions and then it got a we got away from the core lessons and started
talking and started teaching how to spell yeah started teaching you how to use
grammar and syntax yeah it became it was unfocused it was unfocused yeah it
lacked cohesion hopefully these hopefully these problems I can see the
levels I couldn't see the levels in the background above the of other levels I I
want I want frog fractions to so fucking much
um some someone some some somebody on fucking somebody on fucking the
internet um fucking gift me frog fractions gift me frog fractions please
someone buy it for me on steam no seriously do it's save save me money um
I want I want I want I want well no it's not called frog fractions to it's called
like glitter glittering oh god I don't know but it's called like glittering
grotto or something and oh and I want grow up yeah but everyone buy me video
games um my my steam handle is one four four Enoch or Enoch one four four one of
the other buy me video games everyone and then I'll play them on rfk to rfck
maybe I won't it doesn't matter it doesn't matter how do you feel about all
that munchie
munchie speak to me speak to me no no what have I done no oh god I I fucked it I
fucked it up I ruined I I poisoned it I put I've poisoned the rfck I've poisoned
I've turned I've turned I've turned the artistic purity of ratty fuckers cop
killers into a crass cop killer should be it well it should have been it
should have been re recalled been in a munchie disgustingly communicate but now
it's gonna be munchie disgustingly excommunicates bin from being fucking
real life I'm gonna turn you into a footnote of history bin no no look look
into these baby boy eyes do you see big baby good big baby empathy and these
big baby boy eyes I I don't all I see is all I see is all I see is pain and
torment big baby pain all you see is big big big baby boobah big baby ouch out
all I see is a all I see is a boy in turmoil he just he just needs he needs
he needs love all I see is a need a need for love and and and put in some and
to be dandled and to be and to have his big baby body dandled on a knee this
baby isn't even fucking big come on it's big enough it's big enough for me
frankly honestly Ben I think you know yeah I think you aren't even a dad I'm
gonna I'm gonna go for I don't think you're even a dad yet um but but I can be
a dad my you could be my steam handle Enoch 144 buy me glitter mitt and grove
and grow up someone on the internet please buy me video games I think I
think we've been doing this all wrong glitter mitt and grove is frog fractions
too by the way that's what we've been doing this all wrong yeah have we have
we I mean I believe it I mean I'm sure you're right I'm munchie here's the
thing I'm sure you're right and we have been doing it wrong but I but I there's
no way that you could have figured it out because the ways that we're wrong are
too comprehensive microscope to look at the tiny old little woman what am I
tiny old little woman what it's the new one it's for it's for it's replaced big
baby boy it's little old woman little old woman okay okay okay little old woman
little little women little women and big babies they go together like he's in a
pot he's in carrots butter butter and jam they go together like toast toast and
bread they go together like they go together like warthogs and wow wow wow
when are you going to finish playing through Explorers of Skye oh that you
know yeah at some point I just forgot about it I was like most of the way done
too yeah I never finished it how far did you how we mean you wouldn't mean you
are most of the way I got I like I got to fucking future world whoa and and I
met this the Celebi and holy shit but I never I don't I don't remember was yeah
I never finished it I don't know why we'll have to do we'll have to do a
bright focus on that well of me finishing of me finish yeah yeah yeah yeah
of you do of you doing the last dungeon of Explorers of Skye okay yeah yeah fuck
yeah fuck yeah yeah yeah vote in the comments and how much you want to see
it on the scale how much how much do you really really want to see it how much
do you want to see Ben St. the Luxray and his trust and his trusty
companion Steve Carell the Don fan fucking defeat Explorers of Skye in my
opinion it's a lot it's a lot forever
who is this handsome fella I don't know I can't see I can't this handsome fella I
can't I is it is it a little old lady no it's it's you it's a little old you
guys this is what Ben looks like in real life wait where where what are you
talking about what are you I'm on the fucking thing I'm on the thing still I'm
on rabbits still oh I left I left it I left it how do we get to it it's fine
no no oh yeah I see it I see it I see it no it's good I haven't been paying
attention it's me wait what why why man some of the fucking shit that you find
when you search my name is like like some of it is weird like what why like why
that what none of this looks weird to me but no no I mean okay all this looks
enormous like okay I obviously this horse is out of place but then there's
like but then there's like I mean I've drawn a lot of art in my day I don't
know I just have to wonder like why these bits in particular like why this
fucking picture of mage what what the fuck these like pictures from my Twitter
from like two days ago that picture of Jackie with the robot face nobody even
fucking well I got like 20 likes but then there's like what the fuck that's
17 years ago in my DeviantArt why the shit why the shit is some of this I don't
know I you know what you know what it's just cuz I'm a fucking hack it's just
cuz I'm a fucking hack yeah and it's all it's all bullshit and it's all just
totally ran oh why is this though this t-shirt you know why wait I figured it
out you know why everything you know why everything that I've ever done is here
in seemingly random order it's because I'm a fucking hack and I've never done
anything in my in my life and there's just not enough there's not enough of
my shit to populate a simple Google search and therefore it all gets used up
and you see everything and this is clearly been it's all pointless it's all
pointless yeah Ben St. Maxon that's my name and that's my torso I hope you
enjoy we've been doing this all wrong like that fucking mom like why is the
okay the first two my logo and the first page of the champion I get those why is
the third result my fucking mom key fan art that why why these why are the
fucking pictures of the kayfabe commander so fucking high on the search
results list why yeah greatest creation yeah your greatest
contribute to some of this man that that fucking pics that like picture of his
face done in like the call of duty graphics like like a logo editor that's
that's weird why is that so fucking high on the list why does anything why does
anything ever yeah why does anything ever happen I remember I remember that
one I remember getting that one that was early that was just that guy just that
guy just struck while the iron was hot oh now he's forever a part of the
phantom horn lore yeah he's forever and boiled in your own personal story my
own personal cannon my own personal cannon you might say god I fucking
remember all of these you're tripping it's tripping me out it's tripping me
out man guys I'm freaking out here this was a misstep okay first of all man
first of all a hashtag max for 5t back first of all yeah yeah but we have we
haven't we haven't caught we even we even cut to the top of our we haven't cut to
the heart of the issue oh no I the great the greatest web comic ever made
discord and digi brony at that neck look at that neck how many oh oh look at
this part where I poorly resized the image and you can see part of the white
background there when I was underneath pitiful pitiful why how are I just in
my fucking why are I just in my career right now how many of these did you do a
couple man this was such a this was such a stupid fucking fools errands you don't
need to tell me I'm aware that I'm not the greatest webcom I know you know I'm
just making it clear to the viewer man this is this is fucking embarrassing this
happened this was awesome dude you know it kind of fucking sick I don't know you
know what you know what this is okay like this the existence the existence of
this tumblr is just an incredible disgrace and an embarrassment that that
no no no no no let me call that being said that being said I probably would
have done it too because it's fucking cool as hell and it's great yeah yeah yeah
cuz it's fucking awesome it is kind of awesome in its own retarded way it's so
fucking very clean look at these fucking look at look at the art look at the art
chops on these early on these early images okay for the whole seat pay for
the whole seat we only need the edge do you know that one thing we did at
Bronycon and you like remade it in like a thing yeah go to find that it's it's on
the it's on the t-bap tumblr I think no not the Twitter it's t-bap no asked it's
asked yeah that's the one yeah oh it's just t-bap.tumblr.com
oh look at this oh look at Dr. Wolf yeah oh look at this was this is this was
before it was before I knew him I didn't know I didn't know how could I know hey
what do you mean we didn't know how revolutionary his thoughts were hey man
look at all these you know how thought-provoking he was wait wait wait wait
look at the banner again I just want to real quick man hey it's the whole it's
the whole it's the whole horseshoe crew man is there anyone we're not is there
anyone we're missing wait mage mage isn't there and then did mage have one of
those she did what did she have a pony yeah are you fucking kidding me yeah yeah
dude she was okay okay okay I knew I knew that she was like she was a pony guy
but I don't remember where a pony looks like what are you can remember so many
fucking videos of like I'm shocked I'm shocked because like when I think of mage
I mostly think of her pony really well no I guess I guess I more think of her
like you I don't know but her human and her pony like looks so similar that
like they're basically the same person here's the thing the first video I saw
of hers was it was the Halloween thing and they were all like humans right yeah
yeah so I just I just always associated with her man I spent so fucking long on
that banner I spent so I remember spending forever in that fucking bed yeah
yeah here here let me hear that's voice act I'll I'll I'll I'll this is the shit
this is the shit this is a this is like the best I'll be spiky be rarity okay
sure um um I have cancer I'm going to die soon shit but yada sucks anyway look
look at my artistry yeah you yeah you drew this in like five minutes and then
I and then I took it home painstakingly I will fuck any guy can't wait to fuck
the first guy I see at Brody I drew this one I'm very proud of it hmm hmm wow
what a gay yeah very good very good very clean very good very good I love
that one that's the only good one that's not true they were all good but that one
was the best yeah yeah they were all great um let's we had a ton of those are
those are they real are they real yeah yeah yeah I still have them no I still
have them I scanned most of them I don't know why these exist I don't know why
these pictures exist I feel oh god oh god oh god I forgot I forgot about some of
these I had I had I had I had aspirations at one point I plan to make
the fuck you had asked burgers I had I had asked burger rations for the fucking
tea back tumbler now this image is legendary right yeah yeah now this
image is is fucking credible yeah um there's never been it's so pointy god the
paper you had you had what's your fucking what was her name something cookie
cookie cutter cookie cutter I think yeah wait was it actually cookie cutter I
I'm fairly certain yes lol what a terrible incredible man man oh my god he's
so fucking red pill look at my fucking art holy shit I was so red I was so
fucking bad art or maybe I was just not giving a fuck I don't know but she
should suffer a lowly sex out I dude holy shit I I resonate so much dude you
know that there was a guy who followed me the other day who was only like the
anti-vagina police or something like that yeah he was my fucking hero you
know um I got it I gotta say I gotta say I'm pretty I I'm sometimes pretty
nostalgic for the old for the tea back days sometimes I think sometimes I'm
tempted to think back and be like and be like yeah those were the days like yeah
that was when the shit was real that was when I did all my best work but you
know I'm looking at it now and I'm a little I'm it's it's not it's not quite
it's not quite as I remember it it's not quite rose tinted yeah it's not quite
as rose tinted for real whatever it's it's good it's it's that you been that's
even more recent the hashtag max revive t-bap so you can go back and write all
your wrongs oh so I can oh it could just I can I can do HD versions of all these
yeah I can remake I can remake did the long the long-awaited remake of the
t-bap of the ask t-bap tumbler yeah just just with the people just what the
people have been clamoring for my god it's it that's all we fucking need it's
all we need brothers I brothers man man hold on hold on hold on yeah I meant I
meant I meant for like the that the ask t-bap tumbler to be like the actual like
repository of t-bap lore what the fuck oh okay dollars it's oh per video yeah
okay I was like I was thinking like whoa we're still making $14 a month it's
got to be like a hundred bucks in there by now but no no no we haven't no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no I wonder I wonder who I
wonder who is still patreoning t-bap like who like who's doing it just Nate
Just Nate's pledging all $14 he wants a dude he wants the hashtag max revive
tbap oh get the shit fucking out of the way yeah I don't give a shit about that
hold on here here here hold on hold on let's let's learn more about our lord
and say oh fuck this actual okay hold on I hate Dr. Wolf so much did I tell you
did I tell you about literally the fucking happiest the realest guy you know
yeah here's here's how here's when I knew here's when I knew that Dr. Wolf was
not a good person I met him at fucking Brony con at the first Brony con I went
to I we were like making small talk or something and and he was like and he was
like you know sitting all cross-legged and being all like yeah and and he said
something like he was hungry like he wanted to get something to eat and I
was like oh well there's a pretty good hotdog stand right across the the street
like because we were right near the exits and I like pointed right out the door
I was like there's a hotdog stand right over there and he was like I think I can
do a bit better than that and um I thought someone needs to kill this man
nicknames doctor or dog oh good oh good 34 he's 34 and thank God oh okay okay
I I also have a I also have a Dr. Wolf story at that exact same Brony con I
think yeah I think I could do a bit better than that
it's so perfect okay okay okay I forget I think like like like when I first came
up to you guys we were rough we we we we we we were riffin we had um we had a
We had a good report. We got some rapport going.
We were riffing.
Yeah, yeah.
We were jamming in the name of the Lord.
We were jamming.
Yeah.
And there was like a meme sort of, that I don't know how it occurred.
Bottom right corner. Is telekinesis possible? Check out our science fiction map.
Yeah, for a unicorn it is. For a unicorn it is.
Oh, you.
Anyway, anyway.
Anyway, the point is I go up to Dr. Wolf and he's surrounded by his lesion of fans.
And I ask him.
His adoring fans.
His adoring fan base.
Rivaled only by KP's weird fucking sycophant horde.
And I ask him two simple questions.
Number one, did the banks kill JFK?
Number two, did you kill Dryden horseshoes?
Did you kill him?
I've heard this, I think. Or at least I've heard the second part.
Yeah, simple questions for a simple man.
For a simple man.
And then like, he's like sitting down cross legged as you described.
Yeah, yeah.
And he looks up to me.
Sitting down cross legged, looking at his laptop with his hand.
Yeah, exactly.
Cleaning to the side with his hand and his chin.
With his hand and his chin, brow furrowed in concentration.
And he looks up to me.
I've never met Dryden horseshoes.
I don't know anything about Dryden horseshoes.
I mean, I know the name, but beyond that, no idea.
Me thinks the lady doth protest too much.
He fucking knows.
He knew.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I tell that to Jesse later and he said that they've literally talked before.
Oh my God.
So Dr. Wolf lied to my fucking face.
Really, really, really just...
Wow.
You know, has it ever...
You know, I don't think Digi's gonna mind me saying this here.
Because literally nobody gives a shit anymore.
But Digi said that one of his greatest regrets in his life and his career
was fucking featuring that first Dr. Wolf Fluttershy video on Equestria Daily
because it started the monster.
It started the fucking monster that is Dr. Wolf.
Like it's all Digi's fault.
It's all Digi's fault that Dr. Wolf exists.
And it makes him mad and it makes me mad.
Dr. Wolf, fucking look at him.
Just, hold on.
Just look at this fucking guy.
Wait, wait, wait.
Go down.
Art...
Oh, artists.
God.
God damn.
Let's see what they have to say about you.
Oh, I'm listed as a fucking artist?
Bulls fucking shit.
Never.
I never drew anything.
I never drew anything for that piece of shit.
That guy, that guy fucking scammed his artists and didn't fucking pay them shit.
He could afford.
He could afford to pay them fairly and he never fucking did.
I heard it from multiple sources that the dude just fucking scammed his artists
and tried to get by paying them next to nothing even though.
He has a fucking real job.
He's an accountant.
He's making an actual salary and yet he can't fucking afford to take a little bit out of
his fucking rank-eating Patreon.
His Patreon, which is a drop in the fucking bucket to his actual salary,
and just pay his fucking artists.
Fuck that guy.
Believe this innocent face.
Could this face do any wrong, Ben?
Could this face do any wrong?
I hate it, Munchie.
I think not.
I hate him.
I came into this in good faith.
Oh yeah, Doctor Wolf.
What a funny story about that.
What a silly existence.
But now I'm not laughing anymore, Munchie.
Now I'm mad.
I'm mad again.
Do you like how your page is completely fucking barren?
Good.
Hold on.
This is the Rift Cafe wiki.
I wish I wasn't on it at all.
When is this going to be a T-Bap wiki?
A whole wiki for T-Bap?
There could have been, man.
There fucking could have been a T-Bap wiki.
Why didn't we do it?
Why didn't we just break off from the fucking thing
and just do our own pony thing?
You just need to fucking hashtag magsurviveT-Bap.
There's too many unleft questions.
There's too many plot threads unresolved.
Every time, every single time, me or Nate brings up
raise these bros.
We both just get real quiet and sad
because it never happened and we both wish
that raise these bros had actually happened.
But now it's too late and we don't want to do it anymore.
We wish that back when we had the drive,
we had fucking seen it through and made it happen.
It's never too late.
He happens to be a Mormon.
Shut the fuck up.
Oh, his eldest niece is a brony.
His eldest niece is a brony, Munchy.
Her O.C.
That is insane.
Daffodilia.
Doctor Wolf fell into the psychological...
Wait, wait, wait.
The psychological role of the brony fan
without respecting it, expecting it at all.
Even before he started a moment with Doctor Wolf,
people called him the Psychologist of the Fan.
I'm gonna fucking kill myself if I think about
Doctor Wolf for one more second.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Let's go to...
It's not a full page.
Eleora. Let's go to Eleora.
The legendary Eleora.
Girlfriend of the Cult of Personality.
What was his name?
Toon Critic. It's Toon Critic's girlfriend.
Toon Critic?
Yeah. She's 31? What the fuck?
How...
What the fuck?
How are these people literally like...
I thought she was like 18.
Wait, how old is Toon Critic?
She's 31?
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
I mean...
Hold on.
24!
He's 24!
Whoa.
Is it... is it weird?
Is it weird that I think that's fucked up?
No. No.
It's fucked up.
Okay, good. Okay, good.
Okay, good.
I mean, it's certainly abnormal.
I mean...
Imagine calling yourself Toon Critic in earnest.
Toon Critic Y2K.
Like, if that name...
Like, that's literally the worst name I've ever heard.
It is...
Munchy...
I mean, I make a lot of bold claims.
I make a lot of bold statements.
Sometimes I speak without thinking.
Sometimes I go a little too far.
But let me say to you, in complete earnestness.
In complete...
Yes, in anything.
In complete and utter sincerity, with no hyperbole.
The Toon Critic Y2K is the worst name.
And the worst OC.
The worst design.
The worst human being.
Oh my god.
That has ever existed or ever will exist.
You're stealing his fucking bones.
What? What?
You're stealing his bones again.
You're gonna make silverware out of him.
There's nothing good.
Look at his... Look at him.
Oh my god. Oh my god.
Like, I don't have to say anything.
I don't have to say anything.
Just...
Look.
Just look and you'll understand.
Even fucking...
Ah, babes.
Mere babes in the crib.
We'll see what I'm talking about.
Wait, wait.
Oh, sorry. I'm sorry, Munchy.
But there's more.
There's more.
His pony sonan has a name.
Sketch Charmer.
Or Toon Store.
Toon Store!
Oh my god. His name is Toon Storm.
Oh, no.
Munchy,
everything I said about Toon Critic
just a minute ago is absolutely true
and yet I love him.
I love him.
I'm so glad.
I'm so glad he's real.
Can we... I haven't even...
I haven't even gotten...
I haven't even touched on the top hat and scarf.
That's all I've been looking at.
I mean...
Oh god. Oh Jesus.
The red...
The red hair...
The black hair with the red tips.
It's like fucking dementia raven way
over here.
What? Okay.
I've never known...
I mean, I've looked at this guy.
I've seen this avatar so many times.
I've never thought to question...
What the fuck is with the stripes on his hooves?
Not his hooves, his legs.
What is with the fucking stripes?
They're like...
Is he wearing armbands?
They're like, oh, they're like whisk warmers.
He's got to warm up.
He's got to warm up to bring on the Toon Storm, bro.
Toon Storm!
That's...
impeccable. Good job.
Good job, Toon Critic Light 2K.
This man...
He really ought to calm a man.
This boy.
He created this.
He might even not even have created himself.
He might have commissioned someone else to make it,
for all we know.
He made this.
This image that we are beholding now.
He looked at that, and he was like,
this is good.
This'll do.
This is how I want...
This will do nicely.
This fits into my...
This fits into my master plan.
I agree with the direction this is taking.
Everything I want to say,
this image says,
will run with it.
I concur, good sir.
I believe in the message of this image.
I believe in it.
Oh god.
Oh my fucking god.
I can't believe it.
He's just red and black.
He's all different shades of red.
Okay, okay, okay.
Toon Storm is good.
But the fact that he fancies himself
a charmer.
He fancies himself a charmer.
To the point where he would call himself
a sketch charmer.
There's just...
There's just no end.
There's no end to what I could say
about this guy.
Oh, the bands on his legs are not arm bands
as previously blue pair of stripes.
Oh, thank god.
He looks a little trivia.
He's actually called Flame Amigo.
Oh my god, Flame Amigo.
He must have changed his name.
He must have thought he was muscling in
on Josh Scorcher's territory.
Well, okay, okay.
Josh, let's not even...
Let's not bring up the fucking
the fucking nightmare that is
Josh Scorcher.
I like the fact that he just put
his phone number area code
at the end of his fucking
Flame Amigo.
I think that's what it is.
It has to be.
There's no...
You're just not going to throw around
the number 619.
You're not going to do that.
Is that an area code? I don't know.
That's my area code.
Maybe your neighbors.
Maybe I am him.
Maybe it's like a doctor...
A doctor wolf, a doctor hide
scenario.
Toon Critic has been shipped with many others
besides Ellie, including Golden Fox
and Keyframe.
Oh, Toon broke
up with Ellie sometime in late
2015. Oh man, I'm way behind.
I'm way behind on the Pony Lore.
Holy fuck. Okay, okay, okay.
So what I'm gathering from this is that
they were shipped together because that's
how humans work, I suppose.
Wait, was in a...
Was in a cannon...
This is...
This bullet point is blurring the line
of fantasy and reality so hard for me.
It's so meta
that I can't even wrap my puny little
P-brain around it.
Okay, hold on.
I think by in a cannon
ship they just mean that they were fucking dating
these fucking bastards.
I can't believe she's 31.
Alright, okay.
Excellent.
You know, I think past now
she'll ask my phone number.
No way. Maybe that's why he was
flame-flame-amigo-619.
Maybe he put your
area code. Yeah, maybe.
Look, there's nothing.
There's nothing. There's literally nothing.
There's nothing.
Oh, past analysis.
Why?
I don't know. Was he not good enough
for you people?
Did he not come up with snuff?
Yeah, I mean
for fuck's sake.
You know what it is. Come on. You know, here's
the fucking gets me.
Like, the amount
of information on your fucking
rift cafe wiki entry
is like, it has nothing
to do with
your fucking product.
Like, it's just all about how active
in the community you are.
Like, this is what,
the rift cafe does not exist
for any purpose.
Except for the fucking
rifters, for the rifters
who want to be rifters, who just fucking
circle jerk themselves over
just how fucking important in their own
gay little community they are.
Oh, god. Oh, nothing makes me
nothing makes me matter.
Nothing makes me matter in the pony fucking days.
Jesus Christ, Munchy. Munchy, god.
I'm so fucking, I'm so fucking glad.
I'm so fucking glad I escaped
Munchy. I'm so, I
can't believe it. I didn't, they didn't
all make it out. We have to go back.
No, no, never.
We have to go back. We have to go back.
We have to be like,
we have to be like,
like Plato's allegory of the cave.
You know what I'm saying? No.
Like, we, yes.
We found out there's like an entire other
world outside of this little pond.
Yeah, we went, they're not going to believe us.
No, like, we're gonna,
we're gonna, we're gonna go back
in there and like, and they're just watching,
they're just watching like,
they're little fucking shadow ponies,
and there's like, there's like,
there's like, you know, you can make like,
YouTube videos that aren't like,
a fucking review of
my little pony with your avatar
in the corner and they'd be like,
well, well, well,
well, well, well, where's
my birthday cake?
Well, well,
just stop me. I just don't believe
you. I just don't.
They're just gonna like, they're just gonna like,
confer amongst themselves and like,
no, I think, I think it's better.
I think it's better the way we were doing it.
I think we're really, I think we're really getting
some good results.
Oh, thanks for your input.
She hasn't known
a plea. She notably has
a slight hypocrisy streak.
She has known to despise
puns will quite frequently make them
a slight
hypocrisy streak.
I'm gonna fucking kill whoever wrote this.
I'm gonna fucking murder them.
I hate...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
She is, she...
She also
tries to stay as fair as possible
in all things and is not above
listening to criticism. She also is
well aware of how attractive slash
cute she is and will occasionally use
this to her advantage. What the fuck?
What is this?
God, what is this
based on? What is it? It's fucking
it's, it's
fucking turtles all the way down.
It's all the way down. Only the turtle
in this metaphor, the turtle is
like some made up bullshit that doesn't even exist.
Mm-hmm.
That's...
Is this relevant?
Is this relevant to anyone?
Ben, we're looking through world
through our rear view.
Was this ever relevant?
I've, I've...
I have no clue.
I want, I want analysis
anarchy to be like a lecturer.
Oh my god, I know what I have to do.
A lecture on analysis anarchy?
Yes, we fucking...
Dude, I've got, I've got, I'm so
I'm so fucking sad.
I'm so fucking sad that I didn't do a second lecture
at Radcon 2. I should have just
on Tails Get Strolled. I should have just
fucking bit the bullet and done Tails Get Strolled.
It would have been great. Everyone would have loved me.
We just need more lectures.
We just, and chief among them needs to be
TF2 analysis anarchy.
Yeah, we need...
I'm very fucking invested in the narrative
of that.
Of analysis anarchy?
Yeah.
Are you gonna...
Are you gonna watch them? Are you gonna watch
all 30 episodes?
I've watched like half of them
before just like, just thinking like
oh my, my, I'm going to
I'm going to lose function of my body.
My body, my soul
I'm going to be able to control my body anymore.
Okay, I want you, I want you to...
Wait, wait, wait, first I want you to appreciate,
I want you to appreciate, ironically
despite her character's very forward
and aggressive demeanor,
Eliora is fairly shy and withdrawn
in real life. Ironically.
Ironically.
Oh my god.
Yeah, that's irony for you.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
Imagine.
I'm, I'm, I'm...
This is long after the pony days.
I'm thinking about TF2
and I think, oh man,
I wonder if there's any like, TF2 analysis
I could watch, you know?
I really, really get in the meat and bones of this game.
Yeah, I miss, I miss, you know,
I'm so behind on the ponies.
I need pony, I need the, the,
I need to be brought up to speed on the ponies
by watching just hours and hours
of analysis.
I need to watch 45 minute analyses
of 20 minute episodes.
Yeah, I just want, I just want
to watch some, some analysis of, of, of TF2.
So let me type in to, to, to YouTube.
TF2 analysis, to, to get some reviews
or urges, just, you know, whatever
analysis of the video game, TF2.
Oh my god.
And then the first thing comes up.
Thumbnail, phantom horn.
No.
As a soldier.
My...
No.
Analysis anarchy, TF2.
I click on it and I have no idea
what the fuck is going on.
Ugh.
Jesus Christ.
I'm so sad.
I'm so fucking sad
that my name is fucking attached to it.
I fucking, I fucking,
when that video came out
and I saw what I had done,
I fucking lost my shit.
It was like, it might be
like the worst I've ever felt about anything
in my entire life.
Jesus Christ.
It's just like, yeah.
When I saw, when I saw the product
that I had fucking hitched my wagon to,
I was like,
oh god, I've made a terrible mistake.
I've made a terrible mistake
and I hate myself.
But hey,
that's the way the cookie comes.
The, the entire like,
that like, just the idea
of that series is fucking
insane.
Like, it's most incoherent
fucking...
It's...
Okay, okay, okay.
It's like, it's like someone just,
it's like some, some idiot,
stupid people were talking
and like,
two of them said,
one of them said like two things
next to each other
and like,
someone else
laughed about it.
And then they all unanimously decided like,
that is a great idea.
We should fucking
get right on it.
And then they just did.
And then they were like,
this retarded idea that we had,
this retarded thing that someone said,
let's fucking just,
let's fucking make it happen
as necessary.
Let's fucking pool our fucking shitty
Patreon money
and pay some fucking
hack
to make it.
And then,
even though it sucks,
let's keep making it.
Because,
I don't know,
what else are we gonna do?
Oh god.
It's, it's, it's,
okay, it's like,
it's like a fan fiction
of these, these avatars,
these pony sonas.
Oh yeah, that's right.
These pony sonas.
It's crossover fan fiction
of O.C.'s,
of a whole other fucking franchise.
Yeah.
Inside
of a,
a modified version
of the Team Fortress 2
map coal town,
for some reason,
these ponies have formed a
Team Fortress 2 team,
MVM,
Team Fortress 2 team.
And during the fight with robots,
they, they, they engage
in, in relationship scuffles.
One of which.
Scuffles!
One, the, the, the main focus of,
and, and, and one, one includes
the, the relationship of Joss Scorcher
and Ink Rose,
uh, Ink Rose being 16,
and J, I, I believe at least,
and, and Joss Scorcher being like
28, right?
I think he was like 22.
Okay.
It's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's better.
Yeah.
You know, in hindsight,
I got really mad about like the age
thing in hindsight.
I wish I hadn't cause like who gives
a shit.
I was, I was really just mad that I,
they had made this terrible video and
I hated it.
That's, that was my real problem.
Um, yeah.
Um, if I, if I,
put me in a room,
put me in a room
with a gun
and just one bullet,
and then put in front of me
Dr. Wolf,
Joss Scorcher,
and Digi Bro.
And, and, and, and it'll be the most
difficult decision of my life,
the most difficult decision I've ever
had to make.
Um,
but someone's going to die.
Do, do you like
that Digi has
barely anything on his
fucking profile?
Like, like, barely anything.
Oh, on the, on the wiki?
Yeah.
What?
Look.
Even though he fucking,
he fucking made
like a backstory and shit.
Like he has, like he has,
he has his info out there,
his fucking character.
His character had a backstory.
Will no one create
MOP analysis videos.
Uh, uh, upload schedule none.
Oh my god, that's fanart by the
Burning Donut.
I fucking hate the Burning Donut.
I hate that guy.
Why do you hate the Burning Donut?
Who's that?
He's this piece of absolute ass.
Oh my god,
the fucking Burning Donut.
See, Monchi,
let, let me, let me go,
let me take this opportunity to go on a
bizarre and pointless tangent about
my feelings for a minute.
Oh my fucking god.
Yeah, alright.
See, see,
yeah.
Yeah.
I mean,
there's a lot, there's a lot going on here.
Um, the,
see, alright.
I couldn't, I couldn't draw that well for a
long time.
I could like sort of draw a little bit,
like my whole life.
Um,
but I'm a,
not to toot my own horn,
but I'm a real smart guy.
I'm the smartest guy in the fucking universe.
I'm literally the smartest person who ever lived.
Yeah, sure, of course.
And that's, that's true.
That's God's honest truth.
And um,
uh,
and I fucking,
and I learned and I learned how to draw
and I think I did it
because I'm really smart.
Like I think that the fact that I'm fucking smart
had something to do with my ability
to fucking become capable
of producing
grave and images in defiance
of, in defiance of God's law.
Um, anyway,
so all that, that being said,
when I meet someone who can kind of draw,
but who's like
fucking stupid, it like baffles me.
Like, I can't understand
how someone can be stupid
and also like,
can be like a,
like a competent artist.
And the Burning Donut is, is one of these people,
like he's so dumb,
like he's fucking incoherent.
He's, he's, he's like,
I've talked to him once or twice and he just has no fucking clue
what he's doing at any given time.
And yet, and yet he produces
on a somewhat regular schedule
some pretty, some pretty okay,
some more or less competent
fucking sexy
Anthropony pinups.
I mean, I mean,
look at this picture of Trixie right here.
Okay, like the anatomy
is competent, the figure is fine,
um, the lighting is inept,
the lighting is inept because she should be
illuminated by her sparkles and yet she's
weirdly in shadow, so like it kind of
sucks, but like whatever.
Um, I don't know, and he's just
anyway, anyway, I've talked to this guy,
this, this guy contacted me one time
and he asked me like
Ben, how do I
fucking make my Patreon
succeed? And I was like
well, let me have a look at your Patreon
and I looked at it and it was like
this wall of text
with no, there was, it was like
it was like a, it was like no punctuation,
it was like misspelled, it was like a piece of shit,
it had, it was just sort of this fucking ramble.
It was just this pointless ramble
about how bad, about how much he wants
to make art. And I was like
listen guy, listen guy,
what you need to do, like this is
aimless, like you need to like offer awards,
you know, you need to like,
you need to like say in your Patreon
like what you're actually doing, because his
Patreon was like, pledge to my Patreon
and if I make,
if I hit like $500 a month,
then maybe
I'll start drawing a comic.
And I was like
listen you, you stupid bastard,
like you gotta just start doing it
and be like, here I'm doing this
comic, if you like it
and wanna support it, pledge to my Patreon.
You can't be like, if I make money
then I'll start doing a thing
because nobody is gonna want
to support you. And he just
fucking, like I told him all that
and I gave him my advice and he was like thanks
and then he went and like didn't listen to any of it.
He like, he cleaned up the
text on his Patreon but he didn't like
he didn't like actually fix any of the problems.
His fucking
his fucking reward, like his highest reward
tier is like $50 a month or something
and if you pledge $50 a month it's like
you will literally become a part
of the creative process of making my
comic. So it's basically like
you'll write my comic for me.
Like, is what it is.
Anyway, I don't know.
Sorry, that was a big, that was a big pointless
aggression but I just think the burning donut
he just pisses me off especially
and he just represents a lot of what I think
is the worst fucking instincts
and a lot of lazy, shiftless artists out
there. And the worst fucking
part is that he makes like $50 a month
on Patreon. I don't fucking know why.
I guess it's because he makes fucking pony
pinups for fucking KFC's
sex sluts to jack their little
fucking KFC. Their little dicks too.
Listening to
suicidal tendencies
reading
watching Kill La Kill
playing no systems
eating whatever
I can afford on food stamps
drinking NOS
I don't even know what NOS is. Is it a beverage?
Oh, okay.
The idea of listening to
suicidal tendencies
and watching Kill La Kill
and eating whatever I can afford
on food stamps
I really think
this guy
is the next step of human evolution
evolution.
This is what I want us all to become.
He obviously
fares well in all sorts of situations.
is able to
climb through the ranks.
He is fucking
poor
and I feel that
this is what he deserves.
Excellent. Very...
for 12 years.
I just, I just, man
and this is
Digi Brony's legacy.
Digi Brony's legacy is a
fucking piece of fan art by the burning
doughnut. It's a holy
chain.
Oh my god.
He is a ship with Tommy Oliver.
He's one of the first and most popular
shipments in the Brony analysis community.
Really it's not because nobody fucking
wrote in any of his information.
Wait, does Tommy Oliver have a page?
Yeah, yeah. I just wanted to find one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay,
okay, okay, okay.
Oh god. Oh yeah!
Look at that.
He's ship with Digi Bros.
when the first one was pop-thrush.
Oh yes.
Tommy is openly bisect...
Wait, does Vita have a fucking
page?
Wait, wait.
Who's Vita breakfast?
Oh my god!
Why?
Oh
This is why.
This is why people like Vita exist
because fucking idiots,
fucking idiots will catalog all their
fucking misanthropic
sociopathy here.
This is why scumbags like Vita
and Cream Man fucking do their shit
and love it.
Oh my fucking god.
Oh Christ, this is a fucking trap seat.
Can we fucking go in?
This page is a mix of jokes and
facts.
How can we fucking nuke?
Can we fucking nuke the Rift Cafe?
No, I'm fucking going to the Rift Cafe
right fucking now and I'm deleting
Vita's page and I'm probably gonna delete
like it does in other pages.
Why fucking nuke? It's a public wiki.
I can do anything I want.
Just gonna roll it back.
No one will notice.
Nobody gives a shit.
I'm like...
What?
One of the most
likable veterans of the Rift
is how it begins.
Edit.
Classic editor.
Let's see.
Ben, you're a monster.
Oh my god.
Look at this astounding
301 subscribers.
Wait, where?
Where does it say that?
On the fucking Rift Cafe.
That's 301.
Astounding.
Why N1?
Why not just whatever?
How do I delete it?
Shouldn't there just be a fucking delete button?
I don't know.
Hey, hey, hey.
Fucking bitch.
Listen to me.
I need your help.
I need your help to erase Vita's legacy.
They have his Skype.
His Skype? Oh, all I want to do is just
contact him.
Ugh.
Let's go to this YouTube, shall we?
Yes.
He's still using the avatar I made him.
Where? Let me see, let me see.
On his YouTube.
I can't believe this.
Oh, he's all the way up to
399 subscribers.
Oh my god.
In like the two years since then.
He's posted, he posted one week ago.
He's, oh wait, wait, wait.
Okay, but he didn't post for seven months
before that.
What's he doing?
The fuck is he doing? I don't know what these videos are.
Oh, he's got a little fucking
video of him with a keyframe.
Keyframe and puzzle. Oh, keyframe.
Fucking keyframe.
Let's fucking talk about keyframe.
Just some fucking girl.
Just some useless girl
who comes in with nothing.
Some KFC sex life.
Some KFC sex life. She comes in
with like one drawing
of an OC. She comes in
she's there for like a week
she makes like one video
and then on with the waterworks
on with the fucking oh no
suddenly I'm really poor and I'm getting
and my family is abusing me
and oh no my life is
ruined. Oh, somebody help me
and then they do and then
a dozen people pledge to her patreon
get her like I don't know like a hundred bucks a month
or something and probably they fucking
give her money to like I don't know
she's got a bunch of money and now she's
been for a while, for a while
their fucking keyframe was making
more than on patreon than me and it
fucking ate at me. It like ate at my
heart. It ate at my fucking heart
because she's useless.
There's not one
on fucking theory brownie for some
reason which I find pretty
that is odd. That is
that is very odd.
theory brownie is like the poster child
of being real. I don't
he's the realest guy. Why
is there not a fucking delete
page button?
whatever
whatever I'll just um
alright
erase crystal pony very
how do I get away from this page
I don't want to be here anymore
I've lost all
people
video is
or vita is like
Loki. He's such a god
of chaos, Ben.
He really fucking
disrupts the system. Who
vita? He's so fucking
he's
just so stevious, Ben.
he just causes so
much harm
yeah he just um
like he's so
he's just such a classic
memester
like he's just so
he's just such a capable troll
good at what he does
like he really knows
to get under people's skin and he really knows
how to
bug him and really knows
how to make sure that he
is an instantly banned whenever he comes
into the pcp fan chat
he always does
he always tries to make alt account and he's always
thwarted immediately
like he really knows how to ride
that line between
like a trickster god
and just like a biting
social satirist
you know
like he comes in there
with a point to be made
and he makes it
and before he leaves he fucking makes it
damn
just
just damn
damn
i live composable a lot
thanks kp
how
man
thank you kp
what the fuck is all this shit of her with
antony c
kp and antony c were like a big ol
shit
why
that was like a big thing
that was a big thing
guys in the comments
if you have ever
unironically
held a ship
of any sort
please email me your address
and a drone will be sent
on its way
to what end
oh you'll see once you give me
your address
shipping is
like the worst thing
a human could do
god i can't
i wanna fucking delete it
i wanna fucking
delete
can't you just like control a
yeah i can make it blank
but i don't just wanna make it blank
i wanna erase it
i wanna make the link not exist anymore
you could like change the link
or anything that would link to it
would not link to the right page
yeah
i don't uh
i don't see any
i don't see any option to change the name
oh my god
her ship with antony c
i love antony c a lot
it was one of those popular shipments in the brony analysis community
she's often portrayed with two children
from the shipping banner
nellie they're her eldest daughter
and chargeterius
nellie's younger
children
well
okay i've fucking done the most
amateur wiki hack job of all time
i just went in and blanked out the page
and i know someone will revert it
and i don't care whatever
fucking point made
point made
dammit
excellent
hey artwork by mage
uh yeah a bunch of it
a fucking bunch of it
actually oh it's her
no
thank you kp
yeah i really regret that
video or at least that part of it
actually everything else about that video is great
and a work of genius
but everything about it that acknowledges
the existence of kp is a blight
on humanity and on my
career
what okay
this is so fucking sad
it's so fucking sad that anyone gives a shit
about this and that i used to
you know me
i love branding
and i can say with complete certainty
that i love kimpossible
art is the best branding
job i've ever fucking
seen
agreed no agreed
i get a feel for what is going to transpire
when you click on a video
with using him i love kimpossible
almost as much as you get with
Winnie the Poop 2
or Tune Critic Y2K
unbelievable
it is unbelievable
it's unbelievable and it's a fucking sin
um
i oh
still making videos she's gotta be
she's gotta still be just churning them out
she's gotta be
she's gotta be continuing
that vicious cycle of
fucking write like a page
of complete nonsense
um fucking
lispily babble it into a microphone
uh send it off to
whatever fucking asshole
you want because you've got like 14 people
that will just begging you to work for free
for no credit
um and then just like
wait for them to fucking just
send you back some shitty fucking
spaz
spazfest
of a fucking
garbage
fucking flip out the images flying everywhere
words
big white text
big white text fest
and then
i don't know post it and make no money on it
for a piece of shit
then how is it
there's nothing i hate more
literally possible to still
give a single shit
about my little pony
i don't know
i don't fucking know
i see she's still getting
i see she's still getting in like the
the 10 to 20 thousand views
range
uh mlp animation
what if kp was discord
again
i see i see we were fucking
i see we've got a fertile
a fertile uh
mind a fertile field of
creativity going on here
oh god can we watch the fucking
build creative potential can we
watch the fucking kim possible a lot
channel trailer no not the animation
obviously the channel trailer yeah yeah
yeah yeah all right
oh god
all right all right where is okay
all right
this is like a Nate video
um
ugh
like
it's like it's like they just use as many
of her faces as possible
like without
thinking about why you know what i'm
saying like her face will just
be the most extreme face even when it
doesn't fit uh
oh it's so inept this is like
this is just a fucking this is just
best game ever undertale
yeah yeah i feel i feel
you bro um
you get what i mean when i say that i
what in that it's just like
too fucking busy
yeah it's just too busy and it's just
fucking shitty it's just awful yeah
the um
i mean
i mean it wasn't this bad
but uh
ugh
the the the the what was it what was it gonna say
okay the thing the thing about kp
the kp channel the kp channel
is so it's so
so thoroughly suffused
with ineptitude
in in every in every
like step of its creation
and reception
like like
like the ineptitude like
it's like it's like it's ineptly
ineptly conceived
ineptly planned
inept ineptly executed
ineptly delivered
and and ineptly
consumed. Like even, even the viewers, like even the viewing experience is just, it just
couldn't happen. It couldn't be the way it is if it wasn't, just the viewers just have
to be retarded. Like they just have to be retarded. Like everyone, I'm sorry. No I'm
not sorry. Fuck me I'm not sorry. Everyone who watches Kim Possible, or has ever watched
a Kim Possible a lot, has to be retarded. There's no other explanation. You wouldn't,
you wouldn't do it. You wouldn't do it if you weren't retarded. You just wouldn't do
it.
Look, look, look, look recent wiki activity from, from a fandom user on Fee, what, what,
oh my god.
Wait.
It's god.
Wait, I'm gonna, you know what I have to do, you know what I have to do? I have to go
in and make like a couple minor changes just to like get that change off of like the most
recent changes list.
Oh my god.
Like, yeah.
Like that's what I, that's what I have to do.
Let's, let's, let's look at some of these guys. They're, they're up and coming. Who's
wooden sword?
Up and, uh, some up and comers, some fucking up and comers in the pony analysis community.
Age 15.
Oh.
Oh, look at, look at that fucking, look at that fucking, uh, avatar. Um, that is a striking,
that is a striking character design.
It's bold.
Yeah.
Memorable. It's gonna stick with me till the day I fucking die, which is today, said
Ben, cocking his gun.
He was devastated when he heard Club Penguin was shut down. It still haunts him to this
day.
It was shut down like a month ago.
It still haunts him to this day, even though it was like, like two weeks ago.
To date, he is the only person in the 2010s to care about Club Penguin. That's not fucking
true, dude.
What about Gibbo?
I, I, I, if, okay, I want to see if he's like, I'm sorry, go back for one second. Go back
for 77 subscribers, 77 subscribers. Um, what, okay, how's this for fucking characterization?
Wooden sword often complains that because he is in Australia, he's always late to Skype
conversations and podcasts since by the time he arrives, everyone is getting ready for
bed.
Everyone is getting ready for bed. Deep, deep lore, deep characterization, important shit.
Shoot me.
Um, okay, okay. I, I, okay, I'm assuming he's gonna have a video about the end of Club
Penguin. And if it has more than Hippo's video, I'm, no, he's got 77, he's got 77 subscribers.
This is not, this is not a true up and comer.
Okay.
15.
What?
15, lol.
God, what, what kind of fucking retards we associate with a 15 year old?
Hard to imagine. Hard to imagine, really.
Ooh, you have to be retarded.
Uh, wait, uh, I love Kim Possible a lot. Trivia. For her 3,000 subscriber special in which it's
traditional to sing winter wrap up, KP saying traditional or wait, wait, it's, it's traditional
to sing winter wrap up or some other MLP related song, KP saying discord instead of winter
wrap up. Okay. I have many questions. One, since when was it traditional to do anything
for 3,000 subscribers? Since when was it traditional to sing winter wrap up? And what
is the point of saying traditional to sing winter wrap up or some other MLP related song?
Why not just say it's traditional to sing an MLP related song? Even though it isn't
and there are no traditions and this is all just a bunch of made up bullshit. It's all
just a bunch of bullshit from the top down.
Okay. Okay. Okay. We have so many.
Wait, wait, wait. His talents include editing, humor, analysis kind of, and annoying other
ponies intentional or otherwise. He takes inspiration.
He takes inspiration from Cat Icarus, Pina Fina Gala, Zondron, and Space Hamster, etc.
That's, imagine, imagine boldly stating you take inspiration from Cat Icarus and Pina
Butter Gamer, the most, the most original, the most bold, the most, the boldest faces
on the internet today.
Oh, you know, you know, you, you, you, you, you. Okay. Oh, my God. You know how it's canon.
It's canon that there exists the ICPCP that is a juggalo, a juggalo, a alter ego of everyone
in the PCP. You know, you know, that's a thing, right?
I mean, I know about the Japanese juggalo. That's about. The Japanese juggalo is Digi's
ICPCP counterpart. I honestly, I have not heard of the ICPCP.
Okay. The ICPCP is real. Okay. And if this guy liked clowns, he would be my, he would
be my ICPCP.
Really? Yeah. Yeah. Cause he's, he's everything. He's like, cause he's just a baby. He's just
like me if I was shitty. He's just a baby boy, just like you.
He's just a baby. Look at all his friends. Oh, Pet O Pat Rex 11, Mr. Left Turn, Martyr
Boy, uh, uh, Onyx the Dragon, Game Link Reviews, Doodled Pony and Freedom Flash, you know,
all the greats. Although a bunch of nonsense, he often jokes about being horse famous in
his videos. Wow. What a, what a concept. What a fucking original, uh, you know, I don't
even have a problem. I don't have a problem with this guy cause he's a kid. Like I'm not
blaming him. I'm not blaming him for being terrible and being useless and for him being
worthless and for his content being shit. I'm not blaming him for any of that. I'm blaming
whoever wrote this wiki article for feeling that this was a worthwhile thing to catalog.
You know what? No. You know what? It's probably him. He probably just wrote it about himself.
Yeah. I was just about to say, I guarantee you that he wrote this myself.
Okay. So it's fine. In that case, it's fine. You know what? That's, that's why Pete, that's
why like me and Digi don't have any fucking thing on our fucking wiki page. Just cause
we didn't give enough of a shit to go in and write our own fucking articles. Yeah. That's,
that's the solution. That's, that's the justice. People in the PCP fan chat, please fucking make
the wiki, please work. Yeah. Please. Like mine's fine. Mine's okay. I mean, it could
be better. Mine's literally just, lol. Ugh. Now mine's, mine's, mine's alright. I think
I did okay, but like, yeah, mages is like a sentence long. Yeah. Why isn't fucking phantom
horn in the transgender pain? His gender is, his gender is unicorn, dude. He's a, his gender
is trans unicorn. Oh, I'm weak. Oh, I'm weak with rage. Okay. Okay. Undefined gender. Okay.
What the fuck? What do you mean, undefined gender? He's a fucking girl. Whatever. Whatever,
man. Okay. Okay. There's literally nothing in non-fucking. Even though fucking the other
ones are both, ugh. I like how that one's just human. Oh, it's maluminous. That's. Who?
Yeah. That, that fucker. Who? Who? Wait, wait, I, it was, she, I talked to what's his name.
It's also, it's a, it's a guy. It's a trans girl. It's a male. So that's, so that's,
so that's, so that's bullshit. It's a girl. That's bullshit. Well, I guess, I guess it
is under literally female. Yeah, they're, yeah, yeah, yeah. Ahhhh! Look at the, look,
look at this face. Hmm. Yes. The brony gallery. He takes, he takes an in-depth look at a particular
artist on DeviantArt. Currently, she's only done two episodes of the series, but plans
to work. Good. Yeah. Your Patreon dollars at work, everybody. I don't know why I'm so
mad. I don't know why I'm so mad. This person makes like a hundred dollars. This person
makes like, this person makes like a hundred dollars on Patreon, which is not that much
in the grand scheme of things, but there's so many better people. There's like talent,
there's like talented fucking people out there that make like thirty dollars a month on Patreon.
And, oh god, I just want to throw up just thinking about the fucking iniquity of this
world. Keyframe is also a talented artist. Shut your fucking mouth. I want to die. Look, look. I want to
look at. God, just remembering, remembering when I made less on Patreon than Keyframe.
Those were dark days. Those were dark fucking days. Look, look, look, look, look. Jesus. Look at
this. Look. Yeah. I mean, I don't know. It's fine. I mean, I've seen, after all the horrors I've
seen today, this is fine. This is okay. The iPod. Oh, oh wait. I just, oh yeah, I just realized
it's an iPod. iPod. That's good. That's good shit. That's good shit. Don't they have fucking,
don't they have fucking Samsung's in Ponyville? That's my question for you, my friend. Oh,
he's my age. Oh no, he's slightly younger than me, but he's, this is, I'm sure this is out of date,
so he's probably my age. Yeah, probably. He's, hmm. What a fucking hack. Who's, who's, who's,
who's, who's another guy? Digi. We, we've already seen this. He's the only one I know. Yeah,
let's answer what made, let's see what's going on with me. Oh fuck Mad Munchkin. Oh, okay. You're
at Lethal Rormage. Nothing. Wow. Okay, well, there's a couple of things here. Yeah, Lethal
Halloween, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da. Why,
why is all of the people for the, for the horseshoe crew literally like they just don't have any?
Um, is there a reason for that? Um, well, what about, what about Jesse? Oh, go to fucking Jesse.
Oh my. I'll bet he's gonna have nothing to, I'll bet he's just gonna. Oh my god. Yeah, he's, yeah,
it's gonna be bad. It's gonna be real bad. I, prepare to get mad. I'm mad already. One, two, three.
Oh, my. Yeah. Oh, it's my. Oh, hell yeah, bro. Oh, I'm hit with a tidal wave. A tidal wave of
what? Nostalgia? Like, man, holy shit. This is shit, bro. Fucking sick, fucking sick, bro. Okay,
first of all, the fact that it, like, for some reason has this, which I, like, I, like, like,
like, this was the first piece of fan art, I think he got, pretty sure, please. Yeah. Was it, was it
really? It was made, like, 45 minutes after the first episode of, of, of his fucking thing came out.
Uh, impressive. So it must be. Yeah. Possibly. You know, I fucking, I sent him another image that
he used, like, the basis of, of, of, of, like, one of his videos. It was, it was some, like,
thing where he and Digi are the fucking retarded, like, Muppets old people thing, right? Yeah,
yeah. Oh, yeah, yeah. And that, I remember that. That mother fucker didn't even mention me in the
description. Who? Wait, Jesse or Digi? Jesse. Yeah, Jesse. Can't. Well, fuck him. I'll never
forgive him. I'll never forgive him. I wouldn't. A bunch of bullshit. Who's gay as hell? That's
frankly, frankly, that's gay as hell. It was the only word for it. Um, fucking credit your, credit
your artists, credit your artists people. Um, Jesus. Jesus Christ. Mad, mad munchkin. I hate mad
munchkin. I hate mad munchkin. A fellow munchy. Don't ever touch her hat. She said don't ever touch
her ass. Her hat. Don't. Oh, is that, is that her character that she gets mad if you touch her
hat? Quirky. Just kill me, munchy. Just fucking kill me. One time she encountered Mary Sue, a
parody of the Mary Sue is generally found in the MLP fandom. Oh boy. What a fucking load of bullshit.
Hey, you know what? These people are so fucking old. What? This is another, this is another person who,
this is another person who like, like keyframe because she had like a sad tear jerky like, oh,
I feel so bad for myself. Fucking a moment with Dr. Wolfe. I'm pretty sure this person got like,
I don't know, some fucking money out of it too or something. Maybe not a Patreon or something.
Oh, yeah, Indiegogo. Let's fucking see. Let's fucking see because fucking Dr. Wolfe,
fucking Dr. Wolfe plugged her or something. She got $5,000, wants to raise money for local
charities and expand the business. What a bunch of bullshit. What a bunch of fucking bullshit.
Imagine, hold on. Imagine, okay, imagine this actually being successful. The phrase
wants to raise money for local charities and expand the business. What does that even mean?
What does that even mean? What business? What business? Local charity. Fundraiser to support
business and local charities. Raise money to put back into my local community. Oh my god.
Expanding the business itself. Okay, so what this means is that this is money that's going to her
that she can buy things with. Local things. What, like, what charities and support? I have the
means, I have the means. You know what this is? You know what this is? Oh my god. I'll tell you
exactly what this is. This is just, like, I buy things and I give to charity. So just fucking
give me money and eventually it will go into my local economy and the charities that I support
already. Can you imagine a more blatant, like, just give me money? I actually think this is more
disgusting because this is basically like mask, this is like masquerading as a charity, but really
it's just give me money to spend how I see fit. And then because fucking Dr. Wolf plugged her,
she made $5,000. How fucking Jesus Christ. What kind of person do you have to be?
Thanks for reading. Stay creative. Oh, each shit. Oh, each shit. You know what? Her art
fucking sucks and I hate it. It's a terrible style. It's ugly. It's stupid. She's worthless.
I haven't seen. Fucking look at it. It looks like garbage. I hate it. It's not good. It's not good.
It's not even close to good. It's far from good. It's weak. You're gonna kick off. It's weak and
she's wearing, you know what, you know what that is? You know what that is in her stupid head?
It's the webcomic artist hat. It's the hat that all webcomic artists are legally obligated to wear.
You're not fucking wrong. You know what the worst part about it is is that's a big hat too.
It's not a tiny hat. She's disrespecting the munchie name.
Disgusting. Who fucking, the guy who makes Dresden Kodak wears that hat. The girl awkward zombie
wears that hat. Brony Curious wears that hat. Brony Curious wears a much worse hat.
Yeah. I don't know. There's a bunch more that wear that same stupid hat.
Look at this. It's just like shorthand for I draw a webcomic.
Look at this. That's fucking creativity at work, Boyo.
This is literally just Rainbow Dash. This is Rainbow Dash with a shirt on and you change the color
and you tried to fucking screw with like the line work a little bit on the bottom but you
fucked up and it looks like garbage. This is, oh my god. She's a fan of Doctor Who,
Gravity Falls, anime and other anime shows. It's just Phineas and a Fur, Dexter's Laboratory and the
Powerpuff Girls. You know what, I'm thinking that maybe we need to fucking split this into two
rowdy fuckers copkilling. I'm thinking we've spent, we've spent like as much time jerking our dicks
off about how much we hate the bro analysis community as we have been playing Frog Fractions.
Okay, okay, Ben. You have to like make no fucking illusions to like, that's what this is going to
turn into. It just turns into us fucking going down memory lane. Did you say, oh yeah, we have a lot
to say about Frog Fractions. A lot to say about Frog Fractions. We have many video game opinions.
Also, Enoch144 on Steam, Buy Me Grow Up, Buy Me Glittermitten Grove, Buy Me Grow Up, Buy Me Glittermitten
Grove please. Glittermitten, fucking Mad Munchkin, fucking Mad Munchkin can make $5,000 on Indiegogo
for literally nothing. I'm sure someone, I'm sure some generous person will buy me Grow Up and or
Glittermitten Grove please. Thank you. I love you. Does this person still watch the show? Who?
Dear Cotton Candy. Dear Cotton Candy? Did she ever, did she ever watch Rowdy Fuckers Cop Killers?
Oh, well, I just, oh yeah, I guess you're right. I guess like the thumbnail of Rowdy Fuckers Cop Killers
like is a natural deterrent. Yeah, well, against the weak-minded. Yeah. Yeah. In other words, females.
In other words, females. This is, this is, it's a girl repellent and I mean that in the best possible
way. Oh God. Oh my God. That bright acid green just like, they're like, oh, it's like, it's like a
citronella candle and they're like the mosquito. It's like way too potent for their fucking, their,
their, their weak and their, their weak and bland heart to handle. Yeah. Yeah. Um, what were you
saying about CC? Oh, nothing. I'll never say it. Okay, good. Kimmy Sparkle, the only fucking,
the only good one. Oh, wait, wait, was, oh, were you on CC's page? Is that what it was? I wasn't
looking. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Okay. Um, yeah, I love Kimmy Sparkle. I love Kimmy Sparkle so much.
Kimmy Sparkle is actually the best thing that ever happened in MLP. Like, fucking,
it's so good. It's so fucking good. Somebody, Munchy. Yeah. Kimmy Sparkle is like the, it's
like the best idea. It's like the most, it's like such an obvious idea. Like when I saw Kimmy Sparkle,
I was like, somebody had to do this and I'm so glad they did. Yeah. How was she the only one?
Uh, I think, I think we, I thought, I think it was just too cool that everyone embroiled in it.
It was just too cool. Like no one wanted to, to even think about the fact that, that it wasn't
incredibly great. Like it was, it was just the best, the best thing. The thing, the thing about,
are you talking about brony analysis? Are you talking about Kimmy? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's
a brony analysis. See, here's what fucking kills me. Is that like, what fuck, what kills me
about Kimmy Sparkle is that at some point in there, Kimmy Sparkle was like collabing with people.
Like, uh, not Eliora, um, like Persian Poetus, right? Like she had like a crossover video with
Persian Poetus and a couple other people. But the thing is that like all the other, all the people
that they, she crossed over with, like, like treated it seriously. Like, like they made like
serious, like they treated Kimmy Sparkle as though she was like an actual person and like an actual
personality and not a fucking parody of them. Yeah. Like, I don't know, man. I just, it was
so good. How was there not more? How was that? I just, I wish there had been, I wish there had
been more Kimmy Sparkles, but like on the other hand, I guess that like the fact that there was
only one just speaks, just speaks to how much we fucking needed her. And then she made like four
videos and then fell off the map and that was sad. But like, she was just too good. She was the hero
we needed, but not the one we deserved. We definitely did not deserve her. We definitely did not deserve
Kimmy and she was not appreciated enough. And I guess that's why she left. She was too good for
us. Kimmy Sparkle is the special quote unquote self-proclaimed only Pegasus reviewer. However,
this is false because there are many more, including keyframe. I love Composibla and Eliora.
Ah, the three big, the three, the three Titans. Her creator is none other than Shirt Club Palms.
Kill me. Just fucking kill me. Who, who's this? Oh my God, this one, this fucking one, this fucking
one kills me. Okay, let me fucking tell you, I know, I don't even need to read. She's 30 years old,
by the way. I don't need to read. I don't need to read anything about this person. Here's all I have
to say about Lightning Bliss. Lightning Bliss had a moment with Dr. Wolfe and the issue,
the issue that Lightning Bliss was grappling with, that she needed the doctor's help with, was
the problem of having people, the problem of people judging her for having an alicorn OC.
Holy shit. Yeah, fucking unpack that for a minute. Unpack, unpack the astounding,
the astounding absence of self-awareness that would have to, that would have to have occurred,
that would have to exist, the chain, just the unbroken, the unbroken chain of failure to recognize,
to fucking step outside yourself for one fucking second and understand your place in the world
and what you truly are, that would lead up to that occurring, that would lead up to a video of a
moment with Dr. Wolfe, fucking people are bullied, people judge me for having an alicorn OC, but
I'm not going to take it anymore. Fuck. Dr. Wolfe has to help her through it. Yeah, she had, this is
an issue that she fucking grapples with and she, she can't, oh my Christ. There's just nothing,
there's just nothing she can do, there's just nothing, there's nothing, there's, she's being,
she's just the victim of an unwarranted cyber bullying. Yeah, people don't understand,
the problem is that people don't understand the creative vision behind her OC. If they did,
they would see that they are, they are the fool, that they themselves are the fool for, for what
they do to her, but no, they're too blind, they're too blind and too fucking judgmental, Munchy,
they're too judgmental, they can't, they can't see that in this, clearly in this fucking case of all
cases, it's warranted. In this case, it's special and deserved. Like this alicorn, this, this alicorn
that we're looking at right now is not, it's like, no, but look at that fucking avatar,
fucking look at it for a second Munchy, fucking, fucking look at it, look at it Munchy, thank you,
thank you, okay, all like this, this is not your typical run of the mill Mary Sue alicorn
that we're looking at here, this is not that, this, this is unique, this is special, this,
this brings a whole new fucking dimension to the, to the quote unquote Mary Sue. This is,
this is a character with depth and dimensionality behind it, okay, this is other alicorns, yeah,
like other alicorns give the practice of making alicorn or sees a bad name by being like, by
being like too cool and being like too special and being yeah, I'll admit it, I'll, I'll say it,
Mary Sue's right, like those al, like those alicorns give, give this person a bad name,
this person has to grapple with the unearned negative reputation that others have fucking,
the stigma that others have imbued alicorn OCs with. I, I have no, there's no end, Munchy,
there is no fucking end to the spite and the bile and the vitriol that I feel for this person.
There's no light at the end of the tunnel. What? There's no light at the end of the tunnel,
it's all, it's all agony, there's no fucking hope. There's no, there's,
I'm looking into, I'm looking into the eyes, I'm, yeah, there's no light, there's no light,
there's no light at the end of the tunnel that is the eyes that let the, that are the window
to the soul of the person that has created fucking, what is their name, fucking rainbow bliss?
Something fucking retarded. Rainbow wishes? There's just nothing.
Canker sores. There's, there's just nothing. I mean this whole, oh. What? What, what the fuck are
these? I don't know, I don't know what's happening, I don't know what's happening with their feet.
God, I didn't even notice. Are they gems? Are they like metal plates? They're toenails.
Oh, oh, ew, oh, I hope not. Oh, I hope that's not what that is. I fucking hope that's not what that
is, dude. No. Because if that's what that is, we're gonna have a fucking problem.
Look at her like, look at her like too cool for school fucking rat tail. Her like fucking
elephant rat tail. What do you mean, she needs to bring, she needs to breathe some life into the
Alicorn OC and she needs to breathe some life with her original fucking- I guess, dude, I guess
it's original, but don't fucking tell me that it's not some bullshit. Look at that bold stance.
She has something to fucking say, and she's not gonna, she's not gonna be beheldant to your
pre-existing notions that Alicorn overseas aren't cool. Look at how that tail fucking clips through
the ground that her hooves are on. Look at how the tail goes below, goes below where her fucking
hooves meet the ground. How the fuck does that work? Okay, look at her goggles. Do you like how
the goggles are at one side of the face because that horn should realistically be in between,
like above the far side goggle and beneath? I did, I did, I did notice that, Munchy. I did
notice how the goggles are on one side. Um, hey, do you like how her fucking cutie mark,
how her fucking cutie mark overlaps the seam between her torso and back leg? Do you like that?
Do you like that, Munchy? Yeah, me too. Big fan, big fan over here.
This, I just realized too that that that that that these like these these like goggles like like
the actual like like like lens part like are completely different art style and look completely
different than the rest of the body. Yeah, they were clearly drawn by an inept amateur who thought,
I mean, just look at how they're fucking like the shape of the goggles looks like they've been
melted. Yeah. Like, look how thin this one is. Yeah.
This is, it's all on one side, it's all on one side of the hair in the horn. It's all on one side.
The pink lenses, the pink lenses on the brown goggles, on the white, on the black hair.
Think about it.
Look, look, just look at the fucking, look at the fucking pixelation of the edge of that cutie
mark. Look at the fucking aspect ratio of that cutie mark on that tiny ass leg.
It was, it's just, it's like, it's like the cutie mark doesn't, it's like the cutie
mark doesn't even exist. Like it's just been like painted on the glass that we're viewing this caged
animal through. Oh, fuck. God. The way this like, this like line is going to,
it looks like it's going right into her fucking asshole, not going like above it or anything.
You're right. Yeah, it's too low. It's too, yeah, it doesn't look like it connects to the spine.
It should be, it should be coming out the fucking top of the ass, not the bottom you faggots.
Oh my god. Do you like how obviously this is like, like control T and photoshop.
Oh my god. Yeah, I just noticed that. Yeah, look how fucking, look how fucking, what's the word,
skewed? Look how fucking skewed the ass. Yeah, like fully skewed and distorted.
Look how skewed the aspect ratio on those wings are. They're so fucking bad. It's all so bad. Also,
look how, look how, look how huge the ears are. Wait, wait, wait, okay, okay. The ears are huge
and so is the fucking line on the ears, meaning that the ear, like that's an ear asset that was
just taken and like fucking enlarged. Line and all, line and all. Control T, you just, just like,
yeah, just, just fucking drag that shit. Look how, look where the horn, look how huge her
forehead is. Like look where the eyes end and the horn must begin. Look how much fucking space there
is between the eyes and the horn, dude. Exactly, exactly. So the line would be like this. Ideally,
the horn would be right here and then like, like downward because it should be on the forehead,
but now it's like basically on the top of the head now. Yeah, basically, and the ears just
like fucking go bat, like bat, like bat ears. I mean, maybe that's intentional. I don't know. I kind
of, I kind of like like the huge ears. Like I think they look fine, except for the fact that,
that the, that the line on them is so fucking thick that you can tell they were just controlled to
eat. Yeah. It really, it really gets me though. It really gets me that the tail goes below where
the hooves meet the ground. Like that really bothers me. Like the only, the only logical
explanation for it is that like, it's actually like the tail is extending like so far into the
foreground that it like, look, that like from our upward viewing angle, like it looks further down.
You know what I'm saying? But like, but like, it's, it's behind her. Like the tail is behind
her and yet it suddenly like shoots forward. Oh my God, the positioning of the tail in,
in 3D space is insane. It's insanity. Let's, let's, let's examine the chain of events here.
This person, this person makes this OC. Yeah. Actually, actually, no, no, no. I, I, I read a
little bit on the summary page. She originally had a Pegasus like OC. Okay. So assuming just this
without a horn. Yeah. Then a quote unquote important change happens in her life and she
changes it to an alicorn. So she has this OC. Wait, is that, is that what it said? Is that
what the wiki said? That an important change happened in her life and that she made it into
an alicorn? Yes. Okay. That's interesting. This is interesting. So this, wait, what is this person's name?
Uh, lightning blitz. Lightning blitz. That's it. Lightning blitz, not rainbow blitz. Yeah,
good stuff. Good stuff. Okay. Okay. So she is representing herself. She's representing her
ideas and everything about herself through this image. This is the image that she, that she chooses,
that she willingly represents herself with, right? That's, that, that, that's event number one. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Event number two, she, she gets a backlash for having an alicorn OC and
being an unoriginal, deplorable human being. Yeah. Okay. That is, that is what happened,
I believe. I can buy that. I buy that story. Okay. Okay. Okay. So at this point, she's already,
she's already off the deep end for just, for this existing. Yeah. Due to the fact that this exists,
she's already, like, like, she's, she's not worth it. We need to get rid of her. Like,
like, she's not worth saving. Yeah. Like, like, like, like, it's, it's gone to the point where,
like, a police tax force has to be, like, called in. Like, there's no point. Yeah, something has to
be done. Yeah. Yeah. So we're already at that point. Stage three, she contacts Dr. Wolfe. Well,
well, you know, you know, there's, there's another step, which is that she was making,
I think she made like a, like one or two, like, fucking review, you know, like the quote unquote
reviews that you can make in this community and can be considered like a legit creator.
Like, she made some fucking video of her with her OC talking about like, I don't know how
Twilight is gay or something. You know, like, she did a couple, she did a couple of those,
and she got active in the community. And like, she made a bunch of friends with a bunch of the
other people. And like, you know, she had her OC and da, da, da, da, and she was in the riff.
Like, like, that's, that's, that's step three, that's step three. Yeah.
Like, like, she, she just, she just stumbles, she just stumbles, asks forward and, and, and,
and to fame somehow. I mean, I mean, fame is, but yeah, into what, into what is, what is considered
fame in, in, as far as, yeah, she becomes a notable name among this, like, fucking, this fucking cult.
It's called, it's called, it is slu. Yeah.
So, she, she, she achieves, she achieves horse famous. Yeah, such as it is. And then, and, and,
and then do, do, do the immense cyberbullying of people, of people telling her that his,
that her OC is uninspired in sippy drivel. Yep. Yep. She, she, she contacts the mythical
legendary Dr. himself, Dr. Wool. Yeah. Cause she's, cause she's got the hookups, right? Cause like,
she's in the fucking riff and she's talking to tune critic and Eliora and Golden Fox and other
like heavy hitters, you know? They're, they're, they're, they're riffing, they're riffing, they're
having fun. Yeah, they're riffing, they're riffing the rift. Yeah, they're, they're riffing. Yeah.
She contacts Dr. Wool with a proposition unlike any of it. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm with you so far.
I'm with you. Let me come on your show. Yeah. I'm assuming she drew it or, you know, you know,
fuck it. We'll just get someone else to drop for, for, for, for maybe $10. Yeah. Yeah. I'll drop,
I'll drop 10 bucks on this fucking, on this important career move that I'm making.
I've got something. I've got, I've got, I've got something that's been eating away at me,
Doc. You, Dr. Wool, a, a, a re, a real licensed psychologist, which he totally is. He, he, he,
he is the master of psychoanalysis and you need to come to him with all of your problems.
Yeah. Or else just what the fuck are you doing? Yeah, yeah. Just making the point. Doc, I got a
problem. People are making fun of me for being a no talent, awful, meaningless, a horrible waste of
existence. People are getting on my back for being the most uninspired, creatively bankrupt,
like horrible meat minuscule on the planet. Fuck meat minuscule. I need, I need to reach,
I need you to console me. I need you to tell me that everything's going to be okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Please tell me, tell me that it's okay to keep doing what I'm doing. That's what
she wants. Please. Yeah. I need, it, it, I need, I need you to tell me. Make it clear that the
official Doctor Wolf position, make it clear that the official Doctor Wolf position is that this is
fine and good. Let, let the world fucking know. Yeah. That, that hashtag I stand with lightning
bliss, I stand in solidarity with the disabled and wounded veteran that is lightning bliss.
Oh no. Oh God, no. God, no, doc. Don't do it. Don't fucking sign that. Don't fucking sign that
infernal pact. But you know what? I know how the story ends. I know how the story ends and he
fucking, spoiler alert. He fucking did it. I could use another video. Yeah. Yeah. I need,
I need more content to keep my patrons happy, to keep that fucking, to keep that fucking
meaningless trickle of money, just, just trickling away into my bank account so I can not pay my
artists with it. Oh my God. I say it's, I say it's a deal, Miss Bliss. Yeah. Yeah. I think,
I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship. I think we both stand, I think we
both stand to gain from our new union, our new business agreement. Yes. Yes. You supply, you
supply, you supply the childish naivete and fucking utter incompetence and lack of self-awareness
that the community at large can empathize with and all provide and all provide the fucking bogus
trumped up absolute bullshit sense of creepy paternal authority and affirmation that people
like you and your miserable, ill crave, you know, to fucking rock yourselves to sleep at night
in your fucking, in your little, in your little fucking homemade cribs, in your little emotional
cribs that you sleep in. You fucks, you piece of shit. Jesus fucking Christ. You know, you know,
it's actually worse. It's actually even worse than you say, Munchy, because she wasn't, because
the criticism she was receiving is not, you, the criticism she was sensitive to is not like,
your shit sucks and you're terrible, because that, while true, is not a valid criticism in the,
in the Brony analysis escape, right? What, what the criticism was, was not anything substantial.
The criticism was that she was being written off specifically for being an alicorn and that
is unacceptable. You know what that is? That's literally racism. She was literally experiencing
racism for the, for the, for the, you know, she didn't choose this, Munchy. She didn't choose
to be an alicorn. This was, you know, this is just who she is and she doesn't deserve to be
judged for it because it's not like, because it's not like any kind of like creative decision making
or design ethos went into her being an alicorn. This is just who she is and you can't,
you can't fucking judge her for it, Munchy. You, you bigot. And, and if you do-
So much for the internet's most tolerant fandom, am I right guys?
Yeah, yeah. Like they're just, like they're just, they just come into it, like they just come into
it. They come into watching her videos with all these assumptions based solely on the fact that
her al, her OC is an alicorn, which, you know, if they just gave her a chance, if they just,
if they just gave her a chance they would see, they would have all their fucking bigoted preconception
shattered, Munchy. They would have them shattered and they would see the beautiful person.
Their earth would be wrong at the sheer uniqueness and the sheer creativity coming out of, of, of,
of this fucking powerhouse of imagination. You know what, you know what, I'm, I'm look,
I'm not gonna read like any of it, but I looked at the wiki and I get the sense, I get the sense
that this OC, that this character actually does, like I'm not, I can't speak to its quality, although
I'm sure it's garbage. This, this, this character actually does like have some kind of a background
to it, which like, I'm sure it sucks, but I respect that there at least is one, right? Oh no, oh
never mind, never mind, because I'm seeing that like it's all tied in with the fucking Rift Cafe.
Yeah. Whatever, I don't know, at least there's something, like at least this person has some
kind of like a character, right? Even if it's shit. Lightning Bliss was a Pegasus pony, all right.
Even, even if it's shit and stupid and retarded, at least this person has something, at least this
person isn't Toon Critic, whose fucking OC background is, I review ponies and I wear a fucking hat and
a scarf, right? Oh my god. Oh my god. What? After investing her time and her artwork to others
whom requested it, she soon later started up the Lightning Bliss show after she felt the need to
express herself about the MLP series through her own imagery and animation capabilities. Oh my god.
Who writes like that? It's like, okay, so her, so her, so her backstory, so her backstory is
she's an artist who started an MLP channel. That's, that's her backstory. Okay, never mind.
I mean, what is, I mean, there's this thing about, wait, no, go up, go up. The thing about
Lightning Bliss' dimension. Like, that's, okay, you know, maybe I was wrong. I thought for a second
that this person- Oh, I asked God that it was just this image and I was going to fucking die.
Like, I thought for, I thought for a second that they was like a backstory, but apparently there's
not, it's just I started a YouTube channel. Uh, here we go, here we go. Created after she first
started her show a few episodes later, originally Lightning Bliss hosted her show in an old hotel
cabin due she wasn't ready to be fully exposed to the rest of the Brony analysis reviewing community.
She also was nervous of the fact that she was an alicorn and feared she wouldn't be accepted.
With doubt in her mind, she rented out and did her reviews in quiet. Oh my god, after being isolated
and she couldn't expand her creativity. How much of this is real and how much of this is like fake,
like kayfabe? How much of this is kayfabe? I don't know. I'm thinking none. I'm thinking like
literally none, like zero to 1%. Lightning Bliss decided to break free of her fear and hide out
for the chance to become something more as a reviewer and as an alicorn but still have her
place safe within the community. She whipped out her lioness tail and painted the special,
she painted the special dimension that opened within the fourth wall of the rift because she
is an alicorn. She felt it was only natural. She'd be in a place that represented the alicorn
mystery. Hence why it is similar to that of the dimension that was created by Princess Celestia,
though both dimension is tail painted and holds more unusual. Oh, her thing is that she like paints
things with her tail and they become real. That's her magic alicorn. It's even more unusual magical
properties than average. She's so unique. Holy shit. You know what? You know what? I take back
everything I said. I take back everything I said. There is nothing redeeming about this person.
There is nothing redeeming about any of this. You know, I'm really, I'm actually torn because I,
man, I really like, okay, I like the idea. I like the idea of like telling a story through YouTube,
like with the conceit of like it, like with the self-awareness that it is being told through
YouTube. Like, I like the idea of like a fiction being constructed, like knowingly constructed
through the medium of like YouTube videos that are presented as YouTube videos. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah, yeah, like like like a marble hornet's bed and shit. Like spooky ARG shit. Yeah, yeah.
Like, like, like a character, like you're getting windows into a character, but the character is
presented through like the lens of like these are the YouTube videos that they make, you know?
Yeah. This is not, this is like trying at that, but like it's not that and it sucks and I hate it.
Like the whole rift, like the whole rift is like sort of that, but not really and I hate it.
Ben, this isn't a joke. The plot of like painting a window into a special dimension,
I kid you not, that was the plot of like a like right wherever you want short story I did in the
fifth grade. That's not a fucking joke. That's literally what the plot was. Like, it's like,
this is like such a, this is like such like a self-important, important, important self-important
story. This is such like a self-indulgent story, right? And like it's all for the grand,
like the grand climax of this story is that this person becomes a pony reviewer, right?
Like that's the, like that's the grand finale of this person's story.
And how grand it is.
She was, she was tormented, tormented by her fear of not being accepted by the analysis community
for being an alicorn, but she fucking rose above it. Oh god, I'm, I'm tired.
Christ above hate.
I'm tired and I can't, I'm getting, I'm actually like, I feel weak, like I feel weak and sick and hungry.
We haven't, we haven't even gone through the,
is this who I, is this who I think it is?
Yeah, man. Oh.
That's the, that's the man himself, the man in the myth.
It's the man himself.
The man in the myth, the legend. Let me, let me look at, give me a minute.
I need to look in my fridge and fucking find some calories to consume.
Okay.
Pause the right footage calculus here.
He's known for his opinion on, oh my god.
A notable, a notable characteristic of this, of this person is that he has an opinion.
He has an opinion on a word.
Not even that it's like a contrary, he just has a opinion.
He just has a, he has, no. This isn't believable.
Yes. Fuck yes. Jaffas.
Ben.
I got Jaffas.
Ben. Okay, yeah.
Ben.
Yep.
A no, a notable characteristic of this pony has an opinion on double rainbow.
Hat is known for his opinion.
Oh.
He has a opinion.
Oh my fucking god, Munchie.
He has an opinion.
He, he's known for it in fact.
Yeah.
I mean, I mean, I mean clearly what's meant to be communicated here is that he has like
a notable opinion or like a controversial opinion.
Like that's what they're trying to say, but they didn't say it.
Okay. I like, okay, I like how they switch between Josh and Firebrand.
Okay. Firebrand is a Christian.
Josh formerly served in the Marines.
I like how both of these things are associated with JSW Connors,
and now I'm just going to, I'm just going to imagine that they are one and the same.
Wait a minute. So are they saying, so are they saying that like specifically Fire,
like the pony is a Christian?
Like not the guy, the pony is one.
That's what it seems to be saying to me.
That's what my cutie mark is telling me, you might say.
Ink Rose and himself are shipped quite frequently in the fandom,
and even have two Fannin children by the name of Citrus Flossum and Morning Shine.
Well, Fannin, that's like the same thing as being real.
Yeah. So far.
Somebody, somebody made a, oh, these Jaffas ate a whole roll of them.
Somebody made a drawing of keg standard and mod pie's son, and it was actually really good.
And it was weird. I found it on DeviantArt, and it was amidst like a bunch of other OCs
that like this person was not drawing like the analysis community.
Why that picture? Why that picture?
Stop everything.
Like this person, this person was not drawing like analysis.
He was drawing like kids of like in canon characters.
Like like the only, the only analysis personality that I saw among their work
was keg standard, and it was as the dad of like this son of mod pie.
So I don't know. And it was pretty cool too.
Yeah, it's pretty fucking cool. Let's see. Let's see what keg's up to.
Oh, why? Why don't they just fucking picture from the fucking videos?
Why don't they use the fucking canon art? This is Jesus.
Why? Like he looks like fucking garbage.
For him and for you are completely baffling.
Yeah, I just don't understand why.
Just nothing's here besides the fucking reference sheet and some shit part.
I'm fed up. I'm fed up with this world. Everybody betray me.
Oh, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Okay, okay, okay.
Fin the pony. It's pretty good.
It's great. It's wonderful.
Might want to click on that pretty good. Vita pretty, pretty great.
Wait, what the fuck? I fucking erased that article. What the shit?
Okay. Yeah, yeah, there we go. Fuck that boy.
He's done for a voice of reason.
Oh, yes. Oh, yes. Master of the Rift.
The master. Ink is his apprentice.
Voice has a darker side called horror.
Sentience in a physical form and he now lives with Koi.
Can I see a picture? I want to fucking see horror score.
Well, there he is.
Voice of reason protecting his girlfriends.
Oh, Sega sisters, his girlfriend. That's beautiful.
That's beautiful. I saw her on the female list.
I need to, I need to-
Sega sister. Sega sister. Oh, my.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Let me see, let me see.
Look.
That's her. That's her. There she is. There she fucking is.
Can I see, can I see an image, please?
Okay, so she's just Ink Rose. Like, like her pony is just Ink Rose.
Yeah, it's just red.
And brown.
Why?
Why was this conceived?
Sega sister is heteroflexible.
What?
I'm, it's heteroflexible.
Okay, please. Fucking.
Oh, I'm going to puke. I'm going to throw up, I'm going to throw up and die.
Those, I ate a whole, I ate a whole roll of jaffas and it wasn't enough.
Do you like how this unironically has way more like stuff on it than the PCP wiki?
Um, man, I don't fucking get, I don't fucking get the priorities of the people making the PCP wiki.
I just want to make shitty memes.
Yeah, it's, it's, oh my god, I'm in love, I'm in love, I'm in love.
I've seen that guy, I've seen that guy before.
I'm in love.
Okay, after this guy, we got to check out Dr. Fowl.
Okay.
A YouTube channel.
The Looney Turtle.
Eric, Eric the Human and Looney the Turtle. Oh, they collaborate. Oh, he's like hippo.
Oh, he's only 19.
Oh, it's just like, I gotta see this guy.
I gotta see this guy.
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, he has the same birthday.
Isn't this curious?
How does he not, okay, that's a fucking injustice.
What the, well, he's not a, well, he doesn't, Munchy, he doesn't have a pony avatar.
He shouldn't.
Oh, okay.
He should never be, he should never even come close to this place.
It's sacred, it's sacred ground.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
One of, every one of this MLP analysis videos has the line,
hello interwebs.
I'm Eric and welcome to the Looney Turtle.
I want to see, I want to see, I want to see.
I'm interested.
You peak my curiosity.
Oh, my fucking god, this banner.
Look at him, look at him on the left there.
He looks ridiculous.
He looks fucking ridiculous.
He's at 34,000 subs.
Did you see that fucking lip syncing?
Yeah.
This is like,
this is like, okay, imagine if you, if you like, if you like,
you like kidnapped hippo, right?
Yeah.
Like, like, like, like he kidnapped him and he can do whatever you want with him.
And, and he took him and took him to a special factory.
And, and, and you, and you mixed together like all the worst parts about humanity
and all the most naive, awful, horrible, horrible aspects of, of, of, of like 2010,
like reviewer culture.
And, and, and you like, you like tossed them in that you tossed them in there into the meat grinder.
And what came out is, is this disgusting hamburger of, of, of, of just, just awful,
awful, it's awful, it's awful.
It's like, man, I don't know.
Six hours ago.
I look, I look at this and I'm like, man, fucking anyone, fucking anyone can fucking make it on
YouTube if this, like, they just talk about the right things and they have like a, like,
all he had to do was draw a turtle.
Like he drew a turtle and he was, he had it fucking was made.
Like that, that was it.
He did it.
Like he, he did it.
You know, I guess he probably got his, he got a little bump.
He probably got that initial pony bump and then he just moved on.
I don't know.
Does there, I mean, am I crazy?
Do I, am I seeing, does there seem to you to be anything fucking like interesting or
notable about like his comedy at all?
No.
Like it looks like any other fucking goofy, shitty comedy,
fagotry that you'd see on any other channel.
That's what I'm fucking seeing.
That's what I see.
Exactly the same as fucking everything else we've seen tonight.
A, a, a podcast known as Bro Talk, you know, the Rattyfuckers Cop Killers doesn't have the,
the unique and instantly recognizable branding that Bro Talk has.
I love the Rattyfuckers Cop Killers, dude.
I fucking, I need it.
It's, it's perfect.
I need it.
I'm glad we're not just besmirching it at all.
I'm, I'm gonna see.
I want to see how many views Bro Talk gets.
I want to get into the anime James.
Who's the guy you wanted to see?
Dr. Fowl.
Yeah, Dr. Fowl.
Oh my God, he's, he's perfect.
He looks really good.
Yeah, he looks.
Look at it.
Look at his tail.
This is incredible.
Dr. Fowl's den for the mentally impaired.
What's your problem?
He's great.
He's fucking great.
Is this guy like, like a parody of Dr. Hold on.
I think he may be like a satire.
No, you know what?
He's not a satire.
He's just like, he's just like, he's just a fucking regular ass pony faggot.
He's just got like, he's just got like a slightly like kind of quirky and like
unself-serious kind of like humorous edge to him.
Oh yeah, he's the head honcho of the chicken brigade.
Ah, shit.
Yeah, he's not, he's like, he's like, he's like half a notch above your regular
fucking pony guy, but like he's not, he's not like, he's still, he's still one of them.
He's so cool and aloof.
He's, he's still one of them though.
I really wanted to like him.
Yeah, like I really, I really wanted this guy's whole existence to just,
I wanted him to be another Kimmy Sparkle.
I wanted him to be just be taking the piss out of the whole thing.
Dr. Fowl.
Oh my fucking god.
That would have been incredible.
Dr. Fowl, if you're watching this, please, please, please take a red pill, join the PCP.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't go back, don't go back.
Dr. Fowl's backstory.
No, you fucking nerd.
Dr. Fowl's backstory, it is said he hails from the life being a stone of,
a stone bird that shattered to create life on the, okay, first of all,
this is written like a fucking grade schooler.
The byproduct of this being the energy that brought the rift into B.
Oh, his backstory is about the rift.
After a few iterations, Hephaestus, what?
Dr. Fowl was formed from the egg of his father's soul,
when it split off into two entities, Dr. Fowl and King Cocklesworth.
The bronalysis king born of the egg formed by the second Hephaestus.
Well, Dr. Fowl stayed in the present.
King Cocklesworth went into the future and ran the world as its king.
Did Dr. Fowl solve-
This is kind of like incredible.
Yeah, it is actually.
Dr. Fowl saw the world and thought that he would take the form of a pony
to try to fit in.
But after growing a distaste for the content created by the people around him,
he took it upon himself to shed his pony form and take upon his true form.
What does he mean?
What does he fucking mean, his distaste for the content?
How fucking deep does this rabbit hole go?
We have to watch a video.
Yeah, we do.
If there's like a lore video, we have to fucking watch that.
Fowl play.
407 subscribers.
Uh, the Hephaestus story?
Day 6, the birth time of the king!
Wait, wait, wait.
How fucking-
The Hephaestus story full.
Oh my god.
Jesus.
Jesus Christ.
Full screen that shit, dude.
In the beginning, there was the life lead.
An entity of unimaginable power that infused the planet with its spirit.
This caused the life being to the common state.
Causing its body to spit on-
Look at that!
Into many shards named the Aesthetes, throughout the omnivores.
These rune stones were not the only thing coming from the life being.
But underneath the rune stone shelf was the icon, the lane of light and darkness.
And on the small tracks that the lean stone climbs with a glop of icon,
it falls into a beam known as the Wayfarer.
One of these Wayfarers is known as Hephaestus, or the Bird of Passage.
Landing on a world in the taker and mummaging that doesn't clean us.
We are spoken as a journey of good, and, and not, and death, and everything between.
We were completely wrong about this guy.
Yeah, yeah.
Hephaestus took the form of a glowing white, ancient silhouette.
Traversing the barren planet, creating more-
I can't believe this.
More life he created.
I cannot fucking believe this.
I'm so delighted.
We've got to get this guy on the PCB.
He's got to be on an episode.
He's got-
Dude, we should fucking get him on the next Rowdyfuckers cop killers.
Yes, we should!
Mermaids and Sphinxes, one of his neoterics, a harpy known as Shine, caught his interest.
And after a short time together, they fell in love.
In a way to prolong Hephaestus' fate from existence,
the two merged their forms into an egg.
The egg combined with Hephaestus and the neoteric Shine laid dormant-
This is some high-level Christ consciousness shit.
Doing this stuff, the world began to develop.
This is super fucking-
This is super Greenpill.
And neither the two alicorn descendants of the neoterics.
Nearing the end of the a thousand years, the alicorns fought with a strong foe.
The energy of the battle caused the egg to hatch into Hephaestus, the second.
And gave the alicorns one day, capable only of observation.
Hephaestus the second began watching the world form,
and noticed a cave on the side of a large mountain.
In said cave was a wormhole into a space-like plane filled with floating rocks.
This plane seemed to connect many, many planes.
Suddenly, Hephaestus the second noticed a strange energy emanating from the whip.
Noticing the danger in the situation.
Used some of his power in an attempt to see-
This is the greatest-
This is the greatest development in the history of the Rowdyfuckers cop killers.
In the long and storied history of the Rowdyfuckers cop killers program.
Hephaestus took its toll on Hephaestus.
His body was weak and he had taken too much with energy.
His body shook as his soul left his body, splitting into two miles of purple light.
Why were they purple?
The light formed into egg shapes.
One disappeared through time, and the other merged with the limp, lifeless body of Hephaestus the second.
Hephaestus the second's body glowed and morphed into a new-
His own soul came out of him, split into two,
and then half of it went back into him and turned him into an egg.
The energy from the soul egg traveling through time
caused the rift hole to move to one of the many microplates.
The soul egg's destination, five thousand years into the future,
a land in which one hundred seasons of my little pony had aired.
It had formed into a humanoid body with a chicken's head.
After a brief glow, this Hephaestus remembered his past.
Alongside an ability to see specific errors.
Now we're getting real.
In detail, using this knowledge,
he quickly rose to become a respected figure in the future world,
eventually becoming crowned as King Cockroach.
In the past, the egg hatched into Hephaestus the second,
after flying around and seeing how much life had changed,
he overheard a bearded pony still in the past,
and learning the alicorns had taken a few liberties
aligning up the neoterics and Hephaestuses,
writing their names down as Hephaestus Applebee's Juniper Moonberry.
This Hephaestus decided in protest to this blasphemy
to make this his true name,
becoming known as Hephaestus Applebee's Juniper Moonberry.
Now it is known as Hephaestus Applebee's Juniper Moonberry,
through his aeus, Dr. Fowl.
Oh. Oh my god.
That's it. We did it.
Now we know.
He's everything, Munchie.
He's perfect.
He's a perfect human.
He's the next evolution.
Wait, King Cocklesworth teaches you about the future.
Bottom right, bottom right.
This is important.
It's like a merit launch.
Hello. It is I, King Cocklesworth, and welcome to the King's...
This guy watches Jesse.
Did you know?
Yeah, he does.
King Cocklesworth. I'm from the future.
Yes. In the year 4000, we have had around 1000.
And 900 seasons of my little pony.
Each one has gotten better.
The show has gotten so good that they have transcended
and found peace in the plain beyond.
For me, though, well, I can't ascend just yet.
I have a kingdom to rule, and pitch is to take care of.
Like a dorky and linda.
I have to learn what is left of the brony analysis community.
I mean, I'm the third in a very prestigious line
dating back to the origins of the world.
I even inherited my name from the OG Hephaestus.
So I am very important.
He's like...
I'm in love.
He like rides the line so carefully and like so elegantly.
Like completely totally like unhinged.
You know what?
Like reading his description on the wiki just really did not do him justice.
Yeah.
Hold on.
He totally fucking watches Jesse.
Like there's no bones of that.
Yeah, yeah.
He's that's...
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Wait. Featured channels.
Lethal Aurora Mage.
Antony C.
Shelley D.
Huh.
What?
Corpulent Brony?
How I wonder...
Wait, I wonder if Mage knows this guy.
I wonder if Mage fucking knows this guy.
I'm gonna ask her.
If so, why hasn't she fucking shown us?
Yeah, I'm gonna fucking ask her right now and then kill her.
Have you seen this bird?
Whoa.
Okay, there's like one that's like said inside Dr. Wolf's thing.
Oh, okay, it's like...
It's like a remix of The Grinch or something.
I just...
Yeah, this guy is totally...
I'm gonna go fucking subscribe right now.
Yeah, do it.
I'm reading the lyrics of this like Mr. Grinch parody song he made about himself.
And he's totally...
Like the inspiration for this character was literally just he hated Dr. Wolf so fucking much.
Are you sure?
Look at the lyrics on screen right now.
Oh, oh god.
Wait, he says...
I'm not...
I don't know, man.
I'm not sure.
It sounds kind of like he's making...
He's making unflattering comparisons of himself to Dr. Wolf.
Like he's a bad version of Dr. Wolf.
Like Dr. Wolf is good.
I...
I don't know, man.
I'm not sure.
I'm not...
Like I'm actually not sure.
Like I want...
I want to believe that this guy is good.
But I don't know.
I could...
He could...
It could all just be a happy accident.
Could he be...
Like could such a...
Could such a genius...
The freest you could store other drawings while the sky says a therapist.
I feel like that has to be like...
No, but then he says...
Yeah, but he also says you just copied your show from the wolf.
Oh fuck.
Yeah.
Oh shit.
You're a fake gynecologist and psychologist chicken who thinks he's a god.
Uh...
It's...
Man, that fucking backstory was so good though.
He...
This is the most perplexing thing I've ever fucking seen for my fucking life.
Yeah.
It's...
It's so...
I ju- I just can't tell.
No, I can't.
I just can't tell.
I feel like...
I don't know.
I'm kinda inclined...
I'm kind of inclined to believe...
That he is retarded, but like there's like glimmers.
There's like glimmers of understanding just starting to emerge there.
Yeah.
Hmm.
I fucking...
I fucking admire this guy's like...
Drive to like do this.
Like he's...
He's doing something different.
I really appreciate that.
Like does he...
Wait.
Wait a minute.
He doesn't...
He doesn't even have any like episode reviews.
He doesn't.
So like what is he?
What is his purpose?
He's got a...
He's got a couple like podcasts.
Let's see.
Hold on.
Our play...
Oh, I guess this is like a let's play?
Yeah.
Okay.
It's like a let's play.
There was some like...
Actually, it was Dungeon and Dragons.
His latest videos is like a Brony RPG,
which I assume is like a D&D podcast thing or something.
Yeah.
Okay.
Skimming through this.
Here's what I think.
This is either like a Jayce Conner sort of like deep cover troll.
Or he's like...
He's like a hyper-autist.
Like not just like we've never seen before.
Like like like like and he really has like insane like tapestry woven in his fucking head.
And that just just just just still happens to be to be funny to us.
Yeah.
For all the reasons he intends.
It's...
I just I can't I can't get a read on the guy.
I think...
We have to fucking talk to him.
We have to.
Yeah, I think if we're ever gonna if we're ever...
It's the only way to know for sure.
Yeah.
Wait, what is Dr. Fowle's birthday party?
It's five minutes long.
It's probably another song.
Yeah, probably.
Oh shit, singing.
There's no description apparently?
No, thanks.
I don't want to...
Wait, skip ahead.
Skip ahead.
Okay.
I don't know why it's taking so long to...
Because it's paused, you ding-dong.
Oh, holy shit.
Here.
Yeah, do you want to watch this?
No.
Yeah.
Wait.
Okay, hold on.
Third 40 fucking minutes.
King of Limba, Dr. Fowle.
Oh, that's a podcast thing.
Oh, okay.
Wait, April Fool is a moment with Dr. Fowle, the movie.
Oh, welcome to Dr. Fowle's death for the mentally impaired.
What's your problem?
Fucking hell.
He's empty.
What's going on?
Does no one have any problems?
Jack looked across the floor of the empty barn
and bled for a leave into Scott's body, still in pain.
Oh, I'm not impressed.
Yeah, let's skip ahead.
It's just this for 13 minutes.
Maybe if we were like listening to like...
You know, I honestly gotta say, I think you may be a retard.
Yeah, maybe if we were like high as shit, bro,
maybe if we were like super fucking stone,
then maybe we'd like get it, you know?
Yeah, that must be it.
He's undoubtedly an interesting character, however.
Yeah, yeah.
I wonder, let's see if Mage said anything.
No.
I wonder, maybe he just featured her because he likes her.
Maybe.
What can you say about Dr. Fowle?
Say what you like.
He's got Cajones.
He's got show, he's got show bits, you know what I'm saying?
He's got show, he's got show...
He's got a cute bird.
He's got show bits and a vice, you know what I'm saying?
I know exactly what you're saying.
Yeah, he's gonna kill you.
He's got a cool character.
Yeah, unlike just, he's almost as cool as TuneCriticY2K.
Almost, I mean, no one can be as cool as him.
All right, Baroni Dance Party, very good.
We gotta see this.
More nothing.
I am going into the fucking...
Oh no, I can't...
I was gonna edit Vita out of the fucking pages and category mail,
but it won't let me, I think I have to have an account
and I'm not fucking willing to make an account.
God damn it.
Yeah, accounts are late.
That's how they fucking get you.
That's how they get you.
I bet you could delete the page too if you had an account.
I'm actually not sure about that.
I think I'm not sure if the leading pages
is even like a thing that Wikis do.
I think they just expand outward forever and ever
and can never be fucking, and can never be clipped.
Let's see who FNGR is.
I have a basic understanding of him and I don't like him.
FNGR is like, I don't know.
He's just like a guy who seems weirdly invested
and trolling people, but is actually...
I've never actually known him to troll anyone.
He just seems to like to be there when people get trolled.
Like he just likes to see people in distress,
but doesn't actually do anything.
What?
That description.
He just likes to be there when shit goes bad.
He's just like invested in drama,
but I don't know of him actually causing any.
Maybe he does, I don't know.
For no good reason, or FNGR for short.
He likes to like...
The biggest drama lightning rods in the community.
He likes to poke people and prod them
and try and make them mad about stuff
that like other people did.
Although he refers to himself as a Dallas,
he spends more time making his limbo podcasts
as well as weekly commentary on the Brony drama titled
How Not to Brony.
He's an FPFC member.
I don't know what that is.
Pony fuck casts.
Oh, you know what?
Oh man, me, I have no fucking clue why.
I think it was FNGR himself, or maybe it was Vita
that added me to the Pony fuck cast Skype call.
Yeah.
And I joined in.
They did that to me once too.
Me and my friend just recited the history
of the Byzantium Empire to them.
And it was incredible.
The entire time I was playing mariachi music in the background.
It was great.
I see he's got a Patreon.
Yeah.
I wanna see his YouTube.
How many subs?
Like 3,000?
Yeah, like 3,000.
How not?
I hold on.
Yeah.
What is this about Digi drama in the Brony community?
That seems strange.
It's a yo.
That's fucking why.
Why 40 minutes?
Oh, here, here.
The best thing they fucking added to YouTube.
Hold on.
Did you see how he misspelled following?
Yeah.
What?
All right, I don't care anymore.
Yeah, this sucks.
This sucks and it's gay.
One time, I even, someone linked me like the videos that he did,
like specifically about me or like about the PCP.
And I didn't care about that either because it sucked.
Oh God, Munchie.
I don't think I can do anymore.
I'm on death's door.
Hold on, hold on.
I'm here.
No, have mercy.
I don't know what's the trailer.
Actually, no, I don't want to.
I actually don't want to.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Actually, go back.
I just saw fucking keg standard.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Did you?
You know what?
What is this?
I actually knew about this.
I remember this.
Hold on.
Okay, don't care.
I'm glad.
I'm so glad, Munchie.
I'm so glad that we read about the lore of,
not past analysis, a voice of reason so that we know about horror scores.
So I understood that reference.
I'm so, I'm so fucking happy that this part of our lives is fucking over with.
Yeah, it's died down.
I think, I think probably a lot of these people have moved on, but not all of them.
Man, we saw a couple of YouTube channels and they all updated pretty recently.
Yeah.
What's, what's tune critic up to?
Tune?
I just, this person deserves the worst that the world can throw at him.
Let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see.
Look at his fucking avatar.
He's got a beard now.
16 hours ago.
I can't fucking believe that.
Does this guy have a Patreon?
Obviously.
I'm bracing for it.
Let's fucking see it.
Come on.
Oh, well, I'm impressed a little.
That's more than I thought.
Boy.
I, my, this was 12.
Ooh.
Ooh, ah.
This is far better than I was expecting.
Yeah, yeah, it is, it is actually.
Who's fucking, who's fucking paying tune critic Y2K to make, to fucking, to fucking
churn out whatever it is that he does.
Oh my god.
Look at hashtag the greatest secret.
Oh, goodness.
Seven minutes.
Ah, shit.
Oh, oh, look.
Whoa.
Oh, what, what, what?
Look, look at him.
Yeah, I'm looking at him.
Look at him.
He's a handsome man.
He's a, he's a good looking, he's a good looking boy.
He's a big baby.
He actually, he actually dresses.
He, he, he's actually, he actually red, red and black.
That's, that's his actual thing.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Oh no.
Yeah, he's all in red and black.
Uh, well, well, irredeemable, irredeemable.
You know, you know, standard glasses, the, the, the snapback.
It's a Pokemon snapback.
Oh my god.
That's, that's, I know he's a nerd.
Wait, I want to see the pony at the end.
I want to see the fucking pony at the end.
Oh my god.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Wow.
He's, he is single-handedly, the most powerful creature I've ever encountered in my life.
oh he is
he is though
he gets he's got sixteen thousand subscribers
uh... about as many as as t-bat
i think
and uh... he gets his videos get like
six hundred views a piece
the most recent one
what we went down
we were above fifteen fifteen thousand for a while there
i knew it was such frinkled uploads
i wonder if i logged in to t-bap right now and like
looked at like the most recent comments
and posted this video on there
uh...
what oh this video that we're making right now
yeah uh...
that would be pretty meadow bro
uh... you fucking would be
for mod pie was like far and away our most popular one but i guess fucking
sweetie bell toils has like
very nearly caught up to it
for whom the sweet bell toils
that's a that's a good i like i like that yes pretty good pretty good it's a
good it's a good it's a good show may you should give it a try
you know it's got really good it's got really good like now is a show and stuff
like it teaches kids really good morals like about friendship and stuff
and like the it it it has it has a super consistent yeah uh... writing quality
yeah like the animation is really like
on the animation is really good it's made in flash and uses a lot of tweening
but the animation is like really good yeah yeah yeah
tweening is the future it's like really good
it uses a lot of tweens and like it uses a lot of like like eleven and twelve
year old that like they fucking enslaved and like made them work on flash
my fucking favorite thing that i ever drew for t-bap is that picture of
celestia and spike as fucking hank and dale from king of the hill
as we look back at all the bridge
no you know what the best thing ever made was was phantom checks the mail
because i didn't even make phantom checks the mail
fucking fucking dave that piece of shit german
uh... who can't fucking right to save his miserable german life
uh... he fucking drew it for me uh... because doctor wolf told him to and i
don't think he even got paid for it
no you know what doctor wolf
didn't even
doctor wolf just like told him to do it
he did it he drew fucking phantom checks the mail for me
and then i was like and then i
was like you know what i'll just give you like fifty bucks because i think you
deserve it because you fucking made an animation for me
that's
jeez christ i know
the fucking i
fucking
i felt i would have felt terrible just letting him like make me the shit and not
give him anything
he deserves
jeezus christ compensation i can't fucking believe this
yeah
this i actually i actually really like this one it's just such a shame that
it's tied to the fucking uh...
uh... analysis anarchy
yeah
oh well
i i i i i guess i guess that's just that's just what you have to live with
yeah
w-w-w-when you're such an esteemed and honorable title such as phantom porn
but then at the end but then at the end
uh... there's like the there's like the two there's like the team fortress two
outro but then you can hear
nate
yeah there you go
nate yells don't blame us if it's shit which it was
so you know what i feel great actually we fucking disclaimer the whole thing
we fucking annulled ourself of any and all responsibility for it
so i don't have to feel bad
yeah but you still do
uh... yeah
yeah
i'm okay
okay first of all i can't believe this
second of all my
you know what
you know fucking what
my chris chan video has more views than this
so there i win
good job yeah um
yeah my fucking my fucking angry comment thread is on that video
wherein i fucking rail against the the fucking uh
the whole like age gap thing with incrose and josh scorcher and kind of
making an idiot of myself
oh well yeah yeah i mean you make you make an idiot yourself all over the
air so what's why not
yeah video comment yeah i got
yeah i got a fucking you got a solid point look at
fucking dr wolf there i want to look at him i want to look at
i want to look at him
oh my god i want to is that his brother
i don't know oh it's silver quell okay
these look at him look at look at both of them
something yeah something is just so fucking off
this is i hate oh god i fucking hate
i fucking hate dr wolf's demeanor so much
oh my god
okay wait this is like been have you ever have you ever heard of that one like
guy that like he was trying to like he was in love with
like he was in love with like an Icelandic like singer or something
like Bjrk yeah and and he he loved he loved her so much that he was going to
say like a bomb to her and then kill himself uh huh
no i'm not before he did that he required a video
where he like had a wig on and he did a bunch of like weird shit where like
piston bottles and stuff and and and this the tent of this
video and and the way it's like positioned
reminds me of that video where where where they're they're about to kill
themselves and they're sitting there they're sending
this videotape to to to the love of their life in Iceland
who was who has been ignoring them for years
um
that's what he fuck yeah he sits with his legs crossed and he strokes his chin
thoughtfully and i can't fucking he fucking reaches
up and touches that face his weirdly gaunt
face like fucking Ben Stiller
oh god oh god
dr wolf who is that guy in the you know what i was gonna say who's that that
ugly guy in the pony con 2017 vlogs but i don't want to watch a vlog
uh i i i think i think we're done
i think we're done here yeah i think you think we're
oh it's it's oh god it's nine a.m it's fucking nine a.m
munchie are we done are are we done with dr wolf or are we done with
oh they have frog fractions hey you know i heard about this game frog
fractions that was really good yeah yeah it was a you think we should do you
think we should record a right of focus cop killers and like play it on the
show i think i think we should uh oh here we go
again
put this video put this what oh you can chapter select
you oh shoot yeah yeah go to big chair fucking finish it just like blast your
way yes yes we're gonna we're doing it we're gonna
we're gonna finish frog fractions at long last
long awaited conclusion to the frog fraction saga
of the rowdy fuckers cop killers uh
i i can't put any fucking you're fucking kidding me
i literally can't you're fucking kidding me hold on hold on hold on hold on
so
munchie if you close if you closed rabbit and started it again
uh and tried it again do you think you would still get the chapter select
oh i think i would here here here you take the remote control
um okay okay okay
all right this i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming
mama's coming yes remember when rarity said that it was really hot
yeah i was i was very aroused by i can't do anything
no wait oh did you take god what what if we just like fucking
like started a new rabbit room or like what if you opened it in a new tab
yeah open it open it in a new tab all right yeah yeah yeah this is it this
is this the shit this is the real shit this is the raw shit this is the raw
sewage that we came here for this this is the uninspired creatively
blink up drivel that that that we herald so highly
yes yes my favorite my favorite uh game yeah yeah yeah yeah
bug coffee bug coffee i just want to fucking see the dramatic conclusion
i just want to see the dramatic conclusion to the frog to the bug porn
nope
okay um
what a fucking drag what a fucking drag
why here here here here you you try you try okay
uh well i you just just just just like try right now and then you can like
stop no i'm not oh my god yes yeah oh i'm gonna do it i'm gonna do it
yeah you just take it away phantom take it away phantom
uh phantom horn to the rescue making bug porn uh what the yeah fucking fine 50 i'll make
it's it's so weird that ben just spontaneously left the room and now phantom horn is here
to to finish the let's play uh yeah um i i killed keg and my work is done and now
i'm just waiting for the cops to show up uh i'm waiting for the royal guards to come and get me
so i figured i'd play some video games pretty good that's that sounds exactly like something phantom
horn would say that's that's basically his character right murderer yeah um uh how many
uh which which price you wish i wish to charge nine thousand excellent good job
health has been gave your product the thumbs up everybody wants to see makes thirsty bugs
clamor for your product bugs marvel at your low prices and kept coming to your door long after
you ran out of porn uh how much did i make i just want to make shit tons of money uh i made
like no money i lost a bunch of money okay fine oh great good job okay so it doesn't fucking matter
yeah um oh yeah yeah you got poison that well bro you got to poison that well bug um bug drugs uh
uh meteorology satellites more accurate yeah weather better weather forecast that sounds important
i'm gonna make uh one uh megabyte of porn you know this this this is a this is a grueling
this is a grueling system this is a grueling slog however someone has to do it someone has
to take up the bug mantle and do his bug job uh and that's someone is gonna be a me a me a me me me
me me me memester memester phantom horn uh how many yeah nine nine nine print all the money
print all the money print all the money what upgrade uh uh who's that fucking person j j jade
jade morrow out or jade morrow yeah yeah she she she uh he was going to make like a fucking like it
like an animation thing ccp animation and i want you to i want you to cancel that and and
remake this scene but but with but with but with phantom horn and strawberry milk who i am
munchie left the room i would love some strawberry milk right now i need calories i need strawberry
milk the the the the dragon the most the most the the the premier pony oc uh yeah yeah that was in
the fucking comic from brony con we saw pink it's it's spike but he's pink and he wears a bow tie
and his and his head scales are kind of puffy looking yeah it's he's he's incredible yeah that's
yeah that's how i would describe him is incredible um i'm incredible is what i meant to say because i
am uh padlocks oh get get the cybernetic brain retard no no no look look this one's padlock
it's not it's it's available uh yeah yeah it's not locked it's just that the thing is a lock
that's great we got it on lock uh come on come on uh uh uh one one bug porn one pop up one dollar
it's pretty fair uh it's you know it's trickle down economics basically
yeah davoo could tell you davoo could i bet if davoo were here he would make like a fucking
he would make fucking bank he would he would he would revitalize the economy with with with
porn uh presidential swimming pool yeah here we go oh yes yes yes back with my old davoo the the
prime year citizen of ponyville uh the prime minister of ponyville yes uh the heated presidential
swimming pool the the spoils of the spoils of all my labor the spoils of all my labor here
uh i enjoy them you know it it was it it was a tougher job becoming bug president however you
know we it paid off we danced we we danced our way into martian bug white house uh we won the
hearts and minds of the people we inspired change yeah we did it we beat frog fractions
we we we we we we did a phantom our name was on the fucking map now yeah um i can't i can't wait
for our fucking our pcp uh wikipedia page should to include that that we beat it frog factions
yeah that munchie and bin where we're munchie and then we slaughtered we invented frog fractions
just so we could be the first to beat it exactly we're so we're so fucking talented we're so green
pill that we became frogs exactly oh my god look there's that lewd shit there's that raw
shit the real raw dicks bug dicks touching each other oh my god so delicious
um
simply incredible play testing dr. wolf
uh uh graphics graphics by uh uh graphics by uh fuck who's that shitty one that i hate um
keyframe keyframe uh yeah yeah um um sound sound by a voice of reason and horror score uh um
uh bug porn by uh looney the turtle and uh silver quill and story by dr fowl and
and his story story by dr fowl uh uh um uh gay gay sex was had by uh josh scorcher
um because he's gay um he's gay munchie i promise you he's gay uh uh strawberry milk strawberry
milk uh background photography background photography uh is by uh nasa uh what net
and by nasa yeah yeah by nasa and matt from london um and also very good and also jim crawford
and steve jobs of apple fame um and the end the pleasure of being the first to beat it the uh
the the the we made this game our bitch then i'm wearing stride you're fucking stride strawberry milk
is coming back baby but oh look bug photography by bernie's anders sandberg oh my god that's
bernie sanders second evolution bernie's anders sandberg yeah my friend that that censorship
doesn't make any sense that's not even a bug that's not even the bug part it could be it's not even
near a bug it could be a bug if you bought it it's not even close i mean not even close if you
if you squint if you squint maybe i don't possibly i don't think i understand what bug sex is or does
you'll you'll you'll know you'll know when you grow up you'll know when you grow up and and and
and and and you leave the farm oh look at it oh look it's it's so delectable unlike munchie
i've no qualms about sex i'm i'm a sexual dvd strawberry milk you cad you that's me announcing
my sexual dvd i like i'll i'll i'll nothing mean i think this is the beginning of a beautiful
you and me yes we're gonna go we're going all the way we're gonna we're gonna take a little
fuck heck we don't we don't need to make tbap a real thing what we can do it our own yeah
hashtag max revive tbap now with strawberry milk
we always we always talked about how like one day like one of us could just leave and we would
just replace the other one just be a new brother uh it never happened um oh look voices uh voices
goose as in my pokemon the died um well oh well he's whatever i can barely hear him
so fuck it uh yeah yeah pretty good pretty uh that that that's that's good this episode of
the rye fuckers cop oh what the fuck is this dragon doing here get the fuck out of here you
fucking sex however yeah um hey remember everyone phantom horn says uh go to steam uh username enok
144 and buy him uh glitter mitten grove so he can play frog fractions too for free uh and also
get him grow up just because grow home was a really good game by this is pretty good yeah yeah uh
man i really fucking love grow home maybe we should play that no no that's a good game
good game good good and worthwhile good and worthwhile gaming experiences do not belong
on rowdy fuckers cop killers um no thank you no thank you yeah this was a pretty great intro to
the draw cast but we should probably you should probably get into it we should probably start
drawing our our frog our frog requests um our our our our thousands upon thousands of frog
requests that we get daily the people are just clamoring to see some frogs by procrastinators
draw cast episode five frogs uh oh i would do that so would i so would i but but you know
no alas you know unfortunately we can't we don't make enough on patreon we can't
possibly afford that um no it's silly it's fucking ridiculous it's fucking ridiculous don't even
don't even joke don't even joke about that if you donate your your hard-earned bits to to to
the procrastinators at www dot there it is monchi how fucking incensed are you
that like the the draw cast got like less than four thousand views like the draw cast like the
draw like the draw cast got less views than a pcp even though a pcp is literal nonsense
bullshit and and and garbage content and the draw cast is like a masterpiece yeah it the the
homestuck one yeah the homestuck one it it's a fucking i don't understand i don't understand
either it's so good it's so good am i am i crazy perfect yeah it was perfect all of our drawings
were great every single one it's probably just it's probably just that our christ consciousnesses
are too high and the fucking the masses the masses don't appreciate homestuck and they think the the
the masses are too busy patroning dr. wool you know what you know what it's like like our christ
consciousness level is so high and we appreciate homestuck and just like christ himself who was
the biggest homestuck fan in the entire time space continuum we too are being crucified for our for
our for our high level christ consciousness when people when people scoff at us and say oh homestuck
you mean that thing with the shitty fan base and like the gray people gay they don't even have arms
no they don't even have arms bad art man bad art it's like gay i only read like i only read like
fucking i don't know marvel's marvel marvel comics number 9077 uh buttfuck bonanza starring
wolverine and and and well and the other we're all the drawings just look at that google search
something and then drew directly what they saw and none of it has any personality whatsoever
that's good art yeah i like it when my art i like it when my art just looks like a photograph please
please please sir please that's what that's what i fucking want the last thing jesus said before he
died is that uh uh uh dav xj is still possible it's the last thing he said before he was put to death
yeah um i i think they wrote a song about that um system of a down did it was called it was called
it was called that one zelda song that ever that sounded like it was by system of a down
but it actually wasn't yeah yeah it was about it was about jesus you know big fan what did we
what did we learn here today ben um i learned a lot about fractions i did i learned a lot about
decimals actually myself yeah i learned a lot about exponential uh notation uh scientific
notation uh in the dewey decimal system i'm going to drink germax and die
where can i buy some germax use use our use our fucking use our amazon affiliate link in the
description use our amazon affiliate link in the description to buy yourself some germax and kill
yourself like we're about to do no no munchie no
munchie it's not it's not healthy it's not healthy