We should standardize an intro for this.
That's what all real podcast entertainment shows do.
Yeah, we're a little aligned on branding.
I feel like that would be nice. I feel like if we just set our brand better,
then more people will be able to get into it.
And we want many people to get into it because it's the most insane asinine,
like not a real show show.
And so we need that initial branding marketing to get them into a show
that is not about marketing or having any sort of defined motivation.
I feel like the fact that The Routing Markers' Calculator is this obscure niche of a niche.
It's like the biggest part of the appeal.
I know. Yeah, you're right. But I feel like...
Like no matter what.
That it's totally unbrandable.
Yeah, it's so obscure, but it's also so specific.
I kind of like the idea of making it a show that carries itself.
It's like a big deal in spite of being the least known thing.
I love the fact that the B.C.P. or The Routing Markers' Calculator
is a completely unknown, it should be.
No one watches it.
It has the most dedicated fan base of any B.C.P. show.
And no matter what release or the content of the video,
people will rejoice that there's new R.F.C.P. films.
And then you'll have comments on normal B.C.P. episodes saying
Ben and Munchie just keep doing R.F.C.P. films.
You're better on that. Just keep doing that.
Well, we don't spoil them. We don't spoil them with the RFCK content.
I would like to hear the two things that I want to increase its brand.
And this is the only two.
I want to have a standardized intro that will take
literally less than two seconds.
And I want to release it monthly.
We should definitely release it monthly at the very least.
Are we on right now?
Yes.
Is this going to be on the show?
This discussion?
Let me just make sure.
Yes.
That's fine. I'm just wondering.
Okay, okay. Our intro.
How about...
Okay, this is genius. Check this out, right?
Okay.
It's like we each say one word, but we take turns.
So it's like, rowdy.
Fuckers.
Cop.
Killers.
Fuck.
That's pretty good.
I mean, it's a start.
All right, all right.
So R.F.C.P.ers, cop, killers.
And then we should both at the same time play.
And then whatever.
And the thing about the word play is that it's not a
like a let's play specific thing.
So we can have R.F.C.P.ers play me channel,
or we can have R.F.C.P.ers play being in the park.
Like in real life.
Yeah.
Or maybe it could be something more like do or like...
Do New York.
Or like on.
R.F.C.P.ers on Broadway.
Yeah.
R.F.C.P.ers on musical.
Imagine R.F.C.P.ers cop killers on musical.
R.F.C.P.ers in the Sports Resort.
In, in, we sports, I like that.
I like that.
We're in it.
So R.F.C.P.ers, cop, killers.
Actually, now I'm thinking do you like R.F.C.P.ers, cop, killers,
or do you like R.F.C.P.ers?
Cop, killers.
Oh, okay.
In Canon.
You are the cop killer and I am the R.F.C.P.er.
Okay.
That's, I've always forget.
Yeah, yeah.
You are the, after the rowdy fuckers, cop, killers,
they should be like a sound sting,
like a sound effect of like gunshots, like...
That's pretty good.
And I'm like,
fuckers, cop, killers.
Maybe like some police sirens.
Yeah.
And I love, I love those guys.
That we never played particularly violent gangs.
We always played baby shit.
Like we're the toughest, like the toughest fucking gangs.
Like if you just came over to selling drugs
and killing crooked cops.
That's all we have to fucking do.
I love that.
Okay, okay.
So we're gonna go with in.
Okay, I think we do R.F.C.P.ers, cop, killers.
Go back and forth like that.
And then should we do in, and then title?
In, we sports, resort.
Okay, that's good.
I like that.
When people hear that intro and get strapped in,
only to find that the podcast is primarily like we sports
and my little pony drop.
Yeah.
It's like long sections of us saying um and then and.
And then also like punctuated by moments of us getting really mad
about how the video game is too hard for us to play.
The we sports episode was particularly like incredible.
You know, there was a competition, but all,
but we were both so geared up and ready to like just like try our
all that none of us talk.
And the only time that we did talk, we were just doing ass
like insults.
God, the most you told us is don't worry.
But you can't do it.
But now we're here.
We have the webcam.
Yeah.
We're ready.
Oh yeah.
This is ready for this cop killers live.
Take two.
Yeah.
We're right.
We're fucking wrong.
Um, should we pick it up by the way?
The microphone.
Wait, say something.
Hey, it's me.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm in this episode too.
Yeah.
In the same room.
You're on the switch one.
Was I?
Yeah.
Cool.
I think you were in the three share or something.
Yeah.
We're doing strategy.
We were coming from the intro here.
You're on.
Ready.
Fuckers.
Cop.
Killers.
In.
We.
Sports.
Resort.
Baby.
Fuckers.
Fuck.
Cops.
Yeah.
I'm fucking wrong.
I want Digi to make some sort of rap.
I also want him to be rapping.
I feel like write a rap for us to produce or something.
Yes.
It's got to be like the most inner city jungle.
Yeah, I know.
You know, me and my friends in high school actually wrote a rap.
We wrote like a shitty gangster rap.
Let's use that.
I was, my gangster persona was super hard red snapper.
Yeah.
That was my, yeah.
It's bad, but here it is.
Give it up for super hard red snapper.
Get up in his grill and he's going to bust a capo yo ass.
Sprayin' out a buck shot and punchin' and kickin' and keepin' those fat beats red hot.
Like the bitch is my homie slapas guy.
No pants.
Ho slapas got the right stuff.
Always with a bunch of hoes showin' them.
He makes a bunch of hoes and wears one out and finds two more.
See, he pretty fly, but then my man Chewie is one ho stickin' ass kickin' thugger.
And that's why we call him the monkey smuggler.
Cause he go eat shit if he don't like it face.
And piss a whipper chicken ass all over the place.
Yeah, he's a god damn credit to the white race.
Ben, do you understand how the syllables of what you're saying
can easily, perfectly be changed to red for this cop though.
Instead of red hot whippersnapper.
Red hot red snapper.
Super hot red snapper.
And literally Chewy, Munchy.
This is literally the easiest song in the entire world to change.
Should I just cannibalize my old high school bullshit?
Yes, literally.
Yes.
Oh, I used to have a beat.
My friend Ryan wrote a beat for it.
And there was like a chorus.
It was like, suck it out this thugger's way.
You think you got something to say, and I'll break your knees.
It's just another thugger day.
And all the guys say, is just bitch please.
A bitch please.
This is a marketing supernova.
This is the nexus of marketing.
This is the black hole where all brands go to die.
I want the show to be more interesting.
Yeah.
But now, I think you'll get it soon.
This is your mom who gave you credit.
No, no, we have to get to it.
Let's play for me channel.
I'll be stomping on your chest.
Feels like good.
I'm going to be stomping on the cop cars hood.
Much like how I wear the KKK hood.
And the exact same tone and demeanor.
I was just going through the second verse with the rap.
And I was thinking, oh, this is actually really great.
I actually like this verse better.
But then towards the end, it really dates itself really hard
with references to Osama bin Laden and Anna Nicole Smith.
That is perfect.
It's pretty funny.
All right.
Here's what we should do afterwards.
Or even, you know, fucking on it.
All right.
Let's write this down.
We will never play the game.
We will never start playing.
This is all pre-show since we haven't done our intro yet.
So hold on.
Rowdy Fuckers USA is a mythical metropolis where Osama bin Laden
and Anna Nicole Smith are still on the hook.
Let me show you how to start.
So we should definitely work on this though.
I want you to type out this rap.
You can easily be changed to a rapper exactly a brand.
Easily.
We would need a beat.
Because like it had a beat.
But I don't have the beat anymore.
We can just get someone to produce it.
OK.
We could literally just release the beat.
I totally do not mind candle-lizing.
We literally just released the beat that someone made for Slinger Dead.
The only thing...
Wait.
They're very similar aesthetic shows.
OK.
Yeah, that's fine.
We have my rap and your show's beat.
We can combine them.
Yeah.
Perfect.
That makes sense.
All right.
Perfect.
I'll remember that.
I'll type it out.
Ask me sometime and I'll type it.
It won't take me very long.
OK.
Yeah.
And then we'll type it out.
I'll choose the lyrics to be...
Reversed.
...a popular theme.
Which I don't think will be hard.
Like just like do the first line again
but replace the name with reverse calculators.
Yeah.
Well.
OK.
Because I wrote one verse.
Well, I wrote one verse.
My friends wrote the other.
I forget which one I wrote.
Whatever.
It doesn't matter.
It's like I'm curious.
Yeah.
It's parody.
OK.
Try to...
Reversed.
Being...
Instead of your rap.
What?
What is the first verse of the rap?
I forget how it starts.
It's like...
Shit.
I can't remember how the rap that I just sang started.
Yep.
It's nothing...
This is fucking record because you...
He's literally gone out of your mind
through one mouth to the ether.
Uh...
Sss...
This is the right verse type of rap that you want.
It's Vincent and then looking up in the sky.
Because he does that literally every episode.
Red snapper.
Here's the intro.
Super hard red snapper.
What the fuck is wrong?
Wait, the super hard red snapper.
Chewie the monkey smuggler.
And the other one.
My friend Dave.
That was less involved.
I don't remember how it fucking started.
That was like a flash in the pan.
It's gone.
We're gonna start our let's play of the Wii channel.
We're not doing Wii Sports Resort?
Well we gotta make some Mii's first.
Okay.
Alright.
Enjoy the intro.
Wait.
Hold on.
It's coming.
Rowdy.
Fuckers.
Cop.
Killers.
In.
Mii Channel!
The video has officially started.
Here we are.
We're ready to do this fucking bullshit.
We are ready to start Clay the Mii Channel as hard as we can.
We're going as hard as a motherfucker.
We're gonna do this to the best of our ability.
That's really what we've got so far.
Hey, is that you?
Yes, me.
Hey, that's me.
We don't actually have to make Mii's because we got them.
Where's my...
Hey, it's Ben's.
Ben's.
It's made by God.
Yeah, you know.
Here, here, here.
I want to update my...
Wait.
I think I have to use yours.
What the fuck?
I know.
This is really fucking with the theme that we just established.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, that I'm Player One.
Yeah.
You come to me, Munchie, you come to me insisting that I be Player One.
How could you ask for shoulder responsibility?
I rash the controller out of your hand and I thrust upon you a new Wiimote.
And I said, my God.
You can tell the Wii was created at a less advanced age,
as there are only two genders to choose from.
Yeah.
Is this Mii?
Is this one?
Oh my God.
Which one's Mii?
He's all jaundiced.
I don't know.
Wait, you're just like me.
You're bottom left.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, you're somewhere between...
There I go.
You're somewhere between two, three, and four.
You're a monster.
I'm the monster no one deserves, and yet everyone shall obtain.
Oh, look, Mii.
Jumping Jack Jones.
It's the worst guy ever.
Oh, I never told the Wii U Torturer character description.
What is the Wii U Torturer?
The Wii U Torturer is a character that I came up with for a...
Nate, you're looking hairy.
I'm busy.
Okay.
It's a character I came up with for a series of novels that have not started yet
and could probably be called failing and never to exist.
But God damn it, one day they will probably never.
But still, we're working on it.
I mean, I've made a novel idea.
It's quite a novel idea.
Anyway, there's a character called the Wii U Torturer.
His real name is Arthur Wii Allen.
And he...
I forget the entirety of his story, but just first to show that he stomps,
like as hard as he can, Wii U's over and over again.
It is a fetishistic urge that he smashes Wii U gamepads.
Only Wii U's?
Yes, only Wii U's.
Because he wanted to be Sony PlayStation 5 bomb for his first day.
First day?
But his parent, who I believe is the evil CEO of Twitch in the story, Tom Twitch,
got him a Wii U instead, which was about 1,500 generation of video games behind.
Well, God, I mean, I can understand why he's a little fucked up over it.
I know.
And that's why he's dedicated his life to torturing Wii U's.
You need some fan of the Wii U Torturer, even though I already have a design firm,
so you know what you make will be good.
What is my...
What do I...
Is this...
I kind of like that one on the bottom right.
This one?
I mean, it's a little small.
Maybe you could go back one.
Go back one.
This one?
No, no, it's back one page.
I think that the middle one there, bottom middle...
That one's okay.
This is me.
Yeah.
I mean, right?
Yeah, I mean, it's not far off.
Just keep going a little bit.
Maybe it'll be like a slightly, slightly fro-ier one.
Yeah, that's what we need.
There's no Jew fro.
The Wii character creator is so fucking limited.
Even on the Switch, it's so fucking bare-bones and shit.
Yeah.
Well...
Yeah, fuck it.
You win some...
What are my eyebrows?
Well, they're kind of triangular.
Okay.
Go over a page.
Look at me again.
Kind of like knuckle jewelry.
They're kind of like...
They're thickest in the middle.
They kind of get thicker in the middle.
Go back one.
I don't know what I have.
This one?
That one's not bad.
I was looking at that one.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, what about this?
If I angle this a certain way.
Try that one.
You know, actually, top right.
Yeah, you know what?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, this is the real shit.
All right.
When I was a little kid, I used to always, like, without question.
Go for these eyes.
Really?
I mean, they've certainly got their charms.
I have, like, thin eyes, right?
A little bit.
Okay, here, guys.
They're kind of all...
What about these?
I like the one to the right of that.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's better.
Okay.
Whoa.
This is a charm.
God.
I have a big, fat one.
So either this one or this one.
Probably this one.
I think that one.
Yeah.
Shit.
That's good, right?
No, that's not that big.
Okay.
Yeah, I like that.
I like that.
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
You have a small mouth.
That's small.
Do I have a noticeable lips?
Yeah, yeah, they're noticeable, but they're not huge.
Oh, no.
You have a...
You have, like, a pretty pronounced, like, curve, you know?
Okay, like this.
No.
It's like that.
Wait, to the right, to the right, on the bottom.
Make it small.
I'm pretty close.
One more down.
There.
Yeah?
Maybe move it down a little.
Well, actually, no.
No, it's good there.
Okay.
I think we're...
Actually, you know what?
Make your eyes a little smaller.
Okay.
Actually, there might be...
Yes.
Okay, we're getting somewhere.
Okay.
Go try the next page.
All right.
I fucking love making knees, by the way.
I know, this is great.
I used to do this.
Literally, what I would do every sleepover was we would want to play Super Smash,
which was probably me and my offline friends,
but we'd just get so caught up in making knees
and we'd just spend the entire night making knees
and just telling stories about what we'd done
during the most absolutely incredible...
Going over it?
I mean...
I think these ones are pretty good.
I like...
Okay.
I don't think there...
There's none that I think is an obviously better fit,
but I think that there are other ones that could work.
I feel like this mouth does not fit me simply
because it does not communicate that I'm a little shit.
I mean, I think it looks pretty...
I think this one actually...
Actually, that one's pretty good, too.
That I'm a little shit.
I think it's a little less...
...photo.
It's a little less anatomically accurate,
but it's more like...
...totally accurate.
Spiritually, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
That's pretty good.
All right.
I like fitly kind of glasses, right?
Yeah.
I wish I could...
I mean, I guess...
I wish they had half-brands.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Actually, wait, can...
No.
Maybe use the bigger, the wider ones.
I think that looks a little closer
to the reality of the situation.
This guy looks nice.
This guy actually looks like me.
I look like me.
I make like, based off the way I draw myself.
Yeah.
Which, oh god, you know what I do that I fucking hate?
Or is that I always...
I do the webcomic artist curse
of making myself look better than I do in real life.
Yeah.
I kind of do...
I just made my guy look as generic as possible.
So, I don't know.
I mean, everyone does it.
I know.
It's...
I don't blame it.
Like, it annoys me when I see other people do it,
but not too much,
because I totally understand why the compulsion is there.
Yeah.
Because you don't want to like...
Just like, like, no...
And like, constantly portray yourself as being...
Yeah.
You guys have a poop.
Like, the last part of a poop doesn't want to come out.
Oh my god.
You feel it, like, inside your butt all day.
That's what the, like, shit stool is for.
Like, the thing that you put your feet up on?
Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
Dude, I have never used it.
But I have heard.
Oh, okay, okay.
It helps with that.
There are so many points I want to make here.
Like, if an entire podcast
is based off of this short exchange right here.
By the way, we are literally the green triangle
of intellect right now.
What does that mean?
We're a range of...
I don't know, but I agree and support it.
Okay.
First of all, I have heard the shit stool.
Does that mean that all intellect dies?
Yeah.
It goes and never comes back.
I've never tried the shit stool,
but I've heard of it,
and so now whenever I take a shit stool,
I go like this,
as big as I can.
I still have never tried the technique.
There was a chair in my bathroom,
like next to my toilet.
Yeah, he did!
I used it as the shit stool.
Oh, my God.
We are on the same wavelength.
I haven't had to,
but maybe I should.
Maybe I should just fight that bullet.
Do it.
We all got to make it up.
And Roddy fuckers,
fuckers, fuckers!
It is!
It's a shit stool.
Sponsored by the shit stool.
I had an irritable bowel syndrome.
They had to stick someone's hand up my ass.
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Wait, did it go away?
Yes.
I didn't know it could go away.
I think I had some sort of weird option of it,
where it was like I had the symptoms of it,
but I didn't actually have it.
Oh, God.
Very sick.
So the last shit,
the experience I have of trying to get the shit out,
like the last one that you've just tried,
was every part of the shit forever.
Oh, my God.
So I spent...
Jesus, bro.
All right.
The real triangle of intellect, ladies and gentlemen.
Hashtag that shit.
Do you want to...
Is it here?
How do we...
Yeah, this is kind of weird, but I'm into it.
Okay.
Yeah, looks good.
And so I would be in the toilet for like two hours.
Oh, two hours.
Camera, too.
I didn't even notice that one.
Yeah, dude.
Uh, fuck you.
It's static.
Mangle.
Wait, yeah, okay.
Let's turn the mic.
So it goes this...
Then again.
Well, who cares?
We can breathe down.
So, there you go.
Yeah.
Once you hear a little louder, dude.
Jess, like you have short hair.
Like, I would describe it as like some sort of friendly,
a hitchhiker that is too friendly.
And so you don't trust them and you drive past them.
Good.
You look like...
Like you work in a library.
I like that.
I love...
Libraries are like the only...
I love the fact that they're still a place where people are not allowed to make noise.
Or like a newsroom.
Or like a printing room.
Yeah, you want to make me?
Oh, hell yeah.
Do you have any experience in making a book?
You can make yourself a beard.
Let's see here.
I guess the beard obviously sucks.
Should I make it me that looks like me?
Or should I make a fucking freak of hell?
Make one that looks like you and then we can do one.
Hey, what's up with the...
The OBS is not showing the entire thing.
What do you mean?
Well, like, look how little of the video it's capturing.
Um...
Yeah, sure.
Has it been doing it this whole time?
Yeah, but I don't really care.
It sucks.
Man, it's fine.
No, get the whole thing in there, man.
I am. I'm doing that right now.
Hey.
Yeah?
I'll beat you up.
Listen, man, that would be funny if it weren't physically impossible.
Yeah.
Come back with some real-ass coming next time, kid.
Well...
Listen, I bet you didn't even go to Los Angeles.
I mean...
God, I don't want to dox my birthday.
Uh...
Wait, I can put a question mark.
That's not fucking paranoid I've become.
I don't want to dox my birthday.
Yeah, they can find me.
Someone might give me a fucking present.
I don't want that shit.
Jesus.
Someone might be nice.
All right.
This is the real shit, right?
That's not cool.
It's professional.
Dude, do you want to get underneath the mic?
Oh, yeah.
What should I do to get out from underneath the mic?
Uh, we...
Since we're doing...
Wait.
I need it to get out from under the...
Under its thumb.
Hold on.
You can put it backwards.
How is this...
Okay, wait.
How is this any better?
Move that around much here.
And then move the thing around to its axis.
This is some fucking...
Bermuda's Triangle of Intellect Geometry.
Arrange the...
You know, point the mic towards the center of the galaxy.
Let it...
Then Rhymoscopilus will become 10 times faster.
I made me a favorite to help this other guy.
Well, play your cards right.
Maybe one day you'll earn that title.
Well, it's not any better because it's still right in front of you.
Yeah.
I think it's true.
Favorite color.
It used to be yellow.
Don't dox favorite color, Cassie.
I'm taking it back.
I don't give a fuck.
That actually looks quite bad.
Yeah.
Unfortunate.
I'll do purple.
Here we go.
I'm always black.
Well, make sure the audience are right.
How will you know?
Say something.
No.
Yeah, you say something.
Hey, there.
I think I just have a powerful diaphragm.
I just have some sort of...
Whoa.
It's working.
Are you? Because I'm not seeing anything.
Hello.
Ooh.
Hi, it's me, Munchie.
It's working like...
I don't think it's getting in here.
I mean, I'm sorry, audience, that I'm like...
Hello.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, it's...
I think it's just the backside of the mic.
Wait, this is the back of the mic?
No, I just rotated it, I think.
And so I think...
I have no fucking clue.
I have no fucking...
Hey, hey, hey.
It's me saying words.
Hold on.
I'm sure this sounds really good for them.
It's fine.
It's getting in our voice.
Yeah, it's fine.
What else could we be recording from?
I don't know.
It thinks I'm louder when I'm over here.
You know what it probably is doing.
That was perfect.
Yeah, it says so.
That's Jesse for you.
Yep.
Got it.
Hello.
Yes, I forgot.
I forgot how much I love making beats.
Oh, you know what it's doing?
What?
Which is fine.
Is it recording through the laptop speakers?
Yes.
I know it.
That's fine.
No, it sucks to ask.
So can we just get this fucking microphone out of here?
Yes.
The microphone is not recording?
No.
What the fuck?
Complete waste.
This could have sounded really bad then.
I love that concern effect.
I don't really mind that.
Yeah, okay.
That's a bummer.
I feel like we're in a right focus like this.
You don't care about stuff like audio quality.
Yeah.
Yeah, the problem is that this is not plugged in is the problem.
Let's just plug this in and see what happens.
You know, I read somewhere like I'm like cracked.
That like parting your hair to the right looks more masculine to the left.
Like with the part on the right?
That's what was my question because like I was reading the article and I'm like, wait,
what do you mean by parted on the right?
Like going right or from the right?
Well, part on the right, which I do not do.
I part my hair on the left.
So the hair goes from the left to the right.
Like my hair naturally does it like this and sometimes I do it.
I don't know.
Hold on, wait.
But like I had a bunch of examples from like pop culture.
How like Captain Kirk's hair is always like this.
Superman's hair is like this.
But Clark Kent's hair is like this because he's a weakling.
Like you think that you think that the creators of Superman would have had to
have read that crack article to make that creative decision.
They sent one cracked article back to 1978.
So that they could get Superman's hair right.
That's the only thing that was ever done with time travel.
After that we threw the technology away.
We were like, okay, we've got to steal this away.
But first we can make one change.
We have to choose carefully.
Oh, wait.
It is.
I think it's just going to record through this until we restart it,
I don't really care about doing and I don't, am I?
You want me to just let it go?
Yeah, just let it go.
So if we get rid of this thing?
Yeah, it cares.
Okay.
I mean, the people, oh my God, Jesse.
Oh, there it is.
This is the most fucking N with G God.
Oh, shit.
I look at this guy's eyes and like like literally like time has stopped.
My life has paused.
And I have just watched for version finale five times in reverse.
He's so cool.
But is that what you have?
Yeah, you're green eyes.
Yeah.
That's fucking like, that's character style.
That's like clear as that.
Yeah, yeah, I have green eyes like F and Jack.
Oh, fuck!
Oh, you think that's where they got it from?
Do you think that's where they got my eye filler from?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I had to come from someone.
Where else?
Yeah.
I had to come from someone.
It's always done somewhere.
All of these buses are mods.
Oh, yeah, yeah, Skull.
Yeah.
Skull.
Hey, should we move like laptop?
Nah, fuck it.
Oh my God, I love that.
That guy knows what's up.
It's the PCP guy mouth.
He is, he totally is.
Here, guys, do you want to pause for one second
and then just check and make sure the audio is here
quite listenable?
Okay, sure.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, Jesse, screamer will be funny between cuts.
Wait, what?
Screamer, quick.
We're back now, we're back.
Does the laptop not have speakers?
No, it's connected to like two of the Elgato's
so I can't really tell what it's saying,
like I can't believe the headphones in.
Hey, I'm going to show you, here comes back
when you're still on the bus.
Sorry, recording again?
Yeah.
Okay, a second.
Where do they miss?
I don't know.
Jesse finished as me.
I want to do like that.
That's pretty much it.
Yeah.
Here, hold on.
Check out this.
Oh, shit.
Here comes Backman.
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo.
What's up?
Hey, Backman.
Hey, this is a high-end product.
What, a free base?
No, Backman, drugs are bad.
Yeah, can't help it.
Okay, I've heard this.
I have not seen this animation.
Whoa!
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
I feel like Backman is me.
Every single day.
Every day when I wake up, this isn't required anywhere,
but whenever I wake up, I come down and say,
hey, motherfuckers, who wants a freebie?
I'm high, I'm crack.
And I say that every time I come down to this.
Can you say in the video that's just like six minutes
of Hagrid and Harry Potter, of him like,
I'm Harry, just Harry.
He's like, no.
Who is your dad, right?
Like back, like, do you guys know what I'm talking about?
No.
Good, look it up.
Uh, fuck.
I'm not sure what to type,
but type like you're a wizard, Harry.
Or something like that.
Make some fucked up shit.
Coming right up.
I want to do like a skit of like,
if people treat it like how they want to look in real life,
like how they want to look in games.
Like a guy goes to a plastic surgeon,
and like, he's like, look,
I want purple skin.
I want eyes like Brock from Pokemon.
I want to be fat as fucking shit.
Hop to it, you fuck.
I want to be a monster.
Not this.
It's like a, it's like a, like an animation.
This is the top right there.
Is that heck?
Let's see.
This is different than what it's just been.
They're just Harry.
I suppose the lines are just lines.
And gods are just gods.
You know, you know what this has the same tone of?
It's Goat and Seller.
Yeah, exactly.
It's that kind of like bullshit.
Bullshit.
Alright, I want this nigger.
I want, okay, first of all, nigger.
First of all, nigger.
I want this nigger to be like cut,
the kind of cut where you can still beat him up.
Another one.
Yeah, like model cut.
Yeah, like tiny weights.
Or just company has aids.
So a strong breeze will push him over.
I think you want that one.
I think you want that sunken cheeks.
What if, what if you're an anorexic girl
and you wanted to kill yourself because you were anorexic.
But because you were anorexic, you were wobbly.
So you got up on like a lead and you're like,
you know what, I don't actually want to kill myself,
but a breeze pushed you over because you were anorexic.
I feel, well, I imagine
he wouldn't be too,
this guy looks awful.
Yeah.
He's, he looks impossible.
That's like the AIDS hat.
Yeah, yeah.
What's it, what's it with me hats being like the most
the me hats are like the most iconically awful video game
mechanism or any sort of thing from a video game.
Most iconically terrible thing.
Yeah.
Like it's like they knew that they would never approach
like the breadth of what a hat could be.
So they didn't even try it.
I mean, just pick one and did it.
All right.
I guess that'll do.
Would you make one that like looks like your avatar
because they have to be.
Yeah, I've, I've done it.
It's great.
Actually, I'll do that next.
Okay.
Let me flex my mean hats.
On my way.
I think you want real thin.
My, my, my, my stoner fringe.
He's always come over to my house.
He would just make me literally all night.
And he would just explain to me what kind of stoner parties
he's gone to.
And so he comes up with stuff like Ferdinand,
zzzzzzz music.
Sign.
Seed and a lot of.
Who.
Yeah.
I feel like that's our dynamic.
In your.
Yes.
Dude, we should put that at like the beginning of every episode.
You know what's fucked up?
We should make them our mascots.
You know what's fucked up too is that the Applejack's background is literally the same
color as like the background of Roger Scott's podcast.
Oh, the green.
Yeah.
Yes.
Shut your face, dad.
I'm totally me.
Me.
Eating Applejack's from A to B.
That's just the first thing that comes to your head no matter what.
No matter what.
I'm not a fan of the Dramium.
Bye.
We the hell no dogs.
Yo, I'm high on crack.
Wanna free me?
No, I'm straight laced.
I only smoke the natural ganja as God demands.
Yes, she was this Rupert not God to you.
It's free.
This guy looks nice.
I want him to teach me to ride a bicycle.
He kind of looks like my dead grandpa.
Really?
Yeah.
Nice.
I know.
It doesn't look anything like my dead grandpa.
This is like the happiest nigger I've seen in a while.
I'm really uncomfortable with the use of the hard R on an actual person of color.
What a hot take.
Yeah.
He's not a person yet.
He will soon.
That's true.
He doesn't have rights yet.
Yeah.
Those are his eyebrows.
We haven't cut the umbilical cord.
Yes.
What a piece of shit.
This guy looks like Gendo Ikari.
Can you imagine how much better it would be?
He's right here among us.
What?
Gendo Ikari.
So much better.
He didn't get the part.
He was a method actor.
I just love the idea of Gendo so much that he just became Gendo for the rest of his life.
He's got no body.
Just like Gendo in real life.
Gendo has navy blue and red, right?
Yeah.
I like how on the capture, our picture-in-a-picture camera is just tying up so that you can't
see the body.
I forgot.
Hold on.
I have to do something important.
What?
Is it suicide?
Order transform.
Order.
Not order.
I'll do it.
It doesn't make any sense.
It sounds scary.
Alright, let's see.
Man fuck.
Okay, I said I was going to make me, but I don't want some anymore.
I'm going to have something cooked up.
One little change is all it takes to go from a human being to a fat shit.
Do you think we can afford to get some BBW whenever there's got to be some time?
Can we afford it?
I don't know.
Can we afford not to is the question.
No.
Well, I don't know.
What happened?
What?
You lost the signal.
Wait, wait.
Oh, it's back.
Okay.
False alarm.
All right.
Here we go.
Actually, yeah.
There we go.
Okay.
I have centered the webcam within the screen.
So now you can literally not avoid it no matter what you do.
Literally in the center of the screen.
That's awful.
That's the worst.
No, that's good.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess it's in the spirit.
But it's pretty fucking big.
Oh, you know what we should do?
We should make a rather as popular as the Valentine's Day special.
Did you say Valentine's Day?
Yeah.
Okay.
Good.
I don't know what it would be about.
Valentine's Day special.
Well, it would probably be about how much we love killing cops.
What do we love?
We love killing cops.
We love breaking mops.
We love.
We love practicing.
We love killing cops and breaking mops.
Off in our assholes.
The end.
How long do you think you can take before something like a dick of your ass would hurt?
Like how many inches do you need to take?
I mean, I think it would hurt right away.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't think there's...
Unless we got like thicker at the bottom.
Yeah.
It's like a needle.
Dude.
Oh my God.
What if you had like a, like, not like a needle pin, but like a small pin.
Like you could poke and stab with it.
I feel like that would be ideal if you're sucking out the juice of the clit.
For pop and that's hard to pop.
You're sucking out the juice of the clit.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, you're dead.
Oh my God.
Oh, no.
Dude, is that shinging?
Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da.
Yes.
Here we go.
Now we're talking.
Now we're cooking.
Oh my God.
Holy shit.
Pretty cool, right?
Is that a triforce?
It will be.
Hold on.
Eyebrows, these can go a little...
Oh, they all could push together.
Oh, what?
Mouth.
Yeah, it's a little better.
Okay, yes.
What are you trying to do here?
I'm just trying to make something great.
They'll stay on the test of time.
And something to be remembered for.
That's a humble goal.
What do you think it's like after you die?
It's probably a lot like this.
Yeah.
Dude, what?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel like it was just the meat channel on week.
That's a black mirror episode.
I could deal.
I could probably deal with anything.
I'd take anything and I'd be happy for it.
I know.
I want no hair.
Here we go.
Oh my...
I think this is it.
I think I've done it.
Well...
Day is...
Wait, hold on.
Yeah.
That'll be his mouth.
No, yeah, just be really close like that.
Yeah!
Wait, is it better if it's up here?
I feel like below is better.
Yeah, I agree.
It kind of looks like a butt.
No.
Yeah.
That's awful, yeah.
Yeah, just give him some cool shade.
Give him a little beard.
You don't have to be an asshole for beard.
That's actually not too bad.
I almost like it.
But it's a little too human.
It kind of looks like fucking...
Dude, is that Gendo card?
No.
I was going to say ndeki.
Oh yeah.
He looks like...
He looks a bit like an egg.
I don't want this.
Handlebar, handlebar, handlebar, handlebar, handlebar, handlebar, handlebar, handlebar, handlebar, handlebar, handlebar, handlebar, handlebar.
I'm not even like getting gun sex artifacts.
Like you were in stream, you know, just be that.
Yeah.
My baby!
They shot my baby!
The Gendo Capitalist Revolution is here!
Nah, I don't like this.
Handlebar.
He's getting too many gimmicks, he's getting overcomplicated.
Yeah!
My god, he's like a bum now!
Oh my god, he's a praying mantis!
How did I...
Did I fucking do it or what?
You did it.
Did I fucking nail it or what?
Did I knock it out of the park?
I didn't.
You know what, actually, hold on, let me experiment with drugs and lesbianism.
I think this guy was the original bug that started the bug war.
I think this is the genesis of all bug war activities.
Yeah, this is Joey Bug War.
Joey Bug War.
No, just Joey Bug.
Joey Bug.
Uh, I think...
It was named after him, you know, Bug War.
Joey Bug.
I think the color you originally had was the best.
Yeah.
You think so?
We can't have everyone be black.
That's true.
That would be it.
In the words of God, we can't have everyone be black.
Oh my god!
I'm gonna make some white people now.
That can't possibly go wrong.
Yeah.
Fucking...
Okay, God creating humans fake.
Like, humans evolving fake.
The real shape is higher conscious beings are just plain, like, me-maker,
and whatever me's they make aren't a lower level of conscious, like a lower dimension.
It's just me-makers all the way down is what you're saying?
Yeah, exactly.
So, like, the 11th and 12th dimensions are making, like, human-like me's,
and human-like me's are making weird, fucked up monster ghosts,
and those are what probably are the lower dimensions.
Uh, what do you think?
Like this?
Or like this?
I think the one you were just on.
This one?
Yeah, I think that one's the best.
Okay.
Uh...
Oh!
Make them really thin and really, like, small.
What a creepy creature.
Oh!
No, not fat.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, like that.
Small.
Yeah.
He's a bug.
He's Joey Bug.
It's not small.
It's pretty small.
Okay, should I quit?
Go to his name.
Joey Bug.
Um...
I'm...
Jorg...
I'm gonna be honest.
I like Joey Bug War better.
Right, that's fine.
Oh!
Joey Bug War.
Is that French?
Yeah, Joey Bug War.
Joey Bug Wadi.
Okay.
Joey Bug War.
Yeah, female.
Female Joey.
Yeah.
Like a kangaroo.
Definitely a favorite.
Birthday is, uh, 11...
20...
Uh...
He's a few months late,
but he still is ready to smoke that weed.
There we go.
That's Joey Bug War.
Joey Bug War.
Any creator?
God.
He makes all the best of me and stuff.
Save him quick.
Hell yeah.
Hell yeah, Joey Bug War.
Joey Bug War!
You open the...
The fucking Bible.
Oh, look at...
Oh, look at him!
What a good little booge.
You know what game is my fucking shit?
What's fucking Mario...
Not Mario.
You want Balor Revolution?
I love that game.
You've never heard of it.
You've never even heard of it.
Wait, what's Balor Revolution?
Balor Revolution was like the other state.
Like stadium for weed.
Um...
Fake.
You made that up.
This TV...
The colors are so fucking blown out.
You're asking me blown out.
Fucking smoke a pile.
They just washed the shit.
You've washed the shit.
They've been turned into fucking goo.
Disintegrated.
Whoa, okay.
He's got nice hair.
That's Lieutenant Surge!
This is the very fucking capitalist commentary you come for.
Create a guy who...
His wife just divorced him.
And so he burned down his house with his kids in it.
And now he's on the run.
From the cop killers, because he is a cop.
Oh, yes.
That's a twist.
You know, the only...
You know, when a cop goes bad,
you gotta call him a cop too late.
Regular cops can't hit you.
You're a special branch of the police.
You're a cop too.
You're sanctioned by the fucking city.
Yeah.
Yeah, the ratty fucker is a cop killer.
He's a good boy.
We're civil servants.
Like, with us around, people don't have to live in fear of police brutality.
Really?
All I have to do is wear that Oscar brutality.
The mayor gets, like, a speeding ticket.
Get me the cop killers.
We gotta clean up this city.
Oh, yes, sir.
It's too much.
Our pleasure.
We'll take our payment in the...
in the gum, please.
Oh, my God.
Literally, yeah.
Literally, yes.
Please send one month's worth of rent and pizza.
For every job.
For every, yeah.
Don't make us buy it ourselves.
Pay our rent and give us the pizza.
Yes.
We do not deal in money.
We deal in debt shops.
We do it for the convenience.
You think we got on this job?
We think we got on this job to make money?
We got it, we got it, because we wouldn't have to think about it.
You know, it's easy.
You know, to kill a few cops, live another month.
Yeah.