3, 2, 1, DROP!
You know what they say, a bitch on her knees is worth two in a hand basket in the black market.
Agreed.
Welcome to The Rowdyfuckers' live coverage.
You'll never meet a more hardcore set of jugglers and banksters and criminals.
Brought to you in the third dimension. We've just come from jugglers, Take Washington.
We were marching for our rights to exist and procreate as jugglers.
And to be members of the Dark Carnival.
With decriminalized jugglers, we're not a fucking gang we're an art form.
ICP does not produce no violence. It changes your fucking brain to make you a better person.
Basically, it's how I feel.
It's like those fat cats in Washington. They don't know about miracles.
They don't fucking get it.
They've never seen a miracle in their entire fucking life.
They've never listened to fucking Carnival, Carnage, or any of that shit.
All they fucking know is how to smoke cigars, use taxpayer money to emit greenhouse gases.
They don't know anything.
They're just shoveling government tax money into greenhouse gas into the furnace.
They don't know anything about fucking renewable energy.
They don't know anything about clown noises.
They don't know anything about getting fucking jiggied with Wii Sports, the greatest game ever fucking made.
They just don't know, but we're gonna show them.
President Donald J. Trump, this is for you.
This is gonna prove to you that jugglers are worthy of being a recognized citizen.
Think about what you're about to see, long and hard.
Get the fucking neurons fired.
We're going on Fox News.
Soon enough, you're gonna see this.
And if you see this on cable television, on Fox News, know that your fucking kids are not safe.
I don't know why I'm looking at it. Your kids are not safe.
We're gonna fight each other.
In both the online world and off.
Yeah, yeah. We're gonna battle.
We're gonna do battle here in the real world in my house.
Here in the ATL.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here in Washington DC, just off the streets, we went to a random house and fucking here we are to protect our rights.
It was just like, I was just there in full clown makeup with a picket sign.
Like with just a picture of me in full clown makeup, in the crowd around me.
The picket sign was exactly identical to the scene before me.
And it really made a powerful statement to those bad cats in Washington.
They don't believe their own eyes.
We're gonna fucking run them for all their worth.
We're gonna fucking slap them up. We're gonna fucking pat them down.
We're gonna fucking turn them inside out.
We're gonna fucking, you know, we're gonna fucking need them.
We're gonna like whisk them around.
We're gonna fucking add some second hot sauce in there.
We're gonna fucking drink them.
We're gonna drink them up. We're gonna drink them down.
Stupid clown hairs.
That's what we want. We want the clown.
We want to be associated.
Okay, let's just fucking play the game.
Yeah, let's play Wii Sports.
Before we can play Wii Sports, we have to make our own fucking Mi Sonas.
We have to make our own for Sonas.
Yeah, yeah.
With N.
I've made many of Mi before.
Yeah.
I have like a patented formula that produces incredible results.
Unlike Wii U, I have a ton of Mi's.
Pretty much all of them made at 3 o'clock in the morning.
Here, here.
I'm gonna go...
I've already created myself, but it's like a gay version of myself.
Nice.
Actually, you know what? Fuck it.
I'm just gonna use the gay version of myself.
You make yours.
Oh, okay.
Alright.
I've like whitewashed myself in my own memory.
Wait, wait, wait.
Why can't I see me?
Are you in control?
I think so.
Hold on.
Try now.
Or here, just use mine.
What?
Fuck it.
I don't know.
Why don't I use mine?
Well, I don't know.
It just fucking works for some reason.
Well, yeah, it does.
You're in your menu.
Wait, what the fuck?
You're picking your me.
I think.
Maybe this is why the other remote wasn't working.
No, your light is on.
I know.
I think you just can't use two emotes in the me thing.
I don't know why.
Okay.
Just fucking use my controller.
My God.
Is this making new yet?
Yeah.
Alright, here we go.
Here we go.
Start from scratch.
Check out this cool choker.
I got it.
I was doing that first.
I was doing it with my black cop killer version.
Yeah.
I have the white purity version, which stands for fucking police dominance and fucking police
state.
Which one?
I think I use the...
This is so limited option.
There's like a thousand.
This one's mine.
It's yours.
Yeah, I own it.
Remember me Tomo?
Remember when that was real?
Yes.
What a good three days that was.
Yeah, me Tomo was pretty good for like a week there.
I had some good laughs.
I had some good times with me Tomo.
Made a couple of sweet tweets.
You probably came juggling down.
Juggling down.
Honk.
There, there's my hair.
Oh my God.
That looks just like your hair.
I know, dude.
I know.
Unbelievable.
I want like this, but I want it like to be brown.
No, that comes later.
Oh, okay.
That comes later.
Uh, these eyebrows.
These eyebrows are fucking making me thirsty.
Not like that.
Is it like that?
No, that is not at all.
My hair looks so bad right now.
I like tried to like fluff it and it didn't work.
Look how Serena looks in your online persona though.
Yeah.
That's all that matters.
That's what I am.
Yeah, that's how I'm supposed to be.
All the, all the jobs make fun of me when I'm walking down the street and full of clown,
juggalo makeup.
I'll make fun of me and fucking arrest me and whatnot.
Every day when you're walking down the street and full of clown makeup.
They all make fun of me and fucking arrest me and say that I'm fucking illegal and I
can't be a juggalo anymore.
But when I, when I fucking go on my online RuneScape persona and when I start role playing,
when I start fucking ERPing, then this is how I look like and this, this is the real
me.
This is the true me.
No, that's not right.
Dude.
I think it's a formula.
I, yeah, but I forget it.
Is it this?
No.
Your eyes are for a part of this.
You look like a fucking...
A friend.
Man, what was the one that I used to use?
Actually, I have pictures on my Maitomo or on my Twitter from Maitomo.
You know what?
I'm going to look it up.
Excellent.
I'm going to look it up for maximum trees.
Fuck.
Just hold on everyone.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to waste your time.
No.
We're not going to have this.
It's not about wasting time.
No.
It's about churning pure profit.
I, I, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's about churning pure profit.
I, I, I mean saving juggalos.
Pay no attention to that last statement.
Oh god.
Yeah.
Here we go.
We swear we're one of you.
Please continue to donate to our PayPal to ensure the future of the juggalo race.
Please set up recurring payments to the Rowdyfuckers cop killers.
A PayPal account.
Untraceable.
Do not leave your real name.
Uh, do not mention our real name.
The private cop killers can only be donated to through Bitcoin.
Yeah.
We, we, we have a partnership with Dogecoin actually.
And only an installment.
Well, only an install, you can only pay in Dogecoin, but you can only donate an installment's
worth one bit more.
So that's like 18,000 Dogecoins or something.
Uh, okay.
Here we go.
Got to look at my profile.
Got to go to media.
You're going to, you're going to be there awhile.
Yeah, but it'll be worth it.
You're going to be there while kid.
It'll be worth it.
Trust me.
Fucking.
Look at this.
Look at this child.
Oh shit.
The screen went black, bro.
Where?
Oh, uh.
Wow.
It's, it's tearing.
Let me just change the uh.
The settings.
Excellent.
Still select in?
Yeah.
Uh, screen saver done.
Wait, we're going to have to change power settings.
Oh my god.
This is our best episode ever.
Our set up right now is that we have like a webcam facing us, like a laptop up on top
of the television.
Like Vanity, I guess.
Then we have the, the TV and then Bin's 3DS is recording the screen of the fucking thing.
So both of these laptops have built in webcams.
We can't get even of them to work.
We could not fucking figure out how to actually operate them.
And then the mic connects to the 3DS.
So it's a fucked up weird saying, but you don't have to.
So I'm recording this through my 3DS.
Yeah.
The one that was paid for by my kickstarter.
For the, for the, for the Pokemon sun.
Dude, you send this video to all your kickstarter backers so they can get the full experience
of like, like, like, like every dollar they're paid with is going directly to this.
Yeah.
See, it's, it's, it's a cascade.
It's a cascading effect.
It's an S cascade.
This is the same width and like gravitas that cascaded has.
Okay.
At least in my opinion.
I feel like I'm getting closer.
I'm getting closer to the truth.
Striking pure fucking gold.
Which one of us would be Violin J and which one would be Shaggy Too Dope?
Um, that's tough because, because...
Keep in mind, Violin J is way skinnier nowadays.
So it's like not fat.
I mean...
I mean like relatively.
Well, who, which one's the brains of the operation and which one's the brawn?
I would say Violin J is extremely intelligent.
Yeah.
I would say that as well.
He has so much wisdom.
He talks about like being poor.
Yeah.
Beating women.
Smart.
Those are the only two things.
But trust me, there's a lot to say on that.
Smart man.
Good man.
Where are you goddamn?
I hate the image that's on screen right now.
It doesn't look like it's not how I want to be.
I think it looks exactly like you.
For better or for worse.
It's actually, it's actually closer than I'm comfortable with.
It's in the uncanny valley.
That's unfortunate.
Hey Jackie.
Are we keeping you awake?
No.
All right.
I have options.
Then let us continue.
Excellent.
They're here.
I know it.
Our Juggalo names are like
Carcat, Vantaz.
And Therese Pyro.
Yeah.
Original.
Oh god.
I know they're here.
I know they're almost there.
I'm almost to the promised land of Mitomo.
Possibly.
I might have missed them.
This is like the most dangerous thing I've ever done in my life.
Yeah, it's pretty bad.
This right here.
I'm going to die.
That's going to get me.
I'm going to give you the little Southern style right here.
The old, the old.
The old fucking workaround.
The old shakeshack.
I'm going to give you the clockwork orange he says.
Taping a fucking baking clock to an orange.
Come on.
Come now.
I know, I know, I'm in the right spot.
I'm in like the right era.
The viewers demand fucking expertise in this area.
Well, that's what I'm doing.
Art takes time.
Oh my god.
I'm just looking at my old art and I'm just such a genius.
I'm struck by my incredible skill and prowess.
Right here.
Uh.
There's that time that I ate an entire bottle's worth of multivitamins that had congealed
into a single puck.
That was pretty good.
That's pretty good.
That was a pretty good day.
That sort of lines up.
That lines up.
Yeah, yeah.
That's in character.
Frankly, I think Ben St. has become flanderized lately.
I agree.
I think he's been away from what he originally was.
What was I originally?
You know, unbelievable wisdom and fucking intelligence.
Yeah.
Nowadays, the writers are only playing up the fucking gross aspects of them.
Yeah, I have been flanderized.
I'm complex, damn it.
It's time to get back to the...
You know, I'll just nowadays start drama and make fun of brownies.
It's time to go back to the unbelievable fucking mirth and wisdom.
I found it.
Oh my god.
There we go.
The exact same.
I found myself.
They might not even have that on this version.
Wait, can you not do like pupil colors?
No, you can.
But I don't have that eye shape.
Oh god, no.
Phone, don't fuck me.
Don't fuck.
Do not fuck, please.
No, no, they do have that eye shape.
Wait, wait, wait.
Do they?
Oh yeah.
Second row, third to third.
Oh, I need yours.
Yeah.
Bumble fuck.
I put it over here.
Okay, stupid.
Oh, I said something wrong because I'm stupid.
I'm gonna keep wrapping anyway.
Yeah, it was this one.
Yeah, that.
Okay, it just looks wrong because the pupils.
Yeah, brown.
You can put them...
No, far apart, no.
No, no, it's like this.
But then I put the glasses over it and it looks okay.
Trust me.
Pupils.
Fucking pupil colors.
Where?
No.
It looks so light on the screen.
Uh, whatever.
We're gonna be zoomed so fucking out.
We're gonna be, we're gonna fucking take that.
We're gonna zoom it out.
Yeah, you're right.
There should be a Disneyland ride based off
the Riforce Cop killers.
Oh, I wholeheartedly.
What an Epcot, actually.
Not even, not even Disney World in an Epcot.
Uh...
Dead Kids the Future of Fucking Humanity.
Dead kids are the future of humanity.
Dead kids?
Yeah, one day all kids will be dead and then our...
Yeah, in the future all kids living currently will be dead.
And I'm hoping, I'm hoping for that day.
I'm hoping for that day to come sooner rather than later.
Okay, okay, I gotta move everything down
because I have a big fucking forehead.
Oh my god.
Now we're coming.
This is fucking, this is going harder than I could ever imagine.
Uh, wait.
No, they don't have the nose that I wanted.
When I brought my weed down to do Wii Sports,
I never would have imagined that here standing before
a crowd of 35,000 people.
Exactly.
That we would ever have as broad of a reach as we do.
But with such quality content such as this.
Okay, I gotta bring...
Yeah, they don't have the right nose.
They do not have the nose that it's fucking Nintendo.
I mean, whatever.
All right, all right.
All right, all right, don't rush me.
Well, you can rush me a little bit.
This is fucking bullshit, doesn't matter.
No.
Yeah.
No, this one.
This is the one.
And like smaller, I guess.
Uh, yeah, a little smaller.
Perfect.
That's pretty good.
I don't actually know if they're going to have
the kind of beard you want.
Actually, for 100% they do not.
No, they don't.
Why would they have such limited beard options?
This is fucking poor.
This is fucking a poor.
They're going to like have...
You're going to like...
You're fucked.
There's nothing you can do.
Yeah, um...
Wait, wait, wait.
Maybe I can kind of like...
Maybe if I make it bigger, I can kind of...
Oh, that looks awful.
This looks so bad.
How is this ever acceptable?
You know what?
I kind of shave my beard.
I think I'm just going to go with like clean-shaven beard.
Okay, okay.
Like pseudo clean-shaven beard.
I think...
You're going for the classic bin.
So you can get back to what bin thing was all about.
Yeah.
The memes.
I think I'm going to call that done.
Yeah.
Uh, favorite color is...
Damn bro.
Wait, no, no, no.
I'm going to be like...
Damn bro.
Uh, do we do white or black?
I don't know.
Um, both are disgusting.
Uh, I'm going to do black because I have the, um, the black, uh, uh, nunchuck.
Fuck, yes.
Dude, you're fine for the fucking black power.
Dude, you're a black panther canonically within Wii Sports.
Canonically.
Who do you think's more conservative?
Juggalos or Green Party?
I'm going to go juggalos.
Yeah.
I'm definitely going to go juggalos.
Because juggalos are about like...
They're, they're, they're like wholesome.
Like, like, like hashtag juggalos are always right.
That's my opinion on the subject.
Mine too.
I'm glad you do.
Ben S, you know, for Anna and me.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh...
Mangle.
Are you single in here, ready to mingle?
Uh, my me is.
Uh...
Yes.
Uh, no.
Oh my, oh my god.
I don't want to do that.
That sounds stupid.
Taking, taking a chance.
Uh...
Am I done?
You put your me, you put your me, creator.
Oh...
God, that was made by God for a bit.
Alright, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, don't quit.
OK.
Save and quit.
Excellent.
What do we have here?
Oh!
What, what, what, what tightly peach just wandered into our fucking neck of the woods.
Delicious.
Alright, here you go.
Scrum shits, frankly.
Let us, let us battle.
All right, hold on, hold on, let me, let me just see mine again.
I have no idea, hold on. So bizarre. I'm gonna see if I can
figure out. Oh, look at him go. How can I figure out when this guy was made?
Wait, I gotta make my guy shorter. My guy's gotta be shorter than you. How, how far am I in this?
Okay, tall ish. How, I want to know when I was fucking made so I can figure out why
I whitewashed myself and gave me fucking retard hair. Wait, give, wait, go into me and just make me like,
kind of short-ish. Why?
Because, because look at the screen right now, ladies and gentlemen. It's embarrassing, frankly.
Here, I think he's correct for that. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Law. I think, I think you are, I think you are shorter than me. Big man, what, in real life?
Well, a little more, a little more. I want the difference to be more pronounced.
No, come on. No, no. No, dawg. Little, little more. There you go. That's all right. Okay.
No, no. Okay, come on. Come on. Stop making fun. Yeah.
Stop poking shit. We gotta, we gotta get down to business. Look at him, he's very tiny again.
Oh my god, look at them. They're beautiful. All right, time to get down to fucking business.
Time to get what you fucking clicked on this fucking video for. The unbelievable fucking majesty.
We're going to be playing the newest game release on the block. We just picked this up from GameStop.
Came out yesterday. We went to the midnight release. Yeah, but it's, it's, it's 2006. Yeah.
We're fucking, we're stroked and we're poked. I can't wait to play Red Steel and Twilight Princess.
I can't wait to play Call of Duty, the first one.
Fucking, I'm so ready. I'm gonna put on my wrist strap because you gotta have your wrist strap on.
Yeah, but mine doesn't have one. Okay, well, you're fucked. What the shit.
I can actually go and sue GameStop with that fucking asshole, Paul, trying to outsell me. Paul,
if you're watching this right now and you were, if you work at GameStop and your name is Paul,
fucking come to the comments. We're going to find you, give us your address, post them in the
comments below, and then you're going to figure out, you're going to figure out why Storm's a
named it for people. Fucking Paul, I go to pay for the Wii remote and he is like, I'm like,
I just make, I just make a small talk. I just make the observation that like, oh, when, when your
chip gets confirmed, it's like, it doesn't sound very encouraging. And then he's like, oh, well,
he's kind of thinking about it differently. Just imagine you're playing an eight-bit video game
and you're winning. Just like imagine that you're playing a video game and then the world will make
sense to you. And then the world will be true and real and just your fucking like, are you sure
you don't want to play it? Are you sure you want to get the power-ups card? And you're like, no.
You're like, you've never had one before and you're like, no. You're like, are you sure you don't
want one? You want to win us to point? Yeah, yeah, yeah. Even for free points, you're like, no.
Did I just say no? Yeah. No, no. No. Like, I'm glad you finally got the message. Yeah. Like, good on
him. Oh, okay, okay, okay. We're going to play all these games, but what you want me to do first?
You want to go in order? Yeah, just go in order. Okay. Tennis. Tennis is like the most premiere,
like fucking like- I don't know about you, but my cardiovascular endurance is through the roof.
I dumped all my points into this. Yeah, I'm going to soda and then I'll fucking be there.
I'm going to the glittery- I guess it's water, whatever.
Power.
Okay. Get ready to die. Fuck yeah. Get ready to die, viewers. I'm so ready. Not you, the
viewers. I'm so ready. I'm so ready for death. I'm so fucking psyched. I'm so fucking pumped.
Uh, yeah, right hand. You're right handed, right? Of course. Only fucking freaks and jugglers are
left in. I mean only beautiful, strong, independent people. Oh my god. Wait, hang on.
I got it. I got it. Oh, oh my god. Oh, a little crispy. Yeah. I gotta get stretched. I gotta get
lubed. I gotta get limber. Fucking warm up. Wait, no, I actually have to like crack my back.
Oh my god. Your bones are fucking solidified right before my eyes. They just come apart
under under pressure. Under the right circumstances. Just like my personality. Well, I need a certain
some special somebody. Yes. Yeah, fucking me. Get it. You gotta hold it.
Hold it. Oh, uh, where's where's B? It's the it's the back one. Yeah. Okay. All right, come on.
Oh, oh, okay.
Okay, here we fucking go. I'm so fucking excited. I'm so, oh my god, we have two.
All right, uh, yeah, it's the best of five.
This is right. It's not supposed to be punctual. I don't understand. No, no, you will.
Idiot.
God damn it. Oh, oh, oh my god. You're gonna fucking pay for your insolence.
We agree. We had a gentleman's agreement that you would lose this time. Yeah, well, I'm no gentleman.
God damn it. No.
It's a skill. Okay, this isn't true. This isn't true. I'm the best that we sport.
God damn it. I'm retarded.
All right. No, don't worry. No, don't worry audience. Don't worry.
God, the timing. I hate this replay.
I hate this fucking replay.
Idiot. Fucking moron. I can't believe you made a blender such as that in these how and hauls.
Fuck yeah. How do I even control the angle?
Fuck. Damn it. Wait, do you just, do we not pass the serve back and forth?
I don't know. Like, aren't you supposed to lose the serve when you, when I-
No, I think if I get a point, then you get it.
Fuck. Fuck yes. The game is just like you do it once and then you get an hour or you lose.
Yeah. Like, there's no, there's no coming back from a blender.
Yeah.
Or is there?
Oh, oh, oh, oh. Yes. Go, go. Oh, come on. Oh, no.
That happened. What an incredible volley. What an incredible victory for me.
No, fuck. I don't mean to keep doing that. This is unbearable.
That was fucking sick. That was fucking epic.
I'm gonna fucking, I'm gonna turn you into a fucking Native American.
Never. No. Yes. I should have just let it go.
Fucking yes. I want to see a rea- Ah, fuck.
I'm gonna make you fucking emit greenhouse gases from your fucking nose.
Fuck. How do I make them go faster? Is there any way for that to be the case?
I have no idea. I'm-
Fuck.
Fuck. How is he-
Fuck, yes.
How is he even supposed to do it?
Ha, there's no way.
You're about to lose, white boy.
No!
Dude.
You fucked, idiot.
Don't worry. My idiocy has nothing to do with my ability to play or win, Tennis.
No!
This is fucking retarded. It doesn't make any sense.
How am I supposed to do?
Yeah, like how do you even control the angle?
Damn it!
That incredible edge-guarding. The net-guarding skill.
I'm not doing anything differently.
This doesn't even matter. This isn't even fucking real.
Oh, I should have gone for it at the net.
Come on!
Yes!
Fuck yeah.
Fuck yeah. Fuck yes. Fuck yes. It doesn't even matter.
Come on, you idiot.
Don't!
No, no, no.
I'm weak, man.
You little bans. You little bans. You gotta fucking get me.
You little bans.
My back is so fucking like a steel rod that I'll never be able to know true happiness.
Yes!
Did it like matter which direction I swing?
I have no clue.
How was that not a hit?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Get, get, get, get, get, get, get, get, get, get, get, get, get, get, get.
Well, did you just win?
Get, no, no, it's best to five.
All right.
No!
That doesn't even count.
See that incredible restraint that I showed there?
You knew, you knew.
Then say the legendary restraint attribute.
Damn it, that doesn't even make any sense.
That doesn't make any sense.
If we're being honest with ourselves, that doesn't make any sense.
Uh, I don't, I don't have any opinion about that.
And, and frankly I'm confused.
No, yes, yes, oh my god, that was gay.
All right, okay.
I need to come back from the fucking courthouse.
Okay, well, well, all right.
If I lose, I'm going to go to fucking jail.
Yep, that's the agreement.
That's the jailman's agreement that we had.
Fucking I hate you.
God damn it.
Whatever, doesn't even make any sense.
This game has no fucking rules.
Yes.
Damn it, no!
Look at the determination in my eyes.
This is fucking retarded.
No, never play again, quit.
Wait, that took like 30 minutes.
Oh wait, wait, I'm including the, making the video.
Yeah, but okay, fucking, this is such,
even though that was a cheat, even though you cheated,
and even, even though that was conclu, conclusion at play,
and you fucking sucked the dick of the referee in order to get that point through,
like 9% of those points.
That seems like the kind of thing I would do.
Even though that, this is a great change of pace,
from the fucking awful, rigorous, you know, like, like, this is our vacation.
This is our vacation from the living nightmare that is frog fractures.
Yeah, yeah, we finally got, and now we get to take a break and fucking relax,
you know, limber up our muscles, fucking butter up our assholes and fucking,
just go to town.
Yeah.
Wait, am I pitching?
Come on, you, you dumb fuck.
You stupid, ugly asshole.
Hey, man.
Wait, wait, excuse that way a little bit.
Okay.
I'm fucking ready.
I'm fucking ready for you.
Aim your pitch with, oh, I see.
I don't even know what those things are.
Oh my god, look at all these people.
Those are all our friends.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
All, all our, oh, look at that.
Oh my god.
I'm so fucking ready.
You're going to fucking eat shit and die.
We'll see.
J, there's a home run right now.
No, no, hold on, no, hold on, hold on.
This game sucks.
It fucking doesn't make any sense.
You're a tad late there.
I don't, this doesn't, this is fucking stupid.
This doesn't make any sense.
I want out.
That's, that doesn't make any sense.
This is, this is kind of fucking Japanese, isn't it?
All right, we're doing good.
All right, I'm liking this game so far.
Fuck.
No.
Okay, Phantom Ho.
Okay, okay.
What kind of a stupid name is that?
Yes, home run.
No.
Oh fuck.
This game doesn't make any fucking sense.
Almost, almost.
Oh, I don't even mean to throw it.
Oh shit.
What did I even do?
Did I have to throw it to the base?
I threw it as you immediately caught.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold it towards me and then I, okay.
Oh, here we go.
I hate you.
Yeah, get fucked.
What?
They hit the ground.
Doesn't matter.
What do you mean?
These are the rules of baseball.
Wow, huh?
Fucking sheep got his fucking ba-ba wet.
Oh, move over, move over.
Oh, what's going on here?
Look what the cat dragged.
It's gonna die.
Okay, okay.
I gotta fucking get it together.
What's that on your shoe, huh?
Is it fucking pride?
Who can't play this game?
What is this?
What is it?
We're changing.
All right.
Okay, that's the game.
We won't have zero points.
Game over, game over.
Okay.
All right.
The street continues.
Fuck.
Cool.
All right.
Okay, good.
Okay.
All right.
All right, cool.
All right, fucking come on.
Imagine if you paid like $60 to get into the fucking stadium.
No, what the fuck?
How do you score?
Do you have to hit a homerun and that's just it?
Oh, oh, shit.
Wait, am I out?
Okay, I thought I was gonna be out again.
All right, fuck yes.
Fuck.
I dare you to do that again.
All right.
Well, it's not even mean to throw that one.
Oh my god.
No, oh my god.
No.
All right.
You know what they say?
So bad.
Ryan, look at this fucking big little basket, little piece of shit.
Little fucking hat.
I guess he's got a tight boy.
Pussy.
Fuck.
I mean, I guess so.
I guess that's what's communicating.
God damn it.
No.
Okay.
Well, these guys are so fucking good at catching things.
Well, I hope you're going to be able to eat shit after you die,
because that's what you're going to need to do.
Ah.
Maybe you shouldn't have eaten all those fucking poops.
I mean, yeah, I didn't have to.
Maybe you shouldn't have gone in that fucking orphanage
and taken all their babas out.
But even though you were a little baby, you had to do it.
Wow.
Oh god.
Let's see what I sound like.
Don't wear enough.
I can't pop fly.
Oh god.
This is the hardest fucking game of all time.
You can't play.
We're going to fucking break our fucking bones.
Like one of us is going to get a home run completely by luck,
and that's going to be the whole game.
Yeah.
There it is.
There's the game.
One by chance.
I don't know how I did that.
I think we're both like the same.
Yeah.
We're both powerless.
We're just being carried along by the amber waves of grain
that is resports.
Nobody's getting out.
All right.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Phantom Owl.
Yeah.
Traitor.
This is the worst fucking.
How long is this?
This is just like real baseball.
How long is baseball?
Nine innings.
Oh no.
No.
Coward.
Whatever.
Wait.
Wait what?
Do we have to?
All right.
Ow.
I don't think it like matters where I throw it.
It seems like it's all about the timing.
Like my bad doesn't even go where it is though.
All right.
Fuck.
Ow.
It's out.
Great.
Today I learned that it's impossible to play baseball.
It's impossible.
You can't like I dare you to try.
You can't.
Hiroshim.
Fuck you.
God damn it.
America's pastime ladies and gentlemen.
You did come out of this.
Oh no.
No I was about to fucking cry.
Incredible.
Oh my god.
You could you could score.
You could actually score.
I could.
But you won't.
Don't be so sure.
Don't be so cocky kid.
Don't.
All right.
Well maybe you should just get your face fucking obliterated before you come to my house.
No.
That fucking girl.
You're done.
That's it.
You're fucking done.
You're done.
There's nothing you can do.
I can't.
I can't win this.
Peg stand up.
Come on Peg stand up.
All right.
Well that's unfair.
That's cheating.
There's just fucking collusion of play.
I'm not going to sit here and fucking take it.
I'm not going to walk away quietly.
If there's something wrong I need to fucking say it.
God damn it.
Okay.
If I don't win this I'm going to fucking literally get my asshole blown up.
I'm going to die.
No.
All right.
This isn't fucking fair.
Oh no.
Come on.
You're dumb.
You're fucking dumb.
Single.
Stupid.
That's what I am if you know what I mean.
Coward.
Good.
Excellent.
Got it.
Come on.
Fuck yes.
Say.
All right.
Here we go.
Fucking bincing himself.
Get raped.
No.
Don't want that.
Not going to happen friend.
No.
Literally.
These guys are so fucking good at catching the ball.
It's unreal.
Say.
Today I landed.
I hate America.
Donald Trump invented baseball.
Not like he did.
So I have to boycott it.
When we fucking impeach Donald Trump,
baseball is going to go right with him.
God.
No.
Just stop.
Good.
How many foul balls do you get?
As many as you want.
Really?
You can't out on a foul.
Great.
Excellent.
I won.
Fuck you.
I fucking won.
You listen.
It's because you're a punk ass little bitch.
And you can't fucking swing source.
Because you can't swing source.
You just can't finangle long devices.
You're fucking collusion.
There's no collusion here.
Both of those.
No.
Not playing games.
You misunderstand again.
You misunderstand.
All right.
Now I should warn you Ben.
Yeah.
I am the best person in the entire world at We Sports Bowling.
Okay.
And you will never defeat me no matter what you do.
Sure.
Yeah.
I feel it.
Well it did.
Why not take a break?
Yeah.
Fucking right.
No.
Never.
Do you know who you're talking to right now?
We're Frosty Joe and ICP.
Yes.
Frosty Joe.
Yeah.
The Frosty Joe and ICP man.
Dude.
Our juggler names are Frosty Joe and Prickly Jack.
Prickly Jack.
Tortoise slum.
All right.
Hold on.
Is this a demo?
Or did it say?
I have no idea what would just happen.
Good.
Sick bro.
All right.
Oh.
Oh my god.
Coward.
Fuck you.
All right.
You're going to have to learn.
Look at my little pink ball.
Yeah.
Look.
My color is so good.
It is.
I'm so good.
You're so.
You're you're you're you're literally F.A. right now.
Yeah.
Swing your arm while holding down.
Okay.
No per se.
What?
Yeah.
Hold down B and then like.
Hold on B and then like swing it.
Excellent.
No no no.
Good job.
A man.
No.
No wrong.
Bad idea.
Bad idea buster.
So I'll take it.
All right.
Okay.
Cool.
You're fucking done.
Talk a meanie.
You're fucking done kid.
Motherfucker.
Have you ever heard of giving birth?
Because that's what you're about to do to my fucking kid.
Fuck yeah.
You fucking.
That ball's about to go into your fucking.
Let's be a bitch.
That ball's about to fucking give birth to you.
No.
No I won't allow it.
That's what I did.
No you just don't understand.
You just don't understand.
You're just too caught up in like in like the reality of the situation.
You get back into the physical the physicality of it.
What does that mean?
You're just too caught up in like in like the reality.
You need to let your spirit fucking fly.
I think it's because I keep like accidentally hitting the two button with my palm.
Impossible.
No that's wrong.
Yeah.
Buster.
No no no.
You don't understand.
That's wrong.
You didn't you didn't.
You're going down Buster Brown.
You didn't even fucking download that game.
No it doesn't fucking exist.
Oh you can.
How do you do that?
You're fucking dead is what I'm trying to say.
Damn it.
They all booed at me.
This is such a bullshit.
That's spare.
You didn't even fucking train.
22.
Oh good.
Damn it.
It's fine.
I didn't even want it to exist.
No.
Damn it.
God fucking damn it.
I hate you.
I want you to know that I'll never forgive you for these transgressions.
Okay.
All right that's fine.
Listen if you just want to be gay and suck dick in the middle of the football stadium
then that's fine at all.
Just don't just don't do it in front of my kids all right.
Thanks for your blessing.
You're dead.
You're fucking done.
Oh my god.
Check out this fucking shit bro.
There's nothing more powerful than a man with nothing left to lose.
No.
No you're wrong.
You're wrong.
All right.
Okay.
Why'd you flood this?
All right.
Wow.
Trick shot.
That doesn't matter.
No.
Oh my god.
Things are heating up.
Things are purpleing.
Things are boiling.
That's pretty good.
Come on.
Don't you fuck with me.
Yeah.
If I don't get a good role this one I'm really fucked.
You're really gonna get a good role.
Like I really need this role.
I'm gonna roll over your fucking grave.
I'm gonna roll in my grave thinking about you.
All right.
I'll take it.
Taste that pain.
Whatever.
Yeah.
I can still make it.
Whatever.
Damn it.
Fuck.
Oh.
Shit.
Look at that.
Fuck yes.
All right.
Doesn't even matter.
Doesn't even fucking matter.
Motherfuck.
No.
I'm just too powerful for your fucking human mind
to comprehend.
You're a little powerful.
I have to give you that.
You're a little bit powerful.
I can sense the power radiating off of you.
Oh my god.
You're gonna land up in fucking jail.
I'm getting closer.
Oh.
Damn it.
You're a dick.
Delectable.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Damn it.
Whatever.
It's just one pin.
Just one pin.
Don't matter.
Look at me.
Let me fucking scoop it up your brain.
Yeah.
Wait, where?
I'm fucking winning.
Oh, shit.
Wait, where?
Where are you?
You should be in my brain.
Wait, what's going on?
Uh-uh.
Hey.
Come on.
Bitch.
You little bug.
Do I dare?
Dude, try.
Yes.
Power.
If I fucking lose this,
I'm gonna call the fucking buffalo.
Oh my god.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
No, no, no, bad.
Hey.
I'm exuberating fucking joy and warmth,
like louder and more potent
than a Native American brims of petroleum.
I'm fucking, I'm burning that right up.
Mother nature's giving me a handy.
Spiritually.
Native Americans didn't have guns.
They didn't have guns.
I'm so fucking embarrassed.
Just do it.
Do it.
Wee bowling.
You won't pull the trigger.
Oh my god.
That's so bad.
Then how could you try to trap it?
So shit.
Oh, wow.
Shit.
Oh my god.
Whatever.
It's a split, split, split, split, split, split.
Don't matter.
Going for the safe too, like a coward.
No.
This is unbearable.
This is unbearably potent.
Even if you get a strike, I'll still be in the lead.
Actually, that's not true.
No, that's definitely not true.
I forgot.
All right, well.
You're definitely gonna fucking knock that DS, by the way.
Oh my god.
At one point, did I win?
Yes.
Fuck.
God.
That is the face of a fucking loser.
That's the face of a fucking racist.
You didn't let the buffalo stampede on your ground.
And now I'm gonna stampede on your heart.
What a mistake.
Shit.
You wouldn't sell the land back to the people you stole it from,
and now you're gonna pay dearly in hell.
I didn't want it bad enough.
That's what happened.
Fuck you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm representing all, no, I didn't want to do anything.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I represent all Native Americans.
Yeah, you speak for them.
And you represent all whites.
He speaks for them.
I speak for the trees.
I speak for the people without voices,
aka all Native Americans.
They can't speak for themselves.
Don't worry, guys.
If you're a Native American, don't worry.
I'll do it for you.
All right.
An expert.
Oh god, I'm full with.
Nigh-hole.
You want to namp Nigh-
Let's do a Nigh-hole.
Yeah, let's do a Nigh-hole.
Fuck yes.
Okay, we're still going.
No problem.
No problems yet.
Fuck yeah.
Let me show me up my hips.
Here, let me lower it.
All right, that's it.
Okay, didn't mean to do that.
Okay, good.
All right, how do I play the game?
You can.
That's not a feature that comes with the game.
All right, okay, I am.
Oh my god.
Sliced it or something.
I fucking diced it, bro.
Look how fucking powerful that was.
Hold on, hold on.
I'm going to center this a little better.
There we go.
Okay.
Excellent.
Just try.
I'm going.
You give me a second.
Cheese, dude.
Okay, okay.
Wait, so what do I do?
Do I have to hold a button?
I don't know.
Fuck you.
You fucking, you hold down A and then you like swing it.
Just like.
No, like a fucking club.
Like a golf.
Do it like a golf.
Do I have to release A when I hit?
I don't think so.
Oh, idiot.
All right.
Where, where?
Oh, oh fuck.
Oh fuck.
How do I?
Is it because I'm still closer or something?
I guess.
I guess I just drove hard into the paint.
All right, sure.
Okay, okay.
You're roughed it.
You're roughed it, bro.
Okay, whatever.
You're roughing it.
Oh god, look at me.
Look how serene I am.
Look how fucking beautiful.
What the fuck?
You're gonna hold, you have to hold A.
I know, I know, but I'm trying to like test it.
This seriously makes no sense to me.
Yeah.
It's just like you just, you just hit it.
I don't know what your deal is.
I just, what?
Oh no.
Yeah, okay, sure.
Driver.
Oh, I see.
Okay, I want to go with like
fuck, power.
What?
I fucking swung.
It didn't, great.
Did it clip the tree?
I, I don't know what's going on.
I have no clue what's fucking going on.
I think I hate this game.
Yeah, that's probably the worst thing
we've ever done in our lives.
There's gonna be nine holes, nine holes of this.
Good.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Excellent.
Truly remarkable.
What the fuck?
What are you putting this on at?
What?
You were like, you like practiced it so carefully.
Yeah.
And then like, oh, here we go.
Worthless.
No.
I think that was, no, no.
Nine holes, nine holes was a mistake.
Yeah, this was, this was a horrible idea.
Okay.
I don't even want to do one.
No.
I mean,
all right.
I'm probably getting the hang of this game
and the more I understand the less I want to play it.
We can stop early, maybe.
No.
Okay, never mind.
That was a lie.
Fuck.
Idiot.
Maximum over putt.
I'm gonna put you in the next week.
Shit, Christ, idiot.
I'm so effing.
You are.
You could walk into fucking Kanye West's apartment.
He wouldn't even know.
You're so sneaky.
Idiot.
I'm like, can't, we're just playing.
Yep.
Okay.
Oh, it.
It has no fucking clue.
Oh, no.
It has absolutely no idea.
It does.
It doesn't know where my remote is.
I just have to fucking pray.
Yeah.
That would have been perfect.
Oh, oh, no, no, no.
I'm never gonna get that in, by the way.
I will never get that in my entire life.
No, it's gonna glitch out.
Okay.
Yep.
Fuck.
You're fucking dead, kid.
Damn it.
Dude, it's like trying to get the ball into the hole
from this length is like being sweet bro and hello, Jeff.
Trying to get the ball out of the door.
I need to know what angel to eat.
It gets impossible.
Like the closer you are, the harder it gets.
Fuck.
Oh, oh, oh.
Never mind.
Now it's wrong.
Yes.
I was wrong about what I said.
I figured out the angel.
You figured out the angel.
Fuck yes.
Someday.
Hey, hey, hey.
Do you think you're gonna never mind?
Please.
Please never make it in.
Please never win this game.
What?
It's doing the opposite of what I tell it to.
No.
Look, I swing it and it goes backwards.
It's not precise enough to actually do measurements.
So it's just like you have to just fucking hope.
You have to hope with all your fucking dick in your heart.
Don't fuck it up.
Okay.
Fuck.
Tripping bogey.
Fuck yes.
All right, all right.
Second hole of a nine hole game.
Oh my god.
Jesus.
Yeah, just go right into the sand trap.
That's what I want to see.
Yes.
Oh, that delay.
Okay.
Is your skull just lagged?
I don't know.
I don't understand what the fuck is happening.
That's pretty good.
Mike on the sand trap.
No.
No, it actually sucked dig.
All right, all right, all right.
Six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six.
You're definitely holding one, dude.
Dude, we're holding fucking one.
Okay.
Oh my god.
I was going back and it registered me going forward.
That was awesome.
Whatever.
Oh, in the hard rough.
Oh my god.
You're on stroke five.
I have to go.
All right.
Six.
Okay.
This doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Thoughtful, thoughtful approach.
You're a thought.
I'm going to approach you with a fucking knife.
Okay.
I think maybe because I was kind of using with my wrists
and it didn't like that.
Okay.
Apparently I can't hit it at max power.
I can only hit it at three quarters.
Okay.
Cool.
Whatever.
That's fine.
Fuck.
Okay.
Well, I guess you did that time.
Oh.
Done.
That's for retards, as I like to say.
Good.
You did it.
Oh, hey, no, you get to go again.
It's good.
I thought I was using the putter again.
Oh, there's a tree in the way.
Tree in the way.
I did not, did not, did not start me off with the,
with the off hub I was using.
No.
Did you just switch to a random one right now?
I think it just switches automatically to the one
that it thinks is like the best match, distance-wise.
Okay.
I want to see it bounce off that tree, dude.
Oh, okay.
No.
Fuck.
Well, you almost got it.
What?
Did it just make you give up?
It just forced me to give up?
I think it did.
Oh, I think it was because you got six stirrups behind,
so it was just like-
Oh, fucking dumb.
You can't win.
Fuck you.
I guess it's to avoid a blowout where someone
spends like 40 turns on one.
Yeah.
And then it's just like, well, it's pointless from here.
Yep.
No.
This game fucking sucks.
All right.
It don't matter.
What kind of fucking barbarian fucking like ruthless,
uncivilized, non-gentified fucking society do you have to be
in order to invent golf?
To invent golf?
Yeah.
You have to be a savage.
You have to be less than human.
Then Neanderthals invented golf, and then the humans,
and then the primitive humans just ate them.
And they took up golf to mock them.
Yeah.
That's how the Neanderthals would extinct,
that people would just use golf clubs to beat the shit out of them.
You know, they're fun.
Like you do.
Hope you don't fucking die every shame.
Yeah.
Yeah, I could see that.
Worst things have happened.
Worst things have happened today.
All right.
Just win.
Wow.
Just kidding.
I meant lose.
Oh, no.
No.
Idiot.
Dumb.
I ruined it.
Hey, it's me, it's me, it's KC Green.
It's KC Green.
I hope you all got your faces right.
I got my face right.
Let's go in here.
Let's go.
If I lose, I'm going to turn into a fucking...
It's not another race.
Fuck.
Yes.
Bitch.
Fake.
Boo to that.
You are fake.
You are a fake bitch.
Sure.
You are basic.
Why will...
Look, it's like we got my...
Oh, because I'm on the rough.
My power is limited because I'm on the rough.
Now I understand.
Whatever.
Yeah, good.
Excellent.
But yep, good.
Sick.
That doesn't matter.
That's fine.
Yeah.
That's almost out of bounds, dawg.
That's fine.
That's fine, dude.
It's not blows.
It sucks.
No, no.
That has no bearing.
That has zero homes.
You could do it.
If you fucking max powered it,
you could like get it on the green.
What the...
What?
Wait, what?
Where's the ball?
Show us the ball.
Oh, no.
There we go.
You're fucking dead, dude.
Yeah, that was pretty cool, I gotta say.
I just had to wiggle it a little bit.
Oh my god.
Oh my fucking god.
Get ready.
Get ready for your dick to be blown off.
I will do.
Shit.
Oh, that sucked.
Kill me.
All right, all right.
I'm back and I'm ready for action.
You've got attitude.
You're gonna make me fucking...
You're gonna purr once I see you.
Gross.
No?
Fuck.
I was...
No?
All right.
Fuck.
I remember when I first played this game.
And I thought, man, the motion controls are hard to use.
I don't know if they're gonna catch on.
And I was like, no.
No, bro.
This is the future.
Looks like you fucking have the right idea you called it.
Why does the...
Why is the putter just lie to you, by the way?
Why does it not appreciate what its actual max power is and like the range?
I don't pretend to understand golf.
I only pretend to love it.
Exactly.
It's like I'm impressed by fucking foolhardy friends.
Look at the difference between max power and no power.
No power?
Max power.
You are gonna learn so much when I'm coming through with you.
God, I just want to get like near max.
You're gonna learn the three reasons why people don't talk to people.
Because things like this could happen.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh my god.
Run, run, run.
Shit.
What the fuck?
Fuck.
God damn it.
Yes, I have so much bend.
What you're lacking up is right here.
You're lacking is right up here.
You're lacking a little bit up the stairs.
Are you talking about my sixth chakra?
You just can't open your eye a little bit and then you're gonna be able to see clearly.
Wrong.
What do you mean?
It knows.
It's good.
Wrong.
It's nice.
What is this whole four?
Okay.
I don't know how much more I can take.
Maybe one more or I don't know.
No, we signed up.
We signed up for it.
We signed up for nine.
Let's just try to end it quick.
All right, fucking I hope you're ready for this.
I think I'm gonna lose my entire mortgage and my income in my house.
Oh, I'm fucking done.
Oh, I'm in the fucking, I'm in the ground.
I'm six feet under.
Okay.
I'm gonna be buried.
What you guys doing?
Playing golf.
Yeah.
We're playing the gentleman's sport.
This is the worst game we've ever made.
Every sports golf is awful.
We know.
Yeah.
No.
We sports is infallible.
I said we sports golf.
Okay.
Specifically everything else is fine.
We sports golf reminds me of what it was like to like watch my grandfather die.
It's like a heart attack in the hospital.
So it was pretty fun.
Yeah, it was really sick.
Oh, no.
Oh, yes.
No.
I think I'm gonna show you something really crazy.
You're gonna be like, how would you do that?
I'm gonna be like, huh?
And that's pretty much the game.
You're gonna be like.
Golf tastes like pizza.
I bet pizza would solve that problem.
Oh.
Oh, fuck you, bitch.
Jesus, shit.
It's time for the introvert revolution.
It's time for introverts to take over.
No, you've got it all wrong.
I'm gonna tell you right now, you've got it all fucking wrong.
You don't even know the secret.
I figured out the secret.
How?
How could you possibly?
Laws of attraction, my man.
Laws of attraction.
God, no.
You didn't want it.
You didn't want it hard enough.
You didn't actually want it.
You just thought you did.
I was gonna sit down and wait and wait.
No, I can't wait.
I just have to be on the show.
Why does it keep aiming me at the fucking sand trap?
Because it thinks you're stupid.
Well, maybe it's right.
It knows me better than I know myself.
See, that was perfect.
Why can't I do that?
Come on.
What the fuck?
What the fuck is happening?
Yeah, that's what I want.
Do that.
Perfect.
Okay, good.
This is literally-
This should just overshoot the sand trap.
All right.
Excellent, excellent, excellent.
Powerful, powerful.
Okay.
No.
Why?
I didn't-
I didn't do that.
It worked out, I guess.
I didn't do it.
Damn.
Whatever.
It's pretty good.
It's pretty solid.
You're like that one guy, which that-
That one that everyone knows.
Yeah, that one that everyone knows, and they're like,
I don't like this guy anymore.
Yeah, I know that guy.
Sucks.
Oh, no.
It's a hard knock life.
Fuck.
It's a hard knock life being compared to that one guy that no one likes.
It's a hard knock life.
For us.
That's the only line of that song.
I don't even know what it is.
A manny?
Pretty sure.
Um, gross.
Yeah.
Yep.
Um, I'm saying.
Have you ever seen Stuart Little?
Maybe.
Because I'm getting some hardcore Stuart Little lads from you.
I might have.
Mouse.
Mouse in an orphanage.
Yeah.
I'm sure you're about to be what I'm done with you.
No, I'm gonna kill my own mouse pain.
That's fucking blows.
Look how close I got it.
Please whiff it.
Just whiff it like the coward I am.
Uh, oh, you, you, if you find out solution, I know that I'm going to find your spirit.
Wow.
Uh, what, what should I do?
No, it's too fucking powerful.
Just do it.
Just, just.
Okay.
And I thought I was going to.
I, I, I do not think I'm really doing this.
Look at it.
It doesn't know.
It doesn't know you're swinging unless you give it your full power.
Oh, you're catching up.
Okay.
You're too, you're too behind.
I can go ahead.
I can do it.
Okay.
All right.
No.
Why?
I didn't, I was swinging.
I was going.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry that that didn't happen.
No.
Then say it here.
You're here to capitalize on what I've just witnessed.
I'm not scared that if I fucking slice it too hard, it'll go out of bounds.
No.
No, wrong.
Did you fucking see that?
Yeah.
This is this is fucking dangerous.
Okay.
six six six six six six six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six.
Sure, whatever.
Did I lose two strokes because of that?
I think I yeah, you you get a penalty. Oh, but like it moved you to the water. Yeah, so you could theoretically hit it across. Oh
Wait, no, no, you can't because you're in the rough you're not gonna make it
I'm retarded
Fuck yeah fuck yeah, bro
Damn it
Okay, wait what wait what that was out of bounds. What?
No stop it stop no more no more
All right fucking whatever you done doesn't matter doesn't even fucking matter
No, no, no, I angle I try to
Okay, thanks
Pretty good pretty soft. No, oh
There I am look, it's me
with a little
Wait, oh no, okay. I disappeared. That's fine
I
Slice it slice it in half slice and fucking dies
Champion gulcher munchie with tiny hats catchphrase
I'm gonna start a fucking grease fire in this guy's heart this guy right here
All right, I'll take it. Oh
Dear oh dear. Oh, okay. Okay, please. I can take that
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay
I
Just fucking get the fucking
No, you fucking moron
Me
It's whatever it's whatever God game golf really is the worst sport
It's not a single one that's worse
Yeah
Do it do it you fucking martyr. How is it?
Why is it going red do it you fuck you fucking social pariah? Why is everything I do red?
Sick embarrassing it was embarrassing feel bad about myself
No
Okay, no wrong wrong wrong wrong
Whoa, he got the ball near the that's fucking scary did the game
All right
It's like some dice no that was the opposite what I was supposed to do
No, no, I think you're about to give up. I think you're almost six ahead. No, that's wrong
No, that's wrong
No, it's wrong
That's so wrong that's just a wrong thing
Look at me leering at you for my little red tower
I'm not doing anything
I
Just want to point out that we're supposed to be on the PCP right now, but we're playing
Yeah, if you want to know hey
Nate best guy ever if you want to know why we're not on the PCP that we said we're gonna be on we're doing this instead
Because we're having fun. We're having real friend times
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, it's wrong
It's an evil thing he just did
Yes
We just have three more we just have three more you're 11
We just have three more we have three more. Okay. Okay. Okay. That's that's it doesn't even matter. That's manageable. It doesn't matter
Perfect perfect
I
Yes
Bucking nice manageable manageable
I want to play bowling again. It's game sucks. Yeah, actually bowling was a thousand times
All right, all right, all right, all right
Professional engineering
I'm gonna my engineering degree doing this
I'm gonna get my certificate of computer a to draft
Except that part's actually true
No
No, that would never be the case
Yes, you're gonna get fucking slimed you're gonna get slimmered
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay
Like yeah, I understand how to play now, but it's still not fun
No, it's not what I did that's wrong. That's a literally a lie that they lied to me
They've done it before
Do it again
This is fucking brutal no one's watching this no, why would they oh
This isn't for you, this is for us we need time off. Yeah, you people this is our vacation. You're treating a pot
Drive us. Oh
Where's our first cop killers? Oh Ben? Why you why didn't you upload it? Fuck you?
All right, I
Did and I took it down again because I'm a capricious God and I don't cater to my subjects whims
Oh
Yes
Listen, Ben. Don't get sad if your mom dies trying this off unexpectedly
Now that I know
I should put on my wrist
Why the slide
Come on
Cuz sliced and dies
Okay, okay, excellent, okay as they say in the industry excellent
I
Good excellent
This game is for sadness
This is a product is a product for and by a sadness. Yeah
Christian Christian juggalos like us can't can't enjoy this. Oh
Oh
Okay, I fucking did it
Yeah, we're Christian juggalos we're representing the right we're with the right side of history
Of course, I
Can't back in a thousand years and everyone's doing I think how how is it ever possible that we were suddenly getting such a way?
Come on I
Can't just fucking do it. I can't do a bitch
Yeah, all right, excellent double bow. That was that sure was satisfying. Yeah, that's your felt good
They said sure match the game I can't the kinesthetic the game feel of this game is out of this world
this serene
Atmospheric incredible blissful time represents the
No
My hair
Thank you, but it's true unfortunately
If you were smart
No
If you're smart you quickly you were ahead. Oh, I don't think that's gonna make it off the off the rough
Yeah, garbage unfortunate
All right, let me show you a real man plays baseball
That's gonna
Oh
No, I don't understand my strategy was perfect
Hey, I
Don't understand I don't understand what I'm doing wrong as you know
It's as Albert Einstein famously said the definition of insanity is doing the same thing over and over expecting a different result
Learn from history the reason why I'm doing the same thing over and over again because I'm too smart in the game
It doesn't recognize my fucking genius
You're you're like your gamma waves. Yeah. Yeah, well, they can't they can't be like tamped down
It's walking out the fucking Sun
If you go my skull like my gamma waves fucking they're like hotter than plasma. They would obliterate the entire
Yeah, I'm so fucking distraught right now. Okay, I cannot wait to fucking in this
No, all this is just warm up to get our fucking blood pumping
So I can fucking be but we can play the only game that actually matters being the share of each other
All right, all right incredible
Okay
That's what I want. No, no
All right, perfect. Oh
Disgusting so
Truly upset
Oh
No, wait, I'm right there
No
I've so many feet to go
Rose
Oh
End of the line
This is we're all good men come back. That's what I wanted to do
No wrong stop stop all your head
If only the sad set fucking knew these playing right into my trap
And only if you knew if you would just stop right now and give me $25 and I would go easy
You know
It only had the fucking gumption and courage and wisdom to fucking stop the charade once
She would know you should close fucking brains out right out of the course
Oh
You're so dumb
Incredible to feed I
Told you
I
Okay, well, it's fair. It's fair. Yeah, this is the last hole. I think so
Okay, no, this is fine, you know that like this this golf has should count for like 90%
Yeah, yeah, the point. Yeah, oh
Well, I mean zero. I mean it's more like
Yeah, cuz it literally doesn't do what it's supposed to yeah 100% of the time it can be counted upon
All right, all right, it's time to time to buckle them up. I want it right in there that sweet spot
Yeah
Yes, no
It's time to nut up shut up and pack your bags to fucking hell where you belong
Okay, I'm I can accept that
All right fucking
Look at the utter pointlessness of that like zigzag path down the middle. Yeah
Oh
No dad
I don't even know what the bunker is the bungs are I'm gonna take Hitler's body once I'm done with them
Alive so he can kill himself in the bunker. It's what's what's historically accurate
Or so they say
Am I gonna get a three a whole three well
How many things like any a new a numerical value and how many things the United States government is lying to us about?
10 to the power of
Oh my god
Nice song, I don't even know what that means
It means you're a pawn don't even understand what it means you're a sheep
God damn the most
I used all my fucking I used all my man. I used all my my my my my BP you exhausted all your spirit energy
Yeah
No, then don't even try it. I'm just gonna save us both some time
That was par fuck you
All right, all right, this is the final this is it. This is it. This is where this is where this is where boys become men
Become beasts nonsense. This is unacceptable. There's no wind
Good. There's no wind
Yeah
Perfect
Right in the water
All right, don't worry. Don't worry. Don't worry. No, no, it's okay. I understand
Check out this you're not gonna fucking check out this no dude
This is a mistake
That's what your parents said last night when they had sex with me
This is all a false
Bounced off the fucking shoreline
Okay, you'll never get it from the rough. No, no, no, bro
Okay
Justin can visualize what I'm about to do to you, okay
Oh
Instead it was fake trap behind
I'm getting getting steamed
This is the voice of someone who has nothing left to lose
Except the pride will and wife
Wish a lot when you think about it. Yeah. Yeah, okay
What what?
What
What the fuck what is happening? Where's the ball?
Uh
I have to put it I have to put it while it's in the water. No, it was it no
It's looking at where it landed, but it says you're shooting from the edge of the islands. I
Hope my driver is fucking built for hydraulics
All right, all right, this is gonna decide my fucking whether my life my wife leaves me or not
So that's hope that I lose
Well, no, I was in the water you were you were in the fucking water. I you were in the water
Okay, okay, it's fucking figured out now
No, no, no, no, no, no, you got wrong. No, you got wrong
You're playing a dangerous game on she it's called
All right
All right, I figured it out
Yeah, I just have to shoot myself and then I'll win
No, that's wrong
With that then I'm clean with you recognize your own intelligence and your decision making a
Building recognized when you're out of your league so far
But you can't even make your thoughts or rational decisions. I can't oh no, oh shit
I'm pleading you with your for your own sake and for the sake of your family's lineage
I don't care about any of that
Being the true rowdy fucker
I
That's fucking fake
Simulation, okay. No, thank God. Thank God. That's over. That's not even true
That's not even true
It's not even real
Fucking
No
All right now you break it your fucking nunchucks on you stupid silly
Brain is fucking in the oh my god. This is what decides it you won tennis. I won baseball. I won ball. Yeah
Yeah, this is what it all comes down to this is all that matters in the fucking reality
Are you ready?
That's what my fucking mom said when she gave birth to me
Jackie I'm gonna win this
Okay, I'm gonna show you I'm powerful. Why not take a break you can pause the game by pressing the plus
But by crushing the but by pressing the cross doing something Jesus to beat the shit out of you
No instructions you're kidding. I don't what the fuck. Oh my god
Okay
I
Can't punch I can't punch I
Can't punch I can't I can't punch I can't okay
Hold the we remote and then check in front of your
Okay, that's that's to guard, okay
God have mercy hold the we're
Oh
No, check out these fucking
You know what you're gonna catch these hands. Oh, yes, did I win? Oh what that's the start
You're a fucking
We're now we're nervous you take two's lunch money now mother fucker
No, I have to win
What is
What no, yes, yes, yes
Okay
All right, you want you want some more want some more do I do I tell you fucking home motherfucker I
Don't fucking get
Yes
Yes, no no tables have turned
What my wife we won't fucking swing swing
Sweet what my wife
What's happening
What's happening what's happening
What what is happening no no no no I can't let you do this no what the fuck I got so many hits on you
Fuck oh my fucking God bin
Can I play for the real fuck
Oh
No, quit it dude
With it I said
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
No, this is obscene hand gesture. I'm doing
Get up you know we know no no stay down stay down Ben
You don't recognize your own usefulness to me. So if you lose you'll be really good. I can't
No, no wrong
Oh, I haven't been guarding that's what I'm fucking doing wrong. It's a big mistake
Oh fuck all right, I'm glad. Oh, little little side dance check out no no no no no no no no no no no no, check it out, check it out, check it out
Okay, there's like dodging and stuff. Yeah
My fucking Mike my limo won't fucking work
Moon move yes, yes
I'm fucking trying to...
Oh my god.
This is it.
No, no, no.
No!
Two, three, stay fucking down, Ben.
Come on, come on.
Only I get to kill cops in this neighborhood.
Only I believe in reverse police brutality.
Reverse police brutality wins!
Hey, oh, yeah, hey, oh, yeah.
I'm gonna do a rain dance for your fucking funeral.
Your furl's gonna have rained it
because I'm gonna do a fucking rain dance
because I'm Native American.
You won with a fucking Kroxma.
I did.
I fucking win.
Look well and look hard and listen big
and listen small.
Fucking munchie is the only rowdy fucker
and the only cop color there fucking is.
But I...
But I worked so hard to get my golf.
Golf doesn't matter when you have hands.
Golf doesn't matter when you use your hands
in the ancient Greco-Roman tradition
of being a fucking meanie.
Well, we beat we sport.
We did it.
100% we're on we sports.
Perfect game.
We saw all the content.
S ranks, speed runs.
Do you think it's a single game
more competitively viable
in an e-sports environment than in e-sports?
Hopscotch.
And tic-tac-toe.
I'll have to give you that.
Next time on...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Chris wants to see tic-tac-toe and hopscotch.
In that order.
You probably might win hopscotch.
But I'm a master at tic-tac-toe.
Wait, listen to these fucking funky jams.
Yeah, I know.
Alright, in the video.
See you later, losers.