Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
how long has it been munchy it's been like it feels like it's been like six months i mean
we were what was the last one we recorded an episode but obviously i mean anyone
anyone who follows the show knows uh fat three two putting into that last oh god that's right
that's jesus pop tropica right yeah it feels the because the one we recorded that got lost
that was eaten by fat 32 that one it could grow into fat 33 that i mean that was what like
two or three months ago that was that was in november first week in november so yeah about two
two months whatever two two three months ago and uh after that i was like boy that was enough
recording for me for a long time uh that that that dude they could they could watch that video for
months yeah but sadly they cannot watch that video for an area second as it did not exist hey i have
this i have the statistics right now we the last episode was in september are you seeing the screen
by the way yeah i am all right well i don't know let me let me know if you got any input on character
creation now i like how there's only two animal preferences in this game as as i got intended
do these matter at all uh well like you'll have a pet in the game and it'll either be a cat or a dog
i feel like that's i gotta i wish i could i wish i could click this blank space over here and pick
none please there's a very clear killer ratty preference here it's very clear that killers
are cats and rats are dogs oh no i hate that i hate that don't say that i mean i mean can you
argue against it yeah killers hate animals okay well sure fine but if you were i mean of the two
it's a it's a soccer team experiment you see no i'm not i'm not indulging i'm not indulging this
fantasy of yours and what a fantasy what a what a we're going off the rails we're going we're
going off the rails if you notice dear viewer this is a slightly shorter episode at rfk probably
many hours long yet still however not not uh six or seven hours as i am leaving in just a few hours
to uh indulge my mother in some sick depravities that she has lined up for me uh people who know
me in real life know that uh i i took online school for my for my high school so uh i did not
go to a brick and mortar tradition brick and i didn't go to a mom and pop school yeah i didn't
go to a mom but you know this this ain't your uncle's high school uh as they as they uh called it
anyway i got a plumber everything like that graduated it like a year and a half ago however
because it's online you know i didn't uh dress up and go to the frankly god high school graduation
you know i had no uh fallatio you know six hour long fallatio session out in the middle of the
field somewhere but my mom would not you missed out on the quintessential high school experience
dude i've okay i've been the high school graduations before of other people and frankly
miss that fallatio dog i know i thank god thank god there was no woman's lips on my on my male
look at this i can pick my pants color but i can't pick my shirt color
what the fuck wait so they're just preordained shirts yeah i don't like it no nobody does
all black classic been saying it's not i'm not all black give me a little credit give me a little
give me some fucking credit would you never your your your credit is shit i would never lend you a
boat or or or a colored shirt oh i can wear a charlie brown shirt can wear a tuxedo i can wear
oh i can be uh the i can be uh chara i can have let's with this undertale ripoff shit going on
right now is that like a skeleton it can wear like like a skeleton rib cage shirt that's pretty killer
it is i'm gonna grow i'm gonna grow some purple i'm gonna grow some purple killer flower
that's my goal here whenever there's a game like this i always just randomize until i get the
worst looking one and then i play with that it's not that's not how i operate i operate i operate in
a stupid way i mean like like all things in your life anyway in about two hours uh i'm being forced
to go to jay jay c pennies and wear some rented uh graduation gown and cap pose for the jay c penny
photographer so uh i can get graduation photo wow awesome i know i'm really stoked for it
well i mean who wouldn't be i mean i'll i'll look back on those images of my uh yeah happy memories
yeah yeah happy man dude oh i remember that time in jay c pennies i used to go there all the time
i used to steal socks look at this ghost shirt that's fucking cool i would wear that
ooh what was that oh go back to that purple what this purple one yeah this is like something a
it's like a pilgrim would wear what no kind of like this sweater this like gray sweater
mm is this what half of the episode is gonna be been you gotta you gotta move on with our lives we
can't stay in the past like this look we're gonna be looking at this oh there it is there it is look
at that i see it look look at it um we're gonna be looking at this for the rest of the game so
yeah i mean get get comfortable oh wait look look at that like double rested like sanji fucking
okay what are these like locations on the side are these houses wilderness farm i think this is
yeah this is location and i think it determines some some shit about the game like i'm pretty sure
wilderness is hard mode uh man okay so it seems kind of a it seems kind of a you don't wait should
i be a juvie that would be really cute should i should i just be a juvie farman i think i think
that would i think i think our stocks would skyrocket if you were to do that all right
just an all just on all neon green man searing the the uh residents of this local town terrorizing
here we go here we go the juvie's animal preference would be like a goldfish or like
something not threatening um it would be like it would be like uh dandelions yeah it would be
their imaginary friend look at this hair jesus christ yeah it's pretty good right oh it's really
as Nina moria would say if she was still alive today hey speaking of high school graduation
those photos you showed me the other day at your house have been just absolutely seared in my vision
of what of me bald well i mean that of course jave had been worst been uh but but primarily high
school been young been which is it seems like like an oxymoron yeah definitely i mean i feel like
even when you i mean i could tell i could tell from the photos that even when you were young you had
an old soul yeah true you were you were wise beyond your ears wise beyond my ears you say and your eyes
uh should i be okay should i be dark skin should i be dark skin black juvie or should i go like
you're radiated green uh can you change your skin color yeah oh well then
no black black you like the black juvie okay yeah i like the black juvie uh then i'm gonna make the eyes
well you really like to fill around the sir stuff yes i do uh i mean this is this is half the game for
me oh go back to that straight striped like blue this one yeah i'm thinking i'm thinking like
we're a farm in juvie so i'm thinking like overalls you got overalls oh there's a there's a bunch of
overalls uh let's see i just i want to find some green ones you know there's a blue overalls
i don't know all these are gonna be cosmetics and this update by the way yes yes uh that's just
like a oh here we go green overalls there we go uh let me just adjust my uh pants color uh to match
oh yeah delicious oh yeah
all right let's get let's get this on the road wait i gotta choose my accessory
uh
this you really crack yourself up don't you i love it yeah
i don't even was that an oculus rift it was yeah well i think you know we're we're picking
but it's not green though i don't can't bin it's an oculus rift yeah you're not picking that he's
living in the virtual world you can give him a beard god you don't know what he could literally
have a be all right all right all right oculus rift it's oculus rifter but okay so what so what's
our what's our juvie's name j j j the juve no um jenny jerry uh jerry slimefield i like jenny
we've got we've got jenny the juve it's a it's a boy i know that's why i like it okay um
i could make it a girl no no we don't conform yeah um farm name is um uh uh our arson brook
arson brook farm okay wait is there a farm in arson brook i forget duh hmm who who the
fuck wanders that far north uh favorite thing uh favorite piece piece um animal what do you think
animal preference i think a dog because they're i mean yeah all right she was right okay standard
standard farm riverland well i guess arson brook we should pick riverland farm right yeah that makes
forest farm hilltop farm okay riverland farm let's get the intro thank god all right now we're
actually in the game hey yeah we're only 11 minutes in huh uh uh you can now uh devote some of your
mental power from choosing outfits to participate maybe you know we'll see we'll see about that
um so uh yeah how's it going nice one how's how are you how's it going over there
buddy it feels good it's it's sort of a surreal scenario to be recording especially rfck again
rfck is sort of the uh show where i don't have to like pretend to be someone i'm not like how i do
on every other uh performance piece like the pcp or anything it's like a defragmentation for my mind
so i don't even have to uh you know like uh scream or yell i i feel like it's just a a place for
nothing to happen and that's what makes it good yeah it's get ready for a whole lot of nothing
viewers it's entertaining the same way that gossip is or gossip makes it feel like oh you're like
you're on the inside of something you're you're like uh you're privy to knowledge not the not the
average bear is i feel like the same with rfck where it's not particularly like entertaining
like a song and dance or like a particularly good homeless show it's more like a homeless show like
a boss fights no like dancing you know you know but well you see well you see ben i come from new
a new york city impotencies nyc and at least there the homeless have the dcd dance for that
money that makes the difference between a classy homeless person dot dot dot and a bomb really
wow you learn something new every day anyway that's what rfck is like is it like a homeless fight
hell yeah hell yeah buddy um we we were just privy to some major goss i mean i think i've got
you and me yeah you and me together when uh our uh uh what do we call it is there a personal
name ragcon 3.33 uh i don't think we should call it that uh but i don't know what i would call it
either i don't want to call it the meetup which is what i think we called it an all-planning
the meetup i mean that's all it was true is uh there's a whole lot of it was a whole lot of
nothing if you know what i mean there's a whole lot of nothing going on oh i i i do know i say
making a jackoff motion with my hand oh hell yeah bro um okay so what so what about it what about the
goss oh i'm just saying that i mean it was basically nothing but that uh there was goss sure
this is sort of like a continuation of of a long running storyline that was started way back in
frog fractions two episode one that i think uh it's sort of a culmination of all that uh there's
been many false culminations where this might be the real culmination i mean they if like fucking
hopefully hopefully this one will stick fine i actually don't know what you're talking about
i mean that this feels like uh way back in frog fractions two episode one we're talking about
oh peace to be friendship we want to be all close together oh yeah blah blah blah blah
whole bunch of nothing and uh there's been a bunch of uh you know development on that if i develop i
mean maybe in fact uh the opposite of development and in fact the regression um such you know i feel
fine i think i think everything's i think everything's gonna work out just fine with all
that i'm you know i left feeling a little dismayed but uh upon reflection you know upon
mulling it over hearing everyone else mull it over i you know you know everyone's everyone's
gonna everyone's gonna settle into what they want what they want you know what they want to be doing
where they want to be it's all gonna come to its natural equilibrium point uh might be
in too vague here i don't know how how how into this do you want to get i'm sure i'm sure there's
uh is any of it like is any of it like proprietary i i don't think so but i get the feeling that others
might think so are these rocks what are these things what logs no these oh yeah those are rocks
but i think i need like a hammer i think i need a hammer to destroy them and i don't have a hammer
uh i can get one somewhere fiber i got fiber you do please got wood why is there a hole in my porch
why is there a hole in my porch i don't know anyway uh i
i i'm ready i'm i'm i'm down again do it we can always cut it we can always uh you know remove
this video we can always uh make sure that no one right clicks the url this video as soon as it goes
public and then uh downloads as an mp4 and uh saves it before we can delete it hell yeah
no no load please uh well no load um what am i saying you know uh you know it seems like
nate doesn't you know at the time it was like nate wants to do the thing with digi
and did do that this new show or whatever and digi wants to move so nate was gonna move and i was
like ah but do you want to i don't think you want to go i didn't say this because i don't want to
tell anyone how to live their lives or anything but i was thinking like you're gonna do it publicly
now instead well i mean this is after the dust has settled right uh okay i you know i i was i mean i
i mean i told him this in a call or something uh i was like at the time i thought uh you know do
do you actually want to go where digi's going um wherever that is and then you have to remember
that no one knows what this meeting is about it's stuff from the very beginning do i i know how would
anyone know what has happened well we were meeting to discuss like who where people were you know i mean
basically the meeting was just where is digi moving that was it that was the meeting and i i didn't
like it i was very i was very bored i had very little contributed uh from my perspective pcphq
for a while now has been settled like tom digi you and me eventually in yeah in just a short while
will be in the same place and so i thought wow only nate and then maybe hippo need to come and then
like you know oh it's there it is for a while i've been saying like opcpq is founded like the
foundation is already there there's already things happening as because of it i'm games
prime example uh but uh somewhat to my surprise last time uh i was there i found out uh apparently
the the seeds of discourse were planted and in fact it's not at all uh figured out or decided
well it's it's very much an open question well it's just digi wants to move digi doesn't like
boston for reasons uh i don't get them i mean i think i've tried i think we've all tried to
i think you've all tried to dissuade him he doesn't like the cold the what cold he doesn't
like to shovel that's not that's not really the reason i don't know it's not no that's like
that's like eight why that's i mean that's like eighth thing down the list and the first seven are
my house is too expensive um and like i don't know there are cheaper houses but i just don't
i don't know if he wants to hear it uh yeah well well anyway whatever anyway uh this this
this whole mean we've we attended we gathered everyone up it was just supposed to be like i
was there and then you guys were already and then Nate was gonna fly on then hippo just surprise
yeah uh everyone like like a week before and came out uh which was cool
very uh it was a great time i don't really care about getting like to the meeting specifically
though i know people will be clamoring for it in in the comments and stuff like that
but frankly i don't really care about what was discussed yeah yeah i'm with you i'm with you
like it was a bunch of stuff that doesn't really concern me no a bunch of i didn't i didn't like
i said i i didn't really bear that much on me personally it doesn't matter where anyone else
because i'm not planning on leaving here so a bunch of stuff in the future deciding where people
want to live their lives uh seems like it's possible that psphq will not be in boston and you know
like sad question mark
like i i think about it in the sense that like who do i want to be around in my life
for various reasons you know work or or socially i don't know if i need to be around everyone
you know i like you ben as you might be able to tell i don't know if you can gay gay gay gay gay gay
gay and so i want to be in boston or you know around you because we do work together and we're
good friends yeah same thing with other psp members but not like everyone i don't know if i need to
be in pcphq i don't know if i care about like the the group it has a concept i used to i don't
know if i do anymore not through any degradation of character but just out of uh i know what you mean
like you know me like i like hippo but we don't like do anything to get i mean maybe if we lived
nearby we would but as it currently stands we don't and that's you know nothing wrong with that
um but like we don't need to you know let live together i mean same with me and tom like i like
tom i like hanging out with tom if you know he moved it wouldn't disrupt anything about what
i'm doing you know right uh funnily enough the two people you mentioned are the two people who i would
like to be near the most well yeah i mean so would i i'm just saying it's not yeah it's not a it's
it's not like a yeah i i get me mean yeah i i i i i i it just feels like there's no real like
there's no real like personal professional crossover there is what i'm saying that's all that's all
i'm saying dog i i get you yeah i get you and i'm in the same boat it it's like you know there
there are two reasons we have someone either you like them a whole lot or you know you have work
with them and you know if they can overlap then that's good but you know sometimes you can just
work with someone a lot and you know you like them but you don't have to be near them to work with them
in the case of digi like i mean what what would we do together in person that we could not do
over the internet like why do we have to live together not a whole lot of reason we don't have
like similar interests it's not like we have the same i conception of like what to do to have fun
so it's not like we would have that social relationship necessarily let's say that i'm not
friends digi you obviously understand that yeah um yeah nobody understands hating digi bro more than
been yeah yeah gotcha yeah uh man i feel like i kind of didn't really use my didn't really use all
my energy today you know you gotta you gotta be efficient in this game you gotta use your resources
much much like the stock market much much like the stock market you gotta be you gotta be schmott
you gotta be it's a pretty risky game i mean you know vegetation is on the line
it's it's it's it's not a risky game if you know how to play it it's a lot yeah yeah it's not not
if you know how to play it have we told that story should we tell that story on but you definitely
should okay okay so this was uh i think this will no this was maybe between your last two visits
yeah me and uh me and uh kazzie were out for community day uh might have been syndical day
doesn't matter um we went to what's that something cafe dumpling cafe yeah dumb we went to dumpling
cafe and um world renowned everyone everyone rfca knows who dumpling cafe is like oh they will know
they will know dumpling cafe because it's ours like spot now you know we own it it kind of is
it just sort of happens stands developed into our place but it is now yeah we all like it um it's
where it's pretty much like our default where do we go eat when we're downtown in boston um much
like how i'm holding out hope for psphq boss i'm also holding out hope for t do rfca uh headquarters
once you fuck fuck t do man what fuck all you t do bitches that then you'll really basic ass
basic ass t do bitches god i miss those popping bubbles i know i know ben you're
you're missing out i am look i know i know i'm missing out on the popping bubbles i love the
popping bubbles the boba go the tapioca bubbles but but the popping bubbles
it's where it's at man you know i wasn't so canned tapioca but i actually had some tapioca
the other day wasn't that bad actually it's not i mean i don't hate it it's not gross but it's it's
whatever um but the popping bubble anyway the point is we were in um dumpling cafe we were sitting
near like a booth or whatever we were sitting at which we're sharing a table a long table with
this family it was like a mom a kid who was maybe like 13 and the dad on the other side
and the dad was dressed in like a sweat shirt what he was just pretty casually and the mom
and the son they're playing pokemon go so me and kazi are like hey sup pokemon and they're like
oh hey pokemon you know like you do and um the kid is like oh shinies yeah we're talking about
did you get any shinies i think i asked them like did you get any shinies and he's like oh i got tons
of shinies oh and he shows me his alolan raticate and he's like oh look i've got a shiny raticate
and i'm like i got so many of these and i'm like that's an alolan raticate and he's like dammit
wait wait so he knew he was trying to pass it off like he got shinies i don't know i don't i don't
seem like i don't know if he knew or if i had just like and i blew his mind or if he got caught out
and he was upset about it if i if i were in that scenario it wouldn't be like oh dammit it would be
like what like it would be like i like your mind to be blown yeah it wouldn't be like oh like i
it sounds like he's been found you know when i heard the story you know now that i think about it
it's true yeah i wouldn't be mad i would be i would be confused first not frustrated yeah yeah you
know what that's a little punk ass bitch you just caught that guy out dude i think he was i think
he may have i think we may have a little punk ass bitch on our hands and you know we do punk ass
bitches around he had a real punk ass bitch haircut um he um he had another one he had like a dyed green
he had like a like a poorly dyed green sort of flip top no way just like i do just like i do now
this is a real juvie yeah yeah yo he was such a he was such a fucking juvie um it was oh man i love
it okay but that's that's not the point the point is we're talking about pokemon we're talking about
catching shinies and the dad on the other side of the table is like huh these guys in their video game
and i'm like and i'm like haha yeah uh you know i also video game and he's like the only video the
only game i play is the stock market and i'm like whoa that's a pretty risky game you know that's too
risky a game for me and he's like not if you know how to play it right damn this is fucking brutal
i feel like when you spoke those words like flew back like a powerful like blast just occurred
it was like using a blank in uh enter the gungeon everything was blown back all all bullets were
wiped from from screen um i need a hammer i need a hammer so bad um that's it just gotta wait
nothing's open is it the beach south of town before five p.m okay i guess i'll do well i'm gonna
clear my house out a little bit uh i'm just gonna just gonna gotta use some of this energy
gotta use some of this energy dude you have an energy stat yeah it's on the bottom right
oh damn you can only you can only do so much in a day before you get exhausted
uh that's a marvelous story it is thank you for sharing he was a powerful powerful man
and i was intimidated he he's clearly a like i like and that's why he had a little punk ass
bitch of a son why is it that always the hardest men have the softest sons is that true yeah i yeah
didn't you hear did i hear you say it just now yeah yeah okay yeah yeah yeah that's that's a good
point um man i don't know you know some things are just a mystery and that's one of them ben would
i'd be able to beat up your son like newborn i mean did you get the drop on him no fair it's a
duel a fair fight i'd know no i don't think so no i'm sorry what what what what techniques what
skills does he have could he possibly retain um well he uh you know uh like not before you before
it goes to the ground right like on the ground it's all it's all about holds you know but like
before that it's all about momentum and um you know a baby a properly trained baby
you know the the the the mass differential between the two combatants is massive therefore
you know proper technique at redirecting momentum is is even more devastating
uh i've got two questions for you about your son number one how much does he weigh
number two was the date he born on significant for any other reasons such as was it a holiday
was it perhaps uh uh the uh you know the date of a historical event is does he get any sort of
date bonus um was he born on like january 1st and therefore had like psychic abilities first
dancer wait almost nothing second dancer um um talk like a pirate day and he hates it because
every year for his birthday he gets he gets novel he gets novelty hooks he gets novelty
hooks to wear over his hand because because you know everyone's because everyone's just
stocked up on those for talk like a pirate day anyway so they're then they they they double up
on it they double up on it and make it a and make it a birthday gift uh he hates he hates pirates
ben st jr walking down an alley away is topped by some some you know scurvy looking youths and
they say oh it's talking a pirate guy hey talk like a pirate guy talk like a pirate for us yeah
where you don't talk like a pirate guy come on it's try it you know and i and i'm i'm looking on
like this is i'm this is this is all playing out on the soccer fields you know and i'm sitting in
the bleachers with setting one tear throwing rocks at him to try and encourage him to greater heights
of athleticism you you you're shaking a little tear i knew i shouldn't have hired those thugs to
yeah i knew sons of spirits they're just they're just they're good why are they why are they
taking it too far why are they taking it so easy on him uh i don't know you know once it varies
depends on my mood depends on my mood oh i oh god i can upgrade tools oh god i can upgrade tools
oh god but i need fucking copper i need fucking copper i think i'm gonna have my son be like a
puzzle a puzzle like a puzzle solver like puzzler go on like he's like his like his main his only
stat will be intelligence and he'll just be able to solve rubies cubes and tetris games and like an
instant wow impressive on the mean streets of florida he'll be able to uh get by by by only
entertaining the common street criminal that comes into his abodes i imagine a lot of like a sort of
like dingy little shop where you know criminals and outlaws can enter for free and uh be entertained
for the afternoon criminals and outlaw was welcome the sign says on the yeah yeah no no track record
no service do you know what this game's about by the way no i have no idea what's happening the the
intro to this game is you are a you are a corporate you are a corporate cubicle slave shill uh working
for jojomart working at like jojomart corporate headquarters and then you inherit a farm from
your grandpa and you're like fuck this and you uh and you run away to you quit your job and you run
away to uh this little town to like take on the farm and start and start living a farmer's life
that's so clean but also jojomart there's like a jojomart branch there's like a jojomart branch
that's open in the town and like if you shop and like the prices are cheaper but like the more you
shop here like the worst everything gets and like the worst like the local yeah like the worst the
local economy does you need to like like you need to invest in like the local like mom and pop stores
to keep them in business or like jojomart takes over and you get bad end that's crazy i know it's
sick it's like real life it's literally real life it's like when when the opening intro plays
and like you see your your character like being a corporate stooge and it's it's like the game
itself like in your in you the player's real life you're a corporate stooge but you're you know
you're turning on this game and you're escaping you're escaping from your corporate life into the
world of fucking whatever just like you know you're turning on this game to escape from from your
daily they grind you know to go be a be a farmer for a little while if you if you feel me god i hate
capitalism i hate capitalism is that even weird i don't think so i don't think it's wow when are
ben and nate gonna gonna when are we really gonna get their legendary capitalism good
conversation the conversation to end all capitalism um i mean that'll pretty much that'll
pretty much be it that'll oh fuck i didn't mean to do that now there's a hole in the beach
yeah that'll pretty much be it we're gonna sort out this whole capitalism thing
oh fuck i've only got an hour to get to the beach
anyway uh yeah so the answer is patreon patronize me at patreon.com slash ben saying if you want
to see me really kill take take take on a capitalism really take nate to task for his
questionable capitalism feelings shit oh god i'm gonna miss it i'm gonna miss it
what are you trying to say i don't know there's some there's some kind of like thing i have to be
fuck i have to be at the beach at five four you know specifically picking games i was like you
know starting valley seems like a pretty uh you know uh uh low tempo game and that's enough
you're a fool turn it on and i'm like oh god i'm gonna miss my deadline i gotta get to the beach
by five p.m and talk to willy the sailor what we called you son dad no i think my dad's dead
actually i don't think your dad is relevant in this game it's just your your grandpa's
dead though and he left you his farm it doesn't seem like a game i enjoy what a game about your
grandpa being dead no a game without a visible father figure i mean i mean i mean some people
play games to relax some people play games for monetary benefit i play games to uh reconnect
with my father by pretending that i have one i wonder i wonder if uh maybe i mean if if your
dad is not otherwise mentioned maybe maybe it's possible this guy is your dad maybe willy the
sailor is your secret dad the whole time i mean it's not a secret he calls you son
yeah but he was disguising it with colloquialism right like as all good fathers do
disguise and their true intentions hey ben why do you hate your parents don't like you asked me
this before i don't hate my parents they just me and my dad would fight all the time when i was
younger like you they show up to digi's house to drop up a chicken or something innate and to you
know be pleasant for me michelle is michelle the chicken oh no i thought they brought over food
bring me up to you but right on three oh yeah they brought over meatballs right on three yeah
anyway uh they come over and they're like hi ben and you and you're just in a stupor as usual sitting
on the couch splayed out lethargic beleaguered that's trying to play trying to play jack jack three
failing miserably and you say hi mom grating your teeth that's not what happened they were there for
like they were there for like half an hour they were there for like a little while they stood
around and we chatted and then your mom comes comes to hug you and kiss you and you say stop mom
for my bit my friend yeah oh yeah i guess i i guess that did happen ha ha um
look what he's what just what what is it what do you want i want you admit that you hate your
parents on live television okay i it's all true um no just me and my me and my dad we're at each
other's throats all the time i was a little when i was a kid what could you cause possibly be a
throats about about that sweet old man i don't i you know he wasn't always old believe it or not
um i don't know you just fucking be on my case about everything all the time and it really pissed
me off that's it that's the story not there's there's i know it's it's there's nothing to it um
he's just a jerk he was like a really like uh he's very he's very particular kind of like
he's very he's very like detail oriented he's very much like all about fuck he's all about like
you know keep keep keep everything keep all your ducks in a row keep everything really like well
categorized keep a keep a keep a spreadsheets he would like he would like draft up um he would
like draft up contracts for us to sign uh a lot what he would he would he would he would be like
we would have like a family meeting and be like okay here are all the chores here's all the chore
listings or whatever here's how we're like dividing the labor of the house does everyone agree to
ratify this agreement suddenly so many things make sense you just say in that yeah suddenly
everything falls into place does everyone does everyone agree to ratify this agreement okay
then everyone sign like everyone is expected to sign within the week or whatever this i want to
say is a completely obvious assessment though it like like like like literally however it feels
right you can either like become brainwashed by your parents or hate your parents you know
it's either you either you either become them or you go the opposite yeah there's i mean i mean
there's no other option to do you either are like the more you aren't yeah but it's either i feel
like it's intense you know i feel like it's a uh neither you know nate obviously would do that and
does that in real life currently now you know as as i was saying that i was realizing that's like
very that's very that yeah the way he like the way he was at radcon was or not right the way he was
at the meet-up rather is just a very very that was a very dead uh way to be i wonder if he'd be mad
i wonder if he'd be mad hearing me say that maybe but it was why would that why would that be bad
you know nobody wants to nobody wants to become their parents right isn't that like a thing like
you know you get you start getting into adulthood and then suddenly you realize you've become your
parents and you have an existential meltdown um sounds like a cartoon and if you know there's
one thing that i hate it's cartoons uh is this procedurally generated by the way the town is
not i think the farm is uh or no i'm gonna go with no i don't think there is a procedurally
generated part there's like a dungeon in the game there's like a what yeah there are mines and in the
mines there are monsters that you have to like fight with so yeah yeah yeah there are monsters you
have to fight with swords and that dungeon is procedurally generated but i think the rest of the
game is not okay does that answer your question poorly uh i want a hammer i know i have to buy
it somewhere but i don't remember where uh so so i imagine i'm i'm i'm i'm hard on this father
kick as you can as you can probably tell so so so he would just get mad at you about like if your
room being messy or whatever or something um more sinister things yeah i guess like nothing like
unusually yeah i remember room being messy but like i don't know i just always thought he had
a shit attitude about it he was always very like like when he was mad he was very like self
righteous he was very like i like the reason like the like this i am not i am not upset for practical
reasons i'm upset for moral reasons you know like what you have done is wrong uh and i hated it uh
really pissed me off every every every single time i remember there was one time i think i was in
like i might have been in college and i was home for this and i don't remember what was happening
i think he was doing he was doing the thing he was doing the boomer thing he was like ben get a job
but don't like apply online he's like no ben you you must you must like because applying for jobs
online doesn't look like work right like it looks easy you're just sitting there you're just
sitting around the house you know sitting on the computer you know applying for jobs online
bullshit you gotta get out there and you gotta pound the pavement son you gotta get out there in the
car do you say pound the pavement yes he said pound the pavement you gotta get out there in the car
you gotta drive around for eight hours a day i want you out of the house in the car for eight
hours a day going to every fucking shitty restaurant in like in like in concentric circles around the
town hand them an application that's how i want you that's how i want you find and work around
here and i was just like oh god this is i hate i hate it i hate it this is dumb and we got mad
we got into a fight and i'm and i'm like i'm like livid right i'm fucking like i'm like
i'm probably i'm like totally losing my composure as we're having the fight and he and he's and he's
getting and he's getting mad too right we're getting heated and he sees that i'm heated
and he says he says ben control your rage and i'm like i can't believe you're a real person
it makes me so mad that you are who you are i didn't say that like i don't remember what i
said but that was the that was the feeling and that was you know so there so anyway that's why i hate
my parents that's a pretty good reason yeah uh what what a fucking fascinating story
i i'm i'm i'm i'm particularly enthralled by by pound the pavement uh hashtag that put that on a
shirt like pound the pavement you know it's real right it's that's like a cliche but it's real he
lives it i i imagine the solution to your problem would just be like have a laptop and then and then
like say like all right guys all right dad going going out gain some jobs and just take your laptop
to look at starbucks or something uh yeah i didn't exist in 1920 yeah um yeah you know i hopped i hopped
in my model t ford and i yeah yeah yeah yeah you know i went i went down i went down to the local
malt shop for a for a for a for a soda and for a syrup and soda or something and and a cigarette
yeah um you know that i rolled myself out of tobacco that i that i picked with my own two hands
that don't make i don't make them like they used to
isn't it weird how when people get old they just become so pathetic and sweet
um no have you noticed this no
everyone oh wait i have a oh god i'm so dumb i'm so fucking dumb munchie i could have been
breaking those rocks i don't need an i don't need a hammer i the pickaxe the pickaxe does it i have
the tool for it i'm an idiot um is there any like time uh like like uh do you have like a
certain number of days you have to accomplish a task no it's not like it's not like harvest moon
you're playing harvest moon no i know about it harvest moon i mean you can play infinitely but
there is like a time i think you have like a certain number of years and after that number
of years goes by um your grandpa like comes back no it's your dad your dad or your grandpa or whatever
comes back to like see how you've done and if you've done everything you need to do you get good end
um but the uh in this game there is no time limit per se but there is a calendar and like
certain events will happen on certain days of the year but like there's no limit to how many years
you can do shit is there a win state uh i don't think so i mean you can get married uh you can
get married and have a kid um but yeah is he like the npc bot that does the farm stuff for you
the kid no no that would be really funny here we go look at all the stone you're getting i god i
feel so stupid i'm sure how long are we in we're like for 45 minutes and i'm sure for the last
like half an hour someone has been screaming at me like you idiot just use the pickaxe just break
the stones with the pickaxe what did i think the pickaxe was for i don't know i just thought it was a
scythe but thinner that's my story like yeah gotcha i love seeing rip through that those that tall grass
please dude we go i'm gonna kill so many pokemon hell yeah i love this yeah this is so satisfying
you know you can cut the tall grass in pokemon like in the real games yeah yeah yeah with cut that's
so crazy i have no idea i think you you could yeah you could even as far back as red and blue
why yeah i know right like why did they why like i mean it doesn't detract from the game
no really sure but doesn't doesn't really add anything you know about it yeah no i found that
out and i did it and i was like oh my god this game this game doesn't even work and yet they included
that yeah yeah the moves just don't do what they're supposed to do and yet they were like you know
would be really nice to put on top of this broke ass game that doesn't work just a nice cute little
feature where you can cut the grass with the grass tm i think they'd really appreciate that and you
know what they were right it makes easy to backtrack i guess huh makes it easier to backtrack i guess
i mean i guess if you really don't want to have a random encounter but it's probably
by repel it's just faster to walk maybe if you're like maybe if you're if you're nuzlocking right
because they because when they were making red and blue they were planning for that no they're
like if someone's nuzlocking this game and like they really need to get to a pokemon center like
and they really don't want to have and they're like really low they really don't want to have a
random encounter you know let's include this this cut the grass feature um you know fell appreciated
whoa look at this right seed seed fell right into that oh i can't oh i can't fucking get it
the seaweed get the eat seaweed hell hell yeah i'm gonna eat that seaweed that refill your energy
um i think so is it like crafting is this like minecraft i uh you know i haven't played that
much of this game i know that you can take you need materials to like upgrade your tools i don't
know if there's like crafting from scratch but i think probably like probably there are npcs in
town who will like combine shit for you into potions and stuff and energy potions or something
we gotta play minecraft i'll play minecraft uh we did i'm we did for a while they play on rfck
one of these days um what i wonder what the rfck server is looking like these days
oh that shit oh whatever who cares hey should we give well i guess can man already want a
contest we should give him we should give him something for the arg he should have a princess
for that um sure i think we did i mean now we're gonna i'm gonna give uh i gotta make i gotta make
um like league championship badges for uh armisi and sweetmouse because they because they you know
i i gotta do everything i gotta fucking i i i i have to do all my princess cuz i haven't made
any of them i have made four uh there's a bunch from there you know they're not that much work
per se but they're stressful it's like ah should i cut the sapling it's like oh man i
hey if there's a tiny frog it's like you know i really want to i really want to sit down and
think and make it like funny you know make make it good it would be such a shame to make a princess
item and look it's not funny or it's like eh you know there's like no reason to have it yeah yeah
also uh other players can't read the description right only the person who owns it can read the
description uh yes but they can read they can do it publicly i mean they can only do it publicly
wait really oh like when you look when you look item yeah or whatever oh okay yeah all right that's
fair that's fair what did i make i made um i made um retro pks uh giant novelty pencil i may wait
the retro gamer kevins prince applied in the right right right yeah no he's he's i got a whole bunch
lined up for him yeah um retro pks giant novelty pencil i made aj aj shoups okay so aj wanted a pair
of cop killer purple greaves um so i called them did you see what i made them no i was very proud
so you know you know greaves they're like armor they're like leg armor so i called them get this get
this i called them the legislators very good thank you thank you my friends yeah i i i love the
lash raiders from home stuck right i hate you i knew you would say that i knew i knew dullard
that you are i knew you would be i knew you would say that fool that i am i fall for any uh reference
to comic books i've seen it's a you know it's a real word right you know it's a real word
you from yeah yeah hussey actually got that word from real life if you can believe it
i've only read the bible in home stuck that's it well because you need in any other context i would
say that i would say congratulations but not today but well i'm mad at you else i'll say i'll say
what the fuck yes that's right that's right man i dropped what there was a piece of coal there was
a piece of coal down here and i'm not leaving uh without it uh no coal left behind that's it
that's my joke shout out to coal shout out to coal uh shout out to coal who's you know came up with
a lot of the tech in this run you know who really helped yeah he really helped with the route you
know just put in so much work he's just really and you know not to mention you know he's just really
active in the community you know he's just a great guy you know like newbies coming to the
community you know he's just so willing coal is just so willing to help them out he put together
the wiki all by himself yeah yeah yeah um sad you know do you just do you have no life really
you must have no life yeah but still shout out to coal shout out to coal is you know we love having
him around thank god hey ben last night in the pcp chat we were talking and and and and and then
like like chast virgins we said no we have to save this for fck oh god what were we talking about
also it's pronounced chaste i believe chaste i think you know you know it might be one of those
words you can say either way but i think no i'm gonna bet no i'm putting my foot down on this one
we were talking about productivity and and projects and we're doing some of those our lives
oh yeah at uh at the meetup there was a legendary long night of discussion with me you tom caroline
and michelle for kazi for anyone that doesn't know caroline is kazi whatever whatever well
okay fine who cares okay anyway in in in uh conversation it wax and waned many times
it ranged from various uh explicit stories you told about about you know sluts you've banged
yeah and and interdates you've been on and uh it eventually it eventually uh uh you know devolved
into a sort of understated sorrow about how much uh oh we don't uh contribute to society and how our
lives are uh you know not what they could be uh huh there there's written there was a lot of talk
about how uh we aren't productive enough about how we are uh sad saps that one right and uh i i feel
like i i've been on a sort of productivity uh thank space for a few months now and that was a
a really great conversation to have and i'm very much interested in what other people
had to say about their about the productivity about how they work and about uh what what they
accomplish and so i was happy to have that conversation that was the catalyst for uh uh
i feel like at least for you i mean you you had a real fire in your eyes after that conversation
you had a real like you know drive to to work on stuff again after us talking about how uh
we'll never be andrew hustling we have an updated comics every single day for a year so i'm gonna
eat this raw heron thanks uh uh what what and and just last night you said that you had been
more productive than you ever been in months so um i said that i feel that i have become more
productive for a hot second there i mean
for between between maybe like uh i don't know
up up to like maybe september like it's not that i didn't feel like i was working but like the work
that i was doing was not i would like spend like a whole week or whatever like fucking around with
like the store you know like the rfck storefront which was like a waste of that very i remember
that very vividly that was like a like a real like section of your life yeah it was like a week an
entire like two weeks i spent and like it's so dumb like i don't i know i know how that sounds
i know you think about that and you're like how could it have possibly taken that long and yeah true
but like i found ways i found like i was working like hard i was like going at it like
constantly moving between like okay you know set setting up the store you know looking like oh well
making making new products uh making new um uh like look like compare like making a spreadsheet
to like compare like prices and product margins between like the different uh you know the different
store like which one is the best deal which one is the has the best this which one has the
best that where should i make this that and the other thing you know gotta maximize gotta make
it as efficient as possible gotta make it you know good looking gotta make it gotta make assets
gotta make banners gotta make icons you know i made it i made it uh take fucking where's the
goddamn blacksmith where's the goddamn blacksmith munchie what did you what have you done listen
i'm i won't tell you where he is but all i'll say is that you'll never be able to find him
can you enter the sewer also you were midthought what
oh you're just talking about oh uh anyway and you know that that i was kind of doing the same
thing with endless war like i was working on endless war but like there wasn't a lot like
there weren't a lot of moments when i was like okay this is done like it's done and i did a thing
i would just kind of i don't know it wasn't efficient and it was bad like like when i did it
when i did um slime oids like when i finally got back to slime oids like i had left that
for a while because i was like oh that's hard and i don't remember how to do it but when i
finally got back into it like i did it and then within like a week of restarting like it was done
and they came out and it was a new thing and it was it was done um we've got to process this geode
that that's a very interesting thought about how you can do a lot of work more work than you
would do normally but still have it feel like you haven't accomplished anything yeah i feel like that
especially recently when i'm doing more long-term projects like endless war where you can do i
upgrade my inventory or something sorry this is pissing me off okay okay i don't think anyone
would be like particularly surprised to find out that i haven't been like the most productive
member of the pcp or anything like that for the past you know whatever three years or something
but i feel like it might feel like to anyone looking in that i've been particularly absent
like i haven't made a whole lot of things recently but i feel like i've accomplished
way more not just in the sense that like i've been doing things outside of the internet
but even just the stuff i've been doing on there has had more thought put into it and i mean
stuff like endless war sure you can like push an update but even that doesn't feel like it's
anything new doesn't feel like a product you've made yeah like i can release a new video i can
be like wow new video no one can deny that i've made a thing yeah but even when you're making
like code or something you know it may even still feel then you know you put something out you still
feel like it's just been you know you've added upon something it's not like a a new thing you've
done making yeah making slime woods felt like it almost felt like a new thing because it was sort of
like a game within the game but even that is still like like the product the product is still
endless war which you know has kind of been out so it's not like a new yeah it's a little it's a
little it's a little bit of a drag honestly that like yeah endless war is one thing and you can't
be like hey guys it's out because like it's already out yeah even though it's even though it's constantly
being expanded and and we probably like like like it's possibly reached its its natural base
you know without what do you mean well i mean like anyone who would have clicked on it from the
pcp audience oh i see i see what you mean um yeah well oh man i was gonna say this is why
we need to advertise and maybe we still do but i'm but i'm project wonderful doesn't exist anymore
didn't realize didn't realize did you know that you can date this guy no you can date this guy
i think cool yeah imagine that like an old guy he's like old and shit and you can date him
sick hell yeah um uh uh oh yeah project wonderful um doesn't exist anymore uh sad bad uh i was like
oh well i guess i'll just have to find lol the guy's got no shirt on haha i guess i'll just have to
find another whatever service replaced it you know and advertise with them the answer is nothing
replaced it all the web comics that had project wonderful ads on them now just have nothing um
so you know marketing opportunities gone uh i actually got a lot of traffic to my website in
the past i didn't do this all the time but every now and then i would advertise through project
wonderful and the results were not earth shattering but i definitely got traffic for what i would
consider to be generally a reasonable price so i'm actually pretty bummed and i think there's a
missed opportunity here there's lost there's a lost opportunity costs with endless war uh itself
um i mean the i seems like the alternative is like google ads google ad words which i don't
know anything about but that's what they say that's what people say is like probably the other
thing to advertise uh with uh but i don't know
yep well i mean google ad words just sounds evil it's a yeah sure sure oh my god there's a goth boy
oh my god there's nothing more there's like he's a killer he's a fucking killer avoid
avoid i gotta play this i gotta play this game like a juvie i gotta think like a juvie if i want
to survive oh yeah he is in this in this world it's killer be killed
how many i have to make uh i need to meet i need to greet three more people
in this world it's easily be killed in this world it's be killed
uh truly life is hell for a young juve what would you so so would you say that you've
like like how would you say you've been more productive recently because i mean do you
still feel that way you said for a hot second you felt competitive is that is that weighing at all
um
may it well i don't feel that productive today because like for the last couple days
i've done other shit and i haven't gotten anything done um so maybe you don't like it like
there's like social stuff yeah yeah like i fucking went on that failed tinder day at lull
do you want to talk about that sure i guess um well but like you know other than that like i got my
poo videos coming out and those are good i'm doing you know i kept i've kept to my schedule
for two weeks now and that feels pretty good uh i'm not actively working on the secret project
the secret the secret uh rfck project in the unholy slime dungeon right now um because i'm
kind of just waiting for kind of waiting for there to be a little more there to work with um
but like once it's done like the hard part will be over and it will probably take less work than
slime oids did to get to get that new feature up and off the ground um oh hey a plant
i can't okay um fuck what was i oh my date my tinder date uh man boy so all right uh
the way i've been i don't look at tinder much sometimes when i'm bored i will just open it up
and just swipe swipe swipe swipe swipe right right right right right until there's nothing left
sometimes although that's a lot and i don't i don't have the patience to do that anymore um
they'll just swipe swipe swipe swipe see how many matches i get and then don't do anything don't
message them or whatever such a weird system wait what it's just it's like uh yeah well it's
not a system bunch it's not designed to get results like you're pulling a wide net and
laying the fishes die on the seabed that's yeah that's literally yeah i'm passing the widest net
possible pulling in all the fish letting them die right on my deck yep that that's that's how it's
been um and it's fucking sick yeah oh i if you if you couldn't tell it's great it's the best
well i rest assured viewers uh uh wait what what why can't i hear you you sound like shit
i i do what wait you're back it might have been my headphones might have been
discord it doesn't matter well right i'm here rest there is the fuck no no no say it again
say it again say it again couldn't hear you rest assured viewers fucks if if what he says
is to be believed he has fucked before very hard in multiple occasions thanks thanks man that's
that's that's my uh statement i mean don't don't believe it but if it is to be believed which it
isn't um okay what what happened the day um right so i've been letting these these fish as you call
them as you call women so sexistly um and so aptly as well so and aptly yeah um die on on the vine
to mix my metaphors a little bit um but uh this this time this time you know she messaged me and
she's like hey how whatever and i'm like hey and um she's like i look at her pictures and like she's
fine and like here's the thing you expect you expect people to look worse in person than they
do in the picture so i'm looking at this and i'm like in the pictures she looks fine she looks
you know pretty all right in reality she's probably worse than all right because that's
how it works however however um i should probably be out of my house more often so i'm like so that
makes up the difference and i'm like okay fuck it so we talked for a while on tinder and we're
basically just like hey and and i'm just i'm just we're just like so you want to just meet up and
fuck around and she's like i guess and she's like but it's like you know we're gonna like meet up and
like chat first you know so she knows i'm not an x-murder because that's what you do you meet up
you briefly chat you make sure they're not a fucking murderer or a scammer or a psycho or whatever
and then you can fucking it's fine and whatever but so we meet up and i'm so i say so there's a
thing or it's like oh am i gonna go to her like i would have to take a bunch of trains to get to
her i say i'll do it but she could drive here and she says she doesn't care which so i'm like well
then i guess come here well uh did you do anything to prepare for this like like what preparation
like like outside your normal routine what did you do um well i had already showered that day
i um cleaned my room up a little bit you know just made it a little more presentable
and that's pretty much it i mean what else is there when you get right down to it
when you when you get right oh mining level precast proficiency new crafting recipe cherry bomb
damn damn that's that's pretty hardcore for a juvie we got a badass over here
uh we gotta crush this guy before he gets too powerful so you clean your room you showered
right and she's on her way to you she's driving she's so she's like let's meet in a public place
and i'm like uh how about tufts university because that's like right near my house i'm like meet me
in front of such and such building so she gets there so she so i'm like i walk over to tufts i
stand in front of car michael hall which is the the one and uh she's like where do i go and i'm like
car michael hall and she's like um gps doesn't gps doesn't work on college campuses and i by the way
this girl by the way this girl is 32 so she's like gps doesn't work in college campuses and i'm
a little perplexed by this but i'm like huh so i guess this means i guess this means she's using
gps like not google maps she's using like a gps device that's weird i think that's strange but whatever
we'll live right we can we can get we can get through this so she's lost on the campus she
doesn't know where this hall is and i'm like okay new plan because she's told she said she
want coffee so i'm like okay new plan meet me over at such and such cafe it's like two blocks away
it's over on the corner so i walk out over there and i'm waiting for maybe like 10 minutes 15 minutes
keep in mind it is freezing cold out like she's driving around in her car she seems like maybe
she's getting a little annoyed that she can't find the place i am standing out there it's freezing
cold my ears are burning uh while i'm waiting uh my mom texts me and says ben open your pokemon
go gifts um so i do that um and she arrives right and then she while i see her walking up and i'm
like hey and now you're like i said on tinder you expect you expect that they're gonna look worse
than their pictures does she look worse than her pictures yes obviously however not nearly as much
worse as i would as as she could have right so all in all i'm like okay you know i i can't complain
seriously okay i'm i'm just like okay can't complain can't complain like if they show up and
they're like obviously and like like another person you're within your rights to be like you know what
this is bullshit you know i'm out um but it's not but you know that's that's not this that's not that's
not it's fine it's it's fine is what i'm saying so i'm like okay so we go so she wanted coffee
however this cafe and the pastry shop that are on this corner were closed because apparently this
was like eight o'clock and i guess on weekdays or whatever that's night yeah um so i guess they
didn't they don't stay open that late on weekdays i didn't know that so i'm like hey so every so it
turns out these places are closed the only coffee option is dunkin donuts there's a dunkin donuts
like over there and she's like okay fine so we go to this dunkin donuts and we get coffee and we
sit down for a while and we talk about shit and it's pretty you know we're pretty we're both pretty
just like casual we're pretty like candid we're just like ah you know tinder ah you know she she's
like oh yeah you know i'm kind of like a serial like outside of tinder hookups i'm kind of like a
serial date or you know like a serial relationship have or i get it i jump really fast into something
you know too serious and i'm like all right fair you know whatever and
you know you know there's a but like i could go through i could go through the entire conversation
and and like be like point by point i don't remember most of it so actually no i can't do that
contrary to what i just said but the point is right like she like afterwards we get up we walk out and
like well as she was as we were texting before she had made a joke about like you know yeah like you
know you're like we'll we'll go over to your place you know assuming i don't run away in terror
so we get we walk outside and i'm like so are you running away in terror and she's like no i'm not
running away in terror but i got a text something came up you know with work and i got a deal with
it and i'm like okay so in my head it's like all right so i'm being i'm being dumped that's fine
so um so i show her the phantom you know obviously
as she's leaving as she's leaving i'm like hey hey so and so do you uh did you did you uh by the
way before you go did you see the phantom oh my god and and did she and she merely turned around
and said you know what i changed my mind work can wait work can wait yeah that's right um no
how did she respond how did like like like did she did she enjoy the phantom you know
did she see him i wasn't doing it to like impress her i just thought it would be funny like wouldn't
it be funny if i showed her the phantom right now by the way viewers the phantom is not my penis um
in case you don't explain it in any no no no but it's not my penis um it's it's it's it's a um
i mean it's another person it's the phantom there's yeah there's a person there's a being
there is an entity i'm relate to phantom horn before you get out of your mind yeah just just
i mean just guess what the phantom is and you'll never be able to do it no okay it's impossible
so i do so i do that so you show so i show her the phantom well i ask her if she's seeing the
phantom she says no and then i and then the phantom appeared then the phantom appeared coincidentally
and she was just she's just like oh ha ha ha and like what and i'm like and i'm like whatever
okay you don't appreciate she didn't care about the phantom she didn't appreciate the phantom
so i'm like all right no skin off no skin off my back bitch um right so i so anyway i buried her
in a shallow grave in my backyard um no but so you know i guess that's it i guess there's really
not much more to tell you that's how i got that's how i got dumped i don't know like why like you
know i like i get home you know i look at tinder i'm i'm deleted i'm unmatched and i'm like okay as
expected so i'll never know why i can only speculate um i mean do you have any speculation
well first of all are you are you do you like do you care like it does this affect you in any way
i mean this was not a person who i was highly invested in right however the the only reason
that i do care a little bit is that i kind of went into this feeling like i was kind of settling
right but i didn't like it was fine but i was kind of like i guess i guess um but then right
but then you know we met up in person and i was fine with her but she apparently found me
unacceptable for whatever reason and i feel you know i feel judged you know i feel like
someone who's someone who i didn't value very highly looked at me and was like no thanks and i'm
like huh what's what's you know you know what i mean so it's like your expectations of other people
and others are not the same like others of you so it's like you know like people who you think
aren't very good like look at you and think he's really not good so it's like you feel like i don't
know your standards are too high no uh it's just uh you know it's just like uh well shit man
you know what's wrong with me you know what what what what's uh what am i missing you know what
what's the problem you know what is the problem did you think did you find out no i told you i was
unmatched so you know i can't well how would i know do you have a speculation did the phantom
tell you i have a couple of guesses you know i i bet she went home with the phantom afterward
actually he's caught by the phantom yeah yeah um i have i have appears general store affordable
size 24 backpack oh fuck yeah so i have a couple of speculations oh wait wait joe jamart no fuck
oh i'd like to remind you are drilling operations entirely legal responsible stewardship of the
local enviroments of top priority i can't believe you showed her that i can't believe it didn't work
i know right what a what a what a downer so um i have a couple of speculations one she was a cat
person i said i'm not a pet person she said you know that's a sign of a sociopath and i said what
like can't and she and and she's like i mean she was kind of grinning so she might have been
joking but still like the fact that she said it is all at all i found it strange she was like
you know that's rat poison right yeah you know you know that's rat poison she she was like um
um yeah like you can not own a pet but you should at least be like oh i wish i had a dog and i'm
like what no and she's like yeah that's a sign of a sociopath tell me when you see a squirrel
when you see a squirrel on the road like when you pass a squirrel do you think about like
what's inside it and how you can get it out and i'm like what no and she's like okay
she's like well whoa wait what does she mean what's inside like like like that's not what she said
squirrels yeah she's like do you think about disemboweling squirrels and i'm like no and and she's
like okay i was a forensic psych major by the way and i'm like yeah all right sure i can tell yeah
it really shows and not necessarily in a good way um it's just i have a sociopath you know
oh yeah i'm not a dog person i like to watch squirrels get disemboweled though yeah pretty much
so so so that so that so i don't know if maybe she thought something about that i think more like
like i was joking about how small my room is right i was joking about like haha yeah it's basically
a closet i think she might have like believed me you know like and also like i told her that like
okay she definitely didn't like that i have uh housemates which fair you know i'm not even
gonna say they're like oh what the fuck it's fine like no whatever that that makes sense i get it um
so it might have been it might have been that she didn't want to come in here while there's like
other people live here you know i mean there wouldn't be like i mean they'd be in like separate rooms
but like yeah that's fair um maybe she didn't like maybe she thought oh this guy you know he's a
procast bitch and he's got you know his his room he lives in a closet you know no thanks
that while not true really you know if she believed that it's like well all right fair or it might
have been the dog sociopath thing probably not but you never know um yeah those are my spec
those are my speculations on the matter does does this like dissuade you from trying gender
or is this just like a blip on the radar and like you know i mean it was a little bit disappointing
i tried to give it but like i mean it was a little bit disappointing and it hurt my pride just a
little bit but like you know whatever uh that's that's that's what happens right that's that's
that's what that's well that well mark that's life to quote did a man after reciting your mini
past been uh trifles with with with the other gender yeah the lesser gender you mean yeah yeah
the lesser gender yeah uh are you trying like like this is i mean i don't know how often you
go on tinder but i've never heard of you going on a tinder date uh i um i tried to reconnect with
i went on i was on like before i moved in with digi like when i was living here at monkey house um
we'll have before i moved in with digi i was well i hadn't been for like when i when i moved in here
i was on tinder pretty a lot um i was doing a bunch of at some point i kind of like got sick of it
was like whatever uh and i stopped for a while and then in virginia beach it just didn't work
like there were no responses like they like i never got any matches because like nobody was
using it in tinder or whatever funny story okay i thought that like living near boston you would
get a ton of matches and that's kind of true however the matches that i get they don't come from
boston like never like nobody in boston is tinder it's all girls from salem like every single one
of them is a girl from salem i see and i don't get it i just don't fucking get it maybe when
you're in the city you don't like need tender uh maybe yeah maybe maybe it's like if you if you're
the kind of person who would use tender you are and you're in the city you would already be meeting
other people outside of the app so you would have no need for like a secondary source um person who
would need yeah like you know if you're like in a like a smaller town you know you're not gonna
meet as many people you'd be interested in oh wait wait for my return on the dawn of your third
year oh shit there is like a time limit grandpa's grandpa's coming back and he's gonna be in a mean
way oh shit um yes uh yeah that's a pretty good theory i believe that so so i mean are you trying
to take are you trying to get to another relationship no what's happening right now no stupid if i'm
fair uh okay i think that's pretty well covered i think we're this is pretty well covered at this
point what are you doing what are you watering outside right now by the way uh well i was clearing
out my fields oh shit i gotta water my shit god it's dark yeah it really is it why is like the
like the ground like red i don't know it looks like it's like the distortion world from uh
pokemon platinum hell yeah fuck yeah dude it's my least favorite game what level one i've never
i've never played cool wait uh well well i played diamond and pearl i played pearl and it was not
it was okay it was fine new craft i don't even know this before i can make a scarecrow now
does that do anything um i assume it scares away crows are there crows in this game uh
probably if there's a scarecrow then yes okay so today i have to go i have to go to pierre's
general store and i have to expand my bag that's my mission love stones gather if you have a surplus
having me build a well for you oh yes just swing by the shop with 75 stones oh shit i have a thousand
g wait wait wait wait wait wait wells can be placed all over your farm and service convenient
places to refill your watering can't no no i have a fucking lakes i live on a river get
fucked robin um okay so that's so that's what's up with that that that's what's happening made this
game was this like an indie game or is this like one guy made this game uh oh whoa okay yeah if i'm
not mistaken uh i don't remember his name you know it was listed at the beginning it was a screen name
for some reason okay the saloon opens at noon i should come back then uh pierre's general store
so okay i feel like i feel like i got a half i got a half answer uh so so what are you
you're you're making poo videos now do you feel like you're making more projects that haven't been
released or do you feel like you are just like like like how are you more productive are you
working on comics more i asked you this i was i was working on comics more uh for a while i haven't
gotten a page out in maybe like a week or maybe oh god maybe going on two weeks which is bad but i've
been doing endless war i've been i've been i've been organizing a bit that uh you know the secret
project and i've been um you know making the poo videos i'm gonna be on i've been talking to
low art and gonna be on the movie podcast with him uh i'm gonna talk about poo's grand adventure
it's gonna be sweet uh so there's a there's a slight like stab of horror uh i i i was on
stcomics.com rereading the the white lion and uh i went to the about page and there's a a surreal
moment when i when i read that brunswick and the champion both came out in 2016
that feels like wait what what what what did brunswick and the champion the champion did not
come out in 2016 that's what that's what's on the website um that's impossible well i i thought it
was two but i don't know maybe that's maybe wait oh wait did it start in 2016 that's i mean it maybe
shit yeah maybe the first page of it was posted in 2016 the last page of it was posted in 20
like early 2018 or like mid mid to late 2018 or something uh yeah i mean yeah it's a long time
fuck obviously no judgment i'm no better but would you say you're i mean i mean do you have
any like priorities or are you just trying to like like is there any methodology to this or are you
just uh trying to do things harder no there's no methodology i'm just trying to do things harder
and i feel like it's working not like wait and many people stay indoors on days like this is not
how do i fucking get my bed oh here we go here we go oh no i need more money i need another
thousand dollars to buy a fucking bag it takes 10 days to mature but keeps producing after that
yields multiple beans uh oh my god i can plant killer flower plant these in the spring takes
12 days to produce a large killer flower inventory full
okay okay that's fine that's fine gulp swallow the rage um what was i talking about
talking about comics like about doing them uh
uh i find it very hard to focus on multiple things at a time
i said i think many people do um i um i've been working you know this past week it's been poo
videos and endless war a couple weeks ago it was vapors again now it's not but it should be again
soon i'd kind of like it to be vapors and poo video the poo videos they only take about maybe a
day or a little more to make it i don't have enough room in my inventory kill me kill me
do you um have you noticed any increase uh in your in your in your viewer base from the poo videos
uh oh increase in my viewer base yeah any new faces in the comments i do see new faces
in the comments yes there's a lot of new faces in the comments a lot of people i've never seen
comment before uh viewer my channel subs my channel growth which was always slow but consistent
has increased in pace a bit not like precipitously but noticeably it's gaining
follower gaining subs a little bit faster than it was before um oh my god i got copper
oh my god i got copper yes nice sweet um
what else what else is going to be a large a large audience of poo a poo heads just flying
into your your cathedral oh right the uh the the ben sains interplanetary purpley thorny server
formerly known as the hellfire hamlet is that what it is now
sure look for yourself i'm not in it so fuck you um
it is it is the interplanetary purpley thorny server uh it's it's gone through a lot of nameshifts
lately um but you know mage has corrupted purple for everyone ruined it um i'm taking it back
uh hashtag uh make purple cool again well hers is like you're purple and her purple are very
different they are they are yeah hers is bad mine is good um i'm going to go crazy i hate this
fucking town where the fuck is anything this thing is a nightmare it's a nightmare maze it's a real
life okay i think the okay i think the blacksmith's house is over here to the right um
so yeah jesse likes the winnie the pooh videos i i do it seems like people like the winnie the
pooh videos it's weird to hear you scripted isn't you sound very different to me you don't sound
like your usual self no no and i don't mean that in like a it's feel stilted way it just feels
like i don't know it feels like you have a different demeanor about things
this is your more thoughtful maybe that's where i've asked well i mean maybe because i
thought it thought about it i don't know yeah maybe
i don't know it's i mean it from what i know tbap wasn't scripted but it was like you had
notes right tbap was there would occasionally be a scripted bit in it uh it was mostly off the cuff
occasionally there'd be a scripted bit and there were notes we would take notes and we would hit
the points in our notes in our like we would pause where is it fuck this is this is the wrong game
to pick the map says okay there there it is here we go i got it okay it's behind the school
jesus christ wait oh superstar this isn't even what i was looking for lol
i was looking for the museum oh it's right here i saw it i saw it all along
hey i'm i'm ready i'm ready to give this guy some slate
he can't he can't wait for it he can't wait for it
hey i love i love my character design i love this juvie that i've made i love jenny the juvie
uh he's canon he's so he's so canon this is this we're here and we're here in arson brook
fucking around in the mine well we're not in the mines yet
the mines are wait there's a mine next to arson brook right no we're in craterville very close
sure sure what's between craterville that has to say nice wait no cratervilles is down in the south
oh i'm sorry i'm in toxington sorry okay so this town all right head canon the town itself is
astatine heights the farms are arson brook and the mines are craters are uh toxington
there's gonna be a mad color filter on this maybe i will maybe i just fucking will
when we're gonna do our grinch oh um how about next week okay sure i can't do it this week
i'm pretty i'm pretty booked through all this week uh yeah same okay well actually this this
this is this is why my mini notes i am now free this week as i i have uh i've concluded something
most momentous as you will hear a click right now that was me submitting my application to college
i did it just now on rck live oh oh fuck really yeah uh shit oh no uh nate i've been telling uh
nate asked me to read his letter of recommendation for you and i've been meaning to and i didn't
realize that this was the deadline well no uh the way it works is i've submitted my application but
nate and and the other man i've i've asked uh will afterward oh see the last time oh then
forget i just said that okay we'll do that was a secret it was uh it was sort of scary you had to
like sign a waiver that you will not read the recommendation letters like what the what that
you won't yeah like in my entire life uh huh yeah well you're gonna read them no say it say
say it live say it live on on on yeah live live on this pre-recorded rfck please i don't have them
oh yeah like i said uh he he he can't send it he doesn't send it to me you see he sends it to
the school and i have to like invite his email to make it through to the school is how it works
so what is this there are video games in this video game disgusting if this is big iron oh right
what what are these things they look like orcs
terrified anyway yeah uh i must be goblins i think they're goblins from the mines
i'm not in but like i am now entering to be in you know yeah i know i know what i know what an
application is uh it feels good i i've i've been working on this for like two months now like
non-stop basically uh and it feels good i mean i like i like rad con rad con and commissions
were like the only uh this thing stopping me and now uh now it's over i i i had to make a
portfolio and an essay and a resume and all that and now i can just fucking put it all away
i can delete it all and i get back to what i care about which is uh uh coding more hats yeah yeah
yeah um that's all that really matters uh funnily enough uh uh there were like three endless war
related things in my portfolio like art pieces yeah the poster boy um hey have you had like any
interviews yet yeah yeah you've had like well no well you haven't like interviewed with any like
application people i i i have but unofficially the way uh like there's no official interview
uh i do it all online uh through the common application you see uh but i did go to a portfolio
review to see if it was you know to for a representative for mass art to i asked them if
they my portfolio is good and they said quote you've got a shot you've got a shot i mean i feel
like if you talk to someone and told them about endless war they'd be like what i don't know
endless war seems like a really impressive thing to me uh well for a shitty kid such as yourself
in the portfolio you have an image and then you have like a title and description and in
said description i mentioned endless war okay well good it bears it bears mentioning yeah i i also
have it in my resume as programmed a computer game which is quite a lot of sort of sort of
doesn't sound as impressive when you say it like that you think so i thought that sounded more
impressive how would you how would you at most impressively describe it i mean the impressive
part about endless war wait oh fuck that was a bad item the impressive part about endless war is not
that a game was programmed it's that a game was programmed and it's a masterpiece and everyone
loves it yeah okay and that like you know there's a community around it you know that that's
that's the part i mean can i take credit for the community though yes i mean who else
okay i mean the community themselves oh my god oh my god what the fuck what the fuck oh my god i'm
a fucking zombie whoa i'm a fucking pac-man kill everything zombie i'm invincible that's crazy
oh well this is short lived i don't i don't want that well lasted
this is funny the actual game this is way better than um whatever stupid thing i'm playing
pac-man starty valley same thing oh shit i can shoot die i can shoot diagonally i can shoot diagonally
haha ego raptor hero of the people hate him absolutely hate him was he getting on the show
we should we should get him on the show and kill oh my god is this a demon oh it can buy shit
i can buy boots you can't buy it yeah you can only buy boots i can buy a gun
oh i can't quite afford box where's the gun do i have no i've never gotten this far
i i don't like more i don't know maybe i think it might have increased my rate of fire
this is so fucking cool yeah this is way better yeah this is the best this is the best game
big iron big iron
cat aller zone ranger with big iron i'm showing you the mic ness cover big iron no the the one uh
it's it it sounds like uh a dude from goldfinger singing big iron i'm like
to the counter of the free of water strange or one fun day oh um um alpachino yeah basically i mean
it sounds exactly like that it sounds like someone uh really frustrated with the concept of big iron
when you well when you just did the concept um fuck yeah no i think that's it oh no i got one more
okay uh the way you god who is the guy who look at this fucking bear and what i mean what yeah i mean
that's the same that's just that's nuts man i mean that's bizarre there's a bear in this game
there's a bear in this game um
the when you sang that just now it sounded like a guy from the godfather uh al not not mel brooks
the guy who was in source source was lost i mean i mean apocalypse now um
no more mori povich god no david no he's a fucking actor you you fucking know who it is marlon brando
and why are you with marlon brando you bitch nobody thank god well time to play this game
just we just wasting your life playing video games man like like in real life there's a skull shaped
keyhole what does that mean i mean i gotta find a skull key it means i gotta find a skull key
no what is possible what look i'm clicking it i'm fucking clicking it please
it sucks just play the fake video game no what you'd no fuck you fuck you man i want to see the bear
again i want i also want to see the bear again look what what am i supposed to do with this
what am i supposed to do i'm clicking it i'm well it's clearly something
i'm a fucking cursor is turning into a hand yeah fine
fuck it what were you talking about i feel like we got swept up in how great that game was
yeah we got swept up by big iron um um i i i submitted to college yeah it feels good
now my plate's clean finally actually actually it's clean for a moment or two but now it's
going to be completely dominated by commissions again so i guess uh for all the new purposes
i'm still away on how it is commissions are great by the way they're really fun
why can't they're talk they're really useful uh to motivate you to draw every day because you
have to because there's money on the line you see yeah i guess uh yeah i mean they did get me to draw
um at times oh shit that reminds me a guy was like tentatively going to commission me
and i think that he thought that i didn't want to take it but i like did a sketch and like sent
him the sketch like two days ago or something and i don't know if he responded so i should check if
he responded i should check and find out if he responded he was gonna he was like he was like
hey yeah i'll pay you know i don't know how hard this is i'll pay like my budget is maybe 50 to
150 dollars for it that's a big budget yeah so you know i'm tempted you know part of me is like
this guy's willing to pay 150 dollars everything in line everything is worth what people will pay for
it and no more and no less so i should charge him 150 dollars but i don't think i don't think i can
justify it because i don't feel like it's a hundred and fifty dollar job it's not that hard what is it
he just he wanted me to draw like an icon for him oh what like um like yeah like a like a pro like
an well like a profile picture slash avatar image hey come over to munchie w tiny hats on twitter i do
it for ten dollars scoff it works that's how you know that's how you know it sucks dick because
it costs ten dollars yeah true but hey i walk out with a cool crisp ten dollars that that paid for
mini a t-ride like yeah you could go there and back wherever there is like twice on that yeah
exactly hell yeah fuck yeah dude i can even afford to mess up and get off at the wrong station a couple
times easily easily
ah the town of osalito road stranger one day alf no salsalito like the cookie oh like like
velvita the town of salsalito to the town of velvita road stranger one day i'm happy but
it's a recipe i don't need new friends do you ever draw without like like non-comic work
almost never how often would you say you draw basically basically only when i'm drawing a
comic well no okay you know i mean i drew that clefable thing the other day just like when i get
an idea for something and or i mean you know i used to draw every day i don't think i draw every
day anymore but like probably most days or maybe i mean not less than half i don't think
man i should draw every day again wait wait so you you draw mostly every week no most most days
oh you draw most days okay and you're like sketchbook or whatever i don't have a sketchbook
no i told i told you i don't like i don't have a sketchbook and i'd like don't draw other than
when i'm doing a comic page or when i'm like working on a thing that i put out on the internet
okay i told you this i i was confused i thought you said that you drew mostly every day just
yes that's what i said okay how can those two things be the same that exist at the same time
you don't draw almost never but you draw almost every day
no what is no i said that i draw i draw almost never except for those things that i draw
okay there okay
smh yeah clearly
hey what's the goal of this by the way to like date people
um date people get rich
you know say just like life can you get rich can you like get like i mean obviously
accrue a lot of money but i mean can you like can you can you have your affluence
affect your your your social status uh i don't know if it affects your social status but like
you can expand your house and stuff think things things of that nature gross what not living in
poverty discussed me uh yeah well i i feel you i'm funny i feel you on that
fuck damn it i should i would i should have bought those effin parsnips i should have
should have bought those effin parsnips hot hot cha cha nice thanks
we're really on our end game today uh yeah what what what happened we were so good we were
doing so good the energy was up we in the meetup we were fucking i mean that was the height of any
conversation we've ever had now it's just all downhill from here um yeah and you bullied me you
bullied me that i like drink too much did i bully you how did i bully you were making i don't know
you're always you're always like you're making fun of me because like i don't know i guess i get it
i don't even i don't even blame you because every time we hang out at digis well specifically when
we hang out at digis i get drunk so you i think i think i understand why you would perceive me as
like a guy who's like drunk all the time well hold on yeah hold on the most i did was express
how happy i was that you weren't drunk but same that's the same thing that's the same thing
remarking on listen remarking on anything is the same as making fun of the flaw
it was great yeah yeah it was good i was that was i forgot how nice you could be
sometimes i can be nice yeah sometimes once once in a blue moon um not now though
because yeah again yeah you might as well be drunk now because where's my
god i hate i don't like i just can't fucking learn where shit is i just can't fucking learn
where shit is and it's god damn in this fucking ass teen height sucks dick i hate it
go go to the lobster get a lobster what what what all right wait is lobster is
lobstertown anastatine yeah okay i forgot i didn't play you don't even you don't even know what's
happening i mean you know last thing you're confused oh my god you're buying so many do you
have any why get some cauliflower no i'm gonna get that later because those take a long time to
mature okay and i and and i need cash now jd went worth eight seven seven cash now
you know you know those ads right of course i've yeah i know i know bin yeah you know about uh
just just get in the bed just get in the bed Ben you tell me you know about me you know hey
hey munchie i'll try and dug for you you know yeah you'll put on the dug for me yeah oh my god
just get in the bed one what what i i'm so i'm just blown away that one parsnip seed
costs 20 fucking dollars and plants one plant what yes
maybe gold is like cents and you and you have eight dollars and 30 cents right now
yeah i guess i must i guess i must i'm just gonna assume that fuck fuck it i'm spending all my money
on parsnip seeds jesus christ well why not yeah okay oh my god it shook holy shit is this undertale
oh my god it wait and did you notice
um hold on did you know it didn't just shake on the bottom it shakes on the top right too
top right where you know i don't see you know in the top right oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah boy okay sick i wish i had two more cents so i could buy another parsnip
but hey so i think what i'm gonna do is i'm going to uh i'm gonna plant these snips
and uh then i'm gonna go fish for like three days and uh then i'm gonna come back
you know and farm them and that's the juby life that is the juby hashtag juby life
god i wish i was a juby feels good feels good to be a salt of the earth type you know
a humble hope folksy you know full of you know natural wisdom
um you know you know i'm fucking talking about but why don't you why don't you ask me a conversation
starter um
i don't know about that i don't know about all that um
um
oh god yes how's uh so how's the wife how's the white house how's the weather how's the
weather out there how's oh oh real hot huh oh wow how long how long you've been out of school
how long you've been done you're a year and a half basically wait really yeah for a while now
did you get like your did you get like your g ed uh sort of yes
explain well what did you get did you get a diploma or what did you get like yeah well
for all intents and purposes it's a g ed yes but it's under a different name
what's it called i don't want to say wait why i don't know i it's it's sort of weird i don't
want anyone will be able to trace me back because of it wait hold on i don't understand like if you
said yeah i got a g ed or yeah i got a phd or yeah i got you know such and such qualification
that's not that's not doxing yourself is it is that is this like is like knowing what did what
qualification you have like an identifying piece of information no but this is less of a general
diploma and it's more i imagine it's a way smaller group of people it's not like it's it's like it's
like a private thing that i've gotten uh all right fair fair enough i guess but anyway yeah i uh i got
that quite a while ago and so now i've for a while i was just like well this is my life now uh but then
but then like like six months i started seriously considering college now here i am uh the last thing
i did to do college was an essay and i had everyone review it and it was nice if you if you were in
the endless war homework server then then you know what i'm talking about god bless the homework
hey so um so again i don't want to give any details on this but we got i got the uh i got the secret
project being worked on by my by my slaves in the in the slime dungeon in saint ben's cathedral
and man i don't i'm not i'm not complaining about this i'm just it's just an observation
um i'm looking at the stuff people have written because it's a writing thing people are contributing
like bits of writing to the game and it's very frustrating not because it's bad or anything
but every single thing that someone writes i read it and i'm just like i would have worded this
in such and such way you know like i would have worded this differently and i want to change it
even though it's not wrong you know uh well i mean why can't you i might i might just do that i
can i can do it is the i mean it it's it's easier to write than it is you're still saving time it's
not like you're you know there's no point to having to be community outsourced then i guess you lose
i mean i guess you do lose the the conception of like wow get your work in the game like get
yeah in the game that will be i don't i don't want to do too much of that
i don't want to do too much rewriting i don't want to do any more than i need to
i mean i will do i definitely will do some hey no i wanted to give you my fucking fish
i just missed him i just missed him take my fish
alas well i mean it that's it's sort of a good thing to change it i mean rewrite it i mean
to make like to make like the tone of it consistent exactly i mean that's how you make a consistent
you know uh voice yeah i mean i definitely will do some i you know i like i want to preserve the
community aspect of it like i want to keep the like yeah players you know the players came together
to work on implementing this feature um so you know i like that part of it but you know i want
the tone to be consistent and you know i just want to i will probably go in and just oh look at all
these fucking look at all these hanging participles and and you know uh sentence and ended with the
preposition or you know whatever nitpick shit that might bug me that would have
obviously you have to be like grammar and fucking shit like that yeah it's it's mostly fine um but
you know there's there's always something there's always something there was a there was a there was a
there was a panic there was a panic in the dungeon in the work dungeon yesterday over um
improper improper pronoun usage um there was a big push to go back over everything you've made and uh
do some uh it doesn't reference any particular genders do some do some do some do some pronoun
do some do some pronoun uh management generally um
shit how do i how do i get on this subject we were talking about projects we were doing
right talking about about in this war and and doing oh you you had asked me when i finished
school and then i and then i said and then you were like cool and then said so uh endless war
dot dot dot right oh god boy boy howdy yeah one i need to introduce myself to one more person okay um
i don't know how how you've been since you finished school do you miss it uh no i don't at all
it's it's it's quite nice uh i've had an extremely like abnormal high school life
i know it's it's it's it's probably not like the same sort of feelings that one would have it's not
like man i fucking hate my teachers what a bitch or like you know oh i'm not popular
it i i i didn't dislike it at all really it just was annoying so i guess i just dislike it
contrary to what i just said shit i could have bought i could have bought more i could have bought
more parsnips please clint clint i mean pierre sell me more parsnips i'm very upset i think i just
missed him killer name i think it's very it's very like i know i missed him by like 10 seconds
hate my life i hate my life munchy this entire game just seems like you're running across the
map trying to get places in time and you never do sometimes they do sometimes build a coop okay i
gotta build a coop go to the arcade again uh no there's important you you you pivoted and you're
gonna walk back and then you had this look there's important shit to be done all right this business
to attend to you know juby doesn't just the economy this economy is not going to maintain itself
you have to support those local mom-and-pop businesses else you're going to yeah juju
fucking juju corp or whatever isn't it's gonna fuck us all over i'm wearing my slime corp shirt
by the way oh shit nice yeah oh we were so distinct been but i'm i'm glad on the final
day on the final day we were together uh we we we both had the uh the hearts of each other the
routing killer pride on yeah yeah we were really tsundere there like we like we never wore it at
the same time you know we we we we we played tag with it uh but then finally you know that magical
moment did indeed come to pass god hey you know with you and and tom and kazzie was like the
bet the highlight of my trip it was great you mean uh did you place that night it did you
place and and and outside yeah you know tom you know tom's pretty fun you know i like tom i wish
i wish he came out more i love tom yeah you know tom's one of those people that like i didn't
really know very well when i when when the group well when i first entered the group that is
i was sort of he was sort of an outlier yeah over the years over the radicons i've really really
come and enjoy him dude okay tom has a quality which like i like i didn't realize that i missed
from my offline friends like i didn't like realize was a thing that i appreciated but like tom's like
happy yeah he's like inwardly you know he's a he's a tortured soul but like you know when i
meet tom he's like oh like like that fucking restaurant you took me to was really good dude
i liked it a lot and like i can't believe it like i can't fucking like it like shatters my world the
very foundation of of my interpretation of events it just like disintegrates tom is like like like a
joyous soul who is like enjoys my company and like expresses it and like i can't believe it
it's insane like it like like he'll just say like it won't even be like he's trying to like get
anything out of me like it's not even like he's trying to manipulate me he'll just like he'll
like he'll be like wow what a good meal like you like you pick good restaurants bunching like oh
my god tom i love you too uh uh yeah tom's just uh pleasant tom's pleasant pleasant company uh
you hung out with wait have tom and zen ever hung out in the same place at the same time
because i kind of get similar vibes from both of them and no one seemed to agree with me on that
no i dude completely 100 on you okay zen is very agreeable tom's very agreeable very agreeable
people yeah who you can have fun with doing whatever i mean i feel like with a lot of the
people in the pcp it's like you know you have to do thing you want to do things hang out together
but it's always like you're trying to make them appease them try to make often i'll feel like
is this person having fun i have to do things to make this person have fun with tom and zen you
can just like have you know enjoy their company and it's way funner for both of you yeah at that
point i think there's no there's no no expectation from them you know yeah yeah there's no like
i'm so fucking sick of being like not liking things are not liking things well no of like
i don't know of cynical behavior you know yeah criticizing everything yeah yeah
it sucks yeah it's lame it's lame as hell so that's what i enjoy when i when i
tom hippo you you guys are are i would consider probably my best friends i remember i remember
we had we had like a like a like a weird confrontation i feel like i used the term
best friend more flexible than you and i remember that you felt really ashamed that like like you
were like uh we discussed best friends and i was like yeah like vince vince oh that like it was it
was it that was it that like i felt that i couldn't categorically i couldn't categorically place you
as like a definitive number one over and above all others and i was like i'm so sorry yeah yeah
i was like i don't care yeah yeah not a big deal yeah uh let's well meet for me personally
it makes me fucking pissed that you won't definitively place me over and above all
others so are you really no i'm no i'm joking please please know that i'm joking when i say
okay all right i'm i'm really fucking mad right now um just just just to warn you i'm on the war
path that that was that was the sort of thing where i couldn't like completely outrule that that
would be real i didn't expect it to be true but munchie that's such a horrible thing to say
how could you think i meant it well you know oh god oh i'm out well no it's it's sort of like you
know it's one it's one of those things that you you think and you don't want to say to other people
but i mean ben just says ben's an honest man
but he had always told the truth that he was an honest man and brandy does
look at the man in the mirror to understand something make a change
take a look at yourself and make a change if you want to make the world you know you know
you ever heard of a guy named michael jackson uh i don't know if i told this on stream or anything
oh my mom soggy newspaper whoa do read it okay i don't think this is trash
nice no bones about it unironically asked me uh in in full sincerity well do do kids
do kids these days know about the holocaust and about nazis that's a fair question
why no that's not if what are you joking no well look i mean i know that the answer is yes
but i mean imagine you're not in school you don't you don't know any kids you don't talk to kids
how would you know how would you know that the way you know is that like do you know about things
from your past like do you know things like or rather do you know about events that have
happened in the past before you were alive like does my mom know about abraham lincoln
did you know what the silver wars i mean yes so obviously a big event will be remembered
it will be remembered but like i mean until war two was before her time okay well i mean
my grandpa fought in the korean war i don't know almost anything about the korean war
and that's like that's more recent than the holocaust uh well first of all very slightly
more recent yeah like that sure but but still you know i couldn't tell you very much about the korean
war um well i feel like even at time it's cool i mean i don't think anyone was under the impression
well okay specifically with the korean war i feel like maybe some people thought that it might turn
into another global conflict but like even just like a few years out it was clear that was not the
case and the korean war was not indeed another like you know turning point in american history
like world war two i feel it's clear there's a difference of scale there that could ease i mean
i mean even the fact that like surely there's like you are aware that there's a complete over
saturation of media about world war two that's true um clearly you are aware that it is a big deal
to at least like you know moviegoers or you know what yeah yeah there's yeah there's there's so many
world there's so many world war two movies there's so many holocaust movies i mean yeah like obviously
the answer is yes i'm just saying i understand i can understand where the where the question comes
from if it were a lesser event if it was the korean war if i said like do you know about the
korean war i i would have it would have been yes we do my my dad my dad once uh he was there was a
time when he was unbelievably condescending to my sister my sister was maybe like 18 at the time
and he this is so but this makes me a little mad just thinking about it we were i don't remember
we were sitting at the dinner table the conversation referenced like we mentioned like hitler we mentioned
um uh mao mao zidang uh kim jung un or whatever you know we're talking about like dictators and
and stuff and you know we're we're talking about this we're saying whatever it is and my dad like
leans over to my sister i can't believe this man he's like by the way he says to to my adult sister
he says by the way these are all very bad men uh doesn't it make you feel icky i mean was it was
it a joke no no i get the impression that yeah i mean i wouldn't imagine that it is but like
it feels like there's no way it couldn't be yeah no i get that and yet and yet here we are
uh have i talked about have i talked about my
oh i want this chest oh god i need this fish sorry no the fish
okay okay have i talked about my a guy who lived here in monkey house briefly a guy named a chinese
kid named jerry who uh didn't know who elvis was uh you talked to me about this many times but uh
he didn't know who elvis was you didn't know like my my downstairs we don't have downstairs
neighbors anymore but at the time we had downstairs neighbors and their like grandma or something was
like turning 90 and on her 90th birthday they had a party in the backyard and they had an elvis
impersonator and jerry didn't know who elvis was now i wondered you know do maybe in china
elvis isn't as famous as he is here but i don't believe that elvis is like so big elvis is like
transit you know who the beetles are yeah pretty much um everybody knows him right i'm sure of it
i'm sure they know elvis in china oh a new record um but it doesn't even matter because it was just
like ethically chinese who was born there right well he grew up in america he uh half and half
yeah like he had spent enough time in america that no that's not that can't even be the reason um
he's just a fucking zoomer who doesn't know who fucking elvis is i don't even like elvis i don't
care about elvis but like leelo and stitch you gotta know you gotta know by the way meeting
going to your house oh yes you finally met dweeb you finally met dweeb and obviously like i don't
know anything about him in real life i don't know what he looks like so when this man before yeah
yeah yeah when this man entered he was like uh you know i know he was munchie and i was like oh
okay like i had no idea it was him until i remember i specified i remember realizing that oh yeah of
course you wouldn't know that this was dweeb until i told you but it didn't occur to me that i needed
to like point that fact out i i mean like i like you know there was a ton of other there was a gaggle
of other men there that y'all easily could have been dweeb i mean i didn't really like recognize his
voice really yeah sure yeah and you know it sounds way different on the line everything like that
have you ever heard him in a voice call have you talked to him in voice before yeah yeah i've talked
to him in a couple okay uh yeah uh yeah he uh he didn't make it to rfckcon he had plans that day
god i want that fucking bag upgrade oh another one of those in march by the way i don't know the
date yet but uh yeah good uh in like the first week oh my god is this yes you did it why did you
become a farmer i want to make tons of money it's more real than living in a city i wanted to escape
i wanted to escape my old life in the mines of getting shot getting shot every day okay cool um
sorry what uh i was just talking about the fact i met dweeb yeah uh you were the phantom machine
that night that was at your house well not by choice you guys kept bullying me to do it yeah
you you you couldn't i mean you you you were the only one with a vape you're the only one that
could do it sure sure but you you just you just you just kept wanting to see it you just wanted
more and more you just take and take and take well whenever we met a new person i i made been
reveal the phantom yeah yeah person and it like for some reason like the universe inspired against
us because like every single new person like this is a person who had never seen it before and just
by chance their reaction was less and less thrilling each time like at the end i think the last
person we we did is that is that is it so surprising well is it so shocking i would imagine like like a
new text a new test subject each time would be just as thrilled as last but you know no communication
you know maybe our energy level was going to maybe we were less and less enthused about it and maybe
that you know carried over into their reaction maybe is isaac the guy who's playing persona five
lucas lucas lucas the guy the guy with the the ghosts the guy oh was that the ghost that was
that was well that yeah he was the guy who was like let's do the seance for ghost reasons uh
anyway we showed it to him and and his reaction was just uh like like uh like uh
well that's well that's lucas okay okay yeah yeah good stuff good stuff good yeah great work
and it was
is there anyone you can make the holes disappear
why can't uh they i think they just disappear on their own after a while if nothing's planted
in them right do you want you want it nice and clean yeah i do yeah i do too no once you dig a
hole you just gotta like what let it fuck it's you're just you're just fucked
jesus my life's not gonna like this oh my god you're gonna die i'm starting shit i'm starting
to feel exhausted oh my god but it's okay i don't think planting seeds takes energy
can't eat food to regain energy uh i could but i don't have any food well i guess i have this
this wild potato yeah yeah i'll eat this potato yeah sick okay it did nothing for me wow cool
uh i can still do stuff even when i'm exhausted oh wait no i did it did refill some energy that's
good i can still i can still do stuff when i'm exhausted i just like move really slow
oh fuck oh i'm out of i'm out of water i really want to get i really want to get all my plants
watered so that they all um grown us oh god look look look how slow i am this sucks it's okay i'll
get it it's it's early it's only 8 p.m oh yeah see if you're out past like
oh yeah i got it fucking oh no am i like pat oh he just passed out outside
whoa damn it's damn it i didn't get them all watered okay so now i start the next day with
half energy and it oh oh no maybe if i if i'm on the farm it's fine uh okay yeah it's too bad
looks like my my crop's gonna be split now what what a what a damn shame life's life's hard for a poor
juve um it's as much as much like real life they just uh everything whizzes by and you uh waste
your time on this on the surface yeah you um if you're out past a certain time you just like
go to sleep outside and like you wake up the next day with half energy and i think i think like the
like ju ju ju corp or whatever like put like charges you for medical service because they like
put you in a hospital or something because you like passed out on the street
look how much we ran next to a brook uh yeah arson brook was the right choice
now i don't even have to get that bitch robin over here to build a well with all my hard earned
stones thank god how much is this game uh maybe like 15 bucks 10 bucks like it's pretty cheap i think
i think i was gifted it but i can't remember that sounds right you've been gifted many a game
in your life i have uh xavier gifted me um uh endless gungeon recently or no enter the gungeon
oh yeah tadpole yeah tadpole got frog fractions that's right um i think that's right right it was him
yeah i'm almost sure i'm almost positive spider got me uh hollow knight it's pretty nice
this is a solid solid video game if i do say so myself
fuck it's not like an oxymoron uh and there's i'm sure there's more
our rats he did a thing where like he shares his like game list with me so like any game that he
owns i also own sort of see yeah like a family plan something like that yeah
yeah
yeah this takes like all my energy watering this field you're having some food
uh chugal there's a potato there's i have i have a potato so don't worry can you cook
don't even worry about it huh can you cook it for more nutrition um you know probably but i
don't know how i don't know how to cook okay let's see what's going on jenny's oh
damn it no oh okay okay someone dropped you off at the clinic last night i passed out from
exhaustion i was in my own field who came into my field found me sleeping there and was like oh
better haul this guy off to the hospital you passed out from exhaustion you've got to take
better care of yourself and go to bed at a reasonable hour since you have no money i provided
your medical care free of charge dr harvey thanks buddy the pay it pays to be broke
it really does truly then it's it's been like a depressing nightmare to be back in san diego
after being in boston why because do you miss me do you just miss me that much uh bitch yeah
sure let's go with that yeah yeah yeah yeah when i'm in boston i feel like my life is progressing
i feel like i'm accomplishing things and i'm and i'm getting work done especially this trip
times before it's been like you know i'm on vacation you know i'm just sort of seeing the
sites and having fun hanging out and uh you know wasn't really getting a lot of work done but
especially this time like i'm uh like i like i actually i mean i was on that computer i i could
do i i mean i edited the drawcast there before it's a podcast there and a whole bunch of stuff
especially after that since i was there for such a long time i didn't afford not to so it really
felt like wow it sure feels great to live in a city that i enjoy and be able to you know meet my
friends on a reasonable basis and be able to you know go into the city and you know hang out there
and now it like it felt like wow sure feels great to live here uh and then uh you know i was there
for like a month and a half and now i'm back here it feels like wow all my progress has just been
undone like i like i'm i'm right back at square one and now i am toiling away in the mines wasting
away and just counting the days until i can go back that's how it feels oh it's fun now i'm exhausted
again like help um um well well you're coming back in like a month right yeah so it's not too long
it just it sucks and i hate it there's only a few more trips before it is actually well i mean
if everything goes play in only a few more trips are you going to sleep right now at 11 um i i can
barely move okay holy shit yeah i fucked up i shouldn't have i shouldn't have chopped that last
tree i could have let i could have like walked to the pier and like uh oh great i could have like
walked to the pier and gone fishing and made some money but uh you know i fucked up fucked it up
what's happening right now i'm getting a fucking dog
i was just thinking because i saw it's that little dog bowl up in the top left there and
i was like when's that dog coming turns out right now don't you think don't you think this farm
could use a good dog no oh my god like you can decline you can decline
yeah but would but would jenny the juvie decline
hmm well i feel like jenny the juvie doesn't have good wits about him so he'd probably accept the
dog no matter how much maintenance he had to do it yeah i think jen i think i think the juvie move
is to adopt the dog and since this isn't a role-playing experience i'm gonna do it however
let me make my objections very clear what's open yeah uh slime field it's slime field
i don't know but i'm not i'm not particularly invincible we were in that pet store together
you uh you you went out some some strange expressions i've never seen you make before
dogs are cute puppies are cute don't get me wrong they are i don't want one
but they're nice to look at from time to time do you do oh oh oh
huh say when someone else when you're at someone else's house or even just you're out for a walk
and you see a dog what's what's your uh it's generally positive okay it's a generally positive
reaction to dogs you know i i get it i get dogs i get the appeal i do but like fuck it
fuck it no no thanks i mean there would be there would be there would be literally no room for
a dog for you so it's not like it would be even be possible yeah that's true even even on a desirable
apparently um there used to be a guy that lived here briefly named conrad not oh no a different
conrad i doubt it and he uh he kept a cat here apparently and everyone hated it it was like well
sure yeah i mean it's a pet in the in a shared space unless it's like a really good pet like yeah
yeah i mean we take well like our downstairs neighbors moved out we used to pets it their dog
they had a a very sweet dog named mabel mabel was a pretty good dog but you know she was a hassle
and like she like peed on our stairs a couple of times that's not good yeah actually only i think
that only happened once like one time she just like they dropped her off and she immediately
just pissed on our front stairs like inside but you know that's life sometimes in life you just
gotta fucking piss on the ground shit i should have watered these like less mature plants first
oh no this is such a bummer i need to eat something i need to eat something like right now
you like all your life is just like waking up watering these plants and going to bed
exclamation point toil yeah exactly i don't i don't even have any money to buy food
jesus christ i can't can i eat the sap can i eat the sap in my inventory how do you get more money
well selling selling crops mainly okay
okay it's okay it's early in the morning so i can go fish i don't think fishing takes energy
so uh i can just go fish and maybe make some money that way maybe i can buy some food you wake up
you're immediately exhausted because all i want is just to like i just want to finish watering my
fucking crops so they all like grow in at the at you know as close to the same time as possible
i guess it doesn't matter that much because i mean i've obviously i've planted too much
and i can't water at all so like you know it doesn't all need to come in at once anyway
but hey that's just a theory a game theory
huh how much coin does it take to play the arcade game
i'm not sure it costs any money i think you know what we're doing
no no not big iron look there's important shit to do what could be more important than big iron
seaweed seaweed's not important
wait no i have to i have to eat it no i had to eat that seaweed no
the seaweed keto yeah i think so
uh do i need this sap do i need damn it but by the way last night in the pc in the conversation
we had over text you said that you were back on keto you did you ever leave i got off it for the
holidays okay um but i mean was that like an intentional like leave like like you you said
to yourself i'm not gonna be on keto for a while yeah for like a week i was oh shit no i'm sluggish
from over exhaustion i'm fucked i'm fucked i'm gonna die munchy i'm going to die no don't worry
just get a fish i can't do it i can't do it oh oh my god okay can you eat anything
i could have eaten that seaweed but i didn't have room in my inventory for it
that seaweed was my lifeline can you panhandle for money no
no
god i can't i can't let anyone see me i can't let any of my perspective boyfriends and or
girlfriends see me like this better walk into town and collapse in the middle um well during
this long walk home i'll get to appreciate jenny the juvie i just love jenny the juvie
i just love jenny the juvie so much i'm loving him more every moment
he's got good style he does i mean i mean he has the oculus rift on he's probably not
even paying attention to what he's doing no he doesn't he he doesn't even know he's a farmer
yeah he thinks he's a badass action hero and wherever he plants me down he's bringing someone
skull in he thinks he's a space marine
you are you are in my heart jenny jenny juvie first name jenny last name juvie are these cows yours
no these belong to um what's her name down there the girl who gave me the dog or woman rather
man i'm going a long way take the long way home take the long way home let's you know let's just
fill the rest of the episode with like saying something and then singing a song that whatever
we just said reminds us of sounds like a great idea that's how i feel time i don't know about you
fucks gotta fill up my water and can uh hey what time is it how much longer how much longer do we
have it's i i have like 10 minutes really okay yeah i mean we've i feel like we covered some good
ground we covered some ground today i feel like ground was stepped upon uh-huh but not covered
no i feel like it's it's like a splatoon map and we did like 60 of it uh i don't know like
is there more is there more you wish we'd gone into
maybe i feel like we could have gone more in depth about any number of the things we talked about
but i mean i mean i guess it's just not the way the conversation developed there's a way in your
head you expect conversations to go but they hardly ever pan out the way you do that you expect them
to well hey man um we should take this as an opportunity to reflect we should reflect on all
on all the things we discussed today and think about we should do another one soon right yeah
no i don't know uh i i'm i'm i'm a big proponent of the idea that we don't have to do rf2k is
so close together i know i know the game the game of youtube and the game of twitch is the
release regularly i know we do weekly streams but honestly i don't think we have to i think
that's part of what makes them special is that they're an event and also that no one gets burned
out no one gets burned out of rf2k you know you can get burned out of endless war since it's an
ongoing game but like no one's ever going to think like oh fucking man they've just like
run out of things to say well actually everyone thinks that every single episode yeah no one will
think i've heard too much you know like i like oh like jesus christ let it in really like game
grumps at least a video every day where they said let's play every day eventually you're gonna
loop conversation eventually you're going to like you know like actually really have nothing to say
and it will just be game commentary of over and over again which is not anything that i want to
me personally me personally more than happy to just comment about how my farm is
i'm ready to turn this into an immersive role playing experience i'm ready to develop the
narrative of jenny the juvie uh well uh it seems like everything's already pre-decided for you
i mean you didn't decide to get a dog it just like a dog just appeared on your doorstep like you know
i mean how much role playing can happen that isn't already predetermined by the game
well you know i gotta choose my my cutie my cutie gf slash bf um i gotta choose what i gotta choose
what crops to grow you know i got i want to grow that killer flower why are you just intentionally
leaving some some crops i can't pick them because my inventory is full and i'm pretty sure the reason
for that is that they are like uh special they're like silver parts like they're higher quality so
they count as a different item so i'll just have to get them uh in a second
i'll have i'll have to come here we go now oh wait no first i gotta water my cauliflower
i do i have a couple of you're right here did you do can you can you eat parsnips
i can wait what oh oh that was a gold that was a gold parsnip that was the ultimate parsnip
you know i should i should eat in those shit parsnips here
uh gotta sell gotta sell my gold gotta buy cash for gold uh
dot com hey binner those old those jg winsworth commercials why yes
what what what made you think of those where we're in dug and patty made that that pepperoni
pizza and and and then roger uh fell onto them and and his banana pudding uh covered pizza i went
and and and then they were distraught and then left the the school dejectedly but sketer ran ran
over to them to let them have the good news that in fact their banana pudding pepperoni pizza was
awesome yeah everyone's going crazy for it yeah um oh yeah whole boy whole boy do i remember
i looked up videos like i looked up uh binging with babish like cooking the banana the oh yeah
the banana yeah i did i well i okay i looked up one one was binging with babish and he is like
well no he said he's he's allergic to banana so he couldn't eat it but he got his friend to eat it
and his friend was like yeah it's bad and they're like okay so they made like a different banana
i don't believe it um well there was another guy some guy with like 8 000 subs uh doing like
food reviews he just like bought a pizza he just like bought a pizza and like smeared banana putting
on he didn't even make the pizza from scratch the fucking the the fucker um and he's just like man
you know it's time to fulfill a childhood dream of mine yeah you know ever see i was you was this
you it should have been i could have been but he beat me to it and he's like it's time to you
know i've been i've been wanting to do this for i've been wanting to do this for 25 years now uh you
know hey dad you know next time let me let me eat that banana pudding pizza you know don't naysay
the banana pudding you know he's like ha ha humorously like mad at his dad or whatever like
that's the joke um and he eats it and he's like oh you know it's not bad you know it's pretty good
why don't you let me eat the pizza dad
um i mean i mean i mean going back going back ben hates his dad ben loves dug
those are my two things hating hating hating my parents and loving dug um
hey what could have skeeter been my mom don't knock it don't knock it till you try it on both
oh my god a girl oh my god it's a fucking girl dude it's a fucking slut advancement reach
farming level one and craft a scare okay apparently apparently i can craft bro huh craft a diamond
pick bro oh shit i need wood oh okay yeah there i made a scarecrow uh well it's pretty easy well i
had all the shit i had like tons of wood and fiber and coal i don't know what i needed coal for
for making a scarecrow but uh what is the eye of cthulhu spawn say what what is the eye of cthulhu
spawn um let's look don't worry about end game shit okay you know that's the future and you never
plan for the future because if it's if you're planning for the future that means it's not perfect
you know i i i walk downstairs like just a few moments before we started recording
my mom was listening to an audiobook as she does famously a self-help book uh and it was like
listen if you want more in your life and you achieve what you want if you want 10 000 dollars in
the bank and you get 10 000 dollars in the bank you're not gonna be happy you're just gonna want
more so why get more than you what you have right now why even get anything you'll need yeah yeah
that's really the book that's pretty weird that what yeah what whatever it is you have right now
i personally author of this best-selling novel no guarantee that it's plenty guarantee
and if you set goals for yourself when you accomplish them well i mean there's gonna be new
goals well i mean then fuck you if you accomplish your goals fuck you you fucked up you did it wrong
and you're bad listen if your goal is to lose 10 pounds and then you lose two pounds i mean i mean
what now what yeah like like what are you supposed to do now like just lose more weight i mean
like aren't you ashamed of yourself answer yes with good reason
damn dude i i i'm glad i'm glad i know i made the grave mistake of saying something though
you know oh you commented yeah i i know i shouldn't oh no my loud mouth yeah so what happened
she just was very defensive i mean obviously i mean i mean what right do i do i have to say
to say to my mom hey you know i don't think this is uh all there i mean you know you know how it
has been when your mom when your parents do something you hate them so much you have so much
fucking ill will in your heart for them hell yeah it's so hard to not hate you know just say
something to make them feel awful oh i think it's all you live for it oh no you ate a daffodil
i ate a daffodil but it was neither good for me nor bad for me uh it was all things considered
you know i think jubies probably do that a lot they'll just eat they'll they'll have to eat
whatever scraps they can find in the field that's fine yeah it's part of it's part of it comes with
the territory they like it tastes good yeah they love it now they must they must they better love it
otherwise sad times sad times ahead all right i'm gonna fish hey yeah i have to go i have to
graduate from high school right now god good luck thanks dude i might i might play i might play some
more of this fucking game because i'm on rck uh no i'm just mean like by myself should i stop
or what doesn't matter no it doesn't matter okay i don't this game sucks no it's great this game was
just like it was like it was like someone who like doesn't know how to play minecraft playing
minecraft like the most inferior thing of all time all right well look i'm heading on i'm heading down
to slimes and um oh it's totally us yeah i'm or where or is this pull is this uh not polonium
hill or is this assault assault slash no it's not it's not i think i think this is probably this is
slimes and right here yeah definitely all right well you know i got i got the prototype fish command
and you know i'm i'm deep i'm testing it out in the in the development server hold on mom i'm
putting you on speakerphone you're you're you're you're gonna be on a video mom so don't say anything
incriminating i'm putting you on speaker right now mom you're on camera you're on you're on the video
hi amy i'm just calling to tell you we have to leave in five minutes got you mom be right down
hi hi well you heard the woman um subscribe to uh munchies mom's patreon at patreon.com
slash um munchies mom munchies mom and that's it that's my message she gives great seminars
she does she has great health advice for you and uh and and and you won't miss it so thank you for
fucking sitting through another one of these god awful things uh we have to do a fucking stream
later oh my god yeah i guess we're doing a stream later okay all right bye bye