Hello everyone, welcome to another rowdy fuckers cop killers, where we're here and we're queer.
We're doing the same old shit, we're never gonna evolve past our primitive state and we'll just fucking die here, die among the fleas and the ticks.
I think we should, I think me and Munchy, I'm Ben Saint and I'm here with Munchy by the way, me and Munchy have decided that creative stagnation is the way to go.
We're gonna do the same thing forever.
Yes.
But we're gonna play Pokemon. We're gonna play some fucking Pokemon and fight each other.
Pokemon is all you need in life. It's like that NPC said, Pokemon encompasses all of my life and I'm okay with that.
Yeah, that fucking guy.
I truly empathize with him more than anyone else in my life.
He was, I was like, oh my god, I feel you bro.
Yeah man, no, I'm Munchy, I'm so fucking into Pokemon recently.
Dude, don't I know it.
Yeah, I'm way more into Pokemon now as an adult than I was as a kid, honestly.
That's because you were stunnows and you were just fucking gay but now you've evolved past primitive thoughts such as sex and now you can truly see what Pokemon offers.
And that's the ideal asexual world only operated through animal loving.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
So I'm gonna accept your fucking battle and we're gonna have a fucking battle.
We're gonna have one heck of a good time destroying each other's valuable partners.
And I should really stop clicking on OBS because every time I do it records itself and does that like crazy infinite tunnel thing.
Yeah, you just ruined the entire video so.
Yeah, I broke kayfabe, now everyone's gonna know that this isn't real.
It's all just pixels on a screen, it's not even real.
They're gonna know that they aren't been saying looking at the screen. They're gonna step out of their illusion.
Yeah, it's gonna be like being John Malkovich but in reverse.
But even more deadly.
As if we didn't think it was possible.
Anyway, I have this one in the bag immediately.
Yeah, I have gay ones on my team. It doesn't even matter.
I didn't even look at my teammates. They're decent though.
Mega evolving right out the gate. You gotta save that for when the chips are down.
I didn't even realize that was clicked. It's been so long since I played this.
Oh my fucking god, actually now I'm scared. Now that you're double calm minded.
You know what? I believe in myself though.
I'm sturdy. I'm invincible. I'll never die.
That's what they said about gay people in the 1930s and guess what happened to them? They're all extinct now.
You know why? Because of me.
Oh yeah. Don't worry about it though.
Oh come on! Motherfuck!
I need to cool down. I need to simmer down.
That was real shitty dude. I really thought I was gonna get you with a fucking sucker punch.
I really thought I was gonna get you.
You really thought you were cool but little did he know that he was in fact the worst person ever to come out.
You know, I didn't, I think never mind. I was so confident.
When my Scarmory came out with Stealth Rock I was so confident. I was like, well this is this game's over.
The spiritual successor to whoever. What's his name?
I don't know. Oh Jacob. It was Jacob.
And now he's dead. Oh my fucking god.
That should be our first topic. You should go into how you've been feeling, how you've been dealing with the post-traumatic stress of being real life.
Oh yeah, since I've come out of the game.
You see since you've come out of the closet.
Yeah, I really expected to die in there. And you know, if you die in the game you die for real.
I really did not expect to be here living among the living right now.
You know, in that last fight against Getzis he killed all my favorite Pokemon.
I was really banking on Jacob. Jacob was like my guy. I was like this guy is gonna carry me through the whole fucking thing.
And I mean, I was sad to lose 12 but he wasn't as strategically important like I wasn't positive.
Yeah, he was a piece of shit that didn't matter.
Yeah, I mean I just given him low kick and low kick was really good.
Yeah, and it's not like he was a fighting type because it's a dark person that wouldn't have been helpful.
I think there was also a steel person.
No, there wasn't a steel person.
Okay, whatever.
I mean yeah, he would have been good against the black guy. I mean the dark guy.
Yeah, but I really wanted Jake. Oh, and Barry. So bummed to lose Barry.
Yeah.
The Electro, I don't know, whatever. But anyway, I fucking got all my crappy ass B team together when we won the day and it was amazing.
They were a fucking B team.
Oh, thanks for that.
That crucial catch of Voltix.
Yeah, thank God.
Once you the Voltix was there in the box, you know, it had to be someone.
Yeah.
I was maintaining the fort.
Yeah, we wouldn't have had the confidence to go out there without you.
God fucking...
You just accept that you will never be cool.
I don't...
I'm the one who wears the sunglasses here.
You're gonna fucking sweep my old team with your first dude, dude.
No, well, I don't know. We'll see.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, this is bad for you. You're gonna die, dude.
Yeah.
That's what they fucking said in my dreams.
Aw, come on. Man.
Mew's the best Pokemon. You can't beat her.
You're one of those fucking people.
Oh god, wait, it doesn't even have a gender?
Yeah.
That's interesting. Okay, sure.
I want to have sex with it, too. Don't worry.
Yeah, don't worry, man. I'm not worried, man.
I'm not worried at all.
Oh, fucking god, dude.
I can't...
This is so terrible.
I was just...
I was just so fucking fixated on getting those stealth rocks and spikes out there that I was blind to what was happening right in front of me.
I was playing before and I had such a great win. I had like the coolest win.
You're walking through life with your fucking blinders on.
It started when they sent out their fucking Shedinja and I was like, oh shit.
I don't have anything that can hurt a Shedinja.
But I fucking swapped in for Taranitar with Sandstorm and the Sandstorm killed it.
Oh, holy shit.
It was the greatest thing that ever happened to me.
Amazing.
Yeah, but then of course...
Holy shit, you're so fucked.
You're so bad at this game.
I can't believe it.
No, it's okay. I have knockoff. You're done.
Oh, shit.
Fuck, my last hope.
Okay, okay.
You're fucked, dude. You're so fucked.
What do you mean, man? I still have a chance, man. I still have a chance.
Rematch.
Yeah.
Okay.
Really, the moment you just completely obliterated the psychic type person,
I knew that you were going to just get through it with no problem.
You completely just fucking destroyed her and her family.
Well, I meticulously planned out my strategy for the Elite Four.
I knew exactly what that Musharna was going to do.
And I was like, okay, I'll send him out.
Toxic Spikes, two turns. He'll go to sleep for yawn, et cetera, et cetera.
But then, yeah, against the champion, I didn't have a real solid plan or anything,
so I was just like, well, I'll just do whatever.
And that's why I actually...
Ah, fuck's sake.
That's why people actually died against her.
Come on, man. Come on.
I have like a bin saint team with me, which is to say horrible.
Yeah, the bee team.
Uh...
I knew you were going to switch. I knew you were going to switch, dude.
Yeah, man, yeah. Ah, shit.
Yeah, I have like five Pokémon at the same time.
Well, I'll kill each and every one of them.
They're all done.
They're all done, dude.
Nothing can kill me, you know why?
What? Why am I trapped?
Because I'm the drill. Are you stupid?
Are you stupid?
Yeah, okay, I guess I'm fucked.
That's okay, I'm going easy on you.
Yeah, alright. I'm going to wake up this turn.
That's not how sleep works.
Yes, it is.
It might as well be.
Nice stealth rock, you fuck.
Thanks, dude. I learned it in school.
Yeah, that's good.
Yeah, boy! Ah, come on!
You are the worst human.
90% accuracy.
And I'm in fact the best human.
You see, for I was once an ape, and then when I was an ape,
I touched a magic fruit, and then it gave me superpowers.
I love how Ben is actually stupid. I love that part.
I forgot I'm slower than that.
I love that part.
I looked at Gallead's speed, and I was like,
oh, he's so fast, cool! Jesus Christ, alright.
That's my favorite part of this game, is that when Ben is terrible.
I felt so confident of going into this.
Alright, don't worry about it, though. It's all good.
Yeah.
I have no idea what to do right now.
There's nothing you can do.
Look at this man. Look what you're up against.
It's a fucking ice cube. I mean, Ice Snowflake.
Aw, god damn it!
LOL.
Guys, everyone type in chat right now,
like, now you're going to wait for the beat to be over.
There's no chat.
Type now, one.
I mean, if you want to stream this, go right ahead.
I'm like, we should do all GrannyFuckersCoptlers live sometime.
Yeah, we should. Yeah, why not?
Yeah.
Alright.
But actually no, because I don't want anyone to see me lose.
In real time.
So they can berate you in the present as opposed to in the future.
I was so confident.
Alright.
Now we're going to say who's the real champion of Yanova.
You fucking piece of shit.
I think so. I think...
Wait, what?
Oh, no.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
It was all a farce. The nose lock was staged.
We saw that Max revived you, you piece of shit.
Yeah, okay. Did you see my fucking comment about the Max?
No, no, no.
Nate was all like, Ben, did you lie to us?
Was it all faked?
I was like, Nate, look.
I explained it in the comments.
He's like, yeah, but how do we know?
He was like pretending that he didn't believe it.
Well, explain what happened right now for video proof.
Okay.
This is going to be like Edward Snowden revealing NSA leak documents.
Can you just imagine Ben's face right up against the camera
in a not very well-willed room in Hong Kong?
Yes.
Okay, okay, fine.
God, I gotta fucking strategize and whatever.
So, yes, it was during EV training,
and I had to do...
Oh, God.
So bad.
I'm just, yeah.
If you were thinking about this, could this person really have not used a Max revive?
Could this person have one fair and square?
No, just don't lie to yourselves.
Alright. Yeah, dude, you fucking idiot.
Nice. Oh, God.
This means nothing.
This does mean nothing.
Oh, I got you, though. Oh, I fucking got you.
Alright.
Are you going to go for another sick sell?
No, of course not.
Don't be ridiculous.
Live on stream.
This is a deep round.
I can't even think to fucking defend my honor with this shit going on.
God fucking dammit!
I should have known you were going to do that.
It was the obvious move, and I...
And he's just dropping the bomb every way.
He can't even explain how he totally cheated, but he's not going to admit it.
I know. Oh, God, that's not even good. Why are you doing it?
It's not even good. Why are you doing it?
It's not even cool. It's not even good.
It's not even good. It's not cool. It's so stupid.
I'm going to freeze you, dude.
Nah.
I'm going to freeze you.
That's not fact-based.
That's not fact-based at all.
And you're going to have to switch.
It's not fact-based.
Fuck.
Anyway, so during EV training, I had to reduce my speed EVs,
and I didn't have tomato berries because the lady that sells berries,
she sells all the different kinds of EV reducing berries,
except for the fucking the good kind, the tomato berries.
And she was...
So I was like, I needed to reduce Christ.
I needed to reduce friendship somehow.
Oh, God. Here we go.
Hey, there we go.
Yeah, I got one.
You got one.
Yeah, I did. You're fucked now.
Yeah, except that you have a life orb on and you're going to die from next hit no matter what.
It doesn't matter. I'm going to take someone out with me.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll switch right out onto these fucking stealth rocks.
Yeah, right.
What do you think about that?
It's not a fact-based.
Maybe I'll just switch it up.
Regice? Not real.
Not real.
Not a real Pokemon.
Aw, I almost fucking got him.
What are you going to do? You're going to like substitute or something?
Nah, I would never do something so foolish.
Nah, I have more faith in you than that.
I don't know who's taller. I mean, faster.
Oh, it's me, of course.
Well, I won't.
Aw, God.
Nah, well, I'm going to fucking get you, though.
Whatever.
Okay, I'm improving. I'm steadily improving.
Steadily improving.
Steadily improving. I'm getting better.
So, the only way to reduce speed EVs at that time was that I had to go to Join Avenue and give my Pokemon haircuts and shit that raised friendship and reduced EVs.
But they wouldn't let me do it because all my Pokemon were at max friendship.
So off-camera, I went and got deliberately KO'd so that I could reduce friendship by one so that they would give me a fucking haircut.
And then I was like, that turned out to be really difficult and untenable and annoying, so I was like, fuck it, I will spend the five hours grinding.
Yeah, and I used max revives because I had all these revives lying around.
I didn't, I don't know, I just used the max one because whatever.
And then I decided to say fuck it and not do that and grind Join Avenue to get a good berry store and buy some sweet berries instead.
And that is the story of why I used a max revive.
And if you think it's cheating, then please crucify me.
Please come to my house and please kill me.
Please kill me. I don't want to live anymore.
If the people don't accept that I am the greatest Pokemon master of all time.
Well, after this, how could they?
No. No.
I didn't even kill all the Pokemon.
What are you, what? What is it?
Wow, this is a fair matchup. A furfrow.
Furfrow is good, dude.
No, but I have a Mewtwo.
Mewtwo is nothing. Mewtwo is garbage.
Mewtwo doesn't even have a single superpower.
He is not even good. Oh my team is crazy. Holy shit.
I'm going to win this time. Dammit, never mind, I lose.
Never mind, I lose.
That's it. That was my last chance and I blew it.
Do you have any closing statements? Where are you going to go from now?
Where am I going to go from now? Oh, I'm going to go to fucking Alola.
You know, my things didn't really work out with the whole Pokemon Genocide thing.
Turns out it's more complicated, so I've got to formulate a plan.
I'm going to go to Yunova and this time things are going to be different.
See, that's the perfect place because in Alola they don't have an elite force.
You can become the champion and Yunova, they had laws in place and shit,
but Hawaii is like a vast jungle with only ethnicities there.
So you can just assert yourself fully. Only ethnicities.
Oh, I get what you're saying. Yeah, god fuck.
It's a jungle like no other.
Yeah, I think guerrilla warfare will be the thing to do.
What can I even fucking do against this?
I don't know why you did that.
What, but brought out survivor? Yeah.
Bad options.
Yeah, okay. I wasn't convinced by Mewtwo, but if you've got pherothorn, I'm done.
Oh, whoa. What?
God, Christ. God, Christ.
Yeah, boy!
That's shit.
Ah, but I'm still, ah, fuck, whatever. That was only my opening move.
That was only my opening move. They don't even know anything.
No, no, nobody does.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Mewtwo is so crazy. Why is it even in the fucking game?
Oh man, makes me mad.
He didn't have a single stat under fucking 150. What the hell?
And he's got, don't forget his two mega evolutions.
Yeah.
Now those are some, now those are some Pokemon.
Those are in fact Pokemon.
Yes, it is true.
Anyway, you're done. You're fucking done, unless, unless you've got, oh, okay.
Oh, you're a fool, man.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, dude, yeah, bro.
No, call Corona. He's taking over.
Yeah, bro.
Get fucked, dude.
Now he's done. He's going to hurt himself because he's gay. Ah, shit. Okay, whatever.
Yeah, that was a tear. I don't know why I did that. I don't know why.
That was a good idea.
That was a weird decision that you made.
Oh, it's okay. I've got you on the ropes now.
I don't think this affects you, but I'm going to die anyway.
Yeah, whatever.
You are a ding-dong.
Well, I, I was going to die anyway. There's nothing I can do.
Sure, yeah.
Wow.
Oh, dear.
Check out this play. Check out this play.
No.
Oh, come on, dude.
Well, it doesn't, it's still fucking great. It's still the right move.
Dynamic punch is always the right thing to do.
Whatever. You don't even know how to fucking do anything.
So why should I even do anything?
Yeah, that's fair.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
There's one thing I think of when I look at Ben St.
What's that?
It's gullible and terrible.
Gullible and terrible.
I'm going to put those two words.
Oh, really?
I...
I'm going to put those two words on your tombstone.
Cool, dude.
I love it.
I love my official death.
Oh, no.
I hate that.
So, Munchy.
Wait, was there something else I said I wanted to say?
You want to talk about Sun and Moon generally.
And also, you've only said like three things actually about the Nuzlocke.
And you've just been getting distracted by fucking Pokemon playing.
It takes all my fucking concentration to play Pokemon.
What can I say?
Oh, god. What's he going to do?
What's he going to do?
He takes a breath.
Like, oh, okay, here.
I'm going to finally buckle down.
Oh, no. What's he going to do?
You know what?
I think I made the wrong move.
But we'll see.
Oh, no.
Return's never a wrong move.
Well, I won't say why I thought it was a bad move for a second there.
Of course not.
I might lose this, in fact.
I think so, yeah.
I feel good.
I feel like I've gotten the upper hand all of a sudden.
First, I was quite fast.
Faster than I would have imagined.
First row's good, man.
First row's good.
It's like a, it's like a, it's like a, I don't know, it's like halfway between a,
it's like halfway between a lie part and a, and a, oh, what's the other one?
Uh, I don't know, a Chansey?
Or a, or a Stoutland?
Stoutland, yeah.
Man.
See, that's why I thought, that's why I thought it was a bad move because I thought you were
going to switch into pherothorn immediately.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what a smart person would do.
Which is what I am.
I vastly overestimated you, though.
Whatever.
And it's not even real.
Whatever you know me.
Clowns have to make their living somehow, and I make my living through murder.
So, you know.
Yeah, man.
That's how it is.
I mean, I feel that dog.
I feel that real, real hard.
You know what I'm saying?
Bro.
Oh, believe me, white person.
I know exactly what you're saying.
Yeah, white person.
Yeah, bro.
Um, hmm.
God.
I'm going to let you know that nothing you do will ever matter.
Well, this turned specifically, but in general, as well, just to let you know.
Anyway.
Just to clue you in.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah, I did the right thing.
Oh, wow.
Oh, I did the right thing.
It's not like that never happens.
I always do the right thing, dude.
Every, every time.
Anyway, I released fucking Nuzlocke, and I was so happy because I fucking saw the whole
thing through to the end, and it was all great.
I think it was weaker at the beginning.
Like, I think it gets better as it goes on.
I think the ending is a masterpiece, and I'm really proud of it.
It's just a shame that I marred it with this Max Revive scandal that I'll never shake off
and that no one will ever, no one will ever let go.
The whole thing is ruined.
It's all, it's all trash.
Truly, I think, I think the problem was.
Yeah.
I mean, even watching the videos in the first place was the problem.
Watching them at all?
Yeah.
That we all suffered together.
Because due to the fact that we were watching them, you continued to make them, and thus
you let the greed and corporate interest go in your head.
Yeah, all the viewers hurt me by giving me false reasons to continue, and I mean, look
what's become of me.
Look what's become.
Look at me.
I'm, I'm an unfeasance, and it's depressing.
God.
Peer dove is such a cute Pokemon, but it's, evolutions are disgusting.
I don't, I don't get, is unfeasance supposed to be like gross, because it just looks like
a bird?
I mean, it's, it's pink head thing is weird.
Yeah.
But it's not like gross.
Well, I mean, that's fine.
Yeah, that gross thing about that is that what you just said, that it's gross.
Yeah, yes.
I don't know.
I guess I just don't find it that bad.
I think, I don't, I don't know if it's the male one, but there's another one that looks
weirder.
Yeah, yeah, the male one.
It's got a weird pink, like weird rooster tentacle head.
Hey man.
I think most of the gen ones, er, not the gen ones, see he gen paws weird.
Oh god, wait.
It's my, oh it's me.
I forgot that it was me.
Um.
Ben sainte, haul it up to production yet again.
Yeah, I know.
Oh god.
Oh no.
No.
Why?
I don't know man.
Get ready for the coolest Pokemon.
Oh my fucking god.
Yeah man.
Um.
Disgusting.
God, fucking paralysis.
Yeah.
Is the worst.
It's so bad.
It's so good dude.
Like the power glove.
No I'm saying dude.
Oh I know.
Believe me.
No one could know more than I do right now.
I've researched every book on the power glove and I have concluded that I do know what you're
saying.
Shit.
I have concluded that I am indeed in the know of what you are speaking and or selling
to me.
Well that's just terrific.
That's just Stu.
Pendis.
Oh my god.
What am I going to do?
Bam.
Yes I got him.
Look how much I got him.
Oh fuck he had iron.
Ah nerd.
Ah you idiot.
Ah you stupid jerk.
Fucking real life isn't even real.
No.
I should have done that last turn.
Oh.
Oh I didn't even know I had that.
Yeah.
Well obviously.
You tell me.
Yeah.
I was thinking that too.
Whoever sleeps in your team on the nose lock.
What's the name?
The sleepy guy.
The sleep kid.
Who rests.
Fuck.
Wait what?
You were wondering who had it?
Like you knew someone had it?
Yeah.
Oh well.
I don't know.
Some idiot.
Oh well.
Nice use of protect.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Nice use of protect.
16%.
Nice second punch of dummy.
It's over.
It's so fucking over.
If FurFrow couldn't win.
Then nobody can.
Nothing can.
It's all over.
It is all over.
And now it's done.
Your fate is sealed.
I know.
Yeah.
Nice try.
Jesus Christ.
Oh I got you though.
Didn't I get you?
What the fuck?
I thought I turned one.
What the shit?
Come on.
Bullshit.
10% chance to freeze.
That's crazy.
100% chance to thaw immediately.
That's the worst thing that's ever happened to anyone I'm convinced.
There's collusion at play.
I guarantee it.
Yeah I think so.
There's mad collusion.
I mean I was colluding for sure.
For sure.
There's no question about that.
Ben, Max Revives Saint over here trying to act like other people are pulling something.
That is what they call me.
What up in?
It's like calling me on the streets.
Hey Max Revives come over here.
There's nothing I can fucking do against Farathorn with Thunderwave.
He's an invincible demon.
And that's it.
Yeah wow.
That was cheating what you just did.
That was cheating.
Well you see in the Arctic it's okay.
I'm probably Arctic.
Did you see my fucking toxic stall strats?
Yeah I did.
I was very proud of them.
Yeah man I was like this is it.
I gotta be as cheap as possible fighting this champ and it worked.
When you're fighting for Pokemon World Domination you gotta do what you gotta do.
Yeah you gotta do what you gotta do.
Someone in the comments was like you and Getsus aren't that similar.
You both think humans are valued humans over Pokemon and you both use bullshit you know
asshole strategies like toxic stall.
And I was like what come on.
I never asked for this.
That's what you get.
I know.
You're a tyrant Ben you have to realize this.
You are a tyrant over your YouTube channel.
Like at first I was mad like I didn't realize what I was doing was using the strategy of a villain.
But then I was like you know what I'm okay with that.
I like that.
I'm glad.
Fuck.
I think anyone who didn't realize that you are a villain right from the start needs to reevaluate things.
Yeah.
I got through paralysis but I just fucking missed.
Yeah well that's the reason death comes.
Oh no.
Why did I use so far?
I don't know I just picked it because I didn't care.
Why didn't I fucking rest?
Why didn't I rest last turn?
I had rest and I didn't use it.
What a crazy person you are.
I want to just end.
You know I could.
I could just forfeit.
Oh my god.
I should.
This is stupid.
No.
You don't know.
Dazzling gleam.
You don't know a thing.
You're a bitch.
You don't know a single thing.
I'm going to win the next one.
No.
No that's not possible.
It is possible.
Anything's possible.
No.
Even such a thing as that.
Christ.
No.
Terrible.
Well this should do the trick.
Come on furfrow.
Come on man.
Just give me this.
What?
I was using sucker punch.
That's just the faster one go first.
Yeah.
Oh gay.
See it's the one that straight goes first.
Oh yeah.
Pokemon calculates how cool you are.
Yeah.
Straightness being the major factor.
Major factor.
Major factor in that.
Yeah.
It's your secret trainer ID.
It's straight or gay.
The Pokemon showdown fanbase really did not like it when they added the feature that asks
you whether you're gay when you sign in.
Which immediately redirects you to a different website.
Oh shit I closed the thing.
I was supposed to rematch.
Oh don't worry.
Send me a thing.
Yeah here we go.
I got you fam.
All right munchie.
Yeah.
So this battle it's time for me to distract you.
Oh no.
And yeah tell me what you've been doing.
I have.
Because you, there's been talk, there's been talk that you might be at Radcon too.
There's the talk of the town, the word on the street on the grapevine,
that you might be at Radcon too this year.
Ben St. was walking down the street in his Brooklyn neighborhood
and he heard a faint whisper, a faint black ethnicity whisper
stating that much he may in fact be here soon.
Through sensual, through large but sensual lips, African American lips,
it was spoken, it was said on the street.
Well, that is true and somewhat closely related to the topic of I am making something.
Yeah, you're making a thing.
And I know very little about it, you've told me one or two things.
Yeah, which I will not go into in mass detail.
All you need to know is that alligators are cool and that's it.
Alligators are cool.
I don't think anyone would disagree with you about that.
Really, is that...
I know, I already know more than that.
Okay, okay, okay, I'll go into more detail.
Come on, what the f**king balloon, man!
You're so bad, it's crazy, it's crazy.
Yeah, but I got you though.
Oh, Patreon fame is bad.
I shot you.
He shot me.
I shot you, dude, you're dead.
Okay, well, it's hard to figure out what I should say and what I shouldn't say.
Not to the fact that, oh, f**k, I'm gay.
You gay, dude.
It's proof, okay, okay.
Undeniable proof that I do, in fact, love penis.
Yeah, true, yeah, it's true, dude.
F**k me.
I don't even know how to say that.
Okay, it's set in Miami, Florida.
The most villainous scum of the earth live there.
Yeah, totally.
No place on earth could possibly be as villainous and degenerate as Miami,
in my opinion.
I agree.
A close second did for Colorado.
Have you ever seen the Miami connection?
Yes, I have.
You have?
Okay, good.
Wait, that's the one with the guy he does that.
It's like one particular martial art?
Yeah, that's one thing.
It might not be called...
I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, I think it's the Miami connection.
My friend used to have this giant, beautiful poster.
He had this pride and joy.
It was this gorgeously painted, big, fully-framed image of the Miami connection.
Oh, you nerd, dude.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah, dude.
I can't believe this.
What a crazy person.
I tricked you.
Do you think I was gonna ice beam or some gay sh**?
Maybe.
Yeah, well, shows what you know.
Anyway, you're f**king gay.
This is a story plain and simple about evolution.
Yes, it is.
Not to spell you on battle, but that as well.
Sh**.
I don't care if...
Okay, wow, it didn't raise to be cool.
Thanks.
I tried to trick you, but I didn't trick you.
What the f**k's up with that?
Oh, my God.
Oh, sh**.
Oh, it's incredible.
It's unbelievable.
It's never been done.
It's beautiful when a plan comes into action.
That's not the line.
I love it when a plan comes together, you know.
The A team.
Don't even talk.
Ding dong.
Don't even talk, man.
Just don't even talk.
You little ding dong.
Okay, and by what I mean, it's about evolution.
Everyone knows that I'm an extremely pious man.
I know.
Believe me, I know, said Ben, rolling his eyes.
I'm a pious man, and as such, I...
Oh, you f**king nerd, dude.
I'm just so gay.
You're so gay.
I'm so gay.
You're just getting gayer every time.
Every single second goes by.
Every last one.
I'm auto-clicking on a giant cookie, but instead of a cookie, it's a giant dildo, and that makes me gayer.
Every single second.
Yeah, yeah, plus one, plus one, plus one.
Plus one, plus one.
One, one, one, one.
Everyone hit plus one gay in the comments.
Oh, that wasn't fair.
That wasn't fair?
Dude, it's f**king one.
Everything's fair.
Wait, is fighting ineffective against poison?
Maybe.
I forgot.
Yeah, I think it is.
Otherwise, that focus blast would have been super effective.
Yeah.
All right.
Oh, but no, I know.
It's resist fighting, but I'm also dark.
Just weak, so it...
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, yeah, I thought it was going to be super because you're dark, but it was, I guess,
bleh, poison, whatever.
Just read, dude.
Just read.
I know.
Well, if only I had a max revive to revive one of my Pokemon.
Wouldn't that be nice?
That would be nice.
That's what we all want.
That's what we all want in this life.
By the way, no one ever let that meme die.
Well, I mean, you can if you want to.
What the f**k, man?
For f**k's sake.
Whatever.
I'm f**king making progress here.
Yeah.
Worked out just...
Zoroarxoro...
Ah, come on, man.
That would have been hilarious.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Real funny, real f**k.
I'm f**ked.
I know you're f**ked.
Yep, yep.
God damn it.
Let's end this.
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
No, but it is like this.
And it always will be.
Whoa, what the f**k?
Oh, shit, man.
Okay, well, good game, idiot.
Yeah, wow.
It's not like, hey, you started like you cheated.
Haha.
I know.
No, I would never.
I would never cheat.
Anyway, you know what?
Okay, okay.
Like, yeah, the thing about the Max Survive, like,
yeah, you know, maybe...
Cheating.
You could call it...
Maybe some people would think that's cheating.
And those people are cordially invited
to please forgive me and I love you.
Don't be mad at it, friends.
But the...
But Nate.
Okay, Nate being the dick bag.
The dick bag that he is.
We all never trust Nate.
We have him from day one.
He's a sneak.
He's a creep.
He's a demon.
Jeez.
So, you know,
because nobody trusts him,
because of his proven status as scoundrel.
His corporate greed
and basically just everything horrible about him.
That's right.
Has been uncovered through data mining.
That's correct.
He wasn't just about like,
oh, the Max Survive, you know,
use it off camera.
Oh, cheating or whatever.
He was like...
He was like, dude, did you...
Does this mean, like,
you didn't beat the Elite Four?
Like, were you just faking the whole Elite Four?
Were you reviving your Pokemon between...
Like, first of all, it wouldn't even make sense
that I would use a Max Survive in between battles, right?
Like, if I was...
If I had cheated the Elite Four,
the way I would have cheated it,
was that I would have, like, you know,
scummed the battles and done them over and over again
until I won and then saved.
And I was like...
And he, like, pretended not to believe me
for a second or whatever.
But I was like...
Shit. I shouldn't have done that.
Shit.
And I finally, I was like, all right, fine.
I have the full uncut video.
I have the uncut footage of me fighting the Elite Four,
you know, legit.
I will upload it just for you.
But then he was like, no, I believe you.
But then I was like, why don't I upload?
So I think, actually, I already did.
I already uploaded it, but it's not available.
I want to, like, cut...
Because it's not just that there's a bunch of, like, stuff at the beginning
that's not interesting. I want to, like, snip that off
so it's just the Elite Four.
And I'll put, like, a little link in the description,
who wants to know how cool I am.
Anyone who wants to watch this obviously
doctored footage that I cut out...
Obviously doctored footage.
That I cut out when I revived my Pokemon.
Watch me, like, fuck around with berries
and, like, you know, switch around
move sets and stuff
for, you know, 15 minutes in between every battle.
You know, you're all welcome to it.
Mm-hmm.
You will never retain any credibility.
You'll never survive.
No matter what you do.
Ooh, that was bad.
That was bad.
Ooh, that hurt, though.
Dang.
Durant's fucking cool.
Yeah, I know. He deserves more praise in life
than he does. He receives.
Yeah, I have to agree.
Um, he's gay, though.
I don't like that.
I don't agree with that.
Kevin? Yeah.
I wish you could name all of your Pokemon
before going into Glorious Battle.
Even in a random...
in a random thing.
Uh, ooh, I got a lot of...
I got a lot of shit options here.
Yeah.
Well, it's fitting.
Because you're gay.
Yeah, I agree.
Check this out, Faggot. Oh, no.
Oh, but I won't have to.
But I won't have to.
Because you're a nerd.
All right, whatever.
I'm not even gonna...
I should've just done that right at the gate.
I'm gonna be a problem, isn't he?
Why did I waste all my good luck
on that successful sleep powder?
Ah, fuck.
Ah, dang.
Ah, darn.
Yes.
Just what I wanted.
Yeah, whatever.
My chest o' berry didn't mean anything.
Can't sleep, bitch.
It didn't mean anything to me.
Uh...
Yeah, we'll get...
get fucked here.
Ah, I knew you were gonna switch. I tricked ya.
I tricked ya!
Yeah!
Look at that.
Crazy. Look what I've done.
Uh...
Hmm...
Oh,
you're gonna be doing some nasty shit, aren't you?
Nah, I would never do that.
Yeah, I think you're gonna do some real nasty shit.
As I said before, I'm a very pious man,
and I would never use underhanded tactics.
You would never...
You would never do a toxic stall like me.
Yeah.
Yeah, like, no!
You would never be such a villain as this guy.
God fucking...
I can't believe this.
Throughout the nuzlocke,
he's been transformed more and more into snagly whiplash.
Wait.
Why did you go first?
You know.
No, I don't know.
I mean, you don't...
You don't have swift swim.
You're keogre.
Well...
How the fuck did you go first?
I'm just a fast guy.
No!
I'm a fast guy, Ben.
How...
Hmm...
I'm not sure about this one.
I'm unconvinced.
Well, you know what they say.
Come on, jump bluff.
Come on, do this for me.
Oh, you fucking nerd.
Oh, jump bluff.
Jump bluff.
So bad.
Why?
Oh, he's good.
Wait, what were you...
Oh, I think you were...
What were you gonna do?
So bad.
I was gonna do a single thing.
I think you were gonna do something.
I realized his head was like a xenomorph.
Um...
Dialga.
Dialga's so much cooler than Polkia.
Yeah, Polkia's gay.
Polkia looks so terrible.
Garrachina is where it's at, though.
Tell me more.
Oh, right, I was completely sidetracked.
About your gay thing.
Yeah, you know what I'm talking about.
The high sci-fi setting of Miami, Florida.
Right.
In the distant future of the present day.
Yeah.
What's it fucking called?
The herptophon of the world,
meaning reptiles and amphibians.
Herptophon?
Yeah, no, herptophon.
Herptophon.
Herptophon, okay.
Yes.
That's the real term used by real people.
I believe it.
In their everyday life.
Yeah?
Is that a fact?
Yeah, that is a fact.
I learned it from www.com.com.
I learned it from
the wwe.
wwe.
e
Blossom is so bad.
I hate it so much,
even though I love its design.
It's just so bad.
Um...
And they
evolve, not through conventional
means, but they hyper-evolve
using virtues.
Virtues.
Tell me
more about virtues.
Of course, of course.
Once a dirty,
disgusting to generate,
disgusting herptophon,
a member of that family
becomes aware of
through humans teaching it
or through finding out of their own
accords, the concept
of virtues, such as
chastity
and humility and justice.
Okay, yeah.
Once they learn
of these concepts,
they
evolve past their primitive
uh, their primitive
like the lowest rung on the
echeladder of
echeladder.
They're just shit, and they become
not shit by becoming cool,
and to become cool, you have to learn about virtues.
Virtues.
Okay, that's pretty much exactly
what you told me.
Wait...
I didn't tell you that at all.
Oh, I know what... Gigadrain did twice
because I lost flying type.
Oh, I forgot Roosted that.
Yeah, I mean, okay.
You told me about the main character,
but all you told me
about the main character
is basically exactly what you just described.
Like, so
like, before, I was like,
you were like, ah, yes, he is a reptile
of some description.
I won't spoil. What did what?
Who, you know,
who became
this new thing when he
discovered these particular virtues?
And I was like, haha, that's funny.
And then you just described, like, yeah, my story
is about a world where herptophon
have become cool things by discovering virtues.
I'm like, oh,
well, well, shit.
I should have known.
You should have known that. I'm too
slippery.
You're pretty slippery, dude. You're being pretty slippery right now.
I'm not gonna lie.
Not gonna lie.
Anyway.
We can say
he is an alligator.
Yes, yes.
The alligator.
The alligator to end all alligators.
I'm
I'm really
I'm really curious.
I'm really curious to see more
of these virtues, honestly.
That concept really tickles something within me.
What? It's because
you don't believe it, because it's true.
I don't know what I believe
anymore. That's terrible, by the way.
Yeah, I really wish I didn't die,
but it was a pretty good
it's pretty good trade, TBH.
TBH.
GBH.
GBA.
Game Boy Advanced.
To continue,
this alligator has learned specifically
of the virtues
of justice so far.
And he seeks to
better. Wait, wasn't there another one?
Was it
courage? I thought you said it was
courage and justice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Courage and
justice, but mainly justice.
Mainly justice.
And he seeks to fully
shut the fuck up, dude. It's not funny at all.
This isn't a comedy. I know.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing about this.
I'm head over heels in
serious mode right now.
I'm head over heels serious.
Oh
God, please. Yes. Yes, I did the right
thing.
It's not even cool.
So good.
It's ridiculous.
So good it's not real.
So good it's stupid as fuck.
What was I saying?
Oh, yeah, yeah. He
seeks to better, to first of all
to better himself and to
then in turn
spread these virtues
to fellow herptophon and
to humans too.
Because humans like
those fucking... Does he want to spread all
virtues or just the virtues that he has become
aware of? No, well
you can't really spread virtues. You have
a master yourself. Yeah, okay.
So he wants to conquer them all
and then spread them.
Like the patron saint
he is
the beautiful man.
So he's like a walking talking, he's like a
missionary of justice.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Incredible. Alright, I'm gonna lose.
It's over. You're definitely gonna lose.
There's nothing I could possibly do right now.
Anyway
Yeah, I might as well just fucking in my
fucking life right now. Yeah,
bro.
Kill yourself, bro.
No.
Humans are like...
they are privileged pieces of shit
and due to the fact that they are human
and that their ancestors have worked
to evolve in the past
some of them may give up the virtues
and stagnate
evolutionarily
and you can't go backwards.
You can only just be a piece of shit
and not help the human race
if you cast my drift.
I do.
So you don't like
turn back into a
whatever the shit form
of a human is.
A neanderthal.
So
he wants to again just
elevate everyone to a higher plane
and spread the
wonderful things that are
either these virtues.
Shit.
And to do so
he has dedicated his life to solving crime
and
helping those in need
and that's how he will spread his
message by corrupting
or bringing justice to this corrupt
world that is Miami.
This
disgusting wasteland
this filth
this fucking filth
that is Florida.
He will purify it.
Purify Florida.
Okay man.
I understand the premise
and the plot a little bit now.
What is it though?
What's happening?
That's the setting.
That's the setting and that's the premise.
You want to know what's going on
specifically in this
case.
Anything you feel like sharing.
Sure.
All I'm willing to
let out
is that there's a lot of
wine to see. There's mother going
along. There's fucking bitches doing
gay shit.
There's the giant web
Nate from
PCP owns a casino.
Right.
I think I remember
that detail or something like it.
Wait, so Nate
personally is in the store.
Okay.
That's interesting.
Well
he goes by another name to keep low.
Also fuck you.
Yeah!
That's a two in a row. Am I a genius?
That was my three in a row bitch.
Was that only three? Oh it's pitiful.
It's pitiful.
It's pitiful compared to the ten in a row streak
I'm about to embark on.
Yeah.
There's a lot of
people
are very apprehensive to learn of the virtues
as they believe
them to be old fashioned when in fact
they are new fashioned
and they are
they are fashion
weekly. They are incredible
and the main character wants
to spread that around like wildfire
and this
specific case starts out
as a kid mapping
eventually it evolves into something much greater.
Does a leggy dame
is he approached by a leggy dame?
Oh, of course.
One of
intense hysterics in fact.
Fan.
I like to hear that.
Yes, of course.
Yeah.
If you're picking up what I'm throwing down.
I totally am bro.
Of course.
I'm feeling it.
You know.
Okay.
I get the
I know what it is
story wise but it's a comic, right?
Yes.
It's a comic.
Okay, sweet.
What's
how
how long is it going to be?
Where will it
happen?
It will be released around
20 pages.
It's not going to be all done.
The entire thing I estimate
to be around 60 maybe?
60 pages, okay.
Maybe longer.
Probably not shorter.
Can I ask
how done is it?
All the pages
are
sketched out and now I'm doing the finals.
Shit.
That's all I can say. Shit.
I'm so bad.
You're so fucked.
I'm going for 10.
10 in a row.
Well.
Now I know you're paying to me.
I'm just clicking oh.
That's a purple color.
It feels bad, right?
It feels horrible.
You did this to me.
You made this happen, dude.
That was wrong of me.
Whatever.
Come on.
All right.
How long did it take you to rough
the 60?
It took me...
No.
I know you've been working on this
while you've had school and shit.
I know you've got stuff.
Not everything is sketched.
The first block
I'm coming out with
so I have that much done.
To be honest with you,
I have only
really started like a month ago.
I've just been like, yeah, that's the thing
that's going to fucking happen, but I've only gone down
to brass 10.
I know you mentioned it a while ago,
but I only heard that
you'd actually started working on it
pretty recently.
Recently-ish.
Of course.
Yeah.
Really, all I had to do,
the drawing is easy
and writing is easy.
It only took
this shit.
It only took three days
to sketch all of it out.
Holy shit.
You...
I'm fucked.
That's incredible.
I'm jealous
that you could
just come up with all that shit
in so little time.
Yeah.
Most of it was writing
and I just had to...
Once I had all the speech bubbles in my head,
it was easy to just
make it interesting on paper.
I'm doing the Andrew Hussie
the Andrew Hussie way I
format my sketches.
All of them are on little boxes on one piece of paper.
Oh.
So they're like...
basically? Yeah.
Okay.
I don't know.
That still sounds pretty good.
I still think you're doing it faster than I would have.
Well, you know, I'm young blood.
Yeah, you are.
I'm basically old hat at this point.
Basically, just should die.
Absolute.
Absolute. Are you familiar with the broken mat saga?
What the fuck?
No.
I don't watch...
I don't watch the PCP.
You're not familiar with our work.
You don't keep up with us?
No, I'm not.
I just have to do with MatPat.
Did you get MatPat on a PCP episode?
No.
God damn it.
No, broken mat, the wrestler.
His brother, he went crazy
because his brother did something, I don't know.
Did something?
He did something or whatever.
Oh, how could you not know about this?
Yes, okay.
That's right.
I don't know who to switch into though.
Probably...
Wait, I know.
Damn it.
This is a great decision.
Nerd.
Damn it.
Whatever.
You don't even fucking have shit.
Yeah.
Nice choice scarf.
Brill.
Does fur evolve? It doesn't, does it?
No, it doesn't.
So that EVO light is useless?
Yes.
Alright, well, fine.
But yeah, it took me about three days
to get through that.
And I would say about the sessions I was doing it
is like seven hours.
Shit.
And then I would play Minecraft
for another seven hours, and then
that's it.
Good.
I actually do
want to go into specific detail
about Minecraft, because
be as multiple people
in watching this
right now. No, exactly what I'm talking about.
Something devilish. I have been
collectively performing
sacred rituals
in Minecraft.
Alright. Go on.
Go on. Finish it.
Finish it.
I'm so bad.
Yeah, dude.
You thought a burn would fucking stop me, bro.
I'm gonna fucking die.
You're gonna fucking die, dude.
You're a lost cause.
I'm a lost cause.
No.
Yeah, bro.
What the fuck are you thinking, dude?
I have a chance to laugh.
You think Keogre can do shit?
Keogre.
Ben Steele here can't pronounce words.
What is it? Keogre?
Keogre? Stupid.
I think Keogre sounds cooler.
Well, it's also not real.
Anyway.
Anything's real.
That's it. Everything's real.
What is important is Minecraft.
I'm about to explain why Minecraft is extremely
important to my current
mental state.
Sure.
It's time to say hello to my ultimate weapon.
Oh, okay. Oh, well, it doesn't even matter.
Okay, wait, shit, it matters.
Because I miscalculated.
In my brain, I got my calculator out
and in fact, it gave me a wrong one.
It was from 100 years ago.
Calculators didn't exist, so I didn't even
have anything in my hand.
Shit, I knew I should have Dragon Dance.
Oh, good, but it didn't matter.
Even Chancey was no match.
Even Chancey, wow.
Even the unstoppable Chancey.
The powerhouse that it is.
No.
Yeah, bro, was that four?
No, that was three.
Okay, okay, I've matched your streak.
Shit, no.
Yeah, all right, this one's for all the beans.
No.
This is where it gets real.
Anyway, I have...
Oh, wait, what the shit?
Did we just start two battles at once?
Yeah, we did.
Well, let's do them both at the same time.
Oh, shit.
All right, I'm down.
I'm completely down.
Yeah.
More down than you could ever know.
Oh, wait.
Oh, shit, shit.
I have to fucking...
That wasn't good enough.
That wasn't good enough at all, oh dear.
I have nothing.
Okay.
I didn't tell the story about Minecraft.
Oh, shit.
You've been hinting at something.
Yeah.
I have recently started playing Not Discovered.
Well, I have gone back into
a server that
has been
on the same map for six years
and
it has no rules
and it's completely vanilla.
Wow, wow, wow.
That may not seem like much to an outsider.
Those on the...
Those in the
vast and special Minecraft community
will note that most people
are extremely autistic and like to have
non-vanilla, non-PVP
shalom.
Some of these are gay and they like to build things.
Yeah.
But partisans and amazing people
such as myself like to kill people
for sport.
And as such,
I greatly
like things that
that server do the fact that spawn
is like a fucking wasteland.
Imagine if you set a bomb off on Tokyo.
That's what...
And Tokyo is...
I think about setting a bomb off in Tokyo
every day that I remember that
Fully Coolie 2 is still coming out.
Oh, oh, god.
No, I forgot about that.
Yeah, right. I forget about it sometimes too.
But then I remember and that's the worst day in my life.
Anyway,
it's deeply rewarding.
And the fact that has been up
for six years and extremely important
because of the fact that
so much history has been
enacted in these
hallowed halls of Minecraft.
It's a
digital...
It basically is more important than the United States
is what I'm saying.
I can believe that.
I'm sure it's better than
Trump's America.
No!
I told you not to talk about this.
Yeah, bro. We're doing it.
Aw, come on.
That was gay.
Nah, I should do that.
I'm talking about the bannet thing.
Why'd you have to do that?
It's stupid.
It's okay. I have an answer for everything.
Oh, nice stone edge, you fucking nerd.
Your Durant's done.
Fire Punch is unstoppable.
The bannet is unstoppable.
I'm winning both of these at the same time.
I'm just so on the ball.
I'm talking about Minecraft.
I know, right?
I fucking trapped you by making me talk about shit.
Shit, damn it.
Shit, god damn it.
This can't be happening.
I'm in charge here.
It's happening, bro.
Damn.
Wait.
Oh shit, you used wish.
No.
Nooo.
Boo.
Wait.
That's no problem.
Why didn't your wish come true?
Because I used it before, dummy.
Shouldn't it have come true this turn?
No.
I used it two turns ago.
No, you...
When did it come true?
Wait, is it going to happen now?
I don't think so.
I think it already came true.
No, no, opposed.
It doesn't say so.
I'm really confused.
Maybe you're just stupid.
Was it the taunt?
Did the taunt stop it?
No, no, of course not.
Of course not.
It's cheap.
It says Max Revive Ben Sato right here.
That's not okay, dude.
Oh, come on.
Gay.
Gay, dude.
Look at this kid over here
trying to act like he didn't cheat.
Wow.
I never...
It's okay.
You know what?
I have to ignore
all of Munchie's hurtful rhetoric
and just concentrate.
His hateful propaganda.
Concentrate on crushing him where it counts
in Pokemon Town.
With Pokemon,
I mean with Minecraft,
I have been partaking
in recent activities with
most, like six people
from the piece...
From the
Rowdyfuckers Cop Killers
fan base.
There is no fan base
for the Rowdyfuckers Cop Killers.
It doesn't exist.
I am surprised
and alarmed if you're telling me
that that's not true.
Who are these
Minecraft fuckholes?
These Minecraft scoundrels.
Who are these Minecraft wizards?
You've been
you've been conjuring with.
Conjuring.
One of them is named.
Really close to the mic so he can
sample this exact...
This like three seconds I'm saying his name.
So he can sample this in his next
rap.
That one kid.
And Steel Viper
77.
Oh, I know Steel Viper. He posts
shit on the subreddit all the time.
I don't follow the subreddit because it's gay.
I mean
unfortunately the subreddit
is just our shit
being posted by people.
We haven't managed to elevate
to anything other than that yet.
It's a useful repository
if nothing else.
Yes, but I've seen Steel Viper
on there once in a while.
And we are
amassing arms to do
a great deed
and destroy everyone on the server.
And that's been occupying most
of my time as I value Minecraft life
over my real life. Like all
millennials.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean probably.
Wait. Oh, air balloon.
Fuck, air balloon was popped. Why did I knock off?
I must be a
A true
idiot of unrivaled proportions.
I must just be a person
who is
going to be dead soon.
I'm
being so stupid right now.
I'm being so fucking foolish, dude.
Oh, no.
LOL.
I was ready.
I was ready to die.
You know what? I still
fucking am. Come on.
Whatever.
Yeah, okay.
You win this round slow, bro.
Not even good, dude.
Not even fucking good.
And so Minecraft
has been
thoroughly trampling all my
attempts at
well, not trampling, but it's been cleaning
in my drawing time, which I'm 100% okay
with. As that MPC said
all my life is Pokemon, but for me
it's Minecraft. Which is
even more autistic.
Yeah, vastly
more so.
You don't even make shit in Minecraft.
You just say, you just disparage people
that make shit in Minecraft.
So wait, I'm sorry. We've been talking about this
this whole time and I'm confused.
What is it? What is it?
What's happening in Minecraft?
Is it nothing?
No, no.
With my lesions of fans that I have
we are constructing
a base
and once we
are all decked out
with the most least swaggiest of armor
we will enact our
global genocide of all new
fags. Well, I'm looking forward to that.
Yeah. Naturally.
Naturally.
Shit.
Yeah, dude.
Nice fucking
cheap-ass crit, stupid.
Yeah.
But it's too late.
I'm invincible. I can't be beat.
Oh, yeah.
Look at this kid over here thinking he's hot.
You know what they call me?
They call me that hunk of meat
that's tough to beat.
That's what the ladies say.
That's how that works?
What?
How what works?
I didn't know. I was all wrong.
Yeah, bro.
I was all wrong.
Look at this piece of shit I have.
A fucking shatot.
Ugh.
Uh, well,
I mean,
it's a good switch out, I guess.
Uh, actually,
no, he's gay. Yeah.
It's horrible.
Yeah, he's really dumb. He's really dumb and bad.
Uh, he's pitiful.
Blin-pop bitch.
I know. I know.
I'm fucked now.
Um, guess what?
Oh, no!
Hidden power. Oh, come on.
What was that? Ice? Oh, shit!
I'm not even good at this game, dude.
God, why do moves miss?
It's not fair. It's not right.
It's not fair.
It's not fair when things happen.
I'm bad at video games.
Yeah.
Right.
Was it probably hidden power fire?
No, it was...
It could have been hidden power fighting.
Was it hidden power fighting?
You know it, dude.
No, no.
You know it. That's exactly what it was.
Maybe it was hidden power normal.
Yeah, it's probably that.
Oh, of course it was. It was that as well.
I mean, what else would it have been, really,
when you get right down to it?
All right. All right, jelly man.
You're the greatest.
Yeah, there's nothing you can do
against all this jelly.
You know what I'm saying, dude?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Maybe you've heard the...
No, hip-no!
Oh, god. He's at exactly 50.
What a piece of absolute shit.
Oh, no.
Yeah, bro.
Dude, you're paralyzed. You can't do anything.
You can't do anything.
You're weak.
You're weak, dude. Quiver dance?
Pathetic.
No, check this out.
Check this out, dude. Check this out, dude.
Yeah, dude.
Shit.
Yeah, bro.
Oh, I really...
I really came out ahead. You really screwed the pooch on that one.
You really screwed the pooch.
You definitely screwed the pooch.
Yeah, right.
Oh, chat-hot. Oh, nothing.
Nothing. Not a single thing.
Yeah, I have no...
Shit, that was your first guy.
I thought we were further along.
No.
No, not at all.
Uh, fuck.
This Jensen is gonna sweep me.
Maybe.
Probably.
What do I have here?
Not...
I'm God.
I just realized I'm God.
I hope the camera was on that what I just did,
because I'm fucking God.
What, that you just did that psycho shift?
Yeah.
That's just what you do with a sigilif.
Dude, you're just bad.
I really wish I should have taunted the turn before.
But you know what?
I didn't have a choice.
It's all good.
And now you're gonna die.
Fuck. God!
Christ, why didn't I see that coming?
Yeah.
Yeah, you fucking punk.
I really fucked that up.
You punk.
What am I doing here?
Oh no.
Oh dear.
Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear, oh dear.
I think I'm worried about this meowstick.
I hope I don't have another...
fucking...
Who is the one?
Who did you fucking call mine
sweep me with the first time?
Alakazam.
Yeah, I hope you don't have another Alakazam
situation on our hands.
Why are you so stupid?
I don't know, man.
Why did you think that was a good idea?
Because I have many
abilities.
You should give me more credit.
You know...
Yeah, you're right.
Nah, dude.
But ironically, it was you
who was paralyzed.
It was in fact me.
It was me who was gay.
Yes, that is the great irony.
Come on, dude!
What the fuck? You didn't even know I had that!
The power predict
is real.
What the fuck?
The power predict is in fact realer than it has ever been.
Did you just use that
that I was going to switch to
and you were just like...
No, I knew.
I knew, dude.
I knew because
you thought it would be some good.
You know because I'm good.
You're not good, bro!
You're just
not okay!
You don't even
fucking know who's real
and who's not real.
That's true.
But...
Oh, no. Why did I do that?
Oh, no!
You're not even good, dude.
This collusion of play.
I can tell.
Yeah, the two U's are definitely colluding with each other
in both of these simultaneous
battles we got going on here.
They have mass info
that they will use.
What a fucking disaster this is.
That's what you get when you have
someone like Ben St.
aka Max Survive
Ben St. here.
Okay.
You're gonna be sorry
when I beat you up.
In real life.
That's right.
In real life, I'm going to do it.
Damn it!
Not even fucking good.
Not even good.
I think you may not be
as good
as you once believed.
You don't know that shit.
God, did we have anything else?
Was there any other talking points?
You were really gung-ho
about Sun and Moon.
You were like...
I want to hear about General
Pokemon Info.
You know what?
I'm not super hyped about the Pokemon
designs that have been leaked.
Really?
They're not terrible.
But, wait, wait.
There was one that I really liked.
God,
the bug that's called
Wimp-Out.
Yeah, Wimp-Out.
Yeah, that guy's really good.
Let's see.
I guess the Ghost Sandcastle
is kind of okay?
He's alright.
There's already an Earth Ghost,
so whatever.
Let's see.
What else stood out to me?
Well,
Incineroar is the worst Pokemon ever.
There's never been...
and there never will be anything as terrible.
I don't think I...
Okay, yeah, that was fine.
I feel that way about Alolan Persian.
I hate...
Alolan Persian might be as bad
as fucking the other thing.
It's so terrible.
It's amazing how terrible it is.
I honestly can't believe...
It was green lit.
You know what?
I actually think...
I think if I hadn't seen original Persian,
I wouldn't mind it.
Fucking no.
It looks goofy, but a lot of Pokemon look goofy.
It's just the fact that it looks so...
It's...
They just took regular Persian
and made it look stupid.
And I don't get it.
I don't get what they were going for.
I feel like they were trying to make it cuter,
but they just failed.
There's an in-depth Pokedex
on Pokemon.com
that states that it is a beautiful Pokemon in Alola.
And that is
worship towards beauty.
There's no fucking way that's true.
That's more true
than anyone could ever even imagine.
Oh, you have Wonder Guard?
Is that why you didn't take damage from that burn?
That's exactly why.
Wait...
I know it's not going to help me,
but...
Oh my god, are you stupid?
Well, you know...
Come on.
There we go.
I called because I figured you were going to switch.
No.
I would never do something like that.
I would never switch.
That's my policy, is never switch.
Yeah.
And it's got me this far.
And it's pretty cool.
No.
Don't do that.
No, there's nothing I can do.
Don't worry.
I know.
That's not pathetic.
What were you thinking?
What do you mean I healed myself?
Oh god, oh god.
What were you thinking?
God, dude, oh shit, bro.
Wow, Vincent's not even good at this game.
Wow.
I might not be good at this game,
but at least I'm the coolest guy in the world.
You know what I'm saying, dude?
Yeah, woo!
Alright.
How much fucking poison damage is Jellison going to take?
Holy shit.
Well, that's impressive.
Oh, I think I might lose this one, yeah.
Why'd you do that, dude?
Because that's the only thing I can do.
Nothing else could possibly have done anything.
Dude, you were faster than me.
But I only have things that are weak against you.
You don't have a fire move on Infernape?
No.
Weird.
That's wacky.
That's unfortunate.
It's unfortunate.
Truly unfortunate.
She said it doesn't even matter.
It's not even unfortunate.
I know. Nothing matters.
Nothing matters, dude.
Not even cool.
There's nothing.
I know, dude.
That one's a lost cause.
Oh, come on.
Let's see this shit.
That one's done.
A million times Bensane.
You're so gay.
It's over.
It's over with how gay you are right now.
It's so over.
Oh, you think so, do you?
Is that a fact, bro?
Ah, fuck.
I don't care about him.
It doesn't matter.
Dude, I've got this momentum.
Is that the momentum going?
I'm like using roll out.
But in a meta sort of way.
Oh, wait, fuck.
I forgot I'm paralyzed.
It doesn't matter though.
I know you've got...
Oh, come on.
Oh, I'm so gay.
That actually doesn't matter.
Yeah, actually, it's not enough.
Uh, hmm.
Shit.
Um...
Yeah, a little Impersion is the worst.
Yeah.
What do you think about Incineroar?
I'm not too upset these days.
I didn't want to pick Liden anyway.
What I'm...
I mean, aside from whether you're going to use it,
do you think it's good because I think it's horrible.
I think it's the worst Pokemon ever designed.
No, no.
I think it's fine.
It's not fine, dude.
It's not right.
It's not natural.
It goes against the ways of real life.
It does.
It goes against everything we were taught in school.
Boys kiss girls and girls kiss boys.
Not any of this.
Not whatever the other...
Not whatever the reverse of that is.
Yeah, exactly.
Why did I do that?
That was stupid.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, come on.
It doesn't matter. You're a special attacker, but it's still that damage.
Yeah, that damage...
That damage is going to get me. I really fucked up.
I really fucked up.
Oh, no, it's okay.
Yeah.
I think you could have got me if you'd scalded.
Yeah, but I thought you were going to switch.
Yeah.
Everything's fucking paralyzed.
Why are you constantly going in and out of...
like your CWC impression?
That wasn't a CWC.
It sounds like it.
Munchie, are you familiar with baby cakes?
Yes, of course.
Okay.
I think I've sent you a video of theirs before.
I forget what it was.
Wait a minute.
Who do you mean there? Are we thinking of the same baby cakes?
Are we thinking of...
I'm baby cakes.
You are baby cakes.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm aware, but I say they as in...
I don't know. I'm gender neutral.
Yeah, you're the gender neutral pronoun.
Good. That's what I like to hear.
Fuck.
So...
I can't remember what the specific video was about.
Fuck me, dude.
But I remember that I quite enjoyed it
and I sent you and you were like,
oh, LOL, you like them too?
And I was like, okay.
Me and Digi have been...
We watched all of it recently
and we've just been quoting it all the time.
And...
I mean,
DeVoo has started to say that
all my voices
sound like the baby cakes.
All my fake voices sound like...
There's a meme or something where
all Jesse's voices sound the same.
A meme as in not just fact.
Right.
Right. But with my case
it actually is a meme because it's not true
that all my fake voices sound like baby cakes.
They don't. They're all unique and special.
Unique and special.
Yes.
God fucking Christ.
Christ.
Ah, God.
So bad.
Doesn't matter.
Nothing matters.
This is...
I don't know what to do about this slow, bro.
I really don't.
You're just bad, dude. That's all there is to it.
I think I might just be bad.
You're so bad!
You need to do that.
Why don't you just fucking...
Oh no. Yes!
Yeah!
Just crit and then...
Oh, weak.
Kiram, just fucking get a crit, dude.
Just fucking get a crit right now
where I'll kill you.
Come on, dude. You've got one in 16 chance
and you can't do it.
Oh, no.
I'm out of PP.
Yeah, I'm bad.
It's an 8-PP move!
That's what I was waiting for. This is my opportunity.
That sucks so much.
What do I even do now?
Um...
Oh, now you've got a fucking crit!
You bastard!
Oh, shit.
Ah, you fucked up, dude.
You fucked up, man.
I fucked up by not factoring in the
random number generation.
You did.
Ah!
No!
So bad.
Damn it.
Yes! Oh, no! Oh, well, okay.
All right, all right.
Um...
Yeah.
Yeah, I got it.
I got it.
Damn it.
He does have this.
Yes.
Damn it, it's over!
Yeah, that's it.
I can't believe this.
Okay, this is good.
This is going good so far.
I hate you.
I've really managed to turn it all around
on myself.
And prove that I am the greatest
all the time.
It's not even fucking...
It's not even real.
Okay, okay.
God, I don't know.
You want to do one more?
Yeah, yeah, we'll do one more.
Okay.
God, that news post
that says, oh, Election Days,
you're like so aggravating.
It's a Pokemon battling simulator.
We don't care.
Or whether you think Trump will make America great again.
Come and have a fucking chat
in our stupid chat room.
Fuck.
I don't, if that's the attitude
you're going to bring to it, sir.
Sir, good sir.
I'm sorry, but you're done this time.
No.
I can see.
I can see my future and it looks bright.
It's bright.
I can see your future.
It's reflected in your eyes' mind.
Who's faster?
Probably...
Oh, dear.
Okay.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
Oh, no. Oh, boy.
Fuck.
Uh...
Um...
You know...
What? Yeah, what do I mean?
You know what I mean, dude?
I can't...
Yeah, you know what I'm fucking talking about.
I can't penetrate that thick skull of yours
and get the juicy information
on what you were putting down.
Uh...
Um...
I can't even imagine
what disgusting, filthy place
is you are operating in.
Munchie, can you see what item
my Nitto Queen has?
Uh, no.
Not yet.
Huh. Okay.
Weird.
Uh...
I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
Oh, boo.
Boo!
Cheating.
Collusion.
I don't... I don't care if it goes...
Oh, boo!
Oh, you idiot.
Oh, you fucked it up, bro.
That...
That feel when toxic misses.
Oh, there's nothing.
There's nothing that could have
feel me with more and more
fucking rage than what just
right now.
Agreed. Agreed.
Hmm...
Well, this guy's...
I'm not gonna knock off on this guy
because he's definitely got
what you call it...
He's definitely a mega, mega
Evolver.
No, you don't know that.
I'm sure about it, dude. No.
I'm so sure.
Uh...
Oh, man. This guy doesn't have...
This guy's weak to flying ghost
and fairy.
That's not very much.
Yeah. You know why it's not very much?
Because he's trained in the Tiberian
mountains, and he's made sure
that everyone is lower than him.
Wow.
Because he's researched various virtues
that allows him to evolve past.
Which virtues is it that lets
a Gallade mega-evolve?
Uh, probably
Justice and Chastity.
Justice and Chastity?
Yeah, he looks pretty chased over there.
He looks like an anime protagonist.
He does.
Uh...
I should let me check with my list of virtues
that I have.
Can you read some of them off for us?
Yes, yes. Of course, of course.
Thank God. Okay.
Ah, man.
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
Alright.
That's probably a terrible idea.
These are the virtues.
Chastity, temperance,
charity, diligence, patience,
kindness, and humility.
So, I forgot.
I merged Courage and Justice
into one.
Hmm.
So...
Okay. Say you had two Alligators.
Fuck, man!
Did you see that shit? Yeah, I saw it.
Sleep powder fails yet again?
I saw it.
Don't worry.
There's nothing I don't see.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You're so bad.
I honestly can't believe
how bad you are.
That's wrong.
And it's a sin, frankly.
Honestly, it's disgusting.
I think it's the devil's work.
Here's what I want to know.
Say you have two...
Oh, God.
What's a good... What was the word you used
for reptiles and...
Herptophonus.
Okay, say you've got two Herptophonus.
Say you've got a...
Oh, God.
Two annals, right?
You've got two beautiful annals.
And they're just like...
And one of them learns
temperance.
And the other learns...
Wait. Patience.
Yeah, patience, sure.
One of them learns temperance.
I mean, those are very similar virtues, but whatever.
One of them learns temperance and one of them learns patience.
Like, do they become
different things? Yes.
Okay, okay.
But if two different annals each learned,
what kind of courage would they become
the same thing, basically? No, no, no.
It depends on both your virtue
and your species.
I know, but I'm saying, like, if two things
of the same species learned the same virtue,
would they become a similar thing?
Well, it's also...
It's like your God tier, so they can't be
two of the same.
They'll be similar, but not completely
different things. Okay, yes.
So there's individual variation there, okay.
Yes.
Yeah, gotcha.
What, is Technoblast
normal type?
Yeah.
No, no, no, it's bug, it's bug.
Wait, really? Are you
futzing with me? I'm not futzing with you.
Are you trickering me?
Are you trying
to trick me yet again, Goofy?
Or Donald?
Is that
a line? Yes.
That is, in fact, a line. Shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
See, now I've got you on the ropes, I think.
Oh, come on! Oh, yeah!
Yeah! I didn't even realize
I had that! How the fuck
is that a thing you can learn? I don't know.
It must be a hidden ability or something.
That's so fucked up, how? It's a fish.
Wait, but he's got a horn, he's got a
lightning rod. That means nothing.
And you know when you attract lightning,
then it's good for you.
I can't
fucking believe that just happened.
That's the worst thing that any...
That's the
real tragedy that happened today.
Well, there's definitely been
some tragedy, I don't know what.
Something
we won't speak of.
Yeah.
You're talking about
how Bernie Sanders assassinated
President Obama. For reasons
that he refuses to
divulge.
To acknowledge and or
even slightly
collaborate upon.
You know what, dude?
You're so stupid. No, you're so...
Oh, what the f...
God!
God fuck!
No!
Let me explain everything that I fucked up.
Ladies and gentlemen,
BeenSaintOfFiction.com has died today.
I fucked up so deeply
this battle.
Like, I was so sure
that Gallade was the mega-evolver, right?
And I...
I looked at... Yeah, I looked...
Cause I was like, oh...
Oh man, I thought because
Absol had been out before and didn't mega-evolve,
then it must not be it.
And then I compared speeds
and I'm like, oh,
Seeking's one speed faster than Absol.
That means I can mega-horn it before
it's 1.5 times attack
from justified has a chance to fuck me up.
Yeah, okay.
Absolutely wrong.
Doesn't matter.
We're just gonna
carry on.
We're gonna continue.
We're gonna push...
We're gonna push for
broad social change.
Yeah!
Come on, man.
He's so bad, ladies and gentlemen.
He can't do anything right.
I was...
There's just nothing he can do that will
make anyone like him. There's just nothing.
I mean...
I thought you were gonna sucker punch
so I bulked up.
It didn't work.
You know what?
I'm not that far behind.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Oh, how foolish.
I'm gonna do this.
It's so aesthetic.
Okay.
Oh, how foolish.
Okay, that wasn't great.
Oh, how terrible.
What?
Oh, come on!
Oh, no!
No!
God, if I...
I didn't...
I would've killed you with a body slam
but I thought you were gonna...
I thought you were gonna sucker punch
I can't...
I can't overstate
how filthy
he is in every way.
That was the worst thing I've ever done.
Okay, no, whatever, though.
I'm hard depressed to think of a time
that Ben has ever showered before in his life.
Has ever what?
Showered before.
That's true. That's true.
No, man.
Let me tell you about hygiene.
I engage in it.
More than you could ever know.
More than you could...
more than you could imagine.
Carnivine's going...
Okay, honestly, I don't think I've ever had
a carnivine on my team and not been disappointed
in its performance.
Yeah, carnivine sucks.
Carnivine, in my experience, carnivine has sucked
really hard.
But not this time.
Oh, shit.
This time, things are gonna be different.
Uh, yes.
Good.
Yeah.
Yeah, bro.
What the fuck?
You're so bad.
Wait.
Oh, no.
Was that quadruped?
Was that doubly ineffective?
No, it was just singly ineffective.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, well, that's terrible.
Terrible.
That's just awful.
If I don't wake up, you might have a chance.
No, okay.
Yeah.
I have made
every possible mistake.
Oh, my God.
It's a good guy.
Yeah, yeah.
It's over now, stupid.
That's over now.
Oh, no.
Oh, let's see.
I got it now.
You aren't really demonstrating
the virtue of kindness there, Ben.
You might...
I'll make a specific exception for stupid people
to de-grass on the evolutionary chart.
Just for you.
Thank you.
Thanks, sir.
Oh, good.
Oh, good, I did it.
What am I going to de-grass into?
A zekrom?
A tadpole.
Uh, well, you know...
I don't think you've...
I don't think you even...
I don't think you've got anything.
Oh, wait, you got Shadow Sneak.
Oh, shit.
I have more options
that you could ever even imagine.
Oh, this is...
Yeah, okay.
Oh, dear.
Okay.
That's fine.
That's good, in fact.
Boo!
That's good, in fact, is it?
And that's good, in fact.
That's actually good.
That's actually what I wanted.
I wanted you to win.
This has all been a trap.
It's all been one trap.
You've taken me home.
You've...
You've wooed me at the bar.
You've successfully seduced me.
You've taken me back to...
Now, sex home.
And now you've realized
the unfortunate truth.
The truly, the truly
savage truth.
That you are, in fact, stupid and terrible.
Munchy?
Munchy, I invited you here to play Pokemon Stay
for a very specific reason.
I want you to look around and realize
that your house is now on fire.
Oh, no!
I knew it.
Okay, I didn't get so blind.
I knew it would work.
I knew there was no way to stop.
I can't believe this!
You want to do one more?
Yeah, well, yeah, sure, sure.
If you want to be completely humiliated again, sure.
I feel like I didn't put my best foot forward that time.
I feel like you have no feet.
And you were a wheelchair-bound,
disgusting Chinese man.
Sure, sure.
But, um...
I mean, what of it?
Oh, you're foolish.
Oh, but actually not that foolish.
Aw, damn.
Okay.
Uh, hmm.
Options.
Options, options, options.
Uh, no.
Oh, he's going to call in his
dirty corporate friends
to collude and destroy
the server so I can't
participate in a fair state.
Yeah, dude, we're going to collude, man.
We're really going to collude really hard.
He's going to call up his
gang, affectionately called the Max Survives.
And, uh...
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, that's about it.
That's about the size of it, I think.
I'm waiting for
Vincent.
Vincent. Hey!
Hey!
Did you ever see
that one drawing I made on stream
of you where you were beating a woman
and you had an MRA card and Vincent was
puppeteering you?
I had what?
An MRA card? Yeah.
No, I don't think...
Yeah! Aw, critical hit!
Just when I needed it.
What the hell are you talking about?
No, I did not see that
drawing. Are you in a game right now?
No.
What? Am I not fighting you?
I'm fighting some Brando.
Yes, you are!
Oh, God.
What a buffoon.
What an absolute buffoon.
I can't believe it.
I just had the most incredible critical hit.
My
whiskash.
My whiskash just pulled off an incredible underdog
victory against a Rotom F
or the wind one.
Oh, the wind one sucks.
Yeah, well...
So what?
So what? What does that mean
in the grand scheme of things?
But I was very proud of that image
for the fact that there was political commentary
on sometimes the
lie between Ben and Vincent is so blared
that it's not even...
you can't even feasibly
recognize who's who.
That's true, man.
That's true.
That's truer than you even know.
Do I know
if I send you another invite
or no? Hang on.
I want to beat Internet
9.9.
I think I can do it.
Fucking Internet
9.99. We're ruining the
ratty fucking stuff.
Say
you're on YouTube. Say hello
in chat.
Oh, God. Okay, I will.
You're on YouTube.
Say hello.
Oh, God.
I feel dirty. I feel dirty
for what I've just done here today.
Well, we'll do as you know that.
He's gonna be Internet famous.
I want fan art of Internet of whatever his name is.
Oh, but I just fucking wrecked
his vanillax because he's a little bitch.
Oh, shit.
Oh, I feel so awful
for what I've said to him.
That seems...
That just seems like a bad wrong thing
to do. That doesn't seem like
the right way to behave in modern society.
It seems
so cruel.
It's so gauche.
How can you be so
without fucking compassion
for your fellow human beings
as to say that someone is on YouTube
and also to prompt them to say hello?
It's difficult. It's difficult to be as bad
as I am. It requires
an active...
It requires actively pushing down
my instincts towards
human decency and all the virtues
that I hold so dear.
Yes.
Kindness, generosity,
laughter, honesty.
What are some other ones maybe?
Generosity, loyalty.
Loyalty. That's the one.
And magic.
And magic, of course.
Like, naturally.
Show us how to see when AST is in
8 right now, right?
7? I want to say 7.
Whatever. Did you watch the last season?
Oh, god! He just...
Internet999 just responded in fucking Russian.
No!
What a hero!
He says...
Backwards are...
...
You gotta Google translate right fucking now
and find out what he said.
You know what? That's the best idea I've ever heard.
laughter
Oh, he killed my jinx with his patcherisu.
Ben Strate has traveled across the world
through many, many, many
flights and travels and he has
mastered all of the
the virtues.
The languages? Oh, yeah.
That as well. But he has mastered all the virtues
and it's worth listening to it to a higher plane.
It's worth listening to it to a higher plane.
We un-evolved
cannot even comprehend.
No. And I mean, why would you even want to?
Even if you could comprehend it,
it's not like you could do anything with it, you fucking asshole.
laughter
Hey, guess what he said?
What?
I am Russian. Hi.
laughter
Oh.
Oh, he said something else, but I gotta
fucking...
I gotta do something about this.
I've got to do something about this.
I have to do something.
I'm gonna kill his cell with my bannet.
Better.
Easiest win.
Actually, I'm gonna taunt because that seems like the right thing to do.
Okay. I am Russian.
Okay. And then he follows up with...
Send a link.
laughter
As in a...
As in a link to the YouTube.
Yeah.
Do it.
But it doesn't exist yet.
No, you have to.
I'll just, I'll just, I'll link him to the procrastinators.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's gonna be so fucking weird.
Dude, that's gonna be so fucking weird.
Dude, if you're, if you're, what's his name?
Internetfan?
His name is...
Internet99.1.
If you are watching this right now,
I want you to comment, press...
No, no, I want you to comment.
Just press one in your keyboard a lot of times.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Internet99.1.
If you're watching this, please, please let us know.
Yeah.
I need to feel, I need to feel that I'm, that I matter.
This is the only way to do that.
This is it. This is it.
It's the, it's the only possible way.
I'm, I'm just gonna link him to the fucking
channel and, uh,
you know,
whatever.
I wonder if he even, like, speaks English,
because, because he just, I mean...
Well, he probably, I think he Google trans,
I think he probably Google translated my message
because it took him a while to respond.
Yeah.
He's gonna learn English.
Just to watch the podcast.
Oh, jeez Louise.
He watch, he watches the podcast and it changes
his fucking life.
Ah, shit.
I let him kill my bannet because I'm stupid.
Just by happenstance,
what do you think would be the worst podcast
to, to enter on?
He, he, he opens up the memes
that needs to die podcast
and his life is forever changed.
I don't, I don't know.
I mean, my least favorite one
is everyone else's favorite one,
which is, um, uh, things we can't get into.
That's the yellow one, right?
I think so.
Yeah, I hate that one.
Yeah, that one sucks.
It's the, it's so bad.
It makes me so angry just thinking about it.
This guy is so fucked.
I've got,
I've got a goddamn
mega Kangaskhan.
It's all over the world.
That, that, that shit's broken.
Oh shit, but I used sucker punch.
And then he used toxic.
Ben, Ben, even when he has
an unbelievable advantage,
he just can't seem to close out.
I fucked it up.
And I, uh,
God, I'm so bad.
I've really screwed the pooch.
I couldn't beat his patcherisi with my mega Kangaskhan.
Oh my fucking god.
Oh, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
My second sucker punch worked.
Um, yes.
All right, let's see. He's on his last,
he's on his last poke and I've got three.
He's a druddigon. Uh, yeah, whatever.
Stupid.
What do I want to do? What do I want to do?
Uh, probably return, double return.
Oh, but he's sucker punched me.
Oh, you suck that.
How ironic.
So ironic.
It's, it's, it's more ironic
than I could ever even imagine.
True. True.
Uh...
Oh God.
I, I, I, I, I, I, all I've been doing
has, I've just been in the,
in these late hours of the night,
uh, I've, I've been checking
the, the MSP and Ventures
Snapchat to see
what, what beautiful post,
post-canon content Andrew Hussie
has sprinkled out for us.
Uh, that hasn't been any today, but I, but I check
back every night because there's been one for Halloween.
So there's, it's not just for important dates now.
It's just, it's just going to be
a slice of life
comic, Homestuck version 2.0
based entirely in Snapchat
and I'm ready for it.
Um, wait, has he actually been
posting anything? Yes.
There? Yes. Oh, shit. I mean, I don't use
Snapchat, so I wouldn't know. Well, neither do I
other than for this. Yeah, yeah.
But the, um, I mean, I have
Snapchat, so maybe I should fucking look.
Uh, okay, dude.
I'm in a fucking pickle right now.
He's on his last Pokémon,
but he just killed my second lesson.
Now it's his druddigon, who's in the middle.
He just used an outrage. He used an outrage
to kill my Latios.
So now he's got his outrage and druddigon, but all
I've got is my fucking credilly.
What the fuck is it?
Oh, oh, that's an amazing installer.
He's, he's not,
he's not.
I mean, I've got Gigadrain.
Alright, I guess I'm just going to recover
and hope that I don't die this turn.
And then once he's... What are your moves?
Rockslide, Stealth Rock, Gigadrain,
Recover. Oh, that shit.
Yeah, it's not good.
I mean, I could try to Rockslide him.
Um...
Eh.
I'm, I'm going to recover.
No, I'm going to, I'm going to Rockslide.
Oh fuck, oh god.
Oh, yeah, it does 51.
Oh, but he's confused.
Okay, he lost 30.
Okay, if he, if he hurts himself and
if he hurts himself and confusion this turn,
I win. If he doesn't, I lose. It's simple as that.
Let's see, place your bets, folks.
Press one for Munchie, 1-1-1-1-1.
Come on, Dreadigon, you piece of shit.
You're the worst Pokemon, you look like a Digimon
and nobody likes you.
I like him, he's just...
I don't mind him too, but everyone, like everyone
that I've, I don't know, like,
Digi and one other person have lately
have told me that they hate Dreadigon and I'm like,
he's not that bad.
The fact that you take Digi's opinion
seriously on any matter
just proves your...
I know, but like, I've been surprised.
I've just been hearing a lot of... Oh, he's...
What the fuck, he sucker punched me. What a fucking idiot.
He, he sucker punched me.
I thought he was gonna outrage again.
I don't know why he didn't. It was his only hope.
Okay, well, now I think I win.
Oh no, he did, no, he outraged again
and it killed me.
So bad.
I'm gonna say to him, well,
well played.
He said Gigi, I say Gigi.
Everyone's, everyone's good.
All right, fuck you internet, 999.
I gotta get back to my real, my real best friend, Munchy.
You were in fact a fake best friend.
Yeah, you're just a fucking B-barrel.
Good job, idiot.
I'm really sorry.
I'm really, I'm really sorry to disrespect you like this.
By bringing a, you never,
never bring a B-barrel to a Yan mega fight,
know what I'm saying?
Whatever I hear the words been saying,
I automatically think of a B-barrel in my head, so.
Yeah, it's, it's disgusting.
It's, it's pathetic.
I don't know what to do here.
All right, let's have, no,
that was wrong.
I did the wrong thing.
Okay.
Wait, what the fuck?
What, I cursed.
But times two, does it always do that?
I don't think it's, it's cause I'm simple.
I have, I have simple, that's why.
Right, that's what, that's what simple does.
It doubles the status.
Yeah, okay.
But it doesn't matter.
Literally doesn't matter.
Or doesn't it?
No, it doesn't, okay.
Well, good.
That was great.
You went on a blaze of glory.
Just like a certain, just like a certain other normal type.
A certain other, yeah,
certain other, just pitiful,
disgusting, worthless, normal type.
I could mention, but I won't.
Because he's not worth the price.
He's not worth it.
Oh god.
What, what a fucking,
what a joke.
What a fucking, yeah.
What a fucking gem of a joke, you know.
Unlike the MPV of the series,
Munchy the Volpix.
Munchy the Volpix is a true hero
to all of us.
Nobody will, nobody can deny that.
Yeah, no one.
Not one of us.
Okay, okay.
Why the fuck?
Nice Uber.
Yeah, you're welcome.
Why the fuck does, um,
uh, you know, the red one
get a new type when it goes Uber
and Kyo-Gre doesn't?
Um, cause people like Red on Barry
cause he's better.
Um,
so,
it's just weird. Why doesn't he become
water-flying, or
something?
Uh, I think you'll have to
ask God for that.
I don't want to talk to him.
We're not cool right now.
We got into a fight.
Oh shit.
Not a nice crit, dude.
Thanks. It was great.
Actually, I really enjoyed it.
Looking forward to the next one.
Yo, check this out. You're fucked.
Oh, what the fuck are you thinking?
Yeah, not even cool.
Yeah, it's pretty cool though.
Frankly.
What are you gonna do?
You're probably gonna do stone.
No, I would never do such a thing.
I would never do such a thing.
I would never soup to your level, Ben.
My-
My gut tells me
that a stone edge
or a rock slide is coming.
This is imminent.
Well, if there's
one thing I have to say to you,
it's get fucked.
Wait, no, I'm not even weak to rock.
What the fuck are you gonna do then?
Uh...
I'm gonna do something,
and then I'm gonna switch out to something else.
God damn it.
Yeah, bro.
No.
Yes.
Um...
His horsey mouth
is too much.
You know what? I'll just let you do it.
I don't fucking care.
What a crazy man to do such a thing.
Yeah.
I don't know what he's in for at this point in his life.
I don't think he knows.
I don't think he realizes the magnitude.
Oh,
stupid.
Fucking worthless.
I don't think he understands
what a pickle, Ben, say, truly is in.
I don't yet.
I don't yet understand the magnitude.
Oh, no.
Yes. Oh, dear.
Oh, no, it's okay. It's okay. It's good.
In fact, it's good. In fact, I'm glad.
In fact,
it is truly great.
Oh,
interesting choice, faggot.
Oh, no!
What the fuck? Oh, cool. I didn't think it
would be that good.
What the fuck are you thinking?
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking
Ben St.
Maybe he's a cool guy who doesn't
cheat after all.
Well, I would be so wrong.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm about to
witness
the most cheating of it all.
Yeah, I think you're about
I think you're about to.
Oh, I was playing it street because I thought
you, god damn it.
What did you think I was going to do?
I thought you were going to try and be
sneaky and
switch out. I was.
I did have a sneaky plan, but I was like
that's stupid. God damn it.
Okay, okay.
Oh, yeah. Oh, wow.
Oh, yeah, I'll do it now.
I picked the best team.
I picked the best team. You just pick the strongest
Pokemon and then you win. You just pick all the mega
evolutions and then you win, dude.
It's not even fucking. It doesn't even matter.
I've got 10 mega evolutions on my team.
I got mega kill great.
I got mega grout on.
Whatever.
What fucking ever, bro.
I got mega, wait, mega Wormadan.
He's the best. He's my favorite.
Whatever, bro. It's not even fucking impressive.
Yeah, it's pretty cool though.
No, god damn it.
Yeah, bro.
I use ice beam, bro.
Ah, shit.
It's so gay.
Okay, you want to do one more?
Yeah, one more, one more.
This will never stop.
No.
Pokemon is the greatest game of all time.
Oh shit, I did a random.
I'm not fighting another rando.
Oh wait, why are you sure?
I did both. Okay.
No, I'm in here. You got your Yan mega.
Why do you have another Yan mega?
I don't know.
That's gay.
In a way.
Nobody can beat pherothorn.
Nobody.
Not a single.
I'm serious, pherothorn is completely overpowered.
He's not even fair.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
Oh wow, okay.
Well, I'm surprised by that.
Oh dear.
Ah shit.
Oh no.
Okay, okay.
Oh.
Well.
You're gay, by the way.
Before this utter destruction
just absolutely ravages you.
I wanted to let you know that I know
more than you could ever know.
No, that can't be true.
It's impossible.
What are you going to do?
I think you bullshit it.
Are you going to try and pull on me?
I'm mass producing weapons in the east
and I'm going to retake the country.
Oh fuck that dude.
So bad.
I don't even know why you even bother.
God fucking damn it.
Alright.
Okay, what do I got here?
What do, oh I see.
Yes, I see. I have the ultimate strategy.
The ultimate strategy is just use Volcanion
because he's the best Pokemon.
Yeah, it's totally not fair that my team
has pherothorn and Volcanion.
Yeah, well we're in doubt
fucking kill each other.
They're the best Pokemon.
Oh, bullshit.
Guess who it is.
It's the game.
Back in the fucking dead.
And I know what he's going to do too.
I know exactly what he's going to do.
God damn you knew!
I knew! I knew!
I remember it.
Oh, he might still...
This might still fuck me though.
I can't believe it.
He used his memory against me.
That's just what you do with an alomololo.
He used his memory
to create.
The ghost of fucking the game
came and whispered in my ear.
I don't have that great of options here.
I can't believe it.
Yeah, iron barbs.
You knocked my rocky helmet off.
Oh man.
Well...
That was good.
Good while it lasted.
Does it matter?
Shit.
Damn it.
I'm gonna get ya.
Yeah, I got ya.
Does it matter?
Doesn't even matter.
Okay.
Please God, please, please.
Well, you're gonna sleep powder.
No, I'm not.
I would never do that.
Wait.
But now that you know that I know you're gonna sleep powder,
now you're gonna not sleep powder.
I would never do that.
In the first place, I never was going to.
Yes, you fucking were.
Well, I mean, I haven't really
gained anything, but I guess...
Um...
Shit.
You really foiled me, babe.
Yeah, I got ya.
Um...
Oh God.
Yeah, okay.
Enjoy that one HP you just absorbed from me.
Thanks.
I will.
Fag it.
Come on!
No!
That's not true.
Little did Ben know that
once you looked through his diary beforehand.
No!
Digi gave me the key for a return
for some Mike's Heart Eliminator.
That son of a bitch.
Okay, dude.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, bro.
Now you're fucked, dude.
Shit.
What to do?
I got it.
Okay.
What is Munchy
gonna do against these
pro strats?
Okay.
Okay, that's something.
Uh...
Hmm. What does Excelsior
even do?
He does this.
He probably just looks gay.
He looks awesome. You're fucking gay.
You were, in fact,
the one who fully revealed the decision
on top of gay men.
No, he does look awesome.
He's edgy.
He's really edgy.
I wish I had a team of Excelsior,
Absol,
Bisharp,
Skarmory.
Who else is edgy?
Oh, Zangus, yeah.
The edgiest Pokemon.
The edgiest team.
The best Pokemon, in fact.
Yes.
Oh, you think you're good,
but in fact, you're bad.
I'm so good.
This man will be
my father.
He'll be my father.
I shall save him
for a later date.
Oh.
Gotcha.
I tricked you.
Did you trick me, or is I the one who tricked you?
I don't know.
That trick that you placed upon me
was, in fact, a trick of great proportions.
A trick so good, in fact,
that I tricked even yourself.
Oh.
That was bad.
Well, that was well tall.
Dude, you're going to die, dude.
You're going to die.
I got damage on you.
You got a little damage, I guess.
I'd do half your health, dude.
Yeah, sure.
Sure.
But you know what they say,
half your health is only worth
a quarter of a Pokemon.
That's not what they say.
That's true.
That's not what they say at all.
That's all true.
That could not be farther, in fact,
from what they say.
I hear that all the time.
I hear your lies all the time.
What? No, boo.
Gay.
Okay, I didn't expect that.
I don't know why I didn't expect that.
That was the obvious thing you were going to do
against you, Vel'Thal.
Shit, that's really stupid.
So stupid.
That's really stupid.
What the fuck do you think
I'm not going to do it still?
I don't know.
At least I didn't lose anyone
yet.
Damn it.
Yeah.
Yeah, bro.
Yeah, bro. Yeah, you know it, dog.
Oh, that's
that stealth rock, though.
It doesn't matter.
Yeah, it matters.
It matters to me.
It doesn't matter a single.
Oh, dear.
What's even the point of that?
That's what it is.
Oh, shit.
I don't think you can kill me, though.
I don't think you can kill me.
Yeah.
Damn it, if it wasn't for that crit,
I might have lived.
Which, what, did I just crit on you?
Yeah.
I think I was going to kill you.
Well, I don't know, maybe.
It went down somewhat slowly.
Oh, he's so fucking fast.
I'm so good.
He's so fast.
He's literally the fastest.
Deoxys is literally the fastest
human being on the planet.
What?
He is?
Yeah, I know.
Shit.
He's way too fast.
No, I'm not fast at all.
Actually, so is...
so is Excelsior.
Uh...
Jeez.
Okay.
Well, when I went down,
I guess I wanted to refresh my beautiful voice.
Yeah.
While I talk, I noticed that
there was a
rally's fast food bag
specifically marked for me, and it said
for a munchie, God bless.
And so I hurriedly
grabbed it and ran it up into my room
to stuff my face with spicy chicken wings.
Yeah.
Did I tell you that I fried chicken before
and I fucked it up?
Yes, you did.
You were so happy
to be able to say it, I'm dead.
I'm fucked, by the way.
Yeah, that was it.
Whatever.
You were so happy, dude, to say it again
you were in the middle of explaining the fried chicken story.
And then you hushed yourself and said
no, I need to say this on camera.
Oh, yeah.
No, that wasn't the story.
No, there were other...
No, no, it's not true.
It's not true. My fried chicken story is gay.
Oh shit, I forgot to hit rematch.
Oh shit.
How long have we been going?
Two hours?
A little more than two hours.
God, but I just can't stop playing Pokemon.
No, no, it's impossible.
It's literally the greatest game of all time.
Oh look, I have Steve Vani on my team.
Haha, that's a Twitter joke.
Steve Vani.
Yeah, basically.
I mean, I get it.
It's because Lucario's gay, right? Like Steve Vani.
Yeah, exactly.
That's fine.
That's all good.
I like everything.
And it's cool.
Um, fuck.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Meltank is such a good Pokemon.
Meltank is good.
I'm so proud of it.
Meltank is a great poke, man.
Oh man, this is just like my battle against
Internet99.1.
Started with the Whiskash.
Started with the Whiskash, now we hear.
I don't get paid to blow up like the World Trade.
Started with the Whiskash, now we
fighting
Steve Vani
on the Internet.
I mean, the heated
Internet debate with Steve Vani.
Oh, Steven Universe descent.
Descent.
Nerd, oh you fool.
Oh, that was the naive thing to do.
Hey, yes.
Here, I'm about to show you how stupid you are.
No!
You were
Fuck you, man.
Not a scratch. Look, 100%
not even a scratch.
Yeah, I see that. Yeah, it's good.
I'm so mad that
Mega Evolution are still in
Southern Moon.
It's so bad.
Um, I don't care.
I'm fine with it. I think Z-moves seem really
stupid, but I don't know.
Maybe they'll be fine.
Maybe they'll just be like
I don't know, just the way that
just the fact that they have these big long
ass animations makes me hate them.
I mean, if they were just
a move like any other
I don't know. I mean, I guess
they could be balanced.
They're just the same as in
Gen 5, like the type of
gems.
The type gems?
Yeah, oh my fucking god.
Dude.
It's type advantage.
Let me, well, Munchy, you see
when a Pokemon uses an ability
that has an advantage over one
or more of the enemy's types.
I forgot what Lucario is saying.
Shit, fuck. Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Shit, shit, shit.
Um...
Hmm...
What is Furret gonna do? Something idiotic,
I'm sure. Something idiotic.
Something just so fucking foolish.
Something that's too
embarrassed himself.
Hahaha.
Okay, okay.
Oh, you mother fucker, you'll pay.
Yeah, I know.
You will pay in time.
I know, dude.
Oh, my focus sash.
Come on.
Bitch.
What the fuck are you thinking?
What are you thinking, bro?
You can't beat Miletank.
Miletank's just gonna drink that milk.
Like, I mean, that rain.
Like, it drinks its own milk every day.
All day, every day.
Mother fucker.
You're done. You're done.
No, don't be stupid, man.
Don't say that stupid shit
at me.
Um...
Hmm...
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna kill you right fucking now.
No, dude.
No, bro.
There's only one way.
Idiot, you're stupid.
You're so stupid.
Everything about you, I hate.
Oh, dear.
What a shame.
It's okay, man.
It's good in fact.
It's better this way.
Wait, um...
Ugh, I'm so gay.
I mean...
Hmm...
Oh!
Interesting.
Interesting texture.
Wait, why would you do that?
Unless you've got something with Arena Trap
that you're gonna switch into.
Shadow Tag or something.
You don't know that.
That's the only way this would be a reasonable strategy.
Tee-hee.
Ah, fuck.
You don't know that at all.
You don't fucking know a thing.
Ah, damn it.
Oh, god.
Pfft.
You're gonna perish, dude.
No, I'm not gonna perish at all.
I think you might perish.
I'm gonna do, in fact, the opposite of perish, in fact.
No, you're gonna get perish right now.
Oh, damn.
It would have been really good if I'd woken up.
It would have been real cool.
What the fuck, Currim?
He's a little bitch today.
So bad.
I know. No, but this is gonna do it. You're done.
No, well, no, well.
Yeah, focus glass, yeah, yeah.
No.
You know what they say, early bird gets the worm.
Yo, hey, what's the name of your...
What's the title of your comic?
Investigator.
Oh, god.
It's so obvious in retrospect.
Yeah.
Why did I even ask?
When's it coming out?
I don't fucking know.
Tell me, idiot.
You bastard.
When you pray.
When you go to church and you pray.
I don't pray.
My righteous prayers will reach you.
Dude, I really want to read it.
I mean, it sounds fucking
weird and bizarre.
I'm done.
Yeah, you're done.
I don't even have this one.
I don't know, man. It sounds really weird and like...
I don't know.
I don't know what to expect from like...
Oh, come on!
Oh, but it's
all for nothing.
But it's all for fucking
not.
Unless you've got...
Yeah, okay.
There's in fact nothing.
Oh,
the drizzle bed.
Whatever, you stupid bastard.
No.
Wait, I don't understand why you did
parish song.
Because I thought you were going to switch out
and then I didn't want you to have
the upper hand and have access
to what you wanted to switch into.
Okay, I was reading way too much into it.
Damn it.
Oh, that choice scarf.
That was a great, that was a great
kirim.
It was in fact correct.
It might have been the greatest kirim of all time.
Whatever.
What's this fucking piece of shit?
I don't know.
Some gay shit, you know.
You know. God,
you idiot.
I can't believe you would do something so stupid.
What's that about?
That was embarrassing.
I admit.
I admit it.
I am gay.
I admit that nothing I do will ever matter.
I'm just going to have to
debuff you
to oblivion.
This special defense will be through the floor
by the time I'm done with you.
Oh, God.
Not this shit again.
Doesn't matter.
No, I'm going to lose you.
I'm fucking Nate's over.
Damn, it's not even cool.
It's not even fair.
It's not even right. There's no reason to fight.
And yet this is our daily life.
Shit, I close it again.
Oh, my fucking God.
I can't...
You will...
I will see you in hell then.
I can't wait, dude.
I can't wait...
I can't wait to Pokemon battle you
in hell forever.
That will be my punishment.
Forever until you
fucking collapse from exhaustion.
You will Pokemon battle.
But it was to no avail.
It was worthless.
No, it was worthless.
Why? No!
Oh, you've crippled me.
LOL.
What do I have? Wait, wait, wait.
Hmm.
Yes.
That was a weird... That's shitty.
I made the right... I made the wrong choice.
It's so bad.
Yeah, it's poor. It was poor form on my part
and I apologize.
Seeking...
Seeking's got mega horn.
Look how fast I'm moving.
Look how fast I'm swimming in place.
Yeah, there's not even any water there, idiot.
I think we're in the desert or something.
So just, you know, calm down.
From the look of our terrain,
it looks like we're in like a back alley.
Like you're gonna shank me once we're done with this.
Well, that's true.
Unrelated to the terrain.
Seeking's got...
He's probably got mega horn.
And that makes me so mad.
I have an irrational hate
of seeking and gullting.
I think they're the worst Pokemon ever made.
They're not great.
I don't know. I don't hate them.
I mean, a lot of Pokemon
and especially
first gen are just
animals.
Like they're just animals.
And it's bizarre.
Um...
And that really...
Did you get the two?
What?
Yeah, yeah, it says you left.
Hold on. Reconnect.
That was quite odd.
My Internet
did not go out.
It was in fact
it was a Pokemon showdown
like eviction notice.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know.
Said you left, but...
Apart
from my investigator,
I'm also working on a decently
sized novel.
Are you? Is that true?
That's more true than you could ever know.
Okay.
With my...
I've talked about this before on the PCP
in my interview.
He got mad at me
for talking about it before.
Who did?
I'm working on it with
a good old friend of mine.
My co-host on almost all of my streams.
And we are working on a...
Shit. Fucking crit. Okay.
I would describe it as a
political novel
about every group,
every demographic of people that we hate.
Um...
Is it about me?
Well, you will be in it
as a side character and you will be.
You will be...
Your plot ends with you being introduced
to buying ice cream and then being shot up
in a dry by shooting by a game.
Okay. Okay, good.
Great.
In fact...
This novel...
Whatever. It doesn't matter.
It follows a...
A...
A normal weed-spoking
gamer who gets transported...
Oh, dude. Yes. Yes.
I do know this, but go on.
Who gets transported
about...
Wait. Was this...
I feel like I've read this, but it wasn't a
novel. Did I read like a...
Did I read like the first chapter or something?
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Who gets transported to the future
via Obama's request
to...
He had a...
He had sacred prowess and knew that
in the future, the Islamic state
would vow to destroy video games forever.
And thus...
That's right. That's what they do.
Plunging into a...
An era of distress like no other.
An era of distress.
Oh, no. Yes.
And therefore, it is John.
John Majors is the way
word weed-smoking gamer
who vows to destroy Islam
forever and bring peace to
the world. God, what a view.
Via video games.
Uh, how...
Well, when can... When's the release date on that?
I mean, I want... The release date on that...
Uh...
I would say
mid-2017
for that.
As it is...
It is quite the endeavor.
I did not expect there to actually be a release date.
I gotta say it.
I'm very impressed already with this book.
Just for the fact that
it presumes to
ever come out at all.
The...
That's the large plot, but
the way John hopes
to destroy
Islam forever
is by
winning Evo, which in the future
Evo is in the fine-games tournament.
It's basically... Sports are extinct in video games
or sports now. And sports is like...
They basically don't exist.
And Evo is like a Super Bowl.
But the Super Bowl isn't just about football.
It's about every sport ever.
Good.
So basically, winning...
Yeah, yeah, you like that Custab Berry?
Yeah, you like that explosion, bro?
It didn't affect me.
I know, but I just wanted to do it.
Anyway, he has to go around
the United States
in various video game
Arcadiums and beat the shit out of people.
Various video game Arcadiums?
Okay.
That sentence made sense.
And defeat all
Islamic presence in the United States
and he shipped off to Mecca.
Does he do it in video games?
Is how he defeats them?
Or does he do it out of video games, too?
No, no.
He utterly defeats them
by destroying them in video games.
So much that they want to commit suicide
and do it instantaneously.
That's the superpower?
Yeah.
No!
What a bunch of fucking bullshit.
I know what you're saying.
Yeah, you feel me on this, bro?
Yeah, you idiot.
Yeah, you dummy.
You're the fucking worst.
It doesn't matter.
No, but guess what?
Yeah, you think that's cool?
You think that's cool?
It's nothing.
It's literally nothing.
You're literally going to die right now.
Yeah, bro!
Heel bell, bro!
That's...
That's crazy.
That's cruel.
It's cruel on unusual, I know.
But I did it anyway.
This guy's probably going to mega-evolve.
But, you know...
One of the characters
in John Major, American Gamer.
That's the title.
American Gamer?
Yeah, okay.
Is a man by the name of...
Did he get even slower when he mega-evolved?
Yes.
Wow, okay.
It is a man by the name of Tweet Burglar,
who a fan of my Twitter
will know is a character
I like to attribute to Nate,
as he often steals tweets.
Oh, yeah!
Last time she did good, I'll see you in hell.
And he is the CEO of a tweeting empire,
and he steals tweets from people.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is Nate?
Well, I often attributed this to Nate,
but he's his own character now,
since I liked him so much.
Okay, so actual Nate is an investigator.
Yeah.
And this is just like a sort of spiritual
we-nate.
Anyway, his name is Tweet Burglar.
Yes.
Good, okay.
He steals tweets from
not as popular Twitter's,
and uses them on his own super Twitter,
and he gets all the love and attention
for it.
Not only does he steal tweets,
but he steals the memories of tweets ever happening.
Oh my god.
If you make a tweet and he steals it,
you won't even remember making that tweet.
And through this, he can control information
since people tweet about natural disasters
and terrorist attacks.
He can make sure people can't even remember it.
Because he can just like
remove the tweets from existence
by stealing them?
Interesting.
You know, you control the flow of information.
You control everything.
Yeah, exactly.
Another one of the elite gaming
administrators
is named Daryl Pluto.
He's sponsored by Arby's.
He's black and he's really fat.
He doesn't have any arms,
because they were blown off in the war.
And instead of arms, he has USB 3 ports.
Okay.
Sure.
Sure, alright.
And he wears a gold chain
that says Arby's on it as a necklace.
And I just don't have his shirt on, ever.
God fucking damn it, Lilligan.
You're so bad.
You fail me every time.
Just fucking kill yourself, my man.
I want to.
We're also going to have a lot of real people in it,
such as Obama.
Obama's going to be a major character,
as well as
of Quake Arena
esports theme, Fatality,
aka Jonathan Wendell.
I have no idea
what you're talking about right now.
Who is in fact the greatest
Quake 3 Arena player of all time
for a short while.
Really? He's not even still
the greatest Quake 3 Arena player.
Even that
small thing has been
stripped away from it.
Holy shit.
There's also going to
be a character by the name
of Cobra Kisser, who is John's worst nightmare.
He's French
and he's a serial rapist
and he...
That's his character. And he likes snakes.
He's magic.
Cobra Kisser.
Did you say he's gay
and he's a serial rapist?
Yeah, and he's French.
And he's French, sure. That's fine.
That's fine.
That's okay.
With me.
Let me get the entire list,
because even just talking about the carries themselves
is rewarding and innovative
of himself.
One of the
elite 4 game administrators
is the name of Sandy Hook
and she's a pirate.
Sure. That's all we know about her yet
for now.
Is that our new Sandy Hook?
Come on, Blissey.
Just sweet, sweet dreams.
The CEO of Sony
is a major character and his name is Rick Blast
and he's just a floating head
in a jar. He's in the future,
and he's bought out by a torturer's
guild.
And the PS5
is an Iron Maiden.
That's just it?
It's just an Iron Maiden
is the PlayStation 5?
And also
it's like 50,000
years in the future, but they're still
making...
They only just recently came out the PS5
because the PS4 is such a pro for its gaming system
with so many games on it that it lasted
for eons.
Eons?
Dammit.
The gravy train had to end sometime.
Balls, dude.
Oh, my god.
That's all a critical hit did?
So bad.
I know.
And by the way,
this was made like
maybe like a year and a half ago.
We started a project on this.
Yeah, I read that a long time ago.
It feels like.
But we're
actually
we're actually
but we're
we're we are an intensely dedicated
to it at this point.
Good.
Fuck, I'm not going to make it.
This toxic skin, this toxic skin
to fucking get me. No!
So bad.
I really thought I could
turn it around a little bit.
No, of course not.
During our
game, I became deeply infatuated
with the story of the Zodiac Killer.
Yeah, sure.
And I turned him
into a character named the Wii U
Torturer.
Okay.
He's basically the Zodiac Killer,
but instead of people, he kills Wii U's.
Okay.
I'm going to read the description for him right now.
I have a giant Wiki dedicated
to cataloging these various characters.
And I'm going to read the description for him
right now as we play Pokemon.
Please do.
His gaming prowess,
which is their special ability,
that's what they call it, gaming prowess,
is breaking and breakable.
And his personality is the most violent person
you will ever meet.
But only when Wii U's are involved.
Anyone who is unfortunate enough to be in the same room
with Arthur and Wii U together
will witness the most graphic display of onscreen violence
they will ever see.
He has almost a fetishistic impulse
like an old bean.
Hides his deadly Wii U
obsession at all costs.
The reason he's like this
is because he got a PS4 for his
birthday when he was 10.
And he wanted a Wii U.
So, so now like
since he couldn't have one.
Wait, how old is he now?
He's like 38.
Wait.
Wait, so this is the future.
Wait, so the Wii U is like a completely
empty console, but this boy
is totally irrelevant.
Oh, oh, oh.
Here's one you're going to really like.
You're going to really love this one.
Oh, for sakes, dude.
Why did it have to be Flygon?
You're so bad, anyway.
His name is IndieIndiaIndiana
and he's the CEO of Undertale Incorporated.
Wait, so
okay, I remember IndieIndiaIndiana
but I forget, wait,
I forgot that it was
Undertale Incorporated.
And he has single-handedly
he through
marriages
and backstabbing, he has become the sole
proprietor of
Toby Fox's legacy, his Undertale
fortune. And he has used that
money to buy
every indie game ever made
sure that
no quality titles can be released under them.
Why would he do such a thing?
Why is he so evil?
No quality
titles
ever.
And every indie game
now is just like a
based off like Cookie Clicker, Tetris
or Candy Crush.
Sure.
I mean, why wouldn't it be?
Aw, come on!
And a fun fact, he used to be
a McDonald's manager
before he became CEO
before he got his scheme in his head
to destroy indie games.
A what manager?
A McDonald's manager.
Oh, okay, makes sense. Why is he
so cruel?
He had to be explored.
Okay, okay.
All we know at this point is that
he deeply does.
Okay, dude, your zygarde's dead.
No, it's not. Yeah, it's Ice Punch, Nigger.
Yeah.
Ice Punch, come on, Nigger.
Ice Punch, Nigger.
The fact that I have warm damn on my team
means that there's nothing I can
fucking do.
I know.
It's pitiful, really.
My team was like made to just lose
to Toxicrypt. Like, I have no switch into it.
Yeah, am I gonna completely
sweep your team with Toxicrypt?
I think you very well might.
I think, well, I don't know
if I can do it with this guy.
Probably no.
Yeah, I don't have the moves.
Oh, shit.
Damn it.
I was gonna Ice Punch you.
But it just didn't happen.
It just didn't happen that way.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, you know what I'm fucking saying, dude.
I'll check this out, motherfucker.
No, that's bad.
I don't like that.
Oh, dear.
I see.
Oh, I see.
Do you?
Shit!
Okay.
Whatever.
Idiot.
Bitch.
Uh...
By the way,
I keep alluding to this novel
just because I'm so proud of it.
It's not even close to being done.
There's no specific reason
for me to even say it.
As I feel in the audiences
for Investigator,
which is like a normal story,
and well...
I wouldn't say normal,
but it is in fact
a project of love
and not of hate.
And John Major
are so intensely different
that, uh...
Really?
Again, just to reiterate, the only reason I'm talking about John Major
is because I'm so deeply enthralled
by everything about it
that I'm so proud of it
that I will talk about it from now until the end of time.
Wait.
What the fuck, dude?
What the fuck, man?
This is some bullshit, man.
It's so bad.
I got you, though.
Yeah, whatever.
Wait, you were saying that about
Investigator or about John Major?
Yeah, about John Major.
Well, I'm also very
concerned about
Investigator,
but it's much more
of a story
that could feasibly
mean anything to other people.
So I want to treat it
with a little bit more dignity
than
the John Major.
Wait, dignity?
No, the last time we talked about Investigator,
it was courage and dignity.
Oh, I see.
You said that, and I thought
the idea
of something discovering dignity
was really incredible.
Hmm.
How am I going to crush you this time?
I have so many ways.
Give up, because I just click something
that will make you run for the hills.
Okay, I might as well just fucking
get out and shoot my fucking brains out.
Yeah, I think you might want to consider
that.
What the fuck are you typing?
I'm searching the type
of ship chart.
Yeah, you idiot.
I'm weak to
fighting ground.
Is that it?
Fire,
fighting ground and fire.
You're dead.
Am I? I'm gay.
Yeah, you're very gay.
You're very gay,
and I would appreciate it
if you never did
ever again. Maybe.
Could you perhaps be less gay next time?
Please and thank you.
Please and thank you, sir.
You're dead.
There's nothing you can switch into, though.
You might as well
fucking kill yourself, my man.
Oh, no.
I might as well.
Oh, come on. Crit, really?
Had to be, huh?
Had to be.
Alright, well, whatever.
Registeel,
you've done your duty.
God, I love...
I get such a rush.
Going for that second protect.
It never pays off.
I mean,
if you find yourself going for that second protect,
you're just...
It's just over.
You've gone astray.
You're good as dead.
Yeah, it's over.
It's all over, dude.
Um...
Oh, shit.
Don't even try. Just don't even try.
I'm gonna do it.
Don't even try.
As a friend, Ben, don't try.
Listen, man.
Don't embarrass yourself any further.
No, no, listen.
No, listen, no.
Yes!
What?
Oh, my God.
I'm just fucking...
It's...
Yeah, bro.
This is the ultimate fucking cheater.
Yeah, yeah.
You're just mad
because of how gay you are.
I'm so frustrated
with my sexuality.
I have to take it out on you.
Yeah, bro.
Yeah, I got something you can take it out on, bro.
Yeah, you know what I'm saying.
Well...
Time to do exactly what I did
in the Elite Four
and just fucking toxic stall my way
into an early grave.
This is...
This is unjust.
No!
The second protect never does it.
That doesn't even matter.
Yeah, no, it doesn't.
No, it doesn't.
But, uh,
fuck you.
Oh, this is just sad.
Don't pity me.
This is where my dam is just...
Oh, dang.
Even that time, the second protect
didn't work.
Don't fucking pity me.
You piece of shit.
It's... come on.
Dude.
Return.
No.
Yeah, there's no escape.
God damn it.
You think I'm going to give you a quick death?
You think again.
I can't believe this.
Yes!
Double protect, it never fails.
It never fails.
I should have seen it coming.
The infinite strat
that never fails to work.
Double protect.
Infinite power.
Ah, you're done.
This is fucking barbaric.
Yeah, this is inhumane.
This is against the Geneva Convention.
Well, how do you like this?
There's...
It's good.
There's a great...
gay...
That fucking sucked, dude.
That sucked real bad.
Yeah, not as bad as you, though.
No, not quite.
There's a great...
Okay, there's a great, like,
fan commentary of
Half-Life
by this guy named Goose Goose.
And then, at one point, he's talking about
the, um...
He's talking about the Combine.
And he's like, you know, this seems like a...
This seems like a...
This seems like, you know, like a...
Like a...
Like a real human rights violation.
Although, I sincerely doubt
that the Combine even read
the Geneva Convention.
Let alone ratified it.
It's got great delivery.
Oh, jeez, yeah.
Those fucking backward pieces of shit.
Didn't even ratified the
Geneva Convention.
They didn't read it. Let'll even read it.
Let alone ratified it.
Okay, okay.
That's enough. Okay, that's a fucking...
Okay, alright.
Okay.
Where's the blood into fucking end it all?
I think we've reached...
I'm just gonna do this.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Just let me have this one.
Yeah, you're gonna let me win this one.
Yeah, you'll give me this one.
Yeah, because I...
I guess I felt so bad for you, because I knew
that you wouldn't win any other way.
Yeah, true.
That I thought you, you know, might as well
just fucking give it to him out of goodness
of my heart.
Alright, you know...
Okay, should we call it quits?
Yeah, yeah.
It's nine in the morning.
I haven't slept.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's way reasonable
that you're up till six in the morning.
Don't you have, like, school or something?
Don't...
I'll make good.
What day of the week is it? It's Wednesday.
Okay, yeah, I knew it.
I'll do what I need to.
You'll do what you have to do. You'll do what must be done.
I'll do what must be done.
You'll do what must be done.
You've got your own agenda.
That's not for me.
I'm paying out for number one.
That's a freeze pop song.
It's a really bad freeze pop song, actually.
Sorry, sorry.
I don't go to gay bars with you
and I don't listen to the...
Well, maybe you should sometime.
Have some gay sex with someone.
I mean, think of...
Open up your eyes.
I mean, think about it.
Okay, I'm thinking about it.
What do you hope to send
to my brain with me thinking about it?
Well, I'm just some gay shit.
Well, then we'll work.
Because I'm talking to you.
Thank you all for coming out
and listening.
Oh, God, I forgot there was people
watching.
You didn't end it.
Oh.
Everyone,
I forgot you were watching.
Thanks for joining us for another
R.F.G.
Wait, another...
R.F.
Rook.
Roof.
Going out on such a strong note.
Maybe next time we'll play
a different game. Probably not, though.
Maybe.
Wait, yes.
Yeah.
Next time we'll beat
fucking Crazy Throne.
Yeah.
We'll beat Crazy Throne.
We'll beat Crazy Taxi.
It'll be all of us.
Yeah, okay.
Good night, everyone.
Stay safe out there, America.
Donald Trump's America.
Stay safe in Donald Trump's
new nightmare dystopian America.
Where the fucking combine
come and beat you in the streets
with their stun sticks.
Where big brothers constantly spying
on each other.
They're gonna do things to you.
Yeah, they're gonna do something.
They're gonna do things to your brain.
You probably won't like it.
Things that you won't like.
Well, things that you won't like,
but in retrospect, you'll look back
and think, actually, I really did like that
because they fucking brainwashed you.
That's what Trump's America is now.
I know. I'm living here.
Welcome to City 17.
Yes. Okay.