Alright Munchy, we're back. We're back for frog fractions. We found frog fractions.
It's time to continue the story where we left off. Everything we said in the last
Radifuckers Cop Killers wasn't canon. This is canon though. This is frog fractions too,
I believe, I think. I'm led to believe. This is the only thing that will be in scriptures,
this and the last one. This will be the only thing worth celebrating.
Just like an alt universe. An alt universe of Munchy and Bin. This is the real universe, canon
universe. Who just came online on my Skype, a little man named FngR. What a coincidence.
Let's invite him on the show, Munchy. Let's invite FngR on the show. After all, he's been
such a good friend to me. He's really reached out. He's reached out to me. Like so
often and just with such tenderness. He's just a good guy. He's just a good guy with a lot to
offer the world. He's just a little sweetheart. Roach is a sweetheart. He just knows how to get
into your skin in a good way and like pollute your bones with kindness. My bones are real polluted.
Real polluted. What is this game? Well, I mean, I guess it's like a roguelike.
Man, there's so many messages. Okay. Okay. Cage. I mean, it looks like I found a towel.
Okay, if I hit Q and W, I punch myself. Oh, it's not good. Oh, did I like knock myself out?
Did I like die from that? I think you'd like teleport it back. I think if you die, then you just die.
Oh, yeah. I mean, I still have the towel, so I guess I didn't die.
This doesn't look very froggy or fraction-y. No, you're right. You're right. And yet,
and yet I know in my heart that this is frog fractions.
I can't take this.
By the way, my cursor and my keyboard are being real shitty in... Oh, gems.
They're being real shitty and unresponsive because we're... Oh, what?
I feel like I didn't explore this room thoroughly. Yeah, because we're using Skype,
because to share screen so you could see this fucking game, I need the cyan key. Okay.
We had to go back to Skype. We had to go fucking back in time. We had to go back
to the past like Samurai Jack. Yeah. Like the Samurai Jack. Yeah, yeah. We had to
hashtag MaxreviveSkype, which I mean... The worst part of the entire face of the fucking planet.
I don't know how they could have made it worse. Short of just not making calls at all,
I don't see how Skype could be any worse of a program.
Mm-hmm. It's so bloated and unoptimized, and then just the... It's so resource-intensive,
and for what? For a worse product or something that's then Discord.
Like Discord works? Why doesn't Skype work? Just make it work.
I don't understand. What is happening right now?
It's too dangerous to let you pass without a sword. Oh, but I can just
go past anyway. No, I think I'm going to listen to him. I'm going to try and get a sword.
There's gems up here. I want those. Harvest, though.
Welcome to the Texworld character creator. Oh, dude, what face should I be?
Oh, dude.
Blueberry Pie, Woodland Meadows. Lapis-Lazuli.
Lapis-Lazuli, apparently. Rose Quartz.
Rose Quartz. Holy shit. Moonlit Walk, Vanilla Snowfin.
Mass Effect 2 save.
Yeah, okay. I'm going to do that one.
This is my actual desktop. This is my actual desktop folder.
If you actually had...
It's the PCP folder.
Oh my god.
Here's all the files from Ben and Jackie's College Fund.
There's spoilers there. We can't look at that.
Wow. Do you have Mass Effect 2 on Steam?
No.
I do. Do you want me to play Mass Effect 2 for a little bit,
get a save file, and then give it to you and see what happens?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Can you fucking give me your Mass Effect 2 save file?
Yeah. I just find it inside of my computer and then give it to you. I'm fairly certain.
Oh, I've got... Maybe Pokemon Showdown will work.
Teams.
Ninja Bugs team, which I never finished making.
All right. No, that's not going to do it.
Dude. Dude.
All right.
So, while you get your Mass Effect 2 file...
I actually nearly download Mass Effect 2, but it'll be fine.
Okay. Well, I'll just... I'll come back. I'll come back for that.
Yeah.
So, yeah, so a lot's happened between...
Since two Rowdy fuckers cop killers ago.
We were just making a nice little quaint frog fractions let's play for the masses on our channel.
We were just talking about what's real and dear to our hearts.
I don't know who could have faulted us for just sharing God's honest truth,
but it did. There was a stir. There was a kerfuffle. There was a cutie mark kerfuffle.
There was a single strife that I know about, a single strife.
A meat minuscule of a strife, if you will.
Meat minuscule.
Yeah, we got attacked. We got...
We got flat. We got trolled.
We got viciously attacked by some internet bullies and trolls.
Weakness, cage matches, okay.
All we wanted to do was just make content and, you know, just be ourselves.
But the powers that be wouldn't allow us.
That's too much for some people. That's too much for small minds.
Yeah.
We're the next Elon Mux, the Rowdy fuckers cop killers.
Oh, what the fuck is happening?
Seems like kind of cool, but also like what the fuck is even happening.
I mean, I'm pretty sure most of this is just bullshit that I can ignore and it doesn't matter.
Like, all these messages are stupid and I'm pretty sure I should just stop reading them.
I got some orange soapstone.
That's...
Oh my god.
Nice.
Soapstone.
Lie ahead.
It said Mass Effect 2 specifically, right?
Yeah, yeah, it was Mass Effect 2.
Because that's the only one I have.
It's a bowl full of wicker balls.
Oh, shit.
I can't carry any more gems.
What the fuck's even the point then?
Maybe I can buy stuff with them?
Maybe I have to spend some.
What's even the point of a system like that?
There's stuff like that in Zelda.
What's even the point?
Like, of limiting how much money you can carry?
Yeah.
Ah, just the fuck with you.
Just like to make you feel bad.
Okay, good.
Video game developers like to make the twisted cistern.
The Twister Caliborn.
I can't take this.
And I can't take this.
I can't carry any more gems.
What's the fucking point?
All right, I'm going home.
My home, I mean down.
Briefcase full of cash.
Okay, okay.
Let me...
All right.
There's a couple more.
There's a couple more side paths that I can check out while we're...
While we're looking for that save file.
This is what video games used to actually look like, right?
Like, this is what like real video games looked like.
Yeah.
I mean, this is what Dwarf Fortress looks like today.
Well, we have a Dwarf Fortress.
This is incredible.
Yeah.
Dwarf Fortress is...
Oh, it...
Federal insanity.
I used to play.
I used to play a bunch of Dwarf Fortress.
Dwarf Fortress is cool, dude.
It's really cool.
But, you know, the thing I eventually decided about Dwarf Fortress
is that it's more fun to like talk about and think about
than it is to actually play.
A little bit.
I got to a point where I was like,
I've played Dwarf Fortress a bunch.
I've kind of mastered the systems, but not like the advanced systems.
And I just don't know how much...
Like, I feel like I get it.
And I've got like some good Dwarf Fortress stories.
I've had some real fun times, but like...
I get it, you know?
Like, I see you.
I see you the writing on the wall.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
Oh, damn idiot.
God, I wonder if I can even make it.
I think you just have to like hold down air.
You have to go just as soon as the blue like disappears.
All right.
You have to go fast.
Faster, faster, faster, faster, faster, faster.
I actually think that maybe like my shitty Skype fucking with my keyboard
might like be messing up my ability to do this challenge.
Oh, God, I just want it.
It like freezes for a second for me.
This guy just cannot fucking keep up with this.
You know what?
Okay, I think I can get it.
I feel confident.
Yeah.
I can't hold it.
I have to mash.
How many things have you stolen before?
Have you stolen anything?
Yeah, I've stolen stuff.
Yeah, like what?
Um, I've like shoplifted stuff.
Oh, yeah, that's big time shit.
That's big time shit, bro.
Yeah, I'm a big I'm a big time like groceries launderer.
No, I've like I've like stolen groceries.
Like some like I stole some like the first time I think I ever stole anything.
I was in California and I was real poor and I and I like I just went to the grocery store
to buy some like rice because like that's what I was eating at the time.
And hang on, let me let the cat out.
Cat out of the bag, cat's already out of the bag, Nate.
I mean, Ben.
Okay, goodbye.
Fuck, monkey, lunchie.
And like I went to buy some shitty groceries and I saw some gushers and I just really wanted
the gushers.
Like I knew I didn't want to spend the like six dollars on a box of gushers,
but I was like, but I really want those gushers, but I don't want to pay for them.
So I just bought my I picked them up and I bought my other groceries and I went and I
checked them out at the fucking self-checkout line and I just didn't swipe the gushers and
I just put them in my grocery bag and I just walked out with these box of gushers.
And yeah, I've done it.
I've done that a bunch.
I've done that a bunch of times.
It's good.
That's like federalized.
Like like all my students are like small scale, like, you know, like, like, like, like
just like take a little bit of like, like, like, like, like one time I was at a guy's
house where I didn't really like in like fifth grade.
And I just stole his like little like, like, like a full of Minko, like fucking, uh,
you know, the, the, the pink where it's long next.
I still like little Minko.
Yeah.
I still, I stole a little bit of a like a statue, a statue just because I thought it was cool.
Um, did he ever notice?
No.
Um, no, I, I, I like, you know, actually this is, this is a good time to bring this up.
Um, I, because I don't know when else this would come up, but like there was a PCP.
I forget which one there was a PCP where like the, like me shoplifting came up and I like
said it and then I got like scared about it and was like, and like didn't know if like people
would be like, oh, he's a, he's a bad guy.
So I like went back and edited that and it was too bad because there was like a real good story.
I don't remember what the story was, but there was like a real good story that I had to cut
out because it was like interwoven with like the fact that I have shop lifted before in my life.
Yeah.
Which like, I don't, I don't really think it's a big deal.
Like on, on, on, in hindsight, I'm like, I don't really think anyone is going to care that much.
Yeah.
To me, like I wouldn't, like I wouldn't do it at like a mom and pop store.
I wouldn't do it at like a small local business, but at like a chain, like at like a Walmart or
a stop and shop, like fuck them. Who cares? They're not people. Corporations are not people
and they don't deserve, they don't deserve moral consideration of any kind.
So I don't feel, I feel like, and not only do I not feel like it's a bad thing to do,
I actively feel like it's a good thing to do.
Yeah.
It's great.
Okay.
If I go to a Walmart and I just put a cashier at gunpoint, then, you know, it's just a good
thing because they're part of the, they're a cog in the machine, dude.
You gotta break my auditioning.
Yeah, they're like, they're part of the problem.
Oh my gosh.
You're way too fucking slow, dude.
I really feel like, damn it, phone. I really feel like this should be working and just like,
my keyboard is not doing what I'm telling it to do.
This is like, I'm playing this game on hard mode right now.
Oh my god. Oh my fucking god.
Hey, can you go like, like go to like where you're about to jump into it and then like,
can you go up?
No, I can't because there's water.
Hmm.
It's like, it's like a zigzag path I have to take.
And maybe you can't see it on screen share.
Oh, oh, okay.
Yeah.
I see.
Oh yeah.
That's so fucked.
It's like, I'll go like, like I'll,
maybe I'll just hit the keys slower.
Oh my god.
I am so upset.
It can't be, you know, maybe it is impossible.
Maybe it's just impossible and it's just here to fuck with me,
but that would make me so mad.
So it can't be like, it can't be true because it would make me mad if it were true.
I'm just gonna just go on the internet until lies.
Do you really think someone would do that?
This is what the hell looks like.
This is what we get for stealing.
This is our punishment.
Oh, did you fucking see that?
Yeah.
Okay.
I think I can do it.
Oh god.
I'm going to kill myself.
Myself, Mike.
Yeah.
I, I really do think that Skype is fucking up though.
Oh, yeah.
No, it's definitely Skype because I can see my, oh shit.
I can see my cursor flickering and it's very upsetting.
Like whatever, like whatever that fucking square root sign is up in the top left,
like I just want it more than life itself.
What if you can't even carry it?
I can carry it.
I got a towel.
Of course I can get a square root, a squirt for short.
Oh wait, I can, maybe I should just hold it.
Oh, I fucking did it.
I'm a genius.
Good luck and try Fleur de Lis.
All right.
Fleur de Lis, that's a pony.
Is it?
That's a pony.
Be wary of butts, insulated boots ahead.
Oh, I got it.
I got it.
I did it.
I have done it.
Can you get through the other side?
No, your way is blocked by dire shrubs.
No, I think I just got to die.
Okay, there we go.
Let's try through here.
Blocked by water.
Is this a bank?
Yeah, it looks like a bank.
All right, I guess.
Until it gets it's gray and it makes you want to kill yourself.
It looks like it.
You know what?
I think those black blocks are supposed to be stained glass windows.
So I think maybe it's a church.
Oh, maybe.
The lion bunker.
Good luck.
Again, like it can't go anywhere.
It's blocked by shrubs and water.
All right, so that's a bust.
That's a bust.
It's a bust.
You have a sword yet?
Maybe what you think you just got up is a sword.
Yeah, maybe.
You need the red key to unlock this door.
Need no bless oblige and try pressed digitization.
Okay, so this is like some Dark Souls stuff.
So like need skates and imminent flaming tomb.
Again, blocked by shrubs, blocked by water.
Oh, I can push crates.
Oh, shit.
Oh, this might.
I wonder if maybe I could have progressed before.
Amazing trap.
Amazing trap ahead.
I can't believe the story you're telling me.
It's macabre.
I bet I can get that bracket.
You get that fucking bracket, bro.
I'm so fucking.
I'm having so much fucking fun with this game, munchie.
Oh, you might have fucked up.
I found a pair of auto correct skates.
Oh, shit.
Nice.
All right.
I did it.
You just auto.
Oh, if space, I can doff skates.
You need you need the white key to take off the skates.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
Well, whatever.
Like I'm fine with them on.
Oh, that's a monster.
Okay, I've got all the I've got all the gems I need.
Anyway, we're game.
I'm totally I'm just so fucking immersed inside this video game.
Me too, dude.
I like I'm like I'm loving this like not even as like a joke.
Gorilla Grove.
The Gorilla Grove.
Oh, the thing is like fucking going crazy at me.
What?
Oh, they like go after me.
Oh, no.
Now that I've got all the gems.
What the fuck?
Now that I've got all the gems I can carry,
the gems are like an impediment.
Okay.
You know what?
I can do this.
This is how they punish greed, Ben.
This is how they punish greed.
I mean, I guess I guess so.
The Megasort.
You see a message here.
I did it.
Master.
Oh, God, you're so fucked.
Master master using it and you can open this.
So I have to master the Megasort before I can obtain it.
Yeah, it's deep.
That's deep and it's important.
The two way slider doesn't move.
Oh, God.
At some points, I think in this like, yeah,
abstract art style is actually like benefiting it
because it's like, you know, you use your imagination.
That's kind of magical.
Other times I just think I just cannot fucking understand
what is happening.
I understand everything.
Oh, I found the red key.
Red.
My way is blocked by shroobs.
I've got all the gems that I can carry.
Okay.
Good.
I suspect two is done downloading.
Really?
Okay.
All right.
You know what?
I like, I wonder if I can.
Oh, I wonder if I can get in here.
They're giving me like CD keys right now.
The crates path is blocked.
Okay.
Look at my micron pen and write this down.
That's fancy, dude.
Yeah, that's fancy.
That's fancy stuff.
I paid, I paid, I paid good silver, silver shekels for my micron.
Centipede corner.
What the?
I just want to win, Munchie.
I just want to win the game.
You think we'll even see a frog?
Um, I mean, maybe we're, maybe we're looking at a frog right now.
I want to see a frog.
I want to see him spit his little heart out.
That's what dogs do.
I mean, uh, frogs.
That is what dogs do.
Harpy ahead.
Okay.
That's, that's, oh God.
I'm so fucking annoyed by this purple.
I found a thing.
Okay.
Whatever.
I think I got what I needed to get.
Although I kind of want to, I feel like those white blocks over there
are going to give me like an important message.
Master using it.
I got a master this, I got a master the Megasword.
How?
Shit.
This fucking key is so, why would they, why?
Why is this part of the steam release?
To have a built in like CD fucking ROM like code.
God, fucking physical media.
Yeah, what the fuck dude?
Why did it ever exist?
Why, why was there a time when we needed to have physical like anything?
Yeah.
It was bad.
Like it was bad.
It was a bad time.
And like history will frown upon it.
It was like even worse than slavery or killing gays.
I mean it was maybe a lot worse than either of those put together.
Play Master 2?
Yeah, of course.
Oh wait, I see, I see.
I got here before but I couldn't go anywhere because the crate
because the crate, I hate these monsters.
I hate them.
All right, now here's what you need to do, Ben.
What's that?
You need to open up, here I'm going to start, I'm going to do my screen share
and then you like put the window like off of the side
and then you have also my screen share up of Mass Effect 2
on the other side of the screen.
Okay, I'll try my best.
I think I just got to go over here.
Oh, you can also share your system sound.
Sewer blimp.
Wait, wait, hang on, do I need to do that right now?
No, well what do you mean?
Like, okay, do you have the...
Oh, I'm on the blimp, dude.
What?
The world shifts as you touch Gliok's Mind Stone.
Sorry I was gone for a bit, I was making a sandwich.
I see you found the municipal sewers.
I wouldn't poke around in there too much, it's rather unsanitary.
How are these the sewers?
I'm on a blimp.
Dude, wait, did you close the screen share?
Maybe we can only do one at a time.
Wait, no, I didn't close screen share.
Yeah, what the fuck?
Well, can you not see this?
No, I can't see you, no.
I can only see mine.
What is going on?
Here, I'll here, I'll in the screen share.
How, but how, but how could a man do that?
But how was a man to do?
Oh, wait, you know what?
Yeah, I can tell.
Oh, wait, did you not see the blimp?
No, I can't, I can't end it.
I can't end screen share.
Here, okay, let me try it.
Sorry, I'm fucking up.
Fuck.
Call share screens start.
Do that, is it better?
No, I can't see you.
How do I stop screen share?
Should we just end the call?
I, yeah, yeah, let's do that.
I'll call you right back.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay
The
Okay
Uh my house recording yeah, okay, okay, um let me share screens
by the way my um
My keyboard is doing a weird thing now
like
It's more responsive
but it's doing a weird thing where like if I hit a wall it will like randomly
change my direction like I'm like I'm just holding one key right now I see
like if I bump into a shrub it stops me but if I just hold up it like turns
me around anyway anyway whatever I can live with it so I'm on I'm on the beach
and I just got to get on this goddamn sewer blimp here we go oh wow a blimp I
thought this only existed in human tails um hmm why did why did that message
about the sewers only appear like a minute ago I feel like I was in the
sewers a long time ago I know I don't need gems I don't need money I don't need
yes yes okay so I've got red key I got gray key I'm I'm what what the fuck you
died the thing killed you oh wait you just what the fuck why are these
messages coming so late something's something's off something's so fucked
right now dude something's off and like it's crazy and yet somehow I feel like
it's all skype's fault I can't fucking see literally anything because Mass Effect 2
is in like windowed mode but the window mode is just a full screen but at like
there's no difference I can't see the screen because like like whatever trying
to tell or something Mass Effect 2 is always on the top it's always on the
top of my screen so I can only see Mass Effect 2 now um what are you gonna do
man I mean well the boulders path is blocked everything's fucking out this
is going so horribly well will it will it be all right if you just close Mass
Effect 2 yeah well I have to play it oh well do you want to like I have to play
it to get the save file that we need for that game okay here here I'm gonna
screen share and then and then you be munchie for a while yeah fuck fuck that
game for a little bit just just play just watch me play this one okay let's let's
see munchie let's see your screen dog how do I share okay I got an
advertisement okay okay can can you see it can you see me now hold yes there's
Mass Effect all right there we go I'm gonna I'm gonna make this big fuck we
have to input oh no okay we're gonna have to go to fucking that and then you
know that are you just gonna like save like start Mass Effect 2 and then
immediately save yeah yeah yeah okay okay fucking cool excellent what the fuck
I did I did not open that okay god for I just not it's so fucking far out there
like no wonder it took like so long to come out from its Kickstarter I've I've
never played this game before by the way I'm just gonna skip anything I don't
care I fucking I got this on a steam sale and I literally don't care about
Mass Effect I don't care at all about Bioware or like but like that like Mass
Effect style RPGs yeah just see they just seem obnoxious and terrible to me yeah
what the fuck I leave me alone leave me alone leave me alone just let me get a
second can I not skip this are these unskippable cut scenes I I'm pressing
every button I fucking know about yeah great I don't even have the audio on I
can't hear these people are saying they aren't saying anything I I am why why is
the world such that like what I'm doing now is screen recording your computer
while you play a video game or while you wait to play a video game that won't
let you play yeah I look at this look at what the people think this is good
I saw I saw I saw a muted cut scene and I can already tell it's awful there's no
there's no upsides to the series there's there's no there's no saving it yeah I
don't know man I really don't see the people over what rip off what the fuck
fuck overwatch man and fuck it's and fuck it's spin-off Mass Effect this is
this is literally just a Star Wars big a because there's no like like funny guys no funny
guys no funny guys in this space station drama space drama space we're like the
space power sexual I like to have big dick in my asshole ship yep there he is
now there he is now just hey hey hey big dick they call them big dick for
short oh and his father I'm so fucking gay cuz I like to eat me is that what
this is right now it's just a vegan documentary can we play the fucking game
please I hate video games munchie I hate what culture has become I hate this
world look at this guy he's obviously a fucking communist globalist what the
fuck please play the game I just want a fucking I just want a save file I just
want the same file that's all we're here for I hate it fuck video games you
know here's like roaring like we're in so fucking bad cuz I'm running Skype
that's the problem I'm running sky yeah you're running you're running you're
running Mass Effect 2 you're running Mass Effect 2 the most cutting edge the
most cutting-edge space simulator simulates over 15 quadrillion planets
this is like fire right now is the inside of my computer this is what the inside
my computer looks like for running and like and yet it's Skype like it's Skype
that is bottlenecking yeah the whole situation what's happening oh fuck I
did you have to play the video game quick I swear word play like your life
depends on it holy shit people just don't even like I don't even know if you
want Skype anymore this one since I even open Skype I don't know who just is who
the fuck is jish I don't know what these fucking questions are I said to
answer by I don't have audio on I can't hear what I'm answering it's it's good
it's actually better this way cuz like the let if you don't know the question
then your answer will reveal like who you truly are you know no yeah I'm just
answering by it's widely exactly exactly think about it when Lego Star Wars not
like Star Wars but like like Lego Star that's Lego Star Wars that was like that
was very very Lego Star Wars this is like like like they fucking really like
um um Josh Josh scorcher as creator of as creator of Mass Effect we were
wondering what your biggest influence influences were and he'll say well um
well Munchie I was heavily influenced the story was heavily modeled after my
favorite video game Lego Star Wars to the Phantom Menace and and you know the
rest is history did you ever play Lego Star Wars no never never played a Lego
game like Lego Star Wars actually great because okay this is the most like
satisfying like sound ever is like like many kids are like basically like like
just like these like items can't throw at the level and you know if like if you
collect them all you get like 100% and the sound it makes is like this was
satisfying fucking thing you could ever hear in your entire life you know what
this actually looks kind of cool it's like space this this part this part I
like I like this part I'm like uh find a save point like you find a safe find a
save point dude wrong wait wait wait wait wait does this game have save
points wait you know what I'm gonna say I think you've already got a save file
because I'm pretty sure it auto saves whenever you make a decision really I
think so yeah let me just get the next load yeah yeah here here let me wait for
this cutscene and then I'll I'm gonna quit cuz I do not want this for any
month longer than I have to no don't be stupid fucking fag yeah like like look
at like look at the difference like like which of these men is straight like
just ask yourself like like looking at them like what do you guys got the
mischievous grin he's got the you know wild personality yeah clearly
sexual all the straight guy yeah yeah yeah am I like a girl is that what's
happening are you I mean yes but women can't space no they're they're hymens
just go haywire yeah when you enter when you leave Earth's atmosphere they're
uterus just cannot compute they just it just starts fucking up this is the
inside of women's uterus when like this is what this scene is about yeah this is
the end like if you pick a female character yeah
this is the end of the game I mean it's a space adventure no it's more like a
fucking real life like like this is like the red pill this is it like this is the
much the much Ballyhood red pill I think I think she's done for anyone play a
video game and think that it's okay to do I don't know like I can't I don't know
anyone I don't know anyone that really thinks it's okay like like there's a
really thought about it because really like sat down and like look taken a long
look in the mirror and thought like is it okay to play this video game and come
back with an affirmative answer oh my god doesn't happen frog fractions to frog
fractions to baby I'm pretty sure you can just like close it and like you'll
have a save file all right although I don't know how you'll find the same
I can't I can't do it I can't I can't I can't escape you can't control all
delete oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah okay here here here all all tab right
there we go all right dude yeah yeah just fucking crash your whole system
computer it's all part of the frog fractions to brand it's all on brand for
frog fractions to all right so do you think can you can you get me that can
you get me the save file I needed yeah yeah yeah here here I'm gonna go mess
back to properties oh local files browse local files and not not okay it's
probably gonna be in data probably no it's gonna be wait did you find the
mass effect to folder yes okay launcher I mean I just need to find where the
folder is maybe I haven't been local father might be in like documents some
games do that you might just have to Google like how to fucking copy your
fucking save yeah yeah yeah yeah here I'll do that how to rotate oh look
another timely message from these purple gorillas were imported from Chilcina
to populate the gorilla grove but they broke loose and now they're all over the
shop wait this is a shop all right oh shit find the binaries fold okay we'll
do well we'll do bud we'll do
wait wait you throw a gem into the voice well into what over on won't let you
near the serpent of chaos you throw a gem into the well a voice says snakes need
to be steered well in advance you throw a gem into the well a voice says remember
to take proper care of your teeth being polite to your party will get you
invited back okay whatever this is stupid gems of ill for an obsolete form of
currency but if you collect enough perhaps you'll find a vendor who still
accepts I'm so fucking lost what the fuck are you looking for no no yeah no
my save file is empty I think I had to have saved fuck oh you're but like but
like it I think I'm really pretty sure it auto saves like when you make a
decision like I don't think you can like unmake decisions or maybe you can oh wait
no no here here I'm reading the wrong article okay here here well I still
think I might be fucked I can't I can't find it bro I can't find it
no god no god damn it so I mean do you think you just had like get further yeah
here here yeah yeah I'm gonna open it up again okay all right Godspeed I'm like
fucking around like there's a puzzle here but I can't I can't I'm not seeing
like any solution solution I'm not finding it in salvation you know you
can't trust those soap zone messages right the people who write them aren't
even in the union yeah I gathered that oh oh oh got it all right I got it kind of
real me this been has there anything a video game ever made that produced
anything worthwhile new game fuck a video game that produce anything worthwhile
gonna have to give you a big fat negatory on that one munchie oh I think I
got it my weight my game I think my game just crashed no no no no no are you
are you seeing this come on see in this munchie I don't know you're screening
you're not screen-sharing I'm not no oh whoops
yeah I'm gonna turn levels on auto look what that means oh shit yeah oh oh shit oh
man we're this is completely different I found like a I use like a red key and
then I found like a door oh no I touched like a one of those things that were in
the that were in the oh this is floppy bird oh god what do we do um stop it stop
it you're gonna crash bro I've got it I've got to add fuel I see okay well I
fucked up here I got here I take a shit oh no the toast okay here keep them in
a camera to shoot real quick yeah yeah I'll figure this out
kindling zero I guess I'll buy I guess wait I have to like sell the kindling like
I need less fuel so that I don't go go too high okay it's like oh man this is like a
parody of all of my favorite video games all like the bullshit addictive like the
bullshit this is this is like the kind of bullshit that like Magikarp jump is and
like I fucking love games like Magikarp jump where you just like accumulate shit
you just like hit imaginary milestones and accumulate meaningless crap but like
it's all like a self it's all like a self a self fulfilling oh go go down go go
down how do we go down how do we go down I've sold I've sold everything no go
down no go down you fucker no no alright oh you oh you you buy it you buy it for
fuel okay so you add fuel to get your temperature up and then you spend the
temperature to buy the fuel which increases your temperature regularly so I wonder if
there's any way I wonder if there's any way to reduce your temperature because that's
what I need oh I see you buying fuel weighs you down and you go down oh okay okay okay now
we're good I've got it figured out I've got the strategy oh my fucking god I love it I
love this game dupe dupe dupe leisurely I bet that Munchie is gonna I bet we're gonna go
through oh shit we're gonna go through all this rigmarole to get a mass effect to get
the mass effect to save and I bet it's not even like I bet it'll do something but not
like something that's actually good but that's fine that's fine actually oh there we go yeah yeah
okay I'm getting it I'm getting it God I'm so fucking smart just feels so good to be this
fucking good at video games do you know what I'm saying whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa okay okay
this red thing bad oh god god it looks the red thing reminds me of like the Sims when
something bad happens what um oh I think the red I think it might be a symbol I think it's an
ASCII symbol that maybe I was like I'm here to get I think I may have achieved what I was supposed
to achieve here but I just just really like this game I just really like this one I'm just gonna
fuck around with it until either Munchie gets back or I get like really bored which I mean stranger
things have happened but I have infinite patience I have infinite patience for video games that's why
I'm so fucking good at video games I'm just like I will just play I will just play the worst game
and not even care no no no no yes yes no no all right um how do I leave
do I have to do I have to like get to the end
the fact that there's no like quit to the main game thing makes me wonder maybe I have to get to
the end the crack in the ground looks suspicious that crack cocaine all over the ground looks suspicious
okay okay okay am I gonna make it I think I'm gonna make it okay
okay yeah yeah I think we're good I think we're good maybe I'll just
oh my god no I don't think I don't think I could beat that I don't think there's an
end I'm gonna Google it oh god there's lightning outside I like it oh god fuck yeah oh how frog
fractions to want you import your mass effect to save to save file of the game oh let's find out
there have been conflicting reports circulating about whether to save file actually does anything in
frog fractions to be on existing as a get of course it's just a gag whatever I just want to know how
to beat the toaster I just want to know how to beat the toaster all right all right
I think maybe I'm done I think maybe I'm done here with with this toaster
uh no what my keys what the oh no oh no oh no what have I done
Ben I just threw up I'm sick oh why no continue continue I mean Monchi I think I just really
fucked up oh yeah yeah I think I just uh well I mean I can probably get back to well I lost all
my keys like I've still got all the items oh fuck like I was in I went to this toaster mini game
and like I think like I thought that I did what I needed to do there like I thought I got what I
needed to get and so I like left the the place like I went back to the what like I couldn't see a
way to quit like I couldn't find a way to quit so I just went to the thing and well here here we are
I I a lot I reset to try to get back to the menu and I lost all my keys well Jesus Christ yeah it
blows Jesus Christ well you can you can just get back to where you were right I yeah I just well I
need the keys okay but like I okay all I need is two keys and then I'll be right back where I was
just just hold it down yeah yeah excellent yeah I get fucking massive I do I'm lactose intolerant
pretty sure I don't know I'm wait it makes sense what what what happened why'd you throw up Monchi
I throw because well the only thing I ate today was coffee and I put in the way I eat coffee is that
I I put in like half a cup of coffee that filled the rest with milk and then some sugar because I
hate coffee yeah I get that yeah and then yeah and then see whatever I drink dairy or you know
whatever I consume dairy I always immediately have like like like sweaty ball like like sweaty
ball soup and I like I always have like like like fat nasty shits so I like I thought that was just
part of life until I realized you maybe I'm lactose intolerant because it's literally every
single time it's dairy yeah man I mean I'm not gonna do it I'm just gonna keep it I'm not
gonna you're just gonna you're just gonna like be you're just gonna like take your licks yeah well
all right yeah you got it you got to do oh man I don't under like I've done like I've made
progress like I opened up this door but I don't have the key you shouldn't have picked up so many
gems yeah I know oh wait it's that person that person's back yeah yeah yeah she's the glitter
mitten ladies is is helping me I need the red key yeah I know god damn it what is this okay like
some things remain and others don't the autocorrect roll case with the highest of fashion in the
mistake prone royal court of ancient gents and these are like I Skype I'm telling you I swear to
God Skype is fucking up this game because I should have gotten all these notifications this is
literally a fucking hellscape gamepad support unlocked good throw it into the well yeah I just
need to throw like I just need to throw away all my gems like that's all I need to do here yeah
yeah yeah yeah I guess so here I'm gonna start screen sharing again you don't yeah like I won't
be able to see you but just keep just keep playing they're just like how Skype open like like a
little bit so so so they can like see what I'm doing too and I don't really need to see what
you're doing because it's just a fucking game wait wait wait wait wait wait what the fuck no
no no I no no no no no no I got full gems no yeah dude guess I'm gonna get gems dude I fucked
up all right you know what I'm gonna I'm gonna retry so many save states holy shit I don't know
I don't know all right wait so you're gonna start screen sharing with me yeah and just so the
viewers can have my spec 2 on screen in their back fractions to video okay let me know yeah yeah
now so yeah so just like just like have like just like drag our frog fractions to like one side
and then like the Skype to the other okay we'll do all right Jesus Christ I have to do this all
over again oh yeah I have subtitles on this time but I'm not gonna read it I'm just trying to make
it like through here without picking up jewels I'm just trying to make it through this this
mess back to series without having to know anything about mess back to because if I knew
anything better I'd probably kill myself probably I need okay good go go go good it's like this
like like these guys are pretty like like you're like roller coaster no no hands outside the
vehicle shit one I needed one more gem slot oh my fucking god I just got to throw away one and
then I'm good can you do that yeah yeah there's a there's a place you can throw gems into a well
but like when you throw nine in it like explodes with more gems oh fucking great so yeah yeah but I
don't know what to do all right Jesus Christ oh wait I'll just wait wait are you screen sharing
right now yeah okay oh there it is there it is oh my should not have turned so proud on those the
worst mistake I've ever made my entire life probably where do I go oh my god no no dude
no bro this is like different somehow somehow this is different what the fuck where do I go
yeah this looks totally different maybe you made a different choice choices matter I guess oh no
getting on there like the point of the game no no it's fine choices don't matter okay good
huh too many gems too many gems space too many damn it the fucking Brony community did this to me
oh the Brony community just one it just just the latest just the latest in the laundry list of
crimes they've committed against us yeah against the PCP and the RFC K yeah what the fuck why why
do they insist on like destroying my spaceship and thrusting me into this it's a fun space
adventure scenario why are they in the community yeah the Brony community insist on I don't know
they're just jealous I think yeah don't be stupid normally he's dead okay one more guys
name is Joker what kind of Joker would be named Joker I don't know man I don't know man why
don't you ask Bioware or Mass Effect or Bethesda or Sony Sony whoever made whoever made the
steaming pile of embarrassing shit that is that is Mass Effect 2 can you imagine actually like
attaching your name to this brand and and go like honesty and like trying like believing like
believing in your product you're like hey look guys look I made like a space opera it's got like
aliens and stuff and like and like and like actually like being able to like to like wake up the next
morning and like knowing yourself in the mirror and like and like tell your wife and like tell your
wife that you love her and like and like and like mean it yeah no it's it's it's beyond me hey guys
I made a video game get the fuck out of here with that shit get the stop stop embarrassing yourself
jim jimmy they say oh oh look oh look where I am yes yes yes I mean progress yes yes yes
well why is every theoretical bad person named Jimmy like like like whenever a youtuber she's
like oh shut up Jimmy that's not true that's only me only me by the way munchie look I made it back
to the church I can't see you I can't see you why don't you look what do you look with your eyes
we can't screech at the exact same time because Skype sucks God oh I'm in like a like at the green
key oh I can I'm in like a fucking platforming section it's beautiful I love well I mean I'm in a
fucking shitting simulator I mean I'm gonna suck my own fucking dick and kill myself simulator
can I can I come yes please that's not making me can end this fucking charade of wanting to live
and of breathing what is this why is it so different from last time it's exact same but I just quit
it's like quit before I think oh what is happening oh no oh no munchie what I think I think it's
played a horrible trick on me I think it just gave me the green key before like needing me to
jump on some platforms that are made of green doors oh my god so now I have to like restart the
game to get on the fucking platform or trick that's terrible that is terrible a cheap trick oh
that's so mean okay okay here we go what is this literal star war what is this literal star war
this is literally a star war what the fuck here we go here we go here we go we're solved we
problem solved now I see oh no no no no I'm wrong because there's no way around the key there's no
way around the key what's my name what's my name gonna be um um tech F and GR F and GR yep yep yep
Tony Tony F and GR F and GR got a fucking hate F and GR God I'm fucking so embarrassed about F and
GR I'm just so vicariously embarrassed for him like all the time yeah I don't know if you can like
you can even like understand like he's just indescribable he's like unfathomable it it well I mean
he's pretty unfathomable but it's really unfathomable to me that like anyone can like understand what
he's talking about like like the man cannot string together like two concepts into like a sentence
and yet people like voluntarily listen to him
well I say people but yeah it's generous insects bugs comfortable bugs yeah
yeah what what is this a big tidied slut doing why is she here leave me alone I just want to play
video games and like obviously can't play a video game if there's a girl in the room
obviously I I wonder if there's any fucking way no okay god god this is disgusting this is the most
gross ass video game I've ever seen before in my life I'm I don't I got I got the green key maybe I
should just fucking you know what maybe I just have to come back here man this sucks man this
sucks ass all right whatever I got the green key is that green it looks more blue no I need
the cyan key all right all right cool just fucking up and explode wherever I go
uh hang on I gotta punch myself wait no I'm gonna walk through this I'm gonna walk through
this door I'm gonna walk through what is apparently not no no I have to fucking shoot things I guess
wait I have to play this game no no I can't you just save like just save bro how oh
safe safe safe safe save save save save save save save save save save save safe safe oh you did it
same you did it I knew it all right all right all right all right all right sick sick sick sick sick
all right all right all right all right I said any unsleeper yeah yeah I saved I
saved I saved I saved I saved guys I saved all right stop shooting recording
stop stop it stop it what me no me all right um um um yes yes yes I have I
have the files I have the power okay fmgr underscore 31 soldier fmgr is a
child soldier all right I am I'm just I'm just hanging out in a blimp I'm just
hanging out in the in a blimp on the beach so um yeah turn your screen
sharing on it is on it's not it's not for me because it's not on okay okay
she's literally unusable Skype the Mass Effect 2 of programs no no I think I
may have fucked this one up and just forgotten that it wasn't on so here we
go share screens start and how's that how's that what the whoa have you not
you have not seen any of this stuff I've been doing some important stuff I've
been doing important shit yeah like I got it I got into the church etc you all
right all right two female symbols the two female symbols yeah he's oh yeah yeah
I got the green key I don't know what I'm gonna do with it yet I got the gray
key and somewhere there's a red key which but I've been through I don't
remember what was through there when I've been there before you know what oh
wait no no through that red door was the fucking um was the fucking iron mini or
a toaster mini game which I couldn't beat it was too hard it was too it was
too little baby boy like like did you see it like did you see what was going on
there well I saw I saw it look like flappy bird and then I it looked like
flappy bird no but like wait did I just lose the wait what happened to my fucking
roller skates oh I think I reset I think I reset uh you know what I'm going back
because I want those roller skates and they're this way I feel like they may be
important even though they may not be like I don't know what's important I
don't know what this game values it obviously doesn't value Christian values
no traditional values it's a complete loss on this game yeah sad fucking sad
okay gotta unlock gamepad support there we go I don't understand why it's doing
this thing where like when I hit a barrier it like randomly picks a new
direction for me it really pisses me off and okay oh that oh that's the red key
okay that's the red key all right all right oh god no this I did this before
okay yeah oh shit all on that solves itself okay those colored quartz deposits
sometimes from natural internal gyroscopes limiting their movement to one
axis all right it makes sense makes sense lady oh how the fuck do I have a
fuck do I get out of here shit are you fucked no no no okay no yeah here we go
okay I was just gonna die just gotta die I have this full screen now wait it's
full screen yeah yeah no for me but I mean like I like on Skype I can see
so I can actually see what's happening now okay there's an item over small I
can see anything there's okay yeah yeah through that red door is that like in
the bottom left there through the red door is the the fucking toaster minigame
which I guess I'll have to do again at some point yeah 100% this game yeah
like by any by some okay you know I'll go do it I'll go do it now well it was
like we should we should import save the mess like to save oh that's right
that's right all right I gotta go back I gotta go back to the past like Samurai
Jack damn it you know what I hate what Western cartoons yeah Western cartoons
are pretty much worthless Western cartoons are stupid and people that like
them embarrass me they're only two no actually no they're none they're none
yeah maybe you should come back after you get a sword well where like the so the
only sword I know about is over there okay okay here we go Mass Effect wait
wait did you send me the Mass Effect yes I don't know which one there's like a
couple files in here I don't know which one is like preferred just send me like
just send me like the whole folder or whatever okay or something no no yeah
yeah yeah just to send me send me just send me whatever you think is a save yeah
try any of these also I have to close fucking Mass Effect 2 because I never
want to eat again oh my god I need close team I can't imagine like can you
imagine like opening up steam and then like saying to yourself like to play I'm
gonna play a video game like I can but not without like puking a little bit yeah
yeah all right I'm gonna make a new folder let's call it saves all right
here we go all right it is moment truth I played the shitty by the way I am like
wearing I can't find my normal glasses I'm just wearing my prescription
sunglasses your prescription sunglasses indoors yeah because I can't find my
normal glasses oh munchy munchy munchy what will what are we to do with you what
are we to do with you where okay I please tell me the oh no I don't know where
they saved I don't know where the other one saved god damn it they probably my
downloads file let me see let me see let me see a new folder open the new window
date modified no no no why don't you download them again but I like three
kilobytes like seven oh here I was showing folder here we go okay they just
saved to like a Skype folder right it's retarded yes really fucking stupid and I
hate it okay now I've got them I've got them on my desktop okay here we fucking
go yeah it's the moment of truth it's when it's when all your hard work pays
off finally no no never play video game again that's the only time I needed it
just for like one one horrible one horrible section here you go import
Mass Effect to save desktop saves which one I'm gonna go with chapter save yes
there we go welcome back commander commander fngr shepherds all right
we've done it yes yes I'm also gonna make ourselves a summer lemon
vanilla snowlings was where she's such special snowflakes that we have to make
another video we were all right well we were already vanilla snow where that's
but that's fine okay I actually like it better this way okay yeah yeah um hell
all right I don't I don't want to do this I don't want to play this fucking
toaster game it's all right okay um I think I think this is the way to advance
by beating this this mini game I may I may have fucked this up oh wait no no
no wait yes I fucked it up okay let's try it again yeah a big deal a big deal
we just we just gotta do it okay it's okay it's easy there we go
and some right on some on some matters of more importance
you don't you don't you don't understand yet I don't I don't understand you don't
understand yet but you will
oh god look at this shit here it's approaching so slowly and yeah I can
feel I can feel it on my bones like I can't I don't know if I can even explain
like why this is so bad but just it just oh no I'm fucked yeah idiot I don't know
why bad
because the way the way that you get height is you buy fuel and then you
gradually gain height but like initially buying the fuel costs you height
that's ridiculous yeah it's it's I'm if I can beat it I'm gonna feel really good
about myself and really excited and feel like I'm what is inside of the toaster
toast when you die some toast comes out okay I will feel like floppy thing going around is
that the frog no that's a wing oh that's a wing on the side of the toaster oh incredible
no no yeah yeah I was doing I was doing way better before I got through like five of them
oh damn dude yeah I know I know
I mean you'll see what happens if you sell uh if you sell you gain some height
and lose some acceleration
yeah oh god
like see I've already fucked up because I'm too high now and the only way to lose
height is to like buy like that yeah fuck okay now we're good for now
um do you have anything left anything left to do what like like like you have any fuel left
you're originally gonna run out right no you like gradually gain fuel
oh god please please please please please please
but you know what I've actually figured it out I've actually like figured out that the way to
like control your height oh my god what the fuck is that I think this is like what I need
from this minigame I think I need to like get this and take it back
okay you know I figured out the way the way to control your height is to like quickly buy and
then sell yeah okay so like it's like the stock market buying sell buying sell
I've got it okay you know what I've got a I've got a plan I've got the plan now um okay okay
no uh oh am I am I good or what am I fucking good or what you're god but you're god oh my god
that was the scariest fucking thing ever oh my god I almost I almost clipped the edge um good
oh god no I fucked up yeah I fucked up I should have bought molotov okay you know what I was real
close we did good we did good so we have that thing all right good like can you do anything with
it or is it just with you I think you just have to like get it and then win look at all these
fucking buildings in the background you can feel there's a brony each one of them
at like each window each window hides a brony yeah that's just like it's just looking out the
window and just like just like ready to like be ready to like censor us yeah ready to attack
control at a moment's notice um are we are we gonna are we gonna are we gonna touch on the
elephant in the room are we gonna dress the elephant in the room uh let's do that after we
get out of this mini game okay okay and then like smash cut yeah
oh Jesus Christ my my fucking house is singing to me how how can it be it's doing that
noise my house is singing to me it's it's trying to alert me of the grave danger
of the thunder the thunder of the thunder from the land down under
man i'm so glad i'm sorry i might have to say it worked
no oh what you're too you're too trigger happy dude i am i am trigger happy okay
okay we gotta take the slow methodical
yes yes yes come on pipes should reveal yourselves
all right that's good incredible this kid's got the magic touch dude this kid's gonna go places
soon soon all right all right all right michael jackson michael jordan michael brown
bin sane and you're about michael brown michael michael brown is one of the black kids who got shot
what oh no i'm i don't even know how he could have avoided that uh just i don't know do what
you did last time oh wait i got oh i fell i fell through the crack the crack in the ground i fell
through the crack in the ground holy shit yeah thank god thank fucking god thank christ i well i
wait i think i got you got it you got it dude but i can't like leave like how do i fucking move
what what the shit what's happening like
okay um i can't leave the space so like maybe i should punch myself oh wait wait wait what
that's your sword that's your sword i think it's my sword it's your sword i guess i guess i guess i guess
i got oh i can i can chop down shrubs oh my god this this is well we're the new extreme
like like like without putting like this is this is a literal game changer this is this
has literally changed the game oh my god oh my fucking god we're not gonna need brownies where
we're going yes i can kill the purple gorillas now i can fucking charge them oh they're damn
i hate them and they're dead now that's what i always wanted oh my god this is great my dogs
just this is fucking incredible all right they'll just look like the power oh sheer might oh no oh i
thought i lost it for a second i'll be able to fucking kill these these fucking bitches
these absolute monstrosities i did it i did it
the megasword of xanthar is mine xanthar i love that part
now what is what is this here nothing um all right well i've got a sword now i guess yeah
yeah you can cut down the shrubs and you can kill the bitches oh that's right cutting down the
shrubs cutting down the shrubs is what is like what's really important here again again inside
the little doorway yeah but i've already been in that little doorway yeah okay oh but i can go through
here it's actually really annoying that like this sword like blocks my movement yeah well you know
it's like it's incredibly incredibly just just like deliberately like deliberately poor design
i feel is what's going on here um god i fucking hate spaniards yeah understandable you name a
worse country other than spain a single spain um portugal okay yeah portugal is pretty bad
oh what the shh portugal is like gay spain oh it spawns them um a lot of portuguese people where i
grew up um no particular feelings about them i've in any in any way they i didn't even i didn't even
realize i didn't even realize people were portuguese i didn't even realize it was like a real thing that
someone could be yeah even though like everyone around me was it yeah it's like like i just feel
like if you're from like spain or portugal then you like you you like you are like in a different
realm like you do not exist in the same space me obviously cannot like me no in like our shared
space yeah okay okay okay okay so let's oh yeah yeah push push and crates push and crates
cannot open lions nearby what oh i think it's these red things
yeah probably i think these red things are lions yeah yeah i just have to eliminate them
oh there's like a spawner oh okay okay i can kill the spawner okay good it's like minecraft
there we go oh that was scary for sure i was gonna jump on you there we go
just run right into it yeah jesus christ we're just fucking unlimited they just can't wait to
die these fucking jesus oh did you fucking see that shit come on
the like path finding for this is like so like so advanced yeah
this is like actually like beat this is like one everyday life like
yeah like it's really relatable yeah like um oh god oh jesus relatable teen shit right here no
oh son of a fuck okay whatever uh it actually doesn't matter at all no uh just makes just makes
me feel bad about myself how fast do you think someone can speed run this game wait how fast
do you think you can speed run it probably really fast oh yeah yeah like i'll bet if you know exactly
what you're doing you can do it and like like you like like if you know exactly where the keys are
and exactly how to like solve the puzzle like if i had known if i had known that i had to like
fail at one of those cracks in the ground then like i could have beaten that mini game in like
a second and a half would have taken would have taken me uh damn it oh frustrating you should probably
go to the top one first like there's there's water in the way there's water fuck yeah
oh yeah it's really uh it's just uh okay okay it's just it's just getting there
where where what's that e there like it maybe it's an eight those those like
zero those like purple zeros and green zeros and like yellow zero i think it's a i think it's a
centipede because like in another room it was like centipede beware and there was like two of
those going around oh okay that's my yeah yeah i guess like the e is like the head
yes okay that's one down does it lead all the ones that have spawned from it
look they're just suddenly less now uh i don't think so
shit
damn it fuck like like me in that line did a delicate dance yeah and you know
but sometimes in a dance sometimes you lead sometimes you lead and sometimes you follow
and that time i followed i followed right into the grave yeah who will inherit your grave
jesus christ's second body when jesus comes back from the dead do you think he's gonna
have a buff body this time um yeah like he's gonna be like he's gonna be shit he's gonna be
he's gonna be like well he's gonna look like brad pit and fight club yeah he's not gonna be like
ripped jacks like girls don't like that he's gonna he's gonna be like he's gonna be like toned you
know i think like he's literally going to be brad fritt from fight club like he's just going
to look exactly like that yeah yeah yeah you like they'll be they'll be like they'll be he'll be like
hey i'm i'm back i'm back for vengeance and like steven spielberg will be like ah are you here to
try out for my new movie uh uh brad pit and fight club and he'll say yep well what what are the
benefits and you know the rest is history shit oh god i hate this i think you just have to be
brave i think you have to be aggressive okay oh you were right you were right it um oh god there's
another one okay let's see this door cannot open centipedes nearby but the centipede is fucking
in the room yeah but there's nothing in the room any oh no yeah there is there's like a little like
triangle yeah i want that triangle um okay try and what was the green one say up there
i don't know i haven't read it i gotta go back uh i mean it might be like there are shrubs nearby
maybe all right let's oh wait i can walk through this pink yeah pink boy oh yeah you're right
shrubs nearby no all right we can we can fix that
that's a little gardening shall we a little a little extreme gardening
let's fucking obliterate these pieces of shit a little overly zealous gardening yeah
a little racially motivated gardening yeah yeah yeah i feel that uh all right yeah oh god i have to
fucking deal with this goddamn sword all the time okay i found a thing that's good that's no
that's progress um go to that little side area you know what i can do before i go there i can um i can
like make myself a shortcut here like if i push this block into this water then that's a that's a
permanent shortcut sick as hell okay uh go this way go this way this way where is this
oh oh i've uh
oh oh you're you're you're you're this is like dark souls you can like see the map
we're like other areas of the map this this game is go on vooms koons work we're we're closed come
back between six and nine p.m. shit all of our out tours of the fairy kingdom end here at the gift
shop it's just smart business um well guess what it's it's five oh three p.m. you know what here let
me just adjust my fucking computer clock uh change date and time settings you might have to restart
oh no
we're closed come back between six and nine
all right you know what i'm just gonna leave this for now it's gonna leave this for now i'm gonna
change my date and time back uh uh Jesus this game so advanced you know it's like undertale
you know like it knows what you're doing even outside the game god dammit god fucking dammit
i don't have the cyan key i've never even thought of a cyan key before
uh all right all right all right well i've got a green key have i used the green key already
i don't know i can't i can't remember i there's a gray key which i don't know if i've used before
uh over here is just the blimp which like i don't think there's anything
i don't think there's anything whatever oh you know what i i can oh i can kill things now that
have the sword of course i can go on this blimp this is gonna change everything the the
straight is like stuck on like the clock for me oh here we go wait what i can't like like the screen
is like frozen for me really yeah but back when you hit the clock over and i thought you were just
there still well i'm not fuck hmm weird um here here i'm gonna leave the calm and come right back
okay
all right okay
you there
oh fuck there we go there we go sorry i hit i hit i hit yep yep i did
uh what can i say red is just more attractive put put put your put your screen back on again
oh all right hang uh let's see what the fairy the cockroaches seem to stand very still most of the
time maybe you can just run okay so they're cockroaches uh where is my fucking skype settings
call audio settings share screens here we go
uh oh delicious delicious incredible
what a lot of cockroaches a lot of cockroaches around here boy yeah just just like my real life house
just kidding folks i don't have cockroaches i have silver fish
mmm oh i can push i can push the boulder okay that's good it's like strength and pokemon
it's exactly like strength god remember hms um yeah i miss them i hate them i mean i hated the i hated
the ride system too should emotionally i agree with you but functionally it's so superior
i yeah i guess i guess it is it just felt like like i wish they had i wish they had taken something
bad and replaced it with something good instead of taking something bad
which is right you're so fucked yeah yeah yeah that's that's sucked ass okay whatever i can get
back there that's fucked ass no no no no not in this not in this neighborhood
hmm can't get away with that not in not in this good white christian neighborhood
hey uh when uh when you get to the next like loading screen let's uh switch back from commercial
break and then we'll go back to the show switch back from commercial break what are you talking about
well well you know uh so so so we can start the show this is just commercial break like before
the show starts oh yeah yeah yeah yeah like we're getting spots wait yeah what
excellent thank you
uh all right yeah thank you how wacky was that all right yeah yeah it was pretty um pretty random
pretty random pretty zany all right you want to switch back from commercial breaks yeah here we go
remember kids spax wrist contains elements which may be unsuitable for children okay
all right so we're back we're back from commercials
hello and welcome to tbap yeah yeah um i'm back i'm back baby that's what you say you say that's
two bitch brothers bitch about that's oh that's oh god it's been so long uh that's two best brothers
two best two best bros bitch about pony faggots on the internet and today's our this week's episode
was uh the last time i made a video people made fun of us so now we're gonna bring the
fucking fight to you you piece of shit now we're we're here but again people didn't just make fun
of us people were incensed people were incensed and offended and uh things got pretty personal
things got pretty personal and ugly things got real ugly on this little corner of the internet
for a while there yeah but but but now we're back it's me strawberry milk i killed you know
i killed keg he's gone he's dead never come back he's dead in canon yeah yeah yeah i remember i
remember when that happened yeah it was pretty funny i think at least yeah yeah it was in between
rowdy fuckers cop killers frog fractions one episode one and rowdy fuckers cop killers frog
fractions one episode two frog fractions two episode two yeah it was somewhere in that in that
wind time frame but but but now we're back now we get to talk now we get to you know
defend ourselves against the trolls that's so fucking harmfully like ruined our image
and made us go into fucking hiding because we were just so scared for our fucking lives that we
had to abandon our house we had it we like like when we got the death threats we had to like leave
our house and go to a hotel and stay with like with a friend because we were just so like you know
shaken up by the fucking threats we were getting we were real shaken up so someone said they were
gonna kick you in the dick if you ever went to do to brony con so yeah yeah yeah if i ever showed
my face with brony con again uh he was going to uh he was yeah kick me kick me in the dick uh that
was the threat jesus christ dude how are you supposed to live i'm i'm i don't know man like like i just
have nightmares about being at brony con now and i'm like oh no i gotta get out of here before it
yeah what the fuck 20 age jesus christ i was almost i just tried to do my real age but i couldn't
do it pale or lead colored nails indicate um shut the fuck up this isn't about frog factions
to anymore get up the video oh god all right fine fine uh let me use this professional show god
damn it how do we turn off the volume hang on uh syphilis if you miss another you can't possibly be
from 68 you're a kid shamming you for all right okay this is fine yeah now fuck it all right
let's get back okay back to business back to business all right let's let's talk about let's
talk about let's talk about probably the coolest brony of all time yeah the coolest brony of all
well you you should you should do it in uh the watch together yeah yeah yeah yeah i'm i'm just
getting the uh thing how do i how do i fucking here search your paste wait wait wrong wrong
video we'll get we'll get to him so so so we made a video calmly and sophisticatedly
disagreeing with some of the points that the brony community is we made we made some jokes
we had some laughs we said some we said some things that might be taken as disrespectful
but like you know i won't apologize for any of that we we we were we were we were just being
ourselves do we were just showing off for our our our natural god-given talents yeah and yeah and
by god if that's not you know if i'm gonna if we're gonna be trolled then i might as well go and
fucking kill myself yeah hello so here's one of the many the the many people who who who who
frequently and and indiscriminately illegally like against against against all laws of god and
man yeah um he yeah he had a lot to say this is going to be a very very yep yep here yeah let's
get into it i recently saw a disgusting display of just pasted in space right in and it's the
type it's actually not working for me for some reason wait for those of you who forgot it's
playing on um watch i i feel like you're not in the watch together we see it says here here i'm
i swear to god like my screen is showing me the watch together yeah yeah but yeah but my screen
isn't showing me the rods together hold on oh wait are you yeah are you are you the yugio brony
yeah okay yeah just restart then there was a duo is it working analyst who went by the name of
cake standard and phantom horn they starred in their own series known as two best brothers
bitch about ponies where they basically sat in front of their microphones and did commentaries on
the newest episode of mlp not personally not what tbap was i really think much is completely
mischaracterized it wasn't really presented in a way that was interesting more it wasn't really
presented in a way that was interesting as he shows a clip of two live action pony figures
rocking back and forth the sound of like the commentary yeah yeah like what's being shown here
is clearly not of any interest yeah just about any of any kind yeah like some like someone like
misanthropony couldn't fucking wrap his head around like this you know this took more work and has
more creativity than the entirety of misanthropony's entire life i agree um misanthropony look at
misanthropony's oc like like just look at misanthropony's oc to understand like the
utter depths like the utter depths of his of like the artistic what the fuck just like the
utter depths of like artistic abandonment and like lack what's like the lack of creativity
that he's that he like lives within yeah like there's nothing on display here that would make me
like believe that a human made it i would think it's like an ai or something yeah like an ai or
maybe a small animal like a bird or a dog yeah um yeah i hate him i did understand the appeal behind
their content at the time they were bringing something unique to the analysis community that
not a lot of people have thought of yeah it was a simple mini series wasn't interesting there was
something about its simplicity that gained at its own fan base thus becoming a huge part of
brony analysis huge part he he thinks he's so clever because he's saying like he's saying there was
something about the simplicity of it like press like press him on that and like what does he actually
mean like can you imagine him actually like meaning anything by that like like yeah this the simplicity
of the matter has nothing to do with it and i don't know what he's trying to describe by simplicity
what simplicity like we made jokes it was like yeah like it like was a review that's pretty simple
like it's way it was way it's way less simple than like the bog standard like fucking pony review
shit that was like you know common like what stood out about it was not its simplicity it was the way
it was different from the rest yeah the way it was presented and like the like like the actual
like timing and like editing and the things that made it different like like it wasn't it would
have been simpler to just do a normal review like with the pony in the corner but you actually like
put work into it and like made like jokes and like intros yeah yeah yeah so like really there's not
it's not the simplicity really is not the appeal no missanthropony uh but after season five their
content was starting to dwindle until eventually it just stopped i'm not even exaggerating when i
use these choice of words these two just disappeared from the face of the fandom without an explanation
completely inaccurate completely not not correct at all yeah there was in fact a lot of videos
explaining where they went and uh if you if you were self aware whatsoever then you would know
exactly how well to the pcp i mean there wasn't there wasn't a video on t-bat but like i don't
know why missanthropony is saying this because like he knows about the procrastinator so like
he knew where we went so like he can't have been confused and and and in like like like there were
obviously ways to get to know the pcp outside like like like even though there was nothing on t-bat
for an unknown reason yeah there was like you know my my deviant art and like my twitter and stuff
yeah and and like you know all those like like phantom plays where he's talking about the pcp
and the vapors and shit oh yeah yeah yeah uh so there's no way he dropped off that was a pony game
you were playing when you were discussing that there's you didn't drop out the face of the fandom
you were easily trackable and it's like and and and the mere idea that he like dropped off the face
of the fucking earth because you stopped making pony content like like because like because like
because this channel stopped uploading videos that's equivalent to me just i just vanished
without a fucking trace yeah there was like nobody could have found me no one completely
indescribable eventually it was discovered that the two decided to split up although they
what in contact with each other and they've been working on their own individual youtube
channels no phantom like it's just a weird way to characterize it it's just a weird way to characterize
what happens the the two split up the two split up but still keep in contact think about no if you
didn't know the situation how would that seem like we're just like we're just each doing things yeah
yeah we aren't yeah we like like imagine if you were got if you if you didn't know anything about
the pcp or tbap and you watch this video you would think that they like you and you and me
or keg sorry i had like a falling out but like and you like you're like you're like stop making
videos together when in fact you just like you just don't do tbap is is the point you just don't do
tbap yeah like all all of what he's saying is to say that we stop making tbap videos yeah like
that's that's all he needed to say here yeah and then oh shit saint who was a member of the horseshoe
crew eventually joined the procrastinator showing my consisting of the original horseshoe
crew as well as a few new why does he say that i joined i'm personally subscribed to the procrastinator
channel because i happen to be a fan of the content that is made by the people who are
part of this team then came the moment where i saw this video in my subscription box and this video
was literally so heinously awful that it almost made me want to unsubscribe from procrastinators
how dressed it starts fencing saint as he prefers these days along with this guy named
munchie i'm going to be talking about some some guy named munchie who like he's never heard of even
though he like follows the talking about every single thing forgive me for leaving anything out
but you have to understand this video is literally over four hours long and seriously who the fuck
has time to listen to four hours of these two guys talking about whatever's on their screen share
yeah yeah who would have time for that thing that like several thousand people
watch we are in the bottom corner right there yeah yeah more than five hours the video named rowdy
fuckers cop killers frog the way he says it i mean they do play the game for a good chunk of time
but literally at least 75 percent of what we see in this video has nothing to do with them playing
frog fractions so much he's hung up on this leading up to the parts that i actually want to talk about
is just this irrelevant commentary with a painfully boring tone and no direction the two sound very
bored and unenthusiastic about the stuff that they're doing which like look what's on look what's on
look what was on screen yeah the big the big baby boy interest from the like how yeah like we're so
bored like we're not having any fun we are we are not we like like we're so we're we're just doing
the right for these couples for money we have no we have no fucking personal and sensitive to do
whatsoever we've yeah we've sold out cold hard cash we sound bored profitable thing to ever exist
and we're only doing it just to sell out and you know make some green it's just amazing to hear
misanthropony like like drag on in his weird monotone like they seem very bored in the video
and it's very uninteresting to hear them talk for literally four hours like for him to say that in
that voice yeah in that voice and the the entire like like like how we like change subjects no rhyme
or reason is the point of the video is that it's not supposed to be a highly edited like like you
know like frog fractions let's play it's the right figures copies which is notorious for being long
and just for the entire show is dedicated to the chemistry of the host that is the point of it
and the video completely smashes your expectations like frog fractions so it's thematically relevant
yeah well i mean obviously all that's gonna be lost on this guy yeah but it's it's weird it's
it's amazing to me like how like he comes back to this point multiple times that like the video
is bad because it is called frog fractions but like not all of it is about frog fractions like
like that makes it bad it like that proves us wrong when that is in fact the point and we wanted
it to be that way yeah they showcase a very strong lack of enthusiasm and that's not a good thing if
you generally want the people watching your video to take it seriously don't want to take it seriously
it's a fucking comedy show is very very slow and there's a lot of parts that really should have
been edited out like if the words frog fractions is going to be in the title of your video you think
that the majority of its content would be relevant to the game they spend entire portions of the
segments just googling themselves and looking up pictures of babies
oh my god with no real rhyme or reason they literally feel like those annoying college students
who spend their free time looking up repetitive material on their computers this is how fucking
bizarre like what like they literally they literally seem like describes a totally innocuous thing
like these people like they literally they literally come off as though they're like
wearing pants and shirts like Jesus what the fuck are we doing we're we're we're college
students who are looking up images online we're looking up repetitive materials on our computers
like the fucking nerve the nerve and and i just want to say like he's going on now and he's
going to continue to go on for a while like criticizing the video as though like the video
being bad is like the point that he's like it's going to come out soon that like he's really he
actually has like a moral objection but for now he's like playing it coy like he's playing it cool
and pretending that he just thinks it's like a bad video and it's not entertaining yeah but like
the truth will come out he's just looking for excuses to shit on it because yeah he just knows
he doesn't like it for one specific thing that happens later yeah so he's just coming up with
like weird like buzzwords fucking he's yeah he's he's he's trying to scrape up he's trying to scrape
all the all the shit he could possibly fling at it he's he's like he's he's trying to he's just
gathering up as much as much ammunition as he can just to take us down a peg yeah because we did
release a video that he didn't like yeah yeah yeah and we should be punished and it was so bad he
almost unsubscribed from our youtube channel oh my fucking god dude it broke him into a fucking
brink of destruction like can you imagine can you imagine being bad upset with someone that you
would unsubscribe from their youtube channel oh okay continue video i have ever seen in my life
and i've been through smut boys channel after a bunch of more rambling that goes nowhere one of
which involving digi bros old time we finally get to them like totally relevant totally relevant
and at this point the focus of the video has gone way off due to the way the video is presented
up to this point it's very clear that they did not know what they wanted it to be about it's
just aimlessly going from one subject to the next without any meaningful segue between any of them
i mean imagine if i made a video named spongebob squarepants obstacle odyssey playthrough and i
play the game for 20 minutes and then the next three hours of the video is just me going through
youtube poops or random artwork on deviantart because i forgot to turn off the recorder
dead so we finally get into no no it's not like that it it's not that we let it we were like like
it's like he thinks we did this by accident yeah like like like we didn't mean to we like like like
like we wanted to have a frog fractions let's play and just play the game but but but due to the
same tip we just had we like due to our ineptitude minded that we just accidentally opened up this
the rift cafe wiki and just started just going haywire we said we just had no saying it whatsoever
and we were just completely the like the slaves of our of our aptitude minded destructive thoughts
we didn't know any better yeah there's just nothing we could do we just accidentally typed
in the rift cafe we just accidentally started going there and we were just the entire video
which was just supposed to be this really like tight concise highly edited let's play because i
know that's what he likes that's the only kind of let's play that he that he views is valuable
so that yeah yeah yeah that's obviously what we were going for too we also have the exact same
you know amount of taste that he has and in exact same way so that's obviously what we were going
for but you but just some just some stroke of of sheer misfortune we we we accidentally opened
up the fucking rift cafe and we just accidentally did all this yeah it's incredible that he can be
like a fan of the pcp and not understand the idea of watching a video that is just two people
in the pcp talking like where's the fucking disconnect here like what's not getting through
i went through a comment chain like like like like last night i was getting like like notes for
this video and i went through it like on the pony cast the the the uh video that the videos like
the podcast that uh jesse and uh hit play yeah yeah uh f not f and g are miss anthra probably
commented on a video that was it was like oh man this is a really good video i really enjoy this
which in and of itself seems like okay he like like obviously he obviously just doesn't like us
or he doesn't like what we said so that's fine it's not the problem he has no problem with the
like the content itself he just wants to you know fuck with us but uh the thing is in that video
jesse comments on this drama and like like doesn't call him by name but like calls miss anthra
weird and he just doesn't pick up on it like he's obviously what it is oh my god yeah you know
you know what here like here's what i okay like what what i know about miss anthra pony is that
miss anthra pony used to be a dick to like tom digi and mage and i think he even says this later
in the video like he used to be he used to like bully them or like call them out and like try and
do hit videos on them because he he like thought they were quote a bad influence like this is his
excuse and like i think what's probably but now he's like super apologetic and like feels super
bad and he's like he's a good boy now you know like he doesn't do that anymore so i think that
probably he at one point he probably like hated jesse at one point and like said nasty things about
jesse and then like someone smarter than him like told him to stop being retarded and then he felt
like super bad and super guilty about it and now he like did a complete 180 on jesse and like now
he thinks jesse is a great guy and a cool guy and like and like so he's not he's gonna like he's
gonna be nice you know like he's not gonna he's not gonna like have any problems with him because
he's been told not to that's my hypothesis yeah because because there's no way he could like
like just like think about it for a little bit and just like come to a different conclusion
like you just have that in his body he can't he can't think he cannot he does not have reason
no i don't i i don't think he does he has no good reason you might you might say you might say
awesome fucking shit into the brony fandom or the analysis community by using the rift wikia as a
source and if they really wanted to make a video ripping into the analysis community this is the
worst way they could have done it i mean it's just them browsing through an incredibly outdated
website and using it as a source to justify their criticisms towards these people i mean okay
considering that past analysis has no information on his tab at all i think it's safe to assume that
this website is long long dead and it certainly should not be used by people who want to make a
point okay first of all no no again he thinks we're coming at this from like a journalistic
standpoint no yeah like he mentions that we're using like the rift wikia as a source for our
bemusement for the brony community when when the only thing we're doing is to like we're like like
vaguely remind us of like our past like our past yeah yeah yeah like our source we're not like
reading this and then making a judgment based on that we're just remembering what happened and you
know we forgot about a lot of these fucking geeks and freaks a long time ago so we're just using this
to like remind oh yeah room lappers and yeah remember that osemer where they did that we didn't
like yeah that's like we have like we have like we have per yeah we have personal experience with
these people like this is not yeah yeah we're not like learning about this for the first time
yeah yeah yeah um although there is like there is one or two people that i'd never heard of
and like i said they were shit and like uh but like whatever like that's different the vast majority
and and and also i think even if we were using this as a source which we aren't yeah uh that would
still be valid because these are like what the people think about them like this yeah like somebody
wrote this is about it them yeah yeah like sure it's outdated but like i'm sorry like find me a
better source then yeah yeah yeah find me a fucking better source miss antherpony what would you
recommend that i use to rip into the brony fandom yeah and and and the only people that we make fun
of like just for it is because we don't like the website itself like the website itself is funny to
us yeah so like it's like it's like when we find someone who we the majority of time we just make
fun of them through the website as a source quote unquote we're just making fun of the website for
being terrible yeah he doesn't get it like he really he really just doesn't he let me
it's just it's just lost on him you know yeah like and i can't i can't believe that this guy
watches the pcp and still doesn't like get what the point of ratty fuckers cop killers is like
that like that doesn't make any sense to me it's just he just completely he will never not be confused
and he just doesn't know he's confused he's confused on the inside and he just doesn't know it
you're so right you're so right he's so confused he's confused about his confusion yeah he he he
thinks he knows things when in reality he doesn't know things and he knows he doesn't know things but
but who cares it doesn't matter like like like he i mean he's still gonna have an opinion like
he's still gonna form an opinion despite knowing that he doesn't know anything yeah yeah yeah why
not because why not what what what what could possibly go wrong good amount of time bitching
about shipping and the analysts and some of the artists and all of that dumb jazz and at one
point munchie asks ben saint how it's possible for anyone to still give a shit about mlp
then oh how is it there's nothing i hate literally possible
incriminating evidence still yeah yeah the proof is in the pudding shit about my little pony
i don't know i don't fucking know may i remind you this is coming from a guy who spent 34 minutes
of his life discussing taco bell with digi bro as if it actually holds any weight and because of that
we're supposed to take this seriously he says that he says that in a way he says that in a
voice that is like he's really got you like he's really caught you in a contradiction here
that that sentence doesn't make sense that does not that is not how you speak it's like
munchie said munchie said that he doesn't understand why people like tuna fish but over here he spent
34 minutes talking about how good salmon is and we're expected to take that seriously like i guess
yeah like okay okay so so we ask this okay okay there's a clip okay what i say is how can anyone
still care about mlp a seven-year-old show with a little to no substance the what's so ever that
we only watch like due to zeitgeist and perceived like lack of options on tv that's the only reason
anyone watched that entire fucking show yeah it sucks it's bad it's horrible it sucks i hate mlp
it's awful no one should watch it sure it's horrible so so so so i dare i dare to question why
anyone watching lp uh a fucking it like a meme a literal meme a literal meme show i i dare to
question what what what value it could have and then and then like he like shits on stealing your dad
as if that literally means anything if that has any bearing whatsoever first listen to your dad is
more like just it like you can call it a food review show when in fact it's just me and digi
making jokes and like the food review is like a backdrop much like almost all of our content is
about the chemistry of the hosts and not the actual subject matter itself that's the point of all of
our content maybe he said no maybe he didn't know that's the point and and you're welcome you're
welcome for me explain to it i mean of course he doesn't know of course of course he doesn't
understand that like listen to him look at him look at him and and and what does me making bad
content and not you know send your dad's the best show ever made but like if it if it was just dog
shit what she doesn't uh what would that do with mlp being bad yeah yeah what would that what would
that have to do yeah it's like it's like it's like like let's see you do better it's like yeah like
like the fact that you did anything that he doesn't think is good means that your opinion about anything
at all is worthless and like should be should be discarded immediately it's not even that i like i
reviewed like it's not that like i reviewed a show that he thought it was bad and he's like oh well
your tastes are just bad it's not like that it's not like i am fucking like like i just don't i can't
review shows correctly or something it's completely different like medium it's like how does my opinion
on food invalidate my opinion on a cartoon you did you did something completely unrelated
that he doesn't see the value in like therefore just like you're wrong about everything yeah
i don't fucking understand i don't understand what his point is or what he's trying to like get
across like he like he obviously think that's that's kind of like a weird but it's kind of like a weird
ad hominem like like the fact that you would do that like the fact that you would do that means
you're stupid and therefore we shouldn't take it seriously or something like like that's what he's
trying to do which is like terrible like even if even if he succeeded at doing that like it would
be shitty and embarrassing that he did but like he didn't even succeed because his point doesn't make
any sense it's it's indescribable it is okay continue they do eventually come across digibro's
page and they don't really say anything bad about him and i suppose that does make sense considering
that ben saint is friends with both friends but not not you though not really out of nowhere
ramble on how much ben saint really hates burning doughnut just because he saw his i was a little
hard on burning yeah he takes his artwork and proceeds to call him an idiot but what exactly
does he mean he literally says nothing about the burning doughnut except for how he sets up his
patreon he doesn't really say anything about the burning i literally self he just i literally
say nothing about the burning doughnut except for like a thing that he did well yeah here let it go
criticize it is what he does on the internet oh and speaking of okay okay okay so he's this this is
like this is what he says all he does is make fun of his patreon he doesn't make any he doesn't make
any points about the burning doughnut himself if he just criticizes the stuff he does online
do you understand the problem with that sentence do you like like like like like the like the stuff
you do online is not real like that's not what some that doesn't represent a person in any
meaningful way he doesn't like that stuff like that stuff is is like like that stuff is like above
criticism okay he doesn't criticize the burning doughnut he just criticizes what he does yeah
what the fuck like like like i mean that's insane that's insane from the get go but like even
overlooking how obviously retarded that idea is there's like you know i could be like well
that's what you're doing to us right now you're criticizing what we did on the internet yeah
you're criticizing a thing we put on the internet
uh are we are we are like the neurons firing are you putting a picture are we painting a picture
of your brain blast i he needs he needs a good brain blaster too he needs to have a brain in the
first place which he obviously doesn't he needs something like okay i i want to harp on this
because it's fucking insane yeah he just i just don't understand how it can be so
blatantly contradictory like and he also have like a script this way this is scripted i'm sure
i'm sure i'm positive yeah so how can you write okay you you think that you think that sentence
you write that sentence you record that sentence you edit that sentence yeah you do all of those
things and you don't catch how it's clearly a contradiction onto itself yeah and that it makes
zero sense he's you are you're you are criticizing the burning donut for the things that he's doing
online the things that he's doing online are making you make judgments based you are judging him
you are judging him based on the things that he does yeah yeah yeah yeah judging him based on his
words and his actions yeah and that's and that's and that's ridiculous like that's a ridiculous thing
to do yeah that's insane it is insane insane it is completely insane that is unbearable
um someone needs to stop him he needs to be fucking stopped right continue okay
patreon get used to ben saint going back to this because he bitches about patreon
like he spends a lot of time complaining about the amount of money that people are making on
patreon despite that he has no reason to do so why would he even want to he's clearly making more
money than at least half of these people so it shouldn't even be phasing him at all is it because
he just doesn't like the idea that these people are getting money for expressing their talents
because that's literally what it looks like while it's not the worst thing that i've seen so far
it definitely makes him look pretentious on pretentious it makes me look pretentious specifically
on a very heart-to-stomach level and from there they just spend a lot of time being complete
hold on pause the video like pause making me making the video yeah yeah yeah
what are we doing what are we doing he's making fun of me for the fucking minecraft thing
wait who is nate and hippo hold on oh when is that like net fucking
like like now he says he like he gave me the time i converted the time to my time zone and
then i guess i just fucked up somehow but i think that he's the one who's fucking up so i'm gonna
get mad at him good good i'm gonna look i'm gonna take a quick bro a quick
brony moment or broment for short i'm just gonna look through the fucking comments of
misanthropone's video um some pretty good ones uh ukrainian zygok says yeah fuck ben saint he
actually believes in the mirage of originality yeah fuck me oh um are we gonna leave the sin are we
gonna leave me like getting mad at hippo for the fucking frog fractions video oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay okay that's fine wait wait mad mad at me right now this isn't t-bap anymore like
yeah t-baps off for a second i don't understand you're mad at hippo because of the frog fractions
video i thought you were mad at him about that minecraft yeah yeah yeah that minecraft oh man
this this comment by brony buck if you make good on that closing statement the closing statement is
that he's gonna kick me in the dick if you make good on the closing statement you'd be my best friend
favorited by misanthropone i just want to say that brony buck is a confirmed bigot and homophobe
and um he is my enemy i hate him like i personally hate him and like he knows that i hate him and i
and and and he's a like he's just a really bad person like just personally like this anyway um
this this this comment by shell dog by shelly d it oh my god it's like it's like several pages long
um i mean i like that he's calling i like that he's calling misanthropone retarded which he is
and i guess he's like i guess he's like more or less defending me but like man that's a lot of words
um oh no it wasn't on this video it was on the fngr video that um uh that kaze and uh and uh
what's the other guy vita the kaze and vita we're talking about you that was good we'll get to that
yeah uh a lot a lot of good comments i really i really enjoyed reading the comments on these
like a handful of people were like oh you're right ben sain is a dick and because he's mean
but like a lot more people were like misanthropone you're fucking stupid and that was very satisfying
hey are we are we ready to continue oh yeah so
oh and then someone called gushing toilet says it's fucking hilarious that you made a 20 minute
video about this without finding out munchy equals tommy oliver which i don't know if he was just
trolling if he's just joking about that yeah oh well no no like like someone says i forget who says
that i think fngr says that i know that that was a thing that someone like like someone thought that
i was tommy oliver probably misan not mis probably fngr like that's something i would believe
fngr would think despite like knowing us yeah uh yeah fuck here i i i have to get these fucking
stupid minecraft retards set up so bad so bad i'm fucking
god can you imagine playing minecraft like the fucking baby game i hate minecraft actually it
sucks minecraft really sucks the worst fucking thing to ever exist it sucks ass it's stupid and uh
uh i hate it i don't ever want to play it again but maybe i will anyway just so i can be friends
with my friends yeah yeah
logs
okay fucking jesus christ
it's it's this is my my my my folder how i plans to overthrow the pcp
hey show me i want in all right yeah i really want mad shit yeah i really want i really want to um
defeat everyone else everything we know it's everything that we said last time was a total
facade and it's just a front for us to get more power yeah like we got to kill them with kindness
like we got to pretend that we want like to be friends like we want to pretend like you know we
want oh oh no no no let's let's let's get close you know let's get close and then when we get close
we get in for a hug and then just bam just pull out pull out our guns just pull out our hand guns
and our shotguns and just just fucking in them please all right i can't fucking find the world
i'm going to kill myself i'm just going to kill myself i'm just going to kill myself why because
i can't find the fucking i know i have it somewhere instead of finding i can't find like the world
that i used for the fucking thing oh my god miss antherpony called us junkies
what in this comment thread by kurt wilkinson yeah miss antherpony says you must be a pretty boring
person to think that nearly five hours of two junkies aimlessly internet browsing on someone's
screen share is a good use of your time uh miss antherpony i'm literally the most straight
person you will ever meet i turned down so many offers for alcohol and smokes during an expo
i'm so fucking happy about myself i mean i'm wondering if miss antherpony even knows what a
junkie is yeah i mean i don't like he hasn't like there's no reason why he would use that word
unless he just is confused about it like he's confused about so many things yeah
all right here i almost have the minecraft server up you just have to move all these pictures of
the star of david oh my god what the watchful pony wow just that part where they start talking
shit about keyframe i survived lily peat cr and so many other shitbags in this community without
even flinching but this was so scummy that i literally had to pause the video and take a break
i am dead serious serious is misspelled even lily peat wouldn't do something that slimy
you're done fucked up i'm glad this guy gave up on pony because his attitude would have done
nothing but give not just the bro analysis community a bad name but make the entire of
brony look like assholes wow you don't need help with that certainly wouldn't want to do that
munchie what are you doing i'm sorry we're on air yeah i well i'm hoping we we stop
we stop being on air no no this is all going in i i have to get the fucking stupid minecraft
the hippo i know you're going to be watching this i know that you and ney are going to be
watching this i want you to know that i fucking hate you i want you to know that i will never be
your friend ever again i will never talk to you ever again after this day thank god i want you
to know that i'm leaving the pcb after you're gonna be like why why did munchie leave the pcb without
saying yeah yeah he left the chat and then like and then you're gonna watch this video you're gonna
be like oh that's why because i was just like whatever i just like whenever i get around to
making this video like weeks later like oh is that why i have to i have to prepare the spawn area
how much fucking work do you have to do just like just like a little bit just like a
just like don't worry about it basically i'm worried man i'm worried like we're losing like
we're proving misanthropony right right now but like not having yet by not having tightly tightly
edited content
yeah i i i have like the world file for him
so like here i'm just gonna make like a r
yeah here i'm gonna i'm gonna make a r i have to make a compressed zip folder
it's just it's just so sad it's just so sad that people
like people like shelly d and like fng are are like still in like they know that the brony
analysis thing sucks and is stupid and like they make fun of it like they make fun of it and call it
what it is and yet they're still in it you know
like they're still like like they just don't understand that like
they can leave like i don't think it's an option for them like they just don't understand
like i mean maybe they'd all have to like collectively decide it
but whatever you know no no of course not like i guess it's because i guess because like they're
all friends and like it's what they're doing so like the rest of them are gonna keep doing it
or something something like that i like fucked up somehow and like i deleted well i did i didn't
leave anything but like but like like i can't host the server fast lee so i'm just gonna send them
the like roar of like the like the server like i'm just gonna like send them the server world
so they can make their own server but but i know i know for a fucking fact that they're gonna be like
what how do i set up a minecraft server there's no possible way i can figure out how to do that
like there's no way i can just google how to make a minecraft server it's literally easy it's not
even like i did it very fucking easily oh my god you just fucking just do that man let them let
them fend for themselves what have they ever done for you not one thing
and like i i i did like make i did like say like yeah i would be here so i feel kind of bad but
like this is like yeah oh oh man hippo career i don't know nothing about hosting the server
yeah well i mean i don't know how how complicated it is i don't know how to do it
here do you want to get hippo on this recording so i can i can walk him through getting a
minecraft server while we're on air oh my god yeah sure why not
do
Alright guys, I'm letting them know.
You're letting who know what now?
I'm letting Hippo know he needs to come in here, but I don't have Skype, download it.
We have to get Hippo to download Skype so we can be on.
No, this is good, no this is good, this is what we want.
This is commercial break.
Do you have frog fractures?
Just go to frog fractures and start playing more.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
Pretty good.
Pon Luffing Ulysses S. Grant used this political slogan in 1872, take a-
I think it's Grantham No Quarter.
Pretty sure.
Grantham No Quarter, oops, you blew that one, okay, he who cannot lie does not know what
the truth is?
Oh, Otto von Bismarck unified this collection of territories, the German Empire.
Oh no no no no no no.
None of these are right.
You sure it's not the German Empire?
No, definitely, yeah, no, definitely not the German Empire.
Definitely not Bismarck, definitely not Belgium.
I'm fairly certain it's not rugby union, but you can try that it's not the rugby union. I
I know for a fact that it's not any of the other ones. It's the German Empire's what they had after he did that
Yeah, yeah, because because he unified them. He made them by unifying these collection of territories
It's not like what is it called after he unified those territories like I think it is I think the difference is academic
I'm pretty sure that like he unified a region that then became the German Empire. I'm going with German Empire. Oh
Look at that. Oh, look at that. Look who knows a finger. I was I know I know my shit. They were just gay
Everyone had a hip-hop to the call
Okay, women. Is he gonna is he recording? Yeah, I think so women in the garden is a painting by I
Don't know I'm gonna look it up
For somebody that can't see his name on here
What's this is it given? Oh, it's a given. Okay. It's Claude Monet
The phrase gas pipes
Hello hippo
My god
Is he here? I don't hear anything wait what is that him? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you're really quiet. What what?
You're on can you hear us? Yeah, but are you recording?
No, okay. Okay, you're you're on from fractions to because I didn't want to explain to you
And then we would have downtime and I have to explain to you on fact for our actions, too
So here's what you do. I'm gonna give you the file right now for Minecraft. Oh
Okay
Very confused. No, it's fine. This is good though
This is so the pincers are unique among glasses and I
All right. Meanwhile, this is we're gonna we're gonna we're gonna have downtime, right?
All right, so what you're gonna do is well while you're doing this you're gonna want to you are on Windows 7, right?
Yep
No, no hippo hippo. I am. Yes. Oh, okay. Okay. Oh, sorry
That was been first because I can't I can't tell go go to and like I go to like open up like the start menu and type in I
P
C O
in
F I
G IP config
The temperance fountain is a good. Oh, sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. You want to you're gonna want to see MD Edward
And then you're gonna do I
In what's your type and see you type in cmd.exe
Okay
All right
I'm looking at
Okay, okay. Now now you're gonna want to look at for IPv4 address
All right, I got that. Is this streaming by the way, you shouldn't be streaming this. I don't think
Okay, it's fine
Then type in that address you see into your like your like browser. You're like internet browser. All right
well, I can't stream that but
Yeah, I know I'll just I'll just turn it off. It'll be the be the this will be part of the frog fractions
So we're being streamed right now, right? Like like like this part of frog fractions will be on the street, right? Yeah
Yeah, okay, good. Nice. All right, so I type that into
Hey, just a little preview
I had to play mess that too so we could advance and fraud fractions too in this of YouTube video
This YouTube video will be the best YouTube video ever made
So here I am like these questions are like the hardest they're so hard
Okay, okay. So so it's it's in there and when when you open that up
IPv4 address I type that into my browser. Yeah, and then like it didn't happen. It didn't work
I don't know. Maybe a rarity. Yeah
Donald Denny became widely known for his I got there's so many different IPv4 addresses
Okay, be I IPv4
V4 a Scottish strong man. Okay
So so you typed in oh, wait. No, this I'm just I come in the lowest one
They come as a boon and a blessing to you know what you might actually want to use might you want to use default gateway?
I'm just trying something else
That didn't work
No, you know what you hear here go to the IP config thing like that like window and then try and type into your browser
What is an effective treatment for hysterectomy
Not not like the words default gateway as in like those numbers and then yeah, yeah for hysteria
You should get like a brink screen that says what's your password you?
Yes, yes, I did it
What at least that's how it is for netgear. What do you have? What's your what's your router?
BT oh, I got I got a thing saying BT. Oh
Oh, it says that doesn't ask for a username or password. I
Don't think so. Okay, so you're just in there like try and look around
It'll probably like it'd be an advanced advanced saying somewhere something like that find a place. It says port forwarding
I
Might be in like a few for me for me in netgear. It's
Advanced then advanced setup then port forwarding slash port triggering. That's what it is for me
But it might look probably different Pico
This is this is fucked. This is
The fact that you're trying to explain that in a tutorial to the I just want to play Minecraft with my friends
You couldn't turn the server on. I mean, it's funny
I mean, I mean, I couldn't do that because like I like I actually like reset like my server
Like I would have just done that but my like my like the world is fine
But the actual like server itself doesn't have like the right like like settings in it
Which I guess I could do right now and it actually be really easy. So I guess let's do that
But wait stay here in case it doesn't work all right
You can also you can just stay here if you want to get Nate on here
You could just stream minecraft and then the Minecraft stream will be in frog practice to that would be pretty funny
Oh
Hey, by the way, what do you think about far corrections to just so you have that on like record?
So when Santa reporting can see this video and then he'll be like, oh my god, he likes it
What do I think about for impressions to I know no no for corrections one like the video like our video
I think I talked about it in my own stream and he's seen that because he followed my my my YouTube for that
So he knows, you know
He knows whatever it was I said
Yeah
Make sure I'll find
All right, I hope you fucking god. Oh, yeah, I'm trying to do three
online mode
Fuck fuck Jesus fucking Christ. Oh, yeah by the way, I got really mad at you earlier like I was like
I'm gonna kill hippo
Why did I get mad at you and you were like that? I didn't do anything wrong. Yeah
Yeah
It's fine though. We're best friends. I'll never not be I'm gonna kill Nate still though
All right, all right here here, let me try this try trying it's it's gonna it's gonna be like loading
It's like try it in a second
Yeah, sir, all right, I'll tell you when you like start
All right, yeah, try now try now. All right the turning on game capture
Join server
Yeah, okay good
All right, so so yeah, so uh, yeah here get the fuck out of here so we can go back to prog practice, too
Get the fuck out of oh, right. All right later. Oh, I'll be a fun shrieking. What? Okay?
Imagine what's gonna be like he's gonna like watch this video and then he's gonna be like, oh my god
That was me like from a while ago
It's gonna be crazy Nate, I mean Ben are you there wait? Oh, did he leave? Yeah. Yeah, I've been I've been playing frog fractions
We gotta you bet we gotta do the show. Oh, yeah. Yeah, right um
Okay, done
Let me just turn the let me just turn the fucking volume off on the on the frog fractions
Okay, I don't hear this this jaunty sitcom music anymore. Yeah. Ah, all right
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
Ms. Anthropony. All right, here we go more
After Wolf they rip into doing critics saying that he didn't go for me
I didn't go for me. Oh the video started with him saying fucking assholes. No, here here here. Here. Let me refresh the page, okay?
My dog wants me to go. Yeah, it's restarting the entire fucking thing. God damn it. I'm at like eight minutes
You're what I'm at eight eight minutes and four seconds
five
seven seven
Get used to playing for you now. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I love it. Okay. Yeah a lot Josh scorcher
Mr. I love her
Munchkin FNGR lightning bliss Rosie severe sweet. What that's seriously you went after Rosie severe
What the fuck was she gonna do to you? Oh?
How could we how could we go after the I don't even have a
Rosie severe
Cuz he's a kid
Like I'm not blaming him
I'm not blaming him for being terrible and being useless and for him being worthless and for his content being shit
I'm not blaming him for any of that then why the fuck are you wasting your time?
criticizing him
See the thing about wooden wooden sword is like I went to his channel later and I watched his videos and like well
I didn't think they were good. I thought they were perfectly like fine
They were they were just like bog standard like you know goofy YouTube yeah, and I was like well
I mean, yeah, like there's worse people
There's it's still shit cuz it's pony shit cuz he's making pony reviews, you know, there's inherently bad
Yeah, what he's doing isn't there like brute force like with yeah, yeah, yeah, it's an uphill battle
Now I understand there are a lot of people who like and dislike these analysts for different reasons
But the way that Ben saint is doing it
He really doesn't give us a lot to work with like the way that he just kind of slurs on his sentences
As he talks about these people really makes it seem like he doesn't know much about them at all
Which right from the bat doesn't make him very resourceful for this
criticizing a speech impediment which I don't even have yeah and like
like like I
Just I just can't understand like we know these people it's especially you like I know of these people
But you've taught these people like yeah, you know you know them
Yeah, you are like like where the fuck does missanthropony get off telling me that I don't know what I'm talking about like yeah
I have I have like personally interacted with these people before
It's disgusting like it's really disgusting that he thought he had any fucking grounds to say any
He's making money you're not anything what in fact he is the one who knows absolutely nothing about the video
He's watching he just does not understand a single fucking thing about the appeal or the draw of it or even what the video is
He just does not understand. He's not understand. He really really
Is just like he's just literally retarded. Let's just let's just put it right out there like he's actually retarded and there's something wrong with him
He just he just is not smart. He just is not a smart man
No, oh, and they also not perceptive
Mr. Enter doesn't have a Pony OC despite that. He actually did have a pony. Oh heaven forbid on a video
I really fucked up. It was also just on a thumbnail and yeah, I was just really starting to get bored
Like I can't say that I'm getting upset with this video. It doesn't piss me off. It's just so boring
It's just I don't make an example. I don't make this video entertaining
So they start talking about Vita and at some point they go to his channel
Oh, he's got oh, he's got a little fucking video of him with the key frame key frame and puzzle
Oh key frame fucking key frame. Oh great. This stick is gonna start talking about key frame. I wonder how this is gonna go
Let's let's fucking talk about key. Why did he bother making that?
Oh
Way to show us how you're willing to look down on people then personally criticizing key frame and mocking her patreon
I seriously cannot figure out how I like it any worse from there. Why? Why is that?
Yeah, yeah, yeah like
like
Like just like just like with burning doughnut. He's like it's like I've incriminated myself by criticizing the wrong aspect of a person
And also not only that which we've already explained how that is making sense
Like why why now? Why not any of the other like like he's just mentioned by name the brain
Like he's been he mentioned like them in like like a list like oh, I look impossible
I don't fucking doctor will but he didn't go in like like this is like he goes in like oh my god
He's talking about this about key frame. Like why is this any worse than you know the other people?
You know why it's because it's because he had some personal thing
He had some like personal connection to key for it because someone told him because someone told him
It was a big deal and shouldn't be joked about you know
It just goes to show that he just doesn't like he like he doesn't actually care about these like the things that we're saying
He just cares that he like like he wasn't told they supposed to care when we make fun about Kim possible or about Dr. Wolf
We're not he wasn't he wasn't like informed that's bad as well
He only knows that it's bad. He's we're talking about key frame and that specific instance
I think that even worse. I think that probably like
Like Miss Anthropony gets mad and indignant when someone else does something that like he has done and been scolded for
like
He like he gets upset about about like his path like the fact that he was mean to lethal or a mage and stuff
Like I think that maybe like maybe like he was mean to key frame and someone told him like dude
That's not cool because this is serious and now he's like oh now
He knows like this is serious and if anyone else does it I'm gonna fucking step in and be like, you know
Justice, you know, yeah, like that's that's my that's my headcanon at least
Yeah, is that he's just like like he's been scolded for this before so he's like I made them
I learned from my mistakes because later on in the video
He does go into bit like like I learned from my mistakes, but these guys didn't
Yeah, fucker. I'm here
She comes in she's there for like a week
She makes like one video and then and then on with the waterworks on with the fucking
Oh, no, suddenly. I'm really poor and I'm getting and my family is abusing me and and oh, no
My life is ruined. Oh somebody help me and then they do and then the fucking doesn't people pledge to her patreon
Get her like I don't know like a hundred bucks a month or something and probably they fucking give her money to like
I don't know she's got a bunch of money and now she's been for a while
For a while there fucking key frame was making more than on patreon than me and it fucking ate at me
Thank God
Yeah
You know that's
That that's a thing that's a thing that Josh Scorcher used to do like he would
He would quote unquote not swear like he wouldn't call you an asshole
He would call you an a apostrophe apostrophe hole like like it like it's any better
Yeah, like he's not just like he's not just calling at you
But like with like them the moral high ground of like oh, but I didn't actually say it. That's bizarre like yeah
Like I was gonna call him the C word
Okay, so we know that you wanted to call him a cunt. How does that that has why didn't you just say it?
Yeah, why like you don't have any reason to not say it. It's one like
That would have just been better because it means you're not a fucking weird coward was weird such a weird coward
Like he's misanthropony is such a coward. It's amazing. He's just like slimy and gross and untrustworthy and just completely
He just doesn't have any values or morals whatsoever
Only those have been like only only those worlds which have been just imposed upon him
And he doesn't understand whatsoever and are completely impersonal and he just he just follows like oh, I'm not supposed to swear for no reason
Yeah, just yeah, he doesn't have any he doesn't have any like critical thinking or like higher level like like meta like meta
Thinking skills like he doesn't have any like he doesn't have any like ethical like principles that he follows
He just has like rules that he's like learned rules that other people have told him. That's that's my takeaway
All right, he clearly knows that the keyframe movement was a thing and yet
He's talking about it like it was just a complete scam despite all the evidence pointing out that it's not bro
Yeah, I can understand your detachment from the brony fandom in recent years
But you are really starting to trend on show me show me any evidence
Like like he's claiming there's evidence, but he doesn't give any of it. Yeah in the comments in the comments
I think he was like, oh, I wouldn't I don't want to give any evidence because I don't want to like divulge keyframes personal
Shit and well, no, how am I supposed to see?
Well, I guess I'll just take your word for it then
No, faggot
This is another person who like
Like keyframe because she had like a sad tear jerky like oh, I feel so bad for myself fucking
Moment with dr. Wolf. I'm pretty sure this person got like I don't know some fucking money out of it too or something
Play that again
Like keyframe because she had like a sad tear jerky like oh, I feel so bad for myself fucking
Moment with dr. Wolf. I'm pretty sure this person got like I don't know some fucking money out of it too or something
He's so mad
Okay, it was bad enough for you to muck that situation once but twice you seriously had to go back to it twice
Why wasn't he this mad the first time? Yeah?
Like like like okay, it's like if it's so bad
Why did it take me doing it twice to really make a mess? Yeah, like I
Just just another weird rule
I guess just like it sounds like something bad like or like so horribly bad just once and it's fine
But if they but if they say it again
Then then you know they really mean it and then you then it's okay to criticize
Yeah, no, I was going to do some kind of over-the-top yelling or some kind of really angry facial
Oh, is it coming to show you how is it about to happen? I am with you right now, but there are no words
There are no facial expressions that could possibly
Capture how pissed off I am right now the only thing that could possibly and appropriately
Represent how pissed off I am right now is this one clip from injustice gods among us
Forget the doctor video. I don't even know I don't even know what to say about that. I
Don't even know
Ben it's just it's just a mate like like he's like how
How can I like how can I put like the biggest fucking exclamation point on like what I'm saying here?
Like how can I really can like the like the most the strongest
Convance of the the feeling that I have like what is what is the most heartfelt sincere
expression of this feeling
Okay, I want you to really really ponder. I want you to ponder and think and reflect. Yeah, okay
So he says that he could like make a big stink about it
Like, you know like like I guess he has some sufferers where he knows that it's like out place
We want to really emphasize it
But the only way he like it comes off is the only way he knows how to express himself is by just
Using a clip from a video game like yeah, that's exactly those sort of terms
We're like like he wants to like what what video game moment made him feel this like he made him like think about
How angry something is that one thing from justice gods among us like I that just feels so
Low functioning, you know, yeah, it feels like he saw that scene and just was impressed by like the anger on display
And like never forgot it. Yeah, I was like really really impressed by it and like
Was and so when he thought like I'm angry. How can I explain? I remember the time Superman was really angry
Here here we go
Just he can't express himself
Doesn't know how he doesn't know how to act or think or feel no, I mean this is like I
Mean I we watched a couple of his other like reaction videos
Like we watched through the video or where he like reacts to like the the the MLP movie trailer and how he like
Started giggling like just like when Pinkie Pie appeared on screen like just Pinkie Pie showing up and being seen he just started like
He just started giggling like a girl like a little girl
And it's like this is the kind of person that we're dealing with like he just
He's very enthralled by media of all kinds and yeah, he that's how he chooses to communicate
Yeah, yeah, like like very low functioning very low
Missing throw a pony could he would talk exclusively like mule and from Homestuck in just Tumblr gifts
That's how his ideal communication would work. I imagine yeah, like no words
Just move like like just moments from movies strung together to make a sentence
Yeah, I just hate him I just hate how he looks like oh, yeah, I just hate his OC
Let's talk about how shitty his OC is for a second. Okay, it's just really bad
It's like it's really bad like it's just Pinkie, but like bad
It's like I just I hate how it's but his OC is a rip-off, you know, I can't I can't fucking stand that
Anyway, that's that's kind of a side of the point not not everyone can have like be like an artist and like make a good OC
I guess I get that. Yeah, well, even though I think the art of making an OC is disgusting
However, I understand that for some reason you may want to do it. Yeah. Yeah, there are reasons
This is one of the worst OCs I've ever seen this I actually think you know, I actually think
Miss Anthroponies OC is like really close to tune critics in terms of like my least favorite pony OCs
Like if they're both like in the extreme leagues
Yeah, like like like like it's just the red
It's just the red because he knows it like red looks cool because it's like evil. It's like yeah
It's like it's like an evil color. So I'm gonna use a red because I'm like I'm like I'm like morally gray
I'm like, you know, I consider myself the least gay
It's just like he took he took sad pinky pie and then just like tweaked it in ways that made it so much worse
And was like done. I'm satisfied with this
What is that key mark by the way? What is that? I don't I don't know
Like is it supposed to be like comedy and tragedy because like it's not he's this isn't comedy. This is only tragedy
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't know man. I don't know what it's supposed to be
I guess it probably means something real retarded. And you just have to ask
Like an angel of death. He's like a death merchant. He's gonna like you like like pop a cap in your ass
But like not ask like like a asterisk asterisk because he can't yeah, his mom is on the phone
Yeah
When I when I said that for did I say apostrophe when I meant? Yeah, okay. Okay. Okay. Well, excuse me
Fuck me F F apostrophe CK me
Mm-hmm
God you want to keep going? Yeah. Yeah, so bad
The key frame movement happened two years ago
And that's not including the ten years prior where she was struggling to not get killed by her mother or worse
The only reason she's still alive is because by some miracle her shitty father is a slightly
Less shitty person if you still think that any of us were making this up while it was happening
I still have that video that was uploaded on DeWelstonators channel saved onto a flash drive in my room
Before it was put as unlisted or private
I can mail it to you whenever I can provide it that I have permission from key frame or wants to mail me a video
He wants to mail me a video as proof of
Something like I'm just really unconvinced like yeah, maybe that like maybe there is a real
Maybe there is a real problem here that like I don't know about but like he's really not convincing me like it's like
He keeps alluding in fact out there
It's just so plainly and like like just get just everyone was about key frame when in fact I okay first of all
I don't know about key frame. I don't even know who key frame is so I don't know anything about that
But I'm assuming I'm assuming that it's not that easy to find out information of this because you aren't providing any evidence
What so ever you're just saying that you do have
Yeah, yeah, there's secret information that he alone has yeah
That explain how this isn't a scam
Yeah, like I never even said it was a scam
I just said that like she just like people gave her a bunch of like pity money and like
Now and now she's hot shit even though there's nothing special about her
Like that's all I was saying which is true, and I'm not gonna walk that back ever
and
Yeah, what does he want? He just just the way just the way that they allude like oh, it's so bad. Oh, it's so it's like
Is anything that bad like the way you talk about it? It's like it was the second fucking Holocaust, you know like like
Don't fucking don't fucking sit here and tell me oh, it's so bad
I'm not gonna tell you how bad it was, but just trust me. It was that bad
Yeah, just just leave trust me leave me alone, you know shut up. No, I don't trust I don't trust you like like he like
Okay, first of all
There's no like like there's no like way to gauge that so like like he obviously just like like got caught up in the zeitgeist
Like with watching my little pony. He was just like he just he probably just heard some things
They're like yeah, like he frame has some bad parents and I got telephoned and then and then he just just believes things
I mean, you know, I don't I don't know. I don't know what I'm sure. I'm sure. Yeah, I don't know
I don't know what the truth is, but I do know tell us
Yeah, and I and I am sure
And I am sure that that Miss Anthropony believes things uncritically
So like I'm not even if he told me the story like I wouldn't believe it like I would need someone who's not stupid to tell me
Yeah, I
Want to know I mean, you know, I don't really want to make fun of someone but like for no reason
But it just seems it like he just will not he just won't tell us
He won't like here's like the like the you the fucking link to the YouTube is where it
Proves all this stuff is happening and like he like explains the story about like I don't even know what it
I don't know what the keyframe situation is. I assume it's something like parental abuse. I don't know
happening and
And Miss Anthropony is not forthcoming with the details. So
It's not I think we've done our due diligence. Yeah
I'm gonna fuck around here. Okay. I am just not this is a very very very very very
Very touchy topic to this day. I still have a hard time looking back to it and I'm
he
He is traumatized
by the keyframe situation
situation that
Probably didn't happen to him. No happened to keyframe
He's trying he's not talking about something that like happened
He's he's traumatized by someone else's problem and it's bad that we're triggering him
He has nightmares about it. Like like he is really held up on the fact that he knows he know he he
I don't get the I don't get the feel that he was like
Like I'm assuming do the fact that I've like seen some stuff like this where it's like there was like some like task force of like
Kickstart or something assuming is happening. I'm assuming that this is all assumption because again, I don't know and he won't tell us
I'm assuming that he just kind of like saw the kickstarter and like saw that things were going down that people were trying to help
I think he like talked to friends of hers or something. Yeah, that's I think he's friends with her boyfriend
and
So he's upset that he knows about something bad that happened
Yeah, and that's the extent of his involvement with it. Yeah, he just he heard about it
Yeah, you heard about it sure that a lot of people have a hard time looking back to it, too
Because it was that bad the heart. Oh my god
Struggling to keep my mind together
listening to all of those horrifying stories and
His his trauma of hearing the horrifying stories. Yeah, I
Don't I don't I mean it all right
Yeah, he's so empathetic that like he he felt it even more acutely than keyframe herself
Yeah, he was the real victim. So so that proves that it's so bad
But yeah, because he felt bad because he heard stories that proves that key
That's just how serious this is and how we shouldn't be fucking with it. Yeah
Do you get off claiming that her situation was a stunt to gain popularity I didn't
Using it as an excuse to bitch. I just think it was milked again
Now I will admit that I really wasn't that much of a better person when I started out
I was being really really horrible
Judging people despite that. I really didn't know anything about them because of some fleeting assumption
That influence yeah, yeah
To this day, it really means a lot to me that after I was given another chance
I was able to train myself to know and he made such he made so much good out of that extra chance
She was given knowing like look what he's done was wrong for me to assume that lethal Aurora mage or golden fox
Or Tommy Oliver were a bad influence because I only looked at their content through a one
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I don't know what he's talking about again
I know that I know that he was a dick to lethal or a mage, but that's like the ex why do I keep calling her lethal?
I know that he was a dick to mage. I don't know the details. Okay, but I want to harp on here
It's like that he got mad at them for being a bad influence. Yeah a bad
Influence I cannot imagine
Anyone thinking that about mage like Tommy like I know people have they had their divisive opinion like some people didn't like Tommy
He was because for whatever but mage
Who okay, who would think that sure you're but you're taking that criticism at face value, but you're like thinking
Okay, yeah, how are they bad influence? Yeah a bad influence though
Oh, yeah, like is a problem like the fact that he is upset that someone may be a bad influence
Oh, my little pony brony analysis community
Like that that's even on the list of crimes that someone can be guilty of exactly. Yeah. Yeah possible
because they're making fucking YouTube videos about analysis of my little pony they
How who are they influencing who are they too bad influence?
Anyone how could they bad influence anyone? I wonder if he means there are bad influence within the community or like to people watching
You know like which like what specifically is the grievance here? I am I am honestly curious like what the fuck
Any of this could have possibly been about what does it mean? How could we?
like okay, okay
How could like yeah, okay, Tom like mage obviously did nothing wrong and there's nothing
Even viable there to talk about Tom
What did he do that could even be construed as a bad influence like like he'd be broke honestly and them
But a bad influence on leaving the fandom leaving the fandom on bad terms
And I but I think it was before that like I think I think it was before Tom left
And before that I think the only thing is like
criticizing the show and maybe being a little hard on like Brony culture
being like bad
Influence not being a bad person not being a bad person not being mean or like not any of those criticisms being a bad
Influence on people you are badly influencing someone. How?
What does that mean Tommy never had this video that was like guys you should do this guys this is this is how you should act
What does it mean
I knew I wish I knew I wish I could get a little window
Into the mind of like you know just like a fucking insect like this, you know
Just a small little you know aside leaving the fandom
That doesn't exist. That is not a real thing that someone can do leaving fandom is a useless term
Yeah, I agree because you don't but it's real but it's real to him. It's real that like no one in
No one not a single person
Wakes up one day and says you know what I've had it
I'm not going to enjoy my little pony anymore. I'm just I'm you know
I just I just I just decided I will not partake in my little pony. I'm over. I'm going to leave the fandom
It's going to be over. I will I will not it's like people who leave the fandom quote-unquote
Just don't just kind of like I like oh well, you know, you know after a while I've kind of done all I can do
I don't I'm not really feeling anymore. I'll just make some other stuff. It's not like you're not like leaving it
You're not like leaving behind an interest
You are just deciding on like a moment to my moment basis
Maybe maybe I don't really like feel that strongly about this anymore. Maybe I don't have anything to say
That's all you're doing. You're not like making a point to leave the fandom
That's people the people like this like they see it as like a fucking lifestyle that has to be like actively maintained
And simply an interest
Yeah, yeah, like like it's like their personal little garden and it has to be like cultivated
You know and it has to be cold like like like malignant influences need to be cold from it because it's important
Because it's important and it needs to be kept pure like like the good like the good vibes have to be maintained
And like it has to be it has to make continue to be like like, you know, what it always has been to them
Bronies the burning community you ask beauty and my little point itself is inherently insidious
Yes purified bronies are definitely it needs to be purified from these people we need to save it from these people
Yeah, it needs it needs to be saved from like its most ardent members. Yeah, you are the bad influence
You are the bad influence
People may think that this is okay to do
Like Miss Anthropony and FNG are are like terrible and like the fact that people listen to them is like horrifying
They are actually the bad influence. They are influence. They're influencing the youth
I think that it's okay to communicate such as like this
Yeah, like it's because of people it's because of people like Miss Anthropony and FNG are and like and dr. Wolf and Kim possible
I'd that like a fucking, you know a modestly talented youngster like wooden sword
Who can like can make a fucking YouTube video and have it not be terrible gets fucking on this track of like
Why don't I make fucking pony videos? I don't know man
I'm not saying like I'm not saying it's like he's like he's he's done for but like yeah, that's not good
That's not a good thing to be doing. Yeah, I don't think so
It's definitely it's corrosive and the reason why the reason why I don't think it's good
Is because it means coming into contact with people like this and like having to fucking deal with people like this and risking fucking
Being influenced by people like this
If there were just
P-baps if there were just digipros if there were just fucking give-and-takes then it would be fine
But do the fact that these are the these are the people who are in the community
But like the community now is like the community now is like Lily Pete
Which like fucking kill me fucking like put a bullet in my fucking head. Yeah that I even said that name
That I know who that is the saddest thing that's ever happened to me
These the kind of people who are you in social, but this is this is not an admirable situation
This is what's left like that's what's left
Like it's them and the people that think it's so important that they deserve money to keep doing what they're doing to like carry the fucking torch
and keep it alive
Disgusting absolutely fucking revolting it is like that is awful
Like it was bad enough like when like when we stopped doing it like it was getting bad, but like
The fact that it continued beyond that point and only continued to go in that direction is just really scary
Yeah, it's like how long can they keep this up forever? Yeah forever like show runs
What like what's been left like like this like the cicada like like the cicada of the fan base has like
Crawled out of its hideous shell and it's left like it's dead husk lying there
And like the people that make up the husk will never leave it and it will continue to be important to them
Even though it's empty and even though it's dead
And they'll just be like we we just got we've just got to like keep going through the motions because this is what's important
And and okay, it's obvious that they have no
Grasp of quality none of them do because there's no like just the fact
Yeah, yeah, but like it doesn't matter what it is just like because this institution is important to them like anyone
Who contributes to it is like important and validating like they need that they need to be validated and anyone will do
It doesn't matter who it only matters that you are making a video
That's the only thing that matters and they will be associated with you. Yeah, they are
it's
They're corrupting people that they're corrupt really corrupted insidious and scary
They could be talented, but they are they are forced into this
They like like once they come to contact with it
They are now like associated with this community and that community will reach out to it and it will be enticing
It will be very enticing you will have a lot of people if it seems important and just and good
So you get in here and you realize that everyone's complacent and none of them make any content whatsoever that could be
Even described as good on any level and they love it that way
That is what they are aspiring to they are inspired in my mediocrity
Nothing they do will ever be good and that's just the way they like it. That's just the way the fans like it too
Yeah, yeah, yeah, they want they like that. They're comfortable with the status quo
Like something new would be would be scary something something new would be like well
That's not what we're here for something new would be uninteresting
Like that that was that was new that had different parts to it and that was yeah interesting
Yeah, miss anthra pony miss anthra pony didn't find it to be presented in an interesting way
What's what's interesting about the thousands of clones of each other? What's interesting about that?
What's interesting about the exact same fucking video being presented by a myriad of the same
Score out of character archetypes over and over again in the exact same visual way
What's interesting about that?
I just worry I just worry about I worry about the wooden swords of the world who are like
Fucking caught up caught who like stumble upon this thing and receive like praise and validation for what they're doing
And like, you know
I'm worried. I'm worried about new people getting caught up in this and getting tricked getting fucking tricked
It really is like a weird cult like mentality. It's despicable
Is despicable
Should we continue continue but I will say that I have learned some things since then and one of those things
Is actually knowing when someone is being a piece of crap
Not just because they have an opinion that you don't want to hear
But because they're presenting themselves as an insufferable douchebag in other words
What I'm trying to say is you are a shit
Sucking a bitch Ben. You think you're so cool with your hole
You're a bitch because you don't watch our podcast of us talking about how you're a bitch because you don't want
When did I ever say that?
When did I ever say that like people that don't watch the rowdy fuckers cop killers of bitches?
I mean they are but when in the video did I say that?
What?
Question mark. What's he talking about? What's he talking about?
You
You're a bitch because you don't watch our podcast. I mean that's true. Yeah, it is true, but I didn't but
Like it's like like is that my thing like is that my thing now?
That's not what the podcast. That's not what that video was about. It's just a fact. That's an objective fact
But like that's not what it was about. That's not
That's not even the reason you're upset like yeah, like are you you're suddenly mad because
You think that I think you're dumb because you didn't like the video?
Like is that why when did that become what this is about miss antherpony?
Why when and why this fucking picture you made this picture?
This is what you were talking. This is what you were talking about like he just needs he needs to communicate through like scenes from tv shows. Yeah
you
You thought this was
Okay, I don't know the scene from he thought that maybe it has some sort of like
I
I mean, I'm pretty sure
I mean bobby
I don't know. I'm not entirely sure what's going on in the scene either, but like
I don't think what's happening here is that like bobby is like
Righteously kicking hank in the nuts because hank was like legitimately in the wrong
Like I do not believe for a second that that is what is happening
So I fail to see I fail to see um what what you what the what point you're trying to make the framing the framing of this
that like you're like
He's like an underdog. He's a small child soldier underdog
And you're like this big bad like fucking dad trying trying to like try trying to fucking impose his values onto this community
Uh
Which is like I'm a complete outsider. Yeah
Yeah, I don't know
I don't know like
Again, he's just like so mad that he needs to convey
His emotions not through his words, but through a picture from a tv show because like that's
That's the best way he knows how and this was the best he could come up with
worthless
Yeah, worthless
Zero values without value
Worthless no merit. No merit. You thought no one was gonna care enough to rush on to this bullshit
You're dead wrong ass face
Did you not think for a single microsecond that did did you continue? I did. Yeah, you know
Oh, yeah here here. I'll here. I'll be sure it's at 1608
For some reason it just like doesn't work sometimes
All right here like like just like change it a little bit like like go back like a second or two
and then like
All right. Yeah. Yeah, okay good. Someone was gonna care enough to respond to this bullshit. You're dead wrong
Thanks. Did you not think for a single microsecond that this could get you in trouble that this could make someone feel uncomfortable
Get me more importantly. Did you not think that this would look obscenely bad on your part?
Yeah, he thinks he thinks that this will a get me in trouble
false
B
Make someone uncomfortable
True him. Yeah, see look bad on my part. Well, wrong if you're retarded
Like yeah, I'm I'm risking alienating some like overly sensitive retards here
I'm risking alienating the very people who I'm making fun of for being awful and undesirable
Yeah, I
I am alien like if I were to join the army. I am well look at something like if I were to like
Kill a Nazi. Yeah, I'm ricks alienating other. I would risk alienating Hitler
Yeah
problem
If I alienate the very people who I want to dispose from reality
That I'm fine with that. I'm fine. I'm fine with alienating the very people who I dislike. Yeah. Yeah, um
I you're you've well said munchie and I like I wish I wish that I wish misanthropony could see things with such clarity
I wish I risk I I wish I wish
that misanthropony
Was real
I wish that he was a real person
But I know my heart of hearts that he's just like a computer ai designed to be the worst possible human
I
I wish that he I wish that he had a beating heart. I wish that he had a brain a dick or a soul
Any one of those things would be fine
But he has none
Oh, yeah, yeah, like we like because if you had any of those things we could revenge ourselves upon them
But we can't like there's nothing like there's nothing there's nothing to be struck back against
It's just it's just
We can't do anything. He's just too. He's just too powerful and my powerful. I mean
He like like what are we gonna do?
His mind is just armored. He's his mind is just armored too impenetrable. Yeah, like we can't it's like
Like if we can't say anything to like make him think like he's not cognizant. He's not cognizant
He's not lucid. There's no getting through to him. Yeah
there's no
Getting in there continue
Are you really this desperate to spike the analysis community?
That you would openly spit in the face of such a delicate event that has actually had an impact on people's lives
Yes, no regret. Yes, definitely with no reluctance
This entire video has just been you rambling on and on like a bitchy high schooler about how the brony fandom is below you
Which would be annoying enough on its own
But what you say here is thoroughly disgusting in the worst way possible
People say that tommy oliver is a backstabber
But you directly take the dagger shove it through the stomach and disembowel with it
At least he had the decency to raise awareness on a struck from the front
Honorably the way that you speak of it so absent mindedly shows me that you knew nothing about this situation
Thus you have no fucking right to comment on it
I have no and and what makes you feel like you
Know about the context of this video
What makes what makes it seem like you are in like you know anything about what's going on in this video
Or what's happening in the pcp?
You obviously sound like you don't know a single fucking thing you're talking about
So maybe it's likewise
Maybe maybe we don't want to think about each other
And there's no reason for you to get so mad because we obviously are just misunderstanding
Or but but that's obviously like too like high level. That's too like high strat
You can't just understand that like like okay if we don't want to think about that
You probably don't think about us too. So like what's the what's even the problem here?
Like like like we just don't know anything about it. So what's the problem?
I think he's mad like he's mad that I like he's mad at me because I didn't know anything
Exactly
And if you don't know anything then we obviously don't fucking know anything. So you might as well just brush us off
Yeah, man, and then he doesn't even try to fuck and he doesn't even try to educate us
Yeah, just try he just chides us for not knowing anything and then provides us with no information
Exactly
Fucker or earthly clue as to how any of your fans let alone subscribers to the procrastinator channel
Could actually get a kick out of this piece of shit video not okay. Okay. Okay
Most of our subscribers are not from the pony days. This is not a pony channel
Yeah, I sincerely doubt
Okay, okay. Look at the view the view count compared to the fucking subscriber count not like a small portion
It's like it's like it's like half or it's like a I can't even read it
But like yeah, it's like a quarter a half and like there's more. I think it's like doubled since then
Oh, yeah, okay. Well still still
Uh, it's like that and then this was paused around in the in the pony community
So I guess it's not a really good example, but yeah, what I mean. These are not pony guys
I'm I'm certain that the majority of our subscribers don't know who any of these fucking people are
They have no way to tell if we're being like justified or not and this is purely for us
We were not doing this for like the fans
No, like that's the point of the rowdy fuckers cop killers really it's not for anyone
It's for no one. Yeah
Ah
Just giving it views
But giving it likes the fact that mage is still willing to put up with you is a true act of saint
Here he goes white mighty white knighting mage because of something
Anyone else putting up with your insufferable ass except
It's like it's like he could say
Like ben I can't believe
Like like I think a reasonable thing would be to like
Suspect mage of being bad because she associates with with bad me and you
Yeah, but no, he's he's like impressed with how good mage must be
To be able to put up with with bad me and bad you how is that good?
How is how is associating and like clearly being friends with bad people? How is that good?
He's just got it
He's just previously decided that mage is good because he feels bad about something and it's like oh no
I thought mage was bad, but actually she was good. I made a mistake. So okay
I'm gonna fix it. The mage is good. Mage is good. Let's this is this is our operating position from here
That is literally he just oh wait. No no stop
Stop, okay. Yeah before you do that. I have one point and then I and then and then hold on uh like like
Like he is just arbitrary like like he just decides things
He does not think about things and then decide afterward what to do
He decides and then like reviews
Yeah, he did he decides and then he and then he like
He has he has his conclusion
And then he has his thought he then then he puts thought into into justifying it. Yeah, and yeah, it that's that's horrible
That he just one of the many things that shows that he just is not lucid. He's not he's not really it's really low functioning
And no wait, uh, just a side note
I want you I want everyone at home to turn up the speakers all the fucking way so you can hear this next line
Because I know what's coming and it's my favorite line in the entire video. So please play. I'm gonna be quiet
Enjoy your ignorant patreon supporters who are blissfully and mindlessly
Throwing enough money at you for you to buy yourself an oculus rift in two months time
Yeah, it doesn't feel so good when someone does it to you does it I could have
Okay
Yeah, you know
Yeah
my yeah, it's
Oculus rift
It's at this point in the video where I start to feel bad because we're obviously punching down
You're
We are obviously dealing with someone who's just like not
Who just can't like this is this would be the equivalent of like an MMA fighter going up against a fetus
Intellectually yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's no no not a stillborn baby who's already dead
Like
Yeah, like like can you imagine like trying to have like a lot like a live one-on-one conversation with this person
Yeah, like can you even imagine like the stonewalling you would get as he just like
Fails to fucking take in the information you're presenting him with
And just like backpedals and like invents facts to try and like cover his own his own like tracks like
Just the anyway, anyway, that's all to say like what the fuck is he talking about like with this oculus run
Okay, okay, okay. He like slightly explains the comments that
like
Like someone's like, you know three hundred and thirty dollars isn't a lot of money, dude
He's like all I'm saying is that he can buy an oculus an oculus lift rift in two months. Nothing. It could live on it
so he's like
Wow
Does that wow have to do
With fucking anything like he's trying to be he's trying to say like look at all this money
Like this guy's like look at all this money that this guy is like, you know
Can you believe that such an asshole would get this much and it's like
Three hundred and thirty dollars enough to buy an oculus rift in two pay jacks
Not in one in two
Will pay for an oculus rift. Yeah, if I didn't eat or live anywhere. Yeah
Completely saving he could buy an oculus rift in two months
Oh my fucking god. He can buy a video game console in fucking two months of work
Oh my god, this guy's living the lap of luxury. I know right like
Silver spoon in his mouth
Let's let's
Let's and that's not even to touch on the fact that he previously said
He previously said that it is like completely unthinkable and unfair and like unjust to like criticize someone else for their patreon
And now here he is. It's not too good when you do it. It's like, you know, it's a feel too good
You're doing what you don't like
You're doing the thing that you said it was so bad that I did and then and then he's uh, uh, I bit my tongue
Oh god, and then he's acting like oh, he's really turned the tables. It's like well, I guess but like
You are just making it worse for you
You you said this was wrong to do and then you're like, I've really I've really
I've I've shown you by doing it
Like like we obviously have no problem with doing that to people
So you know, but you said you did. Yeah, like like like he's he's the only one who's not benefiting from this
He's the only one who's at a disadvantage here. He's the only one who's feeling bad about it
Yeah, yeah, yeah
We are not affected you you're just doing this to yourself the problem is entirely the problem is entirely on his end. Yeah
Oh
Oculus Rift I just can't I can't go I just can't stop of all things to measure your wealth with why oculus rift
in it and then in the comment in the comments there was like people being like
So I think someone was like I really he's gonna buy an oculus rift with that money. What a piece of shit
Guys
wait
No, you don't you don't understand
We like
Have you ever even said the words oculus rift publicly? I don't I honestly don't think I ever have
So like where that came from. Maybe he was just thinking about the oculus rift that day, you know
Maybe maybe just had like like an oculus rift ad and he was like, oh, I love video games
And I love media so much. Yeah, he's gonna have so much money. He can spend it on media
Yeah, yeah, because like what else would I spend on like what else would a person spend their money on then video games? Yeah
I don't even know if this rift is pure video, but it's just fucking
It's so it's not like he could buy a fucking house in a year's time
He could he could spend so much money on grocery. He could he could get so many valuable things
an oculus rift of all
Yeah, it's
This is like this is the thing this is the thing that he measures wealth in, you know
Like this is a glimpse into what's important to him. Yeah
not of like
Rent removed. Yeah, not like rent or something. Yeah, or like
I don't yeah, or like a house or like a car
An oculus rift
That's it matters
And uh, this is all to say a check the description for the Kickstarter to get been an oculus rift. Yeah
um
Fuck dude when when we get pcp headquarters, we should fucking get an oculus rift
Yeah, and like fucking live stream and fucking live stream vr
We should get miss antherpony on that stream
He's invited miss antherpony is invited to pcp headquarters. He's invited
We wouldn't have thought of this if it weren't for you. Thank god. You said something
Oh, I hate him
So it's just it doesn't it it does not compute. It doesn't compute
No, he's made a critical error
He's made a he's made some kind of logical error that like just can't be rectified
Oh, should I continue?
What yeah
My i'm
I hate him imagine jesse wood and gibbon takes snoring through your content given how boring and repetitive it is
Considering that they themselves have made much more interesting content jesse and hippo are my friends
I would sooner watch one of racer fists aimless republican superior
What okay, okay. Well, that was pretty good right that's right there about razor fist
but uh
Like first of all we are like, I don't know if he understands like the pcp isn't like
This is this funny because you were just talking about how it's too business oriented like last episode
But like yes, but it's not supposed to be that way. Yeah, it's it's not like
It's not like we like we like clock in from nine to five and we like we like hash this out
And like like we're not in like a huge like studio where like we like barely pass by one another
We are aware of each other and we like know what we all do. We're all subscribed one another
We're all we all like our friends
Like so so the idea that like so the idea that like mage would be like saintly like putting up with my like
like my like wicked deeds
And then like and then hippo and jesse are like scoffing at me just aren't aware of what we're doing
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah that they wouldn't know
Like no they know and they love it because we're geniuses
And it's incredible
Like
Your heroes you you're fucking heroes give and take and and and jesse
Yeah, they they they enjoy it. They like they're on our like they're on our side of this
They're on our side of this dispute guy
I don't know about jesse, but I know for a fact a gibbon is hippo is
I'm pretty sure jesse. I don't know. I don't remember if he said anything about it. I'm pretty sure I'm pretty sure he was on it
Either way, that's one out of two
yeah
Uh, great. All right, let's let's keep going. Let's let's let's let's kill this
Oh, did we did it go for you? No, it didn't it didn't go for me. Okay. Yeah, go go go ahead
Uh rambles before I even is going for you
To revisit one of your t-bab videos again right now
You are one of the worst things that has ever happened to the brony phantom. Yeah, look how terrible that is
Look how cool phantom work is that we're sent to aim to ketan rogers
Literally the best thing that has ever happened to the analysis community is that you left it
You are a piss-gargling scumbag who deserves to lose all the popularity. He currently has
All the popularity all of the patreon pledges that are being given to this micro
Penis ass wipe and give it to me so that she actually has something to eat outside of whatever's left over from his mcdonald's happy meal
And by the way, what the way, you know, did she bro? I don't know what he's
What
I think he's saying that I eat mcdonald's and eating mcdonald's is bad and I eat happy meals because
saying like
Mage
Okay, the three like the three ideas there are that
Maid doesn't have a lot of money ergo is eating table scraps, of course
A lot of money on patreon ergo is eating table scraps. Yeah
uh
and she like
like he says
something like
Play it again like roll back. I need like digest so that she'll have something to eat besides the leftovers from his
mcdonald's happy meal also
I just want to say that like if he thinks that if he's showing this picture of phantom horn
And he doesn't think that it's great like like he's he's just so fucking
He's just so fucking out of touch because this is like the greatest thing that ever
This is this is the best thing that ever happened to the mlp fandom and like the fact that he
Like the fact that he thinks that telling me that like
It's good that I left like the fact that he thinks that would like hurt my feelings. Yeah
Like this is again, we're just we're just getting a glimpse into it. It's just like watching it's like walking
It's like walking up to like a renaissance pain and say like oh my fucking god
This is the worst thing to ever happen to medieval times. I'm so sorry that like I'm so sorry that like we got like machines
And like advance to the modern era. What the fuck
What the fuck dude?
Lee has you know what we should do
We should take all of the patreon pledges that are being given to this micro penis ass wipe
And give it to mage so that she actually has something to eat outside of whatever's leftover from his mcdonald's happy meal
And by the way by the way, you know digi bro that great friend of yours that you were hesitant to say anything bad about
While you were criticizing everybody
Yeah, he's a pretentious sick muncher who stumped his thumb up people's asses over how they produced their anime content
I honestly don't get like I don't know like I don't know about that video instead
He practically makes the same content and he's not a complete conch and oh my god
Oh my god
Just the woeful just the woeful ignorance like
Telling me this like it's a great revelation
Like oh like he's spilling the beans that oh digi's an asshole
And we should watch jeff like he doesn't know like shouldn't he know that like we kick jeff out
Okay, well first of all first of all on record. I think I said this last time too. I'm I'm I'm pro jeff and I think jeff is cool
I don't care. I don't care one bit about jeff is
Does he not know that jeff was on the pcp?
He might he might know that
He doesn't seem like he knows like
That doesn't like like like oh, why isn't jeff on here's way better than did you know like we should all watch this guy
Because I think he I think he's thinking that like he's problem
He might be drawing the equivalents. They're like because jeff was on the pcp
All right fair fair, I suppose
Uh, but first okay. Yeah, but to go back
I'll concede maybe maybe he knows
Something about the pcp. Maybe maybe he knows one fact about the pcp. I'll give him that. Yeah. Yeah
First of all again, we're all friends of one another. We all know what we do
Ben you lived in the same house as did you when he yeah at this time. Yeah, yeah, yeah
But of course he wouldn't know that yeah, I lived in his house
You lived in you were roommates
You lived at his house. You lived in the same house when he made that video
Yeah, yeah true
It's not like a loose confederation. It's not like a loot like we all know what we're doing
We are like like like look at this crate. Yeah, I bet you didn't know did you bro made this video
Well, well, well, well, you know what let me I'm not entirely sure whether he's
Trying to do like an expose and like expose digi as an asshole or if he's just trying to like hurt me by insulting my friend
You know
Oh
Maybe but like he might just be being like and about your friend digi. He sucks this guy's better, you know
If so completely irrelevant and also just weird and mean
Yeah, yeah, I mean he's just being mean like he's just being like
Like know what like nowhere in our video. Did I say I don't okay? I don't think I was like
Listen everyone who's pledging to tune critic y2k keyframe
Whoever the fuck else I don't think I I never said like
You all need to stop pledging to them and pledge to like me or pledge to hip or pledge to someone else
I didn't do that. I was just like man. I can't I don't think so
I don't think so because I think I was more like I just can't believe that people see value in this and are pledging and it
Upsets me
This and then for him to come and be like you all need to stop pledging to ben
Like I'm not worried
Like obviously I didn't think that it was going to happen, but it just strikes me as really malicious and
Just like a really nasty thing
To even want to do, you know
Yeah
Just like a really nasty thing to say and I really just really
Makes me kind of wonder why he thinks that why he thinks he's got any kind of moral high ground to come to like look down from
Hashtag save misanthropony not been
Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly
He needs it. He needs to be saved from himself
It's off
I'm gonna continue. Oh, oh, wait, wait. I was tried to do it. Uh, by the way, uh, he says, uh, your friend did you bro?
He was so hesitant to talk bad about uh, we just like didgy. Yeah, like have anything bad to say about him. He's yeah
It's it's weird like it's weird that that's not where his mind went
Yeah, like how he could not piece that together
Like yeah, like it's yeah
In the comment section of this video because no reply that you make will ever justify the unbearable level of ignorance that you displayed
And fuck you shit, man. Whoever the fuck you are for accompanying this madness
Why doesn't he know who you are
What he just showed a video of mine earlier. He showed to your dad. You know who I am
like
I don't I don't get it. I don't get like what
He's talking about like why doesn't he know who you are like he well
He knows the pcp like he's familiar with what's going on there. How can he not know?
like like
I he's just
I have no idea what information he has and what doesn't
You see like it's a rant like it's random some information. He just has to block out some
Yeah, have the full picture, but how are we supposed to know?
I don't get it. I don't I don't know and like me like fuck you too much if you're accompanying this madness
Not fuck you too for saying the same thing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's like
It was like this was a group effort. This was a group like it's not like it's not like I committed a crime and you like
Covered for me. It's like we were both in it doing the exact same thing. Yeah
I don't know
I don't know man
Like like why like like like why is he maybe he just doesn't know me so it doesn't matter
But like that's still like a it feels like it feels like the crime isn't that you just did these things
But that you were in the community and did these things. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I was gonna say it's like it's personal for me
like for me it's personal
Uh
Yeah, yeah, like like when it's me it's a betrayal
But but when it's me it's just me doing bad things
Which you know, if you're so much just doing bad things, I don't who cares. He's just doing horrible things. I find your poor
Yeah, yeah, but if he didn't use if I didn't use to think he was an ally then it's no big deal
Jesus Christ
Know that a lot of people who were featured in your video have seen it already and they've been pretty merciful towards you
But not me. So I've got one thing to say to you pal
Own up to your stupidity and take responsibility for it because people are generally not gonna want to put up with your
Shit, you're lucky that I decided to format the audio for this video before golden fox sent anything to me
I'm pretty sure he has some very special choice words for you after what you just said about his girlfriend
Um fun fact. No, he doesn't uh, he never said a thing to me. So there we go
And hold on hold on. I just want to analyze it soon as for a second
So he formatted his audio before like you're lucky. I did that before golden fox sent anything to me
So I'm sure that must mean that that he was like chatting with golden fox and was like, oh man
You should send something my name was like, oh, I don't know
But I I want to just imagine I want I want this headcanon to be real. I want this to be what I actually had
I wanted I wanted golden fox to come at me. Like I thought that sounded great
Well, okay. Okay. I want this to be what happened
He missanthropony knows about golden fox
And he knows that he is dating keyframe
So he watches this video and he like makes a video
He like makes a video and then he's just thinking
man
What if golden fox sent me some audio that would be crazy like he like like like do you understand what i'm saying here?
Like he doesn't know
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like like this is not a thing that was ever like actually going to go down
Yeah, this is just like what he wanted because he says it's odd to me that he says he's pretty sure
The golden fox has some choice where like that vague wording makes me wonder like what he's actually talking about
Yeah, so I want to just conclude like I want this to be I'm sure this isn't the case
This seems unlikely, but I want to be the case that he just does not know golden fox and golden fox doesn't even know about this
Know about fucking frog fractions
He just knows that they are like related
I don't I'm not sure. I kind of think that maybe
He did but like I don't know. I never thought about it. Yeah, maybe maybe he doesn't maybe maybe golden fox
Just like listen, I don't care and and and uh and miss anthro is just like choice words
Yeah, exactly fucking jesus christ
I mean golden fox like I said, I would have I would have loved it if golden fox had been like
Hey, I heard you talking shit about my girlfriend like I would have loved to defend my position to him or keyframe herself
But nobody ever said anything
Fuck you and have a nice day and if I see you anywhere near brony conigan, I'm slamming my foot up your dick
Oh
Jesus christ, what a nice guy. Yeah, what a nice dude
Really really vindictive when we obviously had the tone that we didn't actually care in that video
Like like none of this is really negatively impacting us
Like like to to him. This is personal like like like like to him
The right there just talking to his frog fractions was the end of the world, but to us it was Tuesday
Exactly exactly. I don't know. It's just it bugs me
It bugs me that he can like think this is okay that like I
Say mean things about someone and his and what he believes to be an appropriate response to that is like to fucking kick
Someone in the dick, which is an action that can cause like serious injury, you know
Like he's like he thinks it's fine. Like he thinks it's fine to threaten violence against someone
Like he thinks that's appropriate
And like what do you even say to a person like that?
I'm not I'm not trying to be all bleed and heart like oh he threatened me but like for fuck's sake
I just it's just completely unwarranted and disgusting like
like
He is doing everything that we that he considered bad in that video, but worse 10 times worse and more personal
Yeah, we didn't spend I mean, I mean, I mean sure I'm sure we spend like large segments talking about one person
But none of it was this in-depth and like personally like
Like we never had like fucking like like like like material. We never had like oh here. I'm gonna edit this
I'm gonna I'm gonna fucking script this it was all off the cuff
Normal just friends like shit talking in like completely closed off
Yeah, none of it was this highly edited our video was not a hit video unlike this one, which is explicitly was yeah
Speaking of hit videos, um
Shall we go on to the next one?
Should we go on to the next man? That one took a long time to get through
I don't know if I don't I don't know if I've got the energy to like spend to pick this next one apart to that extent
Well, I certainly do so you can just pick it back off me
It's because this next one is like really like that one was mean to you
This one's like mean to us both this one
Yeah, this one's real this one's real shitty and like
Even less coherent. We have to understand
Here here like this one. I honestly can't even understand like what his point is. Yeah, uh, okay
I watched this one before obviously and I just want to I just want to let you go
Oh, by the way, we should mention that that video you just watched was by Miss Anthropony
It was called something like uh, you know taking down been saying uh all credits, you know
That was his video go ahead and watch that if you want to not claim your ownership there
It's you know a little disclaimer. Anyway, this is by fngr for no good reason
How not to bring 35 of tumblr insane?
Okay, I watched this before
I don't understand it whatsoever. I do not know what this video is
Miss Anthropony's video was about the video like at the very least you can you can
You know what the point of that video was like like reading between reading between the lines
You can understand what it is that Miss Anthropony feels about the video and like what it is that's bothering him
That video was a response to right-fingers copulars fog for actions
That was describing what happened in the video that made him upset. Sure. None of his points make sense
But you can understand what the video is. Yeah, I do not understand what this for no good reasons video is
His like there's no like none of his none of his things that he says like point to any like central idea
Or like reason which I guess that's his name. Haha his name. Yeah. Yeah good
um
Like this one is like
Basically the like this entire not the whole video is about us
But the part that is is like just calling us shit and like not even trying to back that up
Yeah, go ahead and start it
Are we first or we later? I don't I don't think
This is a last minute pre word before I get to being needlessly bitchy
I'm not I think I skip with me. Sorry. Sorry. I don't want to I skip the important
Yeah, yeah, we just gotta find out I think it only goes I think the first like eight minutes or so are about us
Yeah, it's just probably first us and then later. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you know some weeks ago
I oh, I should say that before this video came out fngr
Tweeted at me
And he was just like I don't remember what he said, but he was asking me like are we cool?
And I was like
What what do you mean? Like what wouldn't we be cool about? I think
I don't even know if I mentioned him in the frog fractions video, but I think I did
Yeah, yeah, maybe you did
But he was asking me like are we cool and I was like are we cool about what?
And he was real cagey and he kept asking like are we cool are we cool?
I'm just checking and finally I was like what are you fucking talking about
And he or I forget how I phrase it, but I got mad. I was like what I said like what are you talking about you cagey?
Fuck. Yeah, he was like never mind
And like dropped it and then a couple days later this video comes out. Oh, okay, and let me read the text on screen
Uh, boy, I can't wait to get this puke
Uh, this puke class. This is what a fail abortion looks like that wasn't capitalized
I'm actually such a garbage human being if he was the crap and the divus diaper
Uh, the dude's girlfriend's diaper. Uh, he dumped her
Okay, pretty good pretty good so far
I'm enjoying this content pretty yeah, yeah pretty good content so far pretty good
Uh, we're really getting the lulls here, bro. We're really getting the lulls here. I'm gonna laugh out loud when I see this
This is just setting the tone for what to expect. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, this is this amount of intelligence we're dealing with here
Uh, hang tight. We'll get there Ben. I need you to focus reach down deep
Percent like there's a big bag of pain chips waiting. Look at how he spells theirs
Wait, wait, it didn't work for me for some reason. Yeah. Yeah, here. That one. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, there we go. There we go. There we go
Yeah, yeah
Look, just look at how he spells theirs. Like I don't understand of what joke he's trying to make here
Just the spelling is it's funny problem naturally
There's the horse news situation, but that looks like a big one
This is a last minute pre word before I get to being needlessly bitchy
I'm not interested in the moral high ground. This is not me being the better man
I've glanced at and skimmed Miss Anthropony's video on this topic and left it up for attention
So he can get his sweet 20 minutes. I could work really hard to pander why I'm right and ben's wrong
I'm just gonna be salty right and wrong about what we called chelise's bluff last night
That being tuesday to have a talk with tune critic and chelise in true horse news fashion
Dick tucked despite having a skype account. He said that he didn't have the means to log on to it anymore
Journalism folks like even if you forgot the password it would take him what 60 seconds one minute
Should I skip a little bit? Let's see. I think so. Yeah, it's all just bullshit. The horse news is still stuck on the
Where he had tried to oh, yeah
Oh, here we go. Here we go. Goldfish. I nasty youtube thing. Dear ben saint
I know you're too lazy or too stupid to walk kind of looks like a 20 year old
I'm actually older than that. That's right. I bent over backwards monday to try and make peace with you
Ben had done a four-hour hit video on the brawny fandom
Where he had tried to bend over backwards to impress his fellow pcp member munchie the mongoloid knuckle dragon of the group
Dear munchie
First of all, yeah, what the fuck are you talking about? I don't I mean
There's so there's just so like everything he says is nonsense
I mean like if he was trying to make pee like he didn't try to make peace
He asked me if there was anything wrong and I said I didn't know what would be wrong
And like I don't know what and then he kept pressing me until I got annoyed and basically told him to go away
Yeah, and then he left and was mad at me. That's bad
But the way he describes the video like okay, first of all, it's obviously he calls it a hit video
Yeah, that didn't even he didn't even watch missanthropone's 20 minute response to it. Yeah, he just skimmed
Okay, so right off the bat. He just doesn't know what he's talking about. He just does not understand. Yeah
So he so so I guess this is again punching down
Like we like we shouldn't even be doing this because he obviously just does not understand anything
I mean, I said it about missanthropone. I said about fngr
I really believe it in both cases like I really think they're retarded and there's something wrong with them because they
Just don't act or speak or behave or like convey thoughts in the way that like a functioning human being does
Yeah, and and like we wouldn't I like if it was just like
I don't really understand what's going on. They were being mean to key for like again, like I wouldn't care
But this guy gets like mean
He gets fngr gets mean and never says why he never says why?
Uh, but but yeah, okay, but the way he described it as you made the frog fractions video to bend over backwards to appease me
The mongrel, where does he get that idea?
Like where does that come from? What does that mean?
What
What?
It's like what does it not enter these people's heads that maybe we're just friends and we want to hang out and be friends
And talk shit about people that suck. Yeah
Like could that could that is that not a reasonable explanation for why this is a video?
How like
That's not like a marketable that you can't even say that was for money. That's not a marketable video
No, that's not like what people want to see that's that wouldn't get us money
And how would that appease me to do that?
how
You like like I don't even know most of those like I don't of them and I had stuff to say but it's not like like like
I don't have the I don't have the beef here. I just kind of ride the beef. I read the coattails the beef basically
Like I want like I want to theorize like where this idea comes from
But I've just got nothing like I've got no idea why he thinks that like I'm trying to impress you
with any of this
I don't understand. I don't understand
Continue
I'm gonna take care of you right now. This is my friend Vita. I could spare 100 munchies to a single Vita
For those of you guys who don't know once upon a time ago Vita used to be boys with digi bro
And digi bro cut Vita out because and Vita got all bitchy and huffy about it because and the ensuing
Shitstorm has reached levels of fuckery that the bernie fandom might not have known
Well, if not for this channel
Munchies case on like digis where digi just cut Vita off and Vita
Wondered up taking it very poorly about as bad as say lily peat took being cut off from joss scorcher
Munchie
Did the same thing and Vita asked for me to go find out to which munchie told me
Sometimes some niggas just don't get along anymore and that's fine
And Vita's response was and nothing of value was lost
Vita didn't mindlessly harass munchie. He let shit go
In fact, I was really proud that Vita had the most mature rare moment
I've ever seen him have in one of these situations. Later on Vita snuck his way here here
Let me pause this so I can explain what's going on. Uh Vita made accounts on steam over and over trying to add me
That is a fact that is what he did and I'm pretty sure the timeline of this
After effing you're asked me he didn't do it anymore, which was fine
The facts still remains after I blocked him and I'm fairly certain that I that I said I blocked you or even if I didn't
He could take the hint making a ton of accounts to message me and me ignoring every single one
Probably doesn't seem like I want to talk does it?
You know like he's
I which like fngr just he just goes off on this thing and like there's no context given as to like why there's be
like he says that like Vita used to be boys with digi and then
something about you and
Something see like this isn't even like drama
This is just like a weird sort of like Vita wanted to be friends still
Or maybe he just it just seemed like you want maybe he didn't want to be friends
Maybe he just wanted to talk for some reason. I didn't want to talk so I didn't accept his friend's request. That's it
That's the entirety of what transpired, you know the entire the entire section was just uh mean vita didn't talk anymore
That's it the the the thing that i'm getting here like I've thought about this before and I like the closest thing
I can get to like
An underlying reason for why fngr is so upset is I really think that was like vita that was upset
Like I really think he's upset on behalf of vita because of probably because we shit talked him and we like went and tried
And I I deleted his page even though I knew it would come back
Yeah, um, so like I think I think that he's indignant because we were mean to vita
And I think that probably what this video is is just like a sort of diarrhea stream
That like came squirting out as the like as the aftermath of like some really angry like back and
Forthing between like the people that like fngr hangs out with like, you know corpulent brony and vita
and
Shelley d and like whoever the fuck else like I think this is like they kind of took this idea that like oh ben and munchy
Were mean to vita echo chambered it around being like oh well, they're bad. They're the ones who are bad
They're shitty and I hate them and then like this video is what's like squirted out like of the black box
Like we don't see we don't get to see what went into it. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, we don't we don't really know what happened there
We just know that this is like the feeling that this indescribable in like
Unfathomable video is what was is what was created
We don't like it's just we can't describe what it is because it makes no sense
It's really like it really feels like it's all based on like some some like cultural some like
Like clicky shit that is like deeply understood by like five people. Yeah
But we have like no context for but then like a thousand people watch it anyway because it's like vaguely related to the brony fandom
And that means it's worth watching for some reason
I just I don't understand
Now by the way, and none of this is a point about the video. This is just like weird backstory between me and vita
Continue. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah where he was getting along with people in there
We'll more the fans and say the pcp members, but that was never gonna happen
I fully understand that vita didn't belong there. We kind of popped in the call and munchi showed up and went
What are you doing here vita? Nobody likes you kill yourself. Oh, hi fng. Are you're cool?
Let me respond munchi. No, I don't also when you first of all
I don't think I like my entire okay. I know I might have said
Me, you know fng. You're cool. My entire
Knowledge of fngr was that he was like this weird like shady sketchy guy that I didn't like
But I knew I knew that people thought were cool. So I was like, okay
I guess I'll just like I I never wanted to be friends with fng. I just thought like, okay
I won't start shit like I'll start shit with vita because I hate him. Yeah
And uh, that's my entire like I I never was like trying to like like boot lick fngr
Because I I didn't like him, but I I didn't think it was okay to not like him. So I didn't want to start any shit. Yeah
By the way, I still like don't even know like what's being like
I guess they came into a call at some point. Like I don't know what the call was
I don't know like when this was happening or I will explain the entirety of what
Of what this person tried to explain. I will explain to you in like human terms
Yeah, one day in the pcp fan chat vita came in and uh, he was acting kind of weird
And then I was like, oh man, it's vita. What a fucking weird asshole
And then I called him a weird asshole and told him kill himself
And then I told sorry, but how he fucked digi's chair and he got all embarrassed
And and uh, people made fun of him a lot because he was being weird and creepy and an asshole
Uh, he wasn't he wasn't even being like that like, you know, he wasn't even being that weird
It was just vita and I hate vita. So I wanted to make fun of that was like a that's understandable to me
Yeah, I just don't like vita. So I wanted to give him a bad time
Like I've heard I've heard enough about vita that I don't think he deserves the benefit of the doubt
Yeah
And so that happened and then fngr was there too and they they gone to a call by them
Like in a voice call by themselves like it like they joined the voice channels
What I'm saying not like a call off on their own they got into the voice channel
I was going to but I was out of the house and uh, so I just I just told him to kill himself and the
I think he's gay and then jesse came in and then uh, me and jesse talked about how uh, stupid and uh,
Faggy uh, vita is and vita got really pissed off and like mad and like uh, like like angry, uh
Like like angry and started crying like pissing his pants and then he like left
Or no, he didn't left we banned him and then he tried to make all the counts to come back and spam the pcp chat
Because quote he said this to one of the mods quote. There's nothing more dangerous than man with nothing left to lose
But oh my god all of his attempts to come back to the pcb fan chat
We're in vain because we immediately realized and banned him
We just immediately banned him. He didn't even have time to spam
Like like he came back like six or seven times and i'm fairly certain and uh, we just banned him like immediately and he didn't
He didn't have any of the epic trolling lulls that he wanted to he was completely and utterly defeated
And nothing he did ever mattered
So he was just pissing his pants publicly and we always made fun of him for being retarded and it was great
It was a great time
Uh, sounds pretty good. Um, should I continue? Yeah, go ahead
You were in the pfc munchie. You acted like a cringy autistic kick who literally screeched into his mic
You went full retard and everyone bent over backwards to be cool with you after vita came back
To say hi and he acted like you were a big deal
You're a star fucker munchie. I want ben to know if you could ever step over him for something bigger
You wouldn't a heartbeat so you could be an even bigger toadie munchie
You're a sniveling groveling two-faced puke once upon a time ago
You blew your nose and showed it to digi and that's not bubble somehow resembled fan art and you
Indeered yourself to someone talented. That's why you are where you are. Shit. That was me
You're been seeing someone else I just I just
Munchie I I know I know that you'll betray me if I ever give you a chance
But but you're like that's that's that's just what I would expect like like I wouldn't ever I wouldn't expect anything less of you
So like I keep you around to keep me on my toes so I don't slip up and get sloppy
Okay, okay, so so a lot of things a lot of things here first of all go back like well, no not go back
I'm gonna go back in my brain to the beginning of that clip where he describes a story
I told on five fractions one where I once went through the pony fuck cast which uh, I don't really remember my interaction with them a lot
I I do I like I described a story where uh meeting a couple friends went into that chat room
And described the history of the Byzantine empire to uh them and it was very funny. I thought it was very funny
uh, that did happen and uh, I'm sure like I was pretty
Like I I I kind of a dodgy memory. Uh, I'm by the memory of the goldfish
And I don't truly remember how often I was associated with the pony fuck cast but I know
Vita added me to cause a lot. I know that for a fact
So I had a lot answer twice to yeah. Yes
So I'm sure I had a lot of interaction with them and I'm sure one time I did scream
I'm sure what I'm a screaming kind of guy. I'm sure I did scream for a while
I don't doubt that that happened
But I also don't doubt that my fucking weird Byzantine empire story happened
So that's not really a gotcha. That's not like there were just two times probably he's saying all these things like they're gotchas like he
It's like everything he says it's like he thinks he's like really he's really like
Putting some shit out there and then it's all just like but it's all just like a big star fucker great
Like he was on to say that like I I'm only friends with digi because I'm I gave him fanner one time and that is completely accurate
Yeah, that is not I'm not like how like how
Yeah, like that like I don't know. How do you fucking meet people? How do you fucking meet people fngr? You fuck?
Yeah, and so like like like we like again, this wasn't to appease me
We just did that because we are friends and we like to have fun
It's like he's reading all these like sinister
Intentions he's reading he's reading all these like weird like Machiavellian power plays into the whole thing that are just not
I'm a star fucker like like
If I was a star fucker, I could do a little bit better than been saying don't you think? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, yeah, you could you could um
Oh, no, I'm sad. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you could go after jeff. Oh man
Um, that'd be really easy mean jeff got into a good
On a good fire red calm. We could easily I could easily use jeff for subs that would be incredibly easy
I you know, I could do for subs. I could not make the Japanese Juggalo ARG
I could I do not do that. I could make anime videos instead of making the Japanese Juggalo ARG
But I don't because I'm a weird fucking emotionally stunted freak and I just want to do cool things. Yeah, like
We're like we're not we're not
We're all here. We're all here because this is where we belong, you know
Not because not because we're not here on some like false pretense. Yeah, it's like there's there's
If we were if we if like if the pcp
Were a thing that we're just like
A business. Yeah, if like if we were here to do business and we were here to like promote an agenda
Like there would be better ways to do that like that's
You know fngr. He just doesn't fucking get it and why would he you know? Yeah, he just doesn't he just doesn't understand a single fucking thing
Yeah, continue. No Ben phantom horn. You ever see the movie twins the one where Arnold Schwarzenegger and I love this
Twin brothers
There's a line in there
When they're talking to old Arnold and saying that all the greatness went into him and all this shit that went into his brother
Afterwards now. This is best guy ever clearly. You know who this is. I'm gonna do this nice and slow
This is the Arnold in this situation, Ben. You're the shit that got left over the pig lips and assholes
You're why does he big old batter of hot dog goo?
Yeah
The brony gets more views than your nez lock series and that's with you having that's that's not that's not true anymore
By the way, I've passed him
I don't know. Well, why is he why is he so why is he so sweet on Nate?
Yeah, yeah, do like what did like what did Nate do to be what did Nate do for him to be like?
Wow, this guy's really bad
But his brother is like the cool guy like this like this like that that guy's cool with me
And this guy's that's not a one-off thing. He mentioned that again
How like how like like ben is like this groveling disgusting sack of shit, but like Nate's so cool
Yeah, what yeah, he shows I believe the kin hearts lecture. Is is that what got you on Nate that video?
that of all videos
I mean
I don't know he's like
I don't think like I'm sure that Nate doesn't interact with fngr
I'm sure that Nate thinks that fngr is is retarded just like I do like
There's no doubt in my mind that like we're completely on the same page about fngr
And yet here he is
Being like then why can't you be cool?
Why can't you be nice and good and and a cool guy like this other guy that thinks I suck ass?
Yeah, I don't understand and also since we're past the mungy part that had no
There was no point there
The point was simply that I was like oh
It was simply that I was a mongoloid. That was the point
I mean the point here is simply that I am inferior to Nate. Yeah
Like there's no
There's no relation to the ratty fucking cop killers. There's no there's no reason given. Yeah, it's just
It's just stated as facts. Yeah, and and and and because because I was mean to vita justly
Therefore, I'm a therefore. I'm a mongoloid and a star fucker. Yeah. Yeah, and and
Again
Why make this video?
You're not making any points of that the friday fuckers fired frack frack frack frack is a bad video
You're just making a video that we are bad people for like he called rowdy. He called rowdy fuckers cop killers a hit video
But like a hit video is exactly what this is. This is nothing but that and we and it wasn't a hit video
It was just us shitting around. Yeah, like it wasn't even mostly about that. Yeah
Um, all right. Okay continue
One thousand subs than me. I'm told that you're pissed that tune critic is making more money than yourself
Well, Ben, he's not even before he makes his streaming money
You seem to poke fun at the burning donut who unlike yourself
Went to be homeless then got a job and pulled himself up by his bootstrap
A man who holds you innate in a high regard
But then you turned around and act like a cunt to the man in front of your little mongoloid friend here with 700 subs
I tried to have a word. I'm really upset. You asked off to me 700 subs. So let me give you a reality
First first of all, how is your sub count relevant? Second of all?
I'm second. I mean, you know, I'm sorry if burning donut thinks I'm cool
Whatever the I don't I don't like his art and his fucking patreon was an embarrassment. So what what the fucking up?
What am I supposed to say?
Uh, and and and wearing a homing became don't a dirty and homely fucking burning donut became homeless
I'm pulled by his bootstraps. Oh, Ben. How's your living situation? How's that going out? How's that working out for you?
How's the majority of your of your fucking life? How's that? How's that? How's your leftover eating situation? How's that?
Um, it's it's on the upswing
I mean, uh
Well, I never I never was homeless, you know, I'll give him that much. It never was never was fully homeless
Uh, so, you know, lucky me. Don't see what that has to do with my fucking
criticisms of the way burning donut chooses to run his fucking art pr campaign
Don't really see the relevant there. Sorry. He was homeless wouldn't have wished that on him doesn't really make
Yeah
Hate him. What else did he say? They're like there was more going on there. Uh, uh, uh
Hot dog goo
It was just more like weirdly specific insults that no one cares about and aren't effective whatsoever
Him saying like him saying like I have more subs, but for no good reason gets more views
Which is like it's not even true. I looked
So something about like some kind of point about how my audience isn't as engaged as his which like sorry. Are you the police?
Yeah, um
Munchy you have 700 subs
You suck. Yes, which I don't even like I don't
Make youtube videos as a profession. That's not what I'm about
This will come up again. This will come up again
But fngr is like is fixated on sub counts and view counts as a measure of a person's worth
Yeah, like yeah, he throws that out there a bunch as opposed to patreon money
Which is more because it shows how much people like your stuff. Yeah, I mean, it's not like exactly
Yeah, it's yeah, yeah, but like it's definitely more of one than like a sub count. I mean look at sigh for example
Yeah, exactly
Look inside your big revelation of leaving pony was to become a pokey tuber
Fresh and original benny, you know because brony is dying benny
You lift mlp to get about half the views that tbb ap used to make not just that but
I mean
Does it even need saying that he just doesn't know what he's talking about?
Yeah, like he just obviously just does not understand like he thinks that people can only exist on youtube
And there's nothing else one could possibly do
Yeah, yeah, yeah like like the thing the things off the things off youtube are not even like entering into this dialogue for him
Like they're not relevant. They just don't even exist in his mind. Yeah. Does he even know
That you have made a comic before does he know that?
Who knows? Who knows?
Like there are creative aspirations outside of youtube. I'm sorry if that's a news flash to you
But there are there are things you can do outside of making youtube videos
well
God
It's really frustrating. It's really frustrating because he just it's like it's like trying to like explain don't touch a stove to a child
Yeah, they don't understand but why though. Yeah, well
It'll you'll try it and you'll see and then he tries it, but he still doesn't get it
And the way he calls you bunny benny is the most disgusting. Benny is creepy. It's creepy
It's super creepy gross and like he's trying to be like
He's trying to be like demeaning about it and it's like just makes me
Sweat just make it just makes me feel feel dirty
Like he's it's so it's so gross. He's like such a gross disgusting person. He's
Really like offensively just unpleasant. Ben. This is proto mario. He has 500k subs entertaining guy
Poketuber his average views today are 10k. That's two percent benny
Which is okay for milk, but not so much for youtube
That's your big breakaway benny going from mlp to pokemon with your staggering dead dry boring thumbnails those numbers
What's what's he what's what's wrong with my thumbnails?
What yeah, they're clear and concise and convey what the video is like look at fucking look at this guy's thumbnails
His these views are his thumbnails are a fucking nightmare. They are in yeah, they can't even read them
You can't read them
They just have like a bunch of photographs and like drawing like it's too small to even read like it doesn't even read
My fucking thumbnails are designed to read well
This guy doesn't know and and and not only fucking that but the shit he said before that where it was like it was like
Can we just replay it can you just go back like a little bit so I can just fucking see that again the proto mario bit
Yeah, yeah the other proto. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Just like just like
The fact that he again again. He just does not understand views
He just doesn't understand that that's not what you do tvb ap used to make
Not just that but see this ben. This is proto mario. He has 500k subs entertaining guy
Poketuber his average views today are 10k. That's two percent benny
Which is okay for milk, but not so much for youtube. That's your big breakaway benny. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay first of all
He makes it seem like leading t-bep and going to pokemon
Well, okay first of all, that's not even what happened
But even if that word to have been what happened like like that's what that's what that's what happened in his mind
Yeah, that's not
That's just not what it is on any level on any level
Hey, you there
You thought that that was a good business decision because as previously stated that's not what you
And even if it was strictly for money
It wasn't it wasn't for money. You didn't do that for money. It's just because you wanted to do it
It wasn't it would have been smarter to say with pony. Yeah
No one doubts that
Yeah, um
and I mean it's just
I don't I don't even I really don't even know what to say about it. Like it's just so missed. I mean
I mean, I don't
I don't know what
Like yeah, like
but like
Here's the thing like he's he's he's saying all this like, you know
Oh, like I've clearly fucked up like I've clearly fucked up so much and like
And like oh, I made such a terrible decision
But like it worked out for me and like I fucking make more on patreon now than I ever have and like my fucking
Shit has like like shit has gotten better for me and like
I consider everything I've done to like like I see it as like like I've really succeeded at what I set out to do
Like I've really made good progress towards what I wanted to do
And like the fact that he just like frames it all as the exact opposite of that
Just just what am I even supposed to say to that?
Just like no, I I just wrong wrong and act like incorrect
Wrong like wrong by any metric. Yeah
And like just told just there's there's not even like a basis
There's not even a basis for me to critique that on because it doesn't even get like the basic assumptions of reality, right? Yeah
Holy shit
Should I continue? Yeah
Going from MLP to pokemon with your staggering dead drive
Go ahead and start those numbers did not work here here like move back. Oh, sorry. Sorry. Um
Here
Are you on the thumbnail?
Hold on one fucking second here
Yeah, here I'll reset I'll refresh the pages weird that this keeps happening. Yeah, I guess it wasn't designed to be paused that often
Funny like I think it's explicitly designed to be paused like I thought that was like the point of this
Yeah, but you're like like move the cursor a little bit like like like like move it back and forth a little bit
Yeah, okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, he was strictly coming from you hanging on to everyone else's coattails
So the next time
That's your big breakaway, bennie going from MLP to pokemon with your staggering dead drive boring
Thumbnails those numbers strictly coming from you hanging on to everyone else's coattails
So the next time you look at my videos and go boring
I challenge you to show me your retention to your shitty videos and I bet mine beat the fuck out of yours
By the way, bennie, they don't asking off was the original reason why I turned off the PCP podcast
Nate was working really hard trying to put the show over and then you were there acting like a faggot in the background
See this toilet paper roll. This is your fucking legacy, benn
It's not that I'm not grateful for you giving me a chance when you did bennie, but I ain't nobody's punching bag
Thank you. Fuck you. Bye. Dear lily pete another. I never said anything bad about fngr
Yeah, that rowdy fuckers cop killers. I have no idea what he's talking about
Yeah, and again just to reiterate
We he's not addressing the video. He just does not say what's wrong with the video
No, wouldn't that make more sense to describe what he has a problem with instead of like he he he's like
He's like describing that we are bad without describing why we're bad
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Um, or like what we did to make him think this
He he described like
The only thing that's like slightly like that is how he described that I was like mean to vita
That's the only that's like the only like reason you could give for like no
No, no, no, yeah, yeah, but that wasn't that wasn't even in the video, but at least it was something
At least it was something me. It's just he just like it comes off like he's just dragging me up to try and like prove
That I have failed at something and like that's the point in and of itself
When it's not like I don't know what the point is why now if he's always felt this then why now
I mean the only thing I can think of
Is that he's mad
At me about the fact that I like told him to fuck off on twitter
But like then what was he asking me about on twitter in the first place, you know
Again indescribable he I do not understand this video. It makes no sense
and
Fucking fucking uh talking about talking about how I've like how I'm like writing people's coattails
Like it's not like my fucking nuzlocke's got like crazy promoted or anything
Yeah, like like Nate would retweet them once in a while like when I treat it because he was a big fucking fan of them and love them
Uh, I don't know man. Like what I don't even know what I don't even know how to answer some of these things
Because there are these it's like asking like like it's asking you to explain something that you didn't do
Yeah, like so what am I supposed to say? I just wrong. That was that was not a correct question
Like your accusation is simply untrue and I have no other response. Yeah
Um, I like you're just misinformed sir
I this might be the end of the video about us, but I'm pretty sure that was more
I thought that was more about how I'm like not like I like I like I am just like writing the coattails of digi
I know I think
I think I think we got to that part
First skipping ahead to like the very end
I am I'm skipping around
Skipping through a bunch of lily Pete stuff
wanting to puke. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're right
Weird I could have sworn there was more but uh, yeah, I guess I was just something
There's some cartoon thing at the end. Like I don't know what yeah, there's some like weird like animation
I guess but it like doesn't yeah, I'm pretty sure it's not relevant to us at all. Yeah
Yeah
Well, that was
That was yeah, that was that was fngrs. That was fngrs big takedown of us where he like
Really fucking put us through the ringer and like put us in our place
He threw us some fucking nostalgia critic tier like like insults that we've all heard a thousand fucking times by now
And then I have no weight or gravitas whatsoever
He threw those at us with no context as to why just for the sake of it, I guess just for the mere sake of it
I'll never understand like I don't like I'm sure that if I asked him I'm sure that if I asked him like
Tony
Why were you so mad? What did I do? Like I'm sure that I wouldn't get an answer. Yeah
Yeah
Because what because what what did we do? What could it possibly be?
I I can't even I can't even imagine what he could be mad about because I don't understand him
I mean for you it seems like he's mad at you because vita has some kind of beef with you
So like but for me, it's saying weird
Dispusting human
Jesus
um
The I mean the last thing
The last thing is like there was this other thing that this this some other twitter guy did some guy with like 100 subs
He did like a response to misanthropony
I don't know if you wanted to watch that but he was actually
I actually liked his I thought he like he's kind of like a weird nerd or whatever
He's kind of goofy and like stupid but like I thought he made some good
Shit and I appreciate like even if he's just even just the token effort even just the token even just the fact that someone
That someone else was willing to be like this video makes no sense and is retarded
And uh, you know, it's just nice
It's nice to hear it from an outsider. It's merely just trying to bring reason to do a space or reason
Yeah, yeah, I appreciate I appreciate like this wasn't even like a fan of mine
This was just a guy who saw that video didn't know anything about me
And then was like but wait, here's why this is wrong. Yeah, that's incredible. Yeah, I want to see this
Yeah, did you have you seen this before? No, I haven't. Oh, it's so this is youtuber named misanthropony
He does all sorts of pony related content and from what I've seen it's
I mean his content is okay, I guess
But at the same time I would be lying if I said it left any kind of impact on me
But anyway, recently he did a response this group of people they call themselves the procrastinators or something
Basically, they were skeptical of a situation keyframe found herself in a few years back
Now I'm gonna get something out of the way
I have expressed this taste in keyframes content
Particularly the one review I saw her do with golden fox
However, I am willing to let that slide in the face of more serious issues
Basically a few years ago keyframe had to go fund me. I believe
Started because she was in an abusive household
Ben saint from
Procrastinators
Said in a recent video that he denied this and felt it was an attempt for keyframe to get fame via dr. Wolff
Wolf now I never denied that's not quite what I said, but whatever
however
The best argument against something is a bad one for it misanthropony
At least that's what I would say if misanthropony actually offered up an argument
By a timely point is about 12 minutes into a 20 minute video. So already the majority of the video is done
However
misanthropony doesn't really even debunk ben saint's idea
Instead he just sort of
Complains that he had the idea to begin with instead of debunking. Yeah
He then talks about how hard it is for him to think back about it
Not ignore the fact that someone was actually abused. It was hard for him to think about fact here
I am going to create a very scientific
Yeah, I like it on this whiteboard based off f from jozine. Um, you see this is this is a circle
This is how important it was that she was being abused or whatever
This is how important it was that it made the santhropony uncomfortable. It all was this. Yeah, I fucking like this guy
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Seriously, he said he had a hard time thinking about it. Really
Really
That is actually what he said go to the video. It's in the description if you don't believe me. That is literally what he said
Yeah, now I will give misanthropony the benefit of the doubt and assume that was just bad wording
but
That doesn't escape the fact that it was still at best bad wording at best
Yeah
He mentions doesn't excuse it frame. No, no doesn't prove anything
Anecdotes aren't real evidence misanthropony
For that matter. He claims he has all this evidence and you want to know how much of it he shows in the video
Zero
Not a bit
He just assumes that I should know you have evidence
and actually having evidence
Are two very very different things
And considering how there were people who were around that didn't see the proof such as shelly d for instance
Should at least bring up the fact that you need to show proof at the very very least
He then goes on to spout
Fake humbleness
Guys
He's talking about bad guy. Yeah, oh
The status quo is always right and I've accept that
people
Who have told me that they're right
are right
You know, this guy's fucking red pills fuck. You have a reasonable trusted humanity
And video like a little shit with misanthropony threatening physical violence
Upon ben saint. Yeah
Right, it's to kick ben saint in the balls
That's what it comes down to
Uh misanthropony. I don't think you understand this
But assault is illegal
Okay, we got everyone got that down
And even I at my most hyperbolic don't condone assault
Because it's illegal
And should be illegal before anyone brings up my position on drug war assault should remain illegal. Okay
For that matter, this isn't even a time where I'd be willing to say yes, their words
Count for violence. This isn't like ben saint was saying I'm going to commit violence against you
No, you know what he just said
I'm kind of skeptical about this one situation involving keyframe
That's it
And it's just it's just good that it's good that like someone who doesn't know the situation can like come away with the correct impression
Like in spite of in spite of misanthropony trying to like confuse it as best you can
Yeah
That's what this is
For that matter you guys remember what I said about emotional manipulation
Because people like misanthropony
Are that ideology taken to an extreme?
You are wrong
Because I feel like you are wrong and people are telling me that you are wrong. Therefore you are wrong
And when I ask him
When anyone asked him
Why is he wrong?
misanthropony does not have an answer
He just wants to drum up sympathy and he wants to make it so
Oh, you'll feel horrible if you think you're wrong
You'll feel horrible if you think I'm wrong
When if his arguments were solid, he'd just have to say here's the proof as to why you're wrong
Now shut up. He didn't do that. He didn't show any proof
He just sort of said this was a delicate issue
And then they will preside any fucking reason this shouldn't have convinced anyone
I'd love I'd love to see something
Like I'd love to have come away from that with like a real idea of like exactly what happened
So I could have responded to it in a reasonable way
All right, and everyone go subscribe to that guy. Yeah, go subscribe to f from jozine linked. He's a pretty cool guy
Yeah, yeah, I like him
Maybe he should be I wonder I think I think he does I don't think he's just like a pony guy
I'm pretty sure he just like talks about whatever
The only advice you could possibly give was I'm not on the realm to give advice because it's not like I'm like teaching him anything
But I would just say you don't need to always be on camera and that's pretty much it
Yeah more more concise, I guess
But uh, I don't know. I think I think I think he's got I think yeah
Um, I mean, I know I'm biased because he's like agreeing with me and like defending me
But like I thought yeah, but I thought he made his points pretty I thought he made his points pretty reasonably
Yeah, we're the people who are like thinking cognitively
Cognizant we heard the old who are cognizant at all. It's good. It's good when some cognition can can occur and like be evident
Uh, that's not always the case. No as we've seen as we've seen today here on frog fractions, too
Feels so good. Now, why don't we finish frog fractions, too? And you know that guys this has been too
This has been t-bap. This has been this has been t-bap. Um, two best brothers frog fractions, too
Yeah, right if I could stop killers. I hope you enjoyed
Uh, this and we'll see you next week. I forget. I forget what you said. I'll see you next time with frog fra- with rowdy fuckers cop killers
Seven frog fractions episode two frog fractions two part two
Exactly. All right. Yes. Bye. Bye. Later. Later gator. Yeah later investigator
I hope you enjoyed. Oh, fuck you vita and also fngr and miss fngr. Fuck you miss anthroponi
Oh, oh, wait, you forgot to mention, uh, your your friend dying
Oh, yeah before yeah, yeah, um, I finally blocked fngr because my friend died and I tweeted about it that I was like sad and like
You know, it's sad that someone died
And fucking fngr of all people is like fuck. I'm sorry, man
So I just blocked him because like fuck you trying to come in here and give me your condolences
Because that was the first time I'm pretty sure I'm pretty sure that was the first time he talked to you after that video, right?
It was the yeah, yeah, nothing else had been said
Nothing else has been said so he makes that video kind of a fucking puke full of crap awful awful
While having no like, you know, act later that didn't affect us at all
Just just making like a bitter like vitriolic screed against me for no discernible reason
And then trying to act like and then offering condolences to me because someone I know died
Get fucking disgusting get absolutely fucked you
You fucking vile creature. He is a fucking vile creature vile very vile. Uh, so yeah, uh
That was important but later investigator have a fucking tater
You