PopTrop is one of the holy grail video games that we have to play in RFCK. It's PopTropica,
it's Webkinz, it's Super Smash Bros. Ball, the subspace industry.
You were insisting on Webkinz for a long time and then...
Yeah, we'll get to Webkinz. We will get to Webkinz.
I can't, I can't wait. Hold on.
We have to deal with this demon first though.
Yeah, so he just got messaged, so he just got messaged by our good friend Econ. He wants
to borrow $20, so I'm going to quickly pay Pal him $20.
What does he want?
He says that he spent too much on cards and he needs to buy gas.
That sounds like Econ.
Yeah, you know, he spent, legendarily, he spent over $200 on manga when we were driving
up to Boston. We stopped at, oh god, I always forget the name of some manga store called
Mio Kunio or something? Kino Kunio? I don't know.
No, no, it's probably one location.
Some big Boston manga location and he spent $200 on manga because it was on sale.
Anyway.
What's it like being back in Boston? Do you walk around anywhere or just stay in your
house?
I was walking around a bit, mostly for Pokemon Go purposes. I haven't been doing that for
the last like two weeks or so, two or three weeks, but sometimes crack comes over and
like we'll go out for burgers or stuff. I mostly just hang out with my weirdo roommates
or housemates. I want to say roommates because it just sounds more natural, but we don't
actually live in the same room or anything. We're not on bunk beds.
Well, why not? I'm sure that would save space.
You don't have any bunk beds.
Oh, I'll tell you what you do. Okay, you bunk bed with someone else and then you can turn
your current room into like an office space for recording vlogs. You can set up like a
bunch of posters, you can set up some like Watchmen pages in the background.
I mean, that's pretty much what my room is. It just also has a bed in it.
Well, okay. I mean, it's almost there. How often do you spend time with Tom and Digi?
They like live extremely close to you.
Oh man. Digi told me to come over like two weeks ago. He said, when are you coming over?
Like come over anytime you want. Like come over sometime this week. And I just never
did. I mean, I'm sure the invitation still stands.
I think you might have taken too much time. It's over now.
Yeah, it's over now. The moment has passed.
Ever since we made the secret discord group that only me and Digi are in, where we're
following your demise in the PCP, and we're going to eventually open up to everyone else.
You're going to be kicked that day.
Ever since that day, I think that the invitation has been rescinded.
Here's how I know that I will never... Look, I'm going to jinx it right now and say that
my position in the PCP is bulletproof because I can never be kicked from the PCP no matter
what I do because me and Nate form a voting majority and Nate will never vote against
me.
Wait, what do you mean a voting majority?
There's two of us and that's more than there are of anyone else.
Oh, well, okay. I mean, I didn't do the math. I just assumed that was wrong if I said anything.
Yeah, there's two and two is more than one and everyone else is one.
Right.
So everyone else loses. Yeah, no.
You're probably one of the only people that's bulletproof. I think you're bulletproof. I
mean, Nate probably just because no one has the nerve to.
Me and Nate are both bulletproof.
Everyone else at a moment's notice could be gone.
Yeah, I think so and probably will be. Watch your back.
Sleep with one eye open.
It's interesting that you think that Nate would not vote you out.
Nate would never, of course, Nate would never vote me out.
What makes you think this?
What could ever compel him to vote me out?
Well, that would be like, that would be, I mean, that would be a betrayal.
That would literally be a family betrayal.
If there's one thing that I know Nate has no qualms about, it's betrayal and slash or
killing you.
I mean, he'll do it in Endless War.
Like in Endless War, he's explicitly plotting that.
Out of the open and yet you still fund him.
Yeah, and yet, I don't know.
Ben, start the game. Start Pop Tropica.
Wait, hold on. I have this off in your long game.
Sorry, I have to send the econ $20 for gas.
God damn it. We're on Jesus Christ.
Econ, we're playing Pop Tropica.
I know and he just, he sent me a message like 15 minutes ago and I haven't responded yet.
Hold on, hold on.
If PayPal didn't have banks as an information, I would say do it on the show.
I mean, probably I could show my screen and nothing that sensitive would be released,
but just to be safe and keeping it off screen.
I still believe that one time where you leaked the RFCK password, we had to spin like 30
minutes tracking down like a new one.
Okay.
Good times.
I don't understand. I don't understand living so close to the margin, living so close to
the edge of your means that you have to borrow like, to like $20 is not a lot, like that
that would make the difference in whether you can, are going to make it is weird to
me and seems like really terrifying.
Well, why am I wondering about how he spent so much money on Magic the Gathering cards
that he doesn't have enough money to forget?
Did he like not realize how short he was or did he just make the tactical decision like
knowing that it would screw him over in the future where he just needed those cards in
the temporary?
I think he just lives really close to, and I think not just him, I think lots of people
just live really close to, you know, the brink of financial ruin.
You know the real, like the chain of command here is that your $10 is going to go $10 to
Econ, $10 to Nino.
20. I mean, I don't, I don't care.
I don't care what he does with it.
I mean, I'm just saying that, that he's asked you for money and Nino has asked Econ for
money and God knows who's asked Nino for money, so we don't know how far the chain
goes.
Supposedly, Econ tells me that Nino has gotten better and is not as much of a mooch anymore.
I don't know if anyone can believe that.
So I mean, alright, alright, so my favorite Shakespeare quote is by Polonius in Hamlet
and he says, I'm going to try and quote it off the top of my head, he says, um, neither
borrower nor lender be for loan off loses both itself and friend and borrowing dulls
the edge of husbandry.
So in general, I don't like to lend money and I don't borrow money, but Econ did do
me a big favor back in the day, you know, a couple months ago when he let me crash at
his place for a while, and he's also good about paying back loans.
He's never, he has yet to, he has yet to shaft me.
If he ever shafts me, that will be the last loan I ever make for him, I ever give him,
but he hasn't, it hasn't happened yet, so it's fine.
What's your age band?
Well, how's the highest to go?
It goes with the highest 15.
And only as low as six.
Should I just do random?
Wait, no.
How old is RBCK, well, well, it's definitely not six years old yet.
It's maybe two years old.
Um, let's go 12 of them.
12 it is.
Uh.
We're 12 years, how's it feel to be 12 again?
Ooh.
Oh, neat starfish.
Uh, point and click the mouse to move here.
Can you change the way that you look?
Yes.
Oh my God, this is the, oh, I fucking remember this so vividly.
Incredible.
Incredible beetle.
Beetle.
Uh, hold on.
How big, this seems like, oh, you know what?
Let me, let me, let me change my aspect ratio.
I think I can squeeze a little more of this onto the screen here.
Uh, there we go, getting that high res, high res.
See how well you can make, you can make, uh, the cop killer in here, the cop killer himself.
The cop killer himself.
Oh yeah.
Good old, good old cop kill of, um, Pokemon XD, hey, so I made a, I made a twitch, um,
selection for the Pokemon XD episodes.
I called it like Pokemon XD, heaven or hell, Nuzlocke, um, I don't know, I thought, uh,
you know.
I'm very proud of you.
Yeah.
Thank you very much.
I made, I made a thumbnail.
I made a nice thumbnail featuring, uh, dredge, legendary dredge.
I, I, I saw it.
It was quite nice.
It's nice.
It's maybe not very RFCK, but that's okay, because it's a video game.
Yeah.
It's gonna be way more crushed.
Crushed a high hell.
Hmm.
The, the, the physical, like feet of making that collection must have been incredibly
strenuous.
I'm very proud of you.
It was, you know, it tested my moral fiber.
Like, like, like pushing a bold, they're pressing that keyboard, must have been like
a real fucking, like an all day affair.
Sys, it was a Sisyphean task.
Yeah.
Uh, I think I'm, I'm so jealous and mad at you in every way, but the most, the most,
you know, front facing way that you're so, you're in fucking Boston.
You're squandering.
You're fucking squandering it.
I guess I am kind of squandering it.
You haven't, you haven't been to Diddy's house once.
That's not true.
I've been a couple of times.
Well, whatever.
You haven't been recent.
I have not been in a while.
And ain't good faith.
You have not been there under, under, you know, normal circumstances.
You've just been sneaking around.
Uh.
Fucking snake.
Do we have hats?
Uh, you probably won't be able to get the beard either because, you know, you're 12.
Yeah.
That's true.
Unfortunately.
But there's no hats.
There's no hats.
Well, you know, I mean, does that, is that what your hair looks like?
Yeah.
You look like a hat hair.
There we go.
Yeah.
That looks just like you.
Hey, how's your, uh, how's your quest to become an SJW going to, to infiltrate the,
the liberal flank?
Oh, um, there's only two kinds of eyes.
How is my, my quest to become an SJW, it's, uh, it's been pretty successful.
I've seen, you know, it's, it's, it's already paying dividends.
Um, my social capital is skyrocketing.
Uh, it's through the roof.
Um, my, the moral, I gotta tell you, it feels, feels pretty cool up here on the moral high
ground.
Did you finally have a moral compass to speak of?
Yeah.
Had had any scruples whatsoever.
Uh, yeah.
You know, I, I, who, who would have thought, who would have thought that me, Ben St, the
cop killer would ever have any scruples.
This, this character looks awful by the way.
Yeah.
She's, she's, he's a real nightmare.
There we go.
Jesus Christ.
What's his name?
The quality and discordant solo classical frog.
Comical fang.
Okay.
All right.
Really?
Comical fang.
Stupid.
Look at that roll.
Wait, how do I, how do I make him do that?
What the hell?
Whoa.
Yeah.
It is.
I know controls.
It's like Mario.
Wow.
Splendid.
Oh, he jumped into the little.
Yeah.
Do you want to go?
Are you, are you down?
Are you ready to go to pop tropical?
I don't know.
Does he, does he look ready to you?
Um, he'll never look ready.
He looks like an unbaked chicken.
There we go.
All right.
That's the exact look I was going for.
Oh my fucking god.
Get ready.
You're going to have to pick your, your island.
It might chop you off on an early pop chop guy.
Actually, it might, it might auto pick you the first one.
Do you want to learn how to play pop tropical?
I'm, I gotta say I'm pretty ambivalent about that prospect.
Uh, hold on.
Once again, I have, I have cut off some, besides the window keeps changing.
I'll, I'll figure it out.
We can't, we can't lose a single pixel of this gold.
No.
Yeah.
Listen, it took thousands of artists and thousands of programmers to do this.
We got to pay them more respect.
We got to press F to pay them more respects.
This feels so wrong.
I think this is a new, I think it's a new tutorial.
Don't you hate it when they go back and they improve your favorite video games?
Yeah, I really do.
I really sincerely do.
My favorite items were, were shark tooth island.
I liked the one with the, the rap that one was good too.
Are you here early pop truck is hard.
Are you hearing the music?
No, I can't hear any music.
Is it good?
I can only assume.
I actually like it quite a bit.
I'm glad it's here.
It makes it feel like a real experience.
Oh, uh, where, where are we?
We're in the middle of pop tropical.
It's a race.
Oh, what?
Yeah, this is definitely new.
This is definitely new and I hate it.
Their eyes move.
Where your, where your cursor moves.
Look at you.
Look at your eyes.
Oh, I'm seeing it.
Let's go.
Is this how you respond if this were happening in real life?
Would you have this cabler attitude?
Yeah.
And that smile on your face.
You should say, we should save it.
It might run into a storm up on this rickety old plane.
Yes, please.
I can see you saying that.
Click the save.
I, the music is actually pretty loud.
I'm going to turn it down a little bit.
I didn't want to click the save button to create a username and password.
We're going to be living on the edge.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Why does the window size keep changing?
I don't know.
It's, hold on.
I'm going to, I'm going to take, okay, username.
You know, you know, the old saying is, you know, absence makes the heart go stronger.
You know, you might think, you know, it's been so many years since I've been able to
take in my, in my old, with my old flame, you know, play this, this classic video game.
And you think yourself, you know, maybe it won't impress me when I go back to it.
My nostalgia goggles may be shattered to a thousand pieces, but I'm happy to see that
PopTropic is just as how I remember it.
And it's splendid.
And there's nothing that can taint it in my mind.
Yeah.
And that's, and that's going to be the arc of this video, everyone.
Not having his memory of PopTropic attainted by the green reality.
Some arc, if, if, if I get over it in the first 10 minutes and some arc.
Oh, oh, oh, look, chocolate Frosted Flakes, a banner added on the side.
Well, I'm in the mood for chocolate.
We got, we got, we got to see that.
We got to see that.
Check, check that out every, every pony.
Sponsored by Frosted Flakes.
Welcome Races.
What the fuck is happening right now?
Race to win credits and this medallion.
This has nothing to do with anything.
This is like fake and weird and I don't understand it.
This is what PopTropic is.
No, it's not.
It's not true.
They've changed it.
Can I, can I go somewhere else?
Do that.
How do you get, how do you get cool costumes?
By costumizing.
I'll show, I'll show you how.
Now.
Ooh.
The more, the more, the more I feel like you've hit the nail on the head here.
Exciting our character.
Click to keep, click on the parts you want to try.
Is the only difference in character sprite that she's got eyelashes?
Yeah.
This is awful.
No, you got, no.
Yep, I did it.
I'm just going to be a.
Oh, you ruined it.
You fucking, I was just saying how perfect our character design was.
Well, not anymore.
Can you swap your skin color?
I cannot.
I cannot just click on his skin and get his skin color.
You know, this is actually horrible.
What do you mean?
I miss the old one.
Yeah.
You can't change it back either.
You fucked up.
Okay.
Click on all the buttons.
Save up.
Okay.
That's the closet.
This would wait.
Hold on.
There's one more button I haven't tried.
No.
No, it's over, Ben.
Man.
God damn.
This game is.
You want to restart?
This game has a vicious learning curve.
Maybe you can get out of this tutorial too.
No, I'm sure.
I'm sure I can fuck around with it later.
We're ready.
You're going to do some weird fucking minigame.
It makes no sense.
It isn't related to the game at all.
Look, there are the islands down there.
The whole point of this game is there's like a thousand islands to explore.
You're on the fucking sky right now.
What a great start.
Is that you in the back there?
This is just a cutscene.
What is happening?
We're setting up a villain.
Sorry to throw our wrench.
Stop trying to say I'm a villain.
It doesn't have its over.
What is happening?
Sorry to throw a literal wrench in your literal plans.
Sorry to make you fucking crash into the ocean.
Thank you for showing me this game, Munchie.
I'm glad.
Oh, maybe I can get that monkey costume.
Oh yeah, maybe.
Clear the map up there.
Click on the map.
Up in the top right.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Do you mean the menu?
Yeah, the menu.
I think you want me to follow him.
Okay.
The controls of this game are so satisfying.
You know what?
Also, we got to play Super Mario 63.5,
which is the Newgrounds Flash game.
That's a 2D rendition of Super Mario 64.
It has the best controls of the new Mario game.
Uh, sick.
Hey, I saw you...
Speaking of...
You ever played that 2D portal game that's on Newgrounds?
No, I didn't.
Oh, I played Terraria, though.
Crush the crab.
Squish.
They don't allow violent violence on this video game.
Well, then what kind of video game...
Isn't that a novelty?
No violence in a video game.
Terrible.
Waste of my goddamn...
Waste of my goddamn time.
Friends, home, settings, mute, costumeizer...
Holy shit.
I can't change my outfit.
What is...
What? Lego City?
Look at that Lego guy.
He just is a Lego person.
He's way taller than you are.
Oh.
Oh, he's awful.
He's a nightmare.
I wonder if I can costumeize myself.
Oh my god, please.
No, I won't let me.
Talk to him.
What's his deal?
Quick, get in.
Okay, you have to get out of here.
Find the mammoth.
Oh, you know what game we got?
Oh, okay.
I don't know what you're doing right now.
Wait, why am I still on screen?
Why can I still see myself?
Are you controlling the ship as well?
Yeah.
Oh.
I don't think my character is supposed to be here.
Well, you know, maybe it's like a metaphorical,
maybe it's not literal.
I don't know anything.
It's like a metaphorical vision of yourself.
Yeah, alright.
Where's the guns?
Where's the violence?
I need violence in this game.
As far as I can tell.
What is a video game without violence?
As far as I can tell, I have no weapon.
Oh, I did it.
I got to the mammoth.
Thank God.
Now, buy our product.
Follow.
You have to get out of here.
Oh, press space bar to use the power.
Wait, what?
You have to go.
Oh, shit.
Oh, looks like I'm doing it again.
We have to stop this.
I'm sorry, I gotta find the mammoth.
Jesus Christ.
I mean, it's not gonna find itself.
I'm so happy that violence has returned to our video game.
Ever since that white fucking...
Oh, God.
Shit, we forgot.
Yeah, that was the whole point of this video.
Yeah, violence reigns supreme once again in Slime City.
I'm so happy that we've come to our senses
and we've started a whole new gang warfare era.
Yeah.
From our senses and stopped just lazing around the apartment
and we're finally recruiting more children to do our bidding.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The proxy violence has picked up again.
The proxy child-based violence.
My favorite kind of violence, in fact.
In fact, the only kind that I personally engage in.
Do you want a scoop of gang warfare?
Yeah, child-flavored, please.
Okay.
We finally found it.
Alright, get out of this Lego-based hell, please.
I can't.
I cannot do it.
Holy shit.
This is against all what PopTropica stands for.
Is it so?
This is what PopTropica is and was always meant to be.
This is a nightmare.
Where's Sharktooth Island?
Where's early PopTropica?
I didn't need this tutorial level.
Oh my god.
Another happy landing.
I don't know why she's British in your mind.
Because that's what the Obi-Wan Kenobi says.
Oh, right.
And this is clearly a Christ allegory.
It's too high.
I can't get that high, bro.
Just watch me.
Yeah, so viewer, listen, right now,
right now, as this video exists,
a war is on,
and you can go and click the fucking link in the description
to join the Discord and start killing children
like you always wanted to.
You can also role-play as a child so it will be less heinous.
Yeah, much less heinous.
I don't know adult killing a child is reprehensible,
but a child killing another child is a-okay.
It's fair game.
It's level playing feeling that way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, you know, you can live out all your child.
The point is that we're like,
we're basically Coney.
We're basically Coney, but there's two of us.
You know, we got our child soldiers.
Double the Coney.
We should run for president.
Forget about being mayor.
We should run for African warlord.
Where can I find a wrench?
I guess.
I guess I need one.
Maybe that monkey knows.
Where'd he go?
All right.
Come on.
I feel like pop-trop is the natural evolution of endless war.
I feel like this was more like in 10 years.
This is what-
It's full of Lego products.
Yeah.
Oh, we have to do-we have to add a new mini-game.
We have to add the mammoth finding
at the very end of charcoal park.
You have to be able to find the mammoth.
I swear to God, I'm going to kill myself.
Why?
Why would you kill yourself?
I hate this game.
I hate what's happening here.
Why?
No.
Where's Gun Gale Island?
Fucking solve the crab puzzle.
What crab puzzle?
Right here.
All right.
Release the crab.
Just-no, Jesus Christ.
Okay, I need to take over control of this game.
Well, guess what?
It's too late.
You can't do it.
Oh, wow, I did it.
Look how smug I am about it, too.
I know.
These are going to look like the entire-the entire playthrough.
I can't-I need to find some better costume pieces.
Yeah, that's really the most important thing.
I don't like being a pilot.
No one does.
Not even pilots.
Hey, so my-the only thing worthwhile about me has passed.
Like, my magic is gone in all the desirable aspects.
You're not a child soldier anymore.
Now you're a filthy adult general.
So all the things that people would be, like, impressed by.
Like, all of my, like, social capital has instantly plummeted.
And now-and now I have no more, you know, interest to my name.
There's nothing more people latch onto.
Yeah, the one-the one thing about you is it's over.
It's over now.
And it's never coming back, so...
Now, now, now people can't be like,
oh, you know, like, he's cool for, like, a kid.
Now they just will have to say, oh, you know.
Now you just have to be-he's not cool.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
There's no more qualifiers.
No more excuses.
It's all-it's all downhill from here.
Can-can confirm.
Here we go.
W-what's-what's-give me some pointers, Ben.
What's-what's it like?
Um, well, it's kind of like, uh...
Look how ha-look how pleased I am about what just happened.
Um, it's kind of like...
It's kind of like, um...
Getting, like, sucker punched in the gut every morning.
Mm-hmm.
Um, and just having to live with it.
And not-not being able to take revenge on the person doing it.
Because life itself.
Because life itself is the one inflicting this on you.
Um, yeah.
So I should kill myself, is what you're saying?
You should, but you won't.
Because part of the-part of the curse is that you're too much of a coward.
Now that-now that you're an adult, you're too much of a coward to do it.
You-you aren't brave like you used to.
If-if it were-if it were any other day,
then you'd be able to kill yourself willy-nilly, it wouldn't matter.
But now that you're an adult, you're too coward.
Yeah. Yeah.
Once...
So-so-so, you know, you're trapped now. You're fucked.
You know, I-that's why-that's why adult suicide is way more admirable than child suicide.
Because when you're a child, it's not that impressive.
You know, you could snap your own neck for, you know, at a moment's notice.
When you're an adult, you have to really consider it.
Yeah.
And that makes it way more respectable.
You have to, like, work out.
You have to, like, work out to do it.
Imagine an adult.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It reminds me of when I was a young adventurer.
I was a young man preparing to live my dream.
She's-she's calling him out for talking too much after, like, two lines of dialogue.
Um, yeah, sure.
W-what's-so what's the story so far in this?
Well, we crash landed on an island.
And that's it.
We gotta fix our plans.
We meet some indigenous tribes.
I think they're all tourists like us.
I think we're all just pretending.
The-the indigenous population has been wiped out by syphilis for generations.
The syphilis?
Which we brought.
We brought in springs.
Me and-me and Orange here just gave each other syphilis on the ride over.
And now we're spreading it.
Well, you know what they say, syphilis hurts, but once you get over it, you get over it.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, it's like chicken pox.
Yeah.
Juice machine.
Come on.
Uh-oh.
Whoa, that angry monkey's got all the fruit.
What's he hogging it for?
Pretty soon there's gonna be syphilis shots.
It's gonna-it's gonna end it all, basically.
We-we can't let him have them on this island now.
How do I get this fruit to them?
I-I was walking down the street yesterday.
I was walking back from Chipotle and there was this homeless guy, you know, just hobbling along with, you know, dirt in his skin and stuff like that.
And my instantly, he didn't even, like, look, man, I don't even know if he registered me the entire time, but he just, you know, was walking behind me.
My instant first thought was, if we get into a fight, I can't let his blood touch mine.
I have to be able to cover myself in such a way that he will never bleed onto me.
Yeah.
Because then I will get syphilis.
That's the, um, that's the, uh, like, that's the real challenge in the fight.
The actual, like, fight itself doesn't matter, but as long as I-as I don't get the blood on me, then I'll be fine.
Yeah.
I mean, I mean, the fight itself poses no challenge.
Uh-huh.
Uh, due to his, you know, due to his condition.
His-his stature.
Uh, do you know what I'm supposed to do here?
No, I've never played a game before in my life.
Oh, here we go.
It's completely alien to me.
This has to be.
And frankly, it's scary.
Look.
I moved the fruit.
Look at the animation.
I just need more power.
Oh.
Jesus.
I fell through a thing.
Clever.
Oh, look, some rope.
Uh, wow.
That'll prove useful in the coming battle.
At least we got the fruit up there and the rope in the process.
At least we accomplished the thing that we were doing.
And I'll make a little quip about it and hit this lever.
Uh, I need to find a second.
Who's the writer of this game?
Where can I find the sta-
I wrote this game.
Oh.
Well, you did a really great job.
Yeah.
I know I did.
You fucking idiot.
Uh.
Let's see.
I'm-I'm on the pop-tropica wiki right now.
Pop-tropicon, a convention.
Oh.
Ooh.
That's almost- that sounds almost as tempting as Nickelodeon Slime Fest.
Wait.
Excuse me?
Okay, it's not-
Sorry, I'm at the Slime Corp.
Slime Fest.
Okay.
It is not a convention in real life.
It's a convention within pop-tropica itself.
Oh.
It's-it's-it's-it's an island that is based on conventions.
Uh, I-
So it's a level that you play inside of a convention center.
Is-is the-have any items for me?
Uh, yeah.
I've got, uh-fucking let me click the fucking-what?
Oh, it's based off the fucking San Diego Convention Center.
So it has, like-
Oh my god.
What is happening?
Okay, I'm looking at images of it.
It's a nightmare.
Why would you make a video game level off of a convention center?
With the-like has-has like a-like a comic-con going on in it.
Uh, hey, are you seeing what's going on here?
No, I've long since looked away from the screen.
Okay, well, like, I can't click on anything.
Uh, did you save your progress?
No.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm just getting-I don't think it's showing up on OBS,
but I'm just getting a little, like, spinning thing that seems to mean that it's loading,
and there's nothing-
That's fine.
We'll-we'll just restart.
Don't worry.
It's fine.
Oh my god.
Ugh.
No, don't worry.
This is a-this is a blessing disguise.
Now that we-now we can avoid the, uh, the tutorial.
This is the way things were meant to be.
So you've been staying in the house a lot lately?
I have.
That's true.
Yeah, that's true.
Is there any particular reason, or is it just-
I mean, what's really out there for me?
Fame.
Wealth.
Women.
Ugh.
Return.
Hmm.
Where?
No.
Did you click on it?
Yeah, of course I did.
Why?
Why would you do this?
I don't know.
This is the game.
You had-you had the chance-
This is-this is the game!
This is the game!
Are we-are we here to play pop-are we here to play pop-tropica or not?
Fuck's sake.
Oh god.
At least I would be having fun seeing the game be played that I remember.
This is the game you remember.
This is the game.
No, it's not!
It's a betrayal!
You're a perversion and a betrayal.
I know you are, but what am I?
Well, I guess I'm an Arctic guy now.
I'm a betrayal, I'm a perversion.
That's what your mom said to me when we had sex last night.
Oh no, not that.
It's not- not again.
I still need that cloth.
What?
Oh, sick. Alright, now we're making progress. Now we're cooking the gas.
I have basically spent the entire like past four years inside my room. Almost like never
venturing outside. I've become a hikikomori.
I went out to get the, okay, so I went out to Kelly's roast beef last night to get some,
you know, I went out with, you know, Crack and my friend John.
Is that roast beef, the same derogatory slur roast beef that is spoken by many incels on
the internet?
Yeah, it is, in fact.
Okay.
Just wanted to make sure.
But so I went out and I got, you know, I wanted a keto, right? So I said, no bun, just put
it on lettuce.
And the resulting sandwich was literally just a small pile of sliced roast beef with a slice
of American cheese on top of it.
And it cost me $12.
Was it worth it?
No.
What a retarded question.
Playing machine balloons, drink, me, bucket.
Okay.
Uh, when the animation skills on display here, man, I'll bet you and I could get jobs working
at PopTrapica.
And what jobs they would be.
These were the brains behind the offer.
I'm going to die from playing this game.
I hate it.
Our career path would be so rock solid.
Yeah.
We would be, um, on, it's over.
I think it's over.
I think it's done.
Just getting, I think getting the blimp and then leave forever.
Well, I'm trying.
You click on it.
You click on it, my man.
Oh, there we go.
Where's Crusoe?
He's going to be here to send us off, probably taking a nap somewhere to get back in the
race.
He's actually, he's actually just going to the bathroom and he wants to get off this
just God forsaken island without him.
Yeah.
Like he needed us.
Okay.
What's like, this is still happening.
We're going to win somehow.
Yeah.
We just spent like two hours on my island in like canonical time.
Uh, yeah, this is how you go faster in a hot air balloon as you drop ballast.
Yeah.
Just, just fucking let us just fly up in the sky.
Oh my God, you're so close, dude.
Oh no.
Oh my God.
Jesus Christ.
This is nothing to break your fall.
Somehow the balloon descended faster than I fell.
Okay.
You're going to have to beat the shit out of him.
Yeah.
I'm going to have to take a gun.
I'm just going to have to start shooting.
Is no one else seeing this?
Is no one else able to report to the authorities?
He's dropping metal on you.
Oh, it's awesome.
Ben as a physicist, is this probable?
Is this how, is this, is this, is this likely?
I can't.
I can't, you know, I think when we started a hot air balloon race, I think this was
the inevitable result.
I think this was, this was unavoidable.
All right, here we go.
You're out of tricks to red Baroness.
Now that we've dropped all our ballast, our hot air balloon is as fast as your, as your,
as your tri-
Procolic plane.
Tri-plane, yeah.
Oh look.
Here he was.
He escaped from his, he escaped from his monkey hell like he always wanted.
Well-
Go slave, free us from losing.
We're cat, yeah, I want to drop you.
I want to, I want to drop you out of my plane.
Can, can you, what, what are you doing?
What can happen right now?
I don't know.
It's telling me to drop weight.
And I'm clicking on everything.
Oh, am I carrying anything heavy?
I'm, I'm, I'm, is it the helicopter?
Could it be the helicopter?
Dude, dude, dramatic irony, dramatic irony!
Oh, I almost hit her.
Oh, he's gonna, he's gonna make the ultimate sacrifice?
The pathos on display here is overwhelming.
Now, to win this race.
What?
I just, what the hell?
From a little juice, okay.
I, I can't, this is such a dangerous unregulated race.
I can't believe I'm 12 year old then.
Looks like Crusoe is just, you know, he's just such a disaster.
He's just such an unmitigated, incompetent fool
that his mere presence in that plane ruined.
Oh, and we won despite being beached for like 18 days.
Um, thanks.
It was a shortcut.
Yeah.
Landing and not flying was a shortcut to the end of the race.
Alright, you have to leave. You have to leave this place and be.
Congratulations on winning the race.
No, I did it.
No, look, I'm an esteemed member of society now.
You get one of those medallions whenever you complete like an island.
Alright.
Whoa, look at that slime girl on the left over there.
Oh no.
Look at that RFCK.
Shit.
Did you see on Twitter that I officially declared war on the phrase cute girls?
Uh, I, I did not see, I saw a response to that tweet.
I know the one you're, yeah, why?
I mean, actually I probably agree.
I'm probably in full agreement in what you're about to say.
It's, it's because the phrase cute girls is always accompanied with like slimy, disgusting people
who just want to, all they want to do is just draw, draw girls in different stages of undress,
fucking obnoxiously in forever.
I think it's obnoxious too.
When I see, like some people they're just like, I draw cute girls.
It's like you're a pervert.
Yeah.
Um, which is fine, I guess.
If you want to go to jail.
Visit the map.
You got to visit the map.
How?
How do I do that?
Click on the button that says visit the map.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, it works.
Oh, here we are.
Should I go home?
Oh my God.
No, should I go to next gen?
No, that's way too dangerous.
Should I go to Lego City?
No, go, go to early PopTropica.
That's the first island.
I don't know where you just keep going until you see it.
PopTropica Worlds.
No.
Time-tagled Mission Atlantis.
Frosted Flakes.
Legendary Swords.
Survival.
There's some crazy shit going.
They've added way more on's than I remember.
Galactic Hot Dogs.
Timmy Failure.
Go all the way to the end.
All right.
Skip all these.
Vampires Cryptids.
That's pretty interesting.
You got some interesting choices here.
Mocktropica.
Oh, is that SharkTooth Island right there?
Is that...
Yeah, SharkTooth.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, you go.
Is that where you want to go?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just want to look at everything.
Oh, Big Nate.
Oh, and Great Pump.
Oh, Wimpy Wonderland.
Holy fucking shit.
Oh, my God.
Okay, for the next episode,
we have to get Monkey Island,
so we can go and Wimpy Wonderland.
Yeah, we can bring him to Wimpy.
We got Wimpy.
He's on the Wimpy board.
Okay, yeah.
He's...
All right.
I'll have my people.
I'll have my people talk to his people.
Yeah, yeah.
SharkTooth.
Only you can save it if it's...
I guess I will play...
this video game.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, what have I done?
Oh, wow.
The, um...
God, the fucking aspect ratio keeps changing.
I hope it hasn't been like this for too long.
This game's horrible, by the way.
This game's...
No!
This is the worst sign.
This is like...
It's like, what if Neopets were even worse?
What if...
It's...
What if Neopets were the worst game ever conceived by man?
It's what if video games reached their natural evolutionary course,
and they became the full thing they were meant to be from the very beginning.
Good.
Uh, SharkTooth.
SharkTooth.
It's what if video games became palatable.
The aspect ratio just keeps changing.
It just won't stop.
It's probably because it was meant to fill the computer screen,
but computer screens have changed aspect ratio,
and they just didn't bother formatting it differently, I guess.
It's meant to fill your life with pain.
Get a fart.
Yeah, yeah, a shark skin.
Shark fin.
So, did I put it on or what?
No, you can put it on if you'd like, though.
Well, of course I would.
Oh, put on a smile.
Actually, no, keep your smile.
It's very nice.
Okay, well, you've ruined it.
Too late.
Looks like I can't take my hood off.
Ever since you found that yeti, you've just had to keep it on.
I just have to be an ice climber now.
Look at that cafe.
Oh, this is what Hawaii was like in real life.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is just what it was like.
I'm pretty jealous.
Yeah, I get off the planet like,
here's your committer of shark fin.
Please put it on.
What?
Look at this.
Yeah, what?
What's the problem then?
What is it now?
Nothing.
Put it on the show.
It's on, okay?
Okay, okay.
I'm going to the coconut cafe already.
Fuck's sake.
Oh, this puts me back in my little space.
Roll over a player.
A player?
What?
Yeah, there's gonna be people who have to shoot in here.
Well, normally there would be other players,
but I think no one plays this game anymore.
You think so?
Well.
Do you think that might be the case?
I don't want to be the case.
Yeah, I wonder if I can meet up with you in Pop Tropica.
Yeah, hold on.
Please.
Yeah, I'm gonna try that right now.
We're gonna do some co-op right now.
It's so lonely at the top.
Don't worry, I'm gonna come rescue you.
PopTropica.com.
Get yourself to the coconut cafe.
Yeah, I'm gonna speed up the shoot.
And let's engage in some gang violence.
To celebrate the relaunch of Endless War.
Hey, look at this slime coin.
See?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, it basically is.
Little slime coin there.
Got a little slime coin.
How old am I?
Six.
Half my age.
My name is Silly Monster.
I look like a pedophile.
Hold on.
Well.
Costumerizer.
I gotta be black.
First of four months I have to be black.
Yeah, because you're the opposite of me.
Yeah.
We're like yin and yang.
Oh no, I took the shark off.
All right, I actually prefer the hood.
I don't want to be a Roman man.
How did I get here?
I should be on Time Twisted Island.
Well, sorry.
Sorry, buckaroo.
All right, I'm coming for you.
I'm coming for you, bub.
This is the kind of wholesome RFCK
that everyone strives for.
This is the sort of RFCK that you can, like,
download and, like, put on your phones
so you can listen to it on your commute to work every day.
Hey, how come, uh...
I'm looking good.
How come the...
I forget.
Oh, the music brand.
How about the music? Where'd the music go?
It was good for a minute there.
I was listening.
The intro had music.
Well, it's an atmospheric, it's like a tone piece.
Oh, look, Lego City again.
All right, here, all right.
Go to the Coconut Cafe.
I'll meet you inside.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
I'm waiting.
Oh, there you are.
There you are.
Hold on.
Battle.
Uh, balloons,
Starlink,
Paint Wars, Skydive.
Wait, I thought we had to shoot each other.
Yeah, I have to friend you.
Uh, I'll have to make a username first.
Okay, well, it's a good thing my keyboard doesn't work.
God, I'm looking good.
All right, hold on.
All right, well, my keyboard, literally,
is not responding right now for some reason.
Just in pop-shop, okay, it just won't work.
Why does it say that my name is Comical Fang
when I clearly called myself Cop Killer?
Well, it's usually the choice at the beginning of the game.
Oh, shit, I left.
I can't do anything.
My life is ruined.
Why?
Why don't you just play the game like I did?
We can't see each other outside this room, by the way.
Yeah, I figured.
Okay, great.
Can we shoot each other in here?
I don't know how.
Can I come to play at a chair battle?
I just asked you a question.
Oh.
What an illegal alien that is.
Hey, kid, can you tell your parents
to meet me at the corner of third and fifth?
I don't have a ride.
Hey, kid, can I borrow 20 books?
I spent all my money on Magic Gathering cards.
I'm going to roll.
All right, this sucks.
Yeah, we're going to speedrun this.
We're going to see who gets to win the game first.
It's probably going to be you.
Yeah, that's why you have to try.
Because I have to admit,
I'm really not putting my best foot forward on this.
Just go all the way around here.
Wait, a shark museum.
No, no, don't get distracted.
We have a shark pool.
There's a shark.
We all know that sharks take showers, not baths.
Hold on.
I want to steal this guy's outfit.
Oh, I'm in the fucking side scrolling section
that I used to play all the time as a baby.
I can't even click on anything that he's wearing.
Okay, fine.
Waste of time.
Okay, go all the way to the right
and go to the fucking shark ruins.
That's how you know you're going to get into some mad shit
when sharks build ruins.
Yeah, that's pretty...
It's the ancient ruins, not the shark ruins.
It's on Shark Island, though.
Well, alright.
God, this Lego city is everywhere.
Well, they need to get money somehow, Ben.
Well, I don't think it's working.
I had a page from Hammerhead's journal,
but the wind blew it onto the roof.
Oh, look, a coconut.
Alright, it's going to stop playing now.
Yeah, I'm jealous.
Man, this man sucks to be you.
I wish I could do that.
But this is what the people have demanded.
This is what we had to do to fulfill our
contractional obligations.
Jesus Christ.
Alright, hey, look, I made it.
Oh, look, I fell.
Oh, look, I jumped.
Oh, I...
A bat hit me.
I don't even have any health.
I can't even die, can I?
This is like Wario's Adventures in Wario Adventureland.
Yeah, that's almost exactly what the name is.
Here we go, here we go.
I made it.
Now, you meet an indigenous native.
Hello, do you have syphilis?
Would you like some?
Would you like some syphilis, please?
There's a study journal in the Shark Museum,
but the translation key is missing.
Oh, my God.
Why is this guy over here?
How did he get over here?
How can I get through that door?
I'll have to decide for the code.
What are you doing?
I've been studying those hieroglyphics by the door.
Oh, wow.
Here, here, go to the door.
I'll get the walkthrough open.
Ben, don't pretend and act like
you're above this.
Where's the door?
It's to the left.
Alright.
Here we go.
Alright, let me figure out how to do this.
Are these Japanese?
No, they're not Japanese.
Some of them look a little like Japanese.
No, not all non-English characters are Japanese.
I'm just saying, this one right here in the middle
looks pretty much like Japanese.
I'm just going to brute force it.
It's fine.
Okay, okay, okay.
No, no, no, don't worry.
Okay, okay, I got it.
Alright, listen to me, listen to me.
There's only like three possible combinations.
No, no, okay, I got it.
Okay, so the two things that like,
like two V's on top of one another, do that.
Yeah.
Alright, then you're going to want to do
the fucking thing that looks like a Japanese letter.
It's like two boxes with like a dash through it.
Yeah, that, yeah, yeah.
Then you want to do the box that has like a,
like a corner, a bottom right corner below the box.
Yeah, that.
And then the last one is like the, god damn it.
No, okay, okay, then you want to do the swirly,
the swirly, the little swirly.
Hey, I did it.
You did it.
How did you know?
Oh, call it a beginner's law.
Call it a beginner's, I will.
Oh my God.
Call it instinct, man.
Call it instinct.
Call it team instinct.
Hmm, hashtag.
Whoa, a nasty creepy crawly.
I can't believe you're a disgusting team mystic.
Ew, gross.
I don't like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
I'm thinking about mystics too.
No one told me this game was rated M for mature
for having creepy crawlies.
Oh, that is a really disgusting display.
Yeah.
I miss the music, honestly.
I kind of was enjoying myself when there was music.
And how it's just a silent period piece.
Yeah.
What's the word?
A relic.
Yeah.
Like a weird mausoleum of video games.
Imagine if you raid someone's grave
and then this game starts playing.
No.
I'm going to have this, I'm going to be buried
in a little electric, a little power cell computer
that just plays pop-tropic.
Imagine you're a down-trap man.
You're a popper and you just need whatever money you can
to survive so you resort to raiding people's graves
and then you raid someone's tomb
and then as soon as you do you hear a voice from behind
and you turn around to a Lego figure
and he says, hey, can you help me find the mammoth?
Don't be, I found that mammoth though.
I found that mammoth real good.
Do you think there's a, Jesus Christ, Ben.
What?
What is your problem?
Why are you yawning?
And there's no problem.
Why would there be a problem, you idiot?
It's not like someone's got an attitude.
No.
That's what I don't appreciate.
I have a great attitude.
I have, my attitude is that of a winner.
That of a winner, Munchy.
Hey, wait, what did the Batman give you?
I don't know, did he give me something?
I'm sure you must be something in that room, right?
Says who?
I talked to him, I asked him all three things.
You got it all done.
Look at the, okay, look at the banner on the side there.
The fucking banner ad for smallfoot.
The fucking most blight on American civilization
that's ever happened.
Yeah, I imagine that John Cena probably voices smallfoot.
Yeah, probably.
He's voicing all the kid's characters nowadays.
Yeah, he's that boy.
He's SpongeBob.
Now he beat up Tom Kenny in WWE.
And now he's SpongeBob.
He's the world-famous Lego City Manus.
Here we go.
Costumizer.
It's time to become, look at this.
Pure purple.
Oh, reminds you of someone?
And the cop killer.
There we go.
Look at your ghastly white skin.
Your fucking ghoulish sway palms.
So I got the old bone.
I assume that's good.
Now to bed.
Man, I didn't think this is what my day was going to be like.
I didn't think-
What did you think your day was going to be like?
I woke up.
I didn't think I was going to be having a great time with my best friend, Munchy.
But boy, how I was wrong.
Have you ever played a good game on the show?
Yeah, Frog Fractions 2.
And one.
No.
Heck, it sucks.
No, Frog Fractions 2 was awesome.
Okay, Frog Fraction 1 is good.
Frog Fraction 1 is really great, and Frog Fraction 2 carries on its legacy almost flawlessly.
Disgusting.
Can I-
Oh, fuck.
Let's turn this into the sad RFCK.
We've had episodes ranging from being happy to being like, you know, reflective.
Yeah.
We've had moments of anger.
We haven't had like a sad RFCK.
Have we not?
Aren't they all kind of?
No.
When you get right down to it.
Not in a meta way, yeah.
Okay, so we're turning subtext into pure text here.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I can't think of a better game to do it with.
Where were you when your first family member died?
I was crashing a plane to the Twin Towers.
The family member was screaming.
Oh, I can't.
I can't stay awake.
What, Bind?
Okay, you knew we were recording today.
I don't know why you woke 10 minutes ago.
Yeah, and I got a good night's sleep and everything, you know.
Did you have another soiree?
Or seance, I'm sorry.
No, I did not have another seance.
I just woke up and didn't want to.
I was just like, why can't I just sleep forever?
Can you imagine a seance soiree?
The double?
I think, you know, our seance was kind of, it did kind of double as a soiree to be perfectly,
to be perfectly frank.
You know, okay, you know, it's a follow up to the hashtag follow up on last episode.
The main reason I want to become a politician is that I can get invited to spirit cooking parties.
Like, I can dine and dash on some corpses with my big age here.
My big Hillary.
The big age.
You know about spirit cooking, Ben?
No, I don't know about spirit cooking.
Spirit cooking is what the elite, the elite of the country do.
Whenever they get bored, they just bring up some corpses and cook them like a pot roast.
And then they dip some spoons in and they get a mouthful of the dead stew.
And it's spirit cooking because there's a spirit inside the stew and the cooking.
Uh, how do you know there's a spirit?
Where's your proof?
Oh, I died.
Wait, no, I just fell.
Uh, okay.
Uh, so I have a big, whoa, I got crushed by a coconut.
I have a bone.
I have an old bone.
Uh, I guess I'll just keep going to the right because that medicine man said,
See, he said he doesn't look like a native islander.
I thought if I just, oh my God, Lego city.
I thought if I just stole his mask that that would work, but it didn't.
Yeah, it's like between every room is an ad for Lego city.
Uh, grass skirts.
I'll bet maybe this will make me into a native islander.
Yep, you'll look like a native islander.
Here we go.
Come on.
You can tell by the limp if they're a native, a native American.
A native Sharktuthian.
Oh, appropriate that culture then.
Put that on.
Yeah, I have to.
Otherwise the medicine man won't do unspecified services for me.
Old bone.
It's an old bone from the temple ruins.
Uh, okay.
Here we go.
Yeah, I got a grass skirt.
I'm a native.
I have appropriated their culture and now I'm going to go appropriate this medicine man's goods and or services.
Where were you the first time that the news came on your television that they had refound the first man myth?
Um, I think I was...
I was at my dad's family members funeral.
I think I was under the table.
I think I was under my coffee table, sipping Hennessy.
Trying to make the pain go away.
Yeah, smoking a cigar like a Hollywood fat cat exec.
You know, just living my best life.
This Lego city man myth is really haunting us.
Oh, yeah, over on the left there.
Yeah.
I'll spare the viewer.
But like every single time your fresh as a prey page, a new ad shows up and it's almost always the Lego city man.
Yeah, there it is, right there.
Well, there were chocolate frosted flakes.
Um, there's Lego city mammoth.
There's that Yeti movie.
The Yeti movie makes me so fucking upset.
It's so awful.
There's no...
Why are people making movies that obviously will be bad?
Why would you green light something that will like there's no way can be good?
And then why would you do it?
And there's Lego Ninjago.
Wait, why did I why did he come in here?
I didn't want this isn't what I was supposed to go.
Yeah.
And then I get we got Lego.
We can watch the dragon cam to see what the ninjas are up to now and Lego Ninjago.
God, I almost want to click it.
I'm almost curious to see what the dragon cam will show.
I'm gonna get my Lego premium account ready so I can so I can log in.
Fucking clicking it.
I'm clicking it.
I want to see the dragon cam.
Oh, Ben, you know what game we got to play?
We got to play Lego digital designer 3D.
What?
Lego digital designer 3D is a game where you can you can like like you have access to every single Lego block ever made and you can design your own Lego sets like in a computer setting and then you can actually like ship it to yourself.
You can like order what you have created online and you can have it sent to your house.
You can get like whatever Lego parts you want.
You can build in real life.
Do they do they?
Okay, so you build it online and then they send you the pieces for it.
Do they send it to you?
Yeah.
Or do you have to build it yourself?
Yeah, you have to build it yourself.
Okay.
That's pretty interesting.
That's pretty cool actually.
It's on the Lego.
It's on the Lego set.
Do kids still play with Legos?
Do kids still like Legos?
Has Minecraft not like completely?
Yeah, yeah.
I mean I play with Legos.
I mean I did assume that it's still a thing.
I mean Lego still has a website.
It's definitely still a thing.
I wonder if it shrunk.
I wonder if it shrunk due to Minecraft.
The Lego movie just came out a couple years ago.
That was really big.
Yeah, and I guess Minecraft was huge even then.
Yeah.
I mean Lego's definitely still around, right?
It's definitely not gone.
What about Lincoln Logs?
Now those I think are probably bigger than ever.
Go-Bots.
People still love Go-Bots.
Michael Bay re-invigorated Go-Bots.
You don't know Go-Bots?
No.
What are those?
Well back in the day, sometimes your grandma would buy you, well not me,
because all my grandparents are dead.
And they always were.
Back in the day, someone would buy you.
You would be a kid who really liked Transformers,
and someone would buy you what they believed was a Transformers toy,
but was in fact a Go-Bot.
I think Go-Bots were owned by Duplo.
Duplo is such a betrayal.
Duplo is a perversion.
Yeah, well Go-Bots were pretty much the same.
It was just knock-off Transformers.
But they kind of flooded the market for a while there.
You'd see them everywhere.
It was like Asylum Films.
It was like the Asylum Films version of Transformers.
Oh Jesus Christ, these are awful.
Oh, you looked them up?
Yeah.
I think I had at least one Go-Bot.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
Well, that's life.
Their designs are just so, like they...
I think I had one.
They really did not intend them to ever move,
or be shown from any other angle than the forward-facing angle.
Yeah, they're not designed for functionality.
They're not designed to express emotions other than anxiety and pain.
Let me see, let me see.
Oh, here, I'm going to link it to you right now.
Yeah, please.
We should not have the password open.
Let's look on Discord.
We'll see.
Yeah.
Oh my God, that's even worse.
That's even worse than I remember.
You would think that maybe in toy form they would look bad,
but animated they would look okay.
No, they actually look even worse in the animated medium.
Why?
They actually look more awkward.
This is so bad.
They actually look more awkward in that illustration
than they do in toy form.
Look at how everything about this is so wrong.
Like, it's the most...
Yeah, it's so awkward.
I remember, I remember that grey guy and his weird skull head.
I remember these things in real life.
Look at this.
It feels weird.
What, what...
Hold on, okay.
Oh, look at this fucking garbage meta...
Garbage Megatron.
Yeah.
God, these are really bad.
These are really fucking bad.
I can't believe these happen.
This is worse than I thought.
This is worse than I remembered.
These are like old, you're like ancient.
You're an ancient man, Ben.
I am pretty fucking ancient.
These might have been old even when I found them,
or had them.
Maybe.
Well, no, because they were coming out like contemporary
with the Transformers,
and the Transformers were like on the air,
like when I was a kid.
They might have been around for a little while.
Might have come at the tail end of the Transformers.
Jesus.
These fucking things are the opposite of quality.
They just, like, they just clearly...
It's so bizarre that they were made in such a way
that it obviously indicates that it wasn't meant to move
or bend or be able to be posed or played with
or to be seen from any angle at all.
They just look so flat and horrible,
and yet they had a cartoon and a toy series.
All of which don't fix their designs.
Did they have a cartoon?
Was there... I'm not sure there actually was
any, like, Go-Bots cartoon.
They might have just pretended there was.
I keep looking at animated screenshots.
Oh.
This could just... Oh, God.
Yeah, look at the back.
Oh, God.
This could just be a commercial.
I mean, I would be very disappointed
if this were an actual show.
No, there's a Go-Bots intro.
No. You want to watch it?
It's my Hannah Barbera, yeah.
Yeah, here.
I mix potions and put them in coconuts.
All right. Tell me when you're ready.
I...
We'll do it on three.
It's coming in 1984.
Uh...
I'm going to open this in YouTube.
Oh, wait.
There it is.
Okay.
On count of three.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I got to get... I got to center it.
Yeah, that's good enough.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Oh, the prestigious Hannah Barbera.
Woo me.
Ooh.
Looking good.
Oh, they're looking great.
They're looking perfect.
Oh.
Oh, that one's from the helicopter or something.
It doesn't turn into a helicopter.
It just has propellers on its back.
Oh, my God.
That one with, like, the weird, like, my little toaster.
No, my little toaster.
That weird, brave little toaster face.
Oh, the transformations are not right.
No.
They aren't right.
Challenge of the Go-Bots.
All right.
It's so funny how that is literally just transformers.
Like, they transform everything too.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, it's literally just the asylum films version of Transformers.
Imagine going to sleep tonight knowing that you work on the Go-Bots.
Even though it's like an episode director or just like an unnamed Korean animator.
Man, tough day at the office today.
Tough day at the office animating Go-Bots.
And, you know, tomorrow I'm going to do it all over again.
Jesus Christ.
What is this?
Okay.
Deep in the temple there is a wall carving that will show you what you need to bring.
Did I not already go and do that?
Well, obviously you don't know what you need to bring.
Is it the bone?
I mean, I might be the bone in other things.
Let me see what you got to get.
I found the wall carving and it just let me into that room and I found the bone.
You need to get carbonated coconut milk from the coconut cafe.
What?
Okay.
All right.
Sure, whatever.
And then you need to go deeper inside the temple to get the key ingredient in the temple.
That's what it's called, the key ingredient?
Yeah.
Okay.
I really miss the music in which there is music in every level.
The music was actually pretty good.
Just turn on the Go-Bots intro and you'll be fine.
Just play that on loop.
You know, why not?
You need to listen and repeat.
Why not?
Nice recommended videos, by the way.
Nice worthless from Brave Little Toaster.
Oh, maybe.
I guess YouTube.
YouTube must think that that guy bears a weird resemblance to my little toaster.
Okay.
Can you imagine a Lorne Fouse directed TV series about Brave Little Toaster?
I'm imagining it right now and I've already watched it.
I'm pretty sure Brave Little Toaster already said everything it had to say and that's why in the sequel they go to Mars.
Yeah.
I've never seen the sequel.
I have not either.
Did you know there's a reference to Brave Little Toaster at California Adventure Disneyland?
No.
Yeah, in Cars Land.
There's the car that went on the end.
Yeah, there's the car that drove in the Indy 500 and he speaks and he says,
the one that said I went on the Indy 500, you know that one.
Yeah, that's true, but I wish they had the one that drove the text into the wedding.
This is my favorite.
Yeah, I wish they had Michael Jackson's first one.
Wait, is it was one of them Michael Jackson's hearse?
Yeah.
No, yeah.
Well, I mean, he is a hearse who sounds like Michael Jackson.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Not the hearse that canonically.
I'm pretty sure.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure that was before Michael Jackson died.
It was pathetic.
It was like they called it that Michael Jackson would die eventually.
How the fuck do I get carbonated coconut water?
He was talking to the guy outside.
This is not rocket science.
Jesus Christ.
Yes, it is.
PopTropic has the hardest game I've ever played.
I already talked to this guy.
Yeah.
I talked to him harder.
Oh, wow, it looks like you did it.
I already talked to that guy.
Why did I not already get it?
Okay, fine.
You just didn't ask Karthina.
Sure.
Oh, I feel bad.
I feel ill.
I feel hungry.
No, that guy right there.
That fucking statue Lego person is the scariest thing in this entire game or any game for
that matter.
He's a fucking nightmare.
He's way taller than you for no reason.
There was a Lego City ad on the last room and then I moved to the new room.
But before I went to the new room, I had to get an advertised for Lego City.
Why?
Okay, so.
Why are they pushing the mammoth so hard?
Yeah, yeah.
All the way to the left and up.
Left and up.
Got it.
Good thing these...
These platforming challenges are just way too hard.
Good thing this cop killer bat costume is going to help me be more aerodynamic.
Thank God my family is all bad at me so I can't let them down anymore.
Finally.
All right.
I'm free from their admiration and judgment.
Deep in the temple.
I'm looking for the key ingredient.
Oh God.
Just listening to...
That's going to get you.
Jesus Christ.
I hate that thing.
Just listening to GoBots on repeat.
Here we go.
This is it.
GoBots.
Oh.
No, don't go down any of it.
Too late.
I went down.
You ruined the progress.
So that was not...
Okay, so that...
There's more to the left?
I see.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Then I won't go down.
I see.
I thought that hole was like the end.
No.
Wait.
Can I...
Oh, I can't get out of here.
It's too...
All right.
Okay.
I got to knock her down the spike pit.
Yeah.
Who would have thought?
Ew.
Really not a fan of that buggo.
Why is there a giant bug in this underground temple?
I don't know, because this is his ecosystem.
What does he feed upon?
Spiders.
There's spiderwebs too.
Platformers.
Yeah, he feeds...
He eats platforms.
Okay, okay.
So now it's time to be very, very cautious and careful.
And skilled.
There we go.
All right.
Easy.
Hashtag easy.
We're making mad progress.
We're going to get a medallion.
We're making mad dash.
Can we please get another ad, please?
I forgot that I have to buy Lego product.
I forgot about the Lego mammoth.
I am going...
Oh.
Oh, the ingredients.
The carving on the temple shows something that I couldn't read.
Sick.
I'm not going to mess with me.
He should deliver you.
Will he deliver me from evil?
Yeah, he'll take you to the Promised Land.
He'll take you to the land of milk and honey.
He'll deliver you.
That's not keto.
Yeah, all the Jews are kind of like,
God, that's not keto.
Coconut milk?
Sorry, man.
It's not keto.
Take us to the land of unsold cashews.
Yes, please.
The only thing I'll eat.
Did I...
Oh, I've got to climb this rope.
I've got to climb this rope.
Definitely do not want to go to Bugabay
because, frankly, it sounds pretty racist.
Oh, can you swim in the Bugabay?
Hold on.
After me and the medicine man conclude our business together.
There's another typical white man walking up
to the indigenous natives of an island
and demanding, you know, potions and brews.
Yeah, like, this is their potions.
You know, I didn't...
I didn't come down...
He doesn't come down to where I work
and slap the potion out of my mouth.
So you brought everything.
I'll put the potion into a coconut for you.
Yes, please.
Here's a little chant.
This is Uga-Buga.
Mmm, some nice bone and milk.
Okay, so I did need the bone.
This cocoa contains a thing.
All right, cool.
There's nothing else I can do for you.
I'll miss what you need to do.
I probably got to go to Bugabay.
Problematic though, it is.
Yeah.
All right, all right.
You got to like drain.
You got to shoot the potion into the water.
Do I have to drain the swamp?
Yeah, if you'd please.
I mean, someone...
Please help.
My son is stranded at sea, trapped by that monster shark.
Woo lad!
Are you her son?
We're gonna have to buy some children there, no.
What happened to the boats?
Man, these go-bots sure are enticing.
I want to buy some for my children.
We're gonna have to buy some mammoths.
We're gonna have to buy some go-bots.
We're gonna have to buy some chocolate frosted flakes.
We're gonna have to...
Hey, did you see what I was seeing when we were looking at the Dragon Cam
at the Lego Ninjago Dragon Cam?
Were you seeing that shit?
Oh, it was a live feed of a Lego Dragon.
Whoa, really?
Yeah, kinda.
Wow.
Yeah, then it was like flopping around
and there was like a tank.
I think there was a tank.
And there was a dragon.
Not with a boom and a rage like this.
Do I know anything about Professor Hammerhead's journal?
I sold it to an archeologist.
Here we go.
Oh, wow.
A lot more potions than I thought that would be.
These are just regular coconuts.
Oh.
Alright, well...
I've calmed the wrath of Booga.
Go right.
Well, you did it. You won the video game.
Wait, you're that lady's son?
You're like an old man and she was like a young yuppie.
Oh, there. That must be you.
Does it mean I have to go back to...
He's a fucking zoomer.
Will you lead us back to the mainland?
Oh, look, it's Wilson!
Wilson!
Wilson, I'm sorry! Wilson, I'm sorry!
Remember?
Remember Hamlet?
Wilson, I'm sorry!
Woo!
Oh my god, game design.
Yeah, that was game feel.
Oh, I'm hungry.
Watch your step. Don't step on a shark.
I'm really hungry even though I ate salami.
Even though I ate salami and took drugs.
Mess will probably fill you up.
Take this gold medallion! Woo!
You won. You won, Shark Island.
You won the island. Now you can go to the other one.
I'm gonna fuck out of here.
Alright, I think I get what PopTrop is all about.
It's about fucking sluts. It's about taking names.
Yeah, yeah. It's about banging that milk
after I saved her son from that old rapist on the island.
From the jaws of jaws.
Hey, look, it says that Shark 2000 isn't quite complete.
Should I complete it?
Nah, fuck you.
You got a recommendation for round two.
Yeah, early PopTropica.
Oh, there it is. Early PopTropica.
This is the first time.
Whoa, they're pixelated!
Yeah, I know. It's almost like a video game.
Dude, that's awesome.
It's like the remake.
It's like we're going from the original Binding of Isaac
to the remake of Binding of Isaac.
Where they pretended to be pixel art.
They made fake pixel art to make it look as though
they had integrity.
Yeah, why is the remake of Binding of Isaac so terrible?
I... yeah, I don't like it at all.
I think it's... I mean, it's got more features
and the features are good, but art-wise,
I hate how it looks. I think it looked better before.
I feel an unpopular opinion on that.
No, I completely agree. It looks like...
Oh, Khaled's Frosted Flakes!
Oh, my God. You know what really bothers me about it?
Is that like, okay, yeah, all the art is pixel,
but it still moves like a flash game.
And it just feels weird. It doesn't move like...
Like, you can tell the pixels...
You can tell the pixels are like a fake affectation
that they made to make it look like a video game
instead of just looking like itself.
Yeah, why would they disregard the original art style?
For what purpose?
I think... honestly, I think they did it for Mass Market Appeal
because they thought people like retro games,
people like pixels.
I do like pixels, but I hate being lied to.
And that's what those pixels are doing. They're lying to me.
It's not even real pixel art,
so everything just has like a dark black outline?
Yeah.
It's not trying all.
Yeah. It's ugly.
It's ugly and stupid.
And, uh...
I don't know why they did that.
I don't know why they couldn't have just added more features.
Well, you know what? They had to remake it.
They had to pay someone to remake it
so that they could sell it again
instead of just selling like DLC.
Because not everyone will buy a DLC,
but everyone will buy a remake.
I'm gonna kill myself.
Yeah.
The world would live in.
Is this what you do every single day?
Ben, you leave your house, you go to downtown Boston,
you start jumping on clotheslines.
Yeah, sorry.
It's just a summer song through the air,
you know, running up on people.
Man, I gotta... Oh, I can go down to the sewers.
That sounds like a good idea.
Um, shit. It's probably too late now.
Well, no.
I was gonna call around to those comic shops
and ask if my books sold.
Someone tweeted at me a picture of themselves
having bought one of my books.
Ah, yeah. You haven't followed up with that?
Uh, well, kinda.
Uh, I went around
and put books in a couple of stores
and had a couple people tell me, like,
come back later.
And then I went around a second time
to a couple more stores,
put them in some more stores, had a couple stores
be like, we don't really do that.
And I was like, alright, that's fine.
And then I went, I hit up, like, one or two
of the first places that told me,
like, that bought a couple more.
So, yeah, I feel like the books actually
are selling.
What's the process?
Do you just, like, walk into the store and say,
hey, I've made a comic before,
why don't you sell my comic instead?
That's literally what you do.
Really? Really?
You just walk in and you say, hey,
I made a book, do you want to sell it?
Because some, you know, because
book store is right, we're talking about old media, right?
And these old media people,
you know, they need
something, they need something
to compete with the internet. And that something
is, like, the idea that they are, like,
supporting local artists or, like, working in
a junction with local artists. This guy is selling
race.
This guy is selling the abstract concept
of race.
Oh my god.
Alright, I'm a little
left ghastly pale now.
Oh, no, you've ruined it.
You have to go back. Yeah, should I?
Yeah, that's what you look like in real life.
It's funny how this guy does not have any of these
pigments. He's above it.
This guy's got jaundice or whatever.
But yeah, you just walk into a store,
and not every store will do it. It depends
on the place. But if a place is interested
in, in, hey kids,
hey kids, this is advertising!
Wait, what?
Is that what it says? Yeah, look!
Right next to me, it says, hey kids,
this is advertising.
I...
I don't know what to make
of this.
Like, it already says advertisement
underneath frosted flakes.
This is advertising.
Frosted flakes of corn. I feel like the devs
put that in there because they felt bad
about selling the ad space
and they wanted to undermine it in any way
they popularly could.
Yeah, I can.
What's like, oh now that I know it's an advertisement,
now I'm, now I'm gonna buy it.
Now, now, now I'm really convinced.
I know, I think it's the other way.
I think they want it to be like, guys,
just don't look at this. Just ignore this.
It's fine, don't worry about it.
It's just advertising, don't worry, don't worry.
Yeah.
Anyway, yeah, you walk in.
I walk in with my Sonic Boom backpack
with a box of comics in it
and I say...
Oh, so you bring the comic with you?
Yeah, yeah. Cause you know,
all the places they've just been like,
yeah, they just take it and put it
right on the shelf, like right out of my bag.
Really?
Yeah.
What the fuck?
They pay you for each thing that you give them, right?
Well, okay, some of them...
Actually, I think only one place...
Wait, why is the pet...
Wait, okay, hold on.
Why in this big game is the pet...
Why is the pet right here?
Oh, the Pieta?
Oh, the Pieta.
Um, and the thinker.
Well, because... and Disco...
Discobolis.
I thought that was a joke name for a second,
but then I realized, no, it's what it's actually called
Discobolis.
This is not pop art.
This is classical art. I don't know why this is called
the pop art museum. No, no, it's just pop
Chopika.
Idiot.
Um...
Wait, I wanted to do...
finish my thought before.
Uh, something about...
They pay you for each book you sell.
Only one place just like
handed me some money in exchange for some books.
The others were like, just give us
some books. We will take your name down
and like, we will like
give you... we will like, split the profit.
We will like, split the cost of the sales
from you after we sell them.
Uh, so, yeah.
It makes like...
Yeah, it makes like no money, by the way.
It makes... they took like... each place would take
like, three to... like,
three or four copies and they sell for like,
six bucks a piece.
Yeah. Well, I mean, you know, it's exposure.
I guess it is exposure.
To the like,
yeah.
I feel like that's somewhat real exposure.
I mean, if you're going to a comic book shop,
you care somewhat about
comics in any way.
Yeah, I feel like this is like,
a more hardcore audience.
We'll see it here.
These people are legit.
Assuming anyone actually cares.
Assuming the people that
freak with these places are not just like,
cape readers, you know?
They might be.
Uh, anyway, there's a couple of places
that I have not checked back in to see if any
of my shit has sold. It might have.
And there's also, there's one more store
in Boston that I have not
hit up yet to see if they'll stock my shit.
I've hit up like, all the other ones
that exist.
Do you only try things that you think
have like, a decent chance?
Or do you try...
Uh...
I've tried a couple of like, long shots.
I walked into like, a book slash
game store.
They did not...
They were not interested because the guy
who owned the place was like, I pretty much only do
sell sci-fi shit.
I was like, alright, fair enough.
Yeah.
Mostly I do...
I mean, mostly it's
comic shops. And almost every comic shop
has been like, yeah, we sell indie shit.
Only two have been like,
one was like, we don't sell indie shit
unless we are like, unless
like, we are like, publishing
with the artist. Like, the artist
is like, an affiliate of ours that
is publishing through us. And I was like,
okay, well, I'm not interested in doing that.
So good luck.
And then the other, another one was like,
kind of an out of the way place. And he was like,
we don't really do indie shit. We like,
our clientele only, only buys
cape shit. And I was like, okay, cool.
Thanks for telling me.
I like to imagine that he says those terms too.
Indie shit and cape shit.
He pretty much did.
You could tell that he was,
you could tell he was a little abashed to admit that
like, yeah, the people that come here basically
only buy the cape stuff and they're not interested
in anything that you've never,
you've never heard of before. He seemed a little
bit like, eh, yeah, it's
unfortunately this is how it is.
It's really funny. Yeah.
I mean, I assume that this
would not work. Have you tried
Newberry Comics? Yeah, Newberry Comics
is not, they're fully
corporatized. They don't do
walk-in deals.
They don't do walk-in back alley shady dealings
like I'm interested in. It's so
crazy that you literally just walk in with a
fucking box, a box of comics
under your arms and you're hard in your sleeve
and you just infect the people
to sell your fucking comics and stuff.
One, a place
called, actually, you know what?
I think at least
one place explicitly told me like, tweet
like tweet that your store
that your book is in our store and we
will retweet about
your book. You scratch
our back, we'll scratch yours. I have
not done it, but I'm sure there's no time limit.
I should probably do that.
Definitely.
Ben, this is like the coolest
fucking thing that's ever happened to you. I'm surprised
so nonchalant you're treating it. Well, it's
not making me any money.
Yeah, but you know
it's a nice
mental thing. Your book is in the store, dude.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
And plus, I'm sure
if you gave it more attention than
literally dropping the books off, then forgetting
about it for a half a year, that I'm sure you
can break in more dough.
I don't know, maybe.
Look, if I call them up
and the places are like, oh yeah, we're all sold
out, like we want more, right?
Then maybe
I'll be like, hmm, maybe I can make a small
side income off of this whole
physical media business.
But if it's anything less than
that, even if they're just like, yeah,
we'll take another three,
then I'll be like,
you know, that's just not
there's just not very much
in that, you know.
There's just not enough,
even if these stores are
selling out of like the three copies
that I'm leaving there, there's only
like five of them. So that only
Rick adds up to like, you know, 50 bucks
of sales
or less. But it's fun.
It is fun. It is fun.
But it also involves leaving my house, which is a hassle.
Oh, they asked a nightmare.
I wonder if there's any way to like
get the stats.
Like who has visited your
website? Like who's
gone to, you know,
stcomics.com? Well, I
Oh my god. Even down here
in the dungeon, Tony, Tony
the Tiger is even down here in the dungeon.
He's so huge. He's made a house.
Look at the interface between
his top and bottom halves. Do you see
like where his top and bottom
or his top is moving and his bottom is still
I won't. Where's he right
in that bike down here in the sewers?
Why is he even cast away
into the book? Have a nice little white
nice little white picket fence house.
What? Why is he in the pop
tropical catacombs? Why is he
been banished here? What power does he wield
so that the government officials were too wary
of his influence and power?
Yeah, he was banished.
Who's afraid of the dark?
Ooh, spooky.
Hey kids, are you afraid
of the dark? That's still on
television, right? Says Ben
Saint. That's not, no
no. Look, I'm
with it, okay? Whoa, an egg. Oh my god.
Golden.
This is the plot of James and the
Beanstalk, by the way.
Yeah, James and the Beanstalk.
Got it. Yeah.
James and the Giant Peachstalk.
Yeah. Okay, wrong way.
Someone left me a helpful hint.
I gotta tell you, Munchy,
this is important and you should take
note. Is that my
my balls hurt from
sitting and playing this game and I don't know why.
I feel like
garbage. My balls have hurt
like a lot lately and I don't know why. I think
it's because I'm wearing new underwear
and all I have is like really cheap
so it's like a weird sort of like not
really like, it's
it's like, it feels like paper almost. It's
like a weird paper, like really stiff material
that isn't really like bend
and you know, fold well and I really
hate it. It really sucks. All I'm saying is
I'm right there with you. It's making my guts
hurt. This game is making my guts hurt
by way of my balls and I don't
like it. I don't appreciate it.
This is, not only is this RFCK
but this is also an audio show so you don't
have to wear any pants if you don't want to.
Though it might be a criminal, no it's
not even a criminal offense anymore. I'm of age
it doesn't even matter.
You children aren't allowed to be naked.
Yeah, no, yeah
fucking uh, no
no, no jury would
persecute you. No jury would, no jury would
convict me. Ooh, yeah. Here we go.
Okay, I've got the giant
big egg because
Oh, is that, wait, wait, okay I can't
tell because the quality is too bad. Is that the font?
Is that Showcard Gothic? Wait
No, no
way. It's like
that font right there. Yeah.
No, well, no, wait, wait, he's spoken.
I don't think it was
Showcard Gothic.
But I wasn't paying attention. Okay, Ben you
have to enter the Kellogg's Frosted Flakes
house. Oh god, no.
I get, maybe I'll find another mammoth.
Yeah, I hope so.
Talk to Tony
to ride the bike.
We got cinnamon frosted flakes.
Oh my god, that's some like bourgeoisie
shit.
Hey kids, this is advertising.
Why?
I like the hey kids in front of it.
Oh, you have to
avoid the frosted flakes.
No, surely
I'm supposed to get the frosted flakes.
Surely.
No, they're bad.
The frosted flakes impede your
progress.
You can't hear it, but like the GoBots
theme is playing
it's action packed.
At least my character is not
on screen anymore
for this minigame at least.
I wonder how often new sponsors
show up to like put minigames in
Pop Tropica.
Oh, this game
actually has music.
Uh
It's loading. Hey, you still there or what?
Uh oh. Uh oh.
My internet. Oh no.
Oh god.
Oh god, the recording.
Oh
Oh my god, my internet died.
My internet died while recording an RFCK.
Now what do I do?
Alright, stand stand by
stand by ladies and gentlemen.
Uh
Got it.
I'm back.
Hello?
Hey, you there? Hey. Yeah, Tony
is striking us down.
Tony, okay, so my internet just died
but it's back.
Okay, well fortunately
I saved right before
that but obviously I have to
obviously I have to do that again
to complete Tony's bike challenge.
Sure, sure.
I mean, if Tony's running for breast cancer
then you'd do too. Yeah, that's
it's just what you do.
You know how they should just must beat people
to do those runs? They'll say if they don't run fast enough
then breast cancer will catch up with them
and they'll get it.
Uh isn't that
isn't that what happens? Trying to outrun
outrun breast cancer is what they're called, I believe.
Yeah, yeah, something like that.
Oh god
I've never
never been less comfortable.
Uh, here we go. Returning to my game.
Uh, yeah.
Did you ever
post on like Tumblr or DeviantArt before
it's also ugly or was that like the first time
you ever posted your art online?
Um
Hmm
I think
I had a DeviantArt account
that I would post like
crappy pixel stuff that I
made like
when I was like 20
when I was like
still didn't know how to draw
um
Oh wait, I gotta complete the Tony
challenge.
Yeah, you gotta concentrate really fucking hard for it.
Oh wait, oh no, it's Lego City. Okay, well fuck that.
Fuck Lego City. Oh Jesus Christ.
The mammoth give it and the mammoth
take it away.
It's Tony or Bust. It's Tony or Bust.
Um
So yeah, I
drew some. Did you ever see those like
uh, I posted them on Twitter.
They were like old like
sprite parts of
people's characters on um
D&D on TG
on 4chan. Oh right, okay.
So D&D the 4.
D&D the 4chan room.
Uh, yeah, I did that.
Oh my god, every fucking room is an ad.
Hey, this is advertising.
This is advertising.
That, oh my god.
That room does not say hey, this is advertising kids.
At least I don't think it does. Only, only
I guess it's Tony himself speaking.
Or maybe it's just because that one's kind of like white
and on snow. I'm gonna look closely next time.
Maybe the white text was just disappearing
against the snow.
This looks like
an item. It is. Oh my god.
A jetpack. Wait.
I can
I can take off.
Oh my god. This menu. This menu
is so annoying. I don't understand.
It looks great.
Oh my god.
You're unstoppable. Dude, I can fly.
I'm Jimmy Neutron.
Got a blast.
Got a fast, he says. Got a fast.
Uh, ugh.
I'm Jimmy Neutron's
key though.
I hear.
Yeah, I feel, I feel like,
he's like Sheen. Like, why are you
eating so much carbs? Why are you
taking so much protein? Sheen, why?
Sheen, don't you know all those, all that gluten
will cause inflammation?
Carls of vegetarian.
Never makes fun of them even Jimmy.
Yeah, well.
Oh, here we go. Here we go. I gotta climb this.
No.
There was nothing there.
Maybe I need to go back down to the ground?
Look at his awful feet.
This reminds me of MapleStory.
Is PopTropicaMapleStory?
Yeah, but better.
Yeah, and for free.
Oh, is MapleStory paid?
No.
Uh, MapleStory 2 might be.
But I don't think so.
Isn't it just MapleStory 2? That's a perversion.
There is a MapleStory 2.
I don't know anything about it or what it's deal is.
Have you ever played Yet Another Zombie Defense?
No.
Yet Another Zombie Defense
is a great game that cost 99 cents.
Uh, I found it one day
in the Steam, deep, deep
in the, in the annals of the Steam Marketplace.
Mm-hmm.
It's a fun game called Yet Another Zombie Defense.
It was made with, like, some built-in,
like, make-your-own-game software
for Xbox.
And it's really great.
And I instantly bought it, and I sent to Ethan.
And Ethan, upon playing it
for 10 minutes, bought 10 copies
and sent to everyone and his friends.
And so whenever we had,
we add a new friend into our friends list,
we bad them Yet Another Zombie Defense,
and we spray it like a curse.
How come you never bought me Yet Another Zombie Defense?
That's a good question.
We have to be the next game that we play.
Wait, wait, I missed it.
This flag signals, um...
This
menu is so annoying.
This flag signals ships to
dock into early...
Click, click, okay, okay, click on the card.
Do you not know what you're supposed to do?
No.
Look, I've tried, look,
you try to put your fucking mouse over it,
and it, like, flies through the other way.
Okay, fine. No, it's not. It's stupid.
It's fucking easy.
It's pussy shit.
So, all you
posted on that DeviantArt account was just
pictures from a TG?
Uh, yeah, mostly.
I drew a picture of, like, some
friends' characters from a campaign
they were doing, you know, just some of that
shit. So, I did have
a Deviant on it.
But...
And then I think, yeah, I think the first
time I was really posting online was it's all
so ugly.
I know, I know the steps that you took.
I remember the original Insight and Incidents.
Why did you want to be an artist again?
Um,
because I,
because
working as a physicist was boring
and sucked.
And, uh, I watched,
and I read Bakuman and got inspired.
And I also watched, uh,
I watched a strip search and got inspired.
And then
you know, and then
we decided
we decided to do T-Bap just for fun
and it took off. And I was like, yeah.
Yeah.
I can do it.
I can be the champion.
That was like, you started T-Bap in, like, what,
2014, right?
Yeah.
That was four years ago, but didn't you start drawing earlier than that?
Um,
it's also ugly was before T-Bap.
Yeah, it was slightly before T-Bap.
But yeah. So you just started drawing like 2012?
Well,
uh,
I would draw before that
just not very often,
you know? Like not, like,
just every now and then. And it was for recreational use
just for your own, just, you know, it's fun to draw.
Yeah, yeah.
Not, not like that regularly or anything.
Um,
I was kind of okay at it.
And then,
and then, you know,
T-Bap started and suddenly I was drawing
a shit ton of stuff for that.
Um,
Have you ever gone back
and looked at the old T-Bap tumbler?
At the tumbler?
Yeah.
Does it hold up?
Hmm.
I think there's no.
Okay, the tumbler was meant,
there was meant to be a lot more on the tumbler.
It was, it was, the tumbler was going
to be, like,
basically any, like, story or lore
idea we had for T-Bap
that we couldn't fit into a video
was going to go on the tumbler.
Remember the joke where the fandom
touches poison joke and he turns into doge?
Yeah, that's where that is.
Yeah.
It's great. Nice. Yeah.
Um, I mean, what would you expect
to happen?
Um, that's something I can imagine. Yeah.
How's the
T-Bap from Brad Kongo? Are you at Liberty Talk
about that? Oh, I can talk
about it. Um,
so actually, Nate just,
like, after the PCP
the other day,
Nate was like, Hey Ben, by the way,
I am like, I'm
going to send you like a
somewhat edited video file soon
and then it will be time
for you to, like, draw some assets
for it. And I was like,
okay, cool.
So he is, uh, I'm currently
waiting on him to do
something.
I probably could draw some assets now,
but like, we're not ready for them.
Uh, we had a plan.
There was a document explaining
like, what
shit we needed, but I forget
what it said and I don't know where it is.
So I'll just... It's gone forever.
Nate's around somewhere.
Uh, hey, what do we do?
I have no clue. Do you want to get the walkthrough?
Yeah. Okay.
Don't worry, I'm coming to the rescue here.
I just got to go to Pop Tropica Wiki.
Do you have the glow stick? Yeah.
Do you have the
prized porker?
No. Okay.
Go to Main Street.
Go down the main hall and into the pit.
Are you in the pit? I guess that's what the
supers are called.
So go down to the pit.
Okay, the dark pit, I guess?
Yeah, sure. Uh, fuck me.
Um, okay.
And you got to go to the bottom until you get
the prized porker. Okay.
Yeah, I did not get the prized porker.
A porker is like a racial
thing.
For fat people? Yeah.
The most downtrodden and oppressed race
there is.
How much weight have you lost because of Keto?
Uh, okay.
When I was fasting, I had lost like 20 pounds.
Predictably,
I gained, okay, I gained a bunch back.
Um,
I gained maybe like 5 or 10 back because
uh,
well, you know, I,
okay, so I bought a shit ton of
sausage and I was eating lots of sausage.
And I think I ended up eating too much
protein.
And if you eat too much protein, it's basically
knocks you out of Keto.
Out of Ketosis, you mean?
Out of Ketosis, yeah.
So I refilled my glycogen stores.
So I was back up maybe 10 pounds.
But I am,
but I am slowly getting back into Keto
because I stopped eating so much meat.
I'm getting back into Keto.
And so I think, I was peeing a lot yesterday.
I'm pretty sure that was my water weight coming off
as my glycogen was depleted.
Uh, so I'm back down another 5.
So I guess overall I've lost like 15 pounds.
Total.
Yeah.
And what's the purpose of this?
Is it just to get fitter?
Or is there any other grander?
It's just to get fitter and so I won't look
like the fat piece of shit that I was
at Radcon 3.
Yeah.
You commonly are remissed about how you look
in Radcon 3.
Yeah, because I look like I'm about to drop dead.
Well, you know.
The, um,
no, like,
I look at the Tales Get Strolled video
and I just think, man, I thought I looked bad
in the, I thought I looked bad in the
Sonichu video, but like,
I would do literally anything
to look like that again.
Instead of like this.
Ben, I want, I want, I want you to promise
me something, Ben. I want, I want, I want to
make it like a, a swear right now.
I want you to vow something right now
on RCK, so that if you don't
fulfill it, you'll get mocked and humiliated
a thousand times in the content section
of videos. Okay.
You have to have a beard for Radcon 4.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know.
I know. I never want to appear in public
without a beard again. Okay.
I just want to, I just want to lay that down.
Guys, if Ben is plucked out
beard hairs and does not have any beard
at Radcon 4, humiliate him?
I feel like I'm getting there. You know, like
I keep pulling my beard out, but like, I make
it further and further each time.
I feel like it's, it's just around the core.
The day, the day when I have an actual beard
that doesn't, that I don't destroy
is, is, is fat,
is close at hand.
To give you hope, by the way, Ben, I want to let you know
that this was a universal feeling
that literally everyone in the Brony fandom
and in the PCP felt
when you and Ben first revealed yourselves
or, Nate, you're the same.
Yeah. In the Q&A,
everyone thought you were the most
handsome Bronies that existed.
Yeah. So if you can just return to your state
which you have achieved prior
in your life, then everything will be fine
and you'll return to, to manhood.
Yeah. I mean, that's
pretty much how I feel.
I'm just going to start wearing flannel again.
Uh, well, I mean,
yeah, now that I'm a little less fat
and maybe if I become
even a little less fat,
maybe I can fit in, like, that, that
shirt that I wore in the T-Bat Q&A
is like my favorite shirt of all time
and I've been too fat for it for like, a while.
Uh, and so
Keto is my ticket out of that.
Personal hell.
Dude, I've been on such a fucking
on an F.A.
killing spree, a fucking, a fucking
fashion killing spree. I've been, I've been slaying
a fascist killing spree.
Yeah, yeah. Uh,
God, side,
side note, uh, I went, I went
water jet, like, water skiing
with, uh,
Kazzie when she was over here
in San Diego the entire time.
I just would scream at the top of my lungs,
I'd go bloodthirsty on these fascists and never
go buy a boat.
On these fascists?
Yeah. Uh, hey, am I done here?
No. Have I won the game yet?
No, when you, when you get a medallion, that's
when you'll do it. Uh, have you,
have you, have you gone to the
Pop Tropica Towers?
What?
Have you gone to the Pop Tropica Towers?
No.
Alright, hold on.
Wait, okay, okay, I think it might be done, actually.
Once you get the medallion, okay, go to
early Pop Tropica and talk to the pilgrims.
I, I, I, I, I gave
the guys pig, I gave the guy the bucket.
You didn't give someone a, a flag.
I gave him a flag.
Did you? Okay.
Tell me your inventory.
Uh, it was just my inventory.
You haven't gotten your medallion yet, right?
I don't think so.
Wait, I, I mean, how
would I know?
I mean, did it say on screen that you got it?
No, I don't think so.
Okay, I have the glow stick for the sewers,
and I have the jet pack.
Okay, um, um,
fuck.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Sigma flag.
Thanks for your help. Thanks for your help.
Yeah, I, you know, I think you did do it.
Right?
Wait, oh no, here, here we go, here we go.
This boat was not here before. Take this gold medallion
and it's token of my appreciation.
Hey!
Alright, let's have it.
Let's have it, friend.
Click, progress.
There we go. Oh my God.
Delicious. Alright, alright.
Uh, let's see what other islands there are.
Let's see what other great fucking islands
we can go to, and it will just be
a fucking delight for everyone.
Um, there, there's reality TV island.
That one's good.
A 24 carat island.
There's cryptids island.
If you want to get some cryptids going on.
Yeah, sure.
Why not?
Why not cryptids, I guess.
Oh, this is difficult. This is a level 3 difficulty.
Oh my fucking God!
I'm doing it.
Oh, you're going, you're going to headlong in there.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, I'm not afraid.
I'm not afraid of what poptropica has in front of me.
Oh my God, Ben.
These islands have been like two paragraphs long.
This one is like fucking like an entire
novel written down.
Oh, good.
Oh, fuck!
Muse is giving away a million bucks.
Alright, just go until you get
lost, and then we'll have to work our way
back up from zero.
Okay, someone called Muse is giving
away money. I assume it's
to find a cryptid.
I assume that the goal here is you get
money if you find a cryptid.
Okay, great, great.
Ever since going, like knowing
I was going to go to Hawaii, I wanted to be able
to get Hawaiian shirts.
But I hate wearing
button-up shirts, because
I'm like way taller
than, like, the people
that they were designed for most of the time.
And so, like, it's too short.
I mean, it looks weird.
So, I hate wearing them.
But, I recently
unlocked what was always fable
for me, what was always, like, destined to be the case.
I've engaged with
full dad mode, and now I
wear a wife beater and a
Hawaiian shirt every single day of my life.
And I've unlocked
Uncle Status, and it's
fucking delicious. It's incredible.
I love it.
Dude, for only 45 cents
we can buy a paperback
book
called
Cryptids Island Pop Tropica.
What is this thing?
Written by Max Braulier.
Braulier.
Based on, based on Pop
Tropica's popular
Cryptids Islands.
This illustrated novel
follows the story of an eccentric
billionaire who is promising a big reward to whoever
can prove the existence of cryptids.
Legendary beasts like Bigfoot and the Loch Ness Monster.
A quest is underway
to track down the hidden creatures, and the competitors
will stop at nothing to find them.
45 cents.
30...
31 U... No, I'm not paying for shipping.
Fuck that.
Whoa!
Dude, 31 U is from 45 cents.
5 new from
$25.
This is $25 new.
Jesus Christ.
Max Braulier must be
raking it in.
Um...
God. Goddamn.
Oh, you know what else I got? I also got a fucking
satchel.
The satchel is the most FA thing
that I can really imagine.
It's functional.
It's nice utility, and also it looks
delectable. It looks delicious.
A satchel, you say?
Yeah, a satchel, I say.
I'm gonna...
Guys are all like, there's gotta be a way off this island
when I literally just arrived on a
hot air balloon.
Like, yeah.
There is.
I could see you walking
the satchel life.
I used to have a satchel.
It was made of like hemp and it had Buddha on it.
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
Can I try out one of these kites?
No problem.
Just point out the one you'd like to try.
I want the pony one.
Of course.
What does this entail?
Fly a kite for free.
Well, I have a kite now.
For some reason.
How nice.
Thanks for returning the kite.
You're welcome.
Oh, we'll get the panda one.
Wow, kitesurf, that would be a blast.
This dialogue is so realistic.
Ben, what is your problem?
You yourself have chosen
the three difficulty island.
It's not about the difficulty.
It's about
what it entails
doing.
It's about what the moment to moment experience
of Pop Tropica is.
Do you understand why I like this game so much?
As a kid, do you get it?
Do you understand?
I think the kite just like
took me away
for a second there.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Yeah, yeah, no.
It makes perfect sense.
It's
one of a kind experience.
It's only a hinder bond for me to show this to you.
Now you understand my life story
even a little bit more.
There we go.
Is this
the gender change that you've been waiting for?
Wait, I don't want
I heard that Muse never leaves this creepy mansion.
I want to jack some of your swagger.
But not all of it.
No, the hit.
That's good. Don't go too far.
Jesus, you've ruined it.
I still got the grass hurt.
It's fine.
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Riding the bike!
Hey kids, it's advertising.
When are we going to get
Hey kids, it's advertising shirt.
Dude, dude, we should...
Okay, we got to put that
on the Rowdyfuckers cop killers store.
Oh, we have a store by the way.
A shirt that just...
Oh yeah, there's a store.
There's gonna be a shirt that says
Hey kid, this is advertising.
Maybe with a picture of Tony the Tiger.
I don't know.
You know, it changed in a way.
This is so weird that you have to
avoid the Frosted Flakes.
Avoid Frosted Flakes at all costs.
Avoid sports balls
and other
active activities.
Eventually it's going to be children
that are laying down, strapped to the side of the road
so that Tony can run over them.
Oh my god.
Oh no.
You're going so fast.
Oh dude, we got to play...
Okay, we got to play Cartoon Network games too.
Flash games.
Dude, Adult Swim has like some good ass games
on its website.
Does it really? Oh, you got a fuck.
Yeah, Adult Swim has a...
It's got the Cream Wolf.
Cream Wolf is fucking sick. You're a werewolf.
You drive around... During the day you drive around
giving kids ice cream
and you sing your siren song
and all the kids you gave ice cream are attracted to you
and then you lure them
into your ice cream truck and eat them.
Oh, whoa. Yeah, it's
very sick.
Look how happy the Spy Child is
to have Frosted Flakes.
It's got Unicorn Robot Attack
which is a classic, obviously.
Yeah.
Obviously.
Alright, well I did it.
Hey kids, this has been advertising.
Thanks for joining us.
That's the new YouTube series.
It's going to be the RFCK spin-off.
Hey kids, this is advertising.
That's going to be Nate's
slime-core rip-off of the RFCK.
Hey kids, it's advertising.
Like, explanation point.
I think this kite lets me
jump ridiculously high.
Show me.
Wow, ridiculous.
Oh, maybe not. Maybe that's just normal.
Maybe that's just normal jump height.
That feels floaty.
This is a really story-driven island.
Yeah.
This is like a murder mystery.
And I'm the murderer.
Grrrr.
Nightmare.
I cannot wait until I'm in Boston again.
It's been like half a year at least.
Yeah, when I moved here
you said that you've come out here like four times a year.
And it's been like ten years since then.
No, I do.
And what I said has not been
proven otherwise.
But the fourth time was before
you came.
Did you see how high I jumped just there?
No, I was paying attention.
So I don't believe you.
Let me try and recreate it.
Oh my god. Yeah, okay.
I think I went even higher before.
Uh, here we go.
Stay away from Grimlock.
Yeah, I will. Thank you.
Stay away from Gridlock.
Traffic speed.
Gridlock is my favorite energy drink.
You can only buy it at Aldi.
Oh my god.
And it costs $0.99 for a can.
And it's almost indistinguishable from Monster Ultra.
Fucking?
Oh my god. Okay.
I took a vow to not drink soda again.
So I'm on the no-soda life.
And it's been going good for like a couple months now.
But before I did that,
I had bought a Monster Energy drink.
And it's still sitting in my fridge
tempting me every single time I open the fridge.
And I have to say no.
I just say no to it every single time.
With the monster?
Just throw it out.
Don't keep it in your fridge.
Yeah, you know, for some reason, that didn't
dawn on me until just now.
Yeah, okay.
Hmm.
Yes?
I feel like...
It feels like this kite
should be able to like fly me over.
But maybe not.
Ben, do a different level, please.
Why?
What difference does it make?
They're all garbage.
This is gonna be awful.
You're just gonna like get so sidetracked
and you're gonna lose the story so hard.
No, I get it.
I'm already invested.
There's an eccentric millionaire.
And that's it. There's an eccentric millionaire.
Yeah, yeah. Like yourself.
Like, yeah.
He's relatable.
That's what we call a relatable character.
I guess you wouldn't know about that.
I wonder if this guy has
child soldiers to do this bidding for him.
I mean...
What...
There we go.
What would be the point of being an eccentric millionaire
Yeah.
If someone's gotta defend his fortune...
What do you think he's gonna do it himself?
By the way, everyone,
if you go to teespring.com
slash stores
slash info-war
you will see designs
for RFCKs in this war.
We've got designs.
We've got one or two.
I wanna make more.
We've got a few.
I've made some designs
for a rowdy shirt and a killer shirt.
Yes.
An endless war poster.
I wanna make some of my own designs
for all these things.
I've been saying that for a while.
Have you ever drawn
endless war before?
Um...
The only time I...
The only time I drew
endless war was for the
icons on Crack's website.
Oh, those are you?
Yeah.
They're not Crack.
Yeah, well, you know,
they're not great.
I didn't spend that much time on them
because they're like
50 pixel wide
buttons.
Yeah, I think that's the only time
that I have drawn them
canonically.
How have you not drawn
the boy himself?
I mean, I've taken
your... I've taken the official
background art
and taken...
sort of copy pasted him
and modified him and turned him into
icons.
You gotta appreciate
the jump.
How the grace thing
about the Roman Empire
was...
how to go from being a pauper
to being, you know, a ruler, a government official,
the social economic, you know,
uh...
What do you fucking call it?
You could transcend the chains that your father
would lay upon you
by your, you know, poor birth
and you could transcend the social plan.
You could, you know, become
a real rich person.
That's what the background art
of R.C.K. has done.
It was just some fucking obelisk
that I had just thrown a Y.V. face onto.
And now he's the
mascot and the main character of an entire video game.
Yeah.
Um...
That was, like, a totally
incidental detail.
I think...
Was it my idea
that, like, that thing is
the endless war?
Was it my thought?
I don't know. Yeah, probably.
I remember I was like,
okay, I will make
a game. I will learn Python
and make a video game and the game will be called
Endless War.
Yeah. Okay.
I approached you to make a discord server
and immediately you were like, yes, we should.
And then, and then, and then I
set up a bot that would
allow you to, like, join
routies or join killers with, like, a fan,
like, you know, like, endless forever.
And then you're like, what if you,
what if you were able to, like, program
the bot, which was just, you know, some
Google search, like, discord bot role
assigner, to, like, be able
to, like, have, like, currency
and to shoot things. And I was like, yeah, but already.
What if we could kill each other?
Yeah. What if we could have gang violence
simulated?
Mm-hmm.
Uh, and, and, and then...
It was just, it was just
going to be, originally it was just going
to be, like, there would be
nothing but, like, the slime command.
You would have slime, and there would
be a kill command, and that would be it.
Um, but that was for cowards.
Mm-hmm.
Hey. How far we've come?
This lady wants to push.
But I don't know how to push it.
Well, run into her, I guess.
I, I did. Believe me.
Well, as soon as I saw her, I ran
directly for her in an attempt
to smash.
Uh, I have no clue. Try and, like,
get, like, a fan item, I guess,
and blow the wind towards her.
This person wants me to cut
their balloon loose.
Uh, I don't have any
means of doing that.
I, oh, I've got Tony the Tiger.
Oh, I've got Serial.
Oh, perfect.
Thank God. Search the world and bring
your proof to Harold Muse to claim your
award. Okay.
We're in fortunate name, Harold Muse.
Yeah. Doesn't he know that's already
a Pokemon?
Disgusting.
Maybe I can, can I get up here? No.
Oh, yeah.
It's so impressive
to look back at it in this war and
think how far it's come.
Like, like, like how we're just describing.
Like, it's gone from just, like, a shitty
fucking, just press one command and then
you die.
The entire ecosystem.
Yeah. Well, I mean,
Crack just, like, executed
on, like, every retarded idea that I
had. He just, like,
made them happen
in, like, I don't know,
somehow.
I don't know how he did it. Uh, he just
I guess, you know,
computers are powerful, man.
Computers do magic things. But the human mind
is powerful. The human mind is weak.
No, the human mind is weak. Only computers
have power. The ideas
in my human brain mean nothing.
This is the core difference between killers
and, and, and raties.
Yeah, killers are, are, are
machine-oriented
drones. And, and raties are full of heart
and passion and human instinct.
Killers are all about that machine learning.
I'm on the map right now and this fucking Genesis quote
still, like, shatters my soul
thinking about how perfect it is.
Do you want to read it? Yeah, sure.
Genesis 1, uh,
134. 1, 2, 3, 4.
Yeah. Yeah.
Genesis ABC.
Uh, and they had Brick for Stone and they had
Slime for Mortar. And they said
go to, let us build a city in a
tower whose top may reach into the
heaven. And let us make a name
lest we be scattered abroad on the face
of the whole earth.
Slime, Slime they had for Mortar.
Slime they had for Mortar.
And, and, and a tower whose top may reach
into the heavens. Yes.
Um,
what could it mean?
What does it mean?
It's crazy.
Cover your ears, children,
in case you don't want the illusion to be broken.
But, uh, the
endless war, you know,
New Los Angeles City just happens
to look very similar to Boston, Massachusetts.
And, uh,
yeah, just weirdly,
weirdly, I don't understand why.
God damn.
Uh, it's really, it's really
like, like, like I, like I've been
to crack a bay before. I know
what crack bay is like.
And I, and I wonder, I wonder, I, like
I wonder what it would be like to, to
traverse those, those
streets that I have done so in my life.
But, you know, with a gun in my hand.
I mean, the, the, the last
time I went out, the last
time I went out shilling my books
to, uh, you know,
oh, shears. I want those shears.
Okay, this guy wants a drink.
And then maybe he'll give me his shears
because I have to cut the balloon, Liz.
Uh, the last time I went out
shilling my comics and such,
um, I gave, uh,
oh yeah, yeah, I took, I took pictures.
I was out in New Los Angeles City
taking pictures, taking
some not at all photo
filtered, uh, you know,
you know, uh, uh,
uh, urban photography.
Yeah.
Just looking at all the green and pink
and purple buildings.
Oh fuck.
Oh, Ben, you know what we should do? We should go
urban exploring. We should find like an abandoned
building and just spend the night there.
I think we were talking about
this. There is a like
obelisk in Boston, isn't there?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
You might do something with someday.
I have not made
any progress.
You have to leave this place.
You must leave. You must leave now.
You must go from whence you came.
Fine.
Pick a baby easy island
and fucking be done with this.
I want to be done with this whole game.
No, no,
not like that. This game is a nightmare.
Nothing like that.
Look, look how much progress I made.
Look how much progress I made on cryptids.
I was getting somewhere.
No, stop.
Wait, just go to the fucking
just look up what the next step was.
No.
Okay, okay, hold on.
They find cryptids on here. I don't even know what step
you were on. I had done
basically nothing.
Jump up a tree,
get a five dollar bill, fun
Loch Ness monster.
Okay, that jumping up a tree
and finding a five dollar bill sounds easy.
Finding the Loch Ness monster sounds a little
more difficult.
Okay, go to like the fucking
convention center island.
This is tearing us apart.
Wait, Burt's bed is breakfast.
There's like six different cryptids
we're gonna have to find.
Oh, I haven't even been in here.
There's a fucking nightmare.
Look, there's fresh food.
Alright, fuck it, I'm out.
I'll go to convention center.
Why not?
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
There we go. Alright.
According to the PopTropica blog,
this is the hardest island to be
created. Really?
Yeah. This cryptid is the hardest.
Well, that's why if we beat it,
we'll have beaten the entire game.
I'll never have to play it again.
No, we, no, the game, okay, go to
the fucking funny convention center.
I'm interested in what that is. Is it
MockTropica? No, it's PopTropicon.
PopTropicon.
Game show, SkullDuggery,
Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
Nice, nice.
Sorry, Johnny Depp are coming soon.
Counterfeit,
Wimpy Boardwalk,
Cryptids,
where's PopTropicon?
Oh, there it is, there it is, PopTropicon.
This one's difficulty level 2.
What's the blurb? What's the blurb?
PopTropicon is the hottest ticket in town.
It'll take all your wits and more
than a few disguises to crash the
party.
Ugh, fucking destroy
AnimeExpo.
Okay, I'm there.
You know, Gern, Ligon,
HunterXHunter, all those are fine
Anime, but when I'm going to get a panel
of what the creators of PopTropicon
at AnimeExpo are.
Okay, I already know how to costume
minds.
Ugh.
Look at this, look at this fucking stupid this is.
Come watch the premiere trailer of
Mighty Action Force.
Only today at
PopTropicon.
Pop, Cock, Pop, Pop
and Lockticon.
Imagine, like,
how many layers remove this is.
Like, you're so engrossed in nerd culture
that you would pass for not, like, playing
a video game about Spider-Man, but you would play
a video game about going to a convention
to talk about Spider-Man.
I mean, maybe
you just really love PopTropicon.
You just really want, I mean this is part of the lore.
Copkiller!
Copkiller's Assemble!
You know, I'm surprised you haven't made
the Copkiller theme song, the song
Copkiller, which the Copkiller name was based upon.
Wait, what?
Yeah, you don't know how.
I am the one
who came up with the writer's Copkiller's name
and the Copkiller part
is based off a song
by the name Copkiller.
Wait, John Manos.
Wait, really?
I had no idea.
I've never heard this before.
I think you would like it.
If you like Shitty Vaporwave
then you'll like this quite a bit.
Oh, and there's nothing I like quite so much
as Shitty Vaporwave.
Okay, so I guess I'm looking for
like a gray wizard guy.
Put this on in the background. Stop the go-bots.
Stop it and put on this.
Fine.
Well, let's get our video flags.
I mean, this video I'm sitting
is on YouTube, so...
So yes.
No, right?
It's fine, it's fine. I don't know.
I mean, whatever.
Let's get our video get deleted
and it'll be a collector's item.
Yeah, download this video as soon as you hear it.
Is it playing?
Yes. Let's kill the cops tonight.
Yeah.
Yeah, this is me to a T.
There's a cop.
I'll let him go for now.
What happened in your past
that made you hate cops so much?
You don't want to talk about it?
No, I don't think I don't want to talk about it.
That's dark.
There's a lot of pain there.
This is the sad episode of RBCK.
This is the official sad episode.
Yeah.
Because we've been extremely sad so far.
You know, I mean,
the first cop I ever killed
was Mad Bull.
And as you know, Mad Bull is my dad
and everyone's dad.
So, you know,
there's a lot there.
Ben, how can we get this episode to be sadder?
Let's say something sad.
Um...
Uh...
This music's actually quite loud.
Um...
I'm tearing it down.
That's sad, because the audio recording won't be as good.
Yeah, yeah, bummer, right?
Yeah, that, you know, I'm crying.
Where...
is the fucking video there?
Let's kill...
Let's kill the cops tonight.
Okay.
Now I've got the pop-tropica music
that you're playing at the same time.
Yeah.
Get down from there. No, you dig.
Oh.
Um...
Hey, uh, well, you know,
life is, in fact,
a swirling maelstrom of meaningless chaos.
None of which we can escape from.
Right?
That's pretty sad, right?
Doesn't that just bum you right the fuck out?
It does.
You've been grumpy lately,
and I want to get to the bottom of why you've been so grumpy.
Have I?
Yeah, you've been nothing but a sourpuss lately.
Well, I mean...
Whenever I join a PCP episode,
you're always like,
oh, I'm in a pissed-off mood today.
You always have to see how this recording goes,
and, you know, if you wrong me one more time,
you know, your head's gonna be clean off.
Yeah.
Um...
Scram.
Uh, well, I mean...
That was true of the last one.
And maybe of the one before that.
And maybe even of the one before that.
Um, but I mean, I'm not...
I don't think there's any pattern there.
Is what...
Is all I'm saying.
Um, I don't know.
I...
I guess I've been...
I don't feel like I've been feeling
worse than usual or anything.
Maybe I'm just an asshole.
Do you think of that?
Yeah, well, I mean, that's why I was first thinking.
But I thought, no.
No, impossible.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to disappoint you.
Um...
It won't be the last.
So don't worry about it.
Can I land on these cinder blocks?
No.
Oh, look at this fantastical world we're in.
The fucking dumpsters in your convention setting.
Yeah.
We're bursting out of the...
Of the building.
Ruining the environment around us.
I guess I'll go climb up some other building.
This is fucking...
This is really based off of Comic-Con.
And it is clearly based upon, like, the convention center.
That I lived here and I passed every single day.
Wait, this is convention center.
Oh, convention center up this way.
Okay.
This is really bizarre.
I don't like it.
Did you earn the Tony and the Tiger blow-up inflatable
at Comic-Con last year?
Yeah, I do.
I understand.
Did that really happen?
No. I'm just talking about the advertising.
The Hey Kids is advertising.
Do you know what a Hey Kids entertainment is?
No.
It was an AI who made
children's
comedy on YouTube.
And he would appear as an Indian man with his skull broken.
And he would say,
I don't forget you to tie your sport shoes.
Sometimes he would appear as Hitler
and slash or Darth Maul.
And he would scream at you.
Um, was he
paid to do this?
No, this was a robot.
Oh.
Was he paid in
circuit chips?
Yeah.
Yeah, energy balls?
He was paid in oil and nuts and bolts.
Delectable.
He was
he was paid in human suffering.
I wish
I could get me some of that.
Ooh.
Do you see that guy's facial hair?
No.
I don't know what to make without any instructions.
Instructions.
If you want to make your own costume parts,
this is the place to do it.
Instructions.
Yeah.
Space John.
That guy has nothing to say.
Uh...
Space John.
No, he spoke Fremulon.
Study Up.
Oh my goodness, like Klingon.
Yeah.
What if it was like Aliens
in space?
Okay.
Great.
You guide to frequent Fremulon phrases.
How are you?
Scrash some Baloo.
I'm fine.
Scrum Belizu.
Where is the restroom?
Crosses up Bamblex.
The restroom is behind you.
Bamblex is up and frozen.
I can't.
I can't be bothered.
Study Up.
Yes sir.
Oh, he's so cool.
But he's not Keto.
He's eating pizza.
So unfortunately, I have to cut our relationship.
Yeah.
You know, priorities.
Blah, blah, pet baits.
Okay.
Great. Thank you.
Pony Whisperer. That's me.
That's me.
Oh look, Bamblex.
That's Fremulon for restroom.
This fucking...
This awful
Frosted Flakes advertisement needs to stop
immediately.
Space Jump.
It seems you've filled the brim with advertising.
You cannot escape it.
Watch the
trailer for Magi Man Action Force.
Can I do that?
How do you do that?
Click on the billboard.
I mean, I'm sure
it will happen.
Is that Starbucks?
I think it's Starbucks.
I have a Starbucks thing.
It says coffee
with something
coffeehouse. I can't read the
top word.
Someone's coffeehouse.
Maybe if I go around
to the other side.
This
level is really depressing
and makes me
never ever want to go
to a convention again.
I don't know
what the fuck they were thinking.
Yeah, it's like
let's recreate
the human misery that is
a convention.
Ooh, Watch Parts.
Now I can go to the steampunk convention.
Oh, thank god.
I think that's literally what that's about.
I think that's literally the point of that.
Yeah, let's recreate standing
in line. Let's recreate getting
shit expensive food.
Yeah, let's recreate
a bunch of idiots
all in a
weird mad frenzy
to consume some culture
for a price
as they all show up
and shill for their favorite intellectual
properties that they don't own.
Yeah, let's recreate the terrible advertising
that's ever around there.
Everyone enjoys because that's the way
that culture is now.
It's culture and it's actively participated.
Ugh, god.
Dammit.
That's how this makes me feel.
Bad.
Um,
Poptropicon.
This is fucked.
Those bushes and that like
structure I have seen in my life
in real life before.
I'm so sorry.
I don't believe this.
I can't believe this.
Why?
Don't tell anyone I'm up here.
Dammit. Where's the...
There's another wizard. I'm looking for a different...
Where's the steampunk?
I'm looking for a different wizard.
Uh...
This watch was just hanging
from like a street sign and I just stole it.
Um, well, that's fine.
That's vandalism.
Can you give me this where you
steal stop signs so that people don't stop
and they hit people?
Hey, that's pretty good.
That looks pretty dang good right there.
Yeah.
Okay, perfect.
Look at me.
Look how perfect I am.
Look how
beautiful.
Alright.
Beautiful, it's true.
I saw your face.
Ooh.
Uh, what is the point of this one?
No turning point for stuck in the road.
Da, da, da, da.
She by the ribs directs
to where to go.
Da, da, da, da.
To choose memories and dead skin on trial.
I got a question, but a lesson
learned in time.
When it hasn't been your day,
your week, your month, or...
I'll be there for you.
And I'll be there for you.
Da, da, da, da, da.
Found a way.
You should open up your eyes.
I'll be there for you.
Da, da, da, da.
Thanks.
Uh, where do I go?
You get to be in the same room
with someone who's made your favorite
children's cartoon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I get to meet someone
who met Lauren Faust.
Yeah.
You remember how
Bronies would ask the voice actors
things about the story?
Did they really?
Yeah. How embarrassing.
Yeah, they would ask the voice actors.
Why would they be so foolish?
The voice actors, they would be like,
hey, so Tara Strong, why did this happen
in this episode?
What was Tara's characterization, then?
Like, why did that happen?
Yeah, like, why did, hey Tara Strong,
why didn't, uh,
Princess Celestia,
why didn't Twilight just tell Princess Celestia
to get fucked?
Yeah!
Why didn't she tell that
to Celestia? Lay off.
Damn straight.
She's trying to be a single mom in Ponyville.
She won't
do it, though.
God damn!
I mean, I feel like I'm supposed to jump
into the basket of the catapult?
Ever since Brad got her teenage
pregnant, she's had teenage
children, and she needs to get rid of them
pronto. God!
Well, Twilight, it would make you Princess,
but you are a D4C twice over.
Yeah, so, you know,
the ship has sailed on that.
Yeah.
Oh, man.
When are you coming,
when are you coming to visit Boston again?
Um,
soon. And by soon, I mean,
probably December.
Hmm, what,
that's like, that's like an entire year.
I, um,
well,
you're such a bullshitter.
You bullshat me.
You could view time
that way if you wanted to.
All right.
You could view
three months a year if you chose
to do that. Wait, when was the last time
you were here?
March. So, like,
most of a year.
Oh, you're saying
that, I thought you meant that December
was a year away. No, no, like, since
the last time you were here. That's like, from
March to December is most of a year.
Um, well been. Yeah.
This, this is a,
this is a, I don't know, I don't know
describe, I don't know the feeling that this might,
you know, give off.
But this might be
starting, like,
next fall
around this time. I might be in
Boston forever.
Oh, really?
Is that so? Yeah. Is that a fact?
I'm thinking of going
to college.
And, like, really thinking. Oh, god.
With my real brain.
Well,
uh, okay.
And you'd, you'd
come around here?
Yeah, I would. Yeah.
Um, sick.
Like, do you know where
you want to apply to?
Yeah, I do. I don't want to
speak in, I do want to talk
about this. This is one of the things I want to talk about.
But I don't know how specific I want to get
for, you know, obvious reasons.
And also the fact that if, for some
reason, I change my mind, I don't want to have
people, you know, fucking
giving me shit about it. But I,
it is a pretty, you know, like
my, my, my
thoughts and feelings are there.
And they might change, but I don't think that they will.
Thoughts
never change.
Yeah, feelings never change.
I can't change your mind.
Okay, okay. Um, I just,
the, the, I feel like
I'm supposed to be putting on, like,
a disguise?
Like, I think that's what the game wants me to do.
They told me to linger over it.
But, I don't know how.
Like, there's the,
like, okay.
They, the lady at the beginning
was like, do you know how to
customize? And like, yes I do.
But, and then, but then
there's this costume closet.
And like, I feel like
I'm supposed to have
like items
in,
I don't know, man.
This costume, I just,
Do you want me to get the walkthrough open? I don't understand.
Yeah, this, this costume closet is
clearly supposed to do something.
Here, here, don't worry.
I'll come to your rescue here.
Probably, I'm supposed to do something with the
Fracksulons or whatever.
Alright, how long have we been going?
Oh, two and a half hours.
That's nothing.
That's two and a half hours too long.
That's absolutely nothing.
Uh, okay.
Ask the girl in line
who's holding two tickets
and waiting, if she has
an extra ticket. She will say that she's
looking for someone who hasn't arrived yet.
Ask her what he looks like
and she will show you a selfie that looks
like a regular photo. Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, the wizard guy, right?
I guess so.
Now, customize yourself to look like him
and steal his fucking ticket, I guess.
And he probably spent like
$120 on it. Look, that guy's got like a beard, though.
Sure. Alright. Okay.
Yeah, I figured it was something like that.
Well, that's why I put on this wizard.
Asshole. Jesus Christ.
That's why I put on this wizard hat.
Um,
is it this girl?
No, it's this girl.
You're not my friend. He looks like this.
Oh, god.
Look at that smartphone.
Okay, I need a fake beard.
Gray hair.
Look at him. What you have to do is you have to
find him and then, you know,
just take all the hashtag
steal his look. Well,
I haven't seen anyone that looks like that.
Well, you have to find him.
That's the point of the game.
I don't think that
is the point of the game.
I think I'm supposed to like mix
and match.
I think I'm supposed to mix and match people's
costumes until I look like him.
Let me consult the rock.
Wait.
Hold on. Open up the
open up the
the fucking
the photo.
Okay.
Can you can you
like click on him or something?
Can you like do it from this screen?
No, I can't.
I cannot do it from that screen.
Okay. Okay. Okay. You're right.
You are right, actually.
I knew it. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
So I just have to
get his staff. Someone in line.
I got the staff. I got the staff.
Okay. Okay. I need like a moon
and stars belt. I need like a Jedi
robe.
All right. All right. Climb up the next level
on the building and run across the tables
and grab some bottles.
I got the bottles. Customize the guy
pushing the solar dispenser. You need his
beard.
Okay. I think the guy at the
solar dispenser is this way.
All right. Well, now that I know
what I'm looking for is probably
won't be that bad.
This is this is a follow
up to last episode where
where I was I think I think was last
episode or something like that where I was
thinking about
I was thinking about, you know, it sure would be
cool if I were able to call him that's gone
and passed and I can't do that anymore.
Why would you think that you're like 17?
I know
and it's silly.
I thought that
you know I had already like
like I had already like
been so focused
on doing like
you know fucking silly shit on the internet
that I thought well that's just what I'm going to have to do with my life.
It's actually a perfect
timing and I can absolutely
do that. What's wrong
with you? Why would you think that it's not
why would you think that this is not the time?
Okay, I understand
I understand it at the time
it looked bleep
but yeah, so
I
I have no idea
I've kept this close to
my chest because I have no idea
how anyone else will respond to it.
I assume that would be like
Oh, I found it. I found the moon and stars
belt. Fuck yeah. Sick.
Oh, is it from the non-kido guy?
Yeah, it's from the non-kido.
I'll have to dip into this.
Have you found the tiny machine guy?
No, not yet. Okay.
Yeah, there we go.
Wait.
What else do I, oh the beard.
Yeah, I think the beard's the last thing.
Uh, let me see.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
After you get the beard
then you'll have to go to the girl again
and then she'll say, she'll ask you for an item that you don't have
and you're gonna go to the public restrooms
and you'll find the girl, like one of her friends
crying.
Uh,
ask him if he's holding something for his friend.
He says he left it in the bathroom.
He'll leave after complimenting your costume
and then you'll have to go in and get the item
to be the person.
I have gone, like, I've gone
the entire breadth of this map
and I have not seen a guy pushing a vending machine.
I feel like I saw him before.
You, you, you did.
He's like on, like, a second story of the villain.
Oh, okay.
Well, that helps.
Let's see.
I'm really hungry
but the thought of eating food makes me sick.
You ever feel like that?
No. I do feel sick from
being full, though, now.
I feel like
whenever I eat any food, no matter how little
food I eat, my stomach always feels like
it's upset now.
Is, okay, okay.
I think it's, I think it's here, right?
That makes sense.
Go to the right.
Okay.
This is weird.
You have definitely seen him before.
Does it say where he is?
No.
Yeah, I've definitely...
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Go to the level.
Go to the part of the map where you see the girl.
The one who's going to give me the ticket.
Yeah, it says that it's above there.
Oh, okay.
Alright.
Let's see.
Come on.
Oh, there we go.
Here we are. There we go.
Now we're cooking.
You want the gas?
Alright, there we go. Get that guy's fucking beard.
Oh, okay.
So that's how you get a beard.
You're the spitting image.
The spitting image, yeah.
You know, I changed my hair color, but whatever.
No pain, no game.
No pain, no game, no pain, no life.
Alright.
Here I am. I'll take my ticket now.
Asshole.
Okay, I give you a ticket and you give me what you promised.
To the restrooms.
I say that every day.
I've never,
never had a convention.
It seems more unappealing.
If this is,
yeah, if this is like an advertisement
to go to Comic-Con, then they're failing
extremely hard.
It almost works.
It's like a, it almost works
as like a cruel parody of one.
Awful.
Oh, my body hurts.
Hey.
A tropical is a cruel, cruel mistress.
Yeah.
Are you holding something for your friend?
I had it when I went into the bathroom, but I must have left it in there.
What? Let me go!
Fuck!
I had it when I went into the bathroom,
but I must have left it there.
In the bathroom, you say.
Okay. Nice costume, by the way.
There, there, there should be
an arcade island
where you get to play this game in Tycho.
And they're trapped in their favorite video game.
There is.
It's called On the Rain Slick
Precipice of Darkness.
All of us have read Cave Story.
I'm racking my brain. Who played Thor
in that old Viking movie?
Wait, is that a real, wait, wait, real?
Yeah, look, I'm racking, I'm racking
my brain
to remember who played Thor in that old Viking movie.
Remind me and I'll trade my spot.
What?
Okay, well, I think
that the guy with the catapult
was talking about
Vikings.
So, uh, you know.
Let's go do that, I guess.
Man, I hate how I look right now.
What do you mean? I mean in real life.
Oh, okay, great.
Yeah.
Owns.
Uh...
Hey, this guy is a Viking.
God, they're in line
to watch a trailer.
It's true, it's real.
They're in line to watch a trailer
and the tickets for the trailer
have been sold out for months.
I'm gonna kill myself.
It's true to life.
Well, me killing myself
is also true to life.
The problem with this is that it's not accurate
in the sense that there's not thousands of people.
Yeah.
There's only a few weirdos.
Instead of this just being what culture is now.
Which is the chaos.
Yeah.
This girl's cute.
This girl's cute, I like her.
Bucky Lucas is Thor.
Bucky Lucas is the Norse god of thunder, sounds like a hit.
But wait, she said an old...
She said an old, uh...
Viking movie.
This is like an ad for a new one.
So that doesn't make any sense.
Maybe you're supposed to say that to her and she'll be like
ah, no you fucking idiot.
No stupid, yeah, that's the new one.
Bucky Lucas is a
is a hacked fraud and
you know, he's getting hashtag me too
on Twitter as we speak, so don't even speak
that name in my presence.
You will be shot.
I went to Disneyland recently.
Yeah.
And the entire time on every single roller coaster
during the drop
I would either say
Alvin, Alvin, Alvin
exclamation point, or I would say
you hire James Gunn at the top of my lungs
or rehire James Gunn rather.
I've never been to Disneyland.
Have you ever been to Disney World?
No, but I think it's gay
because it's on the East Coast.
It's better.
Disneyland is fake.
You've never been to Disneyland.
Yeah, but it's not the real one.
Disney World is the real one.
It's not even true. Have you been to Epcot?
Yeah.
I've never been to Epcot. I want to go to Epcot really bad.
Yeah, there you go.
Disney World is the real and land is a pale imitation.
Epcot is such a weird thing.
I had not known
that there were more theme parks in Disney World
than the Magic Kingdom until like a year ago.
And I thought it was a weird
disturbing discovery that there were like
three parks.
Look what I'm doing. Look what I'm doing right now.
Yeah, it's offensive.
It's fucking really culturally insensitive.
Oh no, I think that I have just had the like
I think that just like the aspect ratio
of the video has been fucked up for like a long time.
And I've been just off screen.
I'm looking at the video. I've been like
off screen, off the bottom of the screen
for like a, oh god.
What are we?
Disaster.
Absolute nightmare.
Okay, no, no, viewers, please
forgive me.
This is what they deserve.
There we go.
I mean, they haven't been getting the full
Pop Tropica experience.
They have themselves lucky.
I'm jealous of them, yeah.
Okay, there you go.
Do you want to stand in line for
six hours and pay $125
to see the new Avengers 4
trailer?
God, yes.
I want to,
I want everyone to know how much personality I have
because I like movies.
I'm so quirky.
Because I like that one movie that everyone likes.
Okay, I've been watching
I've been watching The Bachelor a lot recently
for reasons I won't describe
and that are top secret.
But what's
interesting is that everyone has tried
themselves as a nerd
and I don't.
On The Bachelor?
Yeah, on The Bachelor.
Why are they nerds?
What was their justification?
They just say that they're a nerd
and they're like, oh yeah, don't worry, I'm such a nerd too.
I'm such a nerd.
I get what?
That's just the way
that's just what you're supposed to be.
You're supposed to be a nerd.
Yeah, you're supposed to have
niche interests like the Avengers.
You know,
like being a bachelorette.
You're supposed to be in each niche interest.
You know what, you're right.
I am cranky lately.
Is it because of the Avengers?
It's probably because of the end of
Infinity War.
Yeah, bummed me out.
I've never recovered from when I didn't
see that movie.
How could you not have seen the
Avengers of the summer been?
How could I have not seen the most ambitious crossover
in history? I don't know.
I managed it. And look, I'm still here.
I'm still here.
You're still breathing.
I'm still relevant, baby.
I'm supposed to find out when the
cosplay contest is.
I can't wait for the PCP video
we've all been working on for half a year.
The ambitious last Jedi review
that's going to really break new ground
and impress everyone
with our last Jedi.
I can't wait for that to drop.
We've been working on it tirelessly for months now.
Yeah.
The hottest of takes.
This unbelievable
125 Fahrenheit
taker about to throw at you.
For you to digest.
You might have thought you knew
what this movie was.
We're going to revolutionize it.
Yeah.
We basically will be
George Lucas
in the sense that we didn't make the movie
and had nothing to do with it.
Hey.
Where do I find out where the fucking
cosplay contest is?
Did you go to the bathroom already?
Yeah. The girl was like
tell me when the cosplay contest is
and I'll trade you my spot.
She's Christ.
But it is costume.
Costume craft station.
Get some coffee then.
I have my monster absolutely
zero.
All right.
Look.
The problem is not chemical.
The problem is
the problem is
I can't I can't be expected
to stay away from this.
Go get the backpack
in the dumpster.
Did you get the backpack in the dumpster?
I don't think so.
No.
All right.
Backpack in the dumpster.
I didn't even
backpack in the dumpster.
Also, if you want to, you can run back
to the guy in the restroom line
and tell him who Thor is.
I already did that.
Okay.
Come on.
God, there's so much
fucking Tony the Tiger.
Ask her.
Okay.
Ask the next lady in line
who's next to the guy
who wants to know who Thor is
and she'll tell you in the cosplay convention.
No, you
she's the one asking me
when the cosplay convention is.
That's what the fucking guide says.
Well, it's wrong.
Next to the
next to the Thor guy?
Oh, wait.
Oh, like this lady?
Next to the Thor person.
No, not that Thor.
The guy who wants to know who Thor is.
The person in line is the one
that asked me when the cosplay contest is.
Okay.
Let me see.
Also,
I know there were...
Okay, here's a dumpster.
But there's no backpack.
Alright, run to the convention center
and hop to the second level.
There you'll find a picture of Lance Pitcher
dresses what it looks like
a goggle-wearing adventurer with a pirate sword.
This poster will also say the cosplay contest
starts at noon. Click at the poster.
Go back to the lady and remind her
and she'll trade her spot.
Okay, where's the poster?
It's the convention center's second level.
Uh, okay.
I think that's the one where
the people are waiting, so I think that's this one.
Probably.
Mmm.
Alright.
Cosplay contest at noon.
There it is.
Costume contest at noon, eh?
Oh.
Cheers.
Cheers to that.
Oh, yeah.
What?
What's this?
Slauncha.
Yeah, Slauncha.
Did you, in fact, see
the periodical
post of the Flash Jedi?
Have you seen the Periodic Table
of Star Wars?
You got C-3-P-M, R2-D-Tunium,
you got Obi-Wan-Kinobium.
You see, the laughs never stop.
You see, I'm a nerd
because I can memorize the Periodic Table.
Oh.
Yeah, I remember the first
10 digits of Pi.
Yeah, I know Biggie.
You know, Nate has like 100 digits
of Pi memorized.
Why? I don't know.
Because he's such a nerd.
Yeah.
Only the one
who wields the power amulet
can displace me.
The Cheetah Bandit has it.
The Cheetah Bandit.
Ah, Jesus Christ.
You mean Tony the Tiger?
Tony the Tiger should be an artist again.
Do you mean Cheeto Man?
I think you might mean Cheeto Man
from Tales Get Strolled.
Tell your dog that I hate it.
Thanks. I will.
Good.
Don't worry, the feeling's mutual.
Oh, Cheeto. Cheeto Bandit.
Cheeto Bandit.
Fucking hell.
Got backtracked.
The power amulet cannot be given.
It can only be beat me to the top
of the water tower.
This is just one big fetch quest
to get into a fucking convention
to watch a trailer of the Avengers.
Yeah.
It's a big fetch quest to watch a trailer.
Is that the point?
Yeah, it's the point.
Are you sure?
Yeah, you want a ticket to get it.
Really?
That's what we're after here?
Yeah.
Oh, motherfucker.
What? I fell.
I failed in my task.
This is a nightmare.
Yeah.
Somebody please end it.
Oh, no, no, no.
I gotta learn the path.
Okay.
Get up here.
Get on the window.
Get on the window seal.
How do I...
Do you see anywhere that I could jump to?
I mean, up on that little...
Go to the right, maybe?
On the window seal?
Oh, wait.
Okay, I gotta bounce on this clothesline.
Yeah, yeah.
Alright, well, I failed.
The power of good triumphs again.
Yeah, right.
Wait, what?
Oh, you have to race him.
Yeah, it's a race.
Yeah, it's a bad video game.
Oh, well, you fucked up and you should stop.
No, no, no.
Oh, you're ahead.
I just used a shortcut.
Do you see that?
Yeah, that was crazy.
Yeah, crazy.
That was crazy how I won this game.
Cheetah's never prospered.
Whoa, the whole thing was just for that pun.
Hmm.
Heck's cool.
I don't get it.
I don't get any of this.
You know what they say, Ben?
There's no way out.
You know what they say?
Last year, I was a 4.5 out of 10.
Ugh.
Wow, guys.
Did you know there's no gravity in space
so that when they drop the bombs,
they would just float?
Did you know that the Star Killer
base is like bigger
than the Death Star?
And that's stupid because
fucking, it's stupid.
Yeah, like why would it be
bigger than the Death Star?
It's retarded.
Why are they the resistance
if they're
the good guys
and they're already in charge?
I'm in a real hurry.
Can I cut past you?
Only the one who goes the Power Emerald.
Yeah, I got it.
Mark Davis.
I mean,
Steven Spielberg.
I mean, George, I mean,
Andy Warhol,
director of Back to the Jedi
by my hands.
He's such a fucking idiot.
He made such a shitty movie.
Can you believe how stupid he is?
Andy Williams?
Yeah, yeah.
Wait.
Can't believe how idiot he is.
If you can trade me
the Fremulon Mask from the booth?
I mean, I can get the Fremulon Mask.
That's easy.
I am...
I'm feeling cold.
I'm feeling cold in my extremities.
I think this game is
giving me diabetes.
Hold on.
PopTropica Worlds is the sequel to PopTropica.
Maybe we've been playing the wrong game.
Maybe we should be playing the sequel to PopTropica.
Ooh.
Gosh, you're mine.
Okay.
So I got the Fremulon Mask.
What the fuck is happening here?
I wonder if this will...
I wonder if this will do the trick.
I have a feeling no.
I want to see when the last island was added.
Yesterday.
Twenty-four hours ago.
They're adding...
They're literally adding new islands every day.
They're adding islands faster than you can even play
the game.
They're adding islands faster than you can even play them.
Alright. Crisis Caverns.
May 23rd, 2017.
May 23rd?
27...
Okay, so like a year and a half ago.
So almost as long ago as the last time
you were in Boston.
Hey.
It's very funny then.
Yeah. Hey.
What do I do?
So I'm wearing...
I'm wearing the Fremulon Mask.
He says he wants me to trade him a Fremulon Mask
from the booth.
I guess I have to buy it?
Money?
Yeah, maybe.
Look.
See?
You want... Oh, you want this mask?
See if you can carry on a basic conversation
in our language.
Scram Beelzebub.
That's not right. You should study your Fremulon.
Okay. Okay. Here we go.
Uh...
Okay.
How are you?
Scram Beelzebub.
Alright. I think I got it.
I hate Star Trek.
Uh...
Here. No, no, no. Check this out.
Check this out.
Scram... Okay.
Scram Beelzebub.
I really did it. Okay. There we go.
And...
You really did it.
I really learned a lot today about...
About the nature of trust and friendship
and how it all means fucking nothing.
About... Yeah.
It's not... It's all about what you like.
Not what you are like.
And what I like
is Star Wars.
Did you...
Did you make that after that?
It's not about what you're like, it's about what you like.
No.
That's from
a movie. I don't know what movie.
But it's got... But it's Star's...
God.
Who's Rocky?
Rocky Beelzebub.
Yeah, no, no. Who's the actor?
Sylvester Stallone.
Yeah, it was a Sylvester Stallone movie.
And I don't know what movie it is,
but Innuendo Studios referenced it in a video
and he's played that clip of Sylvester Stallone saying
it's about what you like,
but it's not what you are like.
And, you know,
never has that been more true than Comic-Con.
Heyo.
I'm thinking about coming to Boston for Halloween,
but I don't know how long I'll be able to do it.
I hate Halloween.
It's a retard holiday for faggots.
Oh, I fucking hate you. How could you...
Why? Why do you think it's gay?
There's nothing good about it.
It's a scary holiday.
It's a time to indulge in scary things.
It's not scary. It's boring.
What do you... Okay.
Sure, the last of the Halloween
may not have been fun,
but it's all about the people you're with.
Um...
I guess...
I...
Halloween's great if you know how to spend it.
Well, anything's...
Any day is fun
if you spend it with people that are fun.
Idiot.
Yeah, this is not...
You've convinced me of nothing.
I'm saying
as if I was there
and we all met up,
it'd be a great Halloween.
I guess.
Not because Halloween's any good,
because it's not. It's dumb and...
I don't know.
It's just embarrassing.
Why is it embarrassing?
The whole spooky conceit of it
is dumb and embarrassing
anyway.
It's just a boring hassle
for nothing.
It's like owning a pet.
Celebrating Halloween is similar to owning a pet,
and that you should be ashamed of yourself if you do it.
Owning a pet makes you human.
It's the only way that we can distinguish
ourselves from animals as if we own
and subjugate animals.
Did we own them?
Uh...
Oh, god.
Okay, I guess I need glue
and
a backpack.
Um...
Wait, no.
I need...
I need... Yeah, okay.
I need glue and I need spray paint
or spray...
something.
I have the backpack straps.
I have the watch parts. I have the bottles.
Can you, uh...
Uh...
If you can replace
my busted jetpack, you can
steam right past me.
Yeah, yeah, I gotta have steam punk...
I gotta have watch parts for my steam punk backpack.
Christ, stupid.
I just need... Steampunk and Doctor Who
are, like, my least favorite things
in society.
I don't know anything about Doctor Who, but I feel like
I wouldn't like it if I did.
I hate anyone
who, like,
likes anything about Doctor Who. I hate people who are, like,
like, fezzes are cool.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
People that like Doctor Who are awful.
Oh, there's some glue.
Well, I remember when
Vincent van Gogh cried.
Um, what?
I remember when Vincent van Gogh cried
in Doctor Who.
Uh...
Eee, Vincent van Gogh.
Did that really happen?
Yeah, he cried.
That's funny.
Well, I mean, I think so.
Um...
Oh, look, it's a jetpack now!
Oh, perfect. You know what?
That works.
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
I've done good work here today.
The only cosplay was that easy.
Basically is.
Yeah.
If you've got boobs,
cosplay is just that easy.
You don't have...
There's no craft involved in making a thing.
That looks like a thing.
I'll give them one to ten. How much do you respect cosplayers?
If they make the costumes,
right,
if they craft the costumes themselves,
they might reach...
Okay, so cosplayers meaning
that they're making like an established character,
we're not talking about like original
characters and costumes,
then maybe a seven at tops.
Seven and a half on a good day.
And that's only if they've mastered their craft.
That's the height to which they can aspire.
What's the lowest we would respect the cosplayer?
I mean, I guess one.
There's no lower limit.
Oh, there she goes.
Escaping from above.
Can we watch the fucking trailer yet?
No.
Enjoy yourself in there.
I kept it nice and warm for you.
Great.
Gross.
Why am I even in here?
What did you just do?
Oh, I left...
in the bathroom.
Jesus Christ.
And nobody took it for some reason.
Mighty action force.
I don't know whether this
or an actual convention would be more
miserable and soul-crushing.
I think it's a toss-up.
They've really both got their strengths.
Mm-hmm.
When's RFCKCon gonna happen?
It's only gonna be the only good convention center.
Just imagine RFC...
Imagine the convention center just flooded
with wayward youths all committing
violence against one another.
Mm-hmm.
We're gonna legalize violence.
Yeah, for one glorious weekend,
violence will be legal
in the Boston Convention Center
or whatever it's called.
Uh...
Ugh.
Fuck. What was I doing?
Oh, yes. I wanted to give you
something.
I found your look before.
Hey, I no longer look like your friends.
But it doesn't matter.
Wait, what?
That whole thing was for nothing.
What?
That whole thing was for nothing. The deal's off.
Why?
Because the thing that you wanted
was in the bathroom and bathrooms are gross.
What?
Everything I've done was for naught.
No, it can't be. It was on the walkthrough.
I mean, yeah, obviously I did...
In terms of the game,
I did have to do it.
But, like...
...
plot-wise, no.
Lovingly...
you sound wistful.
I'd like to go to the...
All right, now you need to make yourself look like Thor.
Customize the beard the first guy
in the line is wearing.
Oh, okay.
Go to the parking line,
customize the chainmail suit the girl
is wearing. Just make yourself look like Thor.
Um, all right.
So...
Okay, the costumeizer...
Okay, any chainmail from the costumeizer...
thing.
And I need a beard
from the guy.
You need a Viking hat
from when the guy's in the restrooms.
You need a cape from a girl.
This guy's got a Viking hat.
Yeah, so probably...
Will that do?
Maybe.
I just want to watch
the Mighty Action Force trailer.
That's all I want.
Just wait 24 hours
and it'll be on YouTube. God damn it.
Is that so much to ask?
No, I need it now.
I have to run around the convention center and get in.
Well, I can wear a Viking hat over my wizard hat.
That's good shit.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you've changed everything.
You look so different now.
Yeah, well, you know.
Oh, yeah, there we go.
Now we're talking.
Why can't I equip his fucking
like, shirt?
It's forbidden.
Why...
Why is it not letting me equip
the fucking torso?
I just want to equip his clothes.
Fine, whatever.
Alright, well, I've got the beard.
I guess.
Uh, where'd you say that was chain mail?
Uh, let me see.
I think it's near the bathroom.
Okay.
No, no, no, no. It's the Forge Refinery.
The Forge Refinery?
Yeah, yeah.
It's where you made the jet pack.
Oh, sure.
Oh, the Forge Refinery, yeah.
Let's see.
Costumize.
Chain mail, look at the chain mail.
Ooh, I just got...
Check it out, I got some anime hair now.
Yeah. Awesome.
Okay, I got chain mail.
Uh, am I good?
Yeah, you're good.
Well, I mean, you need more things.
Okay.
What do I need?
Uh, uh, costume...
Okay, go to the restrooms.
Costumize the nearest guy's bike and hat.
Maybe you need a different bike and hat.
Alright.
Go to the bathroom.
I think you just got a...
You just got a Saunter Pass Tony the Tiger over here.
Oh, wait, my beard is gone. Fuck.
Oh, okay.
It's probably this dude's horned helmet.
Yeah, yeah.
That's so...
I mean, how am I supposed to know which Viking hat?
When there's like ten of them.
Oh my god, look at my hair.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Hell...
Yeah.
I don't want to lose that cop killer purple.
No, of course not.
Okay, so I've got a Viking hat.
I've got a hammer and chain mail.
Okay, I lost the beard, but I know where to get it.
I've got...
Thank god I've got...
Thank God I've got all this Mio energy.
Yeah, what would you do without it?
I've got a little bit of pineapple strawberry smash.
pineapple strawberry smash, and when that's done I've got black cherry, I've got wicked
blue citrus, and I've got my personal favorite, green thunder.
Ugh.
How you feelin' there, Ben?
I love video games.
I can hear it in your voice.
Yeah?
Can you hear my enthusiasm?
Oh, oh, I can hear it.
Okay, I think...
Is this it?
Did I do it?
Now that I look completely like shit, have I succeeded in the given quest?
Yeah, go to that at the catapult, and he'll think you are Thor, not the actor, or like,
you know, the, like, you know, anything I've got, he thinks you are really Thor.
You wouldn't think that, like, he wouldn't assume that maybe I was someone in a costume
at a costume convention or anything.
No.
Wow, that's an, okay, no, he thinks I'm a...
Okay, okay.
Only Thor himself could move me from this spot.
Wait, so, I guess, okay, you need a cape, I guess, do you not have a cape on?
Oh, yeah, I've got the, I'm wearing the wrong cape.
Okay.
Um, okay, it looks like I need, like, a brown fur cape.
All right, that'll be, it's right next to the guy with the hat that you got, so right
next to him.
Okay.
Jesus Christ, this 20 chagrin adds, like, like, 20 seconds on to our speedrun time.
At least.
Imagine, imagine speedrunning this, imagine speedrunning Pop Tropica.
Hold on, I'm gonna, I'm gonna search that right now.
Pop, early Pop Tropica, 80% speedrun.
Four minutes, two seconds.
Early Pop, I'm surprised early Pop Tropica by itself takes even that long.
Oh my god, this guy's going so fucking fast, holy shit.
Would you say that he's fasting?
I would say so, yes.
Good, good.
Oh, so, oh, oh, someone got early Pop Tropica in two minutes, 55 seconds.
It's gonna beat the record.
Oh, I found it, I found it.
All right, let's get this fucking cape.
Uh, okay.
Okay.
You look exactly like four.
So, like, the catapult guy, he'll trade me the Mjolnir replica knowing that it's a replica,
but only the real Thor can, can get him to move by trading him a replica of the hammer.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
God, don't you love Thor?
No.
No, because they're not like two years old.
Do you like how they can use Thor knowing that he's an Avenger but get away with it
and not get copyright claimed because Thor is a mythological creature?
Yeah, yeah, it's pretty sneaky.
Yeah, yeah, Thor, even from that old Viking movie about the Vikings.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not like, nothing, yeah.
Like superhero type of thing.
Intellect, you know, intellectually defensible Thor?
I have come bearing an important message.
Oh my god.
The Norse god Thor, is it really you?
Of course it's me.
Just look at my hammer.
Looks like a replica I saw earlier, but never mind.
Hang on, with the con.
Yes, yes, it's all I ever wanted.
I hate this guy.
This guy's a bad man.
He's like the catapult, completely defenseless.
Here we go!
Uh...
Oh, okay.
Yeah, this is a good plan.
This is a great plan.
Alright.
Wait.
Oh, oh!
For glory.
You did it.
I did it.
What did that?
Yes, now I can watch the trailer.
Yes!
Oh my god, thank fucking god, we did it.
Wait, is that it?
Like, do I not get to see what's inside?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, it's over, it's over.
So should I play next episode?
Oh.
Oh, there's two episodes.
So, oh you say you beat the first episode,
but you didn't beat the entire island.
Oh, well that's no good.
Jesus Christ, this can't go on much longer.
Oh, I think it can, I see.
Here we go.
These timings are, the cut-assist doesn't start for until the noon.
Oh man, the whole body is screaming at me.
When the costume contest.
Well, I mean, I've already got the ultimate costume.
Wait, the best...
Omega costume, a walk-on role in the mighty Action Force sequel.
That's the prize of a lifetime.
Who will make the best Omega costume?
I mean, that's if you did really good cosplaying,
then you got to be in the movie you were cosplaying.
Yeah, I mean, be pretty fucking neat.
The card games at these conventions are always the best.
Well, sure.
The same card games as anywhere else.
Yeah, but there's a person.
Oh god, it's Tony the Tiger, oh god.
Tony the Tiger is a certified RC cashier at this point.
Yeah, I think he's earned his place in the war.
Hey kid, come here for a second.
I want to talk to you about an amazing opportunity.
Wicked cool news relies on spies to get us inside information.
We need the first site to post what Omega on looks like before the trailer premieres.
Here's a phone, get photos of Omega and I'll put together an amazing costume.
Oh, we got a smart phone!
I didn't have one before.
Costume contest in the theater meets Stan Ditko, creator of Elf Archer.
I want to kill myself.
Any idea where I can go find out what Omega on is?
It's Stan Lee crossed at Steve Ditko, I get it.
Who's Steve Ditko?
Oh god, I think he made...
He's a god, I don't know.
I'm going to embarrass myself if I try and remember which things he made.
But he made a bunch of things.
There's actually three episodes in this game.
And this is only difficulty level two.
God, how fucking long would cryptids have taken?
I'm so glad we didn't.
What a missed opportunity.
Jesus Christ.
If you guys want a pop-tropica episode two.
Like, comment, subscribe for pop-tropicon episode two.
If we get 300 likes, then we'll do pop-tropica episode two.
I mean, we're doing pop-tropicon episode two right now.
Oh, check it out.
It's Tony Bros. It's Kagan Phantom.
Oh my god, it actually is.
It's actually Kagan Phantom. No joke.
No fucking joke.
How can you sue? Where's the sue button?
Where's the sue button?
Man, I could be playing... I could be playing phenotopia right now.
What is phenotopia? That sounds like a pop-tropica rip-off.
It does, doesn't it? No, it was a Newgrounds game.
It was a game featured on Newgrounds like four years ago.
And the sequel's been in the works for like even longer than that.
It's like a flash, like side scroller. It's kind of like a cave story RPG kind of thing.
With a little more action, a little more adventure-like fetch-questiness
and a little less like twitchy, like action-shooter-y bits.
I didn't even see where she went.
Is that her? Yep.
Look how bored everyone is.
Sam. Relatable.
Is there anything more relatable than paying?
Not for me.
It's even more relatable than pleasure for me, you know.
Oh, I fucked up. Wait, did I fucked up?
I look at someone who's smiling and I say, well, it's fleeting.
And then I look at someone who's utterly, you know, anxious and depressed.
I don't think, no, that's my guy. And now I can immerse myself in the story.
Uh, okay. I could maybe scrounge up some loose change.
You gotta reel off or call me. Here's my card.
Okay. So, I gotta trade her.
I'm gonna close her piece. Okay.
Uh, wait a minute.
Why would I want to call her?
Like, wouldn't I...
Why would I want to call her if I'm supposed to get into the theater
and take a picture of Omega on, right?
Isn't that my goal?
No, you're also winning the cosplay contest.
What? Okay.
Uh, but something about getting a picture of Omega on, right?
Right?
I don't know. Did you say that?
Yeah, totally.
Then yes.
This is the whole...
Look at that. Look at that.
This is a disgusting game. This is a gross grotesque game.
I don't want... No, I don't want the bubble.
I want to have a green furry head.
Piece of shit.
This is grotesque.
This is a horror game for me.
This homeless person needs to stop banging on the fucking mini machine.
This is such a fucking nightmare.
It's me. Look, it's me. This guy's me.
Oh, it looks exactly like you.
He's just like me.
I got a...
Is it that stern cold exterior?
I got to put out some fan art. I got to put out enough fan art.
Some original art by the creators of a cop killer Ben with my skull hat design.
I want to push that skull hat.
Posting community service.
I'll get people riled up.
Yeah, I'm sure that'll get their juvenile cocks big and green.
Don't say that.
No, whoops. Can I not say juvenile cocks on this show?
Leave cell phones and tablets here before entering the room.
Will do.
Oh god, she had to leave her phone.
She left her phone here and I'm going to steal it.
Granny Tech Lounge down the hall.
It's been with no...
Okay, maybe if I give him my phone, then something will happen.
What?
What is happening right now?
Okay, so...
Did I ever tell you how I went to BabsCon one year and I met with someone from SlashMLP
and his...
Not like his wallpaper, but like his lock screen was a picture of Anthro-Vinyl Scratch getting fucked.
Did you guys make that up?
Yeah, basically.
Can you imagine having that as your lock screen?
Not your wallpaper, but like your lock screen.
So like no matter what, it'll just turn on your phone.
Everyone will always see it 100% of the time.
Yeah.
Vinyl Scratch is a cutie pie.
Don't say that.
That's even worse than doing alcox.
I can't say anything.
I can't say anything anymore.
God damn this fucking liberals.
This PC culture.
Uh, what the fuck?
Her phone is in there.
I just need it.
Look, it was fun with early pop tropica.
It was fun with short teeth island.
We were blasting through things.
And now look at us.
Yeah.
We're ruined.
Jesus.
Look at me.
I'm dressed up as Thor.
I want to replay value does this game have.
Do you think you're going to replay this to get 100% anytime in your life?
Uh, like every island?
Yeah.
Uh, you know, all 9,000 moons.
Um, yeah.
I mean, I really don't have anything better to do.
Popular media collectibles.
Is this a parody?
Is this a parody of the con experience?
Because if so, I think it's pretty effective in making me laugh at it and pity it.
Wicked cool news.
Yeah, man.
That's, that's who needs the picture.
That's who needs, uh, the thing.
That's who needs to know about the, uh, thing.
The guy.
Omega on.
Holy shit.
Wicked cool news subsidiary of, of, of nerd news, whatever.
Nerd news nightly.
Kira nightly that is.
Great to see you again.
Do you want to learn how to customize?
I, I must, I know.
I already know.
I have to.
Holy shit.
I can't stand it any longer.
Do you want to go to different islands?
You beat episode one.
I can't fucking stand this game.
Jesus Christ.
What do you mean, man?
I hate pop tropica.
So this is the worst game I've ever played in my life.
I've never been so miserable.
I've never been so unhappy with any video game.
I don't care who, what makes you think that I value your life even a little bit.
You fool.
Oh, I went to the atrium.
Now, now, now here's what.
Oh, oh, it's one of these.
Oh, it's one of these.
A common room.
I need to lie down.
Yeah, you put yawning nonstop.
Yeah, because this game is fucking, it's a fucking snore.
We're talking about battle bots, go bots.
Go bots was great.
Go bots was the best.
Back in my day, we had go bots.
We didn't have fucking pop tropica.
We didn't have any of this shit.
And we liked it.
Back in my day, you know, back in my day, we just, um, uh, back in my day, we had, uh, we had Etch-a-Sketch.
And, you know, we just had like that weird, like white board and you had like the little magnet pen and you could like, it had iron filings in it and you could like draw on it with the iron filings pen.
And then the magnet pen and then you could shake it up afterwards and then you could do it all over afterwards.
And then with the fucking, coming along with these fucking troll two ass pop tropica.
I literally don't know what the fuck you were just describing by the way.
You know?
So it's gone, it's gone from culture and society.
No, no, no.
It's like an Etch-a-Sketch, but instead of drawing with like little dials, it was like a board of like little white cells and each of the cells had like iron filings in it.
And you would just take like a magnetized pen and drag the pen over the server and it would pull the-
Oh!
And it would pull the iron-
I do know what you're talking about.
Yeah, it would pull the iron filings to the front and it would make, you know, a mark and then you could shake it up or whatever and it would-
No, no, you could use the eraser side of the pen and it would push the iron filings away.
I do know what you're talking about actually.
How do I know that?
What's that called?
I don't know.
I have no idea what it's called.
Um.
That's like Doctor's Office Core.
Doctor's? That's like-
No, that's like my weird aunt's core.
That's like my weird aunt's or uncle's or someone who I don't know whose name I don't even know.
Who I just-
They have it in a box somewhere.
The height of childhood pleasure was all these doctors-
Er, no, no.
Dentist-
Dentist Lobby Core.
Because they would always lure you into a false security.
They were designed to be, you know, as appealing to a child as-
There was nothing more appealing.
Yeah.
Than reading Highlights Magazine in the Dentist office.
Yeah, reading Highlights Magazine and like, uh, fucking doing that one alligator tooth brushing game.
I don't know that one.
It's-
Oh, the one where you pull the teeth out?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, Mighty Action Force the card game.
Sign up here, yes.
Want to try a hand at the Mighty Action Force card game?
Of course.
May I-
May I order the-
The Milo Pony train card system?
No.
Good.
Welcome to the-
I only remember, uh-
The flanks.
I only remember Bruce Flanks or whatever his name was.
Oh my god, the first card pony girl.
Uh, show an extra card from your deck.
Choose card.
Ah, Jesus.
What is this final fancy shit right now?
Mutton chops.
He's one tough tenderizer.
Henchbot.
Another one of this-
Mutton chops.
There you go.
Bam.
Robo-dobo.
Yeah, Robo-dobo.
What about him?
Robo-bo.
My mortal enemy.
I'm losing my mind right now.
Is there rules to this game?
Yeah.
What are they?
Uh, okay.
So I think the goal is to get a lot of the jewels.
Uh-oh.
He's gonna get lots of jewels.
God, my deck sucks.
My right, fellow.
My deck sucks balls.
Ben, do you want to form a fief-
a fiefing organization in which we lust after large, uh, cartoonish diamonds?
Wait, a what?
Where we do that?
A fiefing organization.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, uh, like a side gig in international diamond smuggling.
Yeah.
Um, this, I'm not getting any fucking cards at all.
It's making me mad, man.
Listen, don't be mad.
Get glad.
No.
Pay for it.
Invite the trash can organization of America.
You're the trash can organization.
There.
That's what your mom said to me when we had sex last night.
No, not again.
Why do you keep doing that?
Why do you keep having sex?
Stop.
Would you please?
Shit.
Uh, there's one thing we can all agree on.
Yes, I can read the fucking rules of the card.
What?
Yeah.
Don't worry.
It's nothing.
No, but you got to talk over anything anymore.
You got to talk over this game.
Yeah.
I've realized, I've realized that everything I've been saying has just been going in one
year at the other because you're so focused on pop-tropic that you can't, you can't, you
can't do anything.
Under the banner of friendship, little peace is possible.
Uh.
All this conversation starts, I've been throwing out every, every second or so.
You've just been deflecting nonstop.
That's what I do.
I deflect.
He's a deflector, Jerry.
He deflects.
I'll ask you, what do you think about this?
You'll be like, oh, well, that's cool.
And then you know, let's go back to trying to min-max your card, your card capture skills
and pop-tropica.
I'm going to win.
What?
What is the goal of this game?
The goal is to fill up the meter on the bottom of the thing and prevent your opponent from
doing the same.
All right, let me just walk through immediately.
No, I, I understand, I understand how to play.
It's quite, it's quite simple.
Quite simple.
Child's play, really.
It really is child's play.
It literally is child's play.
I literally am playing a game for little children.
Apparently, you're supposed to be getting Pokemon, or you're supposed to be able to get
cards outside of this and supposed to collect a good set of cards so that you can beat him
or her, or her whatever.
I mean, she's pretty much running train on me.
Yeah, so you've got to go get good cards.
I mean, I think we're going to draw.
I don't think you can, the, the walkthrough says to get cards.
It might be literally impossible to do it without.
I think we might draw.
Depends what she's got in her hands.
Here we go.
I love Mighty Action Force so much.
I know, right?
Such a well-beloved, well-established series.
I can't get over the nuance.
There's been sheer nuance of it all.
No, I'm doing it too.
Yeah.
This game is a fucking snooze.
No.
Yeah.
I don't agree.
Yeah, though.
I don't agree with what you just said right now.
Okay, well, I'm definitely going to end with more gems, but I don't know if that's good enough.
Did you restart just now?
No.
She ran out of cards.
Yeah, I'm going to win.
I think.
It might be a draw, I don't know.
Heck yeah.
Uh, well, great.
Is that it?
World Guy.
Under the band.
Great game.
That card should help strengthen your deck.
You can reorganize cards in your deck item.
Just try swapping.
Well, obviously I'm going to get rid of this piece of shit.
Like, this is the easiest card game in the world because you literally just want all World Guys and nothing else, and then you'll win.
Alright, Todd is the girl upstairs and she will challenge you to a card game.
If you win, you'll get an unreleased Omeghani card.
That's actually pretty neat.
This is actually a pretty neat little subplot.
Oh my god, oh my god, look at what it is.
What?
Look what I'm pointing to.
Oh my god, holy shit.
There it is.
It's the fucking Slime Casino Dice.
It's the Slime Casino Dice.
What are the odds that those exact colors would be here?
Everyone go hit up the Slime Casino and play the new Slime Roulette.
Slime Roulette, yeah, Slime Roulette is new and it's there and it's weird and complicated and way more so than it probably needed to be.
And it's a hot new thing.
It's a hot new way to lose all your Slime Coin.
Jesus Christ, it's, oh, remember Investor?
First one for Investor.
Yeah, no.
I remember, I mean, I remember people talking about him as though he was real, but I know he was just an urban legend.
He's a cryptid, coming from Cryptid Island.
I know that a juvie could never really achieve such heights.
I know that he's just a folk legend that juvies tell their children to convince-
To make themselves feel better about their lowly station life.
To convince their kids not to join a gang because they know that once they join a gang, they will have the courage to kill themselves and they'll do it.
It's like children, it's like child suicide versus adult suicide.
You know, gang suicide is more brave than juvie suicide because there was nothing to live for anyway, so why would you even try?
Juvie kids are too cowardly, but gang kids, killer and rowdy kids, they've got the guts.
Hey, where do I go to challenge? What's your name?
I don't know why you left, it was just-
There was no way up, there was no way up.
You gotta get there somehow.
I guess, I guess that makes sense.
Talk to the girl upstairs and she'll challenge you to a math card game.
Well, I've gone the wrong way.
Just like in life, Ben.
Just like in life, I chose the wrong path.
God, I hate Tony the Tiger.
Tony the Tiger is the antagonist of this video game.
Ben, how would you arrange your life in such a way that you didn't have to play this game? What would be the first thing to go?
You.
Oh, yeah, yeah, I would say-
You'd be the first thing, you'd be the first thing on the chopping block.
Um, okay.
A demo area, I think that's where it was.
The bike unit game just entices you so.
I actually really like that there is like a collectible card game.
I think that's really cool.
It's the first-
It's the first thing that's been any good about this game at all.
Look, how do I get up there?
I have no clue, but you gotta charge up on the balloon.
Jesus fuck.
You gotta get up there.
There's a person up there, you gotta talk to that person.
I know, I know.
Maybe you have to collect the other cards first.
Listen, there's not that many of them.
There's not that many.
There's like five.
We can get them.
Okay, well where are they?
Okay, the first one is go to the theater and find a big box.
Push and get the teen acronym card.
Man, I was just at the theater.
Well, go back.
You told me.
You told me I had to go and challenge.
What's your name?
The demo area.
This game is gonna come between us, Ben.
It already has.
There's nothing to say.
I'm just gonna-
I don't like you anymore.
I'm just gonna come right out and say that I don't like you anymore.
And this game is the reason.
Is this gonna be the inciting?
Is this gonna be the lower canonical reason?
This is why it started the game.
Yeah.
Is this her?
I asked you to play pop trap.
I did.
And that was it.
Wait, is this it?
Is she it?
How do I challenge people?
Get the box.
That's the box, I assume.
Oh, yeah.
I think, right?
Sure.
There.
Yeah, the card's right there.
Oh.
With your eyes.
Oh, gotcha.
I don't know why it's so hard.
I can't.
I need to know what angel to use.
You're just somersaulting and back looking over it.
Okay.
All right, all right.
Now find the soda machine in the hallway and bang it.
And a pony girl card will fall out.
Sign the soda machine in the hallway?
Yeah.
Okay.
I assume the expo floor is that...
I mean, whatever.
This is getting me like...
Imagine if real conventions were like this where I just was so smart and there was literally nothing.
Just you going around in an endless circle trying to like look under trash cans and find cards to challenge people with.
That part I don't mind.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
I found the soda machine.
Uh, bang it.
Yeah, draw an extra card from your deck.
All right.
Yeah.
Get a balloon from the demo area and go to the expo floor.
You will see a card stuck in a window.
Go upstairs, jump and collect the trash collector card.
Wait, what?
Okay, I'll read it again.
One more time, please.
Get a balloon from the demo area and go to the expo floor.
You will see a card stuck in a window.
Go upstairs, jump and collect the trash collector card.
So get a balloon from the exhibit hall.
A balloon from the exhibit hall or from the demo area?
Oh, uh, the demo area.
Okay, I think that's over here.
Yes.
God, these frosted flakes houses.
I know, I know.
They're so bizarre.
Like, they're, they're, it's really surreal.
You'll just be walking through a convention center.
There's a nice little white picket fence house.
We're telling you the title.
Just ask him.
That's the guy in the night helmet.
Oh, here we go.
I got the balloon.
Oh, okay.
You got it.
Okay.
Oh, wait, I think I can get up there now.
Oh, well, perfect.
Feed my epic deck.
No, I want to get, I want to get all the cards.
Okay.
I have a feeling it'll be tough.
She's going to be a tough opponent.
Uh, okay.
Where's the next one?
Uh, it's in the, the, the Explo4.
Okay.
All right.
There's a card stuck in a window.
Go upstairs and jump and collect the card.
Okay.
So like it's in a window somewhere.
The card's stuck in a window.
I assume it'll be out of reach if I'm a normal jump.
That's why you need the balloon.
Hmm.
It's like somewhere fucking crazy, I guess.
Okay.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I see, I just got a float over there.
All right.
Not too bad.
Oh God.
Hey, like the controls of this game.
Oh, they're wonderful.
Trash collector.
You mean, okay, okay.
Costumerizer item.
All right.
There's like two more.
Okay.
Go to the exhibit hall and get up on the huge green statue above you.
Jump on the hand and a fashion ninja card will fall out.
Okay.
The exhibit.
Jump on the hand in the green statue in the exhibit hall.
Oh, look, it's Tony the Tiger again.
Oh, wow.
Like I have like a stat bar and it's, you know, one from 100.
And every time I see a frosty flakes thing, it goes by one point.
So I'm going to get there one bit.
Okay.
Somehow I never came here before.
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
Oh, wait.
Wait.
Come on.
I guess this is plot or something.
Stupid.
Get the card.
I can't.
I'm too high.
Come on.
There we go.
All right.
One more.
Okay.
Go upstairs.
This is where we're going to have to find the person anyway.
Keep stomping in front of the bulletin board by clicking on it.
Collect the dirt cloud card on the board.
Okay.
Demo area.
It's where the cards are.
Yeah.
Pretty sure it's over here.
Okay.
Demo area and then I stomp on the what now?
Bulletin board.
Okay.
You have to click on it a lot.
Oh, here we go.
Yeah.
So just click on it.
There we go.
All right.
Now you have all the cards.
Dirt cloud.
All right.
Sick.
Let me just smack him, smash him right into my deck here and steal one jump for your opponent.
Okay.
Play another card.
Yeah.
I want that one.
There's got to be an RFCK praying card someday.
Someday.
Block your opponent's action if it is of equal or lesser value.
Yeah.
I guess I want that one.
Your opponent's next turn is skipped.
Yeah.
I guess I want that one too.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm pretty sure I've got the old dude.
You mean fuck what was it called?
Sea creatures.
Yeah.
Dude, dude, dude.
We can make that.
Okay.
We can?
Once slime oids are in.
Once slime oids are in, I think making sea creatures will not be, like designing sea creatures
will obviously take some work, but I think that's the easy part.
But I think that once slime oids are in, designing sea creatures will be, like most of the work
will be done.
Yeah.
Sea creatures and sass effects are the, are the, are sass conditions are the best thing
I've ever thought of.
For the game.
Yeah.
Here we go.
Here.
Take aim at the heart of you.
Oh no.
She's got an epic deck.
Epic shit, dude.
Oh, make, make your opponent skip the turn, I think, right?
So that she can't attack you or something?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
I wish I could have skipped this turn.
Girl, I'll get you for that.
Nurgh.
And, uh, these nerds.
Yeah, bring out world guy.
Yeah.
We'll probably do just two world guys in a row.
He'll obliterate her.
I'm going to go, I'm going to go for the quick victory.
As opposed to, I could attack her gems down, but I'm going to go for gaining gems fast
as possible.
Oh no.
Oh shit, dog.
Okay.
Are you just putting a world guy again, I guess?
Draw an extra card from your deck.
Yeah.
I think we can do more.
Can you do attack opponent again?
You can only do, only if you use trash collector can you do two cards at once.
That's like trash collector special skill.
Okay.
Well, she gets a free turn, but whatever.
Yeah, who cares.
She can't possibly keep up.
Oh wait, we're tied now.
Well.
There's a little intricate game I've ever played.
Uh, teen erect.
Oh no.
Oh no, she's stealing my gem.
Oh, but guess what?
But guess what, idiot?
I might win next turn.
Oh my god.
Or, actually wait, you know what?
Oh wait, maybe I shouldn't have done that.
Maybe I should have attacked more just to prevent her from winning.
Oh no, if she plays a world guy, if she plays a world guy or a mutton chops, I think she'll win.
Holy shit.
So she might win, depending on what she's got in her hand.
Yep, there it is.
Oh fuck, god damn it.
Bear, you might go faster.
I don't think, I think I always go second.
Block your, oh I could block my opponent's action.
Do that, do that.
No, it won't work, because it's got to be equal lesser value.
I don't know man, we're both winning this turn.
No.
Fuck!
Oh wait, oh no, she didn't, she didn't do it.
Okay, there's one more slot.
We're both one slot away.
She's gonna win though, if she goes first.
Oh, I can block her action, fuck you!
This is the most legendary duel of all time.
Oh my god.
This is it, I did it, I did it.
It's like an out game.
Wait, blocked, draft, that card was used anyways, yeah!
Victory.
Yeah!
Yes!
We triumphed, we won the game.
Dirt Clawed won the day.
Wait, what, wait what just happened?
Why did I not just win?
I literally just filled up my gauge.
Literally.
I literally filled up my gauge.
I don't understand.
I don't understand either.
Oh, now it goes backwards, you have to delete all of her gems.
No, no, no, no, that's not it.
Like, I thought the goal was to fill up your meter.
Like, you can attack to lower their meter, or you can collect to fill your meter.
But my meter was full, what the fuck?
I'm upset.
This is fucking weird.
I think I'm going to win anyway, probably.
Oh wait, maybe not.
I want to show what the rules of this game is.
I understand the rules, but I don't understand why I didn't win.
Alright, get, I mean, you might win this round.
I should win this round, because I'm going to have more gems.
You don't even have another card to take, idiot.
What?
Oh, you know what I think it was?
I think that, like, it didn't let me do it, because it was putting too many gems in.
Oh!
I think it's because I was putting in two.
Beat my, and I'll give you an unreleased Omicron card.
Um, yeah, I want that.
That'll help me win the day.
Alright, okay.
I guess I just didn't understand the rules of overflow.
Stack overflow.
We're going down this time, whatever your name is.
God can only hope so.
Um, hey, what's going on here?
Um, we have to reload the game.
Cool.
Good times.
That's great.
Good times, yeah.
What made you sad recently?
What's made you sad?
What's the sad thing in your life?
Poptropica is the obvious.
You mean, yeah, like, it's almost too obvious.
What made me sad in my life?
Who are my stupid roommates that think that ghosts are real?
Is that sad, or is that just angry?
Both.
I feel bad for them.
Um, they're an embarrassment.
Wait, no, wrong, wrong, wrong.
Do you know what their opinion of Slenderman is?
Um, probably that it's real and coming for them.
Probably that you are Slenderman.
Probably that they probably tried to talk to it with that Ouija board, and we're disappointed that they received only.
Oh God.
Okay, no, I'm pretty sure that I have all the cards, right?
I have all the cards.
Yeah, I think you do it.
The bulletin board is fucked up.
Okay.
Okay, yay.
Yeah.
We got ourselves a game, boys.
Round two.
Well, two and a half.
Last one glitched out.
Round two glitched.
I've never lost a match, and I don't intend to start now.
I'm the ultimate gamer.
I can't wait for the creepypasta cinematic universe.
Ugh.
Same.
Um.
None of the Slenderman movies out now.
We're going to have the Jep the Killer.
We're going to have the Rick movie.
We're going to have normal porn for normalpeople.com.
Normal porn for normal people.
Have you not read that one?
No.
Wait, that's a creepypasta?
Yeah.
No, I never heard of it.
It's a story about a person going on the dark web to find a site called normalpornfornormalpeople.com.
And our witch.
There are videos about a man feeding a dog peanut butter sandwiches until the dog doesn't
watch anymore and he stops.
Uh, cool, I guess.
And then there's another video about a chimpanzee killing a girl.
And that's kind of funny, I guess.
We're both skipping our next turn.
Pretty funny.
Funny stuff.
Did you rock in the game?
No.
No, no, it handled it.
It handled it just fine.
Just barely, just barely.
Okay, as long as I have...
Yeah.
Okay, this is fine.
This is good.
She basically wasted her turn with dirt clawed.
I think that's pretty much how you win is wait for your opponent to play dirt clawed
and then cuck them out of it.
Okay, so I've got, I gotta get five and I gotta get six gems.
I gotta get six gems.
So two mutton chops.
Two mutton chops should do it.
Well, unless she attacks you.
Unless she, unless she does some weird shit.
And you're one ahead of her.
So unless she plays world guy.
Yeah, you're good.
She's gonna do right now.
No, oh no, she's stealing one.
That's fine, that's fine, that's fine.
Yeah, but it means I won't win this turn.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, I can do trash collector and mutton chops.
Okay.
And then I win.
Wait, no.
No, I don't.
Fuck.
This is a complex game.
It is.
I mean, sort of.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, dog.
Alright, then you just need one with two more.
I need one, yeah.
I mean, you have one, you have one, right?
So.
Oh God, okay.
No, she's attacking me for one.
No, she's attacking me for two.
So you need one chop and you have one, right?
She's attacking me for two.
Yes.
Well then you're good, right?
I think I'm gonna win.
Okay, okay, okay.
She doesn't even realize.
She doesn't realize how fucked she is.
Yeah!
There's only one thing to do now.
Return to my lucrative high-tech job.
Damn.
That's the equivalent of me saying nothing about it
when I had sex with her last night.
Oh.
Way to take the wind out of my sails.
Okay.
So I got a body like Zeus.
Why did the battery...
Why did they take the time to draw in
that the battery on this phone is low?
What an unnecessary detail.
Oh fuck, we're supposed to get other things before this.
Oh Jesus Christ.
What do you mean?
Alright, we need...
Okay, oh my God.
You've completed one of three quests
to unlock the different parts of this cosplay.
Yeah, yeah.
I gathered that much.
Oh my God, it's Lego City.
Oh, it's like an old friend.
I want...
No, I want fucking Lego Ninjago.
When am I gonna see Lego Ninjago World?
I don't think that's a thing.
Is it?
I mean, I keep seeing ads for it on the sides.
Alright, okay, okay, okay.
Oh my God.
I'm assaulted by words right now.
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's do it.
Let's guess these games.
Okay, okay.
Look like the elf archer from math.
Customize the guy in green on the left
to get his mask.
This is supposed to be the first area
where you crash through the Midget Center.
Um...
Okay, so that's the theater, I think.
Okay, yeah, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, sick.
Yeah, so sick then.
So sick.
Maybe I can...
Can I customize Lego Arctic Man?
Oh, try.
I'm sure that I can't.
Well, why not?
Because it would be cowardly.
Okay, here we go.
Alright, alright, alright.
Get his mask.
Alright.
Got it.
Uh...
Go to the expo floor on your right,
and you will talk to a man with orange hair
at the wicked cool news booth.
He'll tell you about an amazing opportunity.
He says he hired spies to help him get info
on the next math movie.
Yeah, yeah, I talked to that guy.
That would be the first site to poke
what Omega looks like for the preview
of the next math movie.
Okay, so what this is,
is that you're supposed to be dressing up
as Thanos before anyone knows who Thanos is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that's how you win the costume contest,
is by dressing up as a character
that nobody's ever seen before.
Yeah, but be so impressed that you know
they'll just have to give it to you.
Okay.
So, um...
I'm supposed to dress up as the green archer?
Mm-hmm.
Or elf archer?
Yeah.
Alright.
So, you go to the exit hall?
He says...
Okay.
There's a girl with a red leather jacket
who has a picture of Omega on.
Right over there.
Okay.
Find a girl with a red leather jacket
who I think is in this part, I think.
Maybe.
Not in here.
There's nobody in here.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
In the part with the Wicked New Cools guy.
Wicked New Cools?
Wicked New Cools.
Wicked New Cools brand cigarettes.
I got some Wicked New Cools on right now, dude.
They're so wicked.
Oh, my God.
And my brand is screaming,
Stop, stop.
What are you doing to me?
Okay.
We gotta stop after we fucking feed this episode.
Yeah, I don't want anymore.
Yeah.
We gotta finish what we started,
but we gotta stop some way.
Okay.
So what am I looking for?
A girl with a leather jacket
who's in the Wicked New Cools room place.
Okay.
Which I think is the exit hall.
I think it's...
Yeah.
These in-between rooms are awful.
Yeah, they are awful and they drag the game to a halt
and they suck and they make me cry.
No, I don't know where they are.
I don't know where it is.
Okay.
Costumized the Lego Man.
No, I can't customize the Lego Man.
He's not a real person.
I won't say that about him.
God damn it.
No characters.
He has no character.
He has no moral fiber.
Yeah.
He doesn't believe...
He's lacking in personality.
...in anything.
Okay.
Which I hear.
Wicked Cool News.
So find a girl with a red leather jacket.
Not the pizza girl.
Not Stan Ditko.
There's nobody like that here.
What the fuck?
Wait, wait, wait.
Was it the girl who walked into...
Yeah, it was the girl that walked into the...
The fucking...
I don't know.
The screening or whatever.
Costumized...
Okay, hold on.
Jesus Christ.
Costumized the gray-haired girl.
Get her hat.
Wait.
Oh yeah, right there.
But that's not...
But she doesn't have the same hat though.
It's not the same hat.
That's not what the walkthrough says though.
Okay, fine.
I'll do it.
I'm just saying that that's not the hat that the elf archer wears.
Okay.
That's fine.
So I guess I gotta find her torso bits.
Yeah.
Looks like she's gotten okay.
Alright.
Receive a free elf archer comic from the gray-haired man's booth.
I did that.
In the hallway, okay.
I did that already.
Now you should know what elf archer looks like.
Go into the hallway.
All the halls look exactly the same.
Follow her in each door she goes into.
Once you've finally caught here, ask her what Omega 1 looks like.
So this is you harassing the staff member.
I did that already.
Okay, alright.
Thank God.
Oh wait, wait, wait.
Look, in this one she does have that shitty hat on.
So okay.
Yeah.
That's weird.
Alright.
So I just need that gray-haired man.
Well, you know, they change the costumes for the movies to make it more mass.
Oh, there he is.
There he is.
He's got it.
Pinata man.
Okay.
I think that's it.
I think I have the free-
Did you call that person's phone already?
Uh, no.
Uh, call number.
Once you harass her.
No signal.
Once you harass her, you should have asked if you had any money.
Yeah.
Did that happen?
What did you say?
I said, she said call me if you've got a real offer.
Okay.
But there's no signal.
So yeah, you have to go outside of the conference room.
Okay, go up the platform.
So the tech lounge and call her.
The tech lounge.
I don't know where the hell the tech lounge is.
Tech lounge?
Is that the place with the big demo?
I think that might be the place with the big green float.
Why is that?
Why is that the tech lounge?
Why would there be tech?
I don't...
I don't know.
Okay, the guy in front of the screening hall said something about the tech lounge.
Uh, it's not in the theater.
No.
Try the hallway.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, right?
Oh, here, tech lounge.
Okay.
Call.
Call number.
Hey, someone's network is getting amazing service here.
What?
Okay.
Got it.
I'll just text myself this photo.
Yeah.
Sick.
Wait, this is way too high IQ for me.
What is happening right now?
I just texted myself the photo of Omicron's cape from her phone.
Because she had a picture of it.
Okay.
That's what happened.
All right.
Okay, so now what do we do with all this elf archer nonsense?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, enter the demo area.
You'll see a kid with a bow and some arrows.
Okay.
I guess I gotta customize them?
Yeah.
Okay.
This is the demo area.
No hallway.
The hallway.
Okay.
Yeah.
Demo area.
But I can't make a mistake saying these things.
We have to do one more Lego city ad.
Yeah.
It just gets worse and worse every time.
All right.
Here he is.
Yeah.
He's got the.
Okay.
I got bow and arrow.
There you go.
Bam.
Done.
Enter the exhibit hall and you will see two people arguing over a lost elf archer statue.
When they're finished, click on the empty statue frame and do a pose.
Okay.
I can see a bit of a holly fuck.
I'm going to, I'm going to perish.
This game has perished me.
It's a, this, this game is a piece of poopy diarrhea.
Here we go.
There's got to be a way inside.
I think stand on the red thing.
Stand on the red thing.
Maybe the elf archer could get in.
Yeah.
With my balloon.
Oh, it's going to clip.
It's going to clip.
Oh, no.
It just flipped right through the wall.
Oh, wow.
They're staying very still.
I see that they, they whitewashed the character.
Yeah.
Again.
Thanks Hollywood.
I'm used to it by now.
I'm so sneaky.
Time to snoop for Omeghan's mask.
Oh, we got a ninja.
Wow.
I love superheroes.
We got some masks up there.
Oh, there it is.
There it is.
Oh, imagine this person is such a, the player picture is such a fucking freak in this game.
Yeah.
That's true.
You just have to find out 30 seconds for anyone else.
You're going to these great, any legal lengths.
Wow.
I really like the direction they went with the mask.
That's some fine work right there.
Yeah.
All right.
I got all the pieces.
I've got all the pieces of Omeghan.
Now I can win the, now I can win the day.
All right.
Go.
Okay.
Go to the Wicked Cool News Guy and get the pictures.
You will literally whip up the suit.
Okay.
I fucking, I've done the deed.
I committed, I committed corporate, corporate sabotage.
Now, now, now go to the theater.
Oh, did you like the animation?
I don't know why they didn't just have him walk.
He had to fucking turn a tornado for a second.
Wait, fuck.
Here we go.
Oh my God.
Here it is.
We've done it.
Hey, this is the spoils of our labors.
This is it.
We finally, we've, we've, I can't take my hat off.
I cannot take.
Oh wait.
There it is.
Did you do it?
Yes.
What did it cost?
Everything.
Oh, great.
Now I'm dressed up as this character that nobody's seen.
Go win the cosplay contest.
Yep.
They're like, wow.
A character, a character we've never seen before.
That's exactly what we want.
That's exactly what the people want in the cosplay contest.
I hope I still have the balloon.
Oh, did you hear the laugh track?
No.
Is that a thing that's happening right now?
Yeah.
People, people are laughing and booing and mocking these people.
Put the life line.
Oh my God.
Lol.
Is it the real superhero?
The real him.
Oh my God.
He showed up to win the costume contest.
What?
Is that, what?
Oh my God, they're dead.
Easy.
Dude, there's more.
There's so much more.
There's one last episode.
We've got to do it.
I mean, we've got to find out.
No, no.
No, we've got to find out.
How does this resolve itself?
Oh my God.
Okay, fine.
Look, Omicron has taken over the pop-tropicon.
I've got to save humankind from him.
The first place he lands, he assumes, is like the citadel of all Earth.
Only you.
Only you who are dressed like him can defeat him.
Only you who has hashtag stolen his look.
He has to eject his swagger.
I bet I have to summon the real green archer to defeat him.
And with the power of you have cosplaying hurt.
That insane power.
If we gather the mighty action force weapons, sure.
There are three elf archers bow, gold faces, what?
Electron pulse and world guy's shield.
I read that as worst guy.
Talk to the ninja person.
I need to get the chance.
We'll give you a comic page that should help.
This is just like the reign of Omeghan Arc.
Well, this is just like my comic book.
The entire city is enslaved.
And I'm subjugated.
Yeah, my favorite comic books became a real.
Golly.
And Alphaion.
Look at these character signs.
They're fucking stellar.
Gold face.
Same as gold face and he's gold.
I love the it's a bugs life character.
Yeah, yeah, he has a bugs life.
He's really living his best bugs life.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm going to take another look at that.
Collect the energy drink on the table.
Far left.
Get your nice monster zero carbs.
Oh, thank you.
Zero.
Is it this role of toilet paper?
Is this role of toilet paper, the energy drink?
Might as well be.
Taste the same.
I can't even remember life before Omeghan.
Like, yesterday.
Playing the mighty action force card game is the only joy I have left.
Good.
All we have left from the convention are mighty action force starter packs.
I want one.
Yeah, of course I do.
You fool.
All we have to pass the time.
Wait for inevitable death is just the Avengers.
God damn it.
I know how to play.
Stop.
No, you have to leave.
I can't.
I have to.
The only way to, the only way to win is not to play.
Wait, actually.
No, I can just quit.
It doesn't matter.
Thank God.
All right.
So I got the energy drink.
Let's not, let's not dilly dally.
Let's, let's, let's, it's time to end this.
What a big exhibit hall.
What in God's name?
Oh, I got shocked by a laser.
They pay that guy 10K per diem.
That's a lot of, that's a lot of moolah.
How do you, what, what?
Wait, so exit, I guess.
It's something that you can do.
Just go there.
Okay.
I assume.
All right.
Oh, I was like, yeah, I'm glad to see that Omega is not destroyed the Lego city.
Yes.
No, of course not.
He's left those intact.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go.
I got the expo.
I can go through the vents.
I can crawl through the vents back to the expo.
There.
Even in the vents.
Oh, my God.
Love's expo city.
I mean, Lego city.
Oh, no, not Pinata, man.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
He's dead now.
Dumpster.
What is the point of that?
I thought they were like making new minions.
But no, they're just turning them into cruel cosplays.
Hypersocket wrench and competent henchman.
Uh-oh.
Should I really be walking around here dressed as the, as the almighty Omega?
Yeah, people will be like, oh, it's, it's you.
It's, it's, it's the boss.
Yeah.
What big furry paws you have.
I wouldn't touch that without hand protection.
Oh, there are pop tropical books.
Where?
Uh, on the website.
Wait.
Yeah.
I know.
I remember I was, I was looking, I thought for 45 cents we could buy the cryptids book.
Yeah.
Okay.
Ben.
Yeah.
On the website.
A pop tropical.
They have a picture of Jeff Kinney.
Pop tropical creator and author of the best son, Daryl Wimpkin series.
Jeff Kinney.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Made pop tropical.
Wait.
Yeah.
Pop tropical is by the diary of a wimpy kid guy.
Yes, it is.
Which came first.
I have to assume diary wimpy kid.
Uh, why?
Just because one's a video.
Well, I've never heard of pop tropical before, but I've heard of diary of a wimpy kid.
Well, okay.
It's just because you're old.
You don't, you don't, you don't get it.
You don't get it.
Sure.
Yeah.
That's true.
Um.
You don't know what, what, what fucking video games are about.
I don't.
Um.
I mean, how, how recent is this?
Okay.
Hold on.
How recent, how old is pop tropical?
Okay.
I want to figure it out.
This is the most pointless laser trap of all time.
Daryl Wimpy kid came out in fucking 2007.
Yeah.
And pop tropical came out in 2007.
Weird.
What?
Imagine if like the, like the two series that you're going to base the rest of your
entire life on both of them at the exact same year.
How, how is he so prolific?
In 2011.
Pop tropical and diary of a wimpy kid.
In 2011, pop tropical was listed on China's magazines list of 50 websites that made the
web great.
No.
It's up there with Facebook, with Tumblr, with Twitter, with Wikipedia.
For God's sake.
I don't want to fight.
Okay.
Hold on.
Let me get the website.
I want to see what, like what's listed that too.
All right.
Full list.
What do I do?
No.
Stop.
What do I do?
I'm stuck.
No.
I don't care.
You have to figure it out yourself.
No.
Okay.
Hold on.
We're avoiding the lasers.
Wait.
What?
Well, I can go to the expo and then nothing else is labeled.
We'll just figure it out.
Okay.
Well, maybe this is the exhibit hall.
Whatever.
Now what?
Doesn't look like it.
Well, neither does anything else.
Once you're in the hall, you'll see a person dressed up as the elf archer from math.
What?
God.
No.
Not true.
Well, you're not in the right place then.
Fine.
All right.
The times list of 50 websites that made the web great.
You got eight tracks.
Never heard of it.
HBO go.
How cast my damn channel.
I've never heard of any of these things before.
Well.
Cafe mom, dear photograph.
What the fuck?
None of these are any.
None of these even exist.
I think this is made up.
Police.
Bleacher report.
Grant land.
Jaysky.
Silly season site.
What?
Network.
No.
Espionation.
All right.
I actually do know espionation.
That's the first one.
All right.
Big thank.
Get human.
Instapaper.
Science daily.
Tech meme.
No.
Financial and productivity.
Duck duck go.
Evernote.
Join.me.
Kickstarter.
Learn.
Invest.
The shopping traveler at a Airbnb.
Go.
Bot.
Hip.
Monk.
Polyvore.
Retrovo.
Health and fitness.
Calorie King.
Health grades.
Map.
My run.
Summer tomato.
Zen habits.
Social media.
Google plus.
Clout.
Pinterest.
Korra.
Storify.
Games.
The escapist.
Airport.
All right.
Online.
Retrocade.
Education.
Free rice.
Conak.
Open.
Smart.
History.
Starfall.
That's it.
I knew 10 of those.
Those aren't even real.
That was on time.
You like.
Things have changed.
I don't know.
What I guess we value in the Internet.
I guess we thought the Internet was going to do one thing and it just.
did the exact opposite pop tropica really who would ever look at this and say
that this makes anything great I can't fucking believe this shit that's so
infuriating that's live that's really infuriating Jesus Christ
look at this
what the fuck
why can't I pick up the goddamn shield
kids explore pop tropica each month 10 million kids but the site also aims to
please parents the chat feature for instance doesn't permit free form
conversation instead members can select questions ask you another from a
collection of family-friendly choices
10 million's kids use this no okay
oh temporary ad games in addition to available island quests advertised as
contract for temporary games to appear on their website
sure sure of course of course they do
hey it's loading but why
ow
um
god damn it
okay here we go here we go
okay didn't do anything
uh
alright so I've got to shoot a laser okay I see I see I see it
I see what I must do
why is it so hard it is so fucking hard to move in this fucking game Jesus Christ
I think he just gotta get good why not just fucking use WASD
because kids don't know that they know arrows so use the arrows that's fine
these are fucking mouths click around too hard
damn it god damn it why are you discovering against people who only have one
hand it can only use the mouse
and that's not for them
well it can be if you would just give them a fucking chance and that's not for
them internet is for the able what are you doing get out the way the laser you
fucking idiot I have to deflect the laser into the thing
oh my god how do you do it there there I did it okay thank god
holy shit
meet me in HQ okay thanks
I'm gonna throw up I'm gonna throw up all the food that I haven't eaten today
hold on expansions island creator kit in August 2013 an island creator kit was
made available for purchase on Amazon.com is an activity book a book that walks
players through all the same steps the developers take when they make new island
coming with the storyline creating characters design puzzles so this means
you can make a pop-tropical island are you oh no it's just make pretend
oh fuck okay is this HQ who are we're back in HQ yeah
here we go I got it I do it did you dress up as the elf archer person why would I do
that well okay customize that person to oh oh I know it doesn't matter go all the
way right avoid lasers should a shield on a rock okay okay okay okay if you did all
that a single play out not a man will get turned in okay okay so go back there
okay so go back there you just shoot something I can't seem to get rid of
this map there we go it doesn't matter don't worry you don't have to do that you
guys it's not I'm like covered in I guess it's dirt I guess I'm covered in dirt
sick come on make me green make me fucking green okay whatever fine garbage
okay what do we do help go to the place where you saw those people get turned into
minions okay let me just put my weapon the ultimate weapon here for power I love
power I have the will to power you shoot things with your with your bow and arrow
good blue wow
I'm going I'm going to flip my shit I'll kill him oh it went right through him
there Jeff Kenny owns a bookstore in Plainsfield Massachusetts why don't we make a
pilgrimage will we meet him we get to meet him I think we'll meet him then
we'll ask him hey can we can we speak to you outside please and then and then we'll
we'll show him this video to get to save for himself I don't think there's
anything to say at this point I think it's too late
they're still making dire one begins oh how could they not oh no oh no give a red
one yeah of course I read one through four weird oh why why is that weird why
would you say that why would you ever I don't get it I guess I'm too old
I guess I'm too old I don't get it no no I don't I I don't mean like recently I
remember when I when I was nine years old yeah well I guess hold on I guess I
would have been I mean in my 20s when they when diary of the wimpy kid of a
wimpy how does that make you feel that I was nine makes me feel like everyone
else is wrong to be the age that they are do I do I have to shoot that green
thing yeah okay whatever I guess there's no rules anymore it's it's dog it's a
doggie dog world it is a doggie dog world is all green thing yeah kind of
looks like that other thing sure come on this is a nightmare why can I not
fucking move this is a nightmare this is hell this is this is this is what this
is what I fear this is what goes bump in the night great now I know why God
struck down Sodom and Gomorrah and why he turned my wife into a pillar of salt do
you think that do you think that God doesn't talk do you think this is why
God doesn't talk to us anymore I think I think he lives in fear what he's
created yeah yeah yeah this is why this is why Tom Kenny creator of pop
topica and and diary of a wimpy kid doesn't talk to us anymore wasn't him
Jeff Kenny yeah Jeff Kenny Jeff Kenny good Jesus oh there it is there's that
little pizza shit nice sexy pizza over here don't say that yeah nice sexy pizza
for my juvenile cat no you're on you did a run shut up no look look fuck God this
mouse control is the worst thing ever it's the worst thing ever to let you
suffer it's like why don't we make a game that almost works and then ruin it
why don't we just do that I don't even know if it almost works it comes close
to sometimes where's the last thing I well I guess I've got a I've got to get
rid of this laser oh push the box in front of it I guess you gotta go to get
the banner ad lose progress no it won't go over the thing well okay clearly I've
got to I've got to divert something I've got to divert something into this
battery here I've got to destroy this battery oh by some means devious or
otherwise go downstairs hold on okay I guess meet Dan Darko lesser known
brother of Donnie Darko hmm oh Jesus wait here it is here it is I know what
to do I know exactly what to do I got to get my shield up silver age shield
Captain America here we go yeah wrecked easy outline game what I even need the
walkthrough we're blazing through this this one yeah I poptropica is no match
for me don't you can feel better about the divorce settlement this cage was hard
to escape than my modeling contract hungry for words no hungry for words hungry
for worms no hungry for words shut up I don't get it do you get it I don't get
it no I don't okay good electron pulse gaunce as they shoot sparks rechargeable
equip the power yes oh totally equipped totally the tiger oh these are a nice
prop but they don't pulse like in the car what about Tony the tiger you quit him I
can't go back to the expo room and recharge the gauntlets with the broken
down cord from the defunct hinch bot reading the guy using the gauntlets on
the blue triangle on the left will give you his energy drink I've already gotten an
energy drink I guess I need to yeah now I have the true power gold face what wow
did you see that pulse yeah they really brought out the calvary that's the
moat that's I'm stunned I'm stunned that that's what they thought that they
went with that they thought that was acceptable what do you mean that's the
way a pulse works my advocate mirror used to work cartoon your renditions of
the pulses okay so what do I do now hit hit the blue triangle yeah okay there we
go wow this is so bad why why did you say that is the visual presentation of
these pulses is so underwhelming I think the visual the visual representation of
you is astounded okay so I think that I definitely have to use the the energy
drinks is like batteries right I guess so you also okay go to the exhibit hall
and go to the left until you see a vending machine
that's the exhibit hall right I think so pretty sure
um do you know what scp is the scp foundation yeah yeah you know the one
that's when you turn your back he'll come towards you know snap your neck yeah
the one in like the dirty room yeah I think that's what the Lego guys like yeah
if you you have to keep looking at him yeah oh okay hold on I think I can I can
do this but it's just went past the thing for a second there yeah okay I'm
polished this thing this thing needs energy I'm just the guy to give it to
him I'm just the guy to give it to him here we go what click click on it it
hasn't it says it has no power okay okay maybe if I pulse maybe if I don't
okay try that but also go to the left because there's a vending machine we
have to get energy drink from oh I think you need three okay um did you see that
yeah well yeah did you fucking see me glitz through this yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah good down okay vending machine you have to go to the exhibit hall is this
the exhibit hall yes I don't think it was I think it would in fact was not that
okay well no yeah see exhibit hall okay it says that I might have already given
hall and go to the left please see the vending machine power it and you'll get
oh no no you have to power it how do you power it go to the left until I see no
no no okay go the vending machine go the vending what where they have to turn
on they have to turn the thing where you fuck go to the right no go back in go
back in they were just at go to the right what the thing that you were going
to power was the vending machine okay but that's what I did I tried pulsing on
and it didn't work you know we just have to try everything until it works well
all right is there like a is there one of those blue triangles around
I don't see one oh okay sure now what I got three return to the basement and
exit to the theater power the platform to the left and shoot arrows right as you
pass the green battery
okay green battery go to the theater oh Expo theater here we go here we go
all right we're making we're making great time oh we're we're making great
progress here we are we are we're killing it we're crushing it okay power it
got a power it oh yeah yeah yeah I chewed air I think got him got him fuck you
bitch okay easy easy easy except that you can't fucking move in this game god
damn it god damn it I don't know why you're hopping I can't fucking not hop
when I just click to move it makes me jump you're such a grumpy mood lately
then I wonder why me certainly not certainly nothing to do with pop
tropical it couldn't it couldn't raise nothing but joy and harmony to this
world hey did I did my shield get destroyed what the fuck yeah I think so
all right well ain't that fun why did you get off I don't know it's powered again
yeah oh my god making me fucking jump hey you know okay put on your power
gloves yeah I know okay okay well he's right doing it fucking mmm how am I
supposed to know if you know how to do it if you aren't doing it okay get out no
no I can't I can't move it won't let me move okay great yeah now why don't they
just stay powered because it wouldn't be it would be too easy that way too easy
yeah it'd be too simple there'd be no skill involved I'm going back to
Broadway yep get out all right now wait look there's no shield I have no
shield what the fuck look for the actual icon used to be in a hope that's there
just it's glitched it's just gone okay well it doesn't even matter don't even
worry I mean this looks like I should be able to destroy it yeah it's like
something that I should destroy it sure does Ben but you know what sometimes we
just take it on the chance yeah look right yeah I don't know what the fuck
to do if you'll respawn okay nope hold on let me let me figure this out I mean
I've collected all the three champions okay it's it's supposed to it's supposed
to break okay stardom isn't all fast cars oh here take my shield makes a good
marriage a gear with yeah whatever cool okay so that was the silver age shield
mighty action force weapons here right here my lord oh no I was tricked and
betrayed
for months how long we've been here I guess we were in a coma for months that's
fun was it worth it to go on this quest to get the fucking trailer ready yeah
see even if only I haven't wanted to see that fucking trailer so bad maybe the
world won't be in the brink of the abyss look what I brought
this floor is too potent this fully charged crystal taught me the crystal
looks unstable no boom okay then we gotta shoot a crystal with an arrow
this is the point I gotta shoot a crystal with an arrow
omacron's omagon's throne room okay
what
oh oh oh oh you got to yeah yeah you got the shield again so yeah yeah oh wait no I
guess I gotta I gotta go bring anything over there I think you're ready to fight
the boss now wow I think we might be done how exciting yeah I'm actually
excited on my chair please please let it end please let it end God I'm a praying
man but if I was I wouldn't be against you I wouldn't yeah all right I made it I
did it whoa hey look we shall discard their withered husks on the something of
no some random kid in a hot dog suit all right I guess I gotta shoot them not
good yeah shoot there shoot that shoot down there it's gonna shoot them oh we
have oh there's a crystal there's a little hole in the crystal yeah yeah um okay
that's fine I guess you have to unclog the way yeah I have to do something okay go
to the left we go to the down path oh well that's easy
god damn
god damn it
okay well I don't even know what the purpose of these energy drinks is yeah
I can probably just shoot it now but whatever
oh I gotta overload it I gotta overload it with the super energy oh well it's
really convenient that you just thought that just now yeah yeah look at that it's
really convenient that these alien batteries literally are energy drinks
there's no difference between them well I mean branding and everything you can
empathize with his fight for monster zero energy can't you okay the crystal is
ready we must defeat the enemies all right here we go today is a good day do
what has to be done by me to help my brother to defeat the enemies don't worry
about it do I need to be done by me okay here we go I am ready alright take
the shot take the fucking shot can I yeah yeah we saved the comic on I think
you have to fight him oh no no it looks like he's blown to smithereens hey those
were people those were human beings transformed into those robots that have
got the switch sides I will show you real power oh I don't want to see that I'd rather
see fake power if you if you please if you would be so kind oh god some guests you are
showing me real power whoa whoa now look at the artistry on display here it's there's a bunch of
circles this looks totally well what what what is happening right now oh my god fuck this is
easily the coolest thing I've ever seen so abstract oh my god I am become I am
become Alfion destroy of worlds oh my god I'm invested right look how look how non-plust I
look oh my god for Mega Man yeah it is oh I got shot I got shot by his laser but it was okay
oh the boss fights a puzzle yeah okay I know what to do I know what to do come on oh fucking this
come on fucking use the fucking shield I was hitting space hmm there we go I did it
oh it's fine sorry turn around and don't jump you fuck god damn it Jesus fucking Christ you
know what they say a true master never blames the poor master the blames his tools I can't turn
around yeah okay yeah okay just by well just by sheer coincidence I landed in the right spot
that's good all right all right it's easy okay you gotta turn them on yeah I'm sure there's
something you guys shoot up here yeah yeah it's easy come on I've never seen something so easy in fact
well it will go down again oh no don't shoot me he shot me oh I gotta do it all again well that's
fine no okay no can I get both yes okay sorry you only gotta do one more time okay it's nice
to shoot you know it shot me from behind but okay all right sick that worked out damn it
here we go we're ready time to end this one's in for all hmm okay he's his eyes glowing he's
petrified I think I gotta shoot them with your laser yeah I think I gotta deflect the laser into
maybe you got to have fire and in your laser yes it fucks oh my god this is just an awful look in
his eyes the look of a true child predator ever I've seen he loves it he loves this I can relate
yeah you did it you saved the San Diego Convention Center I say I saved the I saved the
San Diego Tri-County area yeah wow thank fucking God now we can watch the trailer in
peace yeah yeah exactly like that now now comic con can go on on harm yeah months later we can
continue the convention at last look at my tumblr hair right now look at it
cop killer you've done so much for us you've saved the world you ended that tyrant's wrath what
can we do we'll give you money we'll give you women we'll give you fame I I asked for nothing I can
get by all I need is to see that one Avengers I just want to see I just want to see this
kegan phantom pony movie that's all I want I just want you to finish that rip max revive
t-bap um all right are we done do we beat you do not do not get to see the trailer hold on what
the fuck why well we just we do you want to see munchie we just lived the trailer wait what we
just lived the trailer munchie we don't need we don't need a silly movie anymore I just
experienced the magic I thought that there was the the canonical reason was that that entire
setup that was that you were filming the trailer no it's probably actually it though no the real
trailer was the friends we made along the way zero space is the is the gist of it okay hold on
hold on this is important I'm disenfranchised right now there we go there we go oh you're
looking a lot like been saying every every every second yeah yeah go and get naked yeah
get naked dog come on I want to I want to wear black let me let me wear black please god damn it
no it's impossible you look you look just like him yeah there is the man the man himself
hold on hold on boy we just like defeated we just defeated like this this world oh my god
look at that oh my god look at that no we just we just defeated the the king of all evil fans
yeah but you know I want to change my costume around a little bit first can I why do I have
lipstick I don't know why do I have lipstick now when did that happen you know you must have
traded mouth with someone at some point which sounds like a euphemism but it's not no all right
well I did it I was saved comic on I saved it this is like this is like a like you're playing
Kingdom Hearts right and you go to all these different themed world and you go to a world
that is just comic on world and it's just like in this world you know it's like Halloween town
every day is Halloween but it's like every day is comic on every day that's my dream every day
we celebrate every day we celebrate we celebrate popular media you celebrate popular media that
used to be niche but isn't anymore uh uh jack skeleton realizes the value of let's play as you
try to what now have we beat it yeah it's over it's over play on this war in this war season
there's a lot of new features play in this war by our shirts if you were intimidated if you were
intimidated by season one you should be even more intimidated now because there's absolutely no way
you'll be able to catch up but you know what unless you're a pussy coward you you know you've
always got to try you may not know all the steps you you have to learn how to play the dude you
know what I have to add fishing gotta add fishing isn't like the slime ocean yeah yeah and in crack
bay yeah yeah that's gonna be super easy it's gonna be easiest thing in the world it'll be the
simple it'll be actually wait we need some items first we'll get some items then I'll add fishing
bada bing bada boom yeah too easy steps to world domination here what we'll do is we'll we'll
make it'll be like the like the canary in the mines idea that I have it'll be like a fish for
down the fucking cosmetics you put a fish on your shoulder yeah yeah you'll be you gotta catch the
biggest fish you gotta catch the biggest fish you ever get the biggest fish get the big
fish we gotta have quests dude yes we talked to NPCs in crack bay and I'll say I need a big fish
and then I'll give you 125 slime point 125 absolutely dude yes absolutely we need we can we can put
NPCs why not yeah we can put it NPCs we'll do it we'll fucking do it all right this is what I'm
gonna do spend the rest of my life doing this is what I'm gonna spend the rest of the day doing
I have now that pop tropica is dead and lies buried six feet under god what a disaster I hate I
hate you Jeff Kenny oh what a nightmare I feel that we spent the last two rfck episodes talking
exclusively about the game and having no conversation um that's what people want right
yeah people want discussion of topical video games like pop tropica yeah yeah they want you
know uh mighty action force pop tropica they want all that energy that Ben can you please play the
lego mammoth city game again one more time for one more time for all time sake I think I I think
I can make that happen I think I can make that oh wait no I can't oh my god wait they've barred us
this is a fucking travesty what do I what do I do you're fucked dude we're fucked we can't do it
how do I leave how do I leave you're stuck here forever there's no balloon either so how do you
oh okay it's like that okay all right well I guess I guess that's pop tropica I guess that's
pop tropica um god see you in hell Jeff what a disaster what uh yeah um
let's talk about let's talk about let's talk about rfck next time yeah let's talk about rfck
let's talk about let's talk about let's talk about the wiki do you know there's a wiki have we
mentioned there's a wiki there's a wiki there's a burrow too oh yeah we've talked about vying for
we're talking about vying for first place first place in terms of uploads yeah it's tough it's a tough
job there's over a thousand images on there um closing in closing in on 1100 stay tuned and
god knows what will happen to you all right all right shall shall we end it shall we put in um
fucking play a pop if we get 300 likes we'll do pop tropica episode two no no no
if we get if we get 30 shirt sales then then we'll do pop tropica um but what about what about
maple story oh we oh we gotta do all those we gotta do oh i am i am seriously considering
i'm seriously considering a 24 hour maple story stream on my twitch channel yeah definitely
i think i might do it just um teespring.com slash store slash inlis dash war yeah they're
there lill um goodbye buy a shirt so long bye