Routing, fuckers, cop, killers, inn, Kurgostarworth, the complete saga.
Do you guys want to move so Kazzy's like in frame?
No, I gotta be in frame still.
Can we make Kazzy a frame, please?
A frame, what?
Can we make Kazzy a frame?
Yeah, sure, you know what? Kazzy's the new a frame.
Congratulations, other new a frame.
I wish my beard were darker.
I'm not sorry.
It blends in and it makes it like a Hitler stash because this part is not thin enough.
Did anything happen? Did you get a haircut or something? Did you change something about the way that you look?
Are you Roman?
You can sort of look like a god.
You look like you're about to star in a pornography film.
Painous.
I didn't even know.
I thought when you pressed your core we were going to have a little bit more time, I don't know, fuck around.
Whatever, start going.
The game's open, right? The game's open, click that fucking game.
It's not open, actually.
Click open, click open.
It's on the other screen, and here we go.
Hey, give me this shit.
It's mine, it's mine.
Oh.
People have been fucking clamoring for this game ever since we unveiled it at the last rfckcon.
People have just been like, where's the LEGO Star Wars episode?
Where's LEGO Star Wars complete saga for the Wii or the 360?
Or where's my pee?
It's gone all ways.
It's all over the dang place. It's all over my fucking bathroom.
Oh, yeah.
Pee on a keto strip like a normal person.
I pissed all over Ben's room and it was an accident, and then I thought, wow.
I should do this on purpose next time.
Next time?
Yes.
So we're finally delivering it to the people.
This is the best game ever made.
Ben, I know that we've had our differences.
You had a track record of loving shit.
Ben, we've had our differences before.
We've come to different conclusions about classic video games.
For instance, for some reason, maybe you were in a cranky mood that day,
but you just didn't like losing.
You didn't like XT Gale of Darkness for some reason.
You woke up on a bad note that day.
All 175 days that we recorded it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was just bad luck.
I think we're going to bring this one around.
Because listen, you could take Super Smash Brothers Brawl,
you could take Pop Tropica,
you could take Pokemon XT Gale of Darkness,
and you could roll them all into one, into one contiguous ball,
drop it into a pot, boil it into like a nice broth,
and then add noodles to it.
Reduce it down into a syrup, maybe?
Reduce it down into a syrup, drain it into your fucking eyeballs,
or through your nose, and you wouldn't get half the hype.
You wouldn't get half the hype that you get when you play this fucking game.
Lego Star Wars Complete Psycho.
Or as I like to call it, cool wokely lead,
here in the hood, we call it, curgo stirrer work.
Okay, introduce your game.
Uh, you know.
I'm the ratty fucker, and this is the cop killer.
Woo!
Alright, alright, now we can see.
We have the juvie kingpin, Tommy Oliver.
Yeah, that's me.
And the other juvie kingpin.
It's me, Tom Oliver.
We have a loud juice.
We've allowed juice to enter the sanctum.
And to the juice.
Much to our great chagrin.
You know, cop killer sounds really gone downhill, you know?
Boy, boy howdy.
Uh,
Where's up here in Ascertain Heights?
We're just fucking trying to have a good time,
and these juves are coming around,
asking for directions to the fucking Arson Brook farm,
like, oh.
Hey, where's the farm, guys?
Hey, where's the mill?
I've been looking forward to getting some daughter apples.
I just can't wait to saturate my slimeoid.
Oh, yeah, fuck off.
No salt on my razor nuts, please.
Jesus Christ.
See, Ben, look at this.
It's Legos, and it's Star Wars.
How big can you get? How big can you get?
How well can you grow?
It's pretty big.
You're growing so fast right now, Ben.
It's pretty big. Do you want to, like,
do you want to leave the door open?
Why?
I'd probably be really loud that way.
Yeah? I think the louder we are, the better.
Yeah, you don't have to do anything serious.
We respect people's boundaries.
Hey, oh my god, it's the sun god, Apollo.
He's canonical.
He's talking about his cop killers now.
Are you recording?
Oh, yeah, dude.
Let me ask you a question.
Who out here?
We ain't fucking playing.
What is Star Wars the complete saga, dude?
The best game ever made.
Listen, listen, man.
Everyone's going to make fun of Legos.
Star Wars the complete saga coming here.
So, oh, what's this baby game?
Literally for 12-year-olds.
Literally for 8-year-olds.
Literally for 10-year-olds.
For the whole family, and for baby.
Listen, all I'm trying to say is that fun family fun
doesn't mean they have to be not fun.
So we're going to get in here with Qui-Gonjin and Obi-Wan Kenobi,
the two best characters ever made in fiction.
And we're going to hup the fuck around.
Fuck you, Ben.
Slime Fest 5.
Slime Fest 5. Over.
Delete his slime.
You just got shot. How do I kill you?
No, you can't do it, dude. Don't worry.
Don't worry, dude. You can't do it.
Slime Fest 6. Slime Fest 6.
Slime Fest 6.
This is why Legos Star Wars is the best.
Star Wars sucks. Star Wars is awful.
If you like Star Wars, you're stupid.
But you should probably kill yourself.
Yes! Slime Fest 6 is over. Take a slime.
But Legos are sick.
And that makes it okay.
Legos are so zoom-er-core, they're customizable.
They're all about conversation.
They're all about the internet integration.
Dude, you go and you open up fuck...
Okay, literally give me a hashtag
fucking like hard-resonant chat if you know what I'm talking about right now.
You go your mom's work because it's signature child of the work day.
Then you boot up one of the powerful ass computers there at her work.
Fucking Lego 3D builder,
that application that you can get from the Lego site.
And you start making 3D Lego models inside of your computer.
And you're like, what the fuck?
Are you as powerful as the Lego site? What the hell?
Are we supposed to kill all those people?
No, this isn't even level.
This is the hub world, my friend.
Dude, we're going to defend this.
Okay, name one...
Name a better movie than the Phantom Menace.
Like right now, like I'm begging you.
Indiana Jones, The Crystal Skull.
How about The Last Jedi?
Oh, you know what? You're right.
You didn't think they could improve perfection, but somehow they found a way.
Alright, we're gonna get right into this.
Okay, alright. This cutscene
is like the most iconic thing.
You know, Rosebud.
That's baby shit. That's some fucking
chocolate toy fucking...
for a baby's first story.
Baby's first narrative.
The baby's first story?
Here's for some real actual plot.
Here's the plot. Here's the plot of Gilgamesh.
Two.
This is Gilgamesh two right here.
All the chicks, dude.
Yeah, get ready for this.
Anki-Doo. Anki-Doo.
That's my favorite.
Oh, this is Gilgamesh right here. He's so big and chunky.
Oh, he's chunky already.
Dude, Ben, do you remember when we went
to the Trade Federation and they tried to kill us?
I remember that
there was a lot of slime
coin on the line.
And they were
showing for it.
Their eyes? Oh, they're gone.
Oh, they're gone. But you think it's sad? No, it's actually funny and a joke.
Look, oh, they fall down.
They break the pieces like a Lego.
No, we're scared. Now we're on fault.
That's too sad. I can't.
Ben, I'm not to introduce you to something.
What are the friendly characters and why?
You're a friendly character.
We have to do it at the same time.
All right, Ben, I'm not to introduce you into...
We'll assume we're the band of your existence.
Why can't I joke?
These miscolored
slime coin right here, these physical copies,
like these like millennium, like challenge coin
slime coins. These are called studs.
Is that bar that fills up?
Yeah. There's a state.
There's a game state called true Jedi.
When you get enough studs, then you get true Jedi.
That's part of getting 100%.
We're getting true Jedi every single level, Ben.
So that means that we're going to be
scouring each level for
literal hours trying to find
every studs available. We're not going to have to solve riddles.
We're going to have to solve the Spinks' riddles 3
in order to get the studs. What are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
They're dancing and we get studs for it.
We get money. We get fucking cold, hard catch.
Listen, I...
When I was a kid, I was a communist.
And then I played this game and I thought, wow, what a fucking dumb ass I was.
Time to get fucking rich
and banked in new communism.
A.K.A. Kirgo Sturrward.
The complete surger.
Okay, so is this the game just like running around
and using the force on things to make studs pop out of them?
Yeah, but we also... Yes, yes.
All right, well, we're winning.
I think we're winning, Munchy. I think we're doing it.
So I want to let you understand,
just so you know, it means you have no frame of reference.
It's a normal game, like, you know, like the game
that you play, like, to, like, win the game.
Uh-huh.
Like, it's almost like a beat-em-up almost.
You got an attack and you fight enemies,
you just progress through the level, there's puzzles and shit,
you know, it's like a normal, like, 3D platform or whatever.
But the meta game, the real game,
is getting as many studs as you...
A BLUE ONE! A BLUE ONE!
I'm crushing you in studs right now.
Yeah, that's fun.
I used to watch my brother play this game
and when he didn't get the blue stud, I'd be like,
I'm like, I'm fucking in $100.
Dude, okay, you know that feel
when you come across the purple stud
and you just literally have to change
your fucking pants.
Wait, there's a purple stud?
Wait, when? The legendary, the mythical.
Is that in a different one?
Okay, this game is teaching some crazy fucking moral
because only the Sith can get purple studs.
I don't remember the purple stud.
It's because they have, like, 10,000 each.
That's a purple stud.
Is that why I don't remember it? Yeah.
That's a lot of studs.
We're already halfway to true Jedi.
This game is literally free money.
You play this and you get paid.
It's free money, the game.
No, I love this shit because you just knock it.
Like, if you knock your sword...
MEDICATE!
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, we're gonna die.
Kill these guys.
Kill these so we can have
a quiet space for me to do
the most important thing I've ever done in my entire life.
Owls back there?
We gotta go back, we gotta go back
after I...
Guys, please, a moment of silence.
Come back over here, Ben.
A moment of silence for the best video game sound effect
of all time.
BUSH A WING!
That's a mini-kit.
10 in each level. Get them all 100%.
I used to play this game
literally, religiously, more than I went to church.
And you know what? I became more moral
because of it. I understand the concept of justice.
For all the times that I was robbed of my mini-kit,
I learned the value of courage and justice.
You have not explained what a mini-kit is.
A mini-kit with the concept of what I just got.
It is a tiny little, it's like a little box.
It's a little like, like, cylinder thing.
I mean, I saw what it looks like.
Well, then you get it. I'm okay.
Do I? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh my god!
I'm gonna cry right now.
Okay, okay, now you...
Ben, do you want the honors? Do you want the honors, Ben?
I would love to. Thank you, my friend. Die.
Ha ha!
Alright, no, wait, no, we need that whore.
God damn it! You balled the door to his whore!
He was too... Oh, he's back, he's back.
Alright, don't worry. Okay, T9-
109-111-3000. Alright, we're gonna come over here
and we're gonna fuck some fucking whores.
Are you ready? Let's go to the whorehouse.
Go to the brothel.
He walks funny. I don't like the cut of his gym.
No, listen, okay.
You may have thought of yourself, wow, mindless.
Let's give a third eye on his body.
That's just the way he likes to roll, dude.
No, you...
I used the force on him and I turned him and...
Well, he's glowing, it's so tempting.
Well, wait, who's short-haired white man and who's...
I'm long-haired white man.
I'm Mr. Silver right now.
You're Mr. Silver?
Yeah, I am Mr. Silver.
Look at the top right, okay. Why would you do that?
I'll tell you right, Ben. You may have thought this game was brainless.
In fact, it is the epitome of puzzles.
It is literally more puzzles
than any other thing in existence.
Look at this, collectibles, studs.
You have to use your brain to unlock secrets.
Blue, blue, blue, blue, blue.
Blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue.
Capitalism.
This is literally like, better teaching you capitalism
than the society in which we live.
All right.
Ben's more studded.
Oh, it's gonna pick you up.
He's better than studded.
All right.
Oh, no, we have to work together,
but we have to work together, okay, okay.
Use the force, use the force.
I'm using it.
No, you aren't.
You aren't doing it correctly.
Oh, there we go.
Spit out the stuff.
No, no, no, don't worry, it's going to lift me up.
And now, don't push us!
True Jedi!
Oh my god!
What does it mean?
True Jedi!
That means we're true Jedi, true Jedi, pure of heart men,
pure of heart!
Do we have super powers now?
We can beat the level now.
Yeah.
Is that all it means?
Yeah, OK, OK.
All right, now check out this mini kit.
All right, you need to work together with me.
We need to put aside our differences.
Our mental and racial differences.
You know, I crossed the border begging for money
and you supplied like a dumbass.
Now it's time to mend all of our wounds.
Put down the hatchet.
We're going to bury the hatchet in this droid's fucking skull.
Oh no, he shot me, dude.
He shot me, I'm down.
When you die, your studs all pop out
and you can lose true Jedi.
So we have to make sure we don't loot that shit happen.
Now let's fucking run through like men in black
or like the other men which aren't black.
Sorry if you're racist.
Are we over yet?
No, no, over here.
Can we beat the game?
No, no, we're sprinting.
We're sprinting.
Can we, can we be done?
Can we be done with it?
Dude, you fucked up, dude.
Okay.
We got a purple.
All right, this right here, this is only bounty hunters.
Oh, this is only to R2-D2.
We have to come here when we're doing free play.
Once we unlock R2-D2 and such R4,
we're going to have to go back here
and we're going to have to unlock here this zone
so we can get a mini-kit that's inside here.
We're probably at the red power brick.
Red power brick, there are three collectibles.
There are the studs where you use true Jedi or mini-kit.
So there are 10 of them in each levels.
There's also the red power bricks
and once there's one each level
and then they're locked here, the extras.
Dude, I got power up.
Dude, pick up power.
You got power up, you got purple.
Dude, you're killer, you're killer.
I'm Mace Windu.
I'm going to be like that.
I'm just putting you out of your room.
Tom, this game's so good, confirm.
There's Jar Jar.
Where is Jar Jar?
No, no, no, no.
There's Jar Jar.
Don't worry, best game.
Oh, look, fuck Jar Jar.
Don't worry.
Dude, don't worry.
Because she's the cause me daddy Tusa
and we're going to be able to meet with her real soon.
Fuck yeah, all right.
Now I'm invested.
All right, now we have to build.
Remember, Lego bricks, remember 9-Eleven.
We're coming right back real soon.
Oh my God, I'm floated.
Dude, literally.
Somehow you're ahead of me.
It makes me mad.
You're younger and richer than me.
And now this is me.
My two favorite things to be.
Ah!
Fuck him up.
Dude, don't worry, we fucked him right up.
Okay, look at this.
Whoa.
Oh, you fucked up.
You fucked it up for me.
You're gonna get those hybrids.
When does the game end?
There's no part of it.
There's no game here that isn't just collecting the studs.
The studs are the game.
Apparently.
So why?
They make a nice noise when you collect them.
I don't think I like being a true Jedi.
Now I have expectations I have to live up to.
No, don't worry.
You'll never be able to live up to the true Jedi.
Okay, put that thing, Ben.
We're gonna set some ground rules in this version,
but it's gonna work.
You're gonna need to assist me.
Why do my back flips?
Why do my parkour?
You're gonna need to assist me.
Or else I'm gonna fuck you up.
Or else I'm gonna beat you.
This is the basis of good relationship.
Don't want me to use the force or what.
Don't want to use the force or what.
Okay.
No, okay, didn't work.
It didn't work.
Nice job.
Nice job, asshole.
No, wait.
Okay, and you know what?
You're right.
Never mind.
Bye.
Dude.
Ah!
Oh, you got a power.
If you're a pig now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have to destroy the Jets.
Dude, the destroyers.
Oh, they roll.
Just like in the film.
Are you not putting a filter on the game?
No, why not?
No, they're just not filter on the game.
Are you disappointed?
Yeah.
Can I disappoint you?
I'm pretty disappointed in you.
No, listen.
Listen, this game is so good, you eat it twice.
This same game.
End of game.
This game's so good, you'll be nice.
Game over, please.
This game's so nice, you don't make fun of it in class.
You ever notice that Tom and Ben are like the same?
Yeah, they are.
Feeny, beard, other.
Yeah.
That's our character.
No life, no skill, no game, no life.
That's a good one.
Oh, look at this guy.
Can I beat him?
You can't beat the biome.
You can do whatever you want.
This is like a Star Wars.
That's a little bit of an imagination to the audience.
Why can't I build?
Why can't I build new friends?
You can.
You can build.
You haven't been as good as it.
You haven't been as good as me, so you
don't know how to build things.
Look, they have the confirmed child labor in Star Wars.
Why'd you break it?
Because I fucking hate you, babe.
Why'd you break the conveyor belt?
It was moving.
They were going to the over here.
Listen, we're rich enough.
We don't need anymore.
I've said no millionaire ever.
Mm-hmm.
Let's just use the force on these things.
Then we're going to get through.
That's what I'm doing.
That's exactly what I'm doing.
Jump through?
Oh my god.
Hold on.
Oh, it's definitely in a parkour.
He's not smart enough to do that.
Oh, this is one of those puzzles, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I've heard about these.
Bailey, this avenue is a secret former route.
How do you think, Amber?
So that's in my server?
Yeah, in your own server.
Don't you fucking touch my server.
That's my safe space, and you invaded it.
That's classic abuser tactics.
Classic.
Oh my god, this game is going to make me cry, dude.
OK, all right, the blue stuff.
OK, all right, Ben.
By making me play the LEGO Star Wars.
Ben, turn into the whore, and then make the whore button go.
Hey, I did it.
Oh yeah, in the lead.
Oh, blue stuff.
No, no, activate the button.
Activate the button.
What?
Oh, did I do it?
Did I do it or what?
Ben, Ben, I'm rich, climax.
Gross.
So you come, man.
Yeah, dude, look at this.
You need to come.
Oh.
Hey, anyone need to come?
Anyone need to come?
Yeah, yeah, can you pick me up sometime?
Yeah, there you go.
Hey, can you pick me up?
Come from the store, please.
Can you pick me up a Cummys?
Dude, free play unlocked.
We got one gold brick for that.
And guess what?
We got true Jedi, and the unlock of these characters.
We're going to get way more red bricks.
I don't understand, Munchie.
We unlocked true Jedi.
We unlocked a gold brick, but I still
feel unfulfilled in my life.
Oh, no, we're going to reach a million other true Jedi's.
Don't you fucking worry for this stud total.
Our stud total is going to reach the high heavens, bro.
Look at this, look at this.
All right, good time, good time.
Do you know, maybe this game eats so bad.
When we get make-up, we build LEGO sets.
And when we reach, ultimately, we reach a whole set.
Level complete.
True Jedi.
Jesus Christ, Jesus.
Ben, knock it off.
No.
Knock it off.
That's my character.
That's what separates me from Tom.
How would you know the difference if I wasn't vaping?
Knock it off.
Yes, he had to vaping.
He had to suppress and suicide.
He was an absentee fove.
Hey, autosave.
Hell yeah, dude.
Fuck yeah.
Dude, this game has autosave.
Well, this is for the future.
Yeah, this is a little bit of a wrap-up.
Yeah.
All right, we're getting more plot.
We're getting more plot.
OK, all right, all right.
OK, so there are some things happening right here.
Oh, god, oh, god.
There they are.
Look.
They can't.
They think they're going to get run over.
They're going to get run over.
All right, well, that's what we're doing right now.
Which one am I?
Am I those?
You're a walkie-talkie.
I'm the young man.
You're a fucking Obi-Wan, bro.
Die, Gungans.
And die.
And die, Gungans.
Dude, it's a jar jar.
Dude, I saw a jar jar.
No, it's just his race.
You can't say all they'll look the same.
Oh, it took him apart.
It was great.
It was worth it.
A Gungan is a Gungan.
You can't say it's only half of a race.
Half.
Dude, I am best friends with TJ Henry Yoshi on Twitter.
All right, hey, Ben, I'm going to make a hit.
Well, I'm going to make a hit.
I follow him.
So, yeah.
You follow him?
Does he follow back?
No.
Best friends, best friends.
Best friends.
That's all it takes.
I know this guy.
It's like you follow him.
Yeah, that's it.
I have a friend on the internet.
It's time to start the Ben St.
Hit piece.
Here's what's going to be.
You are a race, like a butcher.
No, thief, Ben.
You are the two other people's races.
I'm sick and tired of it.
The other day, I heard you ordering some Mexican food
on this phone.
Not cool.
Not OK.
Not all right.
Just because we're friends doesn't mean it's all right.
So I'm going to kill you now.
I'm stimulating their economy.
Why would you do that to me?
Look, my head is right there.
I know.
You stole everything I own.
I know I did.
Just I'm best nine.
Everything that I own is gone.
Thank you.
Hey, I want to kill that big yellow thing.
Six times the amount of studs that you have right now.
They stole all the studs that you killed.
I'm going to fucking murder him.
I'm going to murder him for the studs.
The cooperation over it.
It's a burst battle.
It's a, how are you evading my weapons?
Duh.
He's so slippery.
You actually gained more health from me trying to kill you.
That doesn't make sense.
I know.
I got him.
Slimefest.
Slimefest 5, baby.
That's not how the movie went.
Slimefest 5.
It's way more interesting.
I want to kill one of those big yellow pack animals.
Remember in episode one where we were like, no, we got to get out the studs.
Don't progress.
We got to kill one of those big yellow studs.
Dude, give me those studs.
Give me those studs.
Don't take those studs.
That's literally how I played this game.
That is actually what I did.
Competitive.
Dude, overheat this fucking bongo.
Oh, damn it.
I fucking pulled him.
Yeah, okay.
I get it.
I get it now.
Listen, you know what?
This game reminded me a little bit too much of my dad, but now...
Listen.
Okay.
Your dad can be many things.
It doesn't have to be only bad.
So let's get rid of him and my dad.
We're also good parts.
Oh, dude.
Guess who it is?
No.
Is it Jar Jar?
She's the cause of my daddy, Tusa.
Jar Jar.
What the gentle soul he is.
She's the cause of my daddy, Tusa.
What does that mean?
It means that Jar Jar is like a frat boy BDSM ABDL kid.
And then he comes over to his girlfriend's house and he's like, and she says to her dad,
She's the cause of my daddy, Tusa, implying that when they have sexual intercourse, Jar Jar is called dad.
We both immediately go to kill him.
Get the fuck back here.
You know these folks.
She's...
What's the one that can fly?
Uh, the nun.
It's a nun.
Yeah.
Thinking of that nun from that one show.
I forget what it's called.
Rocko's Martin Life?
It's about a nun that can fly.
Okay.
That's what I was asking about.
Thanks.
Rocko's Martin?
No, it's me.
It's me.
But it's just me.
It's just me.
Oh, it was you?
Oops.
Sorry.
You just looked really upsetting.
It made me mad.
She's mad.
She's so hot.
We switch characters.
Yeah, it's not a she.
But you know what?
Yeah.
Well, she's the cause of my daddy, Tusa.
No.
Jar Jar is the kid.
Jar Jar is the foot job kid.
No, she's so hot.
Foot job kid.
Is she topless, dude?
Yeah, dude.
No, you dumb fuck.
No, you have to make it.
You have to make things right.
I'm trying.
I can't get back up.
These pulses are out of the world, man.
Ben, you're literally like ruining my life right now.
I can't get back up.
I'm sorry.
Oh, there we go.
Wow.
It's almost like I didn't fucking do anything.
You dumb.
And I couldn't do it.
That somehow I just couldn't manage it.
Jesus.
This is the simplest of tasks.
This is like this.
I died.
You know what?
This is the most let's play episode of our escape.
This is going to be the most like, you know, last thing we're talking about fucking taxes
and we're talking about fucking aspirations.
Sometimes you've got to fucking chill out and just reminisce about how great fucking video
games are.
And with this, literally the best game ever.
This is the for better.
Only.
Only banner hunters can do this.
It's part of these studs.
All right.
Hell yeah, dude.
Dude.
Like three of those were blue.
All right.
Are we whores?
Question and answer.
Answer.
Yes.
Because we get so many studs.
Just imagine their twitch bits.
Where are the mini kids at?
Just imagine their twitch bits and get excited.
Oh God.
I dropped so many.
Thousands of bits.
Help me.
Where's our true?
Where's our true Jedi meters?
You're fucking up.
There.
No, no, no.
Look, I fixed it.
Look, I made everything right.
This is the only part of the game I remember.
Yeah.
Okay.
This is those moss.
This is totally Kazikor.
Oh, Kazisnap.
Kazisnap.
It's Snepkor.
Hey.
Are you able to get fucking Snap in Endless War?
I mean, A.K., let's go start with Complete Saga.
Because you're going to need to get it real soon.
Because you're fucking proper.
I know.
That was my plan all along.
You can Snap in fucking Endless War.
Dude, we got to put Snap in Endless War.
We should literally put it.
Dude, look at this.
This is limited to the jail.
It's food stamps.
We need food stamps in Endless War.
No.
Okay.
Hold on for a second.
Hold on.
I did do that.
I did.
Hold on.
Dude.
I can't hear it.
You can.
No.
Turn that shit up, y'all.
Get the hell ahead, dude.
I mean, we'll shut up next time so you can hear it.
I heard it the first time, but I wasn't impressed.
It doesn't sound.
No, it's so cool.
Oh, Ben.
You're so fucking terrible.
You make me want to kill myself.
How does that keep happening?
How do I...
Oh!
Ben!
You dumb fuck!
I'm better than this.
The only reason I die is because Ben who can't protect me for shit and I can't attack is Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar
Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar No Your Next Video
Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar JarX Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar So we mul it vehmbed it
Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar OD Jar Jar
Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar Jar
That's a BA, aka an abbreviation of Boba Vacchina, merged with Basics, some BA6 from a book entitled
BA6, which is formatted like the Holy Bible, aka 3 colon 7, talking about how we have to
have real actual revolution in the United States.
Was real actual revolution actually entailed, as opposed to fake revolution, as opposed
to the revolution you hear about on TV, it's all a fad.
Listen, I'm telling you right now, real actual revolution has come to the United States.
How did you get up there?
I want to get up there.
You double jump, bitch.
I'm double jumping.
Don't, don't help him.
If he's not Jar Jar Binks.
I wouldn't ever say that.
But I want it.
I want it.
I don't worry.
I won't tell Ben that he can never get up here unless he's Jar Jar Binks.
Thanks to you.
Unless he used a double jump.
No.
Why is Jar Jar such a good jumper?
Because don't you remember the movie?
It's not a she.
The Breastices.
Isn't there a thing?
He speaks funny.
He jumps good.
Look at her Breastices.
Isn't her sticking out of her Lego form?
Isn't that part of like the Jar Jar is a simpler theory that like there's a part where Jar Jar jumps
really high and if people theorize that he could only do it if he had zip powers?
Yeah.
Is that when he like dives into the water and does like a triple flip and then he's weird?
Okay.
You know that feel when you're like talking about Pokemon with someone and then they use
a gendered pronoun so you know they want to have sex with them?
Yeah.
That's all, that's all Kazi has.
Yeah, that's all you.
When I talk about Terran and I say I love her.
Kazi only talks about Pokemon that she calls she.
Well, no.
I talk about Pokemon that are fuckable and call them he like Floatsoul.
Yeah.
Floatsoul.
Everyone's favorite.
Out of everybody you could have been.
That's the most fuckable Pokemon.
Everyone's favorite Pokewifu Floatsoul.
Yeah, okay.
Well, that I understand.
We have a big problem here.
I'm not into that group shit.
Magnemite?
Magnemite, but not magneton.
What the fuck do you see in magneton?
Not magneton.
I don't do foursome.
I'll give you threesome.
That's fine.
I want two magnemites.
No more.
What's the one, what's the two headed dinosaur?
Are you thinking of giraffe or egg?
No, two headed dinosaur gen five.
Oh, durate.
Durate.
Hydraga.
Hydraga, but the second one.
Twinsoul.
That one's fine because that one only has two heads.
Fuck, what's the second one called?
Twin dragon.
Double headed dragon man.
That one's cool.
That one's got like an emo haircut.
Dude, all right, we're about to be boss nests.
We're about to meet boss nests first of all.
You failed so hard.
Look at myself compared to yours.
You're the reason why you need a true Jedi.
I fucking hate you, Ben.
I fucking hate you.
It's because I kept falling off ledges.
This doesn't count for anything.
You're so fucking dumb.
Look at this.
If you had to be raped by Pokemon, which one would it be?
Look against my will?
That's what the word implies, yes.
It could choose, yeah.
You don't get to choose.
He wants the fuck, Jinx.
Yeah, I do.
That's very racist.
That's very racist of you.
She's super effective against Rekweza because she's an ice type.
A nice type?
Why would you want to fucking ice type?
Because it's super effective against Rekweza.
We failed.
We're not true Jedi.
Your fault.
Look at you.
Dude, we fucked up.
Dude, we lost.
We lost the game.
We lost.
It's your fault, Ben.
I'm sorry that we weren't good enough.
No.
We couldn't make it.
We just couldn't make it happen.
You boy jinked four.
You boy jinked.
Boy jinked?
This game's putting me to sleep.
Wait, they're off.
We're making that fun.
Yeah, sure.
I can behind that.
Can you pass me my fucking whore juice right there?
Hell yeah, juice.
I'm not getting...
Oh, actually, yeah.
I guess...
Yes, dude.
I'm not cracking the mic.
Crack that fucking shit with stone juice.
Kidney stone juice?
It's just concentrated kidney stone.
No.
Maybe.
Hey, Ben.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
Yeah, bro.
How long have you been spending on that dumb bitch juice?
Ever since.
Ever since my discovery.
Ever since I discovered it at Aldi.
All right.
And nothing was ever the same.
You're crazy for thinking that tastes like Bangkok candy.
Bangkok candy is so much more potent and so much more flavorful.
Wait, which one tastes like Bangkok candy?
It's the same.
No, it's completely different.
Is there a Rockstar cotton candy?
Yeah, yeah.
Rockstar experience.
I haven't had the Bangkok candy.
He wants the sobby, obvious, scientific fact.
I'll try it.
That's munchies, but I don't know if he's going to drink it.
Oh, it smells so good.
No, you can have a sip, bro.
I don't want this at all.
It's similar, but not identical.
Hold on.
Let me see.
You have so many different ends.
You can drink to your bed.
Holy shit.
Well, that was mine.
That was his...
I've been collecting them.
I gave him that one.
But that one's mine.
This one's mine.
I've been collecting them so that I can smash them on screen.
Dude, this smells like a cotton candy.
Oh, fuck!
I just wanted to be mad at the smashed sour apple.
That smells like a cotton candy and gogurt.
Ben, have you considered like PCP or just cocaine or anything else?
Have I considered PCP on a daily fucking basis, dude?
I would never associate with a PCP.
I wouldn't fuck with that.
Is it a PINE or a MEP habit?
I think I would probably be very well suited to a co-cab, though.
I'm gonna vomit.
I like I love this, but I'm going to throw up at the same time.
This is highly controlled.
Well, it just makes me think of cotton candy and gogurt, which is really good.
Yeah.
But then it's also like an energy...
Ooh, ooh.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, no.
Oh, damn.
Schedule an Uber.
What the hell?
I had no idea that you can schedule an Uber.
Makes sense.
Okay, so I do that?
You can press a button to say, don't talk to me.
Really?
Can you really?
Yeah, you're rolling another feature.
There's also the bus.
You don't have to either.
Well, I mean, it's like, it's the reason.
There is the bus.
Well, if you take the bus, you have to transfer to the train.
All right, so where are you going to, Tom?
Where are you going?
Back Bay.
Back Bay?
Okay.
Crack Bay.
You're going...
Okay.
Where?
I mean, are you going to the station?
No, I'm just at Back Bay is on the computer.
Back to where I'm going.
Oh, damn.
So it's one step, it's a little cheaper to go one step.
Okay.
All right, Back Bay MTA bus station.
Is that where you guys met up?
No, I've been firing this.
Schedule.
What the fuck?
Um...
Oh, okay.
Win?
Do you want it?
Um...
Sure.
This is a weird clock.
Yeah, I know.
I don't know if I like it.
All right, 7.15 to 7.25.
If anybody wants to kill me, now you know where I'll be.
Now's the time.
It's vulnerable.
Yeah.
All right.
Schedule and you'll ride.
Get in town and I'll go the fuck out of here.
Dude, Princess Naboo just got exploded.
Princess Naboo.
There are studs in that plant.
Go left.
Yeah, but I can't get them because I don't have them.
Hell yeah, dude.
I'm not a Jedi.
Hell fucking yeah.
I'm not a Jedi, so I can't interact with this stuff.
Where the fuck am I?
What's happening?
Who are you?
I'm Queen Amidala.
Queen Amidabada.
I'm Queen Amidabada.
Dude, that feel when you open up your doorway and inside is a beautiful Indian woman and
you say what a habadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadabadab
it's from life!
It's from the proud culture of Native American DNA Indians
I always assumed that what it was from was that you made a comic back in The Pony Days where Spike is looking at rarity
a habadabadabadabadabadabadabadeee
thats a room specifically
oh my god you rube up when you get assassinated
Oh yeah i know you can do that, but it does seem like that could be the case in another lifetime
Absolutely, you can see it in his eyes. He's got the glint in his eyes just for me talking about
No, spare he's not freaking spare he's normal in Christian. It's my purpose. It's my purpose
Do do what what ships where you would do what ships? Yeah
I don't like them. You don't know
Yeah, yeah, please come on
This is a Chinese puzzle. No, you don't you don't
Yeah, there's blocks this well this part goes up here. Yeah, I know so get the fuck out of my way
You dumb I think it's the eyes. I make a Chinese. I'm I'm trying so hard and gotten so far there
I did it. Wow cry some more. You're dead Ben. You're dead. You're fucking dead. Not if you're dead first
Give me those fucking stuff
No, we lose we lose studs every single time well, then well, okay, all right
Yeah, of course, dude, it's it's about a mindset. It's all about the frame
You see like a fucking dumb ass whore how about that?
We can't interact with anything and we can't build the blocks we're fucked. Yeah, I'm gonna kill myself. It's so pitiful being not a Jedi
Yeah
She must she must just like Jar Jar Binks
Better if you can believe it far far if you can believe it then Jedi Binks
Whoo
Exploding windows. Do you are you subscribed to the to the Jar Jar Jedi?
How do you keep dying against droid? They don't even know here. No, listen man. This is a dumb robot. Yeah
I have no defense
God, what a terrible fate we can't interact with anything
Stop that
Look at all this stuff. Oh my god, there's so much lore damn it
Yeah, I didn't do it. That wasn't me
Yeah, well, no, no, no, no, this is definitely gonna be a series where we do the entire thing
We might not we're probably gonna do it on one thing does it would take literal hours
No, well, we progress to be a
Via bridge
Oh
This is the captain pinnaca side story side quests to the river captain pinnaca
Captain Panera, I'm an obscure Star Wars
I know about Niamh nub
Dude, that's pussy shit, you know about fucking Glocksbury heard of it heard of it. Oh my god
There's Jedi. Oh, give me me. I'm him. I'm him. I'm him. I'm the man
The sniped the snipes I got the snipes I got we're so fucking die captain pinnaca. No
No
Okay captain pinnaca, can we please add captain pinnaca to endless war?
That was my life until very recently don't go fencing my percusseth
Lucas if I sure as percusseth. It's it's a it's a perk. It's off-brand percusseth
It's off-brand percusseth
You could kept kept in pink is so fucking hot look at them
I don't want to I mean, it's a it's a pain killer. So you might get a little bit
You might get a little loopy. You might get a little you might get a little sleepy. I
Never found you made me itchy just kind of made me like
Took some panko bro
Yeah, oh, yeah, you should make panko doughnuts. Is that dude that sounds great
There are a few pieces left
You're such a keto cook in your keto kitchen. That's right with the keto KKK
Let's tell yeah
Let's talk about what flavors I made really fucking good, okay best one that you made was the lemon poppy seeds
I agree
We enter your household just looking to you know bang some sluts instead of any women, which was fine
We found we found some keto doughnuts. Yeah, and when they were in that and you were making them you were scrounging up materials from raw
From raw earth trying to create them
Drunk enough so we could witness your science and we were able to watch you go to fucking town
Some keto don'ts and was truly magical to watch you in your kitchen scooping up blackberries
You crush them in your hands and throwing the containers into the batter. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah meat flavor
Okay, we're talking about how you made a meat flavor of don't make you don't play
Listen, I was I was experimenting with the recipe. I tried putting blackberry and some it didn't come out great, you know
I that's that's just I bit into the blackberry keto doughnut literally tasted like a steak like a fucking
I don't agree
It was like a chewy skirt steak
It was like a chewy skirt steak that that keto doughnut
Hadn't said that it tasted like me. I would have just eaten it and been like, yeah, okay
But since you said this tastes like me, I've been into it. I was like
If it tasted like me that was your expecting to meet
Thank you, thank you very much for noticing my joke
Noticing my joke
I got it. Don't worry guys. I got the droid. Oh
I'm gonna show you your future in about a second here in like three seven
Yeah, it is well, it's it's on your when you're doing a flip jump you do the ground pound otherwise you just do like an air slash
The air slash combo. Whoa, I broke it for more money. Yeah, dude. Don't what are you? What are you doing inside of here?
Is oh my god, you fucking that wasn't even on purpose, but I'm glad I did it
All right inside of here. There is a dangerous thing. Cool. Is it me? Yeah
Well, there's an ancient evil. Oh in the actually sorry in this one. There's an ancient evil
There's an ancient evil century is old. How do you get it? I don't know
But there is it sits only so we won't be able to interact with it anyway
What was the point but the point is you're wasting my time to let you know that your kinship is in there
My mom called me. I gotta call my mommy. Did you go on stream on on on recording? Oh, I'm already calling her. We got to call mo vlogs
You got what
The dress that we got at the long one. I
Don't know I haven't tried it on again
It's like cream color and it has like
Flowers on it that are like
Dude kill Panenka kill Panenka
Okay, why are they like rotating and then explode?
I don't think this game values my time very much. I don't think this game that's cat and Panenka
Did you see that? Did you see that combo attack we did? We both value studs. We both yeah
Yeah, oh god. No, we just value studs. It teaches you it teaches you that the mom value studs
At the end of the day, it's all it's all about the studs
And if you think about the game we're doing so but okay, you are you are just
Viewers, I'm so sorry that I've let you down. I haven't gotten to Jedi. I've been really on my egg game
I'm going to do it next round for sure for sure. I'm gonna make sure you don't
I'm gonna make sure
This is what I'm dealing with. This is what I'm dealing with the person who doesn't want your Jedi
Anakka gets the standard basic Lego. Yeah, I know that's to my son at all
He's an NPC
Except for that part where he was PC
PC what's here? What's going on?
What are you talking about?
You're waiting for what? I hope you brought it for all of us
Tell your mom that you're with Kevin Panenka right now. Hey, tell hey tell uh
Hargadine and crack to come crowd into the room. Tell your mom that you're with Kevin Panenka and Queen Omidala
Tell her that you're with Captain Panenka and Queen Omidala
Tell her that you're wow have much time you're with
You're with Captain Panenka and Queen Omidala from Star Wars episode one the Phantom is tell her that you're with them right now
Captain Panenka and Queen Omidala tell her that you that you don't have much time
No, that's about right. Yeah
Close enough. We'll take it
No, listen, dude
Detector on that was really rude Captain Panenka is not impressed
She's like out somewhere. I don't know
Level then didn't hang up until just oh my god
This level I forgot this level is right here in the okay in the movie
This is where they meet young Anakin and what does young Anakin up?
What does young Anakin do but pod race? This is the pod racing level him. Yes, that's young Anakin
Why is he huge cuz he's really big for his age. He's just like a big golden man. No
Listen, all right, Anakin Skywalker the boy genius boy. Oh, I can get 500 cents by racing
No, stop go over the game. You're gonna crash a fucking bird. You don't mind fucking for us
Yeah, yeah, fuck him. Yeah, yeah, fuck him. Here we go
Get in that horror
Get all the powerups
Am I fucking? Oh, I don't I can't tell you're green. You're gonna get power. Get the speed boost
We ain't we ain't never gonna make you ever make
No, no, no, no, you only get all the stuff all the stuff bro. Don't crash. No crash or we fuck up, dude
Don't crash or we fuck up, dude
No, bro, get the crystals. That's true. Yeah, I'm a kid
No, the deck of raiders little Anakin. No, they're Tuscan raiders, dude. Oh god, they hate our race
No, no, we're young Anakin. We're young Anakin right now. No, you're not you're Obi-Wan and Qui-Gon
That's I feel like I'm not controlling
No, no, don't worry. We're more control of our lives than we ever have
Oh my god, we're swerving we're crushing that shit
We're crushing that fucking rock into a dark dick like it's a post get that fucking studs
You guys ever fucking coconut before a recommended only for the first day only
First thing it's heaven. Okay. All right first two days. It's like heaven second three days
First three days. It's Kino plus that first four days
First four first four days, it's delicious the last time you get maggots on your you're weak and it's no fun
Oh
You think that murder is a part of Star Wars you forgot that murder is a part of Star Wars. We'll guess what it is boom bitch
9-11 I
Don't feel like I'm controlling the game like what no, don't worry. No, don't worry
Drift Tokyo drift running the 90s running in Tatooine
Fuck fuck you tattooing
Yeah, I know I know no the real hallmark of the unjust no
Get these dogs get these dogs right here. We have to catch up. No, you don't fuck on Ross into a unclean traffic
Wanted that feeling you're running you're okay that feel when you're in the car with your best friend Luke and Luke is there
And he took you to mitzua and then all the way back from mitzua
He stops at a green right then runs a red light and then goes
When you're in the car with life and he won't turn around to get you a lot of time
What the fuck? Oh, that's a neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck neck
Dude that's when you got a whole chicken neck and you put in your fucking stock make a broth with later
No, he's an endless war character
No
No, no, well we can't get 10 unfortunately this last minute is up all the way up there
We have to go back in here with free play unfortunately
So we're building all of them what we did is cuz we could listen guys
We got all nine minikids and we were able to do in this level. We got true Jedi
We're looking for the red power brick right fucking now ladies and gentlemen, and we're in the egg game right now Avengers
Kyrgyz Star Wars a complete surger
Turgo Star Wars forever
Ben's a fucking boomer does attacks it gets on fucking snap can't even pay for a fucking ride Brad from the store
Okay, they came in pay for a right peach from Atlanta
Came in pay for it. It's no we lost
We lost we didn't we got three rocks dude you got three bluish rocks. No you dumb fog me you dumb fuck
That's the sin. That's the signal that we are in the third lab
I feel like if you don't press any buttons you do just as well
I feel like when you fucking turn your brain up. You aren't able to appreciate media. Oh my god. No, we have to lose
I'm sorry. We have to lose. We have to lose. Yeah, we have to lose. No, I know I know what the fuck do
I know what the fuck do we have to lose
To please help me lose please we have we're crashing the walls hard again. We have to lose please please
Please we have to lose please
No, I know what the fuck you I know what the fuck please
What is happening right now?
Why?
Why won't we lose
Why do we have hearts? Why do we have hearts if we can't lose?
Yeah
No, follow my lead follow my lead gold ranger, okay, okay, stay behind me green
Or sweet green we're gonna go sweet green
Yeah, all right, take a hard left hard left like my political sense. All right new communism new communism
Congratulations
Congratulations, we got red power right now. No, no even now we've unlocked a fucking extra for our ships for the fucking college drop
That's me on it. Thank God. Thank God. Now. What do we have red ships now? No
All right, let's go as fast as possible. We have to go Karen. We have to go as fast as possible
We have to go fast. We are also Bulba will fuck us in our ass
Bulby also also Bulby will fuck us on our ass
She hung up on you last time
No, she told me she was gonna call me back
Let Luke
Let Lucas ask her a question
All right, all right, Caroline, you have to drop you have to drop out you aren't you aren't trustworthy
You have you have to stop please you're subjectness to tyranny you are you are subjectness to tyranny
You're subjectness is hearing you right now. How could I possibly lose the game place itself John?
No, doesn't we have to win with three faster than Sonic?
No over here over here over here. No, I feel like this is faster. It's not it's not
No, no, we know we've been losing we've been losing
No, we have to we have we have to beat some bulb
We have to beat we have to beat Bulber
Yes
We can't and until we beat the ball best the best no listen to Bulba will face the fears
No, no, oh my god, okay, okay, Ben you have to fucking be proficient or I'm gonna go fast
No, you just get this you have to get in the speed bumps you get in the speed bumps green arrow green arrow
That seems that seems pretty that seems pretty straightforward. Tom. You're always like a pure kid
You're a fucking like weird pure tin beliefs like oh fucking don't cheat on your wife. Oh
Don't comment on YouTube videos
ever
We're not getting through the fuck well when us this pod race. I don't think I doubt it
Wait, there's a secret. No, you dumb fuck. No, you don't fuck secret cave. No
I saw it. It's all about that speed need for speed need for speed
I can't tell what I'm going fast when I'm going slow. They feel the same. That's fine
Okay, we have to get through we have to get through you can't even jump in this game
No, no, you can you can been you're all over the place right now. You're all over the place. Come on. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I'm just going where I need to be. I'm going over the green
Impossible he's about to win right now. Are you just impossible literally?
Did we just like just wondering about that? How are you supposed to hit every single speed?
I think so. I have no I like this was trying to go through. Did we just do really bad in the first two laps?
No, no, no, you're just really bad at this game. Oh, okay. No, no, no, I
Hope so when we have two people we're more likely to bump in each other and reset our acceleration to zero
Also, we're more likely if you're a bad player aka Ben, then you're gonna hit all the road stop to make us lose
It's all your fucking fault. Don't mess with myself. Yeah
No, no one can play besides me. This is our scams. It's gonna be me playing the game. I wish also Ben
I have an admission. Yeah, I did take that percussa and I do feel good. Why can't believe you took my fucking percussa
I like we go we go so much. I do we go so much faster once we fucking go once you're not here, Ben
All right, don't take any more. I mean, I'm gonna need that if I ever get another kidney stone
Should I have asked my mom to say something on speakerphone? Yes, you should know $10 if you want man
I don't think a one of those worth $10 on the street. Hell. Yeah, dude. Oh, well
Then drop out right
Enjoy
Have a great time
Hit the green hit green green is good. Yeah, green is good
Yeah
It's just hitting no no not hitting anything else. It's it's a fucking cargo Star Wars, dude
Probably have to hit that right slow. That seems cute. No, no, no
Choice. No, it does the choice, but we can't access it because we're not a tie fighter
We have to be impurely aligned if we want to access that part of the game
Damn
All right, hit this one hit this one. I hit this one. Yes
Your yes, is that forward green arrow? Is that subolva? Yeah. Yeah, you're so far behind. I know
No, listen, no, we can do it
Hold on
No, no, we can't do this. I know we can't there's a tie fighter thing right there
Look, we're gonna crash. We do it. It's for if you're a tie fighter
You come back in free mode. If you come back in free play mode, you're able to lock in the game
It's high fighter
No, that won't help us because we get more if we go this way
It's all about the amount that we get we have to maximize the amount that we get
No
No, okay, I think it's impossible to I think it's impossible to player
The second
So bad Tom does it not feel like the game just plays itself. It's a very little it feels like you're not really doing it
I kind of got the sense of like, you know when you give your little brother
There's no we voted you just press the buttons. It's like that
Okay, okay, look how fast
I
Want to restart it's only single player only single player
Why is this a game state? Why is this a game state?
No, don't worry. Don't worry game over. I'm gonna steep state of mind. No right now. Okay. My my adrenaline is pounding
It's already like instantly. Yeah, I know I told you close I told you single player rules single player wins
Let's go
Nothing don't worry about
No, not at all. I I cherish it. I cherish you guys
Should rowdy fuckers top healers be a quiet show. No, no
No, guys, we're gonna bring it down. We're gonna talk about emotion right now. We're just gonna talk about what we've been doing
Yes, yeah, the two people just
You know, you know guys, oh, we're just gonna talk about our feelings right now right now
I'm feeling joy that I'm able to beat some all betters this over game
I'm feeling you know, yeah, I'm feeling relaxed right now. I can't just put your legs
I won look he pulls it out yet the entire time that small fry fuck that little dick bitch
He had in his pocket the entire fucking time. Are you joking me and you just wanted to fuck
You wanted to flex you wanted to vent the slave had 500 bucks. Yeah, why you slam that damn slam that damn
Oh
Okay, okay, now you maybe now you may get the privilege of playing more like a star
Perfect detector. We need to take where the power bricks are that will help us in our journey
But we'll be able to be located all the power bricks in each of the levels in which we encounter them pretty good
That's gonna be fucking
We're at so many jokes fuck right now
Yeah
Hey, Ben shut your window your loudest shit, please I can hear you clearly from outside
Yes trouble that up
Alright, I guess I'm shutting the window. Oh, it's gonna be way too hot
It'll be fine
You should direct the camera outside and then at your street name the street side. Oh, yeah, that's a good idea
What oh, yeah, no be it'll be here really soon. Oh
Oh
Yeah, it's on route actually what's on her at the uber. Yes arrival time seven minutes
Listen listen if you want more of the juby kingpin
Tom you were sucking my dick earlier
You were on your hands and knees that feel when your hands in a box when she's on her knees
Endless war you like it be in it everyone would love you everyone tears you everyone would say hey
It's mr. Gams. Oh
Mr. Gams mr. Gams. That's your new RFC KOC
You please everyone like press one in the comments if you want Tom to be the kingpin of the Rowdy's I mean
He's gonna pull in a frame dude. No
Juvies of the jubies. Did we ban a frame yet? No, but we should he messaged me saying hey
I'm hey kill me, please. I didn't do it cuz I have too much mercy
Too much kindness in my heart, but literally you can be the farming master
It'll take no commitment whatsoever farming farming is farming master farming is powerful and
Emotionally rewarding. Yeah. Yeah, and and hard ass fucking work that you have to do on your hands
And he's probably and what and when do you put your hand on the slime cork mill and I said just a hand mill
But on like the crank where you put your hands there's spikes that drain slime from you
And you have to crank it over and over and over again to use
Trap on you. Yeah, suckin suckin out of your veins. You know, you're really out of your wall. It's hard. So all right, Ben
Uh-huh speaking of hard sell. I'm not hard. So I know this game right here. You may have been thinking yourself level design
Studs
But oh
There's a point. No, there is a clear
Overlining goal when it comes to this game. This game is hints. This game. Yeah
This game the point of it is
To grind and grind reach that one hundred percent and to achieve that you gotta get through Jedi
You know my you gotta get through today because you know all the sudden the world so you can unlock
characters
Gronk join
PK droid
Security pick one pick one pick one pick one pick one. I know
Dratka. Yes, you play as him captain tarpels. I love that boss
Of course, I want to be boss now. Oh god. Padme. No water. Definitely a lot of mushroom man
I got a pit droid for you right now. Get my pit droid right now. Okay. Get my pit droid right now
Hell yeah, dude. Fuck. Yeah, dude. I'm out. I'm all out dude. My other pit
Dude, this is my picture. I got a pit droid right here. She is hell. Yes. You want some pit droids? I would rather not
Do you want some pit drop? Yeah, that's not that's not on brand. That's that's not on brand for me
My entire life used to be unlocking the characters in lego star wars
Dude, that's literally the entire reason that feel when you like okay
You see a character in a cutscene and then you think yourself that character so cool
I love Darth Maul. Darth Maul so well designed and also well developed
Give me the phone
Also crack uh, I went I went downstairs and I went outside
Yeah, and cracks not in his jeep
But I like I like sprinted at the door like really fast like excited to see crack in the jeep
But instead of cracking in the jeep behind him
There was like a van with like four ladies in it that just like stared at me and we're like what the hell are you doing?
Because I like ran outside and I looked really expectedly at the street. We take the palace
I think those women are like buying the house across the street or something. I think that's what their deal is
I think they might not be buying it anymore. Ben. How did you found?
How'd you make it the way that you did today? Like I like you just walked in you just
um
I just took a shit somewhere. Oh, okay. I just took a green shit somewhere. I hate this place is nice
I enjoyed that boss mass looks terrifying. No, he looks so attractive. I so I
I don't know about that. I looked out the window. I saw I saw cracks jeep. I saw him moving around in it
Where's correct then?
We can't find crack
Am I allowed to knock on chelsea's room? I don't see why not. Oh, he's probably in there. Is he in there? Probably
Okay, yeah, you know what? You know what? I don't know. Uh, you you're allowed to knock
That's the way just anthony you have to do it. Sorry munchie where's tiny hats you have to do it? No, not any better
Hahaha
Look at padmin. Look how look at her curves. Oh, she's so well. She's got boobs. Yeah, dude. He's got leggo boobs like a real
Wait, really? Yeah, actually it's jar jar vengs. It's jar jar vengs. Just like a flat-chested lady. Yeah, he's he's rengo dash
She's right. That's right. That's right. Look at how hot pad may is dude
Like as represented in this game infancy's battle
Is that her? Yeah
Wow, dude
That's hot. She's like, um, she's like n
Six six. She's like n six. Yeah, dude. Exactly like it actually like there's literally no difference that I can think of
You dumb fuck get in. How do I get it? We're we're we're going to macy's. We're going to target. How do I get it?
Hey, press y you pressed y. I'm pressing y
So what okay bye, bitch, whatever. I'll just this is good. This works
Okay, I'm going to send a photo of
Why don't you just knock on her door?
Okay, that might be funny. Tom is probably done. Is it time for you to take it? Oh
I had prior to the only
Way we're able to play this game is because of these xbox controllers that tom got us
So the tom is the reason why you're why you're watching this
Tom is the reason why I have to suffer through lego star wars
Kergo star wars the complete surger is the best game ever made. Okay. Wow
We'll leave it up to the people to decide on that. Yes phone in the comments on whether you killed tom or munchie first
Tom you're a god. Hey, I do
Cool to have you over. Yeah, man. We'll let everything out again soon. Yeah, we should. Yeah, we should
Live here soon, right?
Tom you're you're you're welcome. You're welcome to come over here like literally any time
Cool, fuck. Yeah. Oh, what if he came over like
A lot and like forever. Yeah
And like he what if I just like didn't have to leave. What if he just
Dude, just pull just pull an econ and crash on our couch and just like hang out shirtless in our living room for for weeks
All right. All right. That's that sounds great. Yeah
Okay
Tell crack to come up if you see him
No, she's not no, she's not she's not
No, no, no
No
Give me my phone. Where's my phone? Oh, there's my phone and the fucking garbage
You're a fucking garbage, man. You're a fucking garbage. You're off screen. I say by the way, and then I start eating garbage
Ow, I got shot four times. But there was a reason I was eating garbage. See, I was depressed
And suicidal and suicidal
It was no, I thought there was someone
Yeah, dude, I think you're chinese ghost money back. It's a japanese ghost
Oh my god
Was that a japanese ghost? I think that was a japanese ghost. Yeah, like like you do
I can't believe you have so many fucking supernatural spirits
You had the sun god apollo enter and then the japanese ghost made his appearance. Where did apollo go?
He just ate my perks
Classic apollo move
Okay
What's up with you and sun gods, bin?
Well, you know, I just think that
I say, well, I'm a rain god. I'm a rain god. I never tell you about never tell you about
No, I'm a rain god. No, I'm a fucking rain god. I'm a rain coward. Anthony, who's a rain god?
It's it's it's definitely it's definitely caroline. Yeah, I'm in cassey. No
Yeah, no problem cassey snap
By the way, stupid bin, I haven't tell you about brain for breakfast. Tell me more. I'm interested
It was this youtuber that I followed and he said something that reminded me of him. He was no mo vlogs
He was no mo vlogs. Unfortunately the the the truest gym of all
Uh, I want to be r2d2
Well, he's uh dead
So, oh my god, that's fine. Do r2d2 you got a point? No response!
I don't know. What are you even talking about? Oh, but you know, not not like dad isn't he doesn't come to me like dad isn't like he has
Yeah, yeah, who's dead? Who's dead? So this this this youtuber I used to follow he died
I think I told I think I said in the pcp chat and you responded like it was a long time ago
Anyway, it was this educational youtuber. It was like he used a pole in the ball. Which is very nice
How do I use this spot? You have a gun guy. You have to be a gun girl
Well, I don't want to. Okay, that's fine. I just want to be r2d2 and any fucking I I just woke up one day
I saw my recommended and I don't need boss nas
You can you can be him once we get back to the cantina. Well, I try it and then it made me be this idiot
Well, we have to do in free play
So if you ever want to come back and replay level, which I know that you would love to do
Nothing would please me more than to do this all over again. Exactly. So we're only 100% don't worry. I'll play as the cop killer
Yeah, hell yeah, you're gonna be the new cop killer real soon
Actually, now I regret that because I'm going to fall asleep if I don't have something in my hands
Okay, what are the controls for this game? What uh, it's it's up. It's upright left and b
Just use use the left button to shoot your gun
Hold on. You have to get up here. We have to progress. You have to progress to get
Up here
Yeah
It's a gun. Okay up here. It's a little stung. It's a little stung. It's a little stung on here up here
Click on this click on this click on this click on this click on this yeah
Anyway, he was this educational YouTuber that I loved, and he was the best in the game.
He was literally my favorite YouTuber in the genre, in fact, probably of all time.
And I loved watching his videos, and he was like, he was a young man, right?
He was a small YouTuber.
I think he was at like 300k, so like, not like nothing or anything, but he was like,
you could tell.
You know, it's a big pond, you can hover, you can hover.
It was like, you knew who was going to rise to greatness.
Just like all female video games characters, you can float, like R2-D2.
Exactly.
You knew that he was going to achieve greatness.
And then he fucking straight up just died out of nowhere.
Is it?
It's pretty hot.
Well, I can switch it to AC.
I can steal, I can steal, I can steal from you outside.
I don't believe that this is a gun.
It's not literally a gun, but it's in every practical sense.
Oh, I think maybe I should go to the left.
Why?
That's, why would you do that?
Well, I mean, you know, sometimes you're intuition is right, but not always.
Oh my god, all I wanted was to fucking die.
We gotta get, oh my god, look at our true Jedi.
We shouldn't even try.
We're not going to get it.
No?
No, we're not going to get it.
There's no way.
What?
Look at how little we have.
With my dedication to the fucking silver bullet.
You will never be a true Jedi.
This was your last chance.
No, listen, we're about to defeat the Phantom Menace right now.
That's not true.
Yeah, we are.
Wait, really?
Yes, you dumb fuck.
What was the Phantom Menace?
I'm not playing this game.
I think I'm pretty sure I never actually played LEGO Star Wars my entire life.
I think I only ever watched those people playing it.
That's, I mean, that's fine.
That's really, you get, you get a lot out of it anyway.
I want the blue one.
What?
You're not allowed to show feet on Twitch.
Really?
Yeah.
This isn't Twitch though.
There's no rules.
There's no fucking rules.
Wait, are you serious?
Yeah.
Why?
They would turn into like a...
Yeah.
Because there's too many...
Click on this.
There's too many foot dudes on Twitch and if you show feet then like it's basically porn.
Caroline's a private.
What?
The sketchbook?
Uh, I mean, you know...
I've seen it.
Go up.
Go open it.
I've seen it.
There's no tits.
Oh, sad.
Oh, how embarrassing.
There's no tits.
How embarrassing.
There's no tits right here.
There's no tits where?
I've seen them.
Right here.
Oh, I didn't draw that.
But there's...
It doesn't count.
There is tits in there probably.
Well, apparently, yeah.
Yeah.
You've established that.
A two-draw long-legged horseman.
No!
Don't read it.
You can't...
Okay, you can look at things but you can't read it.
Two-draw?
It's like a to-do list.
Yeah.
Draw a long-legged horseman.
Don't look.
Don't forget.
Don't forget about the long-legged horseman.
Look at these bubbles.
Look at these fucking bubbles.
It tastes like forget things that I like to draw.
In beauty.
In every single fucking...
Can I not be this motherfucker?
Yeah.
Go up to another person.
Go up to anyone.
Captain Pinocchio.
What?
And do what?
Press Y.
Captain Pinocchio.
Captain.
What do you say about that?
ClassicHALE.
Hellobaby?
Is itching for die for?
Ohhhh!
Bidna small dick play!
Welcome back to Seder Dick Reviews.
We're gonna compare the top 10 Seder Dicks.
Hey, speaking of our actual show, like what we actually do like no joke for real.
Uh-huh.
The Monsters?
I'm sorry.
The Rockstar?
Pretty good.
Not a good thing, but like surprisingly, like Rockstar didn't fuck up.
Rockstar ex-durance.
Yeah, like despite their history of being the absolute worst swill you can buy.
And there's some swill you can get.
And there's some swill.
But Rockstar ex-durance?
It's a good line.
It's a good series.
I think the cotton candy is just as good as the bank cotton candy.
I don't think so, but you know what?
That's fun.
Oh my fucking god!
Also, I just like that it's blue.
Uh, yeah, it's like, it's weird to me.
I don't know who did it first, actually.
I always say that people are ripping off Bang, but I don't know if Bang was not even the progenitor of it.
It just felt that way, because I learned about it in that order.
Hey, Caroline?
Yeah, what's up?
You're gay.
Stop!
You're going some other way.
Come over here.
Don't touch my shit!
Other people's room, by the way.
You're going some other way.
I can't touch it anymore.
Come over here.
Be a Jedi.
You can't jump as high if you're not a Jedi.
Be a fucking Jedi.
You're passing battle forms, still.
Do Crack and Heart know that they can come in if they want?
I texted Crack, and I said, where are you?
With a picture of his car.
Okay.
What are the controls there?
I don't want them to think that they shouldn't come in.
Crack!
You're going to put it back in the Crack box, dude.
Crack, no.
Okay.
Alright.
No, yeah.
That makes sense.
You haven't acknowledged the fact that you have a wife, like, at all, on any, anywhere.
In text or in video games.
Well...
You have a green card marriage?
I'd get cut if anyone knew that I had a wife.
I'm sure of it.
Cab lovingly incubated Claire for you.
Sinclair for you.
And you haven't acknowledged your existence even once.
Uh, it's a green card marriage.
Okay.
I needed citizenship.
Look at these beautiful bubbles right here.
Yeah, I'm over them.
Dude, look at me pissed right now.
Right into my fucking face.
I like how your piss comes out red.
Dude, yeah.
Hell yeah.
Dude.
Don't look at me.
Don't look at me, dude.
I'm fucking peeing.
No, dude.
Oh, look.
It's my friends.
Okay.
Get them.
Obliterate them.
Yes.
Our whole party.
We need no friends allowed.
Our whole family.
Our whole clan.
I had to do it.
I had to do it to activate my fucking sharring on or whatever.
Listen, when you kill someone, you get their worth.
So you have a binary, like a numeral, like integer.
A numeral?
A numeral integer as it sounds.
A numeral integer.
A numeral integer for each of your worths.
And your worth can go up and it can go down based upon numerals.
That's the guy that did the Colorado piece.
No, you know, stop, stop, stop it.
Oh, actually, sorry.
That wasn't him that was actually watching about that.
Yeah, sorry.
Did he think something stupid?
No, no, no.
I wasn't talking about that.
You can out me as a hack in a fraud.
That's fine.
But as long as you don't fuck me up.
No.
Oh, god, fucking die.
What?
Oh, sorry.
I'm not going.
It's pretty much.
You love it.
Oh, my God.
Carolyn, you.
No, sorry.
I'm getting the blue shit.
Your camera.
Your camera work is stunning.
You'll be a photographer one day.
You'll be a cinematographer.
A photographer.
A forestographer.
Okay.
Where are we going?
All right.
You know, you know, you know, as a small character, well, I'll tell you fucking who it's, but
and just kind of her in parentheses, boy.
What?
All right.
Check out this shit.
You thought this game didn't have small hatches of characters to walk through.
Well, in fact, it does have small hatches.
Carries.
What do you mean?
Small characters.
You're all at the same side.
Small hatches.
You can walk through.
You don't like in, uh, in, in Super Paper Mario for the Wii when you get, uh, pixel.
Anakin is exactly the same size as everyone else.
No, no.
You ruined it.
God damn it.
So bad.
Yes, you did.
Yeah.
Yeah, I did.
Just use the force, dude.
What are you doing?
Get over here.
Get over there.
Yeah.
Forest powers.
Who's Qui-Gon?
You.
Can I jump all the way over there?
Okay.
I'm Noah.
Yeah, come on.
Come on.
Blue.
Oh my gosh.
What you want me to join?
Thank you.
What are those two again?
Anything?
Look at our faces.
They add up to 10.
Oh, okay.
And then once it hits 10, then you get a prize.
Oh.
A prize.
Look at that brick detector.
Did it detect more red bricks?
Dude.
Oh, well, okay.
That's part of it.
That's part of the equation.
Don't you worry.
How damn it.
This game sucks.
Right?
Tell me about it.
So much hard dick because it's so good at having sex.
So much hard dick.
Yo.
You see, Mike went to Whole Foods.
That's what happened.
Oh, you were buying ros.
Dude, dude, dude, dude, dude.
You were just there yesterday.
What were they thinking?
Well, they only got half the foods.
Well, they were buying, they're buying celery and...
Dude, I got all the sea ice you can drink.
What more did you want?
Yes, yes.
So much sea ice.
Yes.
Whole Foods.
No, I got it to save more behind the Whole Foods.
The sea ice is a terrible vodka, but there's two big handles of it.
It's a plastic bottle.
I had to buy both of them because it was $9.99.
$8.99 for a liter, $9.99 for a liter, $75.
These numbers don't lie.
That's closed off.
This is a gated community.
And they're whispering behind me.
There's a gated retirement community on the way between here and Whole Foods.
And it's fucking sick.
Yeah.
It's fucking sick.
Literally, what are gated communities?
It's like you have to apply to get in.
Yeah.
You're just...
Gated communities.
You're just watching TED Talks.
We made it in.
Oh, yeah.
Hey.
Stop.
Please.
Wait, why can't I go?
Because you're not...
Yeah, even though you're the same size.
Okay, we'll have a go.
All right.
Please remove this box.
I'm appealing...
Please what?
Please remove this robot.
Please.
Remove what?
This robot, please.
I don't know what's happening to you.
I don't know what's going on, please.
Hit the red button.
Hit the side button.
Hit the right button.
Yeah, do that.
Do that.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, when things glow, it means you can use force power on them.
I did not know that that was the force.
That's the force.
Hey, what's in this little chimney here?
Oh, it's a red power button.
That was a red...
You gonna do it or what?
There you go.
There we go.
The puzzles are out of the world.
They're fucking nuts.
Dude, they're too hard for me, bro.
They're too hard for me.
That's even the Chinese.
Let me tell you.
Okay, first of all, glowy shit.
You're gonna use force power on it.
Can you each stand on the other block and just raise each other at the same time?
Yeah, no.
That's the puzzle.
Oh, that is the puzzle.
You had another epic puzzle.
Just face me.
Face me.
Oh, my God.
The power of friendship, the power of understanding.
That's beautiful.
That's so cute.
Oh, that's so cute.
So cute.
You raise me up so I can reach to Jeddah.
That's so cute.
Can you go in there?
Are you trying to be tiny?
No, I'm not small.
Either one of you is small.
God, just look with your...
Look with your eyes.
Yeah, just look.
Just look at him.
Look at him.
He's small.
Look.
Make him tell that he can squeeze through tiny holes.
He's so small.
Why don't you wear his tiny holes?
We need more than three of us to unlock.
No.
When are you starting your NSFW vlog?
Why don't you fuck tiny holes?
Why are there stunts in the gates?
There's stunts in every object that's just laden with them.
Every object is just laden with some cryptocurrency.
Like physical cryptocurrency.
I guess it's got to be a true Jedi.
Unfortunately, we aren't even close.
Every space in this universe is diffused.
Like the curled up M-brains of string theory are just packed full of quantum bits.
Wait, what are they called?
Nodes.
Nubs?
Naves.
What are the things?
What are the monies?
Um, dude, like 42.
I just answered the universe.
What are the pieces?
The little shiny little pieces.
Dude, dude, like fucking 42, dude.
I'm so smart.
I love Hot Topic.
I love fucking going there.
I love the Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy.
I love literature.
It was a better time.
Can't we have to go back?
No.
We have to go back.
No, fuck.
This is a nightmare.
No.
This game is terrible.
This is so amazing.
Yeah, this is so...
You made it.
Yeah, no joy.
You got the blue.
We got the blue.
What?
Is there anything else?
No, we got the blue.
I got the blue.
That was all that for a blue.
Okay, okay.
I was a platforming genius.
No, no, no.
I got you.
I was a platforming genius.
You're so...
Yeah.
So, okay, so you can play this single player, right?
Of course.
Yeah.
No.
It's only 42.
Well, I did in fact do that earlier, so you should know.
I forgot.
I was asleep.
Oh, my good boy.
I was taking a little nappy now.
What does Bibendum say when he wants to congratulate you?
Oh, he says, uh...
What is Bibendum's red aura?
Cystis nest Bibendum.
It is time to drink to our life as he drinks a big goblet full of broken glass shards,
because he's so fucking tough and durable.
No, no, no.
Karen, please, please, please, please, please.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Oh, you should be.
Oh, jeez.
You should be, you fucking nerd.
Wait, wait, wait.
What day is it today?
I don't know.
Tomorrow?
God damn it.
Guys, we missed the fucking free comedy, the free comedy night at Limelight.
Limelight.
No.
God.
It was, dude, Ben.
All right.
Literally the first week I get back in Boston, we're fucking doing that shit.
Yeah?
We're going to Limelight.
We're going to the Limelight, so you can see.
So you can have your time in the Limelight.
Because they got the Limelight special going right now?
Hell yeah, dude.
Ben, do you have a type 5 uniform?
Um, a type 5.
Is that like, is that some kind of new Slymoyd breed?
Type 5 set, you know.
What does that mean?
Like a type 5, you know.
Oh, a type 5.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Make me go up please.
I'm going to hang 10 on my type 5.
You're the only type 5 I see is my fucking girlfriend, you know what I mean?
Yay!
Scraping children can we finally release that video by the way if you saying I really wish I had a girlfriend you know
I was being funny on purpose, right? No, you know I was being retired on purpose, right? Ben, me too.
I was, I was, I was being, I was just acting. It was satire. Yeah, but you said, you said you never released that video.
Because, because, because, because brainless like you are all out there and they would be like there's no, I didn't detect no trace of irony in this delivery.
You, you can't like do something bad. I thought you were just embarrassed because you were super wasted.
Look, don't talk shit about brainless when you're fucking five-year-olds, okay? Yeah, literally. They'll both get offended.
No, they have small brains. They're not built yet. Well. But it makes your pussy so tight.
Oh, so it's so delicious.
When I said a, when I said a type five, when I said a type five, I meant like she's a five out of ten. That's what I meant.
That's what I was trying to get. Oh, yeah, right. All right, Doc's this guy right here. Doc's this guy right here.
Hey, why am I this man suddenly?
You probably hit Y. I did not hit such a thing. You probably hit Y. I did not. It's easy to do.
Dude, you go in the different fucking button. No, I want this one. I was, I was here first.
I was here first.
I wanna be, I wanna be a, how much you owe me?
You are, wait, wait, who are you?
I'm, I'm, I'm fucking, I thought you were quite gun-gid.
Hey, get out of this one.
Oh God, no, we're back into the fray. Into the fro, into the fro, yo.
You guys suck. We're back into a fray.
into a frame are you ever no your gun just auto tracks on your enemies the
cop the smokers cop oh there are so many chairs to release duds from I know
that's what I'm doing over here what do you think I'm doing for the first room
of the game had like 20 chairs and all of them had to be interacted with like
four different times in order to unlock all the sweet sweet you think that
there's only studs in these chairs you're done you are wrong you you are so
wrong Apollo we're about to prove you so fucking wrong yeah yeah yeah no well
no it's your real name what's the uh here we go here we go come on where's
Phoebus when's Phoebus getting in he used to be here yeah what happened where
where's the happen to that guy he was here alright break break this and then
and then did you do that because you like that sweet break detector well
fucking yeah we mentioned it wait what oh sorry huh is it different what no
sorry the commander of the enemy force people like okay they're here but don't
worry we got time oh god no it's too valuable that you it would be wrong
I need my blues I need my blues you're giving me the gun break this fucking
dudes ETA it's my time to take dude take a snap benefits wait up no fuck we can't
be we can't be so scattered brain we can't lose track of conversation we were
talking about something really important um hey anyway guys about these red
bricks do you have we have you secured you secured the bread yet the bread yeah
have you secured the bread what does that even mean you hey Ben are you off
keto are you saying you're off keto right no no I'm back I'm back I got my
michael of ultra because I'm a good keto boy my michael of ultra it's the
only it's the only brand for me I love brand you drink so much make up I understand
I I I shut that shit like it's I was it's like shit like it's pee bro yeah it's
just a wall nice I'm sure it was just laying with with with nubs thanks for
the archway architects dumbass dude the R2D2 yeah okay this is really good he's
well I love being R2D2 you're not you didn't okay I'm so small dude look at
the jaunty way that your god this is literally like Kevin Kord this is like
guys I'm so small I'm so small guys like I'm the youngest you know it's like dude
you you are like the same as everyone else I don't mean to be rude but what
is the oldest don't tell him I'm the oldest please don't ever tell him I'm
the oldest so lose all his respect for me I don't want to be rude but dude I
don't want to be rude but I'm the oldest 15 year old munchie meets 100 year old
Ben don't tell me I said that though down the hatch down the hatch down the
I'm Kevin and you shall respect you couldn't you couldn't handle the
what is happening right now I've got I've got fruit punch mango mince creme
do creme de creme brulee creme yeah creme creme de la creme a la
Edgar and a la creme de la creme a la Edgar and cool and cool creme a la
I'll say what we go what are we going let's go here we go
shout out shout out if you remember the rest of cats
I've been to the Vegas myself fan yeah yeah my favorite flavor is a premature death
is that what CBD taste like hey hey hey Caroline you like my sick ride huh you're a
fucking loser kill yourself every ride are you every car yeah hey hey my god
there's a bigger ride a big right hey hey hey hey hey you like this car you
want you want to ride it don't worry it's gone out forever you Yoshi dude that's
so funny let me in there let me in the bigger ride big right big right a big
ride underneath his butt right on his hip big big ride he was writing in the
town of where we are he rode with this big ride big rides that that why that
would really well put that song on put big iron on right good big ride on big
ride oh fuck fucking limelight well Ben I'm so excited to get you into limelight
we're gonna come line line limelight heads every single every single Wednesday
every single Wednesday we're gonna go to limelight in the beautiful city of
Boston Massachusetts and we're gonna limelight we're gonna get that free
comedy hour we're gonna go there people are gonna say jokes they're gonna say
off it in the land and then I'm gonna they're gonna move on to the next joke
okay me me and Cassie been running from his family since his son came out as gay
that's it that was my joke like pins like pins
my joke I mean Casper walked out street we're going to get fucking dinner I
don't even know where and then and then just on the side on the side of the road
there was a merchant there was a vagrant there was a fucking peddler of
wild what color do you think my pee would be in the color filter you think it'd be
purple to know well how hydrated are you not at all dude I'm not there's no
water you probably be green can we find out fuck yeah yeah it would probably be
green you know why you get kidney stones you don't drink enough water I've been
I've been drinking I've been hydrated I've been hydrated I dehydrated myself
deliberately for today so I could pee green on the street
you just gotta get your dick off here with your stream on camera
what if I just go peeing in the jar I just go pee in a jar bring it back and
exam yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we haven't fucking seen your piss or cock once
okay okay all right I'm fucking nightmare all right dude hell yeah
hell fucking dude dude you're the cop killer you're the cop killer you're the cop
killer we were walking down the street and we were stopped by two fucking
emaciated children two juveniles who are like hey it's free comedy night here in
this bar that we're staying right next to you want to come in and we said no
obviously no look why would we want you we're walking dinner what is your game
plan like what is your marketing game plan like oh hey you know I just hope
that some people just on the side of the street we'll just come in here just you
know for fun I hope they just like click quit their plans yeah yeah I hope they
are just walking around for no particular reason whatsoever they aren't
walking anywhere I hope they just are completely plan this they're like you
know what yeah sure and you know what it worked we said we said no we took 10
steps forward and then we stopped in our tracks we looked at each other we said
we got good I said you want to go she was like oh I guess so do you and I was
like you're more and she was like you know what okay sure yeah and as we walked
in we are the only people that are not in the show that wasn't apparent at the
beginning well sure sure at first we walked in we were just the only yeah yeah
souls in the entire audience and then people followed and we thought okay so
we're literally the only people this marketing trick worked on but no we were
because as more and more people walked up to the stage do their bit to do their
sketch Ben's walked in empty-handed dumb ass yeah it was normal pee so we didn't
get a jar I don't know I didn't want to see my pee I got back full oh my god you
get so you make it nice and fluorescent yeah guys are you guys know about the
no I don't know you talk about the after fucking limelight you dumb fuck no no wait
let me in my seat no let me in my seat let me in my you can play the game from
behind the back seat you can play the game from behind the fucking back seat jail cell so so we
go inside like and it's like we are the only people there that's it it's the first time I
ever been to a comedy show and it was like really kind of hilariously bad in a way okay it wasn't
like it wasn't bad but it was it was like okay here's the thing if you tell a joke on stage and
you're at a comedy show I know and there's only a couple people in the audience no matter what
even if everyone like laughs at your joke you're still only getting what sounds like a little
tiny laugh yeah because there's not that many there's not enough people to have it be like
haha yeah oh for sure yeah yeah yeah so when someone tells a joke and they're and then there's
free and people laugh it sounds like the joke didn't land and so they go cool so look at that yeah
that's cool by the way dude fucking the police sirens are blaring they're coming for you so because
we this is the titular limelight by the way what you're doing right now the titular limelight
because we're the only people in the audience that weren't part of the show all the comedians
were like trying to riff off of us no just like at the end well there were a few of them that were
like asked questions about us and like responded to us when we said things so like a few people
that were just like hey what what's your deal what's you doing like how are you doing tonight
we're like good we're watching your comedy show the girl the girl said like what are you all about
and we said what and i said listening to comedy shows and she was like oh okay and then continued
on with their fit okay i'm sorry yeah yeah yeah let me ask you a question what is the jar of
pesto sauce on your dresser that's good shit well because well there's already pesto sauce downstairs
and oh yeah we don't need two pesto's in the same fridge obviously i love the fact that there's three
of us i love the fact that there's three it's so good what do you mean there's three yeah look i didn't
even know yeah that's great dude you're you're such a killer hey you are so fucking like terrible
by the way but yeah go on tell me about the poo videos you completely abandoned them well yeah i did
because they weren't getting that many views wow fucking bitch i know well stick with okay
bin finish finish what you started finish what you fucking start finish season one at the very
least finish season one i did i did say i would i did say i would finish season one uh i don't
know guys uh there wasn't getting many much engagement oh oh wow i wasn't really engaging my
audience because i really care about that i'm definitely making efforts to try and do that
oh by the way don't post things online just post them on fucking patreon have no one know about
the my comic it's just just hey when i go to comic meetups i don't tell anyone about my stuff i don't
actually try and get the word out whatsoever but i really care about engagement i really care about
getting views that's really what i'm about it's insane hey a book that fans never read what how to
win friends and influence people i read that on the toilet every day of my life it's like a good book
did you really have how to win friends it's like it's a good book no yeah it's like it's like an
infamous book it's an infamous business book where do we go there's my dad's always go and rescue
all the hostages there's a bunch of terrorists about right now oh really yeah he's killed kevin
pononka right now i'm even paying attention dude kevin pononka dies every day of his life sorry
ben i'm the new cop killer i hate it you're a fucking jewie and you always will be whoo whoo
but i'm king of the jews king of the jews better better better to rule in hell than serve in heaven
no that's not true i know get over here get over here get over here yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
if i like he gets more studs dude you ain't having studs well i wonder why because you
fucking killed me three times she doesn't have any studs she doesn't i don't see a single stud i got a
stud right there gross gross i don't see i don't see anything i don't see anything dude dude yeah i'm
looking so stud-like with my own life oh yeah i was really happy when you she looked like a
fucking pizza man you look like a fucking demario looking at us that's the nicest thing
anyone's ever said to me you look like you look like you look like you make you make pizzas rather
than being made out hell yeah dude you're no no longer no longer you composed pizza what the
fuck is happening oh shit yeah dude you're using your force powers exactly 30 your guys dead yeah
what happened to those what happened to your bros no no they're they're fine they're just sleeping
i don't think they're just sleeping yeah hold on i gotta get these two silvers no please
what no what do you want me captain panonka please what do you want from me
where's the droids okay please don't okay what's happening right now i didn't know captain panonka
why is that no there's no captain panonka no please there's no captain panonka has
something gone i don't know please get back up please get back up oh there he is there's panonka
well look at real captain panonka please stand up please stand up
can i not jump on this or do i just suck not you just suck shit are you serious i feel like i can't
use your powers i use your gungan legs use your gungan legs no yeah yeah use the gungan
sith powers look at this here drop out drop out yeah here drop out i think very i think you're
just not hitting double jump at the height of your jump you think so maybe here drop out
here drop out here drop out don't worry don't worry i'll get a prize for you i'll give you a
check your cheese you try you can't do it first try hold on oh not that's a camera not yeah it's
helping well yeah the camera hold on see you can't do it no no no no i i almost did it i can
yeah maybe you can maybe you can jump higher than no that's definitely different that is the case
yeah okay well i guess it just works better if you do it from behind
just like with my big eyes solid five girlfriend oh no my airpods
we gotta add airpods to cosmetics as fucking as fucking nutrition airpods what's the airpods
it's uh it's like a case it's blocked it's a blossom case but actually you want an air pod
oh for discrete listening oh my god that feel when you're listening to something and no one
recognizes that you're listening to something i'm gonna try and talk to you with a nightmare
crack gave me this ear hey please try and get up here buddy yeah fucking move your arm though
no no no i'm not doing it okay no i'm er and i'm stubborn i'm i'm er the stubborn rule that's what
everyone knows me for there has to be a better way there has to be a better way there has to be a
better way this is the system or what oh my god it happens oh my lord she's gonna fuck it up she's
gonna fall she's gonna fuck it up no no no i don't know i just don't know i don't fucking i i i believe
in quite god no no no no no no don't worry don't worry don't worry please drop out please
how do you do that press start yeah where the hell is start there now we have to drop out and then
press the button wait just let me do it let me back in get on my seat give me my seat give me my
Drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop
that, drop that, drop that,
drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that,
drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that
drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, drop that, down
where in the house that we remember
everything that comes
in the place that it's supposed to be in.
You left these studs on the table, man, hi.
Well, listen, man, listen, man,
Ace of Spades is playing Ghost Star of the Jedi.
Yeah, not even close.
I know, it's truly pitiful.
Hey, you did it.
Fucking, here, look, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Please, please, please, what do you mean?
Oh, there's the boys!
No.
The boys.
Damn!
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
You want a trophy?
Okay, all right, bid us to play the next level,
because it's the most climactic thing to ever exist.
Caroline, over here, Caroline, over here.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please, please, please, please, please, please.
Oh my God, I have to come right now.
What were we talking about?
Oh yeah, the hot pot sucked.
The broth tasted like fucking dish water.
It wasn't very delicious.
They overcharged us.
They wail.
Ridiculously overcharged us for some shit.
Okay, so there's an item on the menu called meat lovers.
It was called meat lovers.
It was not called meat lovers, it was like a meat platter.
Okay, Laura, beef lovers.
It was called beef lovers.
Was it actual?
Yeah, it was called beef lovers.
Okay, so it was called beef lovers.
We get it.
What was shit?
It's $35, and we think, okay, $35.
That's gonna be like a big thing for a group to eat.
Yeah.
Well, they said it was for two, and we got it for three, so.
Well, okay, okay.
We had to tip this off.
No, wait, hold on, that is relevant.
However, I will say that we knew that,
but you get the information,
and then it got sides all of us each
to compensate for that.
So we got the meat lovers thinking that would be our meat,
and then we would get sides to fill up the rest.
You guys.
Super slide, we got super slide.
Yeah.
Well, you did at the end.
And the point is it was like,
it was barely enough for one person.
Like, I don't think it would even be enough for one person.
No, we would play for one.
Maybe, maybe.
But the point is that it was way overpriced,
way not enough, and it wasn't very good.
It wasn't very delicious.
But you know, the concept of the hot pot,
the romantic, platonic ideal of the hot pot,
being like a social experience,
where you're all in the hot pot,
it's just this big, warm, boiling pot of broth.
You stick shit in the pot,
you take it out of the pot, you eat it.
The idea of that,
mwah.
So we think we must be doing something wrong.
I researched.
I learned how to do the hot pot correctly,
and we went to a place that we were thinking of going to
on the first day,
but we didn't go to in favor of Cassey Snip.
Because you-
Big mistake.
Because no way, right.
No, you, oh yeah, you wanted lamb.
You wanted lamb chops.
Yeah, no, no, no.
I wanted to go to the happy lamb.
You were pushing for lamb chops.
Well, you were pushing for the happy lamb purely
on the basis of the name.
Yeah.
There was no way to tell.
Yeah, no, but I knew, but I knew that would be good.
There was no information.
I was-
No, okay.
Because they didn't have like a menu on their website,
they didn't have a website or anything.
Oh, okay, okay, no, no, okay, hold on.
Here's how I knew.
I walked by.
Oh, the movie's starting.
Oh, oh, yeah.
Yeah, everyone shut the fuck up.
Everyone shut the fuck up.
It's starting.
Chapter six.
Door is small.
The trade federation army has been neutralized,
but I can't, I won't go in.
Give me that.
I'm switching in.
I'm tagging in.
All right, fine.
Now I get to play the video game.
Okay, no, here's how you tell a good restaurant.
Literally, here's how you tell, you look at it
and think, wow, is it good graphic design or not?
It had great graphic design,
and I could tell that it was chic and crowded as hell.
That's great, unironic, great justification
for going to a restaurant.
Okay.
Casus temp was out of the way and not very cool.
Well, you know, when we start,
when we got the regular beef, and it's not the beef lovers,
like it was just the beef lovers
that was overpriced and shit.
Like everything else was not so bad,
but we didn't get any of that.
We just did it wrong.
You are a fucking moron.
We have to play the game.
Come on.
So it just automatically reflects the days back.
Yeah, but you had to time it.
Come on, Dara.
Hell yeah.
Come on, Mr. Mall.
I wonder, I took a picture of when we went to Happy Lamb
and got a really good hot pot.
Yeah, put it on the screen.
Yeah, it was really colorful and really beautiful.
I kept looking at it and I took a picture.
Wait, hold on, before we put it on,
I just want to say, I really didn't like Casus temp.
And so until a couple of days later,
I still wanted hot pot because I wanted to redeem myself.
So we go to Happy Lamb, finally you cave the pressure
and you allow me to go to the place that I knew it would be great
and it was.
We go in like five minutes before they open.
It's completely shrouded in darkness.
It's shrouded in darkness.
We walk.
Wait, you got there as they open?
Yeah, we got there like 30 minutes before they're opening
and we walked in, like the door was unlocked,
but the lights were off, but all the tables were set.
I thought it was like scary.
What are you talking about?
And then some lady appeared from out of the shadow.
Are you literally stupid?
Maybe.
We get true dead eye.
Oh wow, thanks for the droids.
Get the blue.
We got to get all the sets, bro.
Come on, we've lost our ways, we gotta do that.
Anyway, yeah, so we go to Happy Lamb
and just show them the image,
because that's all you need to know.
That's all you fucking need to know
is show them that fucking image.
Let's see how it looks on.
Yeah, great.
Okay, well you can't really.
It looks like a fetus.
It looks like some fucking mess.
You can't really tell that good.
No, no, but trust us, it looks great.
It's really.
It's a lot of meat.
Okay, and.
No, it's not the plate of meat, it's the bra.
Oh, okay, I'm gonna show them the preview.
So can you give like an estimate
of how big the plate that we got at Cassey Snap was?
Like how big the $35 plate.
Maybe like this big, and it had,
honestly there were only maybe like 20 slices of beef on there
and like their thin slices.
It had, I would say it had five different types of beef
and then maybe like.
No, there were like three.
There weren't that many, there were like three.
This under $10.
It's okay.
Oh, there you go, there you can see it.
Under $10.
Look at all that slime.
Look at all that fucking delicious shredded podrans.
Imagine thinly sliced podrans that you dip into a hot pot
full of juvie blood.
Oh, dude, you just fell, you fell, you dropped the glue.
We'll never get through Jedi now.
All right, that's, you know what, that's fine.
That's fine.
Is it though?
No, it's not.
Yeah, I didn't think that.
It was pretty good, and also they had potatoes.
We just started the whole game over.
They had potatoes with this hot pot.
That was one of the vegetable options.
That was a really good decision.
Okay, okay.
You know, like it melts in your mouth.
It might seem obvious to those of you who know
the hot pot experience.
It may seem like, you know, oh, obvious,
but like the point of the hot pot
is to literally just make a soup.
You know, you have to make the broth yourself.
So you're the whole point of it
is that over the course of the meal,
you are creating the exact soup that you want,
adding in the materials and adding all the stuff.
So what's really important to a soup,
obviously is the broth.
And when your broth tastes like fucking dishwater,
it's not gonna be an experience.
But this fucking place was so like into their broth
that they had a giant neon sign that said broth so hard.
Oh yeah, yeah, broth so hard.
That's their slogan.
All the shirts in place. Yeah, yeah, that's their slogan.
It's broth so hard.
Broth so hard.
Three blues, three blues, three blues, three blues.
Blue man group, blue man group.
Blue man group.
No, not.
You're gonna fall as you're dumb.
No.
Oh man.
It was delicious.
You, I got like fucking like a meat
and it was so, so delicious.
I got lamb.
I got the titular happy lamb.
I got lamb and I got, I got, I got,
I got garlic beef, which was really good.
I got Napa cabbage.
I got fucking, I got, I got buck choy.
Raise me, raise me you fool.
I'm trying to.
No you're not.
I got garlic beef and then some mushrooms
and then some potatoes.
That was, that was really good.
So good.
Only stormtroopers can access.
No, we can't do anything up here,
but we can't get blue though.
Well there's blue though.
We can't get blue though.
We can't get blue man group.
Hey Ben, you want to join like a blue man group again?
Oh, you just like, just like fucking.
A blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue, blue.
Yeah.
Is that what they do in the blue man group?
That's what they do in the blue man group.
What is blue man group?
Blue man group seems like it would suck.
Oh.
Yeah.
It's a, well it's like, it's like music,
but it's also like a performance thing.
They like.
On the steam powered draft.
They do like cool.
Yeah, exactly.
They do like.
When he was a boy.
He'd play by the sea and then by the sea.
By age 15, he'd left the shore.
On a captain sailing on the shore.
Woo.
The navy was just taking a lick.
Pirates had invaded the ship.
Balak's was on the Aint Harpoon.
He rang their round with a spark and a boon.
The pirate's away.
And navy said, Captain Albert Alec Zander.
Look down in the sea.
But that Captain Albert Alec Zander.
And the end.
Yeah.
My favorite song.
Hell fucking yeah dude.
It's a good, it's a jaunty little tune.
That's for sure.
Chotey little friend.
He's a chotey little friend.
Yeah, it's a Chotey little friend.
Chotey little friend doesn't die when you cut him in half.
No.
What?
That feel when you.
We haven't cut him in half yet.
We just threw barrels at him.
When you cut him in half, he falls to the ground and doesn't die.
Yeah, he just gets robot legs.
Ben, Ben.
That feels like it's hard to even half.
He comes back in Clone Wars with robot legs.
Ben, you know what makes me so mad when we're walking down
in the city and you like move like faster than me and Kazi.
And these are moving so fast, the screen moves,
and we get like automatically slided to where you are.
Like that.
Classic.
I hate when you do that.
Classic move on my part.
Got no stash, bro.
Blue.
You're so fucking dumb.
And we won.
We won.
We're so close to Tujena right now, by the way.
Look at that mannequin over there.
Are you joking, man?
I don't think they're joking.
I think they're good, luxurious.
What were we talking about before we started singing?
A hot pot.
Oh, yeah.
Never again.
No, not even the good one.
No, no, no, dude.
Ben, hot pot.
All right.
Yeah, you know what?
You're right.
Dude, straight up.
It will be so fucking good.
The Happy Lamb is actually Kino, unironically.
OK.
All right.
You know what?
You know what I want to do so bad?
I want to have another RSVK con.
So, like, unbelievable much.
Aren't you doing one in Europe?
Yeah, but you know, fucking whatever.
How many European members do you have?
There's a lot, actually.
There's actually a lot.
Yeah, no.
Like Portugal and, like, Ireland.
Right at the top of my head.
There's Ladderless.
There's Shawnee.
There's Hale.
There's Magic.
A bunch from Germany.
Yeah, I do two of the codes from Germany.
Spain, Tardis from Spain.
Tardis from Spain.
Slimes is from Portugal, I'm pretty sure.
I'm one-sixteenth Portuguese.
Dude, there were so many Portuguese, right?
There were so many Portuguese.
You're so bad.
Yeah, well, what are you going to do?
You've really ruined the game for us.
Yeah, I should have ground pounded.
What?
They obliterated me.
You're so, you're going to literally make us
lose true Jedi by looking at you.
Like, Ben.
I tried ground, you, that was you.
That was you.
I tried ground pounding and they just shot me out of the air
and I died.
You are so, like, the opposite of someone who's good.
I'm not, you're saying I'm not a true Jedi?
Yeah, I'm saying that you are a fake Jedi.
You're a fake fan.
What's worse than being a fake fan of true Jedi?
No!
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
Da-bup-ba-da-da-bup-ba-da-da-da.
This is like slime pest all over again.
Only better.
And for free.
For free.
Hell yeah.
Actually, you know what?
Apollo was exactly right.
It was just about ground pounding.
Ground pounding you win.
I know.
I've been doing that at the highest entire time.
You may sail the way.
Dude.
Free.
You remind me of a fucking mollusk.
No.
Oh, I only got one.
No, this fucking guy over here is calling his fucking jockstrap assholes to come in.
God, my favorite fetish is jockstrap assholes.
Yeah.
No, yeah.
I love, like, smelly men.
I love men that are smelling also fat and also muscular.
You just keep attacking and you just deflect all their shots.
Yeah.
You'll never get hit.
That's the game.
You're not even MLG.
Racket killer.
Come over here.
I'm coming.
I'm going.
I'm over here.
Come over here.
I thought you were about...
I thought I was going to eat it.
Look at us right now.
Yeah, we were so close.
Ha-ha.
Where'd we go?
Are we done?
No.
Not even close.
Is our adventure at an end?
How long have we been recording?
Two hours.
Not only two hours, it feels like...
It feels like an all day.
Not, dude.
It feels like the 24-hour stream all over again.
No, no, no, no, bro.
Not, dude.
I have the words on Nightmare.
You know what we should do, though?
You know what we should do?
We should just do, like, an episode of each thing.
So we can have six ready-fuckers cop killers fucking this.
Oh, fuck you!
Hey, fuck you!
Oh, hey, man!
No, fuck you!
Come here!
Hey, no, fuck you, dude!
Come on!
Fuck!
Or even be on the show.
Actually, you know what?
No, no, no, no.
I'm still wearing a go.
I can go all fucking night.
Let's do episode two.
Let's fucking go Clone Wars.
The best fucking movie that there is.
That's accurate.
Yeah, hell yeah.
I liked the video game almost as much as I liked.
I gotta get this blue.
I thought it was gonna be good.
Come on, dude.
Oh, dude.
Well.
Wow, you did eat it.
Oh, I lost.
Oh, twice.
I don't have any more bits to lose.
Ah!
190 fucking studs.
That's me.
Oh, my God.
Ben, did you see yourself?
What?
Did I just almost go over?
Yes.
Well, but I didn't, though.
Easy.
Yeah?
Is it?
Oh, oh.
Dude, I don't even have any more fucking things to lose.
God damn it.
Help me.
No, he's not.
What am I supposed to do?
Oh, my God.
You're so defensive.
You're like a juvie.
All right, Ben.
I'm a true Jedi, dude.
Here's what I want to talk about exclusively.
Here's the only thing I want to talk about.
You've been fucking me up.
Oh, by the way, did you release the Vaporette?
Did you release the Vaporette that you said you were gonna do by next PCP?
I forgot.
That was today.
Wait, no.
Is it Friday?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
I totally forgot to do that.
Fuck.
How embarrassing.
That's really embarrassing.
I mean, I have it.
It's not like I don't have it to release.
I just forgot today was Friday.
That's really funny.
Okay.
Well, as soon as we're done, we should end this immediately so I can go do that.
What are we doing?
Oh, wait.
Okay.
One, two, three.
There we go.
Wow.
What a great puzzle.
What the fuck is what is happening?
Like, what does that do?
Okay.
Great.
Speaking of Vapers.
You need...
Dude, I'm so pissed now.
I'm so pissed at myself.
Yeah?
Are you?
Yeah.
I fucked it up.
Whatever.
Dude, you had a busy week or something.
Yeah, I did.
I mean, yeah, that is why, but it's still disgusting.
That's horrible.
All right.
Kind of three.
One, two, three.
Wow.
Why didn't it work?
One, two, three.
There we go.
Get the studs.
Okay.
Ben, when are you going to return home?
No, really, actually this time.
What are you talking about?
Unironically, your presence is needed in this war.
Especially...
Okay.
I'm going to get real with you for a second, Ben.
I'm going to get absolutely unironically real right now.
No, not again.
One of these days, in real life, I will be here in Boston, which will be good for RFCK,
the show, but I'll be here doing college.
I will not have as much free time as I do right now to code and to be the sole kingpin
that there is in the game.
RFCK cannot exist, or I'm sorry, endless war cannot exist if both kingpins are completely
absent.
It cannot exist without us.
RFCK...
I keep saying RFCK when I mean endless war.
Endless war is the most creative, imaginative, and most amazing thing that I have been a
part of to this day.
And to let it completely clay-fallow while I'm not able to personally be there would
be an absolute fucking travesty.
And you need to, as a kingpin, to clock in during that time.
Will you be able to do so?
No.
Yeah.
Yeah?
So?
Yeah, I mean, I don't mean to never come back.
I wasn't a plan.
And I don't want to grill you either.
I'm just saying.
You're totally grilling me, dude.
I know I am grilling you because you fucking deserve it.
Okay, so you did mean to grill me.
Well, yes.
Is what you're saying.
Yeah.
Everyone loves you, Ben.
Everyone wants you to be a part of their lives.
Listen.
It's not that I didn't like it.
That's not why I haven't been around.
I've just been busy.
Well, you know, it sucks.
That's how it is.
Can you not find time to come in?
Can you find it in your apartment?
Yeah, he's dead.
He's excised.
Yeah.
What?
He's dead.
Yeah.
Also, what did Ben not do that was embarrassing?
What?
I heard.
Oh, oh, oh.
I said I was going to release the vaporette on the website today.
And then I forgot to do it.
I mean, it's technically still today.
But I said it was going to be out when the PCP came out and the PCP's out.
And I forgot to do it.
Check out it on his website.
Yeah.
I mean.
Say comments.com.
It'll be out by the time you see it.
I'll do it tonight.
That's so dumb.
Lol.
Dude, are you ready?
Our Just Desserts.
Tell us a story.
Hey, how long are you guys going to record for?
Do you want to do episode two?
Was this just episode one?
Honestly, I mean, not particularly.
But like, I don't, I don't know.
I feel like it's, we haven't gone, we only gone two hours.
Yeah.
We haven't really gone that long.
I mean, how long did you want to go for?
I was thinking we'd do episode two.
I mean, like what's, do you have a plan in mind for like how long you want to go?
And like what, what do you do after?
Well, I think we just beat episode two and that's it.
That's it?
Yeah.
All right.
Yeah, we're doing it boys.
7.1%.
7.1% actually.
That's 7.1% of the entire game.
We got 100% of it.
Well, hold on.
Video games are meant to last for years, if not hours.
Yeah, but.
Come on, come on dude.
LEGO Star Wars.
Ben, do you agree that this is the best game we've played ever?
Yes.
I agree.
All right.
Episode two, dude.
Episode two.
Wait.
Wait, dude.
Did Hart come in here?
Yeah.
She popped her head in.
That is cracks here.
Does it?
Is that what that means?
I think his jeep is down there.
I told you that four hours ago.
No, I know.
But they were at the grocery store.
I texted Crack and he said he was at the grocery store.
Uh.
Tell them we don't have enough.
Can you make sure you have enough?
Tell them to get their sexy asses in here.
I want to get them all so bad.
All right.
I'll get them.
Okay.
I don't know.
They might be busy with something.
Ben.
Uh-huh.
Oh, he has an interview.
How do I?
Press start?
F2.
What?
What's happening?
I'm pressing.
How did you leave?
I don't know.
I mean, I'm pressing buttons.
Press start?
I am.
What?
Um.
Cool.
Hey.
Oh.
Anyway.
Rowdy culture.
Flourishy.
Killer culture.
Stag.
In the fucking toilet.
Yeah.
In the toilet.
There's no, there's no, like, you know, like, cohesive, like, actual culture there.
It's just a bunch of people who, like, are killers for reasons completely other than
you in any way.
That's fine.
Honestly, that doesn't bother me much.
Well, sure.
But there's no, like, actual, like, there's no, being a killer means nothing other than
that your name is purple.
There's no.
That's good enough, right?
No.
No, it's not.
That's plenty.
Okay, hold on.
Is your controller got unplugged?
I think maybe the controller got unplugged.
That's fine.
It's me only now.
Hey, Apollo.
You're the new cop killer.
No.
Cop killer.
Hey, nice.
Still the cops tonight.
Tonight.
Whoa.
Cop killer.
It's the law.
That's all.
That, that, that was the inspiration of the name.
I remember when I first came up with the name where I first cop killers.
Did you pause it?
What's going on?
You, you broke it.
No, you broke it.
What do you mean I broke it?
No, you broke it, dude.
Wait, it moved.
Because you broke it.
It moved.
No, Ben, you broke it.
No, I saw him move, but you broke it.
What do I do?
Well, it's running now.
Good.
No, it has auto saved.
No, no, Ben.
When should I restart it?
It's broken forever now.
You can't fix it like the disc is broken.
Oh, you cracked the disc.
You cracked the disc.
The disc slipped?
Yeah.
You broke it.
Wait, it moved.
Because you broke it.
It moved.
The disc slipped?
You're going to have to fucking, we're going to have to take us to GameStop.
I hate GameStop.
I hate GameStop employees.
I hate when they try and make video game references out of our credit card transactions.
And when we say, hey, you know, this, this, it sounds weird when you get a confirmed transaction
in your debit card and it goes, eh, eh.
Definitely it's like as a cancellation.
Oh, speaking of it, how much am I being paid for this right now?
You are.
$500 per second.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You are making bank right now.
You are siphoning the money out of our bank account.
Okay.
By the way, this is like literally like the worst level in the entire game.
Cool.
I'm glad we decided to do it.
Hey, it still doesn't think that I'm playing the game.
Well, that's fun.
It's not.
No, it's not.
No, no, listen.
It's bad.
Well, here, here.
Well, yes.
Much.
No.
No cutscenes.
They're aged up right now.
They're aged up.
No more cutscenes.
Dude, don't you remember the Clone Wars?
Don't you remember the Clone Wars?
Don't you remember how they're trying to assassinate QAnon?
Look at that, dude.
That's what you look like.
That's pretty cool.
How many cops do you kill while you're at the police station?
Four dots.
Well, you'd have to have a gun.
I don't think that many, honestly.
I mean, how many, like, active police officers are just like,
hang on like the lobby of a police station?
Probably not that much.
You could kill like a receptionist, but that wouldn't be a cop, really.
They'd probably have a cop on duty at the desk, right?
I mean, maybe.
I don't know.
But I'm saying that's not the most effective way.
Dude, they're always trapped.
Unironically, thinking about cops just going into a cop station just now,
maybe you want to eat the rest of those donuts downstairs.
What?
Yeah.
Actually, they might be gone.
Dude, this game sucks.
Why can't I control a character?
Yeah, good question.
Hey, like, literally, like, what happened?
You know what?
This is fine.
It's a senior game now.
Good luck, Ben.
Here.
You're welcome.
This is fine.
I like this.
Oh, oh, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
Oh, my God.
Ben, I'm about to do something crazy right now.
You're not going to fucking believe what I'm about to do right now.
What are you going to do, dude?
What are you going to do?
You're going to make true Jedi?
Dude, no, I'm going to do something way better.
I'm going to do something way, way, way, way, way fucking better.
You're not going to believe the shit I did.
There's so much collateral damage in this game.
So many people die, but it's okay because they just fall apart,
and you can always get more LEGO pieces.
All right, hold on.
One out of five?
Yeah, one out of five, two out of five.
Hold on.
Okay, you guys may be thinking yourselves,
oh, wow, you know, a video game.
I love video games.
You may be thinking to yourself,
this is not my beautiful house.
This is not my beautiful life.
How did I get it?
You may be thinking to yourself,
this is not good commentary.
How did I get it?
Is there a YouTube community of video games?
There must be, right?
There's board games.
I know board games.
I feel like there is a video game,
and I feel like I might have said it.
Dude, it's the anger video game there.
It's not stupid.
The anger video game is Alter Ego Board James.
Oh, it's Alter Ego.
He's like split personality.
Yeah.
He's chill personality.
I remember more.
I think so.
I think Board James is just like a nice man.
So I hate him.
I remember the only episode of Board James
that I ever saw was like him going through
board games that he made when he was like a kid,
and it was like shit.
He's always like, why are you showing me this?
Board James is the number one YouTube channel.
Like what, by the way?
I saw an episode of Board James
where he's playing video game board games.
You know, like there's a Mario board game
and a Pac-Man board game.
The Pac-Man board game I had as a kid,
and it was like a plastic Pac-Man piece,
and there were marbles on the thing,
and you would move it around.
You would stamp it on the marbles,
and it would pick the marbles up underneath it.
And I was like, whoa, I played that game, dude.
I played that video game.
Wow, you're so special for playing a mass
produced game video game.
I also engaged with that media.
Wow, dude, I love brands.
I love brands.
I don't know almost as much as I love franchises.
Hell yeah.
Okay, Ben, you're not prepared for what I'm out to do right now.
Okay, I know a secret.
I know a little bit of a fucking secret.
You can even say that I'm a secret meister.
All right.
Woof, I would never want to.
I don't think I would do that.
That doesn't sound any better.
It requires a little bit of skill.
I might not be able to do it on the first one, but that's fine.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I was so close.
Okay, hold on.
I'm going to wait for them all to respawn.
End it.
No, don't worry.
Yeah, I think Kazzy decided that the bargain cracker
cooler than us.
Yeah, you know what?
That's fine.
I did it.
What is this?
What happened?
The red balloon.
You know what they say about red balloons?
The harder they fuck, the harder they ball.
Red balloons blow by.
You know about new endless warming?
No.
You know about lat dancing?
You know about lat dancing, bro?
No, sir.
I do not.
I know nothing.
Yes, red brick, red brick, red brick.
I'm just a secret meister.
We're going to trouble, sir.
You are literally going to shit your fucking pants
when you find out what that red brick has.
Because that means each red brick has its own
like individual power up that it gives you.
It's not randomized at all.
And you're going to shit your fucking pants
when you see what I've got for you.
Look at this side.
Look, this is like literally just in like
inside slump or HQ right now.
This is how they commute to work.
It's delicious.
And I know, right?
I'm getting you hooked.
Oh, oh, yeah, yeah.
I can't smoke.
I can't get a fucking hooked.
It's far more deadly than breathing in
than just smoking yourself because it's unfiltered.
Yeah, of course.
Jesus Christ again, again with this thing.
Wow.
This game, like, okay.
Oh, no, sorry.
This level is like not my favorite.
Unlike all the other levels?
Yes.
So every other level, don't worry.
It's completely fine for what will happen.
This level is like...
Oh, it's an incredible payoff.
No, no, literally yes.
You're not going to believe what we got.
This game would be so fucking bad
if it weren't for what I just did just now.
Like the game scene that I've entered currently
is going to rock your little socks off.
Am I crazy?
Or is it too cold in here?
Yeah, you are crazy.
But you know what?
Your house, your rules.
That's right.
Wow.
Thanks.
Oh, it actually got colder.
It's actually colder outside than inside.
Wow, I suburbed in and out of that.
Wow.
Please.
Better you than me.
What?
You idiot.
Just touch it.
Just hit it for fuck's sake.
Why can't you do it?
Okay, there.
Even that didn't look like you actually hit it.
What?
That one, I don't know what happened.
Just hit it.
Crack is here.
Does he want to hang out?
He's making dinner.
What?
They're making dinner downstairs.
What are they making?
They're making like pasta with like a spinach cream sauce.
Pasta?
Are they using the Alfredo?
Garlic bread.
Are they using my Alfredo?
I don't know.
Thank God.
Thank fucking God.
You're so bad at this.
No, I'm not.
I'm really great.
I'm so embarrassed for you.
What happened here?
He couldn't fucking hit the thing.
Why isn't it RFCK now?
He couldn't perform the series of tests.
I know, right?
I think purple and green.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
I thought you guys put a filter on it for a minute.
Nah, dude.
This is just straight up.
Yeah, you wish.
Don't you remember Star Wars Episode II?
Were they going to Neil?
Los Angeles City?
I can't even walk in.
Where is this?
This is Coruscant.
What?
Come on, dude.
Yes.
It's a Patreon you get.
You're looking at it.
You see it before you.
It's a Patreon you can get inside Nero Cafe, Cafe Nero.
It's a free Discord game you can play in your browser for free.
Click the link in the description.
I love this by the way.
What?
It's just the way that it's flying.
What do you mean?
He can't.
He just can't do it.
It's funny.
He just can't fucking do it.
He can't handle it.
Nah.
What do you call this right now?
I don't know.
What do I call this?
What do you call this right now?
Come on.
Give me a little cheat.
Give me a little fucking pork.
Cracks a little bit of a snake man.
He's a total snake.
Absolutely.
I'm not really scared because I looked at him constantly and I ran up to him to go to the toilet.
You just charged him.
He got a wrangle.
He got a wrangle that man.
Did he go into a defensive posture?
Dude, it's an all out brawl.
All out brawl right now.
All out brawl.
In this war right now.
By the way, if you ever want to know, there's a video game abstraction of fighting in this war.
You shoot them and you're like, what does it really look like?
This is what every encounter looks like.
What did you do?
I put your ass on Instagram dude.
Damn dude.
Dude Chris, remember this part?
Oh, he got down in flames.
Crash into the fucking ground.
Yeah dude.
Hell yeah.
No, kill him.
Not kill him.
Okay, dead.
He shot him.
Now his face has to melt.
It didn't do it.
Alright, you're going to scream.
We'll let you find out what was in that red brick that I got here.
I already want to scream.
Stunt magnet.
So now we're going to be able to get studs and look halfway across the fucking universe.
Dude, we're going to get true Jedi every single one.
I know.
Besides the one we just did.
Yeah, not that one obviously.
That's fine.
Obviously that's never happening.
Can you story it?
Why doesn't it work?
Please.
Dude, no.
No.
Please.
No, sorry.
Okay, okay, please.
Okay, please.
It used to let you skip the cutscenes.
No, it didn't.
Yes it did.
When?
I remember skipping the cutscenes.
No you don't.
Yes I do.
It was really short.
No.
There was even a button.
It was like Chris started to skip.
No.
Yes.
It happened.
No.
It was like a long neck with you.
A long neck, man.
Hell yeah.
Well, hey guys.
You know what?
Fuck you if you're watching this video.
Straight up.
Oh, I agree, man.
Yeah, come on, man.
Absolutely.
What the fuck?
Dude, you're not picking up these studs from any corner.
Oh, oh, oh.
Because I didn't hold on to this.
Dude, wait.
A fertilizer.
Adaptive difficulty?
It adapts to our actions to create a harder game?
Why would we want that?
Well, because we want to challenge ourselves. I don't I absolutely don't want that. Oh wait what?
What oh?
Ben I forgot I forgot that's a crucial part of this. Hold on. We have to buy the power-ups that we obtained
What you already obtained them?
I'm gonna take a nap
Georgia drop out well the controller broke really or it stopped working, and we don't know why
Couldn't get it to work again
No, what's better? What's better? What's better than that is what this is?
Yeah
Oh my god, what not even close nerd. Oh my god. Okay. You know what okay?
We're gonna grind a little bit. We're gonna grind no keep playing the game
No, no, no finish the game. I know exactly. That's what we're doing. We're gonna grind right now. No
We're a secret skip. We're gonna secret skip. No. No keep going through the story. I want it to be over. No, listen
No, we we okay. It will go over every every stage that you play outside of the story. We're we're ending early
No, listen. No, we're good. We're good. We're good. No, we're much. I'm legitimately not cool with you sequence bridge
Okay, fine. Hold on. I'll break out. I'll break out. Okay good
But we would get so much studs right. I don't want them. I want the game to end
This guy doesn't even want to grind studs
People know this game are like frustrated like dude like you could get so many studs right now
You'd be able to love studying that. If you wanted to give me one of the instructions
I don't
You get here looking up on game facts
In the instruction manual. In this let's play otherwise known as a friendship simulator
We should interact with the audience. What what do you think we should do? Yeah. Hey, hey, hey, man
Hey, man sitting over there sitting on the couch front. This is a friendship simulator
This is you're just you're just hanging out with us on ironically
Rf2k is the best friendship simulator because people are like exiting and leaving the room
People are just like talking like in the background. Yeah, people are like, hey
Like you want to get this guy who's like in the house right now
You can like people right now other people are in the house right now. You can see us walk over and look
I look spectacular. Why don't you not so much? No, I look great
All right, continuing the story for you. You're fucking baby
Yes, thank you. Dude, you gotta go on elite singles. I gotta get on elite singles because I am highly educated
There's an app called elite singles where the tagline is
Like a dating app for the highly educated. Yeah, like so
So it's it's for rich people who don't want to like admit like just like say like outright like hey
This is dating app for rich people. It's it's like, oh, you know, we're not we're not rich
It's just we're highly educated. You know, we're we're just we're just highly educated. You know, we just happen to make a billion dollars
But what 82 but but but Ben but they do two percent of elite
Singles users are between 35 and 50. So fuck those old
Yeah
college
Dude, I want to fuck those old pricks though. Yeah, I want to fucking grind on those old pricks
But Ben you are highly educated
Even though you are poor as fuck what the loaches like, you know against like what is actually practically meant by highly educated
I gotta get in there and fuck up the curve. Yeah, exactly
So you can you can get on elite singles finally I I want okay
Our new segment for rfck the bin is bin getting pussy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah operation get bin late
Yeah, yeah. Yeah for once in his life
Well, did you actually change your profile because then I I think that would really
I did not change my profile. Yeah, I have to do it, dude
When what should I have it say
Who out here trying to suck dick who out here trying to suck dick will definitely work for you. I'm not not sure
I don't even think you're wrong. I don't even disagree. Do you think you think writing that on his tinder will get him girls
More than the evening are now. Yeah
What what does it say right now? What what are your current tender strats right now then? Yeah
Everybody
I'm a new communist. I'm part of the revolutionary communist party. I love boba vac. You know, I listen to the ba6 every single day of my life
Yeah, the ba6. I'm not a ba6. Yeah, you know, I'm a recently ba6. Do you play this fucking game?
I get some ba6
Yeah, I'm gonna get I'm gonna read some ba6 for you
Ah, I guess I gotta play the video game. Hey, why why didn't oh, why what am I?
It was a dead end. Why would there be a dead end? Why wouldn't be why would they gate progress like that?
It's it's it's it's open. It's open source
There's a lot of things in this game that are like
All right, we're going. What does this lead to? Oh, it's nothing. It's that it leads to
Okay, straight up if you don't get true Jedi. I was being so fucking thorough. I was coming through everything
You better get through Jedi and we better get that sub magnet before you end this fucking episode
Okay, I'll do what I can you fucking bite your lip you get a bloody fucking lip you dumb bitch get that stud magnet now
We gotta fucking get that suck that that's suck magnet
Oh, hold on. Okay. Well, obviously I have to
obviously I have to do this
In parentheses Jedi master Jedi master in parentheses Jedi master. Oh, he's he's uh anakin Jedi master or wait
This is obi-wan. No. Yeah, of course. It's obi-wan. It's done. You're obi-wan. Who even am I right now?
Oh, well, it's like a frame your plan is a frame right now. Who is who is this?
It's the cop killer, dude. Who is this game? Who is the audience? Who's that? Who's that? Who is hey? Who's that?
Who is that? Who is that? Who is that? Who is dad?
Whoa
Whoa, I told you
He loves it
Dude, you know, okay. Do that again real quick. This is how you do it Simon
You have to you have to always like you have to like like whenever you want to enter the HQ
You just have to go on these like fucking like dancing little panels right here make the jingle play
Look at this right now
Realizing it was an executive plan course their pro quo they're expecting
No, no, um, of course prick per quo you're expecting a ruler's executive
But it's not the kind you've been used to but certainly game for a laugh
That's that's the cut version of ah, no, uh, please enlist jv
No, no, okay start killer Mufasa's juvia and Simba's rowdy
Simba's a fucking jew
Mufasa's a killer. Yeah, okay. Mufasa's absolutely a killer
The arc of the lanking is Simba becoming going from a juvia, going from a juvia learning how to be around
No, no, no, no, well, that's I actually disagree with that. He goes from being a rowdy with pigma and
Mufasa, pigma and sumo
He's he's yeah, okay. He's a rowdy. Then he becomes a state. He starts as a rowdy hanging hanging out with some kind of a car
He's lying around doing nothing. He's not doing anything at all. Okay. Okay, but but he's being rowdy while doing nothing
I okay, I think the progression is clear
He's a juvia rowdy and then he has to become like a quote-unquote noble person aka a fucking bitch
That'd be mowed down in the streets, right, dude. Dude if Mufasa were here, how would it beat the shit out of him, dude?
We'd beat the shit out of him, dude. We'd be like antelope on that motherfucker
I'm ten times the king Mufasa was. We would be like antelope on the line. What does that mean?
Because he died because he got trampled by antelope. That's not antelope. Will there be?
So you dumb. I don't know what the difference between those two things are
And I don't suspect that there is none. There is a big difference
Wildebeest are just like antelope, but if you like made them barra, that's so terrible
It's not true. It's not true. It's not true. You made that up. You invented that. They're puffing animals in Africa with horns
The same they're just they're just barra antelope
Antelope are just petite wildebeest
Petite? Petite something a fucking like a wrong word to say
Not it not that sexual. Yeah. Yeah, it's it's so like it means something but like, you know what it means, you know
Like people can say things and like like they try to act like they we know they don't want to have sex
But like we know they do want to have sex when you can tell you can see it in their eyes
The worst kind of person is one that wants to have sex
Well that but even worse than that at least people who want to have sex and say that they are are honest about it
People who are like
They do things or like draw things or speaking away and which isn't like directly horny
But you know deep down that they are horny like what are I see I see artists all the time that draw like huge tits and ass
All the time. It's not that they're drawing porn, right? It's not like they are in our nuts. If we're artists
That's their job. They are making porn. They are honest about it. It's like they're trying to pretend in a way trying to not
accentuate
They're trying to not accentuate the fact that they are obviously drawing like porn and tits and shit like that
It's just it's just dishonest. Well, okay, not even that even if they don't have like the big tits and the big ass
You can tell. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, no great. When any artist draws any character you can tell based on the way they draw
Even in just the face if they want to fuck that character. Agreed. Agreed. Yeah, just the face you can tell
Usually it's the indication is
Is they have eyelashes
Well, if it's a girl like just this is just in general if there's if there's blushy if there's a lot of blushy
Yes, they want to fuck the character. I would say if there's a character who doesn't have eyelashes normally
And it's a girl. Yeah, but then they give it eyelashes. Oh, yeah
You see I'm more perceptive with uh, when this happens male characters. Uh, where do we go? Really?
I'm way more prospective with with with female characters. I want I wonder why
I wonder why because this this are tits
No, there are
Okay, muchy, where do I go help walk around? I am do it harder. Oh wait Ben's playing. Yeah, put a dumb ass
Me? No, no Ben. Yeah, dude. Fuck it. Yeah, come on, dude
Come on, dude. Where do I go? Go back. Are you looking at uh, what's this place?
Yeah, I'm trying to find the the 10 step program on how to throw the over go behind this government
How'd you find this?
Because I just came back to the to the
Table and tom we're just talking about it. Well, okay
Because because one of my friends isn't call it down every single day. He gets stopped by
The the bob of vacan uh radical revolutionary communist party
And uh, I want to point so
So there there's some it's it's really confusing you see because there are so many things that are all titled things
That I would think that I would want to click on but in fact, they're actually just dead ends because what's like doesn't work at all
So there's stuff like points of attention for the revolution find out about the revolution club of continuing interest and key questions
Of orientation and strategy important publications. I don't always question my orientation. Oh, yeah
I think it might be under how yes, oh
Duh, of course it's under how we can win wins and bold how we can really
Really and make and revolution are all in bold how we can really make revolution to do this
You need to know we need an actual revolution what we need to do now
How we can do to defeat them why we need real revolution. Do you follow? Yeah, I'm with you, man
Okay, so he has this big long prologue bob of vacan the literal god bob of vacan
In fact before I even go any further
Let me just go let me just point out bob of vacan and the way that he chooses to
Represent himself in like like on the main page of his website. This is how he chooses to to do it
Anyway, I'll also tell how bob I know but again friends in college gets off every single day by these guys
And they try and convince him to join a party a political party that that is called
The the revolutionary communist party and when you put revolutionary in your political party name
It's so disingenuous because it's like if you're a player revolution
Not gonna make that you're like your stated goal, you know, but anyway, this is bob of vacan
He'll show up real gay. He has a fucking true blooded julie, right?
He looks he looks great. He looks great. He looks way worse. Please navigate to revcom.us
Please do that so you can understand what he looks like. Anyway
Here are he he he was he's been campaigning since the fucking 60s. He was a hip the original one nice
He's need deep in communism
And he's been calling for communism and I'm just gonna read
Some I'm gonna read under how we could defeat them. This is his stated wages is 50 nights in his government and
I just want you to listen clearly to what he is saying and try and parse through all the pros what the actual
You know stated steps are so please try really hard. Yeah, okay. This is from bob of vacan. This is part of the ba6
When the revolutionary situation is clearly emerging
rapidly transform backbone forces of the revolution into organized fighting forces in key strategic areas
Carry out the necessary training
Obtain the necessary equipment and provide for the basic logistical needs of this revolutionary fighting force to start the all-out fight
While preventing the enemy from crushing the revolutionary forces at this crucial juncture
Back up these core fighting forces with millions of organized into powerful reserves for the revolutionary
Where's he gonna get millions organized into no no no ben you're not listening
Rapidly transform backbone
into this fighting force for the revolution
So like like when the red when the revolution is a situation is clearly emerging like right now
For example currently then just rapidly transform backbone forces
So that's first step that well that answers my first question
Initiate actions throughout the country
Accompanied by a bold declaration to the world
Which makes clear that there is an organized force determined to defeat the forces of the old order and bring into a new
revolutionary system upon completion of these initial actions quickly regroup forces for
Follow on actions and maintain the momentum of the revolution. Okay. I can I can agree with all
So so so tell the world that the week is this
Yeah, which okay good plan good first
Counter the enemy's superior destructive force by seeking superior force the superior destructive force by seeking to
in in italics
Fight only on favorable terms and actively avoiding decisive encounters
Which would determine the outcome of the whole thing until the quote unquote
Balance of forces has shifted overwhelmingly in the favor of the revolution so win
Yeah, yeah, well, it's like wait to fight until we can win
Utilize equipment captured from the enemy in ways that fit the fighting strategy of the revolution
Build up political and logistic basis of support in key strategic areas
But do not attempt to openly control or govern territory until the necessary
Favorable balance forces has been these are a lot of words. Yeah. Yeah
You're getting it Caroline. You're you're starting to get it
In in a real revolution none of this like means anything tactile. Yeah, so it's all like
Listen when the revolution starts when the revolution starts
We win it. We win. Yeah, basically like we transform into a fighting force
Then use guerrilla tactics to win
That's the entirety of the plan not like what cities to capture and it's not like this is for like to export into the entire world
This is like four of the united states four right here right now
He could clearly get into detail about what his plans are but but i'm sure
I'm sure that he's ready for the legality of it and like if he actually tries to ferment actual revolution
They could very easily get shit on and destroyed by the actual government
So it's just being so vague that it means absolutely fucking nothing
So why write this blog post of it if it is just you saying listen
When the revolution starts
Wait until we win
Okay, so what is this revolution for by the way? What's the problem? Oh, oh, no, no, no, no, Ben
You're way all fucking based on the way out face. Okay, it's new communism
Which is scientifically proven to enhance the human condition
Scientific communism a.k.a new communism, which is what he calls it. I believe that I believe that on 100%
I think he's right. I'm on board. You're on board with new communism. Yeah, I think so
Bob the vacant. He's meditated on communism through the good and the admittedly bad, you know of communism
That's why he's released communism to a new communism. What like new coke this time. It'll be better
It's scientifically proven to our business new communism
Did you even read the b.a.6?
I've been even reading b.a.6. I haven't
He was depressed and suicidal
He had to fuck the pedophore. He had to skip Bob the vacant's course on new communism because he was depressed
and suicidal
Well, what would you do if you were depressed and suicidal and suicidal?
I mean, I mean what mr. Mead man made a video
We all watched it and it was used to Mr. Mead man made a free game you can play
Right now click that link in the description
And list killers all I really care about
Yeah, yeah, yeah, honestly, that's like the best part of the entire occasion is was listening to his voice
And suicidal this degenerate
Uh, I murdered him. You got him. Do you see a killer guy?
No, you didn't dude. You're about to go into the kill or you're about to splatter on the floor
Oh
I got shot with a ship gun. That's bad. Dude. I love Boba Fett. Dude. Oh my god. But dude, that's my favorite character
He's rich. He's rich in that feel that feel when you walk into t-do and you and they say boba and I say
Boba fett because I fucking love star wars start panning on the desk jump over the desk beat the shit out of them
You should
You can't take high five tonight
If I accidentally breathe in your face through my mouth, you'll die. Yes. Yeah. I choke on it
It makes me cough. That's funny. Dude. I love cough the the going with the dead dude. Breathe that in through your mouth
No, when it's breathing in
Yeah
Fuck yeah, dude. That's so terrible. It gets caught in your throat
Oh my god, Ben. We're so close. Not close enough. We're super close. We're super close. We're zero calories sweetener right now. We're zero calories sweetener.
That's right. Close. I know.
Continue your story, bro. You gotta continue that story.
I must. By the way, guys, we were talking over Baba Vakyan's word, dude. We gotta continue. We gotta know how to fight the real actual revolution, which is how we refer to it constantly in bold and italics, the actual revolution.
As opposed to the other revolutions, which don't count.
Oh, this is the thing I can skip at the start, but that's what I was thinking of.
Open. Open. This is the worst level in the entire game. This is so, so fucking...
Wait, I believe it's this level. It might not be. It might be the next level after this. I forget.
Word up.
Oh, no, no, no. This is actually just a long cutscene. Never mind. This is great level. This is fantastic. This is the best level I've ever heard in my entire life.
Okay. I thought it might be. I had a suspicion.
Oh. Again. Again.
Look at it.
I would give anything to skip this cutscene.
Dude, Ben, I'm hard right now.
Me too, but it's not in a good way.
It's too much for the podcast.
Look, you're going into Saturn right now.
That's not.
This is a galaxy far, far away.
Why is someone going to piss in a jar and find out what color it is?
I'll do it. If I have to pee, I'll do it.
You can pee if you try.
Okay. When you pee and you don't have to, or even when you pee but you don't do it, right?
When you fuck it up.
Oh, no, no, no. Ben, all right, Rockley, let me know if you know this feel.
When you pee, but just sometimes randomly, it's like if you still feel like you have to pee and like you were at like mid-pee but you know that you don't have to pee.
When you have an E.T.I.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, audience, it's hard to explain.
Sometimes I'll pee and then like it will like, I'll stop.
I'll just fuck it up.
But I'll fuck it up somehow, like I'll pinch my dick too hard or something to that effect.
And then like it will feel like I'm still pee, but I'm not.
You know, I go for the twist, I go for the dick twist and it just doesn't quite...
Yeah, exactly.
Doesn't work out.
Exactly. See, Ben gets it.
Maintain the initiative, or if it is temporarily lost, regain it.
Oh my god.
Yeah, okay, I'm on board with that.
That makes sense.
That makes sense to me.
Through surprise and maneuver, fight in ways...
This guy's really thought about it.
Fight in ways the enemy does not anticipate.
Full sentence in the fight.
Carry out actions to keep the enemy off balance, disrupting the concentration and utilization of his forces and contributing to their disintegration.
Who's he?
The enemy.
So who's the enemy?
The United States.
Okay, so he is the United States forces.
Yeah.
We'll never anticipate.
We gotta make sure they don't anticipate our sneak attack.
Dude, that...
Okay, you went to a party?
And you invited the United States government?
In part of the enemy?
Maybe a little friend?
I did, I can't get enough of them.
God, Ben, do you remember when I, your truly little friend, N.Y.A., were forced...
Forced a third party to get buffalo wings on Halloween.
I did, I do.
And you know what?
It was cruel and unusual.
Yeah, because with tooth decay, Albert fucked that horse and he went away.
Nay, nay, whip, nay, nay.
Oh, you died to hit those.
You died to hit them.
Even if you jump up into them, even if you jump up into them, you die by the way.
Well, I should probably consider it then.
Yeah.
Don't you jump up into that?
The thing that you would do?
Yes.
Wait, what?
Okay, good job.
Could you just touch it, period?
Yeah.
Who's Ben?
What do you think we're trying to do here?
What are we trying to do here?
Ben's trying to get all the nukes.
Like, there's one.
Ben has such a blue or his.
There's one.
I got one.
Ben's such a kind of person who doesn't try to get all the nukes.
Always conduct operations and act in ways that are in line with the emancipating outlook
and goals of the revolution.
Yeah.
And turn the barbaric actions of the enemy against him.
To win greater forces for the revolution.
Including those who come over from the ranks of the enemy.
Oh, yeah.
So we'll be a forgiving god.
Yeah.
We'll let them.
We're going to go Julius Caesar.
We're not going to kill the people who we probably should kill.
And it worked out really good for him.
Combining strategic direction and coordination for the fight as a whole.
With decentralized actions and initiative by local units and leaders.
Relying on mass support, the intelligence this provides for the revolution.
And the denial of intelligence to the enemy.
Counter the enemy's efforts to find, fix, and annihilate revolutionary leadership and
key fighting units.
Rapidly replace forces and leaders that are lost.
Continue to train and deploy new forces and leaders.
Yeah.
It's going in one or not the other at this point.
Um.
No.
Listen.
Dude.
We got to replenish our leaders.
Directly hinder the relation between this all out fight and the situation, including
the character and level of revolutionary struggle.
Struggle in countries to the south and the north.
Let's struggle like this.
All right.
This is the final point.
What time is it?
How did I make it?
How did I get through?
I don't understand.
Just walk through.
Are you fucking dumb?
Wait, it blocked me.
It blocked me.
No.
No, dude.
Then why is it a yellow barrier if I can just walk through it?
Sure.
This is how to defeat the America.
This is the final step.
How to defeat him?
Yeah.
When the quote unquote balance of forces has shifted in favor of the revolution, conduct
operations aimed at achieving final victory.
Oh, I see.
While continuing to quote unquote calibrate these operations so that the decisive encounters
are still avoided until the forces of the old order have been brought to the brink of
total defeat.
And then fully, finally, rout and dismantle the Romanian enemy force.
That's how we win.
Did he put calibrate in quotes?
Yes.
Why?
Quote unquote calibrate.
Calibrate them.
That means they won't know that we're fucking our chances of winning.
Okay.
If they knew that, then that would just be a disaster.
In case it was lost upon you, let me read what the final action is.
When the quote unquote balance of forces has shifted in favor of the revolution, conduct
operations aimed at achieving final victory.
So when we're about to win.
Win.
If we call all the steps, if we try to win, and then we do win, and then we do things
in accordance with things that we've caused us to have and for them to lose, then maybe
you will win.
We might.
I would be how it would go down well if we conduct operations that will lead to us having a final victory
And then the tide and the balance of forces
Indicate that the revolutionary all that fighting force may win then indeed
I think that we have a good chance of
So you mean that if we perform actions that are in line with winning and the other side
Losing and we stick to those actions of winning which will put us at an advantage to win
And then when we see the goal in sight we continue to try and win
Obviously that we might win like you're saying like obviously
Can you guys put in other words, please?
We got it in the bag we solved all the problems
This is an actual
Unironic
endorsed sponsored paid for ad by the revolutionary communist party of America not a joke
They actually paid us to do this like for real like we are members of that political party
We are we are war criminals
We are literally war criminals because we've read those steps allowed if you read them loud
Then you plans that you are actually doing it get that make it right now you
Fucked up. You are so bad
How the fuck are you? Am I supposed to do it? I don't
You can float you can hover I well I hit the girl. I hit the button
Wait guys
R2-D2 is a girl right?
Right? Oh, okay
Okay, so that's a girl. Okay, you know
No
When he was a boy
By age 15
My favorite song
It's a song about family
Hey, hey, hey, you you left the shore. Wait, where did Obi-Wan go? I want him back
Hey, I don't want to be R2-D2 like your communism. No way. No way. They can eat new communism. Maybe we should win
Hey, hey, you you I don't like your the old order. No way. No way. We should wait for chances of the balance of power
Young money wait, Ben. Yeah, you totally secrets broke there, bro
Yeah, we're definitely not there were like tons of fucking like blocks. No, are you joking? That's crazy
What are what am I supposed to do? You almost walked right up to you. I almost did what now? Oh
They all put you went after me wait. No, you can't see three people can't jump
So what's even the point of them?
You need he's like an escort you have to like you have to do it. He's an escort. Yeah escort
No, no, not like that, but yeah like that
Which one is it like that you have to get three CPO from there to there
So what a dumb thing you just did a dog a dog
But don't where's Captain Panaca
Panera you think I can beat this one up Panaca. Dude Ben got us free
Oh, yeah, okay, whatever right about the guy who hit his kid though. Do we secure?
I'll tell the story. Yeah, please they were turned around
But when we were in the line for Panera bread, there was a father and a mother and like two or three daughters
And one of the daughters just like if he's I don't know what happened
The guy said that she was like fiddling with his watch or something
But the father of this young child how how much like it's like
She's probably like between six and eight. Yeah, something like that. Yeah, she looks so right
and he like
Shows her and like like on the forehead like yeah, yeah like that and like
Does that turn she like falls back and like falls into the mother's like arms
Kid like in the line of Panera bread the guy behind the counter was like what what like he came out
Yeah, like do something about it, but he didn't fucking do shit
Yeah, and the mom was like what the hell are you doing? And the dad was just like
Shoes shoes mess with my watch. Yeah, and they like all the whole family ran out of the store. Yeah
Yeah, that was extremely awkward. I yelled at him. I was like I was just like what the hell get out of here
Yeah, did you yeah, I did I was like get this guy out of here
Okay, it was okay
Well, what I want to hone in on that is is what I found most striking and that's that like the mom
Seemed like so unbelievably surprised like as if it were strange what it which it is
Yeah, well, I just think to myself, okay
You know there are people who are abusive and there are people who are not and you know if you if you're like an abusive dad
You probably have done it before and you are probably will do it again. It's like, you know
An unfortunate thing you are just a bad guy a bad guy
But what if you just you know, we're married to someone completely normal like upstanding person like, you know
A good guy then just one day you're in Panera one day. He enlists around
Obliterate your kid
I mean, I saw the woman. I mean she was outraged. I mean if this had been going on a lot for a while or
You know you'd be outraged either way
Sure
You're so terrible
Don't don't even try you're gonna lose what I just spawns me there now jump out
Oh, yeah
Where where no, I don't think so do
No, I don't think so, bro
You leave her Paul you leaving us back and forth
Okay back and forth
Stream favorite Apollo
We got him okay, we got him on the show. All right. We got Captain Pinocchio. We got Apollo in wars growing so much today
The Lord just keeps expanding
You know, you know
What that Instagram, you know, you know, yeah, do you know what you're talking about when people send
Like selfies and smoking dope when people send selfies and they
They do a peace sign over their mouth
I think I have because they don't want to show off there like this area. Why wouldn't they want to show off that area?
What's wrong with that area?
Okay, I don't know why you'd be self-conscious about that specifically
I think part of it is trying to be like out of cute in a way. I think it's part of it. Yeah, I
Okay
People on Twitter people on Twitter, maybe you want to die. Yeah, you show me like like tweets from this person
You know, that's like it's it's it's frankly say the name
I
Literally don't know but it's like stuff like wow. I'm so horny right now. I'm so desperate
I'm so sad and depressed
Also, I'm horny right now. I'm depressed like the same he was he had depression
He had to fucking know one
So it's like
I just hate people being desperate on the internet. It's such a bad look
Yeah, definitely and he probably knows that it's a bad look, but he just can't help
Fine. Yeah. Yeah, somehow. It's worse. Yeah, cuz I like expected it. Let's see. Oh, is it here?
Oh, I didn't look like it knew it. Okay. Well, whatever
but it's I
Hate seen okay. This is like this isn't like like a like a ha ha much. He hates that's thing
This is I this is feel separate in my mind. So it probably is in reality as well
I think you might I heard that I
What when I see man himself like I don't know
It's so it's unbecoming when people are so like desperate on Twitter and like God, you know, I'm so bad
I'm so gross God. No one will love me. It's just a fucking nightmare. It's so bad
It's such so terrible
I think I think we'd have to be to play
Sick that was great. What a nightmare. Good. I'm so happy. I'm off Twitter. It's it makes it made my life so much fucking better
Now I don't have to deal with that. It's it's so like it was such a
Glory situation because like I stop and I did literally don't care doesn't impact my life at all
It really did not make any difference
Yeah
You know, I said I said this in the last hour of decay last hour of decay was in
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it was I said this in the last episode
I really want to get back into like being online and social media in a way that is like
Yeah, like in a way that is actually I feel constructive
Where I actually instead of just like Twitter. What do you do out of Twitter?
You like on people you yell at people you like
Maybe maybe see an art and it's wrapped up. You're lucky if you're lucky and it's in the worst possible
Format for art. So it's not even like it's like a good place to do that. No, I do not want to look at art on a website where I cannot
Very meticulously archive it. Yeah
Which is why I like yeah tumbler. It wasn't always like this but tumbler right now
Are you sure you wanted this guy?
No, you should want to speak up. Oh god. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we got him. Oh, it's actually a trap dumbass. Oh, am I Anakin right now?
Yeah, yeah, no, what dude Anakin so hot. Yeah, exactly
It makes me mad
Dude, oh my god, that's be your Tinder profile that I'm sure of Lego Anakin
All right done. Please please please
No
Then yeah, my sense of the cantina. Yeah. Oh my god. Oh my fucking god, dude
We're gonna make it are making this happen. We're gonna make this happen, dude. Oh
My I've never been so excited for something in my child. Go back to the front. No, why why? Oh, she's fighting back
Yeah, you fucking idiot
No, other way wrong way. How should I know cuz you have special awareness?
Wow
Here gun throw it. Yeah, go through out south south go south
West west west west west here. Yes
East there. No, no west west
East east east east east east east east east east east east east there
No, no, no
Yes
Got it
No, it wasn't though. Okay. No, no, okay. No first be
Be be shut up be start
Start I'm hitting start. I'm hitting start south south south south south that's extras. No
Be you fucking do it. This guy live doesn't has never played a video game in his entire fucking life
I get I guarantee you he's literally never done it
No, it's on it's on
Hell yes
Okay, it's a magnet for bits. You stop calling them that it's on Twitter. You're you're a magnet for bits. Yeah
Here we go
Jedi battle here you go. Oh, I can't wait. Yeah. Yeah, I'm surprised you're making Ben play this
Well, no, I think he'll enjoy it. He'll enjoy it. Yeah. Well, he love it. Oh, I'm loving it
Listen, I know I know this game inside and out. Oh my look at the back. Yeah. Yeah, they're the 2d. Yeah
Dude save bandwidth
Hell yeah, dude. Fuck yeah, dude. Oh my god
Hey guys, what are you doing?
Mr.. Mr.. Meet me. Oh, can't do good
You may swing to pick up the power up. Yeah, I know now. He's just normal like that
Hey, why are all the black people like the default lego face by the way?
Because being black is enough. Okay. That's fine. Okay. It's fine. That's there special enough already
Dude that feel dude. Have you ever watched the um, the the the gindi terrorist conflicts?
He fucking whatever original 2d animated
Coors like movie
Uh, I've seen it's not a movie. It's like a bunch of like mini. It's like a mini series, right?
Is it a mini series? Yeah. Yeah, it's like a bunch of it. It was a movie. I've seen some of it
It was movie length. I believe like just all total like yeah, okay
So I probably I probably just like it was all the same deal
So I probably just like like even had to autoplay on or something. Okay, but it's even been really fucking cool, dude
Fuck yeah, dude. Look how I don't even have to go anywhere. I know. I don't look at this. Look at this. Look at this
I don't even have to think about anything
Get that blue get that blue though. Get that blue. I hardly even need to approach it together. Yeah. Oh my god. It's so good
So crazy. There is a um, there's a power up in this game call. I think it's called fertilizer or something in that effect
I saw something called fertilizer
Yeah, so when when you are on like like one of the fucking animals you can ride in this game
It will shit and the shit will be studs
Really? Yeah, yeah
Yeah, it's gonna poopy. Yeah make of the poopy
We got the poopy. We had the poopy
Look at the tootie sprigs. I know that. Oh my god. They're so bad. This is so cool. Wait, wait, go back. Okay. That one guy is like
Oh, whoops. Oh, dumbass
Okay, no, they're no other shit. Go back over there. Look at that guy who's just kind of like
Standing there. Dude. Okay. Imagine. Imagine. He's got his hooves up. Imagine that you are an elite athlete
And then you are in your element. You are running
Maxing out your fucking studs right now. You are the champion footballer. Yes, and you are footballing so fucking hard right now
I'm uh, I'm uh, Richard at the end of uh secret in the basement. I've unlocked all my superpowers
You are running to the goal as fast as you can ball in hand
You turn the side you see a man on his knees going
In the crowd in the stands just completely silent like literally like cells do not move nice single twitch
Nairying whimper you guys. He's staring at me right in the attention. He loves this. Yeah. Yeah, he loves it
You're in love and adoration in his uh in his still eyes. Your eyebrows cocked so much inquisitively cocked
So fucking hard that you explode right there in the spot. What do you do? Other than die, of course
Yep, that's the emotion. I'm feeling right now. That's correct. All right
That's
To not delete not delete any rare pokemon and I just have
At what point do you get rid of at what point do you get?
Dude, I was I was clearing out. I was clearing. I only I kept two lapras
And I dumped the rest because they're all garbage. Ben. Are you aware of the trick that we played on Tuesday?
Uh
The epic prank which didn't even accomplish its goal
Okay, some my fault or yeah, no, no, sorry. Sorry guys pokemon community
It was like some like raid event whatever. Yeah, labris china labris
We invited Ben out it started at like what was 11?
He I get there like 12 30 at 12 30. Yeah, this happens every single time every single time. Yeah, so our community day a lot
And he's always there
We haven't done it in a while. You didn't hang out with me when I came into the city for the yang rally
I couldn't why are you such a bully? I couldn't
I don't have a bully anyway
So I believe that one. I think myself listen. I have the power in my hands. I know what to do and so I told you
Today we were going to meet at 11 for lunch. We were actually gonna meet at 12
12 30. Yeah
Well, then why did you then why did you tell me not to come? No, I I I I said that we were we had just met
And then it would probably take you a long time to get there
I said, okay. What look I I I messaged you at noon and I was like, hey, sorry
Like, you know, I I didn't set an alarm. Well, hold on. Wait. Okay. Like is it too late? Like should I not come and you're like
Yeah, it's too late. Oh, I said that we had just met tom which we just had okay, but still do you okay?
Wait, hold on. I could I told you it would take me like an hour to get there. Yeah, and we would have been done
Yeah, we would have been done with our stuff. No, that's wrong because you guys didn't get here until like four
Maybe three
Okay, well past two 30 we may have taken our time
But I don't I don't think that would have been worth it genuinely. All right, maybe no
I think that we would have been just in with our food and then walking around
Mmm. Yeah, I mean, yeah, that's probably that's probably the case. That is probably the case
But anyway, the point is is that I lied to you and the lie didn't succeed. So I'm really upset with you. Yeah
Hell yeah
What lying I want to start telling you
No, don't tell him because then he'll be like, oh time now I can wait two hours extra
Before leaving now. We never have to do anything. Yeah. Yeah
Oh
You didn't have to work for that truth yet. I just it's all came to you
I mean, I've just I've just been like running around killing things and it doesn't seem to be accomplishing anything
No, you got you have targets. You have hit lists up there. Slime corpus is a bounty for destroyka for two. Destroyka
Destroyka, I haven't seen any destroyka, but walk to the center of this tree. Can you get a blinch up there?
I don't think so
No, hey, there's like genocide in star wars, right?
A bunch a bunch. Yeah, damn happens all the time. That's cool
Dude, like why just I always in fiction like why can't we just have some like in real life? Yeah
Why why are they gonna have a monopoly? Yeah. Yeah
Like I just don't like in taste
Oh there there I see him I got some oh, I got some destroyka. Yeah, dude kill you destroyka that destroyka
Perestroika you ever seen fucking like old movies everyone's like oh my fucking god Casablanca
Oh my fucking god Perestroika. Oh my fucking god. I fucking whatever the hell tell me about it
Yes
It's a good film. You've seen it. Yeah
You would think that I would think that movie that everyone agrees is good. Yeah
Good
I could tell I feel I could tell just by looking at you that I've never seen citizen king. Yeah
It's it's like I don't know. I feel like I should but in my heart of heart
It's like what am I gonna watch a movie? I'm never gonna look at the crowd. I know it's all it's so bad. No, no, it's great. Come on
Ben is so like a like objectively like wrong at liking things
Yeah, what about it?
Dude, he likes spongebob outfit king bottom. He didn't like logo star was complete. So he didn't like pop tropical
Well, well, don't worry viewers. This is a two-part episode after we're done with episode. We're gonna start up web. Yeah
I'll be on it. I'll be the cop killer if you have kids. Oh, dude. Yeah. Hell yeah. Hell yeah
Oh, dude. Yeah. Hell yeah, dude. Yeah. Hell yeah, this isn't the way this isn't the way to get me to come back to rfck
No, it was completely removed bro
Finally that's what I was waiting for
Oh, I'll come back when endless war is dead
Don't worry. It'll be that way soon if you continue the path you're on don't start webkins
uh
Like ever no, no, no, don't start webkins
Like when you're in san diego
Look up like I want to be there with you. I want us all like all three
Yeah, yeah, okay, sure
Okay, you're bro. You're bro. Get your brew on bro. Get your tea brew bro
Tea brew bro
You're gonna die dude. Get the heart. Get the heart. Get the heart bro. Get the heart. You don't fuck. Get that heart. You don't fuck
So what if I die like what does it matter? We've got the magnet
You're right. There's nothing else. You know what? I suppose death does not matter. I've got true Jedi like I have everything a man could want
Oh
Is that is that oh no kill these guys
I think it can be more guys
I think you're gonna have to kill a fuck ton of people like you're saying I'm going to kill way
I want to kill a fuck ton of people in real life. Yeah, dude. Who?
No, don't worry about it. No, don't don't ask me wait bins
You don't have to enter this we're not we're not recording right now. Uh, uh, are you playing a tape like life a life?
Are you playing a fake actions that may lead to a change the balance of the forces that may lead to
Well once we're in a situation
Once the revolutionary situation is clearly there is such that we can win the next
I will leave the next step
Uh
There we go. I need to kill these red boys
Hell yeah
About like kingpin blabba back into the leader of the revolutionary communist party
Yeah
And and and and list rep we need that we need the communists, but you have to enlist communists. Yeah enlist new communism
You know, okay
Listen, I'ma I'ma. I'ma. I'ma. I'ma. I'ma shout out. I'ma shout out the worst rfck player the entire world star party
aka
Every single time anyone asks me I pardon star party
Whenever anyone sees no, you know, that's what it's gotta be. Yeah
I I know that he doesn't deserve to play the game
In fact, I've created a brand new funk called ban under which I ban people from joining a gang specifically for star party
That's the only reason I didn't so that he's forced to live the life of permanent juby because I hate him that much
Wait, what does he do?
He's like kevin too
Well, what's up?
Well, it sounds like he just he just joins teams then wants to pardon
Yeah, joining teams and wants to probably does nothing or or or either either does nothing or like, you know
Like steals from like loot crates or something or like like the the
Okay, the people have like piles of items in there in their gang base. Yeah, so people just like like enlist the other team
They come in and like take all this stuff and
It sucks. Uh, yeah
Anyway, he does that at least I've been told well, shouldn't it be like well, wait
What can't you wouldn't it know that you are like enlisted with the other team even if you're a juby like wouldn't it know that you're
Wrong that you're not part of the you shouldn't be allowed in the gang base
Don't let he'll do it for his own game
And I'm like, oh
Or or just take it for himself. Just take it for himself. He's basically a plant kind of kind of
Uh, anyway, I figured what I was gonna say
Hi star party. I love you. Please keep playing our video game. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa
I've got I've got a plug something for our good pal
Give on taste. Yeah
Oh
I got that information. What's the word the a discord that there is a pump plushie kickstarter now
Oh, yeah, I've heard about it. Well, is it live? Yeah, it's live dude. He has a couple hundred dollars like how many hundred dollars
What's the goal? I will check. I think I just like I think it's like seven hundred dollars. He already has
Okay, well, it just went live like today, right? Yeah. Yeah, that's pretty fast
Seven hundred and ten out of six thousand fifty two
Wow, okay
How much is a how much is a plush?
Uh, I don't know
Hell yeah, dude
You know what? Okay. Thank you for the beautiful second way. I want to suck hippos dick. Yeah
Way fucking hard. We did it on the stream, but I want you around here. So it's never enough in time for a memorial
All right
PCP all of us me you
Everyone else has a yeah heaven
Pair up trucks
Ever on the pcp
Our heyday is 2016 because that's one thing for me. That's that's what everyone that's when you were releasing
Vapers. No, I wasn't were you not? No, when were you listening? I never consistently released papers. I always
I don't I don't I'm always waited until the chapter. No, I don't I don't mean like that
I mean is in uh, it was the oh my god, Ben's doing like a comic. He's not anymore anymore
He's making like comics and he's he's been on this like new podcast
That's like in like it's a fucking infancy like a sub 20 episodes. I'm not saying that you were releasing the consistently
I'm saying that they were like a new thing that you've done the rock. That's true
Everything was new things were exciting
It was like a breath, you know
It was the end of an era of a pony area of a pony area in which ponies reside
And it was coming into like a brand new like glossing board into a new era of things under which we were doing art that we had never done before
Yeah, that's long since past. Yeah
Now it's about fucking series
It's about maintained in part of the creative and which is good in its own way, but we aren't we haven't captured
That's awful. Yeah, you know what honestly, Ben? It really sucks. It's dumb. That's stupid
And I am ashamed that it's even part of good situation. Uh, yeah, everything sucks
Yeah, you know, I want to get into that actually in a second though, but just to continue on the hippo train
That was the best time because we were releasing new things
But we got the stagger you were just releasing the same stuff over and over
I mean hippo himself had like the hypocrite show which like, you know
I liked the hypocrite show when it was a thing and you know, it was released
But like, you know, it's a video game review show. Yeah, how like hip and fresh can that be?
hip was a funny guy, but like, you know
Frankly, not that cool of a thing to do video game reviews and I'm sure he'd agree with that. I mean, I think that's why he stopped doing it
It's why he stopped doing it
But this jailbabe animation
Jailbabe is going on for a while now, but you have this amount to have this amount of effort
Put into this genuinely
I'm gonna I want to say that to the day. Oh, by the way, Ben. This is the worst level
And you're gonna want to scream that
I already want to scream dude. It's so terrible. That's what you're gonna look like by the time
Um, I mean, what do I have to do? You just no, just figure it out. Just figure it out
That's gonna be just passed a mini-kip by the way
So
What of it?
um, anyway
Yeah, this amount of effort put into like an animation
There's so much fucking creativity. It's almost like he's an artist. It's almost like he's a real artist. He's a real ass artist
Hippo Craig
Easily the most alpha PCP member that there fucking is this guy's got a real ass creative job
Then he's making and doing like actual work in the real world with his fucking writing job
It has for that fucking studio and on his side like do like while doing like actual real work
I'm sure he's a lot of time
He's always talking about how much he wants to do jailbait on this
But he has to do work, you know writing with even while doing this actual job
He has time and a creative juices point in his mind and a passion for the project
Is able to make a three-minute animation in like what like two or four minutes in like what like two months three months
Uh, not sure. Obviously he has had like a lot of time to prepare for it mentally
But just the fact that he was able to do this
This guy is fucking working. This guy is fucking. This guy has
Real actual creative passion to do more than what he has been doing for the past
He's able to grow and evolve and the best part about it is that he's honing skills that he's always had
You know in the long past
Tall man world tallest man fish at the door
Stuff like that, but he's weaving into this narrative. How do I get past this fucking wall? You need bombs
What they're purple orbs find some purple orbs give so cool
Not not only is he
Outputting the most interesting creative content right now currently besides in this war
He's in this war is sick as hell and also it's me now so fuck you that's right, correct
Hell yeah, where the bombs won't she
Uh, they're they're over to the side somewhere. I think I think they're over there. Yeah. Oh i'll stop talking. I'll put you to them
North north north north north. Wait for me laser north north north north north north. You gotta hit my laser
West west west West West West West West West West. Right there right there right there. Right there
Oh, I forgot. It's not bombs it's toe cables. Okay, press a b
What?
Press B. Just hold B, just hold B. You have to carry that and you have to go bowling.
The game is playing itself.
Yeah?
Okay.
This is fine.
You have to lead it into there.
Is it here?
Yeah.
Hey.
Oh.
No, you have to do the other one.
That's fine.
I get it.
Not only is he making the freshest content right now, out of anyone else in the PCP,
but Hippo is like the nicest person ever.
Yeah.
Hippo is so nice and non-cynical and non-fucking good.
Yeah, he is.
He's such a, he's so real.
He's just a pleasant person to be to because he's not mean or angry ever.
He's just really cool.
He's a really fucking good guy.
Yeah.
He's a really fucking good friend.
Agreed.
Yeah.
I have nothing but honor for that man.
I have nothing but pure joy when I hear Hippo.
No, do you say no bad words?
No.
I said no bad words, but same thing.
Yeah, basically.
Oh.
What?
Ben, I think you have to die.
I think you have to die.
No.
What?
Why?
Okay.
That's fine.
Zero studs.
Why is it that you're in a flying ship when you can't let go over a little old custom?
Anyway, all that to say, donate to that fucking punk plushie.
He's been wanting to do this Kickstarter for so fucking long.
He's got, if you want to give him money, but you don't want to spend all the money for a plushie,
he's also doing art commissions for the first year.
Yeah.
So he wants the plushie.
He'll get art, and it also says, oh wait, it says, shh, don't tell anyone.
I guess we'll have to look at the Kickstarter to check.
There's a secret in the art commission section.
Ooh.
It says, shh, don't tell anyone.
Ooh, okay.
Well, put the link.
Take a look.
Yeah.
I'm, oh god, that's terrible.
No, that's great.
That's great.
Oh my god.
That's outrageous.
That's so controversial.
You have to look.
You have to check out the Kickstarter.
That's insane.
You've got to check out the Kickstarter.
Legitimately, that's insane.
I can't believe that's happened.
Why is it insane?
What is it?
You have to click the link then.
You have to click the link then to click the link.
All right.
Well, now my mind is racing with possibilities.
You know what?
Yeah, you know what?
He doesn't click the link.
Don't be like Ben.
I never click the link.
Don't be like me.
But Ben, okay.
You may not click the link, but have you rang the bell?
Not even once.
How can you ring the bell without putting a subscribe?
Wait, you have to click something.
What?
Well, you rang the bell.
Oh, god.
I rang the bell without subscribing.
I am guilty.
Guilty is charged.
I'm guilty of ringing the bell.
No subscribe now.
What kind of freak?
I can't wait for the bell to become meaningless and then for YouTube to not show you notifications
from the bell so they have to come through with the wazoo.
You have to click wazoo in order to get notifications.
I get a YouTube notification for channels that I don't subscribe to.
Yeah, me too.
Notifications on my phone channels that I do not subscribe to.
Fuck yeah dude.
No, no, no, don't follow that pit.
Don't follow that pit.
Do you don't follow that pit?
You shouldn't be able to follow the pit because you're a ship that is hovering.
Yeah, you're a flying ship.
Off the ground.
No.
You don't understand.
Is it like you're...
You're a hover ship.
You died.
All right.
I don't care if I died.
It gives a shit.
You're gonna die again.
So what?
Dine's not good then.
Yes it is.
No.
It means progress is happening.
Look at your little ship right there.
It's little sucks more than anything I've ever seen in my entire life.
This is the only fault of this game is this level.
The only...
The only fault.
You died.
Yeah, because I wanted to have all my health so I wouldn't die on the way.
What a nightmare.
It's called strategy.
It's called fucking being gross.
Yeah.
And...
Disgusting.
Come on.
This is your precious cargo.
Ball on board.
How I'm ball.
Yeah.
Dude look at this guy right now.
There have to be more.
Oh for sure bro.
Look at that minikit by the way.
This game beautiful.
Yeah straight up.
Look at that graphic design.
Look at that profile.
Look at that profile image right there.
Yeah.
Dude, matching icons for you and your bae.
The player one and the player two of the same thing.
You want it smaller?
Oh bro, yeah.
Hell yeah dog.
Oh yeah.
Hell yeah.
Ow.
Ouchie.
Dude, whoa.
This is sphere.
What sphere?
What are you talking about?
That's sphere right here.
I don't even see a sphere.
I don't see shapes.
Okay.
He was a ship.
He had a bull.
This degenerate.
The gun ship from like a Star Wars complete saga.
Episode 11.
Episode 2.
Episode 5.
Episode 1.
Kill.
Kill him.
Did I do it?
Was that the right thing to do?
No.
fertil the right thing to do?
Oh my Gosh.
A corpo one person who said he was so stupid.
What am I supposed to do with a ball?
Figure it out.
Just tell me so I can be done.
Hit the things with your ball.
That's what I did.
That's exactly what I did.
No, no.
The other things.
What other things?
Wow.
Okay how many things on your on screen?
One or two?
Maybe try the one that you didn't do.
do. What, like these things? Yeah. That's it? I just have to destroy all those? Yes. God,
kill me. No, I won't. You have to play more games. Hey, is this game made out of Legos?
Yes. What? God. No. Slam that shit like your dick. Yeah? Yeah. Now you have to blow up
those. Now you have to blow up those. What, those things they were guarding? Yeah. Shoot
it. Shoot it. Shoot it. How flat can you get your penis? Really fucking flat, dude. As flat
as you can even imagine. I don't think that's flat. I'm trying to think right now. If I were
to, like, really, like... If you were to rest... I think it would have maintained its shape pretty
well, actually. Yeah, I think so. If you were to rest your dick... I mean, there's stuff
in there, so there's stuff in there. Yeah, but it squishes. Sure, it squishes. I mean,
provided circumstances. Circumcision. Yeah. Dude, gang, free government circumcision.
Is that true? No, actually, he's anti-circumcision. Yeah, that's good. Yeah. Good help. Oh, my
god. I'm sorry, by the way. I'm sorry that they can eat all of your kind. Yeah. My kind?
Yeah. It's fucked up, dude. I don't even have a dick anymore. To be honest, yeah. You know,
whatever. You know, I've never known life without. It's fine. It's fine. Without? Yeah, without.
You've never known life without? Or I guess with. Yeah. It's with... Oh. I've known life
with and without. It's fine. Hell yeah. Yeah. If I was a male with a penis and it was
I would be so... I would be like, unbelievably bad. Well, I can tell you that you would be
way overreacting, because it's NBD, honestly. Like, it's fine. I mean, how would you know?
Uh, because I got fucking circumcised as an adult. What? That's true. That's true. Wait, wait.
Did you not know? Have I not talked about this? No. Yeah, no. What? Yeah, no. I had
so I got circumcised. What? Yeah, what? What's the big deal? What the fuck? What's the big deal?
What are you upset about? I'm not upset about anything. I'm just unparalleledly
surprised, impressed, and intrigued. What? I just told you the whole story. I'm about
to get on the ground and crab walk around so that you will please become a real one.
There are no more details. Pinch me, I'm dreaming. There are no more details to explain. No!
Okay. Yeah, absolutely. Oh my god. Okay, so first of all... There's nothing else to ask.
First of all... I don't think Ben wants to talk about it. No, he's great.
I dare you to come up with one thing that I have not already told you.
So, you had fimosis since you were a child. Yeah. When, like, what age are you talking
about? We're talking adulthood. Like, actual adulthood? Or, like, when you were...
He's always had it. No, no, no, no, no. My force game was just, like, too fucking tight on my dick.
No, no. I mean, when did you get the circumcision? About 18. Before I went to college.
Wow, okay. So, like, you're fucked, bitches. What was... Like, okay. So, you have this thing
wrong with your dick. What is the process of becoming a built-circumcised? Because when
you're a baby, I understand that you... What kind of a stupid question is that? They circumcise
you. You fucking brainless. Not like you... Like, like, what happened to the surgery room?
I mean, do you go to the doctor and you say, hey, can I receive a circumcision? Yeah.
And then they do it for you. Yeah. Just, like, just like that? Yeah.
No, no, no. No religion... No religious? No. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Honestly, the reason I'm pissed now is just that I'm annoyed that anyone found it interesting.
No. Because I don't... I don't think it's that interesting. And they're like, oh, what?
That's interesting, trivia. And my reaction is, ugh, it's not interesting. There's nothing
to talk about. It's not weird, man. Wait, okay, okay. Okay, so you had sex without...
You had sex with the circumcised... Or with the uncircumcised, yes. No, I never had sex
with an uncircumcised... Well, okay, but you felt pleasure from that, you know, before
and you're like... Yes. Yes, I experienced pleasure. You fucking weirdos.
You think that there's no difference? Yeah, there's no difference.
Well, well, okay, cool then. Yeah, it's great. I'm here to sit... Guys, okay, I see people
on, like, line being like, oh, they mutilate, you know, these people are mutilated. People
think it's like, you know, it's fucked up that they do this to kids. They don't even
have consent. I agree. Yeah, you should probably get consent, but... And I'm not even going
to disagree with that. But people are like, you know, if you're circumcised, then you've
been mutilated. You should be angry about this. I know from personal experience that it is
no big deal. Like, it's fine. It's gonna be fine, everyone. There's really nothing to
freak out over. Jump. Oh, god. Stand on the fucking thing. It's gonna be a nightmare.
Stand on the thing. No, you have to do it. That's not true. Okay. What? I did it. No,
you didn't do it right. What do you mean? I stood on the button. Do it. Do it right, dude.
Come on, please. Please. All right. Oh, I see. He knows what's... And he has an
uncircumcised penis, and he knows what's up. And he loves it. Yeah, he knows he has better
sex than anyone else. He knows that Obi-Wan was mutilated. So weird. I'm still intrigued.
I have no more questions to ask. What? Yeah. Listen, you're right. I don't get it. There's
nothing more to add to the situation. There's literally no. It was just such a shock. Because
I've never known anyone who's an adult. I mean, I guess I knew consciously that that was a
thing, but I had never interacted or heard anyone say it ever. No, I know. It's messed up, man.
It's totally fucked up. Yeah, it is fucked up. What the hell is wrong with you? I guess you said
already. What's wrong with you? Just got like fucking a tight-ass foreskin. Well, hey, I got
it. Yeah, it was just tight. I imagine... Okay, you know, you know, Mr. Mon... I'm sorry,
Mon Jr.? Mr. Medeker? Yeah. I love that guy. I love him even more. You know, Mon Jr., how
it has, like, a little, like, weird, like, squiggly little, like, top of its head. Yeah.
And that's what Phymosis Dick looks like at the end, where it's, like, just like a squiggly
little, like, artistic rendition of, like, flaps. Oh. I can't picture what you're talking
about. Yeah. And I don't want to. Yeah, you get it? Yeah, no, I get it. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
she gets it. If the audience gets it. Oh, gross. Now I'm embarrassed. I'm sorry I said
anything. How is it possible that two members of our glorious show have had Phymosis?
That's, like, a rare, bizarre, like, freak disease, isn't it? I don't think so. Oh, yeah?
Is it normal? Is it normal? I think it's pretty normal. Ooh. Ooh. You learned something.
I'm learning so much right now. Anthony, you could have had it. You never know. Maybe you
had it. Oh, it was for my own good. You don't have to ask your mom. Yeah. Did I have Phymosis?
Did I have Digi Dick? And she would be like, I was waiting for this day to come. Um, what
am I supposed to do? Jump. That's only for a minute, by the way. You don't need to do
that. Okay. Well, I can't, I can't make it. So whatever. There's Emperor Palpatine right
there. It's count, it's count Palpatine. It's Dooku. It's count, count them. Count, count them.
Just hit them with your big old gun. I killed them. Died. Well, soon. Well, she's jumping
all. I'm a deadly warrior. No, he's forcing you. You forced them. You dumbass. I thought,
I thought that was me, uh, force pushing it. Boy, how will I defeat him? Dude, he's like,
his movements are so like, generate when you hit him. It's just like, just fall the fuck
over. It just stands there looking at you. Radiating force power. Oh, this will work.
Oh, shit. Fuck. Okay. No, don't worry. How could I have predicted?
Just standing around. Look at this. Look at these Lego parts. I know. Wait, is he a Lego?
No. Lol. He's not even worried about it. Yeah. Bye. He's just, he's like, he just pats
him down. Oh, dang. Oh my God, Yoda. The most powerful warrior. Time to fight Yoda, guys.
I'm Yoda. Dude, I'm going fucking ballistic. I know. Dude, Yoda goes crazy in his lightsaber.
And I like, actually, though. Dude, yeah. Um, why is it playing the imperial march when
the empire is not formed yet? In fact, this is still in the republic. And these people
have not instituted imperialist elements. They haven't won yet. They haven't. The, the,
the, the, the, the balance of forces has not indicated that Count Palpatine will win. So
I don't understand why they're making measures that would lead to final victory just yet.
What was I, what was I just doing?
Hey, how far into episode two are you going to win? What is it?
I think this is close to the end. I don't know what I, I don't know what I'm supposed to do here.
This is the end. This is the end. Yeah, this is the end.
Thank God. Thank God.
Just hit him. Just hit him.
Well, he, he, he force pushes me away.
Um.
What's, what's the move?
It doesn't, it does no damn. He just had to like to get you. It doesn't matter. He just doesn't.
He just walk around and it's normal.
What am I, what does it want?
Okay. Walk around. Surely there must be, okay. Force that. Force that. Yeah. Wow. Okay.
Shreddish.
No. Okay. Just walk around. Walk around.
Surely, surely there's something around here that you can interact with.
Maybe get that power up or something. You like get that power up, then walk over to him.
I don't think that's going to do it.
I don't know, man.
What?
Oh, okay.
He's popped over.
Why would he do such a thing?
Um, is there a person with a gun?
No. It's just me and Yoda.
Do you, okay. I feel like you have to be two players for this. I feel like you have to.
Oh, maybe, maybe it's.
He's well, he's focused enough.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
All right. Okay. I understood.
It's what, yeah. It's when he's lightning one. You just got to switch.
Lol.
This game is so fun.
It doesn't even do him damage.
Yeah, it does. He takes down the heart.
Did it?
Yeah.
Oh, okay. Wow.
See?
Cool.
Terrible.
No, wait up.
Hit him.
He's grandparent.
Grandparent.
It'll do, it'll do tons of damage.
Yeah.
Look at that.
Mondo fucking damage.
Just do it.
Oh my God.
Kind of do goop.
Save this.
I hit.
For all, for all kind.
Yes.
Sliced in half.
Slice and dice.
Oh my God.
Come on, dude.
I've seen him say it.
No, when?
I read a book.
Oh.
I'm on right now.
Oh my God.
I can't believe he said it.
Three play unlawed.
Do we end?
Is that the end?
Yup.
Guys.
Three hours, 30 minutes.
That's a good length to stop at, I think.
True data.
Hey.
It's Craig.
He's offering you bread.
Did you make garlic bread?
Put it in the oven.
Wait.
Oh my God.
How do we eat this?
I'm not going to have any, but it looks great.
Craig.
Get in front of the camera.
Say goodbye.
No.
Craig.
Where are you going?
I'm going to say goodbye.
Say goodbye to everyone.
Oh no.
We saw him.
He's on the KAA.
He's coming to the crack house tonight, buddy.
It's canon now.
Shut this shit off.
All right.
End of the stream.
I'm going to whip out my dick.
This game's terrible.
Really?
Yeah, I'm going to whip out my dick.
I can't wait to never play Lego Star Wars again.
All right.
See you guys.
Wait.
I have to close the game.
All right.
Here we go.
It won't let me do it.
It's very unsatisfying.
All right.
I'm going to take it out.
All tab, you dumb fuck.
Yes, sir.
Mr. President, sir.
Take it out.
All right.
Here we go.
Get away from me.
You're stupid.
I don't like you.