Here we are on episode 9 of Rowdyfuckers Cop Killers 9, frog fractions episode 2, part 2, frog fractions 2, part 3.
You've been waiting for this moment your entire fucking lives and I know that you aren't ready. You think you're ready. You think you've been preparing.
You think that you're the biggest reference cop killers fan there is and there ever was, but you don't know fucking anything.
You don't know what you're about to witness today. Here, on Rowdyfuckers Cop Killers 9, frog fractions 2, episode 3.
You're going to be waiting to show it. This is great.
Well, there you go. There's the table of contents for this video guy.
Oh, wait, wait. Should I not have shown that?
No, it's fine.
Wait.
That's what you're in for on this lovely day.
Hang on, hang on. I'm having a problem, which is now that I've started the game, your audio is kind of crunchy and clippy and shitty.
Oh, yeah?
A little bit here. Let me close a bunch of tabs and see if that helps.
Everyone have noticed you and all the PCP just love having fucking thousands of tabs open, where if I have more than two open at a single time, I feel like I'm passing on.
I feel like I am. I have passed.
There's nothing to pass.
I have passed.
I, oh my god, this sucks.
Here.
Wait, say something?
Hey.
This is on show, by the way. This is not going to be edited out.
Yeah, starting the game, starting the game made my cursor all like flickery and shitty looking.
Maybe Discord isn't powerful enough to handle referee scopulars. Maybe you have to go to the more simple and traditional Amish program known as Skype.
Dude, Skype's so much worse. Skype did the same shit. Skype fucked the whole thing up as well.
I don't know. Can you just fucking deal with it, bro? Oh wait, does it? It happens through OBS too, huh? So it's going to fuck up for like the actual recording.
Well, I think. I mean, I don't know. I could, I could, okay, I could stop recording and go back and listen to the audio and see how it sounds.
Yeah, do that. And also, yeah, that's fine.
I'm going to do that.
That's looking to be intro though, so.
And we're back. Sorry for that.
And we're back with Rowdy fuckers, cop killers, episode nine, frog fractions, part two, episode, uh, frog fractions two, a part three.
Uh, yeah.
So I just want to, before we get into this, man, it's doing that shitty cursor thing again.
I just want to say that before we started, I ran around the game for like the better part of an hour, trying to recover all the keys and items that I had found.
Because as you can see in the top, on the right side there, my, my, I'm missing keys from the inventory only to discover that the game fucking does it for me.
And it has this storage area at the beginning where all my shit is saved.
So it was totally pointless.
Uh, yeah. And that's, that's my story.
I went to a fortune teller, like, like, uh, like a, you know, like a, like a carnival, like fucking like gypsy, like fucking like a cemetery gypsy.
And, uh, sure. And I want to get, I want to get my, you know, I want to see, cause I was just weighed with Bain breath for the next episode of breath.
I know everyone in the audience was as well.
I just had to know what, what, what, how was going to go and what was going to happen in it.
And, and, and, and so I went, I went to, I went to this gypsy, I went to this fabled gypsy to understand what, what exactly was going to transpire.
And then they said that all the sins and hatred I have cast throughout my entire life is going to come back now.
And it's going to completely obliterate me on every level and fucking take me out, uh, Adam by Adam.
And it's going to, and it's going to, it's going to be so, so vitriolic for everyone in the audience.
Cause I'm just going to have my, my, my royal of comments.
And I'm going to be, you know, I'm going to be, I'm going to be a tear to part limb by limb for all the sins and hatred.
I fucking put on to all, to all the Brony analysis community.
And I think it's time I have my royal, my royal of comments.
That gypsy was probably just a butthurt, Brony.
Yeah.
That, that, that, that gypsy was probably a fucking, uh, uh, mean commenter on her first video.
If I, if I had to guess, she had an agenda.
You know, that gypsy was probably a lightning bliss in disguise, if we're going to be honest with her.
Lighting bliss looks like she could be a gypsy on the side.
She could moonlight as a gypsy.
Oh God.
Oh, this fucking game.
Uh, have we seen a single frog yet, by the way?
No.
Just wondering.
No frog.
No, no frog.
How unfortunate.
And now I'm realizing that, um, even though I spent all that time playing this game and trying to get back, uh, Max revive, uh, I don't.
Excellent.
I don't remember how.
God, I can't, now that I have the sword, I literally cannot even go through this fucking doorway.
Wait, wait, wait.
I might be, oh.
Now I'm literally trapped.
My sword is wedged into the door and I cannot move.
God.
Well, okay, I guess I don't.
Was this fucking game programmed by fucking immigrants?
I might have to actually, like, re-boot the game, like, to get in there because the sword is too fucking big.
Uh, and it doesn't work.
That's what he said when I chopped him in half.
Because with my sword.
Ooh, child.
You get saucy entertainment here.
You get saucy entertainment.
This is only for mature audiences.
Refuge cop killers is, like, rated M for mature.
Rated M for mature.
Um, just like, you know.
Rated B for brony.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, God, I love bronies.
Can you just name a single subculture better than bronies, other than furries?
Um, breeders.
People with the sick fetish of having intercourse with people of the opposite sex and conceiving children.
You know, you really brought up a source topic for me specifically.
I once met a breeder, and let me tell you Benid did not go over well.
Did I go over well for anyone involved?
No.
What about all of his children?
I assume that he's dead now.
I mean, I'm sure you didn't let a menace like that continue to run the streets.
Well, I'll say this.
He's not going to be consummating any marriage anytime soon.
Oh, thank God.
Let me tell you that.
Rest assured, rest assured, his impotence will not be faked after our encounter.
Few.
Okay, I think we have some unfinished business.
Not in the realm of My Little Pony, even though that's all I care about within my life.
And there's no other, there's no other true as other than My Little Pony.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think we've left our audience hanging for all the real bro-on-bro action that we've
hinted at and alluded to in our very first, reference copular seven, Frog Fractions 2,
Episode 1.
God, it seems like a lifetime ago.
It feels like a literal few months ago, and it truly was.
Yeah, it truly was.
It truly was, months and years.
God, and what have we done in that time?
Nothing.
Here we are.
We're still playing Frog Fractions.
Nothing's changed, Munchy.
Nothing's changed.
Nothing's changed in our life, and nothing really ever will.
So, me and you are going to be meeting up this October.
I don't know, this might be released in January or February, but it's October 2nd right now.
And we're going to be meeting up on the 27th.
Yeah, and I'm real excited.
I am really looking forward to seeing my boy Munch again.
My boy.
We're probably going to record some sort of Frog Fractions copular live there, possibly
with some sort of weird camera perspective with Uch on the couch and like horribly close
up to our face.
Or maybe so far away that you can barely see us thus defeating the point of recording
in the first place.
Yes.
I mean, I think it would pretty much be a crime not to do that.
Yeah, basically.
The reason I'm so eager, not only just to see my good friend and frat bro been saying,
but I also want to scope out the area because it's looking like I might be there for the
rest of my life.
Shit.
I'm not fucking dammit.
I cannot get this item because my sword is in the way again.
Can't you like die angle it and then like flip turnways and then fucking like...
I tried.
I tried two different ways.
My sword can't turn this way.
And if I bring it this way, I can get my sword up there.
But then...
You're so close.
That's the best I can do.
Okay, whatever.
I don't think it matters that much.
Yeah.
Okay.
I thought this game surely wouldn't make the sword literally incapable of you finishing
the game.
Sure.
No.
Surely.
Well, I'll have to just restart.
I have to just close the game and start it up again, swordless, to go back to these places.
Even though I fucking needed the sword to get here in the first place.
So I don't fucking...
Never mind, actually.
There's no plan.
They have no plan.
God has abandoned us.
Incredible.
So yeah.
I want to scope out the area.
I want to see Lanna.
I want to see what my prison's going to look like.
I want to check out the cell before I commit the crime.
Yeah, before you buy the prison.
And why buy the cow when you can get the milk for free.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, it's my cat.
And on top of that, I'm also going to be in Boston in December as well as Ben and Nate
and Tom and possibly Digi.
So we're probably going to do a little pow-wow there as well, to some extent.
To some extent, currently not known.
But something.
Something.
Something, I'm sure.
Yeah, so I'm excited for both of those occasions.
Both of those brocations.
And so, you know, do you have any more things to say about, like, we were pretty gung-ho
about Atlanta when we first recorded all of those moons ago.
The first episode of Froggy Fractions 2.
Yeah.
Do you have any, you know, do you have anything to follow up with on?
Because, I don't know, I feel like in some ways, Atlanta has only strengthened and in
some ways, it's weakened.
Like, enthusiasm-wise.
I will tell you right now that me, I personally, I don't actually go to Atlanta proper very
much because what the fuck would I do there.
But it's nice, and it's good, and it's cheap.
Like, the biggest thing I can say is that the Atlanta area is pretty cheap, like, compared
to similar places across the country.
So that's the highest recommendation it's got for me.
And like, it's got a subway, and like, I don't know, I think, I mean, it's no Boston or
anything, but it seems like a pretty good place, a pretty good city that's easy to get
around, and that there's a lot of shit going on in.
So, and it's cheap, so there you go.
Those are like, those are my two, those are my two qualifications for a good place to
live, and I think it's got both of them.
So, yeah.
It's interesting to say it's no Boston.
Did you see the Google Doc I sent you?
I had like, compiled a giant Google Doc of like, what each PCPimmer wants in their ideal
PCPHQ city, and like, the various things that we would all want, and then I wrote out all
the cities where we were even thinking about, which included Atlanta first, then Boston,
then Austin, then LA, which the only thing written down for Atlanta whatsoever is the
pro that's in like, 96 font size, the only thing that's written that big in the entire
document, and it's just said, close to Si, and then a motocon.
Honestly, I did not look at that document because I don't really have any requirements
for a place to live because I'll just say, I'm not moving.
Oh yeah?
Like, yeah, I'm not, I'm not looking to move for like, you know, yeah.
Well, well fuck.
Like, I'm hoping everyone comes here, but if they don't, well, you know, that's fine too,
I guess.
I see, I see.
Well, well, well, there you go.
Yeah, yes.
Well, okay, on that document, me and Nate are the most, you know, active, obviously,
because me and Nate are the only people who do any bureaucracy within the PZP.
We're the one who like, you know, file the taxes and stuff.
Yeah.
Wait, you too?
Are you in there pushing pencils?
Oh, oh, oh, I pushed so many pencils.
I have lead poisoning.
I've pushed so many pencils in my day.
I'm gonna fucking be foaming at the next time there's an insulin shot in the area.
Uh, a Scalawag is the support.
Okay, according to Google, a white Southerner who collaborated with Northern Republicans
during deep reconstruction.
Okay, yeah, reconstruction.
Okay.
So basically a trader, a trader for good.
Someone who betrayed the South and fought against slavery.
Scalawag is actually a pretty.
I want to be a Scalawag now.
Yeah.
Yeah, I want to be racist.
Yeah, yeah.
Racist against my own race.
The bad race.
People should, I'm surprised that people haven't appropriated that term.
I feel like that term is more relevant than ever now in this era of white privilege we live in.
Yeah.
You know, I'm gonna start wherever I see a good man fighting against his forefather's sins.
And whenever I see, you know, whenever I see, whenever I go to the LA area to get my Roscoe's House of Chicken Waffles meal for the day,
then, then, then, and I see a man with, you know, a full beard, thick rimmed glasses and, you know, clean cut haircut,
wearing possibly flannel and an over shirt in the LA heat.
And I'm gonna call him a Scalawag.
And he'll know exactly, he'll know exactly how much love I have for him.
That'll be the secret code word.
That'll be secret.
What is happening in this game, by the way?
I just had to answer a quiz to prove that I was, in fact, 32 years old, which I am not.
But I won the test and now I get to play a super passive aggressive Xenomorph roommate irritation simulator,
wherein I have to annoy my Xenomorph roommate enough that he'll move out.
Okay, excellent.
Yeah, and I, yeah, yeah, yeah, have until 8PM to convince him to move out, so what's doing?
Well, it's short notice, short notice.
So I just have to up his annoyance and keep his suspicion down.
Current inventory self-loathing...
Oh, oh, oh! Frackzio, you know me so well...
all right um yeah yes so on this document uh me and Ben uh or sorry me and Nate were uh
i've never compared you uh me uh we were filling out shit and uh me me me and Nate were actually
rapping a lot about Boston and uh how fucking uh much we like it and we wrote down a ton of
pros for it and it's it's my first pick and his first quote emotional pick which uh take with
that what you will uh it's Nate best man mm-hmm uh yeah uh so yeah um but you know fucking i guess
wait i'm sorry i'm i'm really trying i'm really trying to annoy my my xenomorph roommate uh could
you could you could you sum that up for me uh basically me me me and Nate oh i i wanted i
wanted to see what your what your opinion on like of Boston was in general i love it it's the best
okay all right um um okay well okay here let me make the case real quick here let let let me
red pill you on on on my affection real quick i went to Boston for for for for various business
reasons back in august and um it was one of the most delightful experiences i've ever had in my
entire fucking life not not just for the business that that was that had transpired in said location
but just um um i'd never been okay like like San Diego i i truly love my hometown however um it
kind of is fucking shit and i don't like it anymore i have realized that it's not as good as Boston
because okay but like like what i had said San Diego has good public transport i truly
benched at the time but like i i i i took the subway or i guess the tea it's called uh and yeah
yeah the tea yeah and it was the most fucking transcendent experience in my entire life
it was fucking insane just how like simple and easy and how quick and like like just how like
reliable it is in every single way and how like everything's color coded so it's super easy and
super easy to get around and it's like not like it's not like expensive really i mean i don't know
it like i it's it's very good very very fucking good and a lot of time and that's really important
because i don't know um um i'm kind of scared of driving i don't know i mean i'm scared of driving
too i'm convinced that if i'm gonna die on early death it's gonna be in a car yeah yeah um same
same yeah so uh i want to uh you know uh minimize that as much as possible also just i don't know
fuck it just i i don't i don't want to i don't have to pay gas i don't want to have to do any of
that and insurance and and all taxes and all this shit all the shit that goes with a car ownership
that's why that's why i always wanted to live in a in a city so i could just fucking do public
transport and not have to fuck around with cars and things like that and and even and even if you
didn't want to like take the subway in boston like in san diego every like street is on like a grid
like like everything is super like mathematically like like you know like like structurally like
sound and like like like mathematically uh poised to make the best possible experience uh like like
like like like like size and distance wise however in boston everything's so fucking dense and the
treats are and the streets are so fucking wibbly wobbly they can just like walk you just walk like
a block and you'll already have met like five new incredible stores that are fucking sick yeah
that's what it's like yeah it's it's fucking incredible and and i love it and it's it's like
super um i really appreciate density in any way my name's digi brony i love uh apple book season
uh it's my favorite episode of my little pony apple jack looks hot in boots
is my feelings on the subject uh i the good the did you bro get the fuck out of here this is
me and munchies show why don't you put your nasty claw sink your nasty claws into another
into another internet property and it's someone else's intellectual property this is our
why can't you just let me why can't you just let me have this this one thing
he's always trying to upstage he's always trying to like like sink his fucking teeth
into our creative spirit mm-hmm why why don't you go think about shit you fucking pansy yes
here we were i really forgot i forgot to tell you we don't analyze you don't think we only feel
we we don't live we only survive and and by and by joe that's the way i like it but yeah
boston was a great was it was a great time and um um tom like lives there currently i mean like
like like outside the sea but like you know he lives there unless he still lives with his parents
right um i think so he says he he's pretty i went i went to his his old place with his parents and
he's pretty far from boston if he's still in the same place he says he's like 30 minutes away
uh maybe that seems that seems generous but okay if he says so i believe it
mm-hmm um but yeah that's why that's why i remember at least he's like he's like he's like
30 minutes like 30 or 40 minutes well i i lived like a little less than an hour from from him
and he is like to the west of me so i would think he would be further but i don't know um
here here let me fact check myself let me fact check myself um even if he was like an hour i don't
know maybe it just means i live in california but it's like i don't know an hour is not that long
to me considering like in the east on the east coast everything is fucking like providence and
boston are two major cities that are like fucking an hour away from each other yeah where if you
want to go from uh san yago to la it's gonna cost you like three hours at like yeah normal traffic
um um um here fucking tom okay okay so so sorry he is an hour away it's specifically an hour um
um but um i don't know fuck off that's that's still boston that counts that fucking counts
yeah sure yeah and and and and and and and both you and they both have family there and and you
have lived there before and i i think i take it as an enjoyable experience yeah it was great yeah
it was swell yeah um um um so you know bro dog um what do you think what do you think dude
uh oh i got you got tarros i got tarros all right i won the master bedroom is mine
incredible uh
oh shit i already had those oh well was that entirely pointless god damn it
oh i i vaguely remember you doing that last episode yeah yeah but i didn't but i didn't beat it
okay uh all right okay whatever well you know you know how it is you know how it is okay i'm gonna
go look for something called inferno investigation excellent yeah you know me and you know me and
investigations have a long history wait i gotta play okay to get inferno investigation i gotta get
snake hell uh snake hell i gotta play biker chicks and to get biker chicks i gotta
uh
okay i just okay i gotta go to a place uh sick yeah somewhere you always have to go somewhere
wait where'd my sword go oh um didn't you like dissolve it in order to enter that or something
isn't that a thing that occurred did i okay is that is that what happened i don't remember any
such thing but all right um i don't know i mean it sounds that's as plausible as any theory i'm
gonna come up with yeah okay anyway well now i can get um wait what the fuck my path is blocked
this the that that secret thing that secret thing that i couldn't get because of the sword
the path is blocked by boulders now what the fuck happened i think i'm in the middle of like a
story moment i think there's like some plot unfolding yeah like yeah like the game the game
trying to make you immerse in the way the character is feeling by by presenting an unmovable
object okay well i guess you just pushed it okay i already fucking had that god damn it um what the
fuck are you supposed to do um i don't know i do not understand what the point of that game was
i feel like i have obtained nothing from this from this misadventure in fact you've only lost
yeah sick i wonder if the mega sword will be back at my starting location now or if it's just gone
this game is a lot like life uh you toil and you die yeah basically yeah i don't have a sword
anymore all right well i don't know what's the sword ever done for you and these autocorrect
skates wait all my keys are gone why the fuck are all my keys gone all right well
oh wait oh now it's night time it's night time oh this this has to be a story moment this has to
be cinematic yeah yeah this is kino yeah it's cinema it has to be what is occurring presently
yeah if if you ever wondered what is cinema looking over there whoa whoa there's some
shit there there's them there's some fucking harlots over there there these are these are disgusting
these are just lewd and crude if you ever want to know what a breeder is look no farther
these people have fucking these people have fucking childburring hips have ever i've seen them
i'm i'm actually super engrossed in what's going on right now like i'm so invested in in i don't
even know what this is but i really want to understand oh it wants you you're under arrest
i'm in jail no okay well i didn't have that before oh i'm in i'm in the wizards hut oh my god
oh you're gonna be rich you're gonna be filled up and then the gyms are gonna block your way like
last time i lost okay i used to have the green key but it's gone now okay here's jail okay i can get
out that way oh my god okay the two-way sliders path is blocked i need the green key what the
i'm i'm super i'm so i'm super immersed right now me too me too dude i'm glad it's not i'm glad
i'm not the only i'm glad i'm not alone anymore yeah yeah i've i've been alone in awe for too long
now oh okay well i can't i can't do anything with that
i just gotta you guys you guys just gotta get that'll do this is wait we're on the rowdy
fuckers cop killers and i'm avoiding the police right now i found a grenade open oh shit let's
let's let's call some fucking like las vegas fucking like um um charlottesville shit going on right
now maybe shift oh shit oh hey these are pairs not grenades okay excellent okay well wonderful
okay gamepad support unlocked already had that that's good okay well the pairs the pairs the pairs
didn't work oh my god i'm the police are really scary when we don't have your your your your your
your good friends and your good utensils to help you achieve your goals i'm falling in love with
this game all over again i think this must be what's like to be a minority in in monday america
god damn that guy's fucking fast yeah yeah the cops are the cops are relentless
in their pursuit of justice oh that's something you can tell me to my Jesus fuck you just can't
even go anywhere near them or you're fucked
oh whiffed him whiffed him he's gonna follow you dude i think i think you think those guys have
swords i'm afraid to ask there's a good friend what's with all these like these these jails
that have just popped up what's what's what's what's what's what's with the oval office keep adding to
the prison spending keep on the incarceration well what's with that subjugating the fucking
minorities by by by by way of racially profiling them constantly what's with that then what's with
that i don't know man but it makes me mad it makes me mad and it's not and it's not right wait what
the fuck there's nothing here there's nothing here this was oh oh i had to get caught oh dude yeah
there were there were super shrubs there were super shrubs there before uh that i couldn't pass
through hey hey the the police are gonna arrest me in real life for smoking those super shrubs if you
know what i'm saying yeah oh my god oh oh it's like chess ben it's like chess it's a real time chess
oh shit this is sick actually this is actually fucking cool that was actually cool this is this
is real this is active battle chess it's fucking sick oh i would i would get into chess it was
actually like this oh my fucking god this is i would i would i would i would i would i would
actually get in chess this if this was the case oh my god i'm so excited i'm more excited than
rarity that one time she said i'm so excited oh i know that oh i know how you feel bro
come on queen i'm i'm banking everything on my queen
no fucking moron god are you hearing this music no no i can't i can't hear anything
there's some you know what they say in cool like final fantasy battle music playing
what happens before every episode the reveres cop killers i say hear no evil see no evil speak no
evil and then and and that's sad i hold myself to whenever we record these i think these are
like the roots of a giant tree or something oh my fucking god you gotta you gotta win dude
you have a such an unfair advantage here too so fucking i don't know i don't know what your deal is
oh fuck oh that guy's gonna fucking murder you not oh he is you're right
you're right along uh yeah i have a super unfair advantage i can just fucking like move as fast
as i want yeah and you're still being your ass kid true
and you're and you're still being fucking utterly you're being utterly pwned true true you know when
you're right you're right munchie and this time you're fucking right oh no they took my queen
because i wasn't paying attention fucking dammit are you a fawn are you are are are are you a
wee pony is that oh my god are you a cub that bishop is such a fucking fool you walked right
into my trap oh no i just never mind never mind i don't how do i win what do you mean you played
chess it's fast but he doesn't have a king i like to win you have to take a limit all this people
that's how trust should be it should just be about killing people that sounds hard
oh god king move right now right fucking now oh fuck god damn
you you just gotta take out this this is this is just like harry potter
yeah but better but better because it's action back
oh oh did i okay that was bad
these people are just gonna fucking trample you like they're just gonna put you into
fucking fucking ethnic ghettos and they're just gonna fucking subjugate your entire
fucking lineage so so so then and so so so then after you're technically legally uh decriminalized
they're still gonna be able to you know subjugate you these are gonna be stuck in the in the fucking
ghettos that they purpose liquid went to subjugate you that's what they're gonna do to you right
and fucking now and there's nothing you can do about it well if there's nothing i can do about
it then i guess i should just accept my fate and that's and that's exactly what i'm gonna do
hey oh hey whoa whoa whoa i gotta get that i got that's like an item that i need
oh god no he's gone dude he's going oh oh oh he's hopping he's a this is the most fun i've
ever had with a video game this is really good i'm really proud of myself yeah me too
oh can i get him can i fucking get him i think i'm gonna get him oh my god oh my
fucking god i have to yeah taken fuck yeah taken taken three taken two like yeah you wrench out
i've oh and i've got the sword back for some reason oh that's a big item that's a big item yeah i did
it i fucking did it okay i'm supposed to drop it somewhere what the fuck oh well luckily this
phases through walls yeah kind of although i can't even i can't even see where i'm going anymore
wait no like actually where am i supposed to go oh oh wait i know i know i just have to like
there okay cool the key the key generator we've just pirated sony vegas 12 and we're ready to get
our key generator uh that's really to get our key that's what i that's what i do every day for fun
i pirate a new copy of sony vegas and give it to a family in need
mm-hmm you know what starving kids in africa need they don't need food they need they need keys upon
keys of of of legal sony vegas copies yeah they need those subs dude they need those
like like dude like dude why not like okay here's how we can solve the fucking hunger crisis in
africa like they don't need they don't need food and water and supplies and medicine like we just
have to get them a shit we just have to like tell them like here's what you do here's what you do
africans just make top 10 videos about undertale and the money will just start rolling in all right
starving all right starting african child all right all right all right yeah you can poke them uh
here's what you do you you you watch the show my little pony friendship is magic and in each time
an episode comes out you just used to crank out like like like like a five to ten minute video um and
you just have to make leave to make a pony so and barely animate it and each time and in each
time you do you're gonna get flocks and flocks of subs so you just do that and then after a while
just you start a patreon and then you continue doing that until the day you fucking die yeah and
and that and that and that and that's you're gonna make it big that's gonna that's gonna pay for like
you know a well a well for you to get clean water and like you know medicine for you know your your
aids epidemic and all that other good stuff that we're imagine imagine african warlords so inspired
by digi brony that he's just so he's just so inspired that he's he's ready he's ready to spend
all of his money and all of his war torn all of his fucking slaves his war slaves and all of his
child soldiers putting them all the work with brand new like like nineteen uh fucking ninety five tech
and make them all like clack away every day making a new mile of money review mash he's just like
you know i think i've done pretty well for myself as a warlord and now i like i need a hobby
yeah and like i'm really into like western it like western animation is really going through a
renaissance right now so i really think i should do something with that
like you like it like let's not lose track of what's truly important i mean you know we've
all got to have fun every once in a while we all get it you know yeah there's more to life than war
yeah
all right kids for for every mile of a pony oc mouth movement that you animate with one frame
i'll give you one loaf of bread yes um enjoy it's my gift to you for me for for for helping me in
my art my artistic endeavors yeah and you've earned it you've earned every god i'm supposed to
god there okay this is really fucked oh i figured out god uh ingenuity that was the that was the
only way uh all right well i've got whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa what oh it's a secret
it's like pokemon like hidden fucking thing what the fuck just happened well okay i think
live and let live why was it why was it pointing me that way i don't understand okay never mind
um well now what maybe i'll go just explore this is an interactive role play experience
yeah i guess i'll just i'll explore and oh i've got some more keys now now i've got the purple key
and the magenta key so um that should help that should help with a lot by the way i don't know
i forget if you if you edit this in such a way where the audience cannot see your desktop but i know
that it was visible in that one maybe you please quest video and i just want to share and all the
audience is agony seeing all these fucking files on on bin's desktop computer um there's not that many
there's a lot bin that it's enough to you just need to admit you have a problem i know it's good
it helps it helps me do my deeds i just have i keep things on my i keep things on my desktop when um
when i feel like there's a lot that like stuff i don't want to forget about when there's a lot
of thoughts and ideas in my head that i need to convey i each time i think of a new thought that
i think is interesting and i'll make an audio vlog about i'll write a notepad document on my computer
on my desktop uh yeah and then if because if i don't leave it on my wait i do i not have the
cyan key fuck god damn it just like storage i think maybe okay i'll go back to storage no i didn't
have the cyan key before i thought i got it though because like look at my inventory that looks cyan
doesn't it i mean i don't know that looks like blue that would describe as blue i think well that's
cyan is blue cyan is fucking bright blue okay well i think that might be okay i think that's
actually green uh and it just like looks looks blue because of tricks because of tricks and yeah
because of a clever spell because of because of pranks yeah due to shenanigans do do do emotional
manipulation that that that sure looks blue um what what were we talking about we're talking
we've gotten off track we were talking about how i want to move to boston is what we were talking
about i need that cyan key so fucking bad um well you should i mean boston's good i think i mean i
think you should move to atlanta because that's where i am but yeah i would never blame you for
moving to boston because it's a great it's a great city and it's a great place um whoa would
you see that guy running yeah i did i think i think it's a thief yeah he looks like a thief
i i have good eyes i've worked in a kevinia store for 35 years i know a thief when i see one
yeah yeah um that guy just he just had a certain he just had a certain air of um arrestability
about him you know i'm not gonna jump to conclusions here ben and you know i'm not a racist or anything
but when i see an ethnic what when i see an ethnic walking into my bodega i know
shit my bodega uh oh i found fuel for my autosword oh oh excellent worthless
oh excellent my autosword ran out of fuel oh what a shame what a fucking shame
uh i'm trying to get through tight corridors with that
you're dead yeah there's no there's no way maybe you can slash the thing i don't think so
there must be another way there must be another way to fucking achieve our goals
let me try to slash it no
no
what i thought maybe i could possibly
maybe the autosword like will actually help oh wait no the fuels i already ran out of fuel
it's too late yeah maybe i can break these barrels try try try doffing skates they don't make
you run faster uh i need the white key to doff the skates okay or you should already have them
take it away i do not have the white key um no no it says to take off the skate so i guess
yeah yeah the skates are already on this this skate i complained about this last time when i run into
a wall it like automatically changes my direction and that's what the skates do that's these are the
skates in action right now excellent i'm just holding up okay good yeah um oh god frog fractions
too all right this i don't know what i'm supposed to do here i feel like oh
yeah i i don't think uh i don't think i have what it takes for that challenge at the moment
uh well fuck um we'll never catch that ethnic red handed just just like how i always wanted
someday i mean we live in a world of possibilities speaking of real shit we alluded to we alluded
to a project of ours an ongoing um um business venture um in the first episode but we were
going to try and reconnect to our roots and you know regain our emotional stranglehold over the
pcp and all of its and all of its uh tentacles yeah yeah and be like real human beings again
yeah and and reconnect with our humanity and not be fucking twisted emotionally stunted freaks
yeah for a change perhaps you know if at all possible yeah um and and so we've created the
real friend initiative where um roughly every week or so around sunday i believe we we try and
pop into a call and you should know uh spitfire you know you know you know rhyme you know um um you
know fucking you know all those sort of uh quote unquote lit activities yeah yeah yeah um drop
unbelievable beats how yeah we've been it's been uh challenging uh it doesn't uh work yeah it sucks
yeah it sucks um we tried it last week and very quickly very quickly it devolved into like
okay here's where we're moving and here's what we're gonna be doing in the future of youtube
so i left because i don't care um law um um i i okay well personally i love talking about
moving since i don't know um you know it's um it'll be my first time but but i will admit that
the youtube is not what this is for no well that's what that's what like like digi came in and then
it all became like okay what about what business opportunities are we looking for in atlanta
and like news to me that that's even a consideration i don't i don't see it happening
like fucking what are we all going to become jeff no fuck it it's pointless it's all pointless
and retarded you gotta voice those concerns dude if you just you just gotta voice your opinion
you just you gotta you know when when when when when when when shit goes haywire and and and when
and when you and when you feel bad you gotta talk about you can't bottle it up dude i guess
i guess you're right but no i feel like nobody's i feel like no one's on the same page as us
munchie like i feel like you and i are really just in it to have fun but like digi and davoo
and nate are just and and and tom and major only kind of sort of here i mean i guess they're just
yeah they're they mean they're just here to have fun too but like digi and nate and davoo are just so
they're so fucking business focused like there's there's so economically viable it makes me sick
yeah well so i don't i don't know i don't have anything i don't like have anything to say about
that whole aspect of it and it makes me mad sometimes i i don't know and i and i feel not
excluded okay maybe a little excluded i don't know i just feel like the conversation isn't
what i wanted to be so sometimes i get frustrated with the real friend initiative for that
well you know news news bulletin board turn on your tv click off of charlotte's
bill and you will see this currently what i'm about to say uh you can speak been
you do have a voice i but i don't have anything to say you can just say i don't have anything to
say and i don't want to be part of this conversation here's what we should talk about well i can i can
do the first part i can i can i can say i don't want to be a part of this conversation but i don't
have a follow-up of like alternative conversation that i do want to be a part of um i don't know i
agree with you that you know like like like no matter where we move to i think the business like
like i don't know it's not like we aren't in like a good business location right now like like i don't
know like like like not really any of us like i don't know like i think no matter where we go it
will work out because i don't know i like the pcb is only growing like it's working out fine now
like yeah i mean the plan was when we move when me and divu moved in with digi like divu thought
there was going to be stuff happening and i was like okay i was like down with it if stuff was
happening like if we were doing stuff and making stuff it didn't end up happening what ended up
happening was i just fucking did what i was already doing and then since i've left i've just
continued just doing what i was already doing so like i think what i've found is i don't really
like sure i'd love to live nearby all my pcp buddies and stuff like that would be great but
like i don't have any i don't have any expectation of like oh if we live together
we can do things like we can do things together i'm just i don't think it's going to make a
difference like it for my like work life whether i whether i'm with whether i'm physically near
to anyone with the exception being of lectures because i would do more lectures if i live near
the pcp and lectures are those profitable thing like both of the most popular pcp videos are you
and my lectures so yeah you know yeah um yeah so i god i'm i i regret so much not doing another one
at radcon too um it's i'm i'm gonna fucking rect i'm i will do another one like as soon as the pcp
is all in one place or even just a few of them i'm doing another one it's like it's so important
um um definitely definitely i i have a few ideas for lectures i don't think i'll be able to follow
up the dark jane one but you know it's something to humble probably yeah i'm gonna get into it um um
but yeah i don't know i i i i i'm i'm a young fella i i i i i'm a young baby boy and so yeah
young buck a young buck a young suave man yeah a young child and so i don't know i i i i i i i
i am with digi somewhat and you know everyone well i like in the sense that like i don't know
it would sure be nice to live in a place where you know uh you know opportunities and like
the sky's the limit and and stuff that effect but i don't know no matter where we are we like i
don't know i i don't buy that like for a second that there's like nothing that we are going to
like do together and like we have to be in like a fucking like you know through through like fucking
like la or like you know filmmaking sort of area i don't buy that for a second like like yeah like
we're oh no matter what is like like we were talking me and you were talking about how rag
com 3 years wants to be a chilling out uh you know uh sort of like real like real like real
friend place hangout time and you know nay didn't really understand because you wanted to just you
know work and do stuff but like see the thing is is that all of us are fucking broken and we all
just want to record let's plays and things we all want to record we all want to make stuff and
that's what we that is just what we want to do naturally maybe not do like the fucking grind
or anything but you know we we we aren't you know we we we like making things we are content creators
so we're always going to do things no matter fucking what so we could live in fucking tim buck
tour any or you know anywhere and we would still be making content together there was nothing
that's going to like change that uh yeah that's what that's why i'm saying it doesn't i don't see
i don't i don't i'm no longer think that a pcp headquarters would like really change all that
much it would just really yeah um i don't know i think it would change a lot and i think everything
would change a lot and be really nice i'm very gung-ho about the idea i mean no no matter where
the pcp hq is i will go despite my my yearnings for a specific location yeah i'm very dedicated to
the idea um i i don't think it's gonna change i mean i would like it a lot because i would i would
have very happily be in things with people but it's not i'm i'm not gonna be like radically
changing what i'm doing on my own because they're because i'm near y'all i i don't think it's about
like i don't know like there's there's like it like i think everyone trying to like think of
like specific things that we can do that like are in live action that that benefit live action
specifically it's kind of missing the point of the entire thing because like like like everything
we do rather as copulars it's perfect example everything we we can do we like we can do it online
but it would be so much easier and like there's no there'll be no technical difficulties and
we'll just be funner and better if we were just in person like everything we do more or less
would just be better if it was in person so it'd be like a spruce like you know we'd spruce up our
fucking lives and and and all that sort of jazz i feel pretty spruce yeah i would feel pretty
fucking spruce and i don't know it's important i i know like i have offline friends here and i do
and i love them dearly but nothing can fucking top my fucking love and and my love and admiration
of my fellow fucking pcp brothers and and you know um i really want to be by you guys specifically
because um i feel like you guys are really cool and i like you so i don't know um it like if you
know even if there was no business aspect to it even if i didn't truly believe that it's just
going to be better for our content to be together in the same room in any way and we can always like
make new content we don't have to just like stick with our old stuff but like no matter what it's
going to be better in every way even if i didn't believe that i still just want to be by you guys
just because i like you and it's it's good for me emotionally to be like be near people who i like
yeah and i think i think it's i think it's a legitimate uh you know reason to want to you know
move um i think it's i think it's legitimate i mean i'm really hoping that it that it happens
but like i said i'm i'm all all this is to say that like since i don't see it as being like
that much of a game changer like i'm i'm not moving just for pcp headquarters so that's why
i'm like uh you know like it'd be i'm just i'm just kind of hoping i'm just hoping it works out
but if for me like everyone comes here but if it doesn't well that's life
yeah um um uh well you know whatever happens happens and you know pretty much i mean i don't
know i i i want to be near you so so you know i don't want to be near you too much you you're my
you're my bestest buddy you're my bestest buddy as well um yeah so you know whatever we go we go
yeah and and that's and that's i guess that's the really all to say on the matter uh on that
particular subject i really i don't know maybe maybe not for you specifically but i think no i
think for you i mean like like being in live action will affect like like we don't have to like
always record what we're doing but just like being in the same room together is going to
breed so many new opportunities just for like everything just just for everything that the
opportunities are fucking limitless for what you can do when we are together and we are like
available actors like i don't know none of our current content like your choirs that
would be in live action but it will just enhance it in in ways that we just cannot even like tell
yet like like like like like if i were to be able to speak to you in the same room that'd be such
a different energy i mean we would and like we would be less tired and groggy because it's like
it's it's fucking like 10 in the morning and you know it would be a far different experience we
could just do um you know whenever and it would be a completely different atmosphere and it would
make a a much better project product all of the let's plays and fucking radcon were like so incredible
and the ever so much better than than they could have ever been if it was just us talking over the
internet being being together in the same room just like breeds such like like just great content
and you know i'm like fucking like like you know me and you are gonna be doing like comics and
stuff so that's not really thing you can like do together but that doesn't mean like you know
like being around people and like and like being you know close to one another in person will not
affect it in some way because you know the experience you have or you're gonna like write
into your comic and it's kind of like you know um fucking you know change change it's gonna change
your fucking life to like like i don't know i fully perceive like my life is gonna be completely
different once i fucking move to the pcbhq not like in like a fucking like you know everything's
gonna be different way but like in like you know i'm gonna be around like like you're i'm gonna be
around people who i legit legitimately love and i'm gonna cherish every fucking second that i'm
with you guys so like i don't know i mean it's gonna be it's gonna be a difference gonna be a
different different sort of uh experience it's really gonna change uh malik on life i believe
truly yeah i'm fucking hopeful i'm fucking hopeful that it that it happens and i mean i
think it would be good i mean i i'd like it but i think everyone would like it and we'd all be a
lot less miserable um yeah the the or sorry the real friend initiative currently though is pretty
awful it's pretty awful and no i feel like you know is it shitty of me to be like nobody's doing it
right um i don't know i mean like like with my friends i want like i want to talk about real
shit i want to talk about like real things and well like i don't know i do want to chill and hang
like move like like moving specifically i i am more than comfortable with because i don't know
it's it's a big thing that's on my future that i that i want to like but and i want to be serious
and you know um fucking normal and not fucking freakish like i am online yeah um i want i want
to not be a freak for just a few moments of my life yeah well that's a total order but
yeah um um yeah so in theory i understand yeah um i i like that aspect but you know um i i don't
particularly and like i don't know i like talking about the future of pcp and stuff like that but
i don't know i i i do as well just want to you know chill and hang when i'm there um i i i don't
want to like preclude any conversation topics because i don't know um it's important and i don't
either the ratty fuckers cop killers like it almost immediately you know it was when nate
showed up that it became like let's talk about let's talk about yeah let's talk about the future
of the pcp let's talk about pcp headquarters and that's fine but it's not what it's for and it made
me mad um yeah i believe it's not what it's for but i don't know like like i don't know it's it's
on all of our minds it's it's it's it's what i'm thinking about a lot yeah i guess i guess
whatever bro um i i do i do agree though i i i i want to you know i don't know maybe you and
me should just do stuff um yeah maybe that should be what happens i don't know yeah i guess i don't
like how everyone else does does things yeah i should just take it upon myself
um i don't know i mean i i i like i like the real friend industry but it's it's
it's just such a pain to talk to my friends it's just such a fucking hassle in order to do it
it's like like there has to be a scheduled time which which is what we wanted like in our video
but i don't know it's like it's like harpy's i don't know i'm i'm i'm doing stuff i i want and
not like business stuff like i don't know i am just existing and so it's hard to like you know
like set aside time and do it davoo has been the one who's constantly been doing it and i'm very
thankful of that and i want i want to do a friend initiative yeah every single time he's been there
i think at least close to that yeah and i appreciate i appreciate that but davoo's also the one who
immediately wants to talk about well no no that's not actually not true he he talked he he has a lot
to say about the business side of things but he also has like talks about his personal life and
things so i i appreciate that yeah davoo's good i i would like to talk more about the personal
life stuff on yeah i mean i don't know it like like is where we live not personal stuff i i guess
it is i guess it is but fuck i just i just hate you know what i just hate the fact i just hate
the fact that everyone's youtubers i don't like youtubers or respect them and uh i think it sucks
and when youtube stuff comes up i just want to tune out uh so yeah that's how i feel about that
um understandable yeah understandable um um well i'm gonna try and be in more since for a while
there i kind of skipped not not because i didn't want to be in just because i was doing uh stuff
this remember was a very busy month for me uh fucking well oh god i need to drink some more of my
for some of my starbucks double shot energy mexican mocha flavored i'm almost through my uh fruit
punch pure zero rock star here uh it's a treat it's a treat and a treasure uh and my favorite
thing i found monchi have you ever heard of aldi no well it's just it's like german supermarket
and it's like a it's like a piece of shit and it's run like garbage but it's really cheap so that's
the trade-off that's what that's that's aldi um but i found these off-brand knockoff monsters
that are actually pretty good they're like they're 99 cents for a full can of something
that tastes almost like a monster yeah and i love it it's called it's called gridlock
it's it's it's it's called it's called the future and yeah yeah it's called it's my future that's for
sure yeah um excellent do you think there's anything more to say about us being uh not freaks
do you think there's anything do you think you think we're doomed to be freaks been you think
we're always gonna be like this um i think i mean you and i you and i want more i don't know how
everyone else feels but like surely oh wait oh here we go all four decided
in the 2004 election uh i was saying i mean it takes two to tango so if nobody else wants to be
real friends if nobody else wants to fucking have anything
going on other than like oh let's fucking let's fucking get our fucking youtube let's get our
push our youtube and get our fucking sub counts up um then fuck them uh it's like it's like it's not
just on us you know like it's on everyone i yeah i think we're supposed to do here's just take
it you're supposed to like write all this down and like write the map of the area then come back
because like there's gonna be no light switch when you come down from below who's like it wants
you to memorize what's going on here so like yeah you're gonna have already got it i've already
got everything oh well then fucking skedaddle yeah i don't there was no point there was there was no
point okay cool okay cool yeah super good super good uh yeah like i don't know i mean i would sure
like i feel like i feel like i'm i'm far more forgiving of the youtube aspect because i don't
know like i like that's part of their lives and while i hate it it's all been i'm just i'm just
gonna fucking say it it's been it's been this no this has been a problem for me forever it has
always been that like the piece ever since the early days of the pcp whenever the youtube stuff
comes up i just i zone out and i stop paying attention and i don't care and i just i hate it
i i hate that whole side of it i want it to stop i wish youtube would never been invented um
it's boring and it's like i don't know man am i crazy i just it always feels the same every
time it comes up it feels like the same conversation it it more that part i completely agree with
it's it's a lot of the same sort of stuff but i don't know it we just all want oh my god i guess
i just blew up all right awesome yeah cool like like like it is it is the same shit over and over
again but like i think it's like we all want to like make sure like of what we're doing because i
don't know there's a lot of there's a lot of i don't know is no there's a lot of um you should get
you should get you should get out you should get out of there okay there we go okay i just need to
figure out what i need to blow up um excellent yeah there's a lot of like you know i'm sure and
in this life snive decisiveness about the entire subject of you know the thing on all of our minds
like is is like where we're going to move that that's what we're all that's what i think about
every single day i fucking wake up that that's where i that's where my mind goes sure like and
and and like i don't know not for like like i don't know i understand the business aspect of it i
understand that and like you know i'm sympathetic to it but i i i want to move to be close to the
pcp no matter where that is i i want that just for myself so i can be i can be sane
yeah i mean i guess i feel i feel yeah it's it's not yeah i guess for y'all it's like a big a big
deal i'm i like don't have anything to think about on that front but sure yeah you know yeah i'm
i shouldn't complain about i shouldn't complain about that part because that part's legit and
it's like a real thing that like is going on oh well what's what's this the fairy queen sent
that big green thing down here to help with sanitation each of the head serves a multi-tool
pipe cleaner uh all right excellent gross this game is incredible by the way yeah oh my god oh goodness
oh okay well um yeah um um i i just think i just think that uh like like like like once
okay we should decide here's here's what i think i think we should decide where we want to go
based on like where we like want to live and like um because like i i know i know that no matter
where we go it's going like like the business side will work out because it's working out currently
and we aren't in the same place you know like we we are all in different locations so no matter
where we all are it's going to be instantly better and like i don't know they're like they're like
best possible solutions but i don't know i i want to i want to be happy where i live sure and i don't
know i mean every place is pretty much the same that's the secret that's the secret about that
sure but there's a little court there's i don't know there's a little quirks
boston was way different than san diego i i guess slightly i don't know it's different
dude that might just be a west coast east coast thing though okay i've almost i've almost defeated
this uh this piece of shit here this fucking asshole he is oh no he shot my bomb this is
this is fucking scary this is so good this is the best game i've ever played oh i got shot but
it doesn't matter he's dead he's dead excellent i guess three heads really aren't better well they are
because it took me three bombs to kill it yeah instead of one so it's definitely better um
you really got ahead of that challenge though yep heads up you're the bomb okay yeah okay
yeah yeah oh bad puns oh good good what
fuck yeah uh what were we talking about i'm talking about how we hate our friends
yeah i hate them they're the worst um i don't know wherever the pc phq may be um no no no not
not even that no no matter where i decide to spend the rest of my life i hope it's somewhere near you
been um well i feel the same way i hope i mean i'm i'm not i'm not moving i'm not moving because i
have a real good stable setup here but okay it's my hope that uh it works i mean i was i'm real
relieved that it looks like digi wants to move here nate i think will go wherever digi goes um
and so on and so forth so if uh that's this is what i always hope that everyone would just
end up moving here and it didn't uh so it's that's still my hope for the future yeah um you know um
um i i i i i hope so too again no matter no matter where it is i'll go yeah i'm i'm i'm
committed um do you have anything more to say about on on just to follow up on on episode one
do you think there's anything you think there's anything more to say about about about about
being real friends other than uh whoever's listening fuck you for trying um yeah um
oh i found the white key uh cool i don't even know what i'm supposed to do with that um about
being real friends uh i wish it weren't a fucking sham uh but it is so fuck it uh i mean i i feel like
i'm i like i'm partially to blame here because i don't know like i like i enable it and i don't
know i i like it on some level but i do agree that it should be it should just be hanging out time
so i don't know next next next next time i'm gonna be i'm gonna try and be it i'm gonna burp
uh next time uh it happens i'm gonna really try and you know um just just relax um i mean isn't
that that was the point right that was the point all that was the point i don't know like it like in
my brain i i i don't know i i i i get a sick sort of satisfaction talking to being serious um sure
i i get a sick sort of you know uh you know fucking you know in in the core of my being
i get this sort of like you know fucking like sicko fucking you know a creepy skeevy sort of
satisfaction from like taking myself seriously and you know talking about things that matter to me
but you know um like gaming hardcore and you know um acting like a fucking asshole is good too
yeah i i understand uh there's sometimes sometimes they bleed into each other sometimes
without even meaning to just sometimes it can can just be like a reflex the meme power can be too
strong yeah into real life i feel you don't i feel you yeah where do i um yeah um i i i'm
i don't know if you're planning on being anymore but i'm gonna i'm gonna try my darkness to try
and turn turn the ship around on the no i'll still come to the real friend initiative i haven't
given up on it yet yeah yeah yeah um um um the last one the last one was pretty good before before
you know but before the um you know the the the the tidal wave of emotions can yes yes garbage
disgusting fucking statistics
uh wait wait wait wait wait whoa whoa whoa what's what's
shepherd there you are here's the report on those donuts you asked us to get
we fought the black hole suns mercenary group for control of their great treasure the crawler
of despair when we opened the donut box was empty their leader laughed in our face says
i'm crazy biotic girl eight a long ago i think come on nice hey hey you smell like mass effect
to save uh yeah i think i think that's what that's what's transpiring around here yeah
oh here we go here we go i think your name was walter wait no jack we couldn't get a lemon
cream donut on trident because i'm jerky to assassinate all the bakers the rs specs it was
this guy thing creos is sworn to spend his research's life assassinating evil people that's cool and
all the evil bakers though we mistakenly received a donut for someone named Miranda Lawson but
these servers operative showed up and took it uh bakers sucks fuck off i'm not reading this whole
thing um we we we get a frog fractures to your quirky nice job fucking freak
are you supposed to like read like all the white letters at the beginning is that what's
supposed to be transpiring here with the white letters yeah like the the first letter of each
line is white compared to the yellow oh it is but i don't think it says anything wait why is it like
that i don't know it's just uh that's strange just okay all right um thanks
okay well okay all right good good um do you think do you do you think perhaps
perhaps it's time to start the show oh wait i killed that guy oh no oh shit it's cool he probably
deserved oh shit that guy that guy who was that guy who kept saying i couldn't pass without a sword
he he lived by the sword and he died by the sword yeah uh oh well you know no baby this is his own
fault no fucking biggie bro i i i know i know that feeling no i feel i feel no biggie every
completely in my life each time i wake up and i listen to hypnotize and i know there's no other
with us i i feel i feel that no biggie i feel that look at that that face went no biggie
god there's nothing i want more than to get through this fucking laser but i can't do it
do you think do you think it's time to stop you know dancing around the issue and fucking you
know tackled this bull but by its horns yeah yeah it's probably time to get into um the real
the real shit the show the show the real enemy initiative
yes um i think it's time you know we stopped we stopped denying our fucking nature and it
would go back to recording we we we go back we go back to you know spray our vile filth all the
computer screen and i'm thinking five people who are more more emotionally sound than we are yeah
we have to go back is what you're saying yeah um so yeah we've got uh we've got shit
we've got shit that happened there was fallout there was fallout from the last rowdy fuckers
yeah yeah um it was gay and uh nobody liked it nobody had a good time all right speaking of
which by the way some some a special guest for today is is being antsy so i'm gonna i'm gonna
assure him that we're gonna be ready real soon okay real soon what are we doing first what's our
what's our first order of business um um um i feel like i feel like we we we we should gain
closure first i think we should regain closure so so i think it's time i think it's time
phantom horn yeah yeah strawberry milk you bastard you you you scallowag
hold on let me let me just assure this fucking this the this villain he is a fucking villain he's the
worst
fucking sick all right uh
fuck yes okay i've i've successfully
um maybe maybe we should start this guy this this guy thinks we're wasting his
fucking time why don't you go tab on over to wait he thinks we're wasting his time his valuable
time god damn that's oh my fucking god the the utter insult
this guy thinks we're trolling him we're we we've never trolled in our fucking life
it's been an hour and a half like if stuff came up we're going to be ready real munchy lull if
you're not trolling god help you what the fuck is he talking about i promise you don't waste your
time these are just fucking long well the first half hours what are we gonna we're gonna like
watch what do we you want to just jump into him first or do you want to yeah yeah yeah fuck fuck
closure let's let's prove we're no better wait wait so we're so we're gonna we're gonna we're
gonna watch his video right we're no we're gonna watch our video of us watching his here let's let's
get it get it open first yeah yeah get it dear viewers um here here's what we should do
we should um um um fucking okay we're we're gonna do is we're gonna invite our our
good friend fngr on on on to our show and we're going to watch uh right first cop killers eight
fraud fractions episode two fraud fractions two part two with him so we're going to be
we want to commentate it we're going to do commentary with fngr of our commentary of fngr's
videos which is a commentary on our original video well his isn't really so much is his video
commentary on our original video there might be a little bit there might be a little bit
okay so so so but you know he has a response he thinks we're trolling him so we so we have to ease
so so so why i think what i think is is is let's let's just say let's just say let's just lure him
into a false let's just let's you want to say like you want to clear the air we want to like go
through this video and like and just like we just want to clear up any any potential like bad blood
you know we want to make sure there's no fucking bad blood between yeah yeah yeah we want you know
we all just want to be friends here yeah um he already thinks that it is a trap so you know it's
gonna be it's gonna be like i assume like like once we once we really get into it okay here okay
here's how we sell it we're just like fngr we don't fucking understand what you're talking about
like what the fuck fngr can you like just explain it to us yeah right like like we don't like we
don't we we don't have to be too too saccharine about it like it's a generally benign as a
generally benign but not overtly friendly gesture of like fngr what the fuck are you talking about
yeah well i feel like we should also just you know rap about something we should also just say you
know like like like there's like again there's no bad blood we we we just want to talk and you know
like like what like what was your impression of our first week let's just start with just talking
before we jump into you know um the intense fucking guerrilla that we're going to saddle him with
yeah yeah yeah yeah um do you also have his it's like a pd a dramatically i have it open do you
want it um um i i have it here i mean it's pretty easy to find yeah yeah yeah um um you know um i i
do have it so so so here i didn't read the whole thing but i read a bunch of it um and i watched
that and i watched that guy's video about like how anthony fucking like challenged him to an internet
debate and then bitched out of it which was hilarious um which is gonna be what this basically is
yeah yeah yeah um i hate him let me just let me just make sure that uh i i have the exact time
code open real quick here for for the watch together okay um um um hold on just just be quiet
second will ya sure hold on hold on
all right all right all right here we fucking go here here here here here we go i have everything set
up everything immaculately timed i have i have every i have every base covered there's no way
this can go wrong at all and there's and there's no way all right you want to start a call with uh
anthony i i think it's time i think it's time okay let me let me go pee real quick i'll be right back
okay go ahead um um viewers the viewers viewers at home i want i want i want you i i want you right
now to to to type in your comment uh predictions about how you think this is going to go because
okay i think there's only two options he's either going to like bitch out immediately and not say
anything funny or to like say something funny and then like like like like like trying just to not
post it which we won't and we will post no matter what occurs um yeah so like okay and literally
has this the setup is like usually me and bin record locally with um you know audacity but now
we're recording uh like bin's getting my audio through obs so even if he tries to bitch out and
like delete his own audio we still have his audio on record and there's nothing he can possibly do to
fucking clear his name or you know state his case um we are we are villains we are we are villains and
there's no there's going to be no respite for our soul what once we pass on and we're going to completely
and utterly be fucking you know uh internal damnation and fucking fire and brimstone for the
rest of our miserable existence um and really i think that's all there is to say on the map okay okay
i'm back i'm back um bin would you say we're devils yeah okay excellent let's get in the
he was a handsome devil but the kind of devil you like jfk oh oh oh yeah we're like that
handsome start up let's fucking start it up i'm clicking on general right now okay
um here we are wait not yet it's authenticating
oh dear
oh dear what happened uh shit
oh no
oh
i um
all right all right
god
okay
okay sorry about that uh there you are there you are yeah it's guy uh discord like crashed
i think because i was trying to join a voice call already in another one um excellent really good
german engineering there yeah um i sent a message on both discord and twitter and he doesn't seem to
be coming this fucking idiot like less than 10 minutes ago he was like we were we told him we were ready
hey man there's no bad blood don't don't get worked up yeah yeah we're just trying to clear the air um
i'm like i don't know i guess i'll i guess i'll play frog fractions while we wait for this piece of
shit this piece of human garbage to respond oh my god i hate him so much no spin spin
we're not we're not like that anymore we've turned over a new leaf oh yeah i forgot
um if only he would show fucking up i mean i don't know like i don't know we did take a long time so
i guess that's true i guess that's true i don't know i don't blame him but um on the other hand
fucking why don't you scroll up and let him read all of our conversation by the way
look have you seen his tweet by the way have you seen his tweet regarding this recording
no can you um can you can you post it yes i i i i i i i i i need to be right happy to
thank you yeah um wait was it about us yeah oh my god he's definitely he's definitely
onto us he's definitely onto us but i just hope that he can find in his heart to play our victim
to play to play our game yeah to play our game
he's like a fly into our spider web
helpless um so so do you think we are drama youtubers now do you think we've we've we
we have officially fucking oh yeah absolutely yeah definitely we've we've gone we've we've
completely crossed the line yeah there's no there's no saving us anymore this is what we do
yeah yeah yeah this is what the show is now this is this is our entire lives in fact
every single day i just wake up and i think about f and g r and i think how can i how can we
how can i extract how can i mine how can i mine yeah yeah yeah uh where did oh wait okay it was
this way i remember apparently there's a secret second game in spraxis uh so i'm gonna go and
get that for many many meta layers this fun video game i mean this this is pretty much
meta layers the game the movie wow this is really this is this is really upsetting i don't think
he's coming back dude this this is this is truly distressing he was here like minutes ago minutes
ago he was here you know what i bet he fucking chickened out just like he did just like with um
mr meeketer or meet me toker or whatever that god did you did you see that did you see that video
about anthony i watched a little bit of it but you know what i remembered what like when when when
he made a video on us he didn't watch our video he just watched someone like he would just watch
mishandler upon his video and then commented completely based on that so i just figured why would
i even give him the grace of doing that i was gonna go completely in blind just accuse him of random
things um yeah um anthony is he he just fucking the the the short version is he mr me toker whatever
his name is he um he made a video about inflation fetishists and in that video he made a unrelated
comment about god is dead like you know as a joke like haha ooh it's so bad ooh faith in humanity
lost ooh god is dead and we killed him and anthony got but heard about just about the simple act of
saying god is dead um and he never heard that before i guess not so he called him out and was
like debate me debate me on whether god is dead and uh and mr me toker was like oh uh oh i found it
it was like okay i will and anthony got scared and was like okay well i need to bring my posse
along with me like i'll only do it if my friends can be in the call with me and mr me toker agreed
to that and was like okay fine if if that's okay you're you're yeah bring your fucking friends
and then even after that he's still anthony still chickened out waited till the last day
said he had to work but then was tweeting at the time that uh he was supposed to be having
the debate with it with the guy long miserable if a coward well um god god the sad part is i
feel like we he could have been on if he would just did this earlier maybe we made a critical
misstep talking about our friends and how much we love them probably that's usually a mistake
um god damn this is really this is truly distressing this is this is really this this
is making me upset yeah this is a bummer um six minutes ago you know
what what what are we to do we're i'm i'm i'm really sorry audience i was just i was just i was
just as happy as you were i was i was i was just as excited
um i was surprised that he was actually i don't know this is i mean this is a pattern of behavior
for him mm-hmm i don't know i mean we assured him i think we sounded genuine i think
i'm gonna like
okay let me see this tweet wait
oh yeah yeah i blocked him because he fucking is an asshole and was all and said uh
oh yeah i blocked him after he was like i'm so i'm so i'm sorry to hear that after i posted that
my friend died because like fuck you you just made a hit video on me mm-hmm uh yeah he's
fucking blocked fuck him um but i don't know um try and you know you you know when he's here try and
try and save face just for the just for the sake of the content but think of the content
think of the content i i do love the content
and you know once we once we we reveal ourselves speed to be mad villains to be to be to be utter
to be utter evil beings then then then only then only then will the truth be uh truly uh uh
witnessed uh by uh
men by ben um if you are a female ryfogers cop killers fan please um leave this is not a space
for you boys oh yeah yeah that's true this is this show is only for with the bros for when you're
gaming um hmm well i just got a candle
you know i'm sorry i'm starting to think he did say he was gonna be doing hold on what exactly
now i'm doing stuff i don't reply hit me up on skype or twitter i'll try i'll try skype i'll try skype
it's peculiar to me that you use you use a skype you know when when when you're this vintage you're
just like you gotta use analog yeah um the analog uh skype is the analog version uh you know skype
is like discord or skype is is does everything discord can do but better and for free yeah yeah
um excellent munchie lol if you're not trolling god help you i don't know what that means
did he mean if you are trolling maybe he means like this is unprofessional you better be trolling
or else you're gonna look like a real you're you're gonna look like a real a dumb man oh heaven
forbid heaven forbid we lose face in front of f n g r um hmm i don't know man i'm i'm i'm curious
what is it what is his angle i don't know i'm just i'm just gonna mess someone's
skype and say hey man uh hey man we're ready for you you want you're messaging him on skype yeah
when i first messaged him um when i first messaged this boy i um um i was like hey my phones um my
phone's about to die so i'll i'll talk to you later today and then i took like two weeks to respond
again he's coming he's coming he's coming he's coming oh my god oh my fucking god thank goodness
do you have the video do you have the video ready on watch together we're just gonna talk to him a
little bit and we're just gonna like be like hey man we just want to figure out like let's just
say like hey how are you doing how are you doing hey yeah hey dude hello hello can you hear me yeah
Anthony hi so hey i'm gonna turn your volume up uh on my computer yeah you're really fine i'm gonna
do that as well yeah you're on air by the way in case that wasn't clear good should i turn my game up
or is the like shit or what uh i think you're good that's fine i mean yeah yeah okay i can i can hear
you just fine yeah the funny thing is the minute you said you're good and i was like i just hit
render on my video and i was like oh okay i guess this works out yeah you sound good sound good
dude i i got i gotta tell you dude i gotta tell you dude i don't know why the fuck you're still using
skype i hate discord with every fiber of my being discord skype is so terrible i hate discord you
couldn't pay me oh i don't know what's wrong with it oh yeah that's that's another thing like when
freaking they they kicked me out of discord or uh out of fucking pub calls like oh thank god
i don't have to use discord anymore the only reason i was still using discord
oh i'm a pub crawl and i said like hey i was like hey cider no hard feelings like it's totally
cool i hope you get your doctor thing everything's fine just you should have just asked me to leave
it'd have been fine i was why did they kick you out of the pub crawl yeah yeah we're behind i could
assume i don't know oh yeah i got in and went argument with asher because he sat there and started
talking about capitalism with shit or some shit like that no that's all right i've only seen capitalism
is bad he says using his computer yeah i've only seen like two uh of the of the pub crawls uh i saw
a few back in the day but back in the day i was pretty into it because you know i was i was a big
uh digi fan boy yeah sad i kind of i have to apologize etc because i kind of ruined the format
a little bit because he's like you got any advice i was like well they they're like two hours too long
let me well you know shorten them down to like 45 30 minutes and you'll have it better but
that works for like attention span but it all the pub crawls that were really good that like
where they would go all deep and shit wouldn't happen anymore because of that and i'm like
fuck should we just shut up well well well well sure sure go anthony i'm sure you call it fngr
what do you prefer uh either or it's fine man i appreciate it all right all right um anthony is
my name in case you didn't uh know so it's great yeah i forgot i forget your real name sometimes
yeah quite often in fact so so so each time ben's gonna say anthony i'm just gonna get like this
weird sort of this this like weird claw in the back of my fucking spine well just call me fngr
then yeah okay okay fngr it is yeah so um well godfucking damn i forgot what i was gonna say um
well yeah anyway it's good to have you on i hope we don't seem too scary here we just um
like like like as as i'm sure you can tell by you know our video and by us not knowing if you
got kicked out of the pub crawl we're not we're not super into this uh whole community more but
we are i don't know it was a big part of our lives so we're still pretty no no this is what
happened originally um i i had like a couple of my friends like hey ben's talking shit about you
i'm like what no no that's never no then i don't believe it and they're like oh it's on this for
our video and i'm like and they're like you wouldn't take that shit from us you're like you're right
i wouldn't i don't i don't remember if we specifically i don't think it wasn't much i don't
think we did we we like we touched on you very briefly yeah i all admitted i had a bug up my
ass and they're like it was it was very kind of like off the cuff dismissive thing i don't know
but maybe it was because like right afterwards i tried tweeting him like hey ben are we cool
you're like yeah whatever and then like you kind of goofed on me a bit when i kept asking it up
because you you like you kept asking and i didn't you like i didn't know what you were talking about
and then like i was like what are you talking about and you wouldn't tell me oh i was i was
assuming that i was like oh i thought we had heat or something all of a sudden and then the no we
didn't because like i didn't even i didn't even talk about you in that video yeah so so i was so
i was confused that you were asking that like there seemed to be anything to clear up so that so
that's why i didn't that's why i was i was like oh i was talking about yeah part of my reaction
was um i talked to uh freaking again i asked my friends and then i saw the video go down i was
like oh see it's nothing we're cool up it's back up again he thinks you're a faggot um yeah so really
we just want to have you on to you know catch up and you know clearly like bad bloods in the air i
mean i don't think i don't think you know any of us are really i don't know you know like i don't
know if we consider each other friends but you know i don't think we're enemies at all no i don't
i don't have any real problems but it was just one of those things is like you know what this is
going to be one of those things i'll just do it and then forget about it um yeah sure i mean i don't
know um um like like i don't know i would understand if our video was you know an attack piece on you
but i don't know like we we we mentioned you for maybe like 30 seconds in passing i don't
mean i i truly don't even remember what we had to say and like i don't know it was we talked more
about vita we talked more about vita we did dig into vita that is oh no that's fine here i'll
yeah we can get to that now currently yeah so what what what happened with vita or something like
that is that we were good friends for like the longest time and i don't even know why you stopped
talking to me originally but he currently hates my current girlfriend he's like sending her like
pictures and leaving notes on da and like steps on how to hang herself and shit like that oh good
good yeah i don't i don't yeah i don't want to sit there and say well you know because people
throw around online harassment like nobody's business like the shit's going out of fucking
business but i'm like hey i i could take a hit and she's not so good at it so i'd prefer he just hit
me that'd be better yeah sure i feel it um yeah so so um how did you originally find our our our
our original frog fractions video i had a couple friends and fans go hey what about this and yeah
i know i didn't have any problems with it um i'd listened to procrastinators a while ago and uh it
wasn't like the length or anything like that i i'd like to format when you guys used to do it on
jesse's channel but uh your first one was on what was undertale uh no our first person was nuclear
thrown oh no no i know i'm sorry the first pcp was on undertale yeah you're right oh oh god it was
wasn't it god yeah i will look again i probably you know maybe i was just in a bad mood but i was
listening to it and i hear like nate's really busting his ass trying to get the podcast over and
bends over there heckling him but i'm like ah this just isn't for me um you know you know i i don't
think anyone will you know deny but nate does the work the hardest um i i think i think it's the
casual atmosphere that makes the pcp like like what it is but you know um um did you watch uh the
original video i assume not completion because i don't think anyone has a time for that other than
our fans um i mean even them i think are pretty like touch and go about it um uh did you uh you
like you like saw missy antherpony's video on the subject right um i glanced at it and i was like well
it's kind of all over the place i didn't hold you up on the the the keyframe thing if you would like
me to speak on that frankly i'd be glad to yeah yeah sure go ahead okay you're probably you're
probably not going to get this analogy are you familiar with um some he's he just had like a
big boxing fight i'm trying to get kind of a greger do you know who that is no i don't i think i
think i've heard i think i know i think i know the name greller okay so long story short he's
this mixed martial artist because he's you know irish and stuff that's the the the nationality
you push because it draws money i don't know why the the the irish are bred for that yeah but you
know it sells well and the way i've described keyframe and i say this with all due respect
nope nobody jumped on me i like keyframe we're cool but i i've said her her push is equivalent
to conor McGregor it's not that she's bad that i could see what if ben ben was annoyed that
she got a lot of um opportunities that other people didn't and i could see where people
would be resentful and that's how i'm going to very gently do that yeah she she does have skill
though uh i'll give you an exclusive which she she oh yeah no doubt she spoke highly about you
got uh she talked spoke highly of ben's freaking she loved the picture you know uh what was it
knights and beta armor she laughed she laughed her ass off but that's why i got away with it too
she was dating goldie that thing yeah yeah i remember that i have it on my i have it on my
i have it in my shame folder somewhere you did a lot of work for that money ben i appreciate it
uh yes i'm that's i i i do my best i do my best uh in all things um anyway yeah the the keyframe
thing uh yeah i never uh there's been there's been confusion people have said that i've called it a
scam i haven't called it a scam like i don't think there's any like outright falsehood or anything's
being misrepresented strictly speaking but i do think that like you know it is getting it did get
sold a little bit it did it did get swept up in that shitty brony thing of like it literally anyone
deserves money for any reason i should have warned you her dad just passed away oh well that's that's
fine but this doesn't really change anything all right we're a little brutal here on the right
okay jeez man um i mean i'm like i know my condolences my condolences yeah i'd like to quote
that i was laughing uncomfortably there sure um okay yeah well i think yeah um um so yeah um miss
for our first firefighters cop killers like frog factions we um like like originally we were just
playing a game but the the really shitty website we were using like didn't allow us to progress any
further and so we were just we just got pretty bored but we didn't want to stop recording because
you know like it was pretty short and also we just wanted to like see if it would just work we just
came back to it later which it did funnily enough i don't know how but um yeah so uh we just like
sort of tabbed over when we started you know google searching what we were talking about i i think
before the show there's been something about like like like like like some sort of like brony uh
stuff i forget we just was on our mind for whatever reason and so we wanted to search and and you
know me and ben were both heavily in that community uh me especially i was i mean well he actually made
a show so him especially but you know yeah yeah yeah um so we wanted to you know go back and it
didn't really it didn't start out as like a hit piece person i don't i don't i don't think i would
even describe as a hit piece because it's not it's not like we're doing you know intense research to
drag someone down like i don't like our intention with the entire video was not to like shit on
anyone particularly well i would not to like like to like spread rumors or like fucking like smear
campaign anyone we um we were just we were just grouchy we were grouchy people we wanted to fucking
you know um it was it was funny and it led you know it led to some stories from our past i think
we're good entertainment for our fans so that was the real like mindset going into it it was not
like you know let's fucking you know let's let's obliterate these people's souls uh it was just you
know um these people a lot of people not even you just you know some people like uh dr wolf
and fucking or some other people like some like like like like kp and lightning bliss or we had
like real like history and stuff and then fucking josh scorcher especially we had like history with
these people that we wanted to have you know air now oh no because like you're free there was
dr wolf at any moment in time yeah yeah like we kind of we kind of conspicuously hadn't talked
about the whole pony thing like since since back in the day uh so i mean i felt like it was time
that we that we uh that we air out that dirty laundry and what better way than our not on our
fucking weird side show that no one watches yeah yeah well i actually think that thanks to that
video it's getting pretty good views now so i guess you know thank god i i guess trauma does
really does sell well oh it does oh it's definitely sure to be sure um i think after i think after
this this whole saga we're gonna go back to our you know uh staying to ourselves because you know
the uh the well it does get views the response is usually not i mean it's been it's been a lot of
bullshit uh and other such i mean a lot of a lot of a lot of what you might call drama has erupted
from it which is like that's fine that's fine and everything you know but like i got you i was
gonna say doughnut took it kind of bad on the chin at the time i feel a little bad about i think i
think i went a little hard and i'm like the things that i complained about doughnut are are things that
i think are true and that annoyed me but i feel a little bad that i went so far as like to just
overall say you know he sucks he's an idiot you know wow i didn't even know about all like i said
i focused on myself uh look there's there's there's critiques i'd have on the burning
doughnut i don't want to go into it right now unless you really press me for it i was i was i was a
little too hard on yeah oh that if i really was like trying to grot then i would have been like
ah maybe i did maybe i made this how dare you the burning doughnut fuck the world of you didn't
have all the money in the world we still threw you a couple of bucks here and there wait i don't
remember that i thought he did the mayor i don't know my collection but that's never here nor there
i guess um yeah um we you're gonna touch on up on that later but uh for uh you know with with you
we um like like once we had made the first five practice video we didn't i i thought it was a
possibility that people might you know um make a whole big deal about but that was not really my
intention i didn't really expect for the amount of response because um the like like a couple days
afterward we got this long like 20 minute video from misanthropony and i think like maybe even on
the same day or like maybe or i think i found them both on the same day um there there was a video
by you that was about like i think us and then lily p i believe i have a series where i touch on
fucking yeah yeah you know whatever the fuck i feel like rambling on about yeah yeah and i was
like okay i think your part was like what two to four minutes i think yeah i think i think it was like
i think it was like four minutes like four they did put it at the start i'll be honest yeah yeah
did want it to be seen yeah yeah um true and yeah uh i i i didn't think of my wildest dreams i would
become the star of youtube drama but but i guess if i'm gonna be in drama it might as well be brony
drama because that's the most fucking interesting one of course of course it's the only interesting
one yeah it's my personal favorite highly recommended and and so me and ben we're talking about it and
and and and we and we were really surprised and you know we like like like on some level we were
fucking ecstatic that that that was that like that like the like like especially with misanthropony we
were pretty much blown away about uh the sheer level of incompetence on display that's true hey
look look he contacted me they said i'm doing my own thing you go do your own thing go have fun
yeah that's you and you and i'm be over here um you know uh you know ever since this last
fifth i think we have some sort of closure on that subject but yeah we were just i at least had never
been in you know in the spotlight like that before so it was a really interesting experience uh so
yeah so so we made um a second video uh what the the way it went is we made five fractions one
a video on that just one video and then uh right now we're recording our third episode
rough raw fractions two and on the first one we didn't talk about the pruning drama but the
second one we did and that was the um that was the one that went up on t-baff uh benzel channel
and that was the one that was like like like five hours long because we had a lot to say on the
subject uh so what we did basically was we just watched through um santhropony's video and you
know um picked it apart more or less and then we and then we watched uh your video and we didn't
really know uh we didn't really know your angle at the time uh so yeah um have you seen have you
seen our our response i didn't see the response i basically like i said when my friends came with
me the second time i was like look i feel stupid for the fucking first reply it's from what people
said it's at the end of a four hour video and i was like well if it's at the end of a four hour
video that means don't look that means like like i should have took that as a hint that's how i
be read it the first time like if you put it at the end of three hours it must have not been that
big of a thing i read into it too much like an idiot and if i keep fucking digging through three
to four hours every time i'm gonna look fucking retarded so i'm like yeah let let let ben be ben
fuck it yeah indeed um yeah um yeah maybe i was slow on bullshit that week i'm gonna just shock it
up to that i yeah i mean um um you know like like we we we we definitely wanted everyone we touched
on we we touched on you missy on the point and then some of the comments uh there's just one reply
by vita that i really wanted to bring up uh that was a really funny exchange that happened on missy
on the ponies video i'm gonna read that right now since i don't want to forget it because it's one
of my favorite uh comment chains of all time it's something along the lines of uh vita saying that uh
he doesn't want to like like like like he heard that i was saying something bad about it on the
ponies video and he was like munchy i don't watch that channel i have standards ha ha
whoo whoo whoo whoo uh like he laughs covering his fucking mouth like a fucking rich person
and then and then and then someone uh comments vita you're using munchies artwork as your avatar
right now which i think the way i think is incredible can i get that for a sound bite really
quick i want to get that repeat that one more time please um vita you're using munchies artwork
as your avatar right now yes right now talking about standards as as we speak
yeah and then he responds with some like some nonsense like waffling about like oh no well
this is fine but you but but everything else is bad or something his response was this is this is
iconic this is iconic yeah yeah yeah munchie sucks but this particular piece of his work is is just
too iconic to like it's just it's just it's just too great to let slip through my fucking stubby
fingers yeah yeah oh unfortunately i can't even find that comment because missy had probably
took down his original video which is uh i remember it yeah i remember oh god that that drives me
insane i'm sure i'm sure you can like internet archive it i think i might have a save as well
but but you know um it trust me it was incredible oh no fucking every time miss anthra pony takes
down one of his drama videos like just scores and scores of untouched gold is lost to the yeah
yeah it's really upsetting what a shame what a shame um so yeah um like like there was a there's
a lot of stuff we talked about um like we really dug into miss anthra pony but both yours we didn't
really like know what was going on and so we like we didn't really know what your like angle was
and i think we like know now um i think i think we like know you know it like it was a big production
or no i didn't i didn't even want to hit ben that's why content i reached out to mage i was like
is ben angry at me i think she's like oh just go ask her just i don't understand why you thought i
was angry at you based on that first video because like we seriously didn't say anything about you
okay i'm sorry yeah it's fine i'm a little mental what do you want it's fine i think we are um but
yeah we were just really like like for me i was concerned because yeah because like we didn't say
like anything about you i think we like mentioned your name i think i think the worst we said about
you is that you were friends with the video which which is the worst thing you could accuse someone
with you know um yeah um but like yeah and and and and then we get to your video and like like
miss anthra pony's video was like you know talking about how like the video we made was like a bad
video which while we disagree with that it was still like you know about something but like we
were confused by your video on like multiple levels and we didn't really like like like we were we
were we were a little hurt we were a little we were a little hurt i think yeah you said some serious
you said some real some real shit in that video and we were we were confused and we're not asking you
apologize we just you know we just want to make sure that like our fans know we don't hate each other
okay i'll put it to this way everybody listening if you're gonna do something wrong do it right
yeah if you're gonna if you're gonna hurt somebody's feelings don't half-ass it well that makes sense
yeah that makes sense uh but there's a large section of our of our you know like there's a
large tradition in the right focus cop killers of like going in and like like looking at our
responses and like see and like in like seeing the way people are reacting to us and going to
watch together and like you know um editing that uh uh like like like in in in the episode that went
up on tbap that the section where we uh you know responded to all of our uh you know all of our
responses from the center party knew was in uh watch together so if you wanted we could watch uh
that right now to like to like see you know like to help like clear things up because because again
we don't want there to be any bad blood and you know we were a little harsh too but i but i think
i think you know we've come to an agreement here that you know there's no bad blood yeah sure no
problem all right yeah sure here uh let me get that right here shall we shall we uh begin shall we
take a take a look oh i just want to i i feel annoying for having to throw the same person
under the bus but i'm i'm pretty sure if you see the name foxwell or night eye die in your comment
section this person is does not speak for me that you're not my friend they're not my fan
foxwell or night eye die yeah okay no yeah he yeah he's he's been distanced from a lot of people
when you say i'm thinking this was mishandler upon these people what what what what exactly
does he do yeah what's it what's his name what's he all about when when he gets himself into
trouble he'll be like mentioned oh i'm associated with us and thus and like no no he's not with us
weird so he's just like a weird commenter i guess um
he he or is he more sure i'll put a deal like this do you know who fallen wishes um i know a
little bit i i i i i i i i i i have heard the name i believe it's someone's girlfriend
everybody's somebody's girlfriend muncher true yeah well a long time ago i i dated her a long
time ago okay and he he got brought along into a lot of groups and after she left for reasons uh i have
that whatever another time uh okay he would screw up just enough not to be tossed until eventually
he was and it's a long headache that's uninteresting so so just like he's just
like a weird kind of ski v guy that used to be friends with you and now is he
now is kicked out I would know he was never friends he was okay so he's kind
of hung out he was a plus he was a plus one that was not removed okay the
original person left okay um all right I got a picture now here Ben do you want
to um quickly quit the game real quick and are we hang on are we am I so are
we screen sharing no I'm just gonna I'm just gonna just record the screen with
OBS and we're gonna be in the watch together right now okay yeah so we're
okay one second one second here I have a time stamp it might be a little bit
before I start but we can just start watching from here just enter this and
I'll start when we're all in here and again um we get kind of harsh because
we just don't really know what your angles we just you know like like no
hard feelings this is not us trying to grill you here okay yeah yeah um Ben what
hurry up I'm sorry what are we doing getting the fucking watch together did
you post the link okay here we fucking Ben's old Ben's always late I'm always
I'm always discombobulated there we go I'm in I'm in all right Ben yeah I'm in
I'm in the main frame all right so so the way we do this is like we just click
play here and then we want to have a point you can pause it too whenever you
want so whenever you want to pause and or you know say anything just just go
ahead and do that so we know we aren't talking over each other so yeah so so
without further ado here we go let's listen to our you know our response of
your video me but like yeah for fuck's sake I just it's just completely
my audio sucks in this by the way like he is doing everything that we
we didn't spend I mean I don't even remember what we said like so I'm gonna I'm gonna be
interested I'm gonna be interested to hear yeah this is as new to this is
like that oh here here we go I skipped too far
it's too fucking long been the scrubbers and back here and I know I know I'm
sorry our video was not a hit video here let's just let's just let's just quiet
this down and then just let it roll I'm sorry I'm sorry for the unprofessional
baby jeez Louise here we go here we go here we go here we go should we go into
the next man that one took a long time to get through I don't know about I don't
oh god you guys talked about it free on Josephine yeah we did a little yeah he's an absolute
fucking nobody you know Vita made friends with him and ditched him it was funny oh yeah we talked
about him because he was one of the three people that made actual videos other than the comments
yeah yeah he was one of just a few yeah so so we want to touch on every base yeah I think I think
we're just like skipping over him real quick though here yeah I think we I think we actually
talk about him later pick this next one apart to that extent well I certainly do so you can just
pick it back off me here we go here we go yeah too huge this one's like mean close both this one
yeah this one's real this one's real shitty and like we have to understand here here like this one
I honestly can't even understand like what his point is yeah okay I watched this one before
obviously and I just want to I just want to let you go oh by the way we should mention that
that video you just watched was by Miss Anthropony it was called something like uh you know taking
down Ben St uh all credits you know uh that was his video go ahead and watch that if you want to
this is me covering my ass you know you lose a disclaimer anyway so this is my F and G
copyright takedown okay I watched this before I don't understand it whatsoever I do not know
what this video is all right so again I kept trying to reach out to you and every time I was
like oh look everything's cool and then like again my friends and fans like no they're ass
it off at you he's laughing at you right now he's laughing he thinks you're a joke right now are you
gonna take that shit Anthony we didn't we didn't say anything I don't know where they got that
impression um this is you know Ben St from back in the day he is laughing his ass off and you
yeah yeah I'm laughing all the way I'm laughing all the way I'm laughing all the way to the bank
to take out a big fat deposit by an oculus rift look look look what he did to pork doughnut
look what he said I do I do feel bad there's only a couple things that I actually would
walk back from a video and the first is I was too hard on doughnut and there was like one other
bronig I think his name was wooden toaster who I think was like I was a little like mean to him
when he didn't really deserve it but uh yeah like the majority of it we're not going to take a bag
yeah yeah yeah so yeah that's gonna set the tune for this it's really just funny in retrospect
I don't know like I just don't know what's happening there's a lot of times where I saw
where Ben would fuck up and he'd like you know like wave his hands off and everybody else because
they're bronies we just let it slide and I was like I'm I'm I'm not going to give you a walk today
yeah yeah fair enough you're gonna have a bad day yeah yeah oh yeah you know what the point of
that video was like like reading between reading between the lines you can understand what it is
that misanthropony feels about the video and like what it is that's bothering him that video was a
response to right for his cup of his fog fractions that was describing what happened in the video
that made him upset sure none of his points make sense but you can understand what the video is
yeah I do not understand what this for no good reason video is
just to cause harm no no good reason things he says like point to any like central idea
or like reason which I guess that's his name yeah yeah good um like this one is like basically
the like I'd like to state for the record I do have a point sometimes I just yeah sometimes
but there was I thought there was a fight going on and I mean I mean but but like the subs I mean
okay I guess we'll we'll get into it in a minute but like if I remember from what I remember the
substance of what you say in this video is basically just a bunch of insults that don't
really have any relation to the video in question um but that's but I wish I wish we
would stop fucking rambling this fucking video yeah this entire not the whole video this does go
on for a while but the part that is is like just calling us shit and like not even trying to back
that up yeah go ahead and start it are we first or we later oh no I don't I love the song oh it's
from super jail yeah this is a last minute pre-word before I I had this video done by the way
before yeah I think I'd skip with me sorry sorry I don't want to I skip the important
god so bad I think it only goes I think the first like eight minutes or so are about us
it's so hard to know like really first speaking if they're in the video or if they're in the
now yeah oh I should say that before this video came out fngr tweeted at me and he was just like
I don't remember what he said but he was asking me like are we cool and I was like what what do you
mean like what wouldn't we be cool about I think I don't even know if I mentioned him in the frog
fractions video but I think I did maybe maybe you did but he was asked all right no no I do remember
that oh no Ben you have to check this out you have to look at this thing and Ben's like
wait to stir the pot over there check what up like he was like trying to show my channel and I know
Ben was being uninterested oh I mean I've seen your channel before okay I mean I was I was on
your channel yeah no I appreciate it I got an animation from your brother asking me like are we cool
and I was like is it playing I played it yeah yeah it was real cagey and he kept asking like are we
cool are we cool I'm just checking and finally I was like what are you fucking talking about
and I forget how I phrase it but I got mad I was like what I said like what are you talking about
you cagey fuck yeah he was like yeah cagey fuck and like and then a couple days later this video
comes out oh okay and let me just read the text on screen uh yeah boy I can't wait to get to this
puke uh this puke class this is what a fail abortion looks like that I wasn't capitalized
much to such a garbage human being if he was the crap and the Davoo's diaper uh the dude who's
girlfriend's I ever read I I'm retarded I can't I can't read pretty good so far I'm enjoying this
content pretty yeah yeah pretty good content so far really in the lulls here bro really in the lulls
here I'm gonna laugh at this this is the setting of the tone for what to expect yeah yeah this is
this amount of intelligence we're dealing with here we'll get there Ben I need you to focus reach
down deep present like there's a big bag of pain chips waiting look at how he spells oh yeah no
my oh all right I'd like to answer this right now but there's a reason why I do youtube videos
is because I can't write where the shit if you have no what do you what do you pretend like
there's a big bag of pain chips paint chips paint chips do I eat do I eat paint chips
oh is that the joke like I'm like I'm retarded because I eat paint because I eat lip paint or
something sure sure sure gotcha I'm making so far yeah yeah there we go there we go there we go
yeah yeah look just look at how he spells theirs like I don't understand the grammar nazi he's trying
to make just the spelling is legendary grammar nazi as well as regular nazi situation but that looks
like a big one oh corpulent brony I remember him before I get to being needlessly bitchy he used
to patron me before I stopped doing pony stuff and then he didn't care anymore oh well I'll talk about
the classic or anything yeah every every week like whenever you I think he would like cancel his
patrons like so he could show that he was on there but not give you the money oh luckily
luckily patreon doesn't let you do that anymore yeah really yeah what a real stand up fucking guy
he did he did actually I think he did actually give me a couple months worth so like yeah but
there were a lot of them just let you know free heads up okay great okay great cool cool I've glanced
at and skimmed this anthroponist video on this topic and lifted up for attention so he can get his
sweet 20 minutes I could work really hard to pander why I'm right Ben's wrong I'm just gonna be salty
right yeah wrong about what we called chelise's bluff last night that being Tuesday to have a talk
uh by the way just pause real quick here what what is this part about I like like like like we like
I don't know I don't know what horse snooze is exactly okay you don't have to go super in
death here since I'm a student a whole a whole nother thing yeah no it's like the huffington
post or some shit like that it's like a satirical right oh god I'm not gonna defend them okay
uh they're not friends with me I wonder who woke up in the morning it's like you know what the
world needs a brony huffington post I wonder who his idea that was they cited the huffington post
actually cited why some some brony blow up doll really really really good job guys really good
job all right I guess we'll just let this part play yeah go ahead chelise in true horse news
fashion dick tucked despite having a Skype account he said that he didn't have the means to log on
to it anymore journalism folks like even if he forgot the password it would take him what 60
seconds I guess this is some guy like chickening out talking I think oh yeah she was talking about
fucking he he had to talk to yeah yeah okay oh here we go here we go goldfish I nasty youtube thing
dear ben saint I know you all right I gotta pause here and be like uh he looks like a 20 year old
silver quill like I'm sick I'm well over 20 years old so I mean thanks I guess
I don't know if I have to really explain that I don't know I guess choosing the hairline yeah
sure I just I just have to mention I can see it yeah I can see it kind of looks like a 20 year
old I'm actually older than that okay here we go I said yeah gotta revisit and revisit
where he had tried to cross over backwards to impress his fellow pcp member
why were you why were you under the impression that I was that like that this was an attempt to
impress much like this is like this is like I'm forcing Ben to fucking up dance for me and
fucking appease me it made it made the most humorous sense of my head at the time I was like
I guess it's a funny idea if I'm gonna do this retarded thing this is the narrative I'm going
with in my head sure sure yeah um I would get really confused by this later I'm like I didn't
I didn't tell him to do this it's real it's real funny you literally were like oh no no don't
Ben check this out like you literally were doing that in the video like like like for your channel
maybe but like the entire like like the entire like like the entire video was not me trying to
fucking like get like like like like fucking lasso and fucking wrangle Ben this is looking at the
shit one of the things that is the strangest to me about the whole reception of this video is the
way that like the dynamic between munchie and me is perceived because like the reality is that we're
both in here just of our own accord as like purely as equals just just talking about this stuff
just as we see fit but like I mean yeah the fngr you you say this thing about I'm trying to impress
munchie and then misanthropony has this other entire interpretation he doesn't even address munchie
no he makes this out like this is all a scheme by me and you're like my you're like my crony in
carrying out my will uh and I don't fucking get it he says at one point later later in like the
first video that like like like fuck you munchie not for like being in this field like like like
like he says like allowing Ben to do this like as though it was just as though it was just me
yeah as though you aren't equally participating yeah oh man he's mentioned me other than like
shit on my on a video series of mine which is fine and all well and good but just extremely
confusing in multiple ways okay from the outside looking in now I again I'm not like super clued
into the fucking passenger podcast I'm assuming that people on the outside just looking at going
okay here's the pecking order here's like did you at the top and I don't know where it goes from
down there because I mean well yeah I mean I guess I guess certain ignorant people certain certain
fucking certain fucking jokes of of humanity might might think that I I I get where you're
coming from there are definitely core members but I think me and Ben are among the core members
yeah no especially Ben and like yeah and rowdy fuckers rowdy fuckers is our show it is me it is a
the me and munchie project yeah since we're talking about misconceptions let's bring up mother's
basement was he just like I'm assuming that mother's basement treated freaking uh procrastinators how
you guys treated the burning fandom that he's like oh I kind of have a little time for these guys
just a little bit I'll make it he didn't really he didn't really do anything yeah yeah like he was
just kind of there and he would pop in and he would pop in and like announce when like he was
doing a thing but like he just wasn't like really part of it he wasn't really contributing he just
wasn't contributing and it wasn't like we kick like we didn't kick him out per se I mean I guess we
did but it wasn't like a you know fuck this guy it was just like it was just like we don't there's
no reason for this guy to be here so we're just we're just gonna and he didn't take it he didn't
take it badly at all he wouldn't be super proud of it and we're still like most of us are still
friends with them so yeah but Ben you're a fucking you're a recluse you're a recluse and brutal
yeah no I I talked to Jeff a lifetime ago he's super cool well he was a lot more available before
you got like I I guess it's okay I had the opportunity to meet him and max but unfortunately
I was at like the trigger panel so I didn't get to it I'm super upset about it Nate did though so
I'm feel I he was he was there with me uh that's a relate though uh should we continue yeah absolutely
right oh here like knuckle dragon of the group
okay first yeah what the fuck are you talking about I don't I mean there's so there's just so
like everything he says is nonsense if he was trying to make Pete like he didn't try to make peace
he asked me if there was anything wrong and I said I didn't know what would be wrong like I don't
know what and then he kept pressing me until I got annoyed and basically told him to go away
yeah and then he left and yeah that's how I remember it like okay first of all it's obviously he calls
it a hidden video yeah yeah that that he didn't even watch misanthroponies for 20 minute response
to it yeah he just skimmed he just okay so right off the bat he just doesn't know he just does not
understand it yeah so he so so I can't wait for our video to get copyrighted I was very up front
yeah no I was very up front when I was doing yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah like we shouldn't
even be doing this because he obviously just does not understand anything I mean I said it about
misanthroponi I said about fngr I really believe it in both cases like I really think they're retarded
and they just don't act or speak or behave or like convey thoughts in the way that like oh we're so
being does yeah and like we wouldn't I like if it was just like I don't really understand what's
going on or they were being mean to key for like no no I heard that they they know you're saying that
I was white knighting keyframe no no I was white knighting myself I wasn't I didn't do it for anybody
else that makes me look worse to admit that but that's exactly yeah yeah yeah yeah you were very
up for it but that is nice I think I think I was talking about I don't know I don't know I think
there's a certain like nobility in being selfish yeah you know I I'm with you I agree yeah I mean
because I mean it's definitely I mean it's definitely I mean the way misanthroponi handled it was
annoying so I'm glad at least you didn't fall into that trap there's a reason why I didn't want to do
it for everybody else because I'd heard enough bronies in the community going oh those people I'm
like no like this is when I did my video when I did my video on digi which I got permission to do
from digi um I ran into so many of those fucking that guy with the glasses josh scorcher spirits
like oh no one of us now I'm like no faggot no I'm not I am not one of you people why would they think
that because they wanted they they wanted someone desperately to be their fucking voice they wanted
someone to be basically map fucking fucking josh scorcher Jesus Christ oh don't don't even get me
started he started fucking finally talking to me and everybody talks to you well it's I need this
and then he fucks right off hey do you have somebody do you have somebody as good as these
these two artists just laying around okay cool bye thanks hey I I need something and then he'll
get back oh I accidentally blocked you you are such a faggot josh suck a dick I think in I think in
this video I talk about josh and like how much he annoyed me no maybe not this maybe it was in
no it was the first video I talk about josh and how annoying I found his like his way he literally
he called me an a an a apostrophe apostrophe hole and then he fucking gets on his fucking high horse
about how he doesn't swear like get fucked dude um yeah I really don't understand it but yeah
like like it's not there it's been a financial point of view again just just to clarify again
so it doesn't seem like we're fucking grilling you here it's like we like we like understood
Miss Ant's point even if you didn't like get it per se like get what he was going on about
but in this we're just so utterly confused that we just don't know what's going on I'm eager to get
to the part I'm eager to get to the part where you really rip into me like I really don't want
to hear it Ben I know your recluse I know you don't like talking to people that's why I lightly
went hey are we cool because I wanted to get in and out and leave you the fuck alone I'm not as much
of a recluse as all that I do have some degree of people's skill and sure enough news to me news to
me yeah and sure enough you got annoyed by just me asking some very little things because
I asked you what was wrong and you didn't fucking tell me
how did you not think hey I just did a video on this guy because I didn't fucking talk to you I
didn't even fucking mention you do it no it's cool no it's cool though it's good it's good we're all
good everything's great but this guy gets like mean he gets me and never says why he never says why
but yeah okay killed a sensei in a duel and he never said why
made the process to bend over backwards to appease me the mongrel where does he get that idea
like where does that come from what does that mean it's so annoying how like everything we're
saying now is stuff we already say yeah oh all right I'll touch him on this too yeah it leads
back to like the digi thing when when digi had his drama I was like oh yeah I was really upset
about that he's like well he didn't say anything to me I was like I don't want to yell at you digi well
who did you yell at I yelled at Asher well why why did you yell at him oh because he's a communist
he doesn't have a soul you're okay digi okay sure I'm sorry I'm sorry you got answered munchy I'm
really sorry solid solid it's like what does it not enter these people's heads that maybe we're
just friends and we want to hang out and be friends and talk shit about people that suck
yeah like yeah that is that not a reasonable explanation for why this is a video
that's not like a marketable like you can't even say that was to be fair when my people do that
people do think it's a master plan and I don't stop them from thinking that because it's funnier that
way um no no there's no there's no master plan we're fully transparent see that's that wouldn't
hear a rowdy fucker's cop killie and how would that appease me to do that how would you like
like I don't even know yeah like I don't love them we're literally agog we're agog after listening
to your to the things you had to say I'm here I just kind of ride the beef I've got flummoxed
like I want like I want to theorize like where this idea comes from but I've just got nothing like
I've got no idea why he thinks that like I'm trying to impress you with any of we're pretty hung
up on this aren't we yeah I don't understand no I'm gonna take care of you right now this is my
friend Vita I could spare 100 months nice nice photo of him by the way yeah no he got that was when
he was drunk trying to big cider to hang out with him oh my god yeah Vita out because and Vita got
all bitchy and huffy about it and the ensuing shit storm has reached levels of fuckery that the
brony fandom might not have known well if not for this channel munchies case unlike digis where digi
just cut Vita off and Vita ended up taking it very poorly about as bad as say lily peat took
being cut off from joss scorcher munchie did the same thing and Vita asked for me to go find out
to which munchie told me sometimes some niggas just oh hold on you did say that word for word
absolutely yeah yeah no no no no no definitely and I'm not denying that and I like I just want to
say like I'm gonna try and not say what I say in here so I'm just gonna stay silent but yeah I'm
gonna touch up on all the shit yeah and that's fine and Vita's response was and nothing of value
was lost Vita didn't mindlessly harass munchie he let shit go in fact I was really proud that Vita
had the most mature rare moment I've ever seen him have in one of these situations later on Vita
here here my positive so I can explain what's going on uh Vita made accounts on steam over and
over trying to add me that is a fact that is what he did and I'm pretty sure the timeline of this
after fng you're asked me he didn't do it anymore which was fine the fact still remains
after I blocked him and I'm fairly certain that I that I said I blocked you or even if I didn't
he could take the hint making a ton of accounts to message me and me ignoring every single one
probably doesn't seem like I want to talk does it you know like he's I which like fng are just he
just goes off on this thing and like there's no context given as to like why there's beat like
he says that like Vita used to be boys with digi and then something about you and something see
this isn't even like drama this is just like a weird sort of like Vita wanted to be friends still
or maybe he just it just I do want to say fng thanks for coming on and sorry about the weight
yeah oh no no it's it's fine or something like that yeah um oh yeah yeah you want to come here
sorry sorry let myself finish okay but the again about this I was cool with him at the time and
basically I I understood why people cut Vita off understand that you guys were getting busy and you
know digi was starting to take off and that was around like when he had 50 000 subs just imagine
now he absolutely I've I've saw tons of his videos like I don't even have time for really cool people
anymore yeah and Vita didn't understand that and my knee jerk reaction is I didn't know about all this
my thought was I was like oh cool he like left fng munchy the fng alone he's growing up which is not
true I mean Vita I mean I wanted to believe that's so bad I'm like oh he's he's finally maturing he's
finally it's no I've heard I've heard did you talk about Vita and I got I think there's more
to it than just that he was too busy for friends like Vita was a real fucker it to hear digi tell
it um um one time um I forget I might mention this later but I just want to mention it again
real quick uh you you know about how like Vita molested digi's computer chair right okay now
I've heard stories go back whether that was legit or not it's funny to believe it's legit
I mean I don't think digi would lie about it yeah he doesn't strike me as the kind
who just tells tall tales tells tall tales tales in such a way okay and and Vita was happy to
acknowledge that this was a fact like after it happened for a while but but but now that we try
and bring it up as like Vita you're fucking crazy you have no proof I'll I'll I'll I guess we don't
but hold up I've hung out with freaking Vita at least to a certain period at like two different
30 cons and I remember everybody was terrified of him until like I remember South fire hearts
like oh he's the worst thing ever after like five minutes he's yeah he's not so bad well digi says
that he's bad digi says that he's real bad when he's off his meds and uh apparently he was off
his meds the time when he hung out with digi so I'm sure that contributed yeah um I don't know I
mean I don't know I don't like Vita but I don't know if I'm I I don't know I'm sure there's some
good things about him yeah all all I know is this originally when basically we added bunchy to the
the pfc chat which I don't even remember how that happened because I don't know how I did multiple
okay I know Vita Vita and I were like we were we were acquaintances at the very least at the very
least we were acquaintances and I know that he I don't know if it was the chat proper but I know
at the very least I was in a chat at one point with I believe I think you were there and I think
a couple like one or two girls were there and I know Vita was there and uh like I was there multiple
like three different instances at least yeah no this is why that was so funny yeah by the time
before you had just been thrown out we had a a week long vote to get Vita kicked out of the room
okay and yeah and then we added some kid who started screeching really loud into his mic
and we're like oh who the fuck is this crazy asshole and I'm just mentioning I have no doubt that
I did that yeah yeah no you totally did and I mentioned it to Vita he's like hey is that munchy
and I look at Sheldon he's like he knows who it is should I put him in he's like put him in
after spending the week throwing him out so Vita made you magical that's it yeah I want to I I
I think Sheldon he posted some like novel of a response to Miss Anthropony's video
and it was I think it was vaguely anti-Miss Anthropony pro us so I appreciated that but
man that guy typed like a fucking essay about the whole thing it's a real shame it's a real
shame that that Miss Anthropony took his video down although I think you do see the comment in
our response to it so it's preserved in some way I I I really hope so I'm really upset that that
video is fucking gone because there were so many great comments and just the video itself was a
fucking masterpiece yeah it was the only wreck we're we're we've archived it we have the only
record of it yeah yeah I'm here on the rowdy fucker's cop killer yeah um we're in a historians
but yeah I touch up upon more of you stuff in a second reason oh I didn't want to do a lot
so I didn't accept this friend's request that's it that's the entirety what transpired you know
the entire the entire second was just uh me and Vita didn't talk anymore that's it the the thing
that I'm getting here like I've thought about this before and I like the closest thing I can get to
like an underlying reason for why fngr is so upset is I really think that was like Vita that was
upset like I really think he's upset on behalf of his speculation because of probably because
my shit talked to him and we like went and tried and I rampage even though I knew it would come back
yeah um so like yeah I think I think that he's indignant because we were mean to Vita and I think
that probably what this video is is just like a sort of diarrhea stream that like came squirting
out as the like as the aftermath of like some really angry like back and forthing between like
the people that like fngr hangs out with like you know corpulent brony and vita okay yeah please
respond I I have not hung out with corpulent brony in some significant time okay but you
should but you showed him earlier in this video I was alluding to like the horse news drama he
wrote a horse news article about someone I was dating was that um wish feather fallen wish
fallen wish yeah yes and I basically like I was trying I bent over back I tried doing everything
I can I was like here I'll throw you a podcast right beforehand and be kissed his ass praying
that it would appeal upon him and you're like hey come on be cool and he didn't put it out
anyways the next day just because he's a fat cunt um yeah we did get a comment from someone named
like mom yuleus or something malimines yeah oh Jesus he was like malimines really fucking
hate you ben because I think you made some kind of remark about like he got in I don't want to
it was some kind of remark about some sexual thing that he had done back in the day oh yeah
you know I think I remember I think I remember like faith remembers I think I remember like I
didn't know who he was or she was or whatever um yeah I think I like kind of came to some conclusion
that he might be a pedophile or something based on absolutely nothing so I can't I can't
really blame I can't really blame this person if he has something against me because that was
yeah yeah yeah I'd like to state for the record faith if you're watching the thoughts of opinions
have been saying do not reflect the do not sue me and do not call you a pedophile yeah I don't
know I hate I hate you faith and I'd like you to burn in hell for all eternity but I'm not calling
you a pedophile I think I think it was I think maybe I was listening to a to a pony fuckers podcast
or something and uh the maluminous I don't know said something and it sounded weird and it and I
was like this person's a fucking creep and then I jumped to a whole bunch of conclusions I don't
remember I'll be completely honest with you maluminous is completely 100% unlikable uh maluminous
is you've seen boondocks right yeah uh yeah okay do you you know uncle ruckus right oh of course
maluminous is the uncle ruckus of transgender people oh my god yes sir uncle he worships
sargon of a cod loves worships every skeptic in the world and still tries to say that you know
I'm transgender and I'm this that the other and it's in it's just a complete contrarian
how bizarre oh
anyway he fucking nice thank you Ben you're welcome he commented something like
like like me and corp like don't hang out with f and gr which you know sorry like like again we
kind of removed from this so we don't really I mean I that was the case at one point so I just assumed
you know yeah cuz he cuz corp cuz corpulent was in there was a picture of him so I assumed he was
still like involved or something that was alluding to like the horse do's thing okay okay well sorry
for that uh we you know we just um we didn't really know yeah yeah all right let's just tell me and
like whoever the fuck else like I think this is like they kind of took this idea that like oh
ben and munchie were me and devita echo chambered it around being like oh well they're bad they're
the ones who are bad they're shitty and I hate them and then like this video is what's like squirted
out like of the black box like you'd we don't see we don't get to see there's another thing here
yeah yeah but Vita and corpulent hate each other like to a fucking zenith okay part of the reason
why I started lose like you know they wouldn't make me a mod and freaking the pfc like Vita would
tap you on the show he's like hey mod me why because I want to kick out corpulent and he would do
it like absolutely he would shoot like a complete punching bag and they're like why are you letting
him do that because like because it's funny what a real stand-up guy that oh well I didn't like
corpulent fucking this is like maybe you know what if corpulent comes forward said that's why
harassed your girlfriend because you treated me like I was a joke you know at least I'd understand
that we don't we don't really know what happened there we just know that this is like the feeling
that this indescribable in like unfathomable video is what was was what was created we don't
like it's just we can't describe what it is because it makes no sense it's really like
it really feels like it's all based on like some some like cultural some like like clicky
shit that is like deeply understood by like five people yeah no no offense ben but that's how they
look at you guys and the the fucking procrastinators that's fair you guys have literally called
yourselves the click and yeah it takes a lot that takes cherry peat levels of fucking
unawareness to say that shit uh I mean I don't know like it's true that that that that is that
like I don't know we do know that's retarded so okay like I don't know like okay well I was I
wasn't around for doing it unironically we're doing it ironically only takes you so far let's
continue true true but we don't have no context for but then like a thousand people watch it
anyway because it's like vaguely related to the brony fandom and that means it's worth watching
for some reason it I just I don't understand by the way and none of this is a point about the video
this is just like weird backstory between me and Vita continue oh yeah yeah yeah we're he was getting
along with people in there well more the fans and say the pcp members but that was never gonna happen
I fully understand that Vita didn't belong there we kind of popped in the call and much he showed
up and went what are you doing here there was a call in the discord chat in the press news call
yeah um yeah it was it was like the voice server and then they were and for the record I was going
to join but I was like that's probably not gonna lead to good things I thought you did I'm almost
positive that you came in and said Vita what are you doing here kill yourself oh you're okay and I'm
sitting there thinking if this were my room I'd say something but I don't feel like being
thrown no I I definitely said that in text no I I definitely said all of that and more in text
I don't know I don't know if I joined the voice call specifically though um yeah and and and I'll
say this I'll say this later but just you know to clarify um I I stand by Vita kill yourself I stand by
that statement um and I don't know like um we'll hear here I'll explain in a second here
okay like why call kill yourself oh hi fng are you're cool let me respond muchy no I don't also
when you first of all I don't think I like my entire okay I know I might have said
me you know fng are you're cool my entire knowledge of fng are was that he was like this weird like
shady sketchy that I didn't like but I knew I knew that people thought were cool so I was like
okay I guess I guess you flounder like friends with fng I just thought like okay I won't start
shit like I'll start shit with Vita because I hate yeah yeah and uh that's my entire thing
like I I never was like trying like like no no I didn't think it was that yeah I'm not saying
that you were trying to boot like me I just thought it was like oh we're cool and then I was like
I thought Vita was cool at the time and I thought it was just kind of shitty to go up and do that
like if I'm trying to be like reasonable with somebody I'm not gonna like turn to their friend
to be like hate for yourself that's okay well me me and Vita are on no reasonable terms and we
know I like like we did not leave as like friends I was missing I was missing a ton of details
and we are yeah yeah because I I didn't like him but I I didn't think it was okay to not like him
so I didn't want to start any shit yeah by the way I still like don't even know like what's being
like I guess they came into a call at some point like I don't know what the call was I don't know
like when this was happening or why I will explain the entirety of what he of of of what this person
tried so I will explain it in like human terms yeah one day in the pcp fan chat Vita came in
and uh he was acting kind of weird and then I was like oh man it's Vita what a fucking weird
asshole and then I called him a weird asshole and told him kill himself and then I told sorry
but how he fucked did his chair and he got all embarrassed and and uh people made fun of him a
lot because he was being weird and creepy and an asshole I think I just heard myself he wasn't even
being like that you know he wasn't even being that weird it was just you know and I hate Vita so I
wanted to make fun of him that wasn't like a that's understandable to me yeah I just don't like Vita
so I wanted to give him a bad time like I've heard enough I've heard enough about Vita that I don't
think he deserves the benefit of the doubt yeah and so that happened and then fngr was there too
and they they got into a call by them like in a voice call by themselves like in like they joined
the voice channels what I'm saying like a call off on their own uh they got into the voice channel
I was going to but I was out of the house and uh so I just I just told him to kill himself and the
I think he's gay and then Jesse came in and then uh me and Jesse talked about how uh stupid and uh
faggy uh Vita is and Vita got really pissed off and like mad and like uh like like angry uh
like angry and started crying like pissing his pants and then he like left or no he didn't
left we banned him and then he tried to make all the accounts to come back and spam the pcp chat
because quote okay to be fair Jesse was already there because I he was venting about somebody
else so you can ask me not to show them the comment for he was bitching about somebody you were
mentioning before leave it at that you should be able to figure out who that was yeah it was me
no I would have told you then yeah I trust you okay okay that's fine I didn't know that
he said this to one of the mods quote there's nothing more dangerous than man with nothing left
to lose did you spit into this real quick like like like like like like like like I don't know if you
caught that but like like Vita said like like seven times in a row um Vita said like we banned him
and then Vita said to one of the moderators like I'm going to come back and I'm like I'm gonna raise
hell and quote there's nothing more dangerous than man with nothing left to lose which is
fucking ridiculous and fucking like so like fucking like edgy it's hilarious yeah and then
and then he proceeds to we should get him on the pcp but oh my god all of his attempts to come back
to the pcp fan chat were in vain because we immediately realized and banned him we just immediately
banned him he didn't even have time to spam like like he came back like six or seven times and
I'm fairly certain and uh we just banned him like immediately and he didn't he didn't have any of the
epic trolling walls that he wanted to he was completely and utterly defeated and nothing he did
ever did so he was just kissing his pants publicly and we always made fun of him for being retarded
and it was great it was a great time uh sounds pretty good um should I continue yeah go ahead
dude we're in the pfc yeah the work reacted like a cringy autistic kid who literally screeched him
to his mic you went full retard and everyone bent over that did happen yeah yeah yeah Vita came
to say hi and he acted like you were a big deal you're a star fucker munchie I want Ben to know
if you could ever step over him for something bigger you wouldn't a heartbeat so you could be an
even bigger toadie munchie you're a sniveling groveling two-faced cute once upon a time ago you
gave your nose and showed it to do you and that was something that was an old fan art and you
endeared yourself to someone talented that's why you are that was that was me you're insane
okay wait we we we gotta we gotta pause about that we we we gotta we gotta discuss what you'll
betray me if I am here yeah but but you're like just let our past version speak for a little bit
and then that's just what I would expect like okay like I wouldn't ever I wouldn't expect anything
less of you so like I keep you around to keep me on my toes so I don't slip up and get sloppy
oh okay okay so so a lot of things a lot of things first of all go go back like well let
don't not go back I'm gonna go back in my brain to the beginning of that clip where he describes
a story I told on five fractions one where I once went through the pony forecast which
I don't really remember my interaction with them a lot I I do I like I described a story where
me and a couple friends went into that chat room and described the history of the Byzantine empire
to I don't remember that I don't know if you were there that I do I love history so I wouldn't
remember yeah like I don't think you were there like I know I know I was kind of a dodgy memory
I'm pretty sure and that's the memory of the goldfish and I don't truly remember how often I was
associated with the pony forecast but I know Vita added me to cause a lot I know that for a fact
so I had a lot of answers twice yeah yes so I'm sure I had a lot of interaction with them
and I'm sure one time I did scream I'm sure it's a different time yeah yeah yeah I did
scream for a while I don't doubt that that happened but I also don't doubt that my fucking
weird Byzantine empire story happened so that's not really a gotcha that's not like there were
just two times probably he's saying all these things like they're gotchas like it's like everything
he says it's like he thinks he's like really he's really like putting some shit out there
and then it's all just like but it's all just like he was on to say that like I I'm only friends
with digi because I'm I gave him fanner one time and that is completely accurate yeah that is not
I'm not like how like how yeah like that like I don't know how do you fucking meet people how do
you fucking meet people yeah and so like like like we well wait wait wait thanks for bringing
that up then yeah so but originally when I'm trying to butter up digi and get to him or something
like that I paid him like some money to go review one of my videos and then Ben shamed me down for
nope you and given both did that nope I remember this shit when you double stand okay tell the
story tell the story all right I I had just had on fucking I think Tom or some shit like that
and I just on the um on on the king of limbo yeah and I remember I was like oh here you know what
I made an anime review I'll send it to digi and then I was like hey look and I'm trying to butter
him up here's 10 bucks you know you can turn me some feedback or not I like you just you know go
ahead and then I wake up the next day and here's Gibbon and Ben screaming at me wait came on your
faggity ass show who the fuck do you think you are what damn time out of you and I'm like one I've
paid you Ben and Ben was not having any of it like oh I don't know this no you totally you totally
lost your shit then you're not gonna fucking back out on this you went off on me that day and I'm
like and then later on when I gave you like 10 bucks to shut up about I feel bad about it yeah
but you're gonna keep the money yeah wait okay okay I do I do kind of remember let me let me make
sure I'm getting this right I was so I was on king of limbo and months later I was still trying to
get in touch with digi I did enjoy talking to you I enjoyed talking to everybody who was like part of
the horseshoe crew I get we'll call it that for now um everybody was really cool even you know
when Nick kicks in fucking it was like a dipshit it was still fun yeah um and then you you went off
on me when I tried to like thrive digi to like you know hey so I was so I was mad I was mad because
I went on king of limbo and you didn't pay me anything and then because you were gonna pay digi
to do the same thing is it do I have it right I threw digi some money to like try and like get
him to not think I was a fuck you know so like okay okay well I don't know the truth okay well I
think okay I do vaguely remember that I think what I thought was going on is that like you you I
thought you paid digi or or someone maybe it was probably digi to be on the show so I guess I assumed
that like oh digi wasn't even on yet he still wasn't talking to me he just took the money and
never bothered to respond okay okay well yeah digi thought I was running the pfc at the time
which never was the case well I'm okay well I'm not saying this is cool like because if I agreed
to be on for free then I should have just then I should have just been happy with that I understand
I understand why Gibbon was angry because I mean you I I paid for your artwork which I I did use
and completely happy with it if you hire been our been saint for artwork I've never been I've never
felt cheated I've definitely gotten mileage out of all those art pieces oh thank you yes I do I do
my best um and and again look look if you want a pleasant memory of Ben saying we're all at Brony
con we're all drinking together and there's been taking his time this is free time teaching an
artist to give them tips while we're all fucking around did I do your cool guy Ben yes you did
there was a girl that was with them I don't it wasn't cotton candy uh whoever the hell the other
girl that was there with the I think I know who you're talking about yeah no I I remember a lot
of good things that Ben has done that's why I didn't want to get into him that's why I keep going
hey Ben are we cool I didn't want to fight with Ben I really didn't I swear we didn't want to fight
either FNG are we didn't want to fight either uh yeah no we did not um well uh wait so why was
why was Gibbon angry um I think he he wasn't commissioned or anything like that I threw him
like a dollar on patreon he might maybe you both were going back and forth on it I did throw him
10 for it and I was like well look you know what Gibbon here here's your podcast it was cool I'll
just give you 10 so there's no hard feelings I don't I don't want the people that I think are the
coolest people in the fandom to hate my guts I don't feel like I'm being shaken down right now
well I guess I I guess I have to apologize for that yeah I think I think I remember that I figured
that like because someone else was getting paid to to go on the show that I therefore deserve to
to in hindsight that's pretty that's pretty fucking shitty so sorry about that my that's my bad
well the yeah the the reason why Tom was paid is because he was up like Schitt's Creek I think he
was like really in a lot of trouble back then yeah and I was like okay here you go I mean I mean if
you know if I if I agreed to be on then like you know what am I complaining about so it's that's
on me that's on me okay all right let's hit play yeah like again this wasn't to appease me we just
did that because we were friends and we like to have fun it's like he's reading all these like
sinister intentions he's reading he's reading all these like weird like Machiavellian power plays
into the whole thing okay again to be fair I had to make a lot of Machiavellian power plays
to different point A to point B so you understand my perspective I had to I had to move mountains
to get to digi that's why I was laughing at him about the anime thing I was like so let me get
this straight you you were complaining that people won't talk to you oh this is the smallest
file in digi do you know what hell I had to go through to talk to you
like yeah if I was a starfucker I could do a little bit better than Ben saying don't you think
oh now I'm sad yeah yeah yeah you could go after just oh man um that'd be really easy
mean Jeff got into a good on a good fire red call we could easily I could easily use Jeff for subs
that would be incredibly easy you know what I could do for subs I could not make the Japanese
Juggalo ARG I could not do that I could make anime videos instead of making the Japanese Juggalo ARG
but I don't because I'm a weird fucking emotionally stunted freak and I just want to do cool things
yeah like we're like we're not we're not we're all here we're all here because this is where
we belong you know not because not because we're not here on some like false pretense yeah because
like there's there's if we were if we if like if the pcp were a thing that we're just like
a business yeah if like if we were here to do business and we were here to like promote an
agenda like there'd be better ways to do that like that's you know fngr he just doesn't fucking
get it and why would he you know yeah he just doesn't he just doesn't understand a single
fucking thing yeah could you know Ben fan you ever see the movie twins the one where
Arnold Swartz yeah yeah yeah this part's good line in there where they're talking to old Arnold
and saying that all the greatness went into him and all this shit that went into his brother
I just imagine
it's great I'm gonna do this nice and slow this is the Arnold in this situation
I often repeat that line that I'm a pile of hot dog goo uh that one's a keeper that's that's
not that's not true anymore by the way um why I don't know why is he so why is he so sweet on Nate
yeah yeah like what did Nate do to be what did Nate didn't hit me that's what happened
but his brother is like the cool Nate didn't shake me down for money that that guy's cool with me
do you know how I got Nate I was like I was like hey I could give you an animation like
fucking Ben he's like oh I can't turn say no to that I I want that animation
for that podcast the only thing that I could find safe that freaking crown prince would
animate was the very beginning and she had had the table flip to make it interesting
because everything Nate did was so brutal those those crown prince animations are pretty sweet I
was pretty fucking stoked when I realized that I that yeah there was one of me uh fuck yeah she
did that for free I was shocked yes yeah that's pretty impressive no no munchie about that I remember
like right before she came on the show and as as a joke like as a goof I was like hey you could always
do an animation if you're coming on the show and I remember Sheldon contacted me while I was at work
he's like look dude look what she did I'm like oh my god I just died she must think you people suck
she's coming on my show and came in animation Sheldon kill yourself that's a wonder we're not
friends anymore yeah that's not a one-off thing he mentioned that again how like how like like
Ben is like this groveling disgusting sack of shit but like Nate's so cool yeah what yeah he
sounds like a Nate Fed fiction in hearse lecture is is that what got you on Nate that video that of
all I I was totally mistaken I should have figured that I don't know he's like I don't think like
I didn't know sure that Nate I almost forgotten that Nate was on king of limbo I'm sure that Nate
thinks that fngr is is retarded just like I do like probably there's no doubt like we're completely
on the same page about fngr and then why can't you be cool why can't you be nice and good and
cool guy like this other guy that thinks I suck ass that had no there was no point there
the point was simply that I was like oh it was simply that I was a mongoloid that was
the point here is simply that I am inferior to Nate yeah like there's no
this is so awkward I'm so I'm so gonna clip this together and make a video please oh please
and and and because because I was mean to Vita justly therefore I'm a therefore I'm a mongoloid
yeah and and why make this video you're not making any points of that the friday fuckers
fired frack frack frack frack is a bad video we are bad people for like he called rowdy
he called rowdy fuckers a hit video but like a hit video is exactly what this is this is nothing but
that and we and it wasn't a hit video it was just us shitting around yeah like it wasn't even mostly
about that yeah um all right okay continue one thousand subs than me I'm told that you're pissed
that tune critic is making more money than yourself well I did listen to that fucking yeah money
you seem to have fun at the burning donut who unlike yourself went to be homeless then got a job
and pulled himself up by his bootstrap a man yeah you were made in high regard do you regret
how hard I was on burning donut in front of your little mongoloid friend here was 700
but by the way fngr I want to comment you like very genuinely like genuinely like genuinely I love
the way you like almost like animate me like like like me on screen like like earlier like earlier
earlier when you were like you were doing an impression of me like like like oh fg you're cool
you're like animated stills of me from the degil nation lecture which is fucking incredible and
I'm going to steal that for if I ever make an like an analysis video I I love just the idea of just
using me as like like a stilted like animation it's incredible I genuinely love it okay I'm really
upset you asked 700 subs so let me give you a first first of all how is your sub count relevant
second of all yeah I'm second I mean you know I'm sorry if burning donut thinks I'm cool whatever
the I don't I don't like his art and his fucking patreon was an embarrassment so what what the
fucking it what am I supposed to say uh and and and wearing a homing became don't a dirty
in home fucking birdie don't pull him by his bootstraps but how's your living situation how's
that going out how's that working out for you how's the majority of your of your fucking life
how's that how's that how's your leftover eating situation how's that um it's on the upswing
I mean uh just for additional context bin eats trash um well one time I pulled some grapefruits
out of the trash can they were still fine divu had totally jumped the gun on throwing those
grapefruits away they were still juicy they were still juicy and delicious I will defend to the
death my decision to eat those trash grapefruits um bin eats trash so so often at the digi house
so often at the digi house there would be like takeout like takeout chinese or takeout
sandwiches would get thrown away they'd be like fully uneaten and yeah I'd fucking eat that it's
fucking good shit god damn it they paid good money for those and someone's got a fucking benefit
from it when I went to radcon and I went to bin's house I went to bin's room it was covered
wall to wall on the floor with peanut shells and and like and like like like like vape business
card just thrown around on the ground and and and whenever I had to wake him up because we were
recording he would he would like like slither on over to the door and fucking his his hair would
be in a fucking mane and and he would groggily like like like beg me to fucking um a couple more
minutes basically yeah that's the story with him in a man bun that would have done it would have
did you have a man bun uh I could have I could have certain points
I never actually pulled the trigger on it but but but yeah the point of that is that bin has always
been falling on hard times I mean I mean I was I mean I was never homeless and I like homeless but
rear that one time you tried a hitchhike from like LA to Boston or something yeah and I mean I did
I did that to save money I mean I think one of your last birthdays I sent you money because
you're like oh I'm like how are you doing not so good and I think I threw you money just because
it was your birthday I don't hate bin guys I don't I don't I don't remember I don't remember
saying oh I'm not doing maybe I did I don't know I don't remember that I do remember you've
thrown me some money a couple times and I mean I appreciate that each time I hear about like like
I hear stories from although that was like that was like years ago so yeah well you love Skype
I didn't I didn't have Skype program I abandoned Skype for discord so I guess I've made my bed
um but yeah but yeah each time I hear about bin's living situation I'm always I'm always
incredibly intrigued by by the squalor um incredible please continue oh I never I never was homeless
you know I'll give him that much it never was never was fully homeless uh so you know lucky me
don't see what that has to do with my fucking criticisms of the way burning doughnut chooses
to run his fucking art PR campaign don't really see the relevant there sorry he was homeless wouldn't
have wished that on him doesn't really make I love the hot dog no one cares about an architect
whatsoever him saying like saying like I have more subs but for no good reason gets more views
which is like it's not even true I looked so something about like some kind of point about
how my audience isn't as engaged as his which like sorry are you the police yeah um munchy
you suck ass which I don't like I don't touch on that real quick okay because you looked at my
content and you went me which was really dismissive and I was like all right let's let's let's have a
dick measuring contest okay okay that's that's basically sure sure sure this will come up again
this will come up again but fngr is like is fixated on sub counts and view counts as a measure of a
person's worth yeah okay two yeah to be fair fngr I know you're gonna say Ben is very fixated on
patreon money um well you know I think I've got good reason to be but I'll leave that up to the
audience to decide I'll leave them to be judge jerry and execution on that subject don't don't
worry fngr I'm with you on that point god damn it he was right he was right as soon you betrayed me
just like fngr promised you would for no good reason subs right now yeah that's fine yeah
is that out there a bond as opposed to patreon money which is more because it shows how much
people like your stuff yeah I mean it's definitely more of one than like a sub count I mean look at
sigh for example yeah exactly true your big revelation of leaving pony was to become a
pokey tuber fresh and original Benny you know because brony is dying Benny no no no to get about
half the views that tvb ap used to make not just that but I mean does it even need saying that he
just doesn't know what he's talking about yeah like he just obviously just does not understand
like he thinks that all right I didn't watch nislac because I don't like pokemon well that's fair I
mean I wouldn't expect you to go watch that no no the problem isn't that you don't like Ben's content
because you know who can blame you yeah who would but yeah yeah oh we touched on this in a second
though um yeah just let go yeah people can only exist on youtube and there's nothing else one
could possibly do yeah yeah yeah yeah like like the thing the things off the things off youtube
are not even like entering into this dialogue for him like they're not relevant they just don't
even exist in his mind yeah does he even know that you have made a comic before does he know that
who knows who knows do you know yes yes I do know that okay okay you know how I know because
the burning donut would shut up about it really what did he say defending he's like oh yeah I really
like Ben's work and then this came out yeah yeah well okay I I deserve okay I deserve to feel like
there was a couple of little things that like kind of like if it's stock piled up and I was like
well you know Bennett though we've kind of done stuff but here I'll just be blunt with it Ben
might have been a faggot but he was a hard faggot oh no he's biting us in the ass well I'm not having
it that's that's what happens like there are creative aspirations outside of youtube I'm sorry if
that's a news flash to you yeah but there are there are things you can do outside of making youtube videos
well god it's really frustrating it's really frustrating because he just it's like it's like
trying to like explain don't touch a stove to a child yeah well you'll try it and you'll see
and then he tries it but he still doesn't get it and the way he calls you bunny Benny is the most
disgusting Benny is creepy it's creepy oh no it's meant to be condescending it was supposed to piss
you the fuck off yeah I could tell I did yeah I could tell and it's it totally did what it was
intended to do right there it's really creepy and like he's trying to be like demeaning about it
and it's like just makes me sweat just make it just makes me feel dirty it's so gross he's like
such a gross disgusting person he's said the guy with the cheeseburger t-shirt yeah well hey don't
just the cheese for the cheese today are 10k that's two percent Benny which is okay for milk but not
so much for youtube that's your I do I do like that yeah I've boosted that from somewhere I forget
where oh nice oh and here's the part where you'd make fun of my thumbnails I love my thumbnails
I'll stand by them to the death okay the critique I said was is it I felt that it would it's the same
picture like every time yeah yeah you see well sure you know I'm not someone I'm not the target
demographic audience and you could definitely sit there and say back but yeah I mean I well
yeah I think I think that my thumbnails are are they're they're supremely readable you know like
you can tell what it is like like it's it's it's I think I've done an excellent job of branding
my content with my thumbnail so yeah when I when I see a bin saying thumb now I know it's a bin
st thumbnail yeah well yeah I was really offended because I really I really like my
these thumbnails are a fucking nightmare they are in yeah they don't have that readability
I'm an expert at readability it's my it's my highest stat even read like it doesn't even read
my fucking thumbnails are designed to read well there we go this guy and not only fucking that
but the shit he said before that where it was like it was like can we just replay it can you just go
back like a little bit so I can just fucking go back to the hot dog I think it's not that far yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah just like just like the fact that he again again he just does not understand
to he just doesn't understand that that's not what you do tvb ap used to make not just that but
see this ben this is proto mario he has 500k subs entertaining guy poke tuber his average views
today are 10k that's 2 benny which is okay for milk but not so much for youtube uh f ngr do you
still talk to burning down uh a little bit why I don't know I don't know if he'll see this video
but if you if you do oh no he did I believe a response I thought he was super nice I'm assuming
oh yeah yeah I saw I saw the response um yeah so I don't know if he'll see this video and I'm not on
Skype anymore but if you do talk to him and it comes up feel free to let him know that I feel kind
of bad for how hard I was on no no I totally will fuck okay okay um yeah the whole point here
they're not being very concise is just that like ben just does he like ben is a comic artist and
like sometimes does youtube videos and I believe the sentiment after he made the last one was I'm
never going to do that ever again yeah yeah so yeah so here so here we're so here we're like
so here we're like uh we're just fucking around about like yeah because you're because you're
criticizing me for for the the move from pony to to pokemon when it's really like a move from pony
to comic yeah and the the pokemon stuff is like a side thing okay I'll be on like I said there's
usually like for the the bernie's who were like pro horseshoe crew there's always been like a couple
of things on the tip of our tongue but we don't want to give the benefit of the doubt to the rest of
the faggots okay so we just shut up because hey they're they're not going to shit with us
oh they're fucking with us now you know donut can go over there and go in an ass ball or me well
I've had a lot of things that I've wanted to say but you know what I'm gonna be cool
oh we're not cool well that changes a lot that's basically all that was but but again we we were
cool okay first of all he makes it seem like leaving teabap and going to pokemon well okay
first of all that's not even what happened but even if that word to have been what happened
like like that's what that's what that's what happened in his mind oh all right no no no no like
look I was spinning a bullshit narrative I remembered you being on mage's podcast and talking
about how art was important to you and how art was important to gibbon and her and this that
the other no I knew more I was I was on mage's podcast yeah you tom and gibbon all came on for
mage which was like really fucking cool and respectful no you mean you mean on king of limbo
yeah oh yeah yeah yeah I do remember that I do no I remembered everything you said about that and
you know you I know you were more than just this I was throwing shit to everybody listening
Ben saint is a deep talented artist oh yes I like his style when change it for the world
I was in a fight I thought I was and yeah yeah you were swinging punches and everyone's just confused
I don't know man I feel like uh you got you got a little you got a little misled you got a little
bit misled on the content of our video yeah yeah yeah that's not that's just not what it is on any
level on any level okay hey you there yeah I'm here no no that was me in the video asking
oh god the the fucking the barriers are breaking down between past and future
yeah it wasn't for money you didn't do that for me it's just because you wanted to do it
it wasn't it would have been smart to be fair what what has been good isn't for money no one
down yeah it's all for that oculus rift and then I don't I don't even I really don't even know what
to say about it like it's just so I mean I mean I don't I don't know what like yeah like but like
here's the thing like he's he's he's saying all this like you know oh like I've clearly
fucked up like I've clearly fucked up so much and like and like oh I made such a terrible decision
but like it worked out for me and like I fucking make more on patreon now than I ever have and like
my fucking shit has like like shit has gotten better for me and like I consider everything
I've done to like like I see it as like like I've really succeeded at what I set out to do
like I've really made good progress towards what I wanted to do and like the fact that he just like
frames it all as the exact opposite of that just just what am I even supposed to say that
just like no I just wrong you wrong yeah like I've I've heard been no sell like a lot of
accomplishments from other people so this this is a very high double standard bullshit
uh examples examples please I I know you absolutely there's it's a lot of the things
that the pfc basically picked up off a fucking horseshoe crew where like oh look someone else
would be doing something else and like oh no no that's not so good that's that's not us
well they're not quite I mean if it's brony stuff then sure yeah I'll stand by that yeah um okay
I'm yeah I I'm ready to believe all right so let me let me ask that um I'm assuming like if
I don't know if if you guys all win anime that probably the same attitude probably would have
carried over there I didn't go anime yeah I mean yeah yeah I mean I don't know what if the world
was very clicky now yeah yeah yeah wait what'd you say munchie so we're all still very clicky now so
yeah like even though that didn't happen yeah yeah we are we are clicky though yeah I'll cut to that
wrong like wrong by any metric yeah and like just told just there's there's not even like a basis
there's not even a basis for me to critique that on because it doesn't even get like the basic
assumptions of reality right yeah holy shit jesus should I continue yep going from mlp to pokemon
with your staggering dead drive go ahead some males those numbers did not work here here like
move back oh sorry sorry um wait was that was that real lunch here was that in okay
guns such a fucking clusterfuck yeah one second here okay yeah we're fucking this up refresh the page
I can't even tell which plane yeah yeah yeah the only way you can tell is if the mouths are moving
yeah funny like I think it's explicitly designed to be part speaking of dead dry and boring look at
this fucking video yeah yeah um yeah we really we really shit this one out um for uh we really we
really betrayed our fans trust yes hanging on to everyone else's coattails so the next time
that's your big breakaway benny going from mlp to pokemon with your staggering dead god damn it again
we hit this yeah we've seen this like four times you hanging on everyone else's coattails
so the next time that's kind of like it I challenge you to show me your retention to your shitty videos
and I bet mine beat the fuck out of yours by the way Ben I mean they don't ask him off was the
original reason why I turned off the pcp podcast I had to move my shit to my other channel but how
not to brony was beating fucking as luck like a faggot in the back uh see this whatever
no it's like the neat name get some screenshots if you want to play this game benny uh don't call me
benny uh sorry okay phantom horn to kidding kidding kidding do that again bad about fngr thank you
whatever his cop killers I have no idea what he's talking about yeah and again that's really the
little breakaway from this she's not addressing the video he just does not say what's wrong with the
video no wouldn't that make more sense to describe is is there more or have we pretty much happy
no no no like he's like oh thank god yeah I think we've beaten we've beaten this dead
if you go back and edit any of this I'd probably cut off like like somewhere towards like
a couple of like at least a loop yeah yeah yeah some of that at the end was a bit but
we're not fucking editing this this is this is oh yeah yeah roddy fuckers cop killers
doesn't believe in editing all right well uh is there a thing you want to say because I'm
I'm the guy we we cleared the air here because like I said I was sticking it for somebody
originally who I thought was my friend I thought we had actual heat there was no okay yeah no I'm
misunderstood okay Vita's a dick he wants my girlfriend to kill herself so as far as that's
concerned munchie um cheeseburger t-shirts are okay thank you that's the least I can ask for
here here here let me pull your channel up here so I can you know put it in um uh for no uh hold on
it's not coming up for some reason I'll just type your name what what are we doing just put
yeah yeah yeah um whoa do you have an encyclopedia manica page absolutely why did she has one
that's true oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I guess I'll I guess all famous people
yeah it's a it's a it's a mark of privilege it's a mark of success really here um fucking lol
do you know do you know who made this all these are made by like one person I guarantee they're
all just like one like mad fucking like yeah like one one but hurt former fan who you oh I'm pretty
sure digits was made by Vita that don't quote me on that that's that's there they're on it I know
it's hard to believe there are more people than Vita didn't you look up this up on YouTube and as
as opposed to like whatever Google or whatever um yeah I try Google yeah here um for no good reason
all one word okay yeah okay yeah um um on that on screen right now um this fucking this article
I'm assuming this is all lies I don't know I can't right now because discord won't load on I wait
wait um the um okay wait you mentioned your girlfriend a second ago is that fallen wish
or not anymore um that was a long time ago that was a long time ago yeah the encyclopedia
dramatic a page says that she's a that she's a scammer and that and that you supported her scam
is okay hold it hold it I no no no like look I'll explain this right now okay well actually I
shouldn't have to explain this to Ben I've seen your current girlfriend you got it going on so
anyways um yes no no sheldon was super fucking jealous today he's like how the fuck did Ben
do this this is oh yeah but it is oh incredible what crazy blackmail material did he have on this
bitch blackmail material Jesus Christ is that is that where his that's where his mind goes huh
so yeah shut up shelly d um yeah cool cool um this this how it goes when you have a girlfriend
and she does something that may or may not be bad if you tell people about it you don't get the next
one see what I'm saying I understand I understand standing by your woman I can't I can't my woman
anymore but here's the whole thing yeah but at the time when future women look at you like oh I don't
know this guy batmoss a lot of his exes I don't know that's a really good idea yeah the most I'll say
is like so-and-so is you know crazy or something like that make it vague move on um fallen is um
um I didn't run or go fund me I have actually never run a go fund me I plugged it uh corp
blint brunny went after that hardcore he plugged it um we're no strangers here for making fun of
go fund me is here on right yeah um right right fruit right fruit for the picking my um yeah my um
my the people and the people in uh me and jackie's discord oh okay they were they were going they
were going through your your encyclopedia dramatica uh they were they were you know they were like I
kind of I kind of popped in and saw some of the some of the stuff um what happened with tune critic
what's the deal what's the story we made oh I do I do want to point out right now since I can't
see the chat right now if if I go to your description it's a link to my encyclopedia dramatica
you're not going to be able to go no no no we weren't starting a fight yes you you will be
okay understood understood okay just let me know don't don't don't don't we didn't know any better
no man because because well I ask I ask because like you know I like I have occasionally seen
your youtube channel and I see and I see tune critic you know like mentioned in a lot of uh in a
lot of your videos and like I assumed that it was like you know pony news stuff or brony analysis
stuff but like I don't know I guess uh like from from what people were saying like I guess there's
like some personal shit that went down and I was and I was deeply interested okay so keeping it vague
okay you don't have to say anything you don't want it you might want to really ask me after the
discord's off because you'll get way juicier stuff yeah let's put it this way if if you don't see it
on how not to brony what makes you think it's going to be here um I guess so um yeah I have a really
hard time shutting up so that if that that that must be means it's really really something um
christ yeah um well will jeez louise can can can you say anything about the subject I mean okay me
me and ben are are are totally anti-tune critics yeah yeah we're you're not gonna we're not we're
not gonna be like we're not jumping to his defense or anything yeah in fact in fact we're we're eager
to throw him under the buns of the very possible opportunity yeah okay so I'd like to say I'd like
to say this for the record that I'm I'm not doing that tune um I want to I want to put keyframe over
which is fucking beautiful you know what happened over there no Josh Scorcher and KP went up to
fucking tune and said you're gonna ditch him or we're not gonna work with you anymore and keyframe
screen Josh Scorcher down wait wait wait wait KP and Josh Scorcher went up to keyframe and said
went up to tune went up to tune and said you're gonna ditch who me you're not gonna hang out with
fngr anymore we're not gonna work with you anymore well fucking went up to Josh Scorcher and told him
to shut the fuck up so so you still you still wanted to to hang out with tune critics no no
we're still cool this was something later like okay one we'd be here for four more hours two I can't
talk about oh no there's there's a that's my other problem here is that you don't seem eager to shut
up about it uh I mean well sorry you know no I got look I got well why don't you I understand why
a lot of other people don't like to critic why don't you like well I mean I just think I mean I guess
he hasn't done anything to me personally I just think yes I just think he's we're not a fan of
his content yeah we're just not a fan of his content think he's I don't understand what the
what the hype is there I mean he's not he's definitely not the worst brony yeah like his
his response to the first video was pretty like diplomatic and like he was like
he said that he found it funny that we were trash talking him I appreciate that yeah yeah
yeah well like I don't know I mean we don't we don't exactly have a hard you know a hate
boner for him but if I had access to this recording right now I'd be able to show
right where the hate boners showed up well okay okay we're by no we're by no means allies
but no but like okay but I just because he's in a lot of your videos so I assumed that you
guys were like enemies but you're saying that that's not the case okay he's in two videos
and to the best of my knowledge other than I'm goofing around oh but I think it was fucking
maybe 41 43 I know I think in 38 where I made the remark there's someone I'm holding back on
talking about and then I think like two videos later is like okay guess what we're talking about
that thing today yeah okay yeah Vita put pushed me into that one he's like well come on say something
here and I'm trying to remember what I already talked about versus what I have to shut up about
and that's where you have to shut up about everything when you don't remember um well okay I mean
you you know um this show is a fucking you know like at this point there's no there we can't be
under any illusion that this is not a drama show whether we like it or not we've thrown our
hand into the ring uh the the the current the veil has been pulled aside um so yeah I mean I don't
know if you want to clear any mispossessions now's the time I suppose I'll I'll put it completely
clear so tune even if Ben and freaking munchy over here offered me procrastinators podcast you
were not going under the bus tune yeah any further than you already have um okay all right well I
guess that settles there I could I could I could talk about it after we go off air
want a little nitty gritty of the details that I tell friends and shit which I'm glad to do which
will be you'll probably be amused by um okay I mean um well I want to switch gears for a second
because uh one of the things because like I said people were talking about it in in uh in my own
discord I didn't know he had one until now who who I didn't know you had this like a
pd dramatic of age just now yeah um yeah I did I did some someone I don't know who went and dug
it up but somebody did um so yeah I there's there's video okay this guy named Mr. Meadoker
would like apparently you got into some to some like okay let me challenge them to a dual
basically like no no no no no let me explain how this happened okay all right no if you have the
time oh no we have we have the time all right so anyway a while but I was just about to say goodbye
but no no please yeah no it's starting to feel that way so anyways um originally uh do you know
anything about deviant art drama um I mean I mean I I've been on deviant art and so anyways it seems
it's it's you know there's it's a it's a hotbed it's good for views and I used to be friends with a
commentator by the name of Reno Rhino Mills and I didn't know that much about commentaries
and I'd be like hey um I want to get into fight with somebody but I don't really know anything
about I don't I don't know anybody about this community like this is Greek to me I I know
Bernie and nothing else and the first person he threw me was somebody named conqueror nine
like a thousand two thousand subs and I slapped the shit out of me folded like a little bitch and
I was like oh this is fun so yeah then I I found somebody on my own uh phantom menace 10 000 subs
and same thing folded like a little bitch and I was like my god this is fucking amazing I love this
I started feeling like custard do you know what happened to custard so my last stand was I ran
into mr meddaker uh ryan its friend doodle tones if you want to look that up she probably has one
of those encyclopedia dramaticus too uh made a video where she's like don't shame you know
and he made a bunch of da videos like making fun of that now I don't have a problem with Jim I even
got uh fan art done of him I've squashed whatever problems I had but at the time I was like oh wait
he does da drama I slapped the shit out of people who do da drama I just went from 1000 to 10 000
subs this guy has a hundred thousand oh baby this is gonna be amazing the windfall I'm gonna
steamroll this no no that didn't happen so yeah and and it got funnier because I started calling
him out and I'm like he responded back to me and he was like look you could bring three of your
cringy friends on to debate me and I'm like oh I'm gonna he thinks I'm gonna bring brony faggots
you're gonna get roasted I'm bringing commentators he's gonna get destroyed and the two of them
backed out like one almost the same day not gonna give the names um fucking thursday two days later
he made me wait a week I don't know why wait wait I'm curious what exactly was the was the point
of bringing in commentators to to the debate yeah and he winds you to do that for some reason
I originally did call him out I was like going oh yeah no I went to go pick a fight because he
was given fucking doodle problem who I'm not really even friends with especially not now um
and then basically after like I lost my second person the only other person that was coming
with him was doodle who I'm not really friends with and I said I'm out okay they they they
roasted me for two weeks and I'm not gonna call it harassment because I turned to Jim and I said
and I quote hit me as hard as you can and to the best of my knowledge off the tip of my head he
didn't break any laws he shouldn't be thrown off a youtube nobody harassed Jim I watch his
shit today he makes fun of fucking um that guy with the glasses he has a series on that and it's
beautiful nobody tears down and by the way it's Medeker nobody tears down fucking Doug Walker
as beautifully and eloquently as fucking Medeker does his fucking videos on like
they're they're they're a trip fucking absolutely put him in my top 10 favorite youtubers okay
but yeah no I I got involved in something I shouldn't have um and that went sideways for me
that's it well but why why did you ultimately decide not to go not to I saw people who were
better at debate than me fuck off and I was like hmm this is a bad idea my common sense
is tingling yeah uh yeah yeah I mean that's understandable like I don't know um I can't
say I blame you I stuck my dick in a bear trap and I got nipped clipped at the tip that's my fault
it happened absolutely okay have a good laugh if you want to if you want to link Medeker's video
in addition to my channel underneath it knock yourself out I have no hard feelings with Jim
none okay um okay are you are you guys friends at all no no okay don't I don't have Jim looks up
because since Faggot's saying he's my friend I'd be cool to hang out with Jim I saw a fucking Jim
get a guest spot on uh if you know who guru Larry's channel is um I saw him on there all right no
mind all right that's fine um yeah I just I just I just I just want to know something I just I just
need to know because like I watched I watched the Mr. Medeker video there's I mean you're saying
you're saying you know we can link it in the description and like yes all right all right
there's just I just I was fucking flummoxed I was fucking flummoxed uh by what I heard and I just
need I just need to know the truth um were you cocked at brony con by tune critic y2k is this
the true okay this this is not not even offended do you know why and oh actually I would have been
able to add fallen wish the call if she didn't do a fuck up yesterday I wasn't dating fallen until
after BC is that so okay she was dating or her to brony's wait a hurt a herd that his OC's name
okay okay I thought you meant she was dating like 20 different brony's at the same time I
swear to god I wasn't trying to set up a joke there all right but now now to be fair at the same
time she was dating her to brony she was kind of screwing around with dark edge um all I knew
is as I was single she seemed fun and I've always said that about fallen she's a very fun person
not perfect but she's a fun person to hang out with um ironically enough I was sitting next to her
trying to put the move on her she shot me down the same time that I was showing her uh ciders
fucking um video on like some kind of turtle brony sex video you know I'm talking about wait
yeah no it was funny tuney tuney the is it tuney the turtle or is it something else uh it was
about um cider made a video about fucking oh yeah it was uh how thanks for the memories about
a male erectile this function okay cool no it's brilliant it's absolutely I know all about that
subject yeah dog all right so so bad you should have just came out and said it look I I should
have just said look I I want to fucking needle you because you gave me a hard time can I bring
up the medicare thing could have said that ahead of time I'd have been glad to come on
okay well okay so so I mean I was like I was like really curious about so okay so but you're
saying that okay you were not you were not dating uh what's her name until now okay now since you
so so so so so so so when mr. Medecker says so when mr. Medecker says that you were cucked at
brony con that's a mischaracterization of what actually happened absolutely didn't happen this
is I will look if you want to press this I'll go this far did fallen wish start to cheat on me and
they get the gentleman's name is the director at one point in time yes the relationship lasted
I think about two weeks the wait wait who who's do I know this person this other person this director
you could look it up if you want to but he's just some animator oh okay I never heard yeah I'm not
looking to come down on fallen wish I have my own personal opinions on that I I mean what really got
me was was because like I mean I don't know tune critic but like just from his public image like
I've seen him around and just imagining the okay apparently that's not how it actually went down but
but the situation described by mr. Medecker imagining imagining tune critic in that scenario
would just blew my fucking mind so I had I had to fucking get I had to fucking get the scoop
all right so let me let me ask you a question yeah and are you are you a skeptic like in like about
like god are you even god no no no no no no no no no no no are you critical of when you hear
bullshit uh I like to think so yeah okay so let's let me please spend this to you yeah five of the
ugliest bronies in the community yeah got together and got laid okay there is no actual proof of this
other than corporal and brony a man who hasn't seen his penis in years oh right they did there was
something about an orgy all right so yes no I the two women in that group I won't go into specific
details okay I don't you wouldn't look at any of these people and think orgy when you saw them okay
sure yeah no yeah no I'm being dead seriously I understood no I I understand I know I know maybe
you did maybe it did but here's the whole thing if everybody's like if you're skeptical and critical
what I was heard that basically I winded up going back to my fucking goddamn hotel we walked back
with stardust and eliora and then supposedly allegedly an orgy broke out on minty root's
bed where he wasn't invited to come into the room wait wait wait wait wait they I don't know who
minty roots is but it was supposedly in his bed and he was not allowed in no that's allegedly
allegedly what happened allegedly what happened according according to some unverifiable sources
yes okay um uh that's that that's all fine and and weird and odd
I just I just see I mean because I know because I know that I can't trust I know that I can't
trust in psych I can't take encyclopedia dramatic at face value I can't take what Mr. Medecker says
at face value so I yes I am a skeptic so I needed I wanted to hear it from the horse's mouth yeah
you could you could do better than that yeah tune and fall wish don't like each other like at all
yeah they've never dated um yeah I mean it's possible I suppose okay this is like a page
dramatic a page is very odd uh it says something about like like sock puppet accounts is that
is that a real thing that is occurring do I have multiple accounts I have analysis daily I
fend in frenzy and have a bunch of other I have an antineagular account on youtube yes I have
multiple accounts on youtube okay jessie woodhead how many accounts I have I have multiple accounts
that is true yeah um yeah okay perfect perfect so yeah um well geez um you know man um sorry to
put you on sorry to put you on the spot there's there's nothing to put off here I'll explain this
to you but we got you we got you here and so no no I want to make an I used to screw with my friends
like Sheldon used to worship jessie wood so you know what I changed the name on one of the accounts
to jessie wood and posted he's like oh my god jessie wood just commented on the pony I remember
when Sheldon fake donated five thousand dollars to jessie's patreon I remember that happening
he was okay to be fair he was he did have hodge okay he said he had hodgekin lin
yeah I remember he had cancer of some kind hodgekins lymphoma stage three which sounds
very serious he's the one who said that it had a 60 percent uh 65 a decent uh chance to survive
yeah and what I said to jessie at the time was well look it's his 60 percent that's that's wonderful
odds at a casino not what I want on my life oh sure but I don't understand why that many had to go
and fuck with with jessie and okay no no I'll explain what Sheldon's thing is that he would
mention he's like look man I might be dying do you think he'd be able to come on my podcast and
he said that jessie said sure and he kept putting them off and he kept putting them off and
you know on chemo you he said he was very suicidal and he's like look I'm just going to get him on
now you could say that that's rude or not but that was a really dark place that he's in
look if you want to hate Sheldon we're not friends right now I don't I don't really hate Sheldon
but I do remember this one thing as like a kind of a shitty thing that went down
oh yeah no it was a shitty thing I didn't know so are you saying that he did it as like kind of a
way to get jessie to be on his podcast or something like that jessie had agreed and yeah he was dying
suppose well he was in the realm of highly reasonably likely to be fatal did he how do you do
did he like beat it is he still sick he beat it okay well cool that was like two years ago three
years ago yeah yeah well I'm glad I'm glad to hear that now I remember basically when they were giving
me a hard time and I was like oh well you're a legit cancer and then they're like oh Vita's like
that's too far yeah show show me a medical report if you want to be like this prove to me that he
had cancer and that's where I became the bad guy yeah which I'll admit was a dick move but they were
pushing me don't do that I mean you know I'm glad I'm glad he I'm glad you know bounce back yeah
for sure um yeah I have a lot of cancer in my family so you know um hopefully I don't get cancer too
bad I just get a like a light case of the cancer yeah the good the shield and kind
um I want I want to go back this it says you have like 2000 sock puppet accounts no
how would you even what would even be the point of having that many like it would take you all day
to to manage I hand to God I do not have 2000 okay okay I'm trying to think across every web
across every website that I've ever been at that ever had I don't even know if I would have 2000
that way if you went to every website that I ever had to make a password and an account to maybe a
hundred let's say 200 for the sake of fucking mirth but no okay well I'm glad we could clear
all this up on the on the internet's number one drama talk show the bridefuckers console
yeah dog um um I like this classification by the way real quick here store brand keemstar I want
that to be the name of my band store brand keemstar oh me and Sheldon used to fight for that title I
was like I want to be keemstar I know faggot I'm gonna be keemstar who is who is the sbks uh nobody
yeah no one knows um bin did you have anything more to say this is like a picture back as like a
sort of uh you know just just come up and and change the conversation um let me let me ask a
quick quick question though once you since I obviously can't see because discord's fucked up on me
it's not showing my address on the video right uh what your your physical address there's no
kind of docs or anything on there's what I'm asking uh I don't think so if they're okay I'll go back
and look and if there is anything like that I'll make I'll make sure it's not shown yeah other than
that lit lit lit lit encyclopedia gematica the encyclopedia gematica yeah all right sure um yeah
do do you know like like like why do you think this came about like why do you think this was made
just just to fuck with you I guess okay um that's a good question to go further down the pipe um
I was arguing with horse news in another group which I won't give the name if you don't know
what it is if you can guess what it is I'll address it is it the pony is it the pony fuckers
cat the pony fuck cast no no no no okay you really are lost if you don't know what it is
beautiful I guess I'm lost I believe it oh no that's cool so anyways we'll say well we'll just
blame it on horse news okay you don't like it so and I was like look I've got this channel
covering me I've got this where's my fucking encyclopedia gematica bag it and then they made
it and I was like okay cool my life hasn't gotten any worse like it doesn't really do anything
okay well I mean that's good to hear so this was just like this this is like a like a joke
between friends I guess and I won't go that far okay I had this argument with licky I was like look
terrorist strong has an encyclopedia dramatic or is it no Lauren Faust has an encyclopedia
gematica there's a big furry name artists it's not the end of the world it doesn't like really hurt
you it's out there so you're just like you know why don't I have why don't I have one haha I guess
is how this came I was being a dipshit they made it okay I'm not asking and I'm not I haven't had
anyone go in there and edit the fucking thing I don't I'm not one of those faggots who goes in and
it's their tv tropes page and if you are I'm laughing at you yeah okay I'm looking at you Dr. Wolf
we can try we can do an entire thing on Dr. Wolf on Dr. Wolf oh I paid to come back for that
so so this is just like so this the entire thing is just like you know um just like like
stretching the truth and like lies and shit I guess um I don't have it open up in front of me
uh well here fucking take it bro um I don't know all right fine I'll look it up on
yeah here um yeah this this seems this seems like a lot of taut tall tales to me
they also mention they describe like Vita as like some like undercover like spy for your
fucking group he did run interference but during the medica bullshit he was completely on my side
for the longest time um when I broke ties with the pfc he sided with me so no there was a lot of
times where Vita was super cool with me I'm not going to rewrite history just because you know he's
a dick now yeah there was a lot of times he was cool and he left the fucking the people I was with
for better I don't know yeah I don't know if you want to describe as he's a dick now more like he's
like he wasn't a dick to me okay okay he's like uh he's very easily to switch alliances
in very awkward ways you can see it took a while yeah okay um yeah I'll look a proper name one
sec yeah of course take as long as you need um I'm glad I'm glad we can clear this all up I mean
I mean this there's probably more than you bargained for but I'm glad you came oh no it's I was I was
like what I was hope was concerned about I was like I hope Ben isn't screaming at me the whole time
no no no when we started this you know or earlier I was like you know we got we can't be too you
know mean to him and you know that's what we want to do we just wanted to clear there's no bad blood
and we've done that and we've gone above and beyond yeah and uh I think well I mean I don't
know if there's anything more to say about it really I'm having trouble freaking pulling it up on my
end uh I guess if you really need to you can freaking uh Skype me the thing uh I mean okay sure
I mean it won't take too much effort you know I don't want to uh you know keep you any longer than
you have to but I do I do think this is good to you know talk about have it out in the open
sure did you did it I don't care yeah yeah freaking Sargon when he read off his was
fucking comedy gold yeah yeah um did you did you see my did a while back did you see me and Sargon
had that had a fight on Twitter um I think they mentioned that over on uh pub crawl briefly
okay I just wondering uh it was just some bullshit just a bunch of
fucking faggots drinking the Sargon Kool-Aid uh jumped on me and you know
been a notorious critic of Sargon of Akkad yeah yeah famous anti Sargonites
okay what did you call him an outraged profiteer yeah yeah an outraged profiteer
which is so okay I'm trying to read this quote here look if she were completely okay she ripped
off a bunch of people 4 000 she would continue to be okay I'll be fine with that I don't ever say
on that okay um and like I don't know it doesn't have any proof like like does does it link to
anything I don't think so well there's a link to the horse news fucking video I did right goofed on
them okay there did I make a video where I fucking goddamn tried to argue that there aren't social
justice where is uh even there's a youtuber I watched called sticks hex and hammer and he basically
said there are social justice warriors but they're like rainbow unicorns you see one once in a lifetime
yeah people will act like you know the Sargon's of the world they're around every corner
oh oh I keep trying to claim that all Hillary Clinton and oh the Democrats are so like come on man
come on so yeah that's fun this if you go down the images there's this like Rick and Morty role
playing thing which is the the the funniest fucking thing I've ever seen in my entire life
on what the encyclopedia dramatically yeah yeah there's this like like on a youtube comment like
like you reply to someone and then like these two Rick and Morty like role players come in
and it's like says that you like you did this I can't imagine that that's the case because this is
the most ridiculous fucking thing I've ever seen in my life so it sounds funny why not okay
so you did sure all right yeah yeah I'm funny funny all right cool it's not like look if you have
you kept up with metacrystal uh no not really briefly I see like one or two I used to be a big
fan of him admittedly did you did you see the one he did on fucking um turn up with a goddamn spoony
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm I am not literally sitting around instead of going out
and doing things in the day dicking around canceling the log I might pop on dick with a friend
or somebody's giving me a hard time and then fuck off that's about it yeah okay
uh all right well all right uh do you want to munchie do you do you want to move on to
talking about other stuff because we've got some others we've got some other stuff we want to we
want to cover yeah but by I think fngr's done it done his job yeah and uh yeah we appreciate it
it's great to have you on sorry for the wait again I mean yeah thanks oh no no it's perfectly
fine I feel I feel pretty good I feel pretty good at this yeah I guess if I if I hear anything
was said afterwards um yeah yeah I mean this whole uh yeah I mean well this is this will be this will
be um this will be on the on the ratty fuckers so um I'm cool to use that clip that you gave me
before because I just took like a small portion maybe four or five minutes yeah of course yeah
I'll link back all right um right yeah yeah yeah just go ahead and see it's you uh you know when uh
when it comes up and you'll get to uh yeah see everything all right cool all right thank you
thank you thank you so much good I will have to end I will end process tree since fucking the
shit isn't working regularly that's fine oh all right yeah say we have all your stuff required
all right thank you yeah yeah no solid all right see you we're trying to get it to fucking work and
you there
okay can you hear me yeah yeah yeah you there holy fucking shit that was uh that was really something
that was really good do you like how you literally admitted that he did the fucking rick and morty
saying uh yeah I hadn't even I don't this is the most embarrassing fucking thing I've
ever seen in my life let me let me actually read it real quick um we'll know you're this is really
bad you faggot still slandered fallen wish this guy here is corpulent brony's man serve and see the
funny thing real human beings see what fallen did was unfortunate fortune parasites like yourself
sit around hopping people like fallen or tune critic commit suicide your account I stopped
horse news from getting an article and agents of discord that felt good cock blocking you fuckers
oh look a random four-channer morty they invented pedophilia and memes rick that's not nice not
every unforgiving fan is a four-chan pedophile with an inflation fedex that stalk girls and go
fun me and has a daddy this is not like an actual rick and morty role play no I don't know yeah
who would do this I mean I don't know why fngr would do this but I don't know why anyone else would
either but by the way fngr yes we were trying to fuck with you just to clear any misconceptions
yeah um I was I was really I was really afraid I didn't want to be too assertive I'm glad you
took the reins because I was I was too like like I couldn't not I couldn't not ask about the tune
critic thing no definitely I'm so glad you did because I was too scared because I was like I
didn't want to come on too strong because I was really afraid he was gonna back out I was the
entire time I was really afraid he was gonna be like oh fuck you guys bye I mean by the time we
got there I'd have been totally fine with him just being like oh fuck you guys this is all a troll
bye like it would have been like that would have actually been better than than what actually happened
um well I don't know he he fests up too a lot he did he did fests up too a lot um the uh
I mean I was yeah I was scared I was like nervous I was like oh god because like it's
such an uncomfortable topic and like I kind of felt bad but like I had to do it I was like I
was getting like the jitters like oh god I have to do it I have to bring up the I have to bring
up the tune critic thing um little disappointed that it didn't that he that he he took it in stride
so well yeah yeah um yeah he took it in stride which which is admirable I know you're listening
admirable yeah it is it is um um so so so good on you uh please don't role play rick and morty
anymore that's true and and I don't know I like I don't know I I don't think there's anything more
to say I don't regret anything I just I just wish uh I just wish he reacted in the way I want but
you know what but you know what good good on you good on you fngr yeah you uh you you you you you
done good you've done good you've done good um it's interesting that he didn't apologize at all
for for any of the stuff that he said but no but I get but I guess nothing you know um perhaps
perhaps we should we should we should have been more forthright with you know yeah um yeah about
how shitty it was but but but you know what maybe maybe maybe after maybe after this we don't deserve
it yeah definitely not um I'm back I'm back to frog fractions by the way okay go go ahead and
start up your stream share again so we can so we can actually no do you want to watch missanthopony's
video now it's a bowl full of wicker balls um hold on hold on some yeah wait wait yeah oh yeah uh
let me just fucking my my wife loves these wicker balls we've got a room full of them at home uh okay
by the way I'm really glad that we um that that that we legitimately just fucking like
played our video again yeah our video of his video like this is this this is a video of us
watching our old video about his video which features his video about our previous video
we're four layers deep and we're only getting deeper yeah um yeah fucking good stuff good stuff
I was I was really surprised how like admin he was about everything like like he didn't he didn't
back down about anything and I and I guess that's I I told I misjudged him I was I was afraid he was
going to you know fumble which which I which I guess he did a little bit but you but you know what
you know what I guess it can't be two it can't be two I am man I still hate him though oh he's
he's terrible he's the worst um no no mercy yeah no mercy all right you want to you want to jump
into missanthopony yeah yeah by the way do you do you believe that the two great stuff happens
I totally do like like like his his language during that was totally like I if not that something
happened something definitely I mean the fact that it's framed as an orgy makes it sound like
someone just like being deliberately salacious with their rumor mongering so but yes something
almost for for it to have gotten any traction something definitely must have happened but
I was looking at I was looking at the um oh fuck did you did you link the uh the encyclopedia
Dramatica yeah yes I did okay um I was looking at a document uh that was linked at the bottom
it was like a uh the horse news article about fallen wish and let me let me control f for tune
critic I do that every single day of my life on every page I don't even see him mentioned here
so I don't know so now now I'm just curious what tune critics relation to this orgy is
do you believe that he that he wasn't dating her at the time um I believe due to my my my my
priviness to this sort of situation I believe they must have been communicating in a somewhat
lascivious way yeah I don't know if he was specifically dating her though I I totally
believe that he was quote unquote cucked yeah absolutely absolutely maybe he was like courting
her at the time yeah something like that like they weren't official but he was trying to get some and
then fucking to oh but you know I didn't realize that fngr was at brony con he was at this brony
yeah yeah I thought like it's he was somewhere else and this happened like no he was fucking there
and then this this this vague event occurred uh so that's pretty cool pretty great pretty what yeah
it's pretty good all right I'm pretty satisfied I'm pretty satisfied yeah yeah I'm pretty good
I'm pretty good about the whole thing um fngr I know you're still watching this I'm not sorry no no
no um are are are are are we are we bad people sure but but you know what but you know what you
gotta be a bad person in this doggie dog it is a doggie dog world and and and and this brony
herd sort of world he she was she was dating a herd of bronies uh hold on oh christ
you want to you want to jump into misanthropone apology yeah yeah I have I have a lot to say
about misanthropone's apology it is I appreciate some of it like there's some of it that I appreciate
but there's equal parts of it that I think are stupid and oh I just I just want to I I'm I'm I'm
I did not think that we like originally I did not think we were going to do like an entire
thing about it because um I didn't know if we had enough to say is it so so misanthropone if you're
watching uh I I don't know uh fuck with Ben don't fuck with me bro uh well I mean I will I'll say up
front that misanthropone says that he wants to like end this and like I'm fine with ending this
year so I'm I mean I'm gonna stick to my guns on everything that I believe about this situation
but I'm not I'm not doing this I'm not doing this to like pick more of a fight I'm actually I'm
acknowledging this so that we can so that it can be over because yeah because I'm I'm tired of it
I'm tired of it yeah yeah and like you don't get to have the last say in the matter since since he
since he started it yeah I'll you know I'm I'm not gonna I'm not gonna I'm not doing this to be
inflammatory is what I'm saying I'm gonna take a piss I'll be right back okay keep playing
frog fractions entertain the audience I'm gonna throw this up this time I'm fucking
stuck on frog fractions like
okay
well without munchie I'm I'm lost I'm a I'm a little lost boy I got nothing to say
is nothing nothing to say on my own I got nothing of interest to contribute
perhaps this video game will provide much needed interests
oh there's box okay
damn it
okay I got that got that thing oh I turned the volume off god I'm so
fucking boring I'm so fucking boring I'm sorry everyone I'm sorry for the way that I am
let's fucking get these video game tunes pump in
the game is the game does a pretty good job of like when it wants something specific to happen
it it railroads you the way where it needs you to go that makes me out I bit my tongue
that makes me feel good that makes me feel good and like I don't have to worry that I'm fucking
things up I really thought I fucked things up
I really thought that I fucked things up when I restarted the game and I didn't have the
what you call it I didn't have the sword but of course that was just me being confused because
as a matter of fact the sword was in my stockpile the whole time this game fucking rules
uh I I'm really hoping to finish it this video because I kind of don't want another video on
it but I'd feel bad not finishing it so uh yeah I gotta fucking get serious gotta get serious about
shit did you win yet I wish I want I was just saying I want I really want to finish this game
like but I don't honestly I have no idea how much of it is left
um I want I want to draw this this frog fraction series to a close do you want to go just until
we finish do you think that's doable like until we finish um what game the game I would if
if at all possible oh there's a secret thing uh yeah yeah well I'll tell you what if it if we
gets too late and like there's just no end in sight maybe we'll have to call it but I'm ready I'm
ready to go for a while yet yeah yeah I'm ready but we have unfinished business uh on the show
hold on should I screen share yeah of course okay because I'm um fucking barbarian uh how do I wait
how do I do it uh you want to do that thing again where you screen share and it gives me the ability
to screen share because I don't I don't have the button for it okay uh most certainly
okay here we go oh f and gr oh f and gr did yeah no no apologies no apology just uh you
know it was a heat of the moment thing uh yeah you know I was just being salty fuck off yeah um well
you know uh six and throw in six and stones may bake my bones but fuck you f and gr yeah
hey you're crunchy again but I guess that's um no actually been the names of munchie I think
you would have gone that I fucked up I fucked up I fucked up bad all right okay okay all right
oh no oh my god the worst the worst year possible
oh
oh this is the legendary shave obama game legendary
hey your name came in a new fucking name more influential person for pcp than president
rock obama um jesus I love you jesus cry um i'm trying to click this beat
I don't know maybe obama likes it maybe obama likes it that way maybe obama likes the levels
oh my god it's the control is so fucking finicky
this doesn't even look like obama it's just like my dad it kind of looks like him from some angles
I guess this is what'll be I guess this is just can obama now there's one more little
fucking no with air right there you're a timer bro you're a timer I know I'm trying to fucking click
there oh my god embarrassing Ben
teen obama look at his mom
wow you did it or did I
oh shit
oh no he's let it come back yeah in the like 20 years the past
he's got some very fine beard hair for an african-american true wait he's not african
never you know what I mean yeah um wait wait wait yes he is no he's african yeah I know because
of his his brother the true person um um do you remember when you didn't have a beard do you
remember how this hard name that was yeah um I think oh fuck I think I look way better with the
beard of course no one no one would ever say for a fucking second that you did not Jackie insists
that I look equally good with her without sometimes I even think she likes me without but me really
yeah I mean she I mean that's just that maybe I'm reading too much into it but she's like I'm like
I'm always like when I'm when I'm beardless I'm like man I gotta get the beard back and she's
always like no it's fine it's fine it's fine without and I'm like really to me it's not fine
I think it's a huge improvement no Ben it's it's it's it's it's impossible it's impossible without
the beard it's impossible yeah I can't I can't do it I can't I just can't make it work
it's yeah like yeah the beard the beard the beard symbolizes all that there is it to you
I've got a shape I've got to shave this bomb
yeah as a bomb is known to do
oh god you're running out of time dude
this is this is how beard physics work
I think I did pretty all right I don't know if you heard or if you saw
but the other day on Twitter I was very impressed with your looks at the fair at the carnival
I did see that I did yeah I liked that tweet um yeah it was nice yeah approaching approaching a
conventional I voted Q&A levels of conventional attractiveness or something along
yeah yeah something along those lines you're really doing you're really becoming you're
approaching conventionality yeah every this is what I'm like every every like six months or so
I'll I'll cut my own hair just because it's gotten too long and I'm sick of it and uh I did that
recently and uh you know so for a while I've got the uh I look like a normal human being
as as I described uh in the real friend initiative you look you had like medieval
poet hair and whenever and whenever you were in the room and I saw you I just like you're gonna
dance around and act like the bard you are yeah um I that actually made me miss the hair quite a bit
because I was like dammit I didn't capitalize on the on the bard look yeah you you were you were
definitely bardish yeah you resembled you resembled a bard in in in most ways in in on every level
including this in looks as well as demeanor yeah god dammit upsetting this is so goddamn hard
whenever you're on recording and there's discord open I get so fucking scared you had you had just
moved please move discord out of the way so you don't accidentally click and like show and like
show everyone our dirty laundry and you won't edit it out of course I won't edit that I never
I would never edit anything here here or anywhere else
I did it I fucking did it
um
oh obama he died as he lived shaving what a what a rascal
well how how fucking many how many of you Jesus Christ
yeah obama's gonna be doing fine in in uh wait wait is this the pass
or the no no no you're doing it to his dad now it's the bomb is bad oh okay
uh all right I'm glad we're clear how long does this go on for I don't know I hope it's over soon
it's oversight it's welcome it it really is I mean maybe I'm missing something
because like in in the in the toaster game there was like a secret thing that I had to do
to um you know to find to find that item which was like the real point of the game so I'm assuming
I'm supposed to get some kind of item from this um can I just like cut I just cut up his nose with
the uh with the razor that's good that's I'm probably on the right track so far you've done a
terrible job but the game is exceptionist I think it's just going forever until you like fuck with
them somehow I mean unfortunate look at tiny obama back there
oh I got it oh oh oh there you there you go okay I just had to fucking
you wake with a start what a strange dream
dear god once I dreamt I was president obama I was conscious only of my happiness as president
obama unaware that I was myself now I do not know whether I was then a fairy dreaming I was president
obama or whether I'm now president obama dreaming I am a fairy yeah that's well that's life
they're gonna have to update this game sooner or later oh did you see that yeah
how odd how odd uh
yeah there's something about I don't think this has ever been fully uh lightened up
uh I did I did before you know like you got the cyan key go ahead and go in there I do
oh yeah I do have this oh it's like I'm on like a timer
Jesus Christ I wish this game would be fucking over it's uh yeah it's it's it's a bit much
let me just do this bit and then
oh god move your sword move your sword I think if you go inside dude
oh yeah perfect okay so now you can return there I guess is the point
what but I want to get I I wish we could see a fucking frog I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm getting
I'm getting antsy I'm getting antsy to see frogs
I want um
I really want to touch these like key things over fuck
I saw I guess you have until 1145 to do shit I guess those
I guess those things don't do anything
Ben I don't even want to like look at this game anymore hold on just let me
I don't even want to I don't even want to I don't even want to
all right I'll come back press one of your fucking board
uh let me grab all my items and then uh and then we'll go and then we'll let's go check
out uh misanthroponies magnum opus shall we yeah yeah
oh christ oh oh christ please please I love you jesus christ
I want to die let me just oh I see it changes the time
oh okay so what I have to I have to go to the gift shop I have to change the the time
and go to the gift shop got it okay okay anyway um that's enough of that for now yeah that's
enough of that forever uh here I'm in the wash get it go go ahead and uh let's see misanthroponies
I'm gonna stop screen sharing yeah of course because it was making your audio a little crunchy
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah um um here we go here we go he's like described that's okay here we go
way behind so so so so welcome back to tbap everyone um you know we had a briefly intermission
there we let our fucking crony friends um ruin the entire video by being incredibly
unenthusiastic and bored and tired uh one of them specifically because he woke up at
fucking at at at 4 a.m local time um great a good good good time well time for him
um uh uh highly appreciated the dedication to the rowdy fuckers uh brand yeah um so so so fan
let's go ahead let's go ahead and put I I think I think this is really we have a couple more tricks
up our sleeves you know we're always looking we're always looking to you know be to be a
trickster and to be and to be a prankster but I think this is one of the last performances
we're gonna we're gonna give together I feel in my bones um you want to break up the band
you want to break up the band lunchy um I'm I'm I'm not saying that I'm just saying you know
I I feel I feel I feel I feel like I feel like we've overstayed our welcome I feel like we've
I feel like we've accomplished what we sad to do and and and to prolong our existence any longer
would it would just be would just be dishonest to our original goal sure yeah I mean I'm all about
I want to mean like like the integrity of the rowdy fuckers brand needs to be maintained above all
above all else even even if maintaining that integrity means destroying the entire operation
and pulling the yeah yeah yeah I'll stand by that um um so so phantom yeah this this is the
last this is the last real tango we're gonna we're gonna have some break dances here and there
but why don't we get why don't we why don't we reach closure for for fucking ones in our pitiful
lives I would like that but first um munchy I mean strawberry I mean milk uh mr milk um I
mr milker mr milk uh I I gotta I gotta pee I'll be right back in a second I gotta pee and turn the
fan on because it's real hot in here okay yeah you know honestly it was audience it was a real
pleasure it was a real pleasure you know being your co-host ever since the the tragic disappearance
and and and assumed murder of of one uh keg standard and I've been completely honored to be on on
this legendary channel in order to you know um help uh help help clear up ben and munchy's name
you know our our group friends ben and munchy I'm very happy I got to spend these these wonderful
moments with you and and and I hope you had the time of your life that that song uh that should
be playing what's in your brain right now we had a lot of goofs we had a lot of gaff we had a lot
of people being mad at us because we were just too smart for our own good um you know um that
sort of cheery stuff and and and you know and you know if you really want to come back um um if
you really want to see more prime tbvap content with with yours truly strawberry milk um and
its first ever canonical video project series and and and and and and old faithful and and and the
old the old classic the old classic phantom horn um please please show your love and adoration um
and and and and and just maybe we'll be back one day okay i'm back gonna head phones gonna head phones
in wait i didn't turn the fan on it's still hot okay oh oh god okay and we're at every single time
every single day i have to record a pcp project and i have to close my fan and then and then i get
so fucking miserable and hot and fucking baked and fucking steamed i turned into a steam uh steamed
clam and and and you just bliss blissfully unaware of your own privilege my ceiling can slap on your
own fan and i'm lucky i have a pretty quiet ceiling fan it's it rules it rules um i want to die
not good just the way i like it um but yeah as i was saying to our audience if if you know
hashtag hashtag um um um keep being alive you too yeah if you want to keep being alive if you
don't keep being alive um we will send the cops on you to fuck you up in a rowdy kind of way
hardcore hardcore see see you've been ringing the name the name wrong the entire time we haven't
been killing cops well i mean we have we have that that's neither here nor there yeah we are
actually in charge of the entire police force and we're ready to we're not we're not killers of cops
we're cops who are killers yes yeah and we are killers of cops but but but again yeah it works
it works both ways yeah we're the true neutral of of the brawny nautz community here on tba we're
the true neutral um are you ready are you ready uh phantom i am ready i'm ready to uh put this to
bed yeah to i'm i'm ready to go to bed uh where the sleeps go in case you did not know where the
sleeps go bed uh here we go certain stuff and i need to get back on track but there's something
that i want to bring proper closure to and i want to get the closure out before too long
months ago there was a certain fallout between me and ben saint and to say that i was upset about it
is an understatement let's just say things were said and it got me real riled up and i felt like
that it was something that needed to be addressed but looking back at it now i figured that it was
not the best way to handle this situation i think it oh okay okay well yeah okay well to
phrase it like that implies that you and this this beautiful beautiful star child this this this
indigo child this this this pure this purely elated fucking gentleman um on a cosmic level
where i don't know pals or something to see there's like a falling out when really we just made
a funny video well yeah yeah there was no there was no falling out there was just
this guy who i do not care about even the tiniest bit getting mad at us like he got it was him
getting mad it was not this was not like a breakup of the brain trust mm-hmm yeah and and you know
it's good it's good you've learned from your mistakes yeah for the a thousandth time yeah but
you know don't don't don't pin this on us bro don't don't don't don't don't don't try and say
that we we were equally at fault here um we would have never fucking even i don't think we even knew
who ms antherpony was in our original video uh i i did not know about him i i i had seen him around
well well i knew about him because he had pissed off we're not pissed off mage because he had
fucked with mage in the past and she was real sad about it for a while really yeah yeah she was uh
yeah she was really bothered by some shit map was saying about her uh and i guess and i guess
map is uh sorry about all that which is fine and and for the record uh we do not speak for mage
we speak purely for ourselves here and you're saying that we uh are uh not friends with you
i don't know how mage feels now yeah um um i'm sure she is benevolent yeah as she always is yeah
was because the main thing that was on my mind was how upset i was over what they said about keyframe
and it led me to making several errors in the process of that video i thought it was a reasonable
response at the time but looking back at it now there were plenty of things that i could have
done differently now keep it sure i mean i don't know i'm i'm i'm glad i'm glad this guy
is like sorry for being stupid um and like saying that there are errors and i truly am
appreciative he but i don't know like this is sort of like a like you know things could have been
better not like i was wrong uh yeah i did not i do not know he he's not quite apologizing well
well he i think he does apologize for some certain things later on uh but yeah there's a lot of what
there's a lot of what fngr was doing just before where it's like it's not apologizing it's excuse
making yeah yeah yeah yeah but like yeah we're not we're not getting we're not getting any apologies
here we're not being able to cash in any of our apology fund bugs here we're just we're
going to be taken for a ride exactly and and here and finally to fucking you know we we're not
probably caught him to fucking freaks around here no never um mind that this video oh what oh no i
was yeah continue please he's not meant to attack then saint on any level i just he says that now
but later on there's a couple points about the videos in question and i want to try and do it
properly and just to ensure that absolutely nothing is blown out of proportion i'm going to
take this quick vow i swear on the soul of my grandmother that i am not going to get angry
i'm not going to raise my voice he totally breaks this i will not reply to any comments in a way
that instigates more fighting and while we're on the subject i would deeply appreciate it if anyone
who chooses to comment he he says that he's not gonna the comments but i remember like the day
or like the day after this video came out i saw him being shitty in a comment thread on our video
so like okay great i'm i'm i don't want to go find the comment right now but i'm extremely
confident that it was posted at some point so he he yeah you know on this video did the same thing
i humbly ask that you will not leave any comments that will instigate more fighting this topic is
going to be controversial enough as it is and i want to keep it contained recently ben saint
uploaded a video on his old pony channel that he worked on with the best guy ever his brother it's
basically a follow-up to that first frog fraction video and as you probably guessed it contained a
response to my previous video on the matter now i'm not saying that ben was wrong to make a response
to my video he has every right to do that but i do feel there are many many things to address in
terms of how he and munchie respond to it now i i am i am pretty confident there's gonna be a lot
of things that we are going to respond to you right now he he gets progressively madder like he
definitely gets mad in this video or at least at least annoyed at the very least so um fucking let
let's see the response that they did was literally over an hour long so naturally there's going to
be a lot to say i'll try not to make it too long as this probably what are we're on they basically
start off by saying that t-bab was not a commentary series as i put it and i suppose that is correct
on some level commentaries and reviews are somewhat the same thing since they're both an expression
of opinion they do i don't know why he's even bothering to talk about saying that it's not
interesting but it's also unique despite that it is possible for something to be unique but still
lacking something good it was unique and how different it was from what other people were
doing at the time but that doesn't always equal interesting i can at least i mean we did have
some things to say about his criticisms of t-bab so i guess he felt the need to respond to those and
like explain what he didn't like about t-bab but like yeah who fucking cares you know i mean i don't
know like it's valid like you know it's valid but like it's really it's really not the point like
my issues the issues here had nothing to do with t-bab um and i don't know like i i suppose like
it's true that something can be unique and not good but he was saying that it was interesting so like
like i don't know like it doesn't have to be good per se you don't have to like t-bab i mean if you
don't then you're fucking moron yeah you don't have to yeah it's just you know like like like like
this was this was more unique and interesting than anything else happened in the entire fandom
at this point so fucking i mean i that's our full point i should think so but you know but
he says he says more later about like us versus the other brony analysis or something we'll
fucking get we'll understand like people would be interested in it it just didn't interest me but
then it gets confusing when they start talking about how complex it was without actually saying
why it was complex i mean they do say that it has jokes and editing and intros but basically
everyone had that stuff were they saying that the jokes were complex were the intros complex
was there something in the editing that was complex i'm just asking what exactly made it so
yeah yeah in a word yes there really wasn't any complexity to it getting together with a friend
or a relative and i don't want to oversell the genius of t-bath or anything like it was what it
placing cartoon caricatures of yourselves on real like especially later like
like the the fact that he could that he would find other analysis interesting like the fact
that he would find something like silver quill interesting and then be like oh well t-bap just
didn't have anything interesting for me like like i don't i i don't understand like and like okay
like sure at the end of the day you could say like t-bap is about two people talking about
my little point episode yeah and then a stand a standard reviewer is just a guy talking about my
little point episode yeah at the core and on paper they are the same yeah but t-bap has so much more
and first of all you have to account for like like like most my little pony reviewers have very limited
you know animation and changes in their voice where t-bap is a fucking ton and it's like basically
every episode there's a new twist there's one where you guys are in fucking like a night armor
there's one where you guys have like the body of fucking john scene and some black fucking basketball
yeah yeah yeah um there's crazy shit going on there's the one where we we uh we took those
cuteness pills and we got the big anime eyes that stayed through the entire video that i really
like that one um so there's so much shit going on with that aspect of the video not to mention the
intros which are fucking legendary and more like far and above like better than anything anyone
else is doing at the time more complex in every way there's that one where you like like like you
put more effort into this one than the entirety of the brony fandom did are in anywhere combined
whatsoever where you fucking you you got like fake horse hooves and like try to draw with
fucking horse hooves on and like spill the ink all over the fucking table and it was in jeans and
fucking incredible yeah um that's one of my favorite that's one of my favorite things i've
ever i've ever put on the internet yeah god i just i wish it had i wish i'd had a better camera
because the quality really sucks but whatever the the point gets across yeah uh yeah so that so
that's more complex than fucking just record like like just having those interests is that one where
you like anime and entire like visual novel fucking sequence yeah that one that got taken down
but it's uh it's back up it's back up now uh yeah um fucking yeah i don't see how you can
fucking ignore all that and be like oh well uh fucking uh dr wolf and kp and silver quill and
all these other fucking jabronis oh they all had jokes to fuck off you know well again it's
about the point like whether or not missanthropony likes tbap is not the point but if he doesn't
then he's retarded so is our humble opinion is our humble opinion okay but by the way i mean i
wouldn't even i wouldn't even i wouldn't wait wait sorry go on if evan jaren left the writer
for example there's boot camp oh good yeah he didn't make the cut he makes the cut yeah um
it can continue can he like i wouldn't i wouldn't hold it against anyone if they didn't like tbap
but the fact that he likes he doesn't like tbap but he likes i mean i don't know specifically
what he likes but i'm i'm just gonna fucking yeah dr wolf silver quill it's et cetera like
fuck off like jesus fucking christ um basically yeah basically that's how i feel okay screen in front
of a background and footage of the episode is only going to get you so far also for a series that was
so complex it really went through a decline in creativity when later reviews were just a boring
image of a screensaver with the i will agree there sure how stupid it was for him to complain about
how the video was called frog fractions but most of it was about shit talking people and no i'm still
not gonna let that go because it is a problem with the way that the video was being presented
it's a misleading title however you look at it the title is advertising something that isn't the main
focus of the video or something that's only there for a fraction of the length which comes
across as misrepresented like what really just annoys me about it is how it's a problem that can
easily be fit i feel like i feel like he's he's advocating troll movie titles you know yeah yeah
like like for it not for it to be fully honest the fucking title would have to be like several
sentences long explaining what we do and obviously that's taken into the stream he would just he would
just like to be called shaded on bronies and also frog fractions yeah but i don't know just like
the point of the video is that it blindsides you with fucking like like being this crazy that you
did not expect and also it what you could tell because we put lightning bless in the fucking
thumbnail yeah i don't i really i really do not get what the fucking problem is with the fact
with with with the title like oh my god it's it's it's got some stuff in it that the title didn't
fucking indicate what what ddo yeah fucking helps at it at the words two friends bitching at ponies
and the title youtube has something that allows you to do that they themselves said that the video
should have been split into two parts one on the game and one on them shit talking these people
i might have said it as a joke like i'm doing this by accident now to be clear i never accused
them of accidentally doing any of this i can tell that they meant to do all of this random
shit but because of the title it still feels like a trap it feels like it is a fucking trap it's
deliberately a trap that's part of the joke yeah i don't know how can he be so mundane and reserved
and calm when you see big baby boy i know he i mean i don't know he's just got some fucking he's got
some expectation i don't know i i feel like he's holding us to a higher standard than he would
for someone else like if someone else like if some vlog channel titled their vlog like uh sucking
sucking dick on the vegas strip and then like one minute was actually sucking dick yeah and the rest
is like what they had for breakfast that morning is he got is would he would he fucking complain i
sincerely doubt it so i don't i don't feel like these are reasonable expectations that he's operating
under and also that that's that's what like like it could we could make it that but that would be
way less funny yeah because like it's funny that someone to her click on this thinking it's just
going to be frog fractions when like a large portion of it isn't frog fractions that doesn't mean
it's dishonest that just mean that like it adds to the video and also we play frog fractions yeah
that's that's the game we play what do you want i don't know i don't know what
fucking would make map happy i don't know yeah i don't know yeah well and a lot of people are
extremely happy that we did that like yeah but we a lot of our fans love that fucking video they
love this video series so fucking um if you don't like it well sorry bro he's entitled to his opinion
but i think it's his opinion is dumb and misses the point and yeah whatever yeah yeah yeah this video
four hours long but they sidestep the idea of making it about frog fractions and they didn't
know what they wanted the other four hours of the video to be about it's not like in the other
rowdy fuckers cop killers we just talked about nuclear throne or whatever yeah yeah which only
further shows how bad the direction is and another thing about that video is that it just wasn't going
to be all that encouraging to watch with that ridiculous four hour length there's a reason why
people okay are now he's just yeah he's making plain assumptions about what our fans want he's
just like our our fans fucking love long videos this is a fact you you fucking goable fucking
sack of shit watching this right now not you miss hand they're funny all of our fans you fucking
eat this shit yeah you've been sitting here for four and a half hours and you're craving more and
guess what you're gonna get more yeah you're gonna get far more than you could ever fucking want of
us yeah um and that's and that's what keeps them coming back uh yeah so miss anthroproni our our
fans are not are not overly consenting but they are actively fucking they are actively pursuing
they are they are actively they are actively pursuing the most like fucking like mundane
and fucking long form content humanly possible they watch digi bro yeah these people watch digi bro
do you understand can you even imagine can you imagine the kind of person um i i frankly can't
i which is all to say thank you for watching our content i just i feel he's like he's trying to
offer blanket statements about what a video should be and it's like where do you get off
where do you get off telling me what this video should be so i'll never i'll never fucking agree
with anything that he says on the subject of the video's titled wrong the video's too long
blah blah but no it's the video is exactly what it's supposed to be it's perfect yeah it's
people break up their videos and departs if the thing they want to talk about is very long
it gives the audience a chance to collect themselves and be refreshed by the time the next
part comes out the idea of going through all four hours of that video in one sitting is extremely
overwhelmed it's no reasonable our video just has a has a high has a low has a high skill floor
one hour long be it one sitting or giving yourself a break from it every once in a while but quadrupling
that feels needlessly time consuming he also says that my accusation of his disappearing from the
fandom were incorrect perhaps that is true but he needs to know that i was a casual viewer of tbap
around the time okay so i obviously wasn't going to be that encouraged to go through his deviantart
or his twitter because i wasn't a huge fan of his work he's it's it's there's no denying but yeah
tbap did stop uploading and i guess i don't even i don't even blame him for saying that i disappeared
from the fandom like if that's i don't remember what he said in the video but if he said i disappeared
from the fandom like that's true and uh there's no arguing that he was like you blipped off the
fucking map with with no fucking rhyme or reason okay well that's if yeah if you're only looking
at tbap i i guess whatever it's fine nope no big no no big i also wasn't exactly aware of the pcp
until fairly later on and when i started watching its videos is when i got the idea that ben and
his brother had retired from mlp reviews i should point out that i did work the two starting their
own channels in an exaggerated way claiming that they split up but still stayed in contact they
never actually split up they simply stopped uploading on that channel and i could have worked it that
better okay there's an instance where he talks about what he thinks is my background in which he
states that there was a time that i hated jesse wood or drowning in horseshoes now that's not true
because i never really hated or i don't remember saying that but i'll take his
word for it during season four and i progressively became a fan of his stuff it did take time for
me to get used to his content as i was new to his channel but i quickly warmed up to it and really
got into the way that he reviews the show cool he was and still is a reviewer capable of providing
thought-provoking analysis breaking down the product in great detail while still injecting it
with a creative sense of humor he may not be as popular as a lot of the others but to this day
he's still one of my all-time favorite reviewers of mlp whether he thinks highly of it or not i felt
that it was necessary to bring this up because the way that he says this line is based on false
assumption he also states that i was oblivious to the way that he referenced that video that i made
in one of his pony cast videos i was aware that he was taking a stab at my video and i didn't want
that to bother me i just wanted to enjoy the video because i do think the man puts out great work
i will admit though i was very why why why couldn't you just leave us be then
like yeah yeah it's like not just why why why do you have to make a video about us yeah what was
the point i i don't know why he wouldn't think i mean i'm so happy you did yeah i'm so ecstatic
that you decided to but from your point of view what did you gain like from like if you want if
you wanted to stay like if you if you wanted to stay in jesse's good graces like taking taking uh
you know taking a shit on us isn't isn't gonna help you do that uh but i mean
i don't know i i guess that's all i have to say yeah uh yeah just just i don't know like if you're
if you can dismiss that sort of thing which is an admirable trade then fucking where was that
where's that capability when we released five options one oh yeah yeah yeah oh right you're
you're saying like why didn't he get mad about jesse uh doing that like like what yeah um i don't
know yeah good question i guess he just likes jesse more i all right yeah fair enough and how i
pronounced him not liking burning donut my intention wasn't out of place but the way that i
said it was it was basically hypocritical of me to state that he was criticizing what someone
does on the internet when i myself was doing the same thing that first video i did was actually
unscripted which would explain why i didn't have good direction now when he originally went at
burning donut he stated that he fucking hates the guy because he's a good artist was able to upload
on a consistent schedule whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa no i did not say i hate him because he's a good
artist who's able to upload on a consistent schedule there's no fucking way i said that
yeah that doesn't doesn't sound like your christ isn't okay i said i hated him and like i've said i
would i did i did not mean that that was i was hard i was hard on burning donut um but i didn't
say all right let's keep going yeah apparently he doesn't really delve into that much like he
literally gives us no reason to side with him on how burning donut is a stupid person deserving
i i explained what was wrong with the patron okay like all i knew about burning donut was how his
patreon was laid out and it fucking was asinine like i did i did i explain how like his page like
his top reward was like if you don't if you patron me for $50 you will become a part you will like
basically fucking write my comic for me yeah and i was like oh my god that's that like not i'm i'm
walking back what i said about burning donut but i'm not walking back that that is the stupidest
thing i've ever fucking heard and i think it's asinine and terrible uh it doesn't make burning
donut a bad person or even a bad artist necessarily um but whatever yeah i think his
matters patron are still valid it's just that you know yeah yeah yeah i i overstated i overstated
the the the level of enmity based on it there uh you know i was i was feeling it we were we were
riffing we were riffing on on dudes and and and you know burning donut got caught up in the crossfire
a little bit you know uh there was some collateral damage you know i could make i should make some
reparations and i might and i'm making them now yeah brain don't if you're watching this please
fix your page yeah i guess um yeah god anyway except that the two have different ways of
constructing their patreon if you need further context on this don't not recently made a video
with a portion talking about what exactly was wrong with ben's criticisms towards him then
might have stated in the newer video that he was too harsh on him but he doesn't do it oh did i already
say that and his ego boasting during that segment still feels really grating i admit again that the
way i worded that part of my video was wrong but burning donut does point out a lot of like
stupid nitpicks that we made like like when i like i i said like because it said listening to
and he put suicidal tendencies so i thought he was being emo and be like oh i'm listening to my own
suicidal tendencies turns out no that's a band so i'm just an idiot okay okay so there was a couple
of there was a couple of things like that that it's like you know it's not really it's not really
the main point but there were mistakes remain but nevermind nevermind but that doesn't make
what ben did above criticism he gave us no reason to justify him dissing burning donut except for
the patreon thing which even in itself isn't really valid evidence and even though what wasn't
really mentioned in the new video it still really bothers me how he thinks it's not evidence of a
larger crime it just is dumb on its own they were making more money than him b they were
making money at all or c he thinks these people are below him and don't deserve support for what
they do even if he does think he's better than a lot of these people it's still very condescending
how he actually puts time into explaining it in such visceral detail he complains about the
these people expressing their talents and making a living off of them which is not only selfish
but pointlessly childish now it was really misleading on my end to say that ben saint was
talking about these people like he didn't know any of them because he was very involved in the
community before i was even a part of it i did know beforehand that he was associated with these
people and that he even did a couple of panels with them i also know that he argued with josh
for hours over the pinky wrap which was actually what caused them to leave the original rinse
but the ways he complains about them well did i did i talk about that no i have no idea what he's
talking about that sounds incredible well do you remember that i forget i remember the stupid
fucking nineties pinky wrap and fucking that one where rambodash has like downstairs or which
yeah yeah well i really liked that part and yeah and yeah because it was because they really went
all out with like the the fucking the vhs the vhs effects and like the screen uh this what's
the screen resolution like they really sold that this is like a nineties wrap video and i
thought it was really great and josh comes and josh comes fucking wandering into the rift cafe
where all the cool bronies hang out and he just has a fucking problem with it he thinks it's he
you know he he calls it he called it cringy and then like would not elaborate
like he had no reason for calling it and i fucking yeah i picked a fucking fight with him over it
i don't remember if that is exactly what i left the rift for it might have been
but i mean i wouldn't have just left over that like i left because that happened and i already
thought it was a retarded thing anyway that was like the straw that broke the camel's back
bin yeah i want to do like a real t-bap one day yeah i want i want to watch my little pony with
you one day oh my god one day just guys hashtag uh please do that but like i'd have to watch so
much to get caught up no we could just pick a random one if you find what what's gonna what could
have changed all right changed um you know what yeah i guess i would do one okay i guess i could
do it at some point why why press one if you want that to happen yeah did you leave the room did you
leave the watch together no no i'm no i'm i would never i would never leave it says you left uh
whatever um um yeah uh well just go ahead and press play also fngr just said sorry i didn't
get your your notification on on twitter um so you know um that that that's fine sure the website
still feels is it playing for you no yeah i'll i'll i'll i'll i'll i'll reset i'll i'll refresh okay
okay oh god i'm hungry yeah i'm starving we've been we've been going for a while we've been going
for like four and a half hours we'll never stop no never it doesn't this video this video is gonna
be seven hours long uh i didn't realize our our our our longest one was only like four four and
some hours so this might actually be the longest one we've ever done um that's fine yeah yeah yeah
yeah i'm push the push the limit i mean i mean i mean i mean you know missy other probably isn't
going to be able to watch the entire thing but you know yeah you know we we have we have a higher
skill floor we we we we we catered to wales you don't cater to the cater to wales yeah yeah yeah
that's true um all right you you ready should we go yeah yeah yeah go ahead mention any personal
experiences with the guy he doesn't even scroll down slow enough to even look at anything that was
on his page he just says that he wants to destroy the website which at this point really wouldn't
faze anyone and a lot of the segments he does in that first video are like this he knows several
of these people but he doesn't talk about any personal experiences he had with them and even
when he comes close to talking about something like that it's only more immature banter there's
no real earnesty to any of the ways he complains about these people i don't these are what these
are vague these are vague complaints like i he he doesn't talk about them but he kind of does
but when he does it's just immature banter so it doesn't count yeah it's i he's trying to be vague
so we can't pull it apart because i guess what he's saying is like technically true on some level
though mischaracterized and phrased weirdly to the point where i don't feel comfortable accepting
no i don't feel like he's really saying anything i feel like he's dancing around
because as we stated he doesn't care about this if this was just if these are the only
problems with the video he would not care here's about one thing specifically and we will get to
that later yeah um yeah it just feels like excuses for bitching as for using the rift website for
making points on these people there actually is an instance where me saying ben talks about
these people like he doesn't know them at all is correct yeah and that woman comes from him
talking down lightning bliss let's see wasn't even making a name for her i've never communicated
the time that ben left so i know from experience that he knows nothing about her and yet he judges
her specifically for what he sees on her page the lengths that he goes to just to talk her down feel
extremely grating it doesn't make me mad as you might assume it just feels really ignorant and
annoying he thinks he knows everything about her just by looking at her oc and saying that she had
a moment with dr wolf about being judged for having an alicorn oc and even though something
like that did happen you get the sensation that ben never saw the video or even knew that i specifically
talk about the video i did watch the video or at least a bunch of it and i i don't know i don't
know what he's going on about and like i is it is it not fair like i know i don't know this person
in real life but is it not fair like this this oc and that moment with dr wolf are our works of you
know art that were put out that were they were created by this person and put onto the internet
so how is it not fair to judge them based on them and i think they're terrible and embarrassing and
i hate them so like what's the fucking problem what do you want from me if you can't be judged by
your art then your art is worthless yeah yeah i agree if you don't put a part of you into your art
and you can't be judged based on a whatsoever then why then fucking why would would you even release
it if it doesn't say something about you i don't i don't remember exactly what i said about lightning
blitz but i mean i i'm guessing even hard on her well like tonight that do what did i say do you
remember i don't think any exact i think we just made fun of her uh we we we we we we we talk about
how she uh she feels so bad about having alicorn oc when she did it to herself yeah like that's all
i know about her and and we are going to criticize what we know and i mean is it wrong that she has
an alicorn oc like the fact that she made an alicorn oc and then you know experienced some
level of emotional instability and heartache over the fact that people did not accept her alicorn
oc as legitimate is fucking hilarious and deserves to be roundly mocked i'm sorry that's just how i
feel and i don't care how good a friend she is to other people i don't see that shit all i see
is what's in front of me and what's in front of me is this fucking nonsense yeah is this
fucking is this malarkey yeah it is malarkey and you know the whole it's embarrassing the whole
brony thing is embarrassing that's why i fucking stopped doing tbap because it was embarrassing
having being fucking a brony for a living so there or even as a fucking hobby so there you go
that's how that's i you know i that's how i feel about people and i applied that same standard to
myself so i feel like i am fucking have put my money where my mouth is on this issue yeah
there we go all right i feel good fucking cleared oh yeah he won't get it though he won't understand
no i if he makes a new thing he won't understand any of this he's just gonna he's gonna say the
same thing over and over again listen i'm sorry dude and you know fucking i know you i know you
want closure here but fucking god damn we have to we had we owe to ourselves to fucking defend
ourselves when we feel like we're being fucking uh unjustly fucking attacked i mean i'm sure i'm
sure you feel the same way you fucking hypocrite i mean i guess we're just i guess we're just not
gonna agree on these things so all i'm all i'm trying to do i'm just trying to respond to all
this with with like how i genuinely feel clear up when i feel that i've been misunderstood
and defend myself when i feel that i'm being unfairly attacked for something that
i don't feel is i deserve to be and we're using terms like attacked and fucking you know misinterpreted
yeah which is accurate and we're trying to be genuine and serious but our real opinions is that
this is fucking crazy and you're fucking an insane person that is really really really funny it's
pretty funny um let's continue yeah assisted he literally had to guess that something like that
happened which gives you the impression that he doesn't know her at all i don't know her but
again i did watch the video about how she'll never amount to anything really speaks volumes on their
character if they really think that she's not gonna go anywhere then why does she have more subs than
either of damn well channel maintains a reasonable view why does why does dr wolf have more subs than
either of us uh you know same fucking question i i suppose he's true that he's that that that she's
doing more than like she she's she's getting more you know popularity than than than than we do i
don't know like like i like i don't know i don't know if i said she's not gonna go anywhere i don't
believe that like i i what i meant by she's not gonna go anywhere that is is that i don't value
her content is what i meant to say by that i'm sure she's gonna she's gonna be more popular than
will ever be yeah and i'm perfectly fine with that she'll she'll have a she'll have a huge
following of bronies that need to be validated and and just want to see the kind of thing that she
is only too happy to deliver uh and there and i can't argue with that that's that's just how it is
and uh she she what i there you go there you go that's all i gotta say but still you know
fuck lightning bliss she's terrible uh she's she's just uh she's terrible just she's terrible just
like dr wolf is terrible she's terrible like misanthropony is terrible she's terrible like
fng r is terrible not in exactly the same ways but in many of the same ways um caught up in this
fucking caught up in this fucking nightmare hellscape that is brony analysis this fucking this
this this parent trap that's been laid and and and and and when and when and when you're a fucking
artist and when you have when when you have and when you have limited time and when you have to
do shit for a fucking living uh sometimes sometimes and and and and even when and even when you can
compile all the evidence sometimes you just have to admit to yourself and you just have to be
honest to yourself admit that the hunt and that your hunches are the only things you actually know
yep no no matter what your hunches are always going to be what you what you truly do believe
that's gonna be the only thing that you know for certain yeah um and no no one there's yeah
that's all that's the best you can do sometimes yeah and uh there's uh should i keep going go ahead
oh is an animation test with over 500 000 views she's hooked people inspired them and made a
difference oh she made she made a fucking pony mashup she made a fucking she made a pony parody
of a popular internet thing guess she proved me wrong guess she proved us right she really is going
places um sorry um yeah art and silly videos and being herself she's a kind-hearted and open-minded
woman and has rightfully earned everything she's gotten in this community i don't know her as much
as others do but i've still chatted with her from time to time and each experience that i've had with
her was really nice after that he states that i once okay i want to say something controversial
here that i don't know i i think you'll agree with um i don't necessarily look for people who are like
nice i feel the exact way i don't necessarily want to be friends with people who are nice and kind
no i that's like that's that's not that high that's not that high on my list of like the qualities
that i look for in a person yeah um i don't know i mean okay i i i'm sure like let's it is a sweet
person but sure that's not what i that's not what we're talking about yeah that's not what we're
talking about here uh yeah okay i'm glad we're on the same page about that yeah tated keyframe which
is also not true i don't mean to harp on this but this was the second time that ben has made an
assumption on me that was vastly incorrect i was a fan and and and and and did i say that he made
assumption keyframe did i say that he hated key i don't know why i would have come to that conclusion
that seems strange um i don't know i don't remember that okay and also okay this the second the second
time that we've come to an assumption about him that was completely accurate uh what's your
fucking count up at buddy what what's what's how many times have you completely misunderstood
what we're doing yeah yeah solid uh oh it's it's great it's great starting making those stupid
rant videos i was a fan of hers before i even started this youtube channel making broad statements
like this before making sure it's false information just making assumptions about a person when you
don't know them very well it shows that at this point ben is simply grasping at straws to find a
reason to shit talk me heck he even expresses concern that i didn't call him the c word and
that i wouldn't swear even though i clearly called him a stupid faggot earlier and a shit sucking
clearly yeah that's literally twice that he contradicts himself over the same subject no
no i didn't say why didn't you call him a c word then you i i said it's i complained that you
didn't say it because you didn't say i didn't fucking contradict myself jeez louise i don't
even i don't even know where to begin you didn't even say it the second time like we know that you
do swear sometimes yeah it's it's it's just like fucking jace w connors fucking parkour dude 91 like
i don't swear except for when i fucking do and don't call me out on it when i do because i don't
swear yeah um fucking nice job you you are you are you are the real parkour dude also the the
thing about how i'm just grasping at straws to uh to to to to to shit talking uh who's calling the
kettle black you know yeah and all that also once again he's addressing me specifically and not you
yeah yeah i miss at their point i me look at me yeah fucking notice acknowledge munchie Jesus
fucking crap this is not my thing i did not do this and munchie was along for the riot we did
this together no one under everyone just assumes that there's horrible there's horrible you know
sinister intentions here yeah when we could not be more delighted to have all this transpire
it's true uh it seems it says you left the room by the way it oh okay let me let me refresh
yeah i tried to play it just now and it wouldn't go all right all right you're back i'm already um so
yeah guys guys take our word for it we like doing the show we enjoyed shitting on people
we are currently enjoying and shitting people more yeah we like this we're yeah more than ever
it just gets better and better we're down guys we're down we're this this is consensual
continue please uh oh okay here we go now for the record i do believe that i went too far calling
him those names which is actually part of something that i'll get to later but this is still another
example of how he doesn't construct his thoughts in a way that's not counterintuitive
he doesn't construct his thoughts in a way that's not counterintuitive all right just putting that
out there yeah we've all been waiting for going back to the key yes basically it's the thing that
sparked all of this drama look i really don't want it to seem like i'm just obsessed with this topic
but the level of disrespect that he shows talking about it is just really hard to ignore then basically
says that she got pity money for a video that she did with dr wolf which was uploaded a year
after the situation was resolved okay okay okay okay maybe she maybe it wasn't that video that
got her the pity money but the bit the money was pity money like that's what it was um yeah
year after the donations were made and he speaks of it like it was a cheap stunt to gain sympathy
from people he doesn't directly call it a scam but it can count as him saying that it was a scam
there are people who say it i didn't call it a scam i didn't jesus uh it's fucking it's fucking
pity money that's what it is you fucking have it you bring a sob story i i don't it doesn't
matter like it doesn't matter how bad it was like like like it is even if the shit is all real and
maybe it is i don't fucking know but even so it's still pity money it doesn't change anything about
what i said what is so hard to understand i'm inclined to believe it is real and even it yeah i'm
inclined to believe is real like the things that are things that are claimed the things that are
claimed to have happened i don't contest that they probably happened yeah it doesn't change how i
feel about the whole thing yeah exactly so fucking god yeah jesus christ who actually think this was
a lie when there are plenty of ways to show it was an actual matter and why it was not to be taken
lightly and the main thing that ben and munchie seemed to harp on is over how i claimed to have
evidence but don't show any of it particularly that video that was on will's channel and everyone
talking in depth about the situation no of course i'm not going to upload something that sensitive
just to feel like i proved a point to these people it's not my call and it's not their call it's it's
it's not that i think he he should upload it it's that he shouldn't expect me to know what he knows
if the information is not publicly available yeah like this is this is this is guarded information
so why would i be expected to have it if i walked up to a fucking to you know some some some bum
fuck fucking homeless person and i was like hey dude you know about mk ultra and they're like uh no
i wouldn't be like you fucking moron how could you not know yeah yeah that's pretty much what's
happening here um so yeah that's that's yeah that's what's up with that it was keyframe
situation it was on will's channel i'd need permission from the two of them to even get
the right to mail it to them i'd also like to point out that there are people associated with ben
who were very very aware of the keyframe situation when it was going down one of them even made a
twitch stream to help raise awareness on it what i'm saying is ben doesn't need me in order to learn
about the keyframe situation he can just ask people about it ask his friends about it look it up just
i i have looked i have looked it up and i have what i believe is a pretty
gen solid general idea of the situation and nothing about what i have ever said on the subject
i i will i will not walk back anything it's it's pity money from fucking bronies who will pay for
anything uh it doesn't like fucking it's not this is like this is not the saddest story i've ever
heard you know like this is not this is not like this is not a fucking life or death scenario
this is not like a an a murder i don't know sure it's bad it sounds like her house really sucked
and i'm sorry for that but but you know but people have worse lives than that people have
worse situations and bigger emergencies and they don't get fucking pity money for it because
they're not fucking brony out analysis assists right that's what it comes down to she brings
her solid story to the brony analysis community and because they are who they are and they will do
literally anything for a fellow brony for no reason uh she that's that's that's what it was
that's what fucking happens there we go is my fucking is my fucking stance clear yet
jesus yeah like like i don't know like i'm a pretty you know um gullible person sure sure
i'm completely ready to buy that you know she she she had a bad home life and i don't know
if i were in the if i were particularly emotionally evoked i i would probably give fucking money
but it doesn't mean it's not pity money yeah that is the emotion i'm feeling and that's the
reason i'm giving money is because i feel pity yeah i don't think it's necessarily like a huge
problem no that's what it is and i and i don't know why you would want to say that it's not i
yeah i in my mind nothing that i have ever said on the subject should be controversial at all
yeah um it is just being the fact yeah it was a bunch of bronies heard a sob story and gave a
bunch of pity money and that's what happened yeah just a uh i'm going to assume a bad thing
happened to someone she told people they felt bad they gave her money that's pity money yeah
fucking what's your problem dude exactly yeah something even putting that aside keyframe
getting attacked by her mother was live streamed there were witnesses to the attack and this whole
ramble that he would not say it's fake yeah while i can understand why he did it still has some
misleading remarks to it i didn't make this oc a friend of mine did i admit that it's not
a complex design and you can joke about it i'll just say i don't really hate his oc that much
like there's so much like i hate it like he's no he's no tune critic you know okay well okay no one's
i don't know like i could make i could make fun of anyone's fucking pony oc you know like the
real the real problem is not the specific design of his oc it's just the fact that it is one yeah
yeah uh i agree being a rule 63 pinky however you want but i still thought that it was nice of
someone to do that for me and it would be rude sure sure and kind of dishonest of me to change
i mean i i'm not invested i'm not invested in shitting on his oc yeah a representation of comedy
and tragedy it represents my emotional duality it doesn't represent comedy and tragedy and it
makes me wonder where this assumption even came from and i also really don't like this rant i i i
don't know dude sorry i mean looking at it again it doesn't totally look like comedy and drama
drama uh i don't know sorry we're riffing i mean yeah like i think it's a pretty when i see like a
mask that is like half happy and half sad like i think that's a pretty reasonable leap to make uh
yeah like sorry if that wasn't your intention with it but like yeah whatever yeah um yeah please
please no bully yeah please god please god spare us we made a mistake please just just let us dive
and bear us where they go on about how the pcp is superior how ben and munchie are any better than
all of these people how the brony analysis community is the scum of society calling it a
hive mind that they're all basically lonely pete how they're all a bad influence how we're
corrupting people even them talking about how if everyone was like digibro and gibbon take it
would be better is just shooting themselves in the foot they complain about it being a bunch of copies
so they wanted to be a bunch of copies simply because those copies i don't remember okay i don't
remember saying that i think that all brony analysis sys should be like digi and gibbon if i
said anything like that i'm sure what i was getting at was not that they should be they should make
content just like them but that they should think outside the box the way those guys and other guys
did and yeah the thing is if everyone in the brony analysis community was like gibbon and digi and
fucking you know the rest of us they wouldn't be there anymore like that's that's what i'm getting
at it's it's not saying that they have to be like them in all the tangible details they like we just
want them to be good people yeah is what we're trying to say it's not it's not as though it's not as
though like if i went back to look at brony analysis videos and i saw that they were making videos
on waves of of giving clones i would not be thrilled yeah it yeah it wouldn't be like oh well
now this is good content that i do want to watch it's like no there's bigger fucking there's bigger
concerns here yeah there's bigger fish to fry and what you all need to do is realize that
uh do things that don't have to revolve around one specific fucking shitty tv show that we were
all tricked into liking yeah yeah but there's fucking money in it there's fucking money in it
because it's fucking people are so fucking they're crazy they're fucking crazy and they just want
more they just can't get enough of pony in the corner they're foaming in the mouth pony in the
corner review the show uh suck my dick and let get out of here please let it die please let it die
hashtag max venue hashtag max revive t-bap hashtag um hashtag uh cyanide uh poison to the rest of
the brony analysis community please i wish i wish the fucking well would just dry up and they would
stop fucking funding themselves god it bothers me just to no end that people that people are like
we need to keep this going we need to keep this going that's what they're doing they're putting
they're pumping money into the fucking brony analysis economy and that is what it's going
so much like like all of our complaints is that it is not good content but who cares if it's not
good content to us because they just fucking love it so much yeah yeah um so so so so i so i guess
so i guess you're fucking right miss antherpony maybe mirkan does does have fucking wealth and
and you know it is a fortune him but um sorry if i don't fucking like the people that yeah um
to me it's all fucking to me like any amount of recognition for for my little pony reviews
is like undeserved and too much and makes me mad yeah and i know he's gonna and i know he's gonna
say that i'm a hypocrite because i made fucking pony videos well i felt differently at the time
at the time i had nothing better going on but now i've moved on and that's what a good person would
do in my humble opinion so there that's my issue they haven't moved on and i don't get why
represent people that they personally like there are people in the pcp that i like but
saying the bro analysis leak should be like them would take away the idea of us being individual
people look it was never my intention and you're fucking individual people right now
you're you're you're so fucking different from one another from one another right now you
it's it's it's not like you could click on like like some fucking bum fuck 50 subscriber person
and not be able to really distinguish them from like like a fucking um um a big name yeah it's it's
it's he yeah he the amount the amount of appreciation for this for the art form of
brony analysis like the amount of individual care and attention that is implied to exist
is blows my mind and it just doesn't i mean i guess there are heroes like dr fowl among them
who are like creating like quality content that breaks the mold most definitely sure
sure of course there are exceptions but yeah the the by the numbers fucking shitty that guy with
the glasses jokes and and the fucking the pony in the corner and the flat the fucking the the
animation the limited flash animation fucking make it look like the show fucking i don't know
fucking attitude the fucking love and tolerate attitude and all the all this the whole melange
of things fucking bullshit that make up the brony analysis community i could talk forever about how
disgusting i find it and i'll just never fucking see every fucking level i'll just never fucking see
what it is that that is keeping people invested you know for me for me i was over a long time ago
and and i i'm really sad to see that people don't feel the same way yeah yeah me too me too
people with my first video on ben saint i just wanted to get some anger and heat off of my chest
over what he's been angry right now raising his voice i wasn't trying to rain wash people to think
like me people can choose to not agree with me for the way i made that video it's called free will
people may agree with me and i may agree with them but it's not because of a result of indoctrination
and that thing about them wanting all of us to be like digi bro this guy made a half hour long video
being a pretentious self internal jerk over how he thinks any enemy totally irrelevant isn't him
totally pointless now this was totally missing the point of what was meant maybe he's gotten
better and improved his attitude since then oh my god who fucking cares right i'm descending
arrogant on the one hand it's retarded being mad that digi complained about the way other
youtubers do their thing because on the other other hand it's shut the fuck up like that's
totally irrelevant yeah ah i just don't i just don't get i just don't get his angle
no me either i just don't i just and like hold on yeah just like okay he's going on about how
like fucking like you know oh how how could we want the brunettes community to be different
how dare we fucking express our opinions on the subject yeah like i don't know like i don't know
dude people say what they want i'm sorry we humans like to say what they want yeah is that such a
crime is that such a crime to express our fucking opinion like don't don't worry miss anthropony
we know we know that you're not brainwashing anyone here we know that what's on display is
just your opinion it's just that we disagree strongly with your opinion and want to fucking make
that known like the road this road goes both ways and and it's fine like you know like like you made
a response to our video you're expressing your opinion on the subject that's completely fine uh
but you know there were some things that we didn't fucking like advance we're going to express our
opinion right back it like like it's it's all about just fucking you know using common sense
and fucking try not to be a fucking weird asshole and i don't think we were going we were yeah
so um there you go like yeah it's a two-way street it's a two-way street and if you're immune
from criticism then so are we and if you're and if we're not then you're not yeah stick jerk talking
down to people oh did you so mean guys oh he totally called out a bunch of anime youtubers
suck my fucking dick there's a reason why i cited tommy oliver in that first video because i still
respect the man even though he's done stuff that i disagree with i still respect him because he's
more of a reasonable adult than the two of you combined oh he swore on his grandmother's grave
or soul or whatever the fuck that he wasn't gonna get mad and now here he i don't know man i don't
know do you think he's pushing that boundary because i think he is i i think i think he's
fucking pushed past that and and like wow he's not screaming well he's not playing out god
injustice god's among us clips out of his oh yeah oh yeah um you know if if you were to show this
someone they would like unrelated like without context of course they would fucking think that
he's angry i mean of course they would that was just a straight up insult like he just straight
up insulted us and said that we aren't mature adults so you know dude bro whatever whatever dude
fucking you know uh uh jesus christ is always please please and i don't know like all of these
fucking people f and g are fucking mishandler pony they're just so fucking sweet on all of our
friends they just love them so fucking much yeah they're such saints to such pair of fucking
guns of virtue um fuck you yeah um i mean i i mean i think if anything we're better we're the best
we're the only good pcp uh okay we're the we're the best there is and if you think that we're the
bad ones and everyone else is the good guys then you've got the fucking problem busters
you don't understand you don't understand that what we're speaking truth to power here
and all the rest of our pcp quote unquote friends are all just drinking the kool aid um i mean i
don't know i don't know i i like the pcp a bit a bit a bit yeah yeah uh but yeah we're the best
yeah yeah um but yeah so i i mean who i mean who can deny yeah press one of we're the best yeah
agreed shit for the way he left the fandom and i don't i really don't i at least understand
why he made that video about ranting at the fandom and leaving it i agree that he shouldn't have felt
pressured into being dishonest with himself just to feel like he was entertaining an audience at
the time a lot of people were giving him a bad rep for no good reason and he was just sick of it
and on top of that he followed it up with a more constructive video explaining his decision to
move on with his life i don't just respect that i admire that about tom yeah nothing i've seen
from either ben or munchie so far has given me the impression that these two are like that as well
i cannot what does he mean like in what way yeah like what did he mean by this i don't know uh like
uh like tommy is good because he left and he ranted but then he did something constructive
he like clarified so what is this if not a clarification yeah this video if not clarification
what what is yeah uh we this is we're on we're we're like well over 10 or 15 hours of clarification
yeah yeah so no your problem is by the way quick quick aside here uh i'm so fucking upset with
myself that like i gave my dragon fucking facial hair because i because i made fun of that for
like other people and i truly i don't like it but i wanted to give phantom a beard and i thought it
would be weird if only he had a beard and i didn't so i put it on but i'm so unhappy with it and i
wish i didn't do it i'm i'm sorry i mean i think it works for i mean i think it looks fine it makes
sense for phantom because horses have hair uh yeah well then i mean you know i guess if i'm using
that logic strawberry shouldn't have head hair either or or those like just weird scales those
those are scale those are weird scales oh well so are the ones on his face then okay okay fair enough
yeah yeah just little little wispy um really long scales i hate it it's fine um phantom is perfect
i love strawberry milk phantom is perfect yeah but strawberry is fine too look look at his dingy
look at his nasty little teeth yeah look at those canines yeah horses aren't supposed to have those
you fucking brutal fuck i'm pretty brutal dog i'm i'm pretty cheeky understand any of the motivation
behind what ben and munchie did with that first video because they were bored wasn't just for a
cheap laugh yes it certainly wasn't funny on any level well one more thing that these guys accuse
the brony analysis community of is how everything should just be maintained i don't believe that
and i'm sure a lot of people don't either if someone wants to move on with their lives that's
their choice there's nothing i can do except try to respect their decision and i haven't been doing
that i know it's not something that's going to last forever and i'm hoping that when it's over
that something good came out of it we try our best to make a positive difference in well guess i mean
guess what the longer people stay mired in this brony analysis nonsense the more you're putting
off the possibility that anything good can come out of it like the time spent on brony analysis
is not the time is not is time not being spent making something good come out of it that's how
i mean okay i agree so i don't know i am completely consenting and willing and fucking
more than happy to say that some good came out of the brony analysis okay even the brony analysis
like even just like brony community as a whole i'm more than happy in fact i'm willing to say a
lot of good came out of it yeah but that doesn't excuse it's fucking false you know i guess i'll
say that like if someone like if someone stumbles upon the brony analysis community
sees that it's like an active community and takes it upon themselves to like jump in and make some
content and they put their own spin on it and like you know they they they grow as an artist
through this exercise you know like we did uh i guess i i guess i have no fault with that
so but but but but but but what offends me what what offends me is the old guard
of the the brony analysis community that wants that wants to keep forever that wants to keep
the same old shit going they yeah like i i i i okay i i'm i i'm i'm a big i'm a big brony
apologist yeah i mean i don't know i i met i met on my best buds like like like even not
not just the pcp my fucking best friend of like i don't know like fucking six years or something
yeah i met on a fucking deviant art con because he liked my drawing of scudaloo foe so fucking i
don't know yeah um i got a lot of shit out of this yeah um but that doesn't mean i think it's all
fine and dandy and i that that just proves that i want it to be better because i want to remember
it fondly i want i want to be happy fucking you know thinking back on it and you fucking
you fucking you you brutal you fucking brutal men and you brutal women are fucking tainting my
memories stop yeah please uh maybe someday maybe someday it'll all just end
i mean i'm in a brutal mood right now yeah me too i i honestly i did not think
i did not think i would be getting mad uh about this but thank you yeah i was right i was ready
to bury the fucking hatchet but now our guys we have to bury the hatchet and miss anthill probably
his fucking head yeah i watched it before and it left me ready to bury the hatchet but now watching
it again and thinking about it and discussing it with you i'm fucking incensed again yeah uh i mean
you know i mean like if you want to make it a asking for that per se it would be funny for us
but i don't know do what you want yeah but on the other hand i don't know like like like why
just like like if you really truly want things to just not happen anymore just say sorry um i was wrong
uh by yeah i mean he's he's free i mean he's free to disagree yeah uncertain on on you know on
whichever many points he wants to but i don't know i'm and so am i i'm here i am i'm fucking i'm
disagreeing real hard i'm disagreeing real hard i'm disagreeing as hard as a human fucking hand
yeah um so yeah i guess i'm with you that like no i guess i won't say that no good could ever come
out of the brony analysis community but like the the relentless the relentless adherence to formula
and the i don't know just the insularity of it and the the
yeah all that it sucks it makes it all all all how every fucking member is a hive mind
cause and it's i don't like that yeah and it's not fucking above criticism like you can't like
i'm not you can't fucking tell me that i'm not allowed to look at something like lightning
bliss is oc and be like oh god i i hate that it sucks and and then like why like why is that
why is that off the table for criticism oh because she's nice because you're her friend
well fuck that and and not even just like some random person doesn't have the right to criticize
it of course they do yeah but not even just that you were an influential member of the community
who else but you is able to criticize it well i mean i guess i guess because i left my opinion
doesn't count anymore you know like now that we were saying this shit in the fucking community
yeah we it's true it's true i was this like i've never changed my tune about this once um i don't
what what is this guy's fucking problem why i never i never i never liked the fucking
the formula and the the way that it was all just i don't know it was so refreshing it was so
refreshing when some originality shown through and that is how like fucking the pcp all met each
other because we all had like a fresh fucking voice in the midst of the sea of mediocrity
and like so that like that's the kind of thing that i think can can potentially come out of a
thing like this but like to me the the alternative to the everything that isn't that is bad like it's
like to argue like to me the pcp is like the cream that rose to the top of this of this fucking cess
pool and to say to suggest that there's anything wrong with me saying that the rest of them should
be like us in some way is to suggest that we are the bad and they are the good when no like they
like we're the ones that fucking stood out you know like we're the ones that that made something
happen with it and didn't fucking save it settle for the same old shit and to fucking to fucking
complain about that as though like why do you why do you want us to be like you don't you want us to
be individuals fucker we were the individuals we were the ones that were different i don't know
and and and to say like i don't know like i don't like t-bap or i don't like drying
horseshoes sure but i i i i don't know why why can't we why why can't we want people to be like us
what's the what's the problem at the end of the day does anyone does anyone want anything that's not
that when you really me really really when you look inside of yourself and ask you what you want
i don't know dude i don't i i yeah like it's it's like digi complaining about the anime like
he thinks the anime analysis should be done in a certain way and why is it controversial then
that he dislikes the alternative ways of doing it and prefers his own and thinks that the way
that he chooses to do it is the right way the reason he does it his way is because he feels
that's the right way to do it just like yeah you know the way that i did pony analysis was
what i felt was the right way to do it and ultimately i felt that leaving it was the
right thing to do with respect to it and that's the fucking that's what it is that's that's
lying short of it i'm yeah that's the longest short of it i'm kind of i'm kind of lost i've
kind of lost track of where this whole thing started i'm i'm i'm getting kind of like heat
stroke delirious right now yeah um there all right should we continue let let's continue
in people's lives because that's what life should be about making a positive difference
nothing that ben or mungee have done with these two videos has made a positive change of any kind
and if it did who are you to say for all of the wrong reasons these two are the bad there he goes
again it's just like when he was like they don't talk about it and when they do it doesn't count
he's like yeah it didn't make it didn't make a positive difference who are you to say if it did
then fuck you yeah and if it did it was for the wrong reasons well great i'm sorry you don't
like the reasons i'm sorry that you don't think that if someone agrees with what we're saying
that that's not valid for whatever reason like that's what he's fucking saying is he's fucking
are saying to say that he's fucking saying that anyone that disagrees with our points
is just invalid and their opinion doesn't count like that's what that's literally what he just
said or implied right there and yeah get the fuck out of here yeah seriously like can you not step
outside yourself and see and acknowledge that even if you don't agree with our stance on the
brony analysis thing and on the keyframe thing and on the way we made our video and on everything
that at least it is fucking legitimate that we see things the way that we do
yeah like it's just so baffling to me that he just he just is trying so hard to like discredit us
when we have thousands of people who love it yeah yeah i mean okay people like the rowdy
focus cop killers okay i i guess i don't know maybe that's hypocritical we were just saying that we
don't respect lightning bliss even though she has a lot of fucking you know popular like she is popular
yeah maybe that's her logic hmm well maybe like i don't know i i guess the difference is that i respect
the people who like us i don't respect people who like her then it comes down to a matter of opinion
and i'm fully ready to call it that just a matter of opinion i never thought this was an objective
fact based sort of fucking court case you know hmm i mean bullshit are we are we being are we being
overly dismissive of misanthropone's points like are we failing are we failing to step
us outside ourselves and like consider his point of view on this i don't know possibly i mean like
like like what more is there to analyze here like like what could we say differently i mean okay
from his perspective these are two people who he apparently knew about and respected on some level
i think uh maybe not me but but but you and so this is the and shitting on their roots so to speak
so i don't know i i get why he would be upset but we've clarified our stances and fucking
like i think clarified them pretty well so at this point i like maybe maybe maybe i'm like the
first response but like we've kept clarifying over and over again so i'm fully fucking ready to
fucking call him out and say that this is his fault yeah i mean i guess whether you think
brony analysis is a valid thing is a matter of opinion i guess i can't objectively prove to you
that it's not uh but i was never any i was never under the impression that it was like an objective
thing yeah and it's completely my opinion but you shouldn't have to clarify that because everyone
is everyone's opinion and you don't like everything you say will be your hunch or your opinion there
is nothing yeah yeah like i don't think you should have to say this is just my opinion but to then
state an opinion and have it you know treat regarded as an opinion yeah uh where
map is map is your your you're watching you're watching yeah all right let's shall we go we got
we got a bunch more we got like eight more minutes of this amaka situation relating to abusive
parenting publicly disgrace people who have done absolutely nothing to deserve their scorn
and believe that would be a lot better if every single solitary member was that guy who recluses
himself to his basement and brags about himself on tumblr i get that the point of these videos
just two guys messing around and having a good time i really do in fact that's the foundation that
the pcp is built upon this episode and talking about random topics and just having fun with them
but this series of videos this one with ben saint and munchy it takes such an ignorant and
disrespectful turn that it comes across as more of a two guys bitching at other people video than a
two guys just messing around that's what we can't get that's what it is that's what's fun to us
wouldn't have spent so much time trying to make them about other people for a series of videos
that's not meant to be taken seriously it sure does get sincere whenever they talk about this
community they once had no shame in associating themselves we're totally sincere we're totally
sincere in how we feel and wishes it could pull off and knowing that people actually embrace this
kind of material and the attitude wait wait what about wishes they could pull off right this video
only further show i want to hear that in fact that's the foundation that the pcp no god just
having fun get that shit out of here as more of a two guys bitching at other people video than a
two guys just messing around video if these videos were meant to be just about them then they
wouldn't have spent so much time trying to make them about other people for a series of videos
that's not meant to be taken seriously it sure does get sincere whenever they talk about this
community they once had no shame in associating themselves with these made me uncomfortable
in ways that a chan wishes it could pull off okay i mean did we ever say that like these videos
aren't meant to be taken seriously i don't know i mean i like okay that that's a whole
can of worms about like what exactly that means to not take something seriously yeah like i don't
know like like on some of i want all my videos to be taken seriously i want people to like
think about it and turn their brain on and intake it but that does that mean i think everything
needs to be like a fucking federal fucking issue no but like i don't know like like to not take
something seriously is to disrespect it in my opinion and if i were to ever say if i were to
ever say like just don't take it seriously i would just mean like it like it it's a sort of video
where like this is gonna sound like we really like really like weasley and like you know fucking
like everything it can be it can be waved off with this but i don't know to like to not take
something seriously i just mean to like view it in a certain sense that's like like i don't mean
turn your brain off exactly i just mean like i don't know i mean that it's silly i mean that
is a silly video when i say when i say like i don't take it seriously i mean it is silly i mean
the things we're saying should take it seriously per se like the things we say in these videos
like we're saying them on public record and like they do represent our true feelings but
like you wouldn't you wouldn't like you would take something anyone said with a grain of salt
right like when i said like when i said that i hate burning donut and think he's a fucking
idiot and a terrible person like you know like yeah i i meant it but not like in a fucking not
like a federal fucking case or anything like yeah like we're talking casually we're using hyper bowl
yeah we're using hyper bowl and like we're like we're stating our true feelings but we're stating
them in a way in a casual way so i'm not gonna sit here and be like i'm not one of these people
who's like dude the whole thing was just a joke dude like yeah like it was all just a joke a joke
why do you think we meant any of it you idiot like no uh yeah there's a there's a middle ground
here that the sincerity of this video uh falls in and it's the fucking and it's the same fucking
middle ground that like any anything should like any fucking thing that anyone says to you ever
should be taken seriously but not too seriously yeah like like jokes can be serious and being
silly can be important yeah exactly so fucking i don't know like you just have to just have to be
able to parse that and i think we've clarified ourselves extensively on what exactly we mean
yeah i mean i don't know you i feel like you could be forgiven on some level if we're not
totally understanding the first video if you came from a background of not knowing who we were
yeah but once with with all of this all of this said how can you not understand what we are trying
to say yeah um i don't know i wonder i wonder if this will i wonder if this will put the kibosh
once and for all or if it will just be more of the same after this misanthropony misanthropony
like if you're watching this we know you don't want to say you say anymore we know and we're not
going to beg you to make another video yeah just if there's just some way just like comment like
i understand if you get where we're coming from not even that you agree not even that you agree but
you just you get where we're coming from dude just like comment i understand please i'm fucking
begging you please i understand just type i don't understand and then we will that'll be
the fucking end of it please i need to fucking know are we insane are we crazy are we are we
fucking are we are we are we the are we the devil um yeah i um i don't know i don't know i don't
know how i'll take this like i i feel like he's not gonna be happy with how we've taken i mean
he made this video as like a clarification and i think maybe is somewhat of an apology but it
really hasn't felt like an apology at least this far and i haven't i haven't felt apologized to
i felt like he's said a lot of things that are like they're just continuing yeah yeah he's he's
explaining where he came from on these issues but he's not changing his stance on basically
anything he's clarifying a few like verbal missteps that he made and a few a few bad assumptions
that he made but his general stance on the whole thing has remained ironclad yeah like like he
keeps saying like you know i worded this wrong but it's still true and yeah i don't know did we
really misinterpret him that much i don't i don't think so i don't think so all right i think we
got his point we just didn't like the way he said it and also the idea behind it was retarded
yeah we felt yeah and knowing that people actually embrace this kind of material and
the attitude of the two making them is not right this video only further shows that they did not
know anything about what was going on and their refusal to even learn about it he's ashamed to
acknowledge that this was part of his life despite that it's the only reason that anyone even knows
i am not i'm not ashamed to acknowledge t-bap i mean it is a little like uh yeah i used to do
pony stuff i understand that that's where i fucking got my start and like yeah i'm a little
sheepish about it sometimes but i'm not ashamed of it and like i think a lot like a lot of the
stuff i did for t-bap was pretty great and like i don't know it's weird because it's not something
that i would show to anyone and expect them to like respect it on any level and i don't know i
guess i have complicated feelings about it i'm not i'm not ashamed of it and i don't i don't
like i was saying before like i don't think that i don't think that making a pony video makes you
a bad person inherently or makes you artistically bankrupt or anything like that it's just the way
that it's generally it's the way that it's done that i think is artistically bankrupt
there's always going to be you know in any fucking thing ever there's always going to be outliers and
there's always going to be things that prove your point wrong but you just have we are talking
generally we're talking generally and how like generally is the only way you can fucking speak
because if you if you didn't speak generally then every sentence would just be clarifying the previous
one forever uh yeah like you just you just like we are saying generally we don't like the way my
little pony analysis videos are conducted that is what we are saying and here are the reasons why
and like these are these are not problems that are all specific to the brony analysis thing
like i have like i have a lot of these same problems with like i don't know anime analysis
video yeah like the whole concept the whole concept of making an analysis video on youtube
i think is equally you know insular and and you know samey and retarded um and this this is just a
height an even more insular and hyper specific example of that that is even that it has a bunch
of like extra baggage on top of it um and i don't think i have i have no doubt that we would not
care about it all unless we were in it before because it matters to us personally and i think
that's good i think i think that that is what it would this this video series would be fucking
shit if we didn't actually know what we were talking about but we do because we fucking live this
shit motherfucker mm-hmm we know we know we were in the trenches we did we did this maybe not me
specifically but i was there i was there for the fucking ride yeah i and and and to say that you
this is completely wrong yeah um i feel like i'm entitled to my opinion of uh
brony analysis and what it all represents to me i don't think that there's he has any right to
tell me that it's you know wrong or not right uh that people that i that people are like agreeing
with the things i have to say about this you you you you you got you got both equally as valid
perspectives you got you got ben on our sorry phantom on the inside inside you got me strawberry
milk on the outside inside we're both on the inside we're like i was just a fan he was a creator we
both are coming to the same conclusion yeah does that not have some weight to it yeah like
i don't know i i mean i'm sure that not i'm sure that i'm sure there are plenty of brony analysis
who will cop to the fact that their chosen art form is like goofy and dumb and i
just i don't know i don't feel like i'm a monster for thinking that
but fuck whatever whatever i i i i i guess for the devil wanted to leave the fandom behind that
that would have been okay but just being a petulant child over this new way of looking at it
doesn't make him any better so years later years later i have a few things to say about the whole
thing and this is like and this is a crime mm-hmm you you aren't allowed to reflect on your own
life you aren't allowed to reflect on the things on my own my own life and the people that were a
part of it yeah yeah yeah god forbid that i say anything about that better than the people he's
been ranting on up to this point it's selfish and it's shameful and it's definitely not a good
influence there's that influence thing there's him breathing fucking hard now i've been saying
throughout this entire video that everything that ben and he used to be mad at mage and tommy for not
being a good influence being a good influence is apparently very important to him that's the entire
reason why we brought up that point i don't give a fuck if any of these people are good or bad
influences i made fun of that exact complaint in that video but if he's gonna say that then well
i'm gonna spin that right back at him yeah and munchie did was wrong and very hurtful and because
of all this you probably have the assumption that i hate them but the fact is that's not really true
i know it's hard to believe but i don't hate them as much as you think that i would especially with
that second video i don't think ben and munchie were in the wrong to respond to me and the reason
for that is because my own video i did on this was not a good influence either as a matter of fact
i really don't like that video looking back to it not because of the misinformation but because
of that angry outburst i went into at the end i admit that at the time i meant a lot of what i
said but now that time has passed and i've cooled down there were many many things that i shouldn't
have said jackie anderson was right about one thing i was not that mysterious bra when i was
making that video in fact i think i ended up breaking my own promise that i made when i did that
to not let my emotions get the best of me i thought i knew how she really let him have it
in the comments but i guess i'm still learning how rightfully so yeah the strongest of our emotions
and it's also the most dangerous it's an emotion that makes us act on impulse more so than fear and
disgust and when we let that get the best i hear here's this is not related to the point at hand
but i am deeply curious do you think that he phrased it that way because he knew that he would
be doing a visual reference to inside out or do you think that he really believes that human
emotions are anger joy sorrow fear and disgust like do you think do you think that's really how he
sees things i i i don't want to nitpick that because i know that he will say something about
it and he will miss our entire point of the video i just been harp on about it it's very yes i do
think it's fucking ridiculous i think it's really ridiculous that he like why those two why why those
two you know i mean i don't know it could be a coincidence i don't know i i i he i mean he's
proved before they just like to use media okay okay okay you're right i shouldn't i shouldn't harp on
about it it's it's that that part really stood out to me though as a strange way of saying it as
of us it leads us to making very bad decisions the decisions we make under that influence can be
things that we don't truly mean or things that we say in a moment of bad judgment it could take days
weeks months even years before we realized that we did something stupid i did a lot of stupid
things when i made that first video i think a lot of those mistakes came from the fact that i was so
mentally pissed off when i was recording for it i was only really thinking about what they said
about keyframe which led me to not thinking straight about a lot of the other topics i did
over exaggerating that i was going to one sub from the pcp because of that one video i
shouldn't have let it influence my feelings on the channel as a whole why not okay why not yeah
yeah like it's part of these kind of videos dude if you don't like the content on the channel
like like this is content on the pcp channel it should influence your feelings on the pcp as a
whole like that's fine okay and i want i want i want to say something yeah because i i feel like
i'm gonna psychoanalyze just just just a wee tad it it it it feel a little out yeah yeah please
i encourage it um the way he says that he was just so fucking overcome and fucking blind with rage
yeah um i don't buy for one single second because real humans don't act that way in cartoon if you
if you were an ad viewer of cartoons and animation and fucking uh and in general human abstractions
that we use to you know uh hyperbolically express our emotions then yes you could you would be led
to believe that you know one could just go fucking ballistic and just not think or act or feel straight
yeah um but the truth of the matter is if you're a fucking functioning human you don't do that and
that's not a real thing that actually occurs in your real actual i mean he had to edit that whole
video yeah this isn't like an instantaneous thing this this isn't like you're at a fucking party
and emotions are flying high and you and you call and you call someone's girlfriend a fucking whore
or something yeah that's a really i don't know why i was very specific but uh yeah this this took
him this took him like i don't know how long but probably at least you know a couple hours
all told probably to put this all together at least five hours and if you're blind with rage for
that long then something's up dude yeah he's just i mean he's just making excuses excuses yeah it's
just excuses yeah so i'm trying to say he's like just excuses because he doesn't actually want to
take responsibility that he lucidly and fucking with all of his brain power all of the fucking
neutrons in his brain fine all there is and synapses in his fucking brain starting up like
like a fucking thought revolution in his premium yeah with all of his power he was having a fucking
brain blast and this is the most poignant thought he'd ever thought of his entire life this yeah this
was not this is not like something i mean i get like sure you were mad when you said it but it's
not like you were out of control of your faculties or something yeah yeah this is not your your body
was fucking shutting down you had no control for what you said yeah like you you did this you can't
just say it was because you were angry i mean okay like okay i'm like you know he says he's angry
and that's why he did it and that's not like i don't know i don't know uh sure fine yeah i mean i
knew that like i mean i knew he was angry like yeah like that part i understand um just it's just
the specifics it's just the specifics that that i get tripped up on um because i just don't i don't
like him no i don't like this guy no no i did wrongly complain about people supporting him
through patreon that wasn't right and i shouldn't have control over that if ben's patreons want to
keep supporting him for expressing himself that's their choice and i don't have the right to keep
them from making that choice i mean no obviously like obviously he can't make anyone unpledged
i don't know i don't think this is a real like well sure to spread the word to like to say like
guys don't patron ben like yes that is hitting me where it hurts that is that is a serious thing
but like i'll i'll be honest like i basically did that to like tune i mean i didn't yeah i
basically said like i don't get why people support like tune critic or uh lightning or
fucking anyone you know like say i don't have a problem with someone saying like i don't like
what this guy does i mean i guess in this case it's kind of shitty because like it's not like the
patreon is for rowdy fuckers cop killers like it's like that's yeah it's just for you personally
yeah yeah it's for my other stuff which like this video is really not about so
mm i don't i forget the point i was making i guess what i'm saying is i'm not in principle
against someone being like fuck this guy he doesn't deserve your money like that's a fucking that's
a consumer judgment call and fair enough um but whatever dude whatever man i also really
shouldn't have said that jessie and gibbon would snore through his stuff i knew all along that
they've been friends for a very long time i was basically making stuff up because i wasn't really
thinking straight because of how bad i was at the time very good job yeah i'm pretty sure that this
scuffle between us cost me whatever chance i had at being on good terms with them i've already
gotten in trouble with them once for causing drama with members of the pcp i'm pretty sure they're
not happy with me for doing it a second time and something that i definitely should not have done
was make that statement at the end when i obviously wasn't in a good mindset then saint
if you're watching this i need to be very clear about this last segment i'm not sorry for calling
you out on your bad behavior but i am sorry that i got angry and i'm very sorry that i said i was
going to kick you in the day and i'm also sorry that i was overly harsh on munchie i don't want
to hate you i don't even want to dislike you but i understand that a lot has already happened
between us and it's stuff that's not just going to go away anytime soon if it helps in any way
there is something that you should know by the time you see this that first video that i made
of you will be gone not private not unlisted i mean straight up deleted from my channel not because
i got wrecked as some people on your side would say but because i don't want it to be a representation
of who i am i know that it'll still be up for people to see on t-bab but if that's what you want
on your channel then that's okay it's just not something that i want on my channel but i believe
that the best way for us to end is for us to admit that we both did something wrong and we both
handled this situation poorly if anything good comes out of this whole thing i'm hoping it's
that we just stop wasting our time making videos about how much we dislike the other guy okay okay
lot of stuff to say a lot to cover in this in a second lot lot to say first of all you don't have
to apologize for being overly harsh on me because you weren't and you didn't say anything about me
yeah basically yeah you you you said that saying your dad sucked basically oh yeah that's right he
did he did yeah he did shit on your stuff a little bit the i don't know like like this is like sorry
i i i like i like sorry i like i mess with like a friend of yours but like not like
sorry i mentioned the person who was your partner in this crime like i don't know
i isn't he why is he why doesn't he want to acknowledge that i'm just as guilty
why am i not why am i why why why is that man in this image not a double-headed person
with strawberry milk and phantom horn in it um that's a great that's a great question i also
unrelated but why did he use that picture of me like that's what not yeah i don't fucking know
i don't know why he would use that one like why not use one of the regular ones that i made yeah
like one of the ones that you drew yeah yeah yeah um okay so i hate i hate okay i hate this
implication that we both did something wrong i don't feel i have done anything wrong i mean
i guess in the broadest sense i guess in the broadest sense i don't really think that
misanthropony has done anything wrong either like making his video was not a crime
yeah but i but i what we have here is a disagreement and i think that misanthropony
is dumb and thinks stupid things um but like
where where what am i trying to say
i i'm i'm definitely not going to apologize for anything is where i'm going with this um
and i and i kind of resent this implication that this image makes and i think he goes on to say
a bit about it that like you know like like we're just having a spat and we need to like
we need to like you know resolve our differences so we can be on good terms again
like we were never on good terms yeah i i have never i have never thought highly of misanthropony
because he is among this group that i collectively yeah i fucking collectively look down on it and
he is he is in the thick of that and i can't fucking respect it and i don't think there's like
like it's not like we would be friends if we weren't in if this this drama was not happening
like this is this is this is not a bad this is not an argument between equals yeah i know i'm
coming off as real fucking as real fucking on my fucking high horse here but that's how i feel
and the sue me there is no there's no accord to be reached you know i will say that i do i do
appreciate that i do okay i do appreciate that misanthropony wants this this this argument to
end like i can see why he wants that because i feel like this has not gone well for him and i
would never have expected it to so from just on a on a purely like a functional level i can see
why he would want this to be over but i also think that wanting it to be over is the the mature
thing and the right thing to want and i appreciate that um i appreciate that he apologized for some
of the things um that he said like like especially like the that he was gonna like if i see you at
brony con i'm gonna kick you in the dick like that's not fucking okay so i'm glad he copped
to that and apologized for that um so that's all well and good and like i am ready to bury the
hatchet on this and my my final takeaway from it is just that like okay as long as as long as you're
on the side of like the bro analysis community like as long as you're in their court like we're
never going to agree we're never going to agree on this issue um as long as you don't see someone
like lightning bliss and just think and feel a little sick and and laugh through your puke um
like if that's not where your head's at then we're just not yeah then we're just not gonna
yeah we just do not think the same way we just do not have the same values and principles and
morals as one another yeah yeah exactly exactly yeah and i don't know um that's all fine and good
just stay away from me you fucking freak yeah um yeah that's that's pretty much i mean that's
pretty much it there we go yeah just like i don't like i don't know like why must what why why do you
want to be on good terms with us what do you nothing we don't like you none of our fans like you
like you've like i've laid my i've made my attitude clear yeah like we've we've explained how we feel
about it about the whole thing and this was his response to it so yeah why do you even want to
be like on good terms like yeah we're yeah he was still he was still really mad at us in this
fucking video yeah he swore that he wouldn't be yeah he had a lot of he he has a lot of things
that get his goat about stuff we said and that's fine uh fuck man yeah i just i just i just can't
see at i with with misanthropone on this i can't yeah uh i just can't i just can't apologize for
something that i believe in oh definitely definitely not yeah i mean yeah i actually do believe that i
fucking hate the brony nests community yeah so sorry i i will apologize for i will apologize for
some of the nastier things i said about burning donut who really didn't deserve even like the
some of the specifics i complained about like the way his patreoners like i do think is retarded
but like yeah i went i went too far in in hating on the guy just for something like that
um and i don't know
what else what else what else am i willing to walk back some of the like
yeah not not everyone in the brony nests community is a terrible person and like
like making a pony video doesn't make you a monster or a retard or an artist or anything
it just gives you a 98 chance of being an awful person and like but like continuing like i won't
judge someone for dipping their toe into that cesspool but like once you've dived in and swam
around in it and gotten a feel for what's in it if you continue if you continue to do so
at that point i'll start to judge you for it and be like why are you still there
why have you not gotten have you not you know done what you needed to do here and moved on
like at this point i just have to assume that this is your native habitat you know what i mean yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it's just like yeah just fucking please just please
acknowledge our resentment please just acknowledge that this is the way things are going to be
and you can't change your minds yeah yeah like we don't he'll never change our minds about the
brony analysis community just like we'll never change his minds about the fact that it's okay
that our video is called fraud fraction yeah yeah yeah um it's just it's just i don't know man
we just do we we we aren't the same we are we are not kindred spirits we are not you're not equals
we are not fucking we are not friends we are not buddies we are not pals no you are not cool i don't
think you're cool no no indeed and i don't want to be your friend no i don't wish you harm no i don't
want someone to fucking do anything to you i don't i don't want i don't want to kick your dick at
brony con no i'll do god never never never i don't i you know fucking god speed god bless
celestia bless celestia speed celestia leave me alone i feel exactly the same way all right
let's fucking uh uh you know god bless your soul and i cannot wait for you to buy a plane a plane
train or car a ticket away from me as far as possible i wish you all the best so you can uh
so you can go to something else i i i i i i i i i hope i hope that your your your method of
transportation finds you well as as as as you rock it and get across the country as far away from
me as humanly possible here here yeah you want you want to fucking bring this to a to a let's put
this let's let's let's bury the hatchet in this fucking guy's head yes wonderful scuffles like this
the one between you and me that lead people no they it's not you and him it's you and us yeah
why don't you love me miss anthermony why don't you fucking do to you why don't you acknowledge
munchie munchie's worked really hard to piss you off and why aren't you taking the bait
why why did you just acknowledge that i am bad too yeah why am i okay why am i good yeah why why
is it only me i want to be a scallywag i don't know man i don't know maybe it's because you
didn't have a ponio see oh wait you do there he is on screen right now strawberry milk bam
what's your excuse now map you got none all i want i want a fucking i want like a i want like a
like a two minute four minute video of him just making fun of my oc please yes oh god oh can you
imagine can you imagine the kind of nonsense he would uh he would think up to say about uh the
colors are too saturated the color make me upset yeah it's it's too much too much too much of the
same color or not enough color variety uh the beard you know dragons don't have facial hair
yeah yeah uh too tall like uh too too big for a baby dragon uh i don't fucking know uh he uh looks
gay he looks gay and that's not cool yeah makes me mad and uncomfortable and and has there ever
been even a single canonical usage of strawberry flavored milk in my la pony i don't fucking think
so bro no i don't fucking think so yeah they don't you don't have we don't it's not cannot
canonical that they even know what that is so yeah so fucking please please cease and desist
yeah um canon ossees only yeah like lightning lightning bliss is canon and strawberry milk
is uh is just fucking a farce i mean yeah and like i don't know like my goal is never to directly
make people feel bad per se yeah but i want to speak my mind and if you have a problem with
bin you have a problem with me um fucking yeah yeah yeah we're yeah so just come out and say it
the rowdy this this is this rowdy fuckers cop killers is our show it is about the two of us
speaking our minds uh so there you go this is this we said this in the last episode two yeah we did
yeah we did deliberately he's deliberately leaving me out of the fucking conversation you're
right we did fucking say this last time and he continued he continued to do it he he gave you
like a passing mention like like a token like a token nod why why don't i get why don't get the
respect that that that that that fucking goddamn phantom horn i don't know i don't know he's just
he's got it out for me maybe maybe he's just wants to fix it on my history with the brony community
or something i don't know i fucking i was i mean i don't know i didn't make videos but i was pretty
entrenched yeah i i i i i i did you you were involved you were involved with things yeah
i fucking yeah i was around people people people know me people i'm a big deal i promise i promise
mom dad i promise this brony now this thing is really paying off
hey uh did you just give me a few more months and i'll promise i'll have rin i promise yeah
yeah yeah my patreon is skyrocketing my view counts just hit the three digits
and i only had to use a couple thousand sock up accounts
please please let's just be okay and that doesn't fix anything there is more to both of us than we
give each other credit for and i want to believe that you understand that this is another one of
those videos that i wasn't expecting to make but the difference here is that it's something that
i want both of us to learn from it's true that i made this video with the idea of it being a response
to your second frog fractions video but i'm also hoping that this video can be a means for making
up for the really bad decisions that i made the first time the one thing that i want right now
more than anything is to bring proper closure to this drama okay bringing closure to a situation
like this is not something that can be done with a simple youtube comment it requires a lot of time
and thought about how you're going to vocally and properly convey how you feel about this if by any
chance there was something you wanted to tell me after seeing all of this you can freely PM me on
deviantart this is gonna sound really crazy but a part of me believes that we could have been on
good terms with each other if this situation didn't get so out of hand like i don't know what
gives i don't know what gives him that impression like i don't know like we it's it's we
meet we do not have history with you no like there's no there's no like warm feelings between us
there's no like oh what if there's no like god this this this has gone so awry this has gone so awry
if only i could be miss antherpony's fucking buddy yeah yeah we were never we were never on good
terms uh i don't know why he thinks this is not a spat this is a fucking this is a stranger
destroy destroying our destroying our our fucking our good times well i mean he's also giving us
some good times as well well okay true true miss antherpony giveth and miss antherpony take
it away yeah um something like this to happen between us again because it's just gonna be another
huge waste of time for everyone involved well if you do make a part i don't know i had a lot of fun
here today yeah i had a lot of fun here in the past i i i had a lot of goose i had a lot of gaff
absolutely and and i'm happy to provide fucking entertainment for the masses indeed so you know
um i don't know waste of time i think not agreed um uh all right let's let's let's bring this home
and chances are it's just gonna be a response to this video i'm not going to leave any comments
that will instigate more fighting i'm just gonna quietly walk away knowing that i did my best to
leave this situation behind on a good note as a reasonable adult thank you for taking the time
to listen to what you're welcome you're welcome even if a lot of it wasn't what you wanted to hear
miss antherpony over and out okay well you know um what's what's there more to say on the subject
yeah he doesn't want to do this anymore so you know what but but by jove i don't either uh yeah i'm
good with calling it there and uh like we're not we're not gonna agree we're not gonna agree about
a lot of the thing i think a lot of his criticisms are dumb um yeah but i'm not i'm not i'm not out
i'm not out to like convince him of anything uh so yeah yeah i guess i'm i'm agree agree to disagree i
guess uh i i i agree for you to never look at me ever again and i hope i never have this pleasure
of looking at you again um well uh we can i mean i guess uh i guess miss antherpony will uh
you know continue continue to be around flip side we'll catch on the flip side and by that i mean
i i'm by that i mean don't don't we'll get we'll catch him on the flip side he'll he'll continue
he'll continue to be in the comments you know uh he'll continue to do his his his his pony stuff
viewer viewer fucking spot don't possibly just let my voice roll as as you minimize this from
being in full screen because i know you do that minimize this then fucking or minimize this or
tab back over either one scroll down look at the comments control f jackie anderson and then read
that entire comment chain because i'm sure it's gold because it always is and and and and watch and
watch jackie obliterate miss antherpony on every level and watch him flounder and flip and flop and
fucking god destroy it destroy his moral compass jackie trying to fucking make safe it jackie ripped
miss antherpony apart in the comments like on several videos um miss antherpony is his he's a
real shitty commenter like i hate his comments they really love me a lot a lot of time yeah they're
upset yeah like for for as like they're actually he's actually even maybe even worse in the comments
than he is in his original video oh no doubt yeah he's he's bad he's bad oh no doubt but he whatever
we have a few more things audience as and i'm sure you can tell by looking at the time code
we want to check out burning donors to sponsor us we want to read the comments but uh burning
donuts i don't know yeah i don't know if i want to watch burning donuts oh oh yeah i mean it's
like 20 minutes long okay well then just fucking um i i know you've watched it so so so let's get
into that if you don't have anything more to say to the fucking to to to our red or a red
compatriot wait wait do we want to wait do we want to look at the comments on this finding
closure video um yeah that would be fine i would be down for that okay um you want to do that right
yeah yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna just look and see uh if there's any good shit yeah
oh it's it's malumis it's sort of i knew it's first uh it's it's more malimines who we were just
talking to yeah uh hey what what's your deal by the way what's your angle who are you what's
going on who malimines yeah i know he's watching he watches he watched all the other ones he or
she or something has like a big channel actually oh yeah he's got 200 000 subs i get the vague
impressions that they don't like us and i don't know i don't know anything about you uh sorry i guess
ooh man retention is not good these videos are like occasionally cracking 10 000 oh wait no no no
oh oh my god no no what okay they recent they recently did a video that got 150 000 views
and it's everything wrong with powerpuff girls the power of four in 20 minutes so it's a fucking
cinemas ends oh no um let me suck
whoa you are a superhero you have superpowers are you listening to this yeah i'm listening to the
my look when he leaves it i don't know whether they commend this kid for having balls to do this
look at this fucking this thumbnail i'm watching this everything wrong with powerpuff girls and
it's disgusting it's like cinemas ends but worse i hate it this is like little thumbnails
they're so they're so obvious they're so obvious yeah i'm looking at the thumbnails and i don't
like them i don't like what this person does on the internet uh yeah please stop yeah please please
stop please stop you're uh you're making everything worse for everyone um sorry bro but please do not
yeah oh this guy this guy hawk snacks have a live debate with ben and munchie please um well i don't
know if ben and munchie have time for that but i but i know that me and phantom would be fucking
delighted if we could do that hmm um he replies everything's gonna happen for a long while oh my
god what i okay i'm reading through this comment by zodia 195 and this is okay i just i'm gasping at
the fact that apparently lightning bliss was the editor on the fucking on the fucking analysis
analysis anarchy tf2 no fuck that's how that's how she fucking got into this thing oh my god
never mind never mind all the things i said are not bad enough i can't i i i take back everything
that i took back i untake it back uh lightning bliss is the devil and deserves to die if you see
lightning bliss kill her that's me that's my official stance all right miss anthra miss anthra
probably he said that one don't don't let me in on that i oh my god i i hate i hate the tf2 analysis
anarchy thing i hate everyone involved in it and if anyone who has any involvement with that at all
uh has has has revoked all right to life in my eyes but ben yeah but ben look in the mirror
episode one i know i know as the team which is two soldiers it was a mistake oh my god i didn't
read the script i didn't fucking read the rest of the script i only read my like three lines and
then let it go and then months later it comes out and i'm horrified to see it's worse than i even
fucking it was a mistake quote from quote from zodian uh 195 uh i don't hate ben either i do pity
him though oh uh is that the whole comment thanks no no no no this is the same guy that like it
shed some light on like what lightning bliss uh you know is doing zodia 195 yeah i don't hate ben
saying i do pity him though uh i'm i'm looking i'm looking for that oh yeah uh no biter's not in the
pcp what the fuck i didn't know nature's mage was dating biter is that a thing she's been dating biter
since like as long as i've known her oh shit yeah yeah um
hmm i feel bad that you don't know a lot about mage and i think a lot of the audience feels bad
too uh they should feel bad well mage doesn't like broadcast a lot i mean she's pretty open
about the fact that she's with biter uh she's done a bunch of animations with him and and stuff
okay um cool uh i'm okay okay spino 41
okay this this guy's saying that like yeah misanthropony you're the one that fucking
blew this out of proportion and made a federal fucking issue of it
yep okay so that's pretty good hopefully you guys work thing hope diamond one two three four
well hopefully you guys work things out and end on some level of friendly terms with this olive
branch no shut up i don't want to be friends with misanthropony that's not the fucking happy ending
here uh the happy ending is him making more videos yeah the happy ending is that this goes on forever
years of rowdy fuckers cop killers devoted specifically to this one person we're gonna have
to break it into two shows dude yeah one right focus cop killers one right focus cop killers
like colon frog fractions this is the sister series no but the worst the only bad thing about
that lineup is that we're gonna have to actually play frog fractions which i don't think i can
bear to fucking do i think that what i might do is maybe at the next um maybe for the next real
friend initiative i might like pop in there while playing frog fractions and do screen share and just
kind of like play it and make that the next rowdy fuckers what do you think about that
maybe i might try it possibly because i want because i want to finish frog fractions three
but i don't i feel like i haven't made that much progress
uh and i don't even know if it has an ending it probably does i don't know i mean ben
fucking recording something in the real friend initiative kind of is the whole thing we didn't
want to have happen oh shit you know what that's a good point i don't even think of that yeah so
fucking stay away stay stay far far away yeah i will please um map i really do love you you're
very passionate about the things you dislike but if you make a steak you you admit it and for that
i can't dislike you i find you interested this is all what no punctuation oh oh i thought you
were just saying those things and i was like no what are you talking about map i really do love
you quote from strawberry milk please uh post that please post that on my grave post it on his grave
someone's grave someone's grave is gonna have that it might be you viewer it might be you
um this person robert who i think said at one point on a common on one of our videos that he
was gonna make a video too let me pop and make sure he hasn't done that yet his channel who okay look
at this guy this is the new guy ben this is the new guy this is the new this is the new person uh
hold on hold on uh wait where am i looking in the discord yeah in the discord this is the new guy
robert who uh this guy looks vaguely familiar but he might just look exactly like every single
yeah let's see i'm gonna i'm gonna what did this guy's comments say insane uh he comments a lot on
these sort of things and i believe at one point he said he was going to make some sort of video
i think it was like can you send me the footage or something that effect i'm gonna make a response
what the footage from rowdy fuckers that's fucking publicly available yeah yeah yeah like
when we go back through our old i think that was on seven points original video which is sadly
lost to fucking time yeah christ how unfortunate i cannot believe how unfortunate oh my god what an
asshole um someone says jojo fanatic uh uh 85 this is a good thing to do christian i'm proud of you
christian oh i guess his name is christian i forget that's like a name is his name christian well i
wonder i mean i wonder if it is or he just loves god that seems like the most reasonable explanation
to me um but i know but no it's um he's christian i want to believe yeah me too um do you want to
talk about brain donuts involvement oh um yeah well i watched i mean do you want to watch the video
if it's 20 minutes i don't know if we particularly need to like like i don't know what what's there
to say you're the one who wanted to fucking bring it up uh burning i don't know i think i've i think
i've pretty much said my piece on burning don't he pretty it's him and some other guy for some
podcast i don't know what it is but they're talking about the video and uh miss uh burning doughnut
gets he gets real hung up on like some of the small inaccuracies we made like the fact that i
didn't know that suicidal tendencies was a band um the other guy is like kind of more pissed that like
i criticized uh burning doughnuts artwork and burning doughnut is kind of humorously like
doesn't really care that i that we that i criticized that like he's like yeah whatever you know is you
know he can have whatever opinion on my art he wants which is fair and i respect that um uh
yeah so i made a bunch of factual inaccuracies and i don't know i i don't really have much to say
about the specifics of what went on and i just the fact that i want to acknowledge the fact that
video exists and i saw it and i've you know i think i've fucking made my stance on that whole thing
um um yeah um you know burning doughnut um hello yep that's that's that's what it's all about
right there um yeah here i'm gonna go to all three of our videos and i'm gonna start from
the beginning and scroll through the comments to see if there's anything that we want to point out
so go back all the way the beginning fucking in april jesus christ it's been six months jesus
fucking christ um right first copulars frog fractions bend makes munchie play frog fractions
but things don't go exactly he has plans indeed in in more ways than one if only we had if only
the if only those two rowdy fucking copulars had known yeah but how could they have only the benefit
of hindsight has allowed this someone says i don't even like munchie why did i watch this
because it's gold people that don't appreciate munchie are like you know i hate to look i hate to
like i hate to shit on a fan but like when people are like man i love the procrastinators but munchie's
so annoying i i just want to tell them to get the fuck out of here like i don't i don't get it
yeah well um yeah that happens um every episode i'm on i know i know it does and it pisses me off
every time i don't know if there's i don't know if i i think i might be the most like the thing is
a lot of people love me but a lot of people hate i think i'm the most divisive um i think i am the
most divisive pcp man they're possibly ever yeah uh i i could believe that and i don't know i'm i'm
happy to have contrast i suppose i mean it's better to be it's better to have people i mean better
to be controversial than to have no one like even have an opinion about you you know yeah like better
better to be munchie than to be sigh true i mean you know by the way i want to sigh is my burning
doughnut sigh is my burning doughnut on the first episode of on of referee sculptors uh uh eight i
believe yeah um you know frog fractions too i really dug into sigh yeah and i don't know i don't
know if i want to say sorry per se but like i don't know um it was mostly a joke yeah i don't
i don't really like you i mean i i think you may i don't know if you i don't know i don't know if
you don't watch munchie stuff anymore um i don't know um not i don't know i don't really like you
from what i have seen but i i i dug into a little part so sorry about that but also please stay away
from me still uh sounds good to me yeah um tune critics here um um on the originals on the original
video um thank you thank you for taking it lightly i suppose yeah yeah i um oh it tune critic uh if
you're if you're listening to this uh tell us what happened tell us what happened to that
brony tell us about this orgy that supposedly did or didn't happen i can't believe genuinely curious
to be honest yeah yeah tbh um fucking do you remember back in the day when like the first
brand can happen and then there was the brony con orgy uh rumor wait wait that wasn't at the first
brand i don't know when i don't know wait was was that at a brony con that we were at i don't i think
so i i think so well okay i was at one okay i i think it was 2013 and that was you were at both
of the ones that i were at and i think you were at well the one before i think i was i was at three
before i was at two i think i went in 20 2014 and 2015 jesus christ i was at five brony cons
oh my fucking god dude how just kick me out how embarrassing um yeah um um um definitely there
was there was there was a rumor i think it started out as like um um you know uh baltimore's all all
about crabs and so someone was said humors i got crabs at brony con and then and then and i believe
i i i recall there being a whole fuss about a supposed brony con orgy and like like someone
everyone got hiv and and crabs hilarious like yeah uh incredible uh i see i seem to remember
that at least one of the brony cons i went to there someone was talking about like tons of people
were like tons of people were posting like like swingers like hook up things on craigslist like
that was oh definitely yeah like i heard i heard about a bunch of that going around uh but i didn't
hear any like actual confirmed reports like from participants or anything but then again why would
i yeah yeah yeah fuck yeah um fucking lol fucking lol the clerk is asleep i'm playing i'm playing
i'm playing frack so playing that shitty game i love this shitty game dude oh i got the purple
key you need the yellow key to unlock this door no okay what is that thing in there i want it so
a lot a lot of old mishandler perney videos that are good oh yeah a lot of them are comments
rather a lot of them are real solid some some some fucking guy i responded to him but i i i
didn't notice some guy has fucking vriska and trezia's avatar but from a specific moment in x6 and
please change your avatar to not be from x6 what i appreciate you liking the baby's you
you as i had commented um yes good please only like the parts of homes like that i specifically
like and yes please if you would be so kind um um um um um let's see let's let's see someone says
wow you two are horrible people um what else is new uh nothing nothing ever uh this one guy is so
happy he says thank you so much for this episode of rowdy fuckers yeah you're welcome yeah let's
let's hear more about the um let's hear more about the positive response let's hear more about the
good the all the good that the episode did that uh most of these are good most of these are like
you know good job guys this is fucking great yeah well which it is so thanks someone made at some
someone made ascii art uh of you know someone uh showing like showing us their middle finger
and they said congratulations you are a boring asshole an asshole is spelled instead of an
e there's just another l you were boring us all yeah okay okay that's fair i'll uh i'll i'll cop
to being a boring us all um incredible most of the comments are just like this is a really
funny video but i was funny as all the people in the comments uh the comments are i really appreciated
the uh the comments we got on on both on both rowdy fuckers on all the rowdy fuckers and all
the people that went and like fucking bitched at map for being an asshole i always if i have one
complaint it was that fng art didn't get enough heat uh for his bullshit he was he was the worst
and and hopefully we we have showed some sort of light on the subject yeah hopefully now you
can make a more informed decision um incredible i'm gonna be i'm gonna be on the second video now
too okay there are a lot of ones here a lot of ones good that's what you as there should be
um guys please if you're going to press one please press one and then do comma and then
another comment because i i appreciate the ones greatly and that's what i want but also please
comment real time real time um not not not a lot of probably stuff on the second one because you
know we didn't uh this is the one where we just cried about how much we love our friends as opposed
today oh right right yeah the second one is basically fake and not even real they basically
fake we pretty much just made that up uh it didn't really happen uh it was a lie uh the friendship
initiative um it's a sham it's a sham on a farce uh we were just in it for the money uh we only we
only started the real friendship initiative for that sweet sweet patreon yeah for patreon money
yeah yeah to post it on patreon uh and uh give up give up on everything if you would be so kind
god is dead and we killed him and don't let uh fucking anthony know that i said that though
oh right that's your your name that's your name fuck lol oh god god god's in a chimmel
god jesus christ what do uh all right all right all right now now for now for the doozy the one
that we all care about run for his cop killers eight frog fractions episode two frog fractions two
part two yeah our our masterpiece our our our our gift to the world mm-hmm by the way is this going
up on tbap as well i i assume so yeah yeah okay excellent incredible
um so a lot of people being being excited that tbap is back f-fucking cag-cag-cag called
the nerds very upsetting yeah how could he mm-hmm someone says this is sex and i say not a hard
a not a high bar to pass they said this is sex no no i know he says this is better than sex i
say not a high bar okay yeah yeah yeah of course mm-hmm oh here's another wonderful jackie comment
uh what what is it um i'm gonna beat uh maps ass in a f-king cage mask oh yeah um we've got
we've got to go fun what this one specifically is really good as signed up by jesse in the
comment but he left um quote i will fight been saying or no way i mean i will fight his girlfriend
or i mean if she hurts me i'll sue i mean uh please someone to help yeah yeah yeah that was good
that was that really that really uh that really summed up the the issue there f-king f-king map
he's like um yeah he like he had such like a
he was so in he was so inconsistent like sometimes he he would be like f-king brave like sometimes
he would be real like uh i'm f-king challenging you and then and then he would turn around and be
like oh well yeah i'm i'm protected by law or something you know he's he's one of one of those
he's one of these cowards he it was you know he's not the only one that's guilty he was guilty of
this but he's very guilty of it is like you know putting acting tough on the internet and saying
oh ben saying if i see you at brony connell kick you in the dick and you know he f-king wouldn't
and it's just like f-king gotta call him out you gotta you gotta call out that kind of behavior
um it's bullshit
awful f-king awful
someone says for god's sakes learn how to use google hang get hangouts this is painful to watch um
no discord is discord is like google hangouts but better and for free
yeah exactly someone says we say that probably versus sigh who wins
um i'm gonna bet on sigh uh yeah me too
probably all the good comments were on my santa pranes video
oh accompanied by shelly d you don't don't let me in with these retards they're gay as fuck
uh what retards is he referring to specifically don't know probably
probably like me saying he's like with f and g r oh yeah that's probably what he means
but i thought he was like i thought he was too i don't even remember like i kind of i thought
because shelly and corpulent don't like each other and and f and g r doesn't like corpulent
anymore so i guess i assume that meant that shelly and f and g r are still tight but maybe they hate
each other too i don't i don't know i can't i'm f-king malomius says um uh he has a time code
where we're like we say like we like name off some people we don't name him we just name people we
just name like uh corpulent brownie and like shelly d yeah and she says uh none of us corp
shelly or me give a fuck what you do nor do we talk to f and g r the fuck uh sorry uh whatever
yeah i don't know what what what are we supposed to say to that major left to comment i don't think
she wants to involve this we won't say anything um but yeah um um um yeah just just just just like a
mix of people saying how could you and and and then another batch of people saying please more
yeah uh so but exactly what you'd expect um yeah for heroes like us let's see what f from
john zine is up to that that that that that that that that that wily type oh on his channel
yeah he's up to he's probably doing calm he's probably commentating on some other brownie
shit i wonder i wonder if he's had any wait a minute i just it got it saved and i don't know
why i wonder if anything's gone down between him and f and g r lately i hope not i feel like
or some sort of any shit with jerry peat god i fucking hate jerry peat so much who's that
he was part of the i think i don't know in my mind he's vaguely associated with f and g r i don't
know if it's true uh but he is basically brony a sargon of a cod and trans from john z's um like
channel is like really active and that's good i don't know why i wanted to say that just just so i
know yeah yeah good yeah okay he hasn't made it he hasn't made a video since mr probably has done
on tba okay um that's too bad uh don't you don't have to make another one if you want to but uh
i would like to see i would like to see if if you notice anything um anything suspicious yeah yeah
yeah uh if you see something say something please um and i think that's all i really have to say
on the subject i think we've cleaned this up nicely what what are we at now ben what are we
at now we're probably verging on six hours uh um oh no we're almost at seven we're almost at seven
hours okay well um how what are we exactly what are we exactly like uh we're at exactly i don't
know why you want to know but we're at exactly six fifty three um let's let's let's let's get that seven
hour mark let's let's let's get that seven hour okay this is gonna be accomplishment all right
let's hang am i screen sharing are you seeing this fucking sick uh frog action no no no no
how do you feel about that surely surely you're missing you must feel like you're missing out
ben i cannot think of a single worst punishment that you could give me then force me to watch a
video game be played i mean i guess i get that i get that i get that a metaphysical yeah
uh fucking jesus christ i'm so i'm this like we we we gotta finish this game and and we will but
we'll probably be in the procrastinators and i don't think i i don't know i i i think as much as
i would like to continue to continue this further i think it's stated i think i think it's done
its job i think i think we've accomplished what we set out to do i let it all right and maybe let
us know in the comments should we finish frog fractions too because i mean i'm gonna finish
frog fractions too one way or another the only question is whether i'm doing it on uh on uh
rowdy fuckers or or elsewhere yeah um please please if you're going to press one which i know you
will because you please you're obedient and you're good and thank you um please uh please write
please respond to all of these all these concerns all of these uh uh all of these thoughts all
of these ideas we want your input um pretty please yeah we want to we want to we live to please you
the viewer mm-hmm we're your humble servant we need we need those those patreon fun bucks
mm yeah yeah dog yeah bro how else is going been going to afford an oculus with rith with his
fucking income i tell you i tell you what um i ain't it ain't gonna happen i think i need the bridge
i think i need the bridge to progress um yeah uh i i just i really hope i really hope uh that uh
you know when all is said and done that none of these people ever talk to us ever again oh oh please
oh please let it be so um i'm sure fng guys could be really fucking pissed that we totally
took him for a ride yeah well he's he can he can i don't care there's literally no one i care less
about in the world than fngr yeah um um please don't mistake us trying to be nice to him as
us being friendly to him we just wanted to secure our belittlement yeah uh true um and um as i said
i think he's a weird ski guy i don't know i don't know anything about him personally uh i just don't
like him so and that's good and that's and that's definitely good enough for me that's 100% good
enough for me yeah i mean what is my knee jerk reaction that is that i don't like what more is
there to say that's that's that's yeah that's good enough for me and it should be good enough for you
to audience look yes if fngr if you're still if you're still watching this um please please
change yes yes please look at yourself and do better please i'm begging you i'm getting my
hands and knees fngr please don't please don't be the same please uh um if only if only if only if
if only if only he fucking could if only if only he had the the mental capability to do such yeah
but as we all know but as we all know that's a farfetched it's a it's a farce that's that's a farce
right there i'm so fucking dedicated to beating frog fractions too you have no idea i've nothing's
ever been more important to me in my entire life how how close are you i have no fucking idea
jeez look it up and like depending on how much you have left we'll like record something um
well let me open up my man i brought the bridge all the way here and i think it was for nothing
because i i don't i haven't found anything to do with it but i think this whole endeavor can be
described as for nothing oh 100 uh yeah i'm so sure that our own sick enjoyment our own sick
deranged fucking sadistic i'm so sure that the bridge is is what i need uh hold on hold on
ben you need to burn that bridge but much how like how we burn the bridge with our good friends
with our good friends who who if only this did not happen we would have been pals with
misanthropony uh let's see find the helipad from the starting point what the fuck is the helipad
jesus christ i'm the barber pole position purple cathedral what is okay i need max gems with
orange key i don't have that uh gauntlet i need a symbol that i don't have uh
sewer entrance go to lower right chamber use the bridge
wait how do i fucking bring the bridge into the sewer that's weird okay so maybe i don't need the
fucking maybe i don't need the god god damn the god damn bridge anyway loma manager i played that
inferno investigator i gotta do snake hell uh where's snake hell i'm there's a whole bunch of
shit i haven't found but i gotta play the biker chip i still that fucking lasers in the way of
biker chicks and requires the megasword yeah i have the megasword i have the megasword and
it's still gonna play oh my god what ben let me ask you something munchie please uh save me
what is funnier misanthropony insisting that we're doing this for patreon money even when we have
never marked it on patreon or green the six the sweet eight dollars on the t-bet patreon by posting
reverse cop killers nine what's funny is it is it eight dollars it's eight dollars
um what's funnier oh man
i see the funny thing is we probably never even get that eight dollars because it wouldn't
like it wouldn't even be worth like opening whatever fucking bank account it's attached to
just to get eight dollars out of it yeah uh dude dude we split that hit 55 we both are able
to get like a drink of mcdonald's only i think actually i think posting it on t-bet would be
pretty fucking funny all right fuck yeah i'm kind of leaning i'm kind of leaning honestly
some some poor fucking soul who just forgot just just forgot just just forgot to unpledge
after all these years some poor stuff who's probably pledged the pcp right fucking now
he they better they better pledge right fucking now or else they're gonna miss
this once in a lifetime opportunity to pay us for something we weren't planning on charging for
thank fucking god and also also nate gets nothing so oh yeah of course you don't even
don't even think for a second yeah i mean god forbid i can't think of a less deserving person
of anything of anything best guy ever
excellent and and and and hopefully and hopefully um um and hopefully phantom horrors
not lost the ages more shrubber shrubber milk um keg standard can be lost because he's dead
and dead people don't matter yeah that that that's the me behind girl in the gun that's the whole
that's the whole message is dead people don't matter and uh if they're dead then forget about
yeah yes uh and uh we all learned a lot we all learned a lot that day
just want to beat frog fractions i just want to beat frog fractions uh i want to i want to
turn on my fan i want to go home i i am in my bedroom right now but i don't feel like that's
home enough i want to walk outside and leave my entire area and and this in this entire planet
and and and and and leave to find somewhere right more over a fit and best
i want to go to hell because i know i'll have kindred spirits there true
uh i see a message here leg worthless disgusting oh my god this game is so full of mystery this
game is a full of mystery and wonder so full of intrigue it is it truly is this game is so my
is so right up my alley it's such it's my jam it's exactly what my jam is uh when my when jam was
invented uh it looked like this a lot it really looked a lot like what's going on all right are
we at seven minutes yet do you want to call this spin what i'm gonna make you a proposition they
don't think you're gonna be able to refuse okay what if i were to say to you yeah close that game
and leave me alone you make a tempting offer munchie um i may be i may be forced to consider
okay all right i'll take i'll take you up on that yeah i will i will i will see you i will see you
in court thank thank thank you for witnessing the the the thrilling conflu the thrilling
confusion confusion confusion yeah um as star wars has said before democracy ends not with a bang but
with a with a whimper quote from anakin skywalk and i feel like that isn't more poignant than ever
that's my favorite in our post trump world yeah yeah yeah yeah um god and in our in our post fngr
world now that fngr is president um we're all just fun yeah um yeah the middle east is doing way too
well there's not enough war there's not enough strife we gotta fucking we have to go back max
revive donald trump yeah i mean you know who's more fit who's more fit yeah who's more fit um thank
you everyone um and please if you take one thing away from this entire video please don't be a freak
and leave me alone yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna take a lesson i'm gonna i'm gonna be i'm gonna
be better about that from now on i promise if there's one thing i can say to anyone whole
hardly is don't be a freak and please please leave me alone all right um yes that's it for
rowdy sianara incredible incredible now open your computers and crash trying to render that
i think it'll be fun uh okay stop recording